<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[someone shoot me so i never have to go to work again please i’m fucking begging]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL SERÁ EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Y… https://t.co/mVayeOCdRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Detectivecomics999 What a end to the latest arc! https://t.co/LHy9aTzP4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I act like I just got my leg chopped off when my sinuses are stuffed up. I’m out for a minimum 24 hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m fr watching BBC earth documentaries on Netflix, they’re actually hella interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannah_bobbi Did your dad scream, too? Or just at the other girls screaming? 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got to Boom Island... Did I miss @amyklobuchar’s announcement?!  ##MinmeapolisMoments https://t.co/6orlpA7MGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance @NatashaBertrand Why hard to assert privilege? Because they already had prior requests?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the person that types a tweet at two in the morning then deletes in because I’m scared no one will like it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't get over the terrible logic of letting one team whack a goalie but then calling the other for just trying t… https://t.co/Pg6YyzNbCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment you find out @TheoFleury14 isn't coming.  That's 2 times I've missed out on meeting you.  Disappointed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 yrs of high school, never taken off for being sick 4 yrs of college never a day off for sickness  But I will be m… https://t.co/dI0BRCfpzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Sumir! Proud of what @instawork has built, helping people find gigs is powerful!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never said they weren't related. I deliberately avoided injecting commentary, precisely because I'm more interest… https://t.co/yiUPGaY5s8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFilmFlamers You guys are speaking my language of gateway horror with Goosebumps, Are You Afraid of the Dark, Un… https://t.co/laBMwbK7wC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Correcting the little things.. singles w/ 405 lbs this morning, it'll all be right May 18th!💪 @KLAPowerlifting… https://t.co/JMd5mlHHDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey @BostonGlobe, your app is actually really decent, but why on earth do you keep pushing me football stuff as ‘br… https://t.co/IFtaGLmuAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drank two shots of tequila and a tall blue moon at the bar and passed out by 9pm last night 👴🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jagoff @Dejan_Kovacevic @DKPghSports @dlolley_pgh @JPerrotto @CarterCritiques @HunterAHomistek @robullman… https://t.co/MHnRiFkxqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Royceda59 Important, no.  Appreciated, yes.  They aren't a necessity but I damn sure look forward to collabs.   We… https://t.co/QzACNBExcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[How you bust through a shoe.. muscle head ass boy stepped down too hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisLoesch @TRPhrophet You are correct but it won't happen the just knows hate.#JessieSmollettHoax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most information received is from what we hear and what we see. You know you can reprogram it right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arkansas/A&amp;M rivalry RENEWED..  Going to become one of the more heated games in the SEC over the next few years!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicholsUprising @harveyjkaye Putin thrives on such as these  Treason caucus Moscow, July 4th, 2018 @SenJohnKennedy… https://t.co/AtoiIA7otA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chocolatemyers3 nascar wants to save teams $ why not make it pit guys must work in your shop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morninggloria I wonder how many people buy prints of this propaganda garbage?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Billy Jeans Denim Workshop https://t.co/NNUKT20gT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrFan Trump you bragging again about https://t.co/P0yqxBmyUv go to a group of Christian extremists sprea… https://t.co/b4mmG1nDlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[i know i got this talk w/ different spins on it @ various stages of my life. white people, u ain’t need this talk a… https://t.co/Qt40KAUnje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillWineBanks The House Righties had every right to pummel Cohen about his credibility but after a while it was pu… https://t.co/qQIbNIhDJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thesillybuddha Not quite sure I believe that one. https://t.co/26OCOW3YuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleMorrill @semil 1. Nothing/less to shill. podcast interviews feel like advertisements for books. Yuck. Have… https://t.co/tTav1Ygi6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToyotaRacing  @FordPerformance  @ChevyLife  @CGRTeams  @LFR95  @StewartHaasRcng  @roushfenway  Please take notice… https://t.co/fly7vV5YWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosyna For me, Cherry Coke Zero is the canonical Coke Zero. I am interested to try the orange vanilla for science.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeCarney00 @glennkirschner2 @randypcox Where’s this confidence coming from?]]></document><document><![CDATA[For whatsoever things were written aforetime were written for our learning, that we through patience…… https://t.co/RqEtbmkqnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, I was lucky enough to see this on Wednesday, thanks to @justinbaldoni and I wish I could see it again, right… https://t.co/iZx5vy0r88]]></document><document><![CDATA[VERY good information in here. You’ll never have the perfect words for someone grieving, but you can absolutely hav… https://t.co/QyrMVJW3mm]]></document><document><![CDATA[To qualify, I don’t trust him completely, but for most of his testimony and certainly the way he conducted himself, props are due.]]></document><document><![CDATA[traveling around the world for pop up shops, 1 day meetings overseas, sleepless nights, having employees, paying sa… https://t.co/NNcc8gRUh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beaumorris0n @KINGDOMHEARTS Dude that’s insane! Seems like I beat the game just yesterday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[sex is cool and all but have you ever had the same taste in music. it like a soul connection 💯❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edwards says second-string RB battle, DL line depth, incoming secondary talent the things he’s keeping an eye on as spring continues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DayanaPerales @davidfloores @AlonsoDT Jajaja neta, de mi te acuerdas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oh_dam_itsadam He has that art exhibit comin' up and I feel like I haven't seen enough of his work to properly app… https://t.co/D5NOTXP7pa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen-“ ya the family had a lot of buffers.” Chairmen Jordan - “ you’re a liar and convict you’re under oat… https://t.co/B1TVJpHgYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I truly hate the loser point in hockey. It’s become more about “who gets the extra point” rather than who wins the… https://t.co/6Yvqhb79mp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino The entire Obama administration needs to be brought before Congressional hearings and finally get to the… https://t.co/GzyNsgO9IB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WINTERJAM What was the toughest part of making music and starting a band?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re back this Saturday! boots_and_spurs_os #oceansprings @ Boots &amp; Spurs https://t.co/3c9GtzsXmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VancityReynolds @ChrisCandy4u @TheRealJenCandy Beautiful tribute to John Candy.  One of it not the greatest comedi… https://t.co/uQhlw7NsTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brielarson I ❤️ u. I had a dream about u a few nights back. Usually the longer ur awake the more u forget the drea… https://t.co/36FncBjR6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaaaahh se mamaron allá en la esquina tienen la de triste y solitario de Toppaz, dejen marcar al depósito pa mandarles un cartón]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t think of a better way to celebrate my birthday than opening our inaugural @OMERSVentures Menlo Park office wi… https://t.co/bTYAQVJ0kA]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s funny cause I was so ready to@ drink then I’m like wait... I have 🍪🍃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another clip from last night, Mich 404 getting in the zone while painting in VR. https://t.co/HIjoWIGvIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReetahBook I try to be sensitive to all people suffering from homelessness, but I'm not gonna lie, I will spend a… https://t.co/FkIt75C6Jx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elite Packers twitter y’all need to follow: @KingDay__  @PrimeDavante  @IKE_Packers  @HailRodgers12  @TeamOhtani… https://t.co/cfVHk7iYv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FirstRespondersLivesMatterToo! #PTSDSucks #FirstRespondersNeedServiceDogs! #AnxietySucks! I have a lot to say!!✊🚒💕… https://t.co/qf822Udcrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Treason, aiding the enemy, accomplice to the killing of Americans. Blocking you for bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissMadeline11 @MangoMonkeyBoy The lovely creative team who brought us this masterpiece! https://t.co/TVYUKyQn2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anytime i see @Kyle_Poucher on the caller ID I know she’s about to yell]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man Reggie Noble 🐐 I gotta tune in. @noreaga @djEFN @Drinkchamps @therealredman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieOliverTX Beyond planning unconstitutional expenditures, what's the authority for seizing private property? Or… https://t.co/grGDuGVBEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[That would be the honourable thing to do and maybe the inevitable outcome, but kind of agree with Tim Crosbie… https://t.co/TP3qjxAmax]]></document><document><![CDATA[In ALL honesty Black people don’t owe White people ANYTHING... not a smile, not a hey, not a hug... NOTHING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DDOTDC @311DCgov 19-00083960. Anything you can do would be great. Also, the kicked up asphalt is occupying the bik… https://t.co/0E443VcJ6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaggerous @WatchFlake @markthius It wasn't planned! And we actually discussed if we should have played a fourth match, to be fair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know that Great Crescent Brewery is a majority Woman Owned business? Let's recognize Lani as we celebrate I… https://t.co/kxZsFhQbhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chin up king, you got more work to do 🏁  #fashionblogger #fashion #styleblogger #style #urbane #bycharlesjay @ Phil… https://t.co/uSH8oYje0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocCivilMx @tatclouthier @m_ebrard @Claudiashein @RicardoMonrealA En lugar de salir de viaje, ahorraría para mejorar de barrio.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moving left of Sanders. Will young activist left get over cultural barriers and follow her?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now I’m in my 30s and moderately successful in my own middle class way, but because of you, it’s now possible fo… https://t.co/yhWOIRBRTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeLoe3 @politico "Insists" was my word. How about "calls upon" like in this WSJ piece. Perhaps "urges" is the bet… https://t.co/Y765DcQhBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tumbaburross Dice el mesias tropical que el tiene otros datos. Que hay ahorros en el combate al robo de combustibl… https://t.co/xFtUlTQ6iI]]></document><document><![CDATA[this fucker ken actually venmo’d me 20$ for guessing the name of thor’s hammer correctly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get some shut eye but this demon kid of mine keeps talking in her sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you think about me def a classic in my eyes but people never mention it when they mention 50]]></document><document><![CDATA[... they continuously lie, defile and abuse children, women and men to maintain dominance and continue laughing at… https://t.co/gBpAWE8efV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@f3lkn 7 hard-chargers sallied out fora special early-bird edition of the MoP. #F3Counts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmazingDancers1 @NBCWorldofDance @nbc Same here. We want new episodes not reruns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxBlumenthal Excellent Venezuelan government propaganda piece! @BootsRiley keep retweeting, that’s really helping… https://t.co/oZQ4CrZX57]]></document><document><![CDATA[As seen today on #Brokers’ #Tour! 👏🏼 @ Berkeley, California https://t.co/q5c7iingjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCWarwick3 @lamabla @joshamat @john_melfyn @MarkDice @realDonaldTrump Do you even realize how ignorant you sound?]]></document><document><![CDATA[No surprise here: @BobBuckhorn this morning endorsing @JaneforTampa as his successor as mayor of Tampa.… https://t.co/vgIyUUYPee]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not saying I’m better than anybody but there’s deadass no one above me 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[No quería que te fueras, no te quería soltar, quería que el Uber se tardara dos horas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussBeenToolin Interesting,  haven't had any time to break down the All-22 film yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @Stargazer2020 That's scary!! And reside in NJ!! Now I'm not only in fear of my local government!! No… https://t.co/gjw60MnFBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TracksideMikeN @PapaBeez @santaanitapark @SwiftHitter @TVG Dude it’s just the way it is. They aren’t a news organi… https://t.co/oXKdzPdVs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @JacquelineHine1 Hate is a strong word. But in this case, its more than appropriate. Not only trump, but… https://t.co/Qw9k8QfBaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will we get to see @SexyChuckieT and @trentylocks #BestFriends vs @BestiesITW #FreeDaveyVega and @TheDirtyRook… https://t.co/cAj17zqhcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my brothers.   St. Matthew Lodge 670 (PHA) at Bokampers last night. https://t.co/JAaDxol2DY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DD1070 @Daniel_Bragg The sport is just so generic now. Even the tracks are. And the rules now are just silly and contrived]]></document><document><![CDATA[#newhaircut #haircut #hairstyle #selfie #newhair #like #hair #love #me #barbershop #instagood #shorthair #fashion… https://t.co/F0pU3kSSse]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember my freshmen year in college and someone broke the glass to the vending machine and all the snacks was go… https://t.co/uJ1H9KuJEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the few benefits of the Trump presidency so far is the reinvigoration of checks and balances that haven't be… https://t.co/x6fvtQRx8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielHabif GRACIIIIIIIAAASSS! JAMÁS DEJAREMOS DE SOÑAR!!! VENEZUELA LIBRE 🇻🇪 #VenezuelaAidLife #AidVenezurla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Traitor.   Why is #individual1 at large? He’s the greatest security risk faced by our country.]]></document></documents></author>