<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I swear it’s hella awkward when I get hit on at work and guys ask me what I’m doing later, like foo I’m working and… https://t.co/Kdqyr3FJyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 months ago today I walked away from my job of 4years ... I’ve gotten nothing but love every since ! My guest stil… https://t.co/mzRoeMtxbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump @MjrCitiesChiefs @MCSheriffs Stfu hater]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our brains are full and our hearts are happy!Thank you everyone for making this a great day! #RRLCMiniCon https://t.co/QYjzcJDA0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyndaquillll girl happy fucken birthday. You deserve eternal happiness!!! Hope ur day is wonderful 😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally got around to making a new Easter wreath. #easter #wreath #easterwreath #crafting @ Chez Nole https://t.co/gws3AE1FHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pittsburghstylists lorealpro #asymmetricalpixie #lifeisartislife @behindthechair_ @hairmagazine  Instagram… https://t.co/9PmC8GgCjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taelon Martin snaps Central's run taking advantage of a serious mismatch and laying it in. 34-30 Central]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 65th Birthday, my sister, my friend, my Ace coon boon. 😋♨️♨️ #march1 #Bonnie Jessee @ Georgia https://t.co/9nGfVgOpgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncusack @CornelWest @RevDrBarber Nope. Voted for Bernie in 16. Will not be voting for him now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexWitt After today's horrid interview where you just gave a platform for Michael Caputo to just tell lie after l… https://t.co/wG4v1Ft77E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rrtfb When can we get you and the family back in Rochester, NY? We could use some of your sweet music to warm things up here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A partir del Jueves empiezo #ThrowbackThursday #TBT #RetroJueves. nuevo segmento en mi canal, 👉🏼… https://t.co/5HVIz6sM4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha...you know what time it is. It’s business Time. #onemarriageconference #onemarriageconference2019 @freechapel… https://t.co/qvFgCS3j47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow When my sister had her first date with THAT HOT GUY, my dad took out his false teeth, put on a plaid… https://t.co/5NQTwIfTkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews Maybe he’s the 600lb person sitting  on a bed hacking the US.  He IS wearing a MAGAt hat.  😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisabledResist Once in awhile I catch myself liking a Trump comment.  That's because I'm so quick to comment that… https://t.co/hTIggBdEQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day in DC with the one and only Congressmen Curtis. A wonderful leader, kind friend and mentor. Thank you for… https://t.co/24wm1mMGVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready for a new tattoo, a bedroom makeover, and a whole new wardrobe...who’s with me??]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEVER DO THE SAME MISTAKE TWICE. Art Print #funniness #laugh #smirk #ludicrous https://t.co/IAkdOBMr2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mluciaramirez @patriciajaniot De acuerdo ☝️ con usted en casi todo, es un sangriento, dañino ,asesino y cobarde y… https://t.co/Nz4pGH2Ag3]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more happy client ! SOLD! New Home! Invista em Orlando! Invista na Flórida! Invista em imóveis! Fale comigo ! A… https://t.co/F9BdiYDoyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @Laurie89764267 @AOC Even though most liberals are against having a wall/fence to secure our souther… https://t.co/pfiraJ9Bta]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want for Valentine’s Day is Beef n Barrel @Asa_Johnson9 #please? ❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Binge watching the real housewives of New Jersey and I have to say @JacLaurita has to have the patience of a saint… https://t.co/IJdFIaVIRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gypsy_3k @Ohmwrecker @_CaRtOoNz @FarCrygame Yaas!! Lmao! XD https://t.co/tgtJ3K1AUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EtihadAirways Selling an international ticket online under 2 hours prior to flight time?And not giving a refund wh… https://t.co/kGeNRrPsqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Garbology101 @JayDarc13 @NYCSanitation I don’t want to think that. I’m annoyed that with a small accumulation comp… https://t.co/7Uei7BApXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make your passion your paycheck. 🤑🤑🤑🤑  📸: Chris Milian  #MayaMcNultyInspires #fundraisingsecrets #fundpreneur @ Up… https://t.co/fjM8A7i3kH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly this is laughable because if you can’t find a recruit’s social media you’re probably not looking hard enou… https://t.co/CKQp9ul35O]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's all about technology &amp; those @ViewSonicEDU_US @VirtucomInc and @DeKalbSchoolsIT! https://t.co/oz8wbI2uFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MizterMordant He is asking for your name? I told him you go by Darpo@MitzerMordant?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having fun isn’t hard when you’ve got a library card! Spending Presidents’ Day weekend on the West Coast with my fa… https://t.co/sxaeTRrk7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrjaxtaylor @BNCartwright You both look so happy. Happy Valentines Day]]></document><document><![CDATA[My only question is are we gonna get the EDC lineup tomorrow on Valentine’s Day like last year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuhBernardezx mano eu tenho q para de falar com vc sua cornisse é contagiosa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the lovely arosafitness class looks amazing. Sorry I could not join. I hope you enjoy your birthd… https://t.co/2GMj1du0j3]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is next on our we gotta go to this concert please list 🙏 @hannahhthib Luke Combs - One Number Away https://t.co/hnCPx5WpPv via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Facial Beauty Acupuncture! #SkinProblem? See #pictures at #PhotoGallery at our site: https://t.co/ee8e714Kjp! (585… https://t.co/MuS0VwqG7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to our Oak Creek Varsity Bowlers who are competing at the State Tourney in Green Bay this weekend!… https://t.co/QnXuvuGDCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErlindaNovenar2 Madam, saan ang video? Maine is not married to anyone. ND told us also that A never gave M anything, not even a ring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFL_LOGISTIC @ElFaaacho Esta de hater, es obvio que sabe pero finge demencia para provocarme. 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I felt when I saw my most recent schedule, I work all next week but I won’t be here. Oops 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almond snow! #californiaalmonds #happysabbath @ Hanford, California https://t.co/ACb0eg04wv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SUZAN916 You always post the best desserts. I want to be your food  tester.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pensé que los fuckboys ya no me pelaban, pero me acaban de enviar este mensaje 😂 https://t.co/uqpdPiJNRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[25 mins and counting for a Dufferin bus that's not too full. Thanks @TTChelps]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sweet of @ChrisEvans to help @ReginaKing up the steps! #superheroinreallife #Oscar2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ll never understand why boys choose to not care until you’re over them? like if you would’ve cared to begin w we… https://t.co/WuXErYMIEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsympU according to the article it gained 6 lbs a day while growing. That's means it's probably cute for about 2-3… https://t.co/CvjB8WzKRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @CASenateDems, @SenateRepCaucus, @CAproTem, @casendems, @AssemblyGOP, @AssemblyFellows#CaAssemblyFellows… https://t.co/xdZ4KcS2i9]]></document><document><![CDATA[When i first came to harvest I was broken, new in recovery, and still felt lost. The sermon that day was about the… https://t.co/RpJrDjBLZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MohamedMOSalih @Venuseswilliams Fighter on the court. Designer and proponent of equal pay off-court. Major spunk,… https://t.co/l03YW2uJ5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that I haven’t been at DeKalb for a year and rarely see/ talk to people from the school and I still hear p… https://t.co/FCEeIQP0qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT’S FINALLY HERE!!! Official video and single! PATRICE JÉGOU and TAKE 6. “WRAP YOUR TROUBLES IN DREAMS”💜Watch on Y… https://t.co/6eXc5gEYiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in History  February 26th DIED #ONTHISDAY  2012 - Trayvon Benjamin Martin  (February 5, 1995 – February 26, 2… https://t.co/weFDzdjcV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn @benshapiro @AOC #Mussolini How can Hillary be speaking to him when he is dead! You attend seances? Liv… https://t.co/qjbMZeB5Tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students @WilsonsCreekInt are using six-word summaries to explain key points from their reading on #prideteam5 toda… https://t.co/xwBg0Xnoi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcraFinan Looks like some good snow, Fair Play is a great place to drive up to, very peaceful!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Says his chances of playing singles at Wimbledon this year are “less than 50%” per @BBCSport #Wimbledon #AndyMurray]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do think about this?? @NikkiSixx I have heard from some family members..saying that it's difficult for loved o… https://t.co/0laOYER3kt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are they letting them continue on(I know why)?Someone should’ve BEEN grabbed her little ass up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LgbtResistance I follow you because you are smart and caring.  I admire those traits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonaldKlain I'm sure he's done a few other sh*tty things with that hand, as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MSNBC (@ZerlinaMaxwell) yet again broadcasts blatant lies, this time about Bernie Sanders's opening speech, and r… https://t.co/S2a3GwgtlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1: @mle_val invited me to share 7 of my favorite books with no review or explanation. I’m challenging… https://t.co/EPQ0BpUjYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I refuse to let anyone help me with my self tapes because I am UNPROFESSIONAL, but they ARE getting better 😊😂… https://t.co/HK45MV0E5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[so it wasnt the coffee of carbs that game me this headache, its this flu omg.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Erie Blu by Cornerstone Brewing Company at @cornerstmadison — https://t.co/BW34LMLKWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mfaulkner43 @Adam_Karpiak @InterviewLady @KatrinaKibben ewwww. We had beef tongue, thanks to a side of beef in the… https://t.co/1Om73nLkmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all the people that made this such a craptastic day: https://t.co/TqfH6LQfbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ingrid O'Connor crossed Lake Hayward. Time 01:39:49, pace 03:41 min/km, est. finish 12:46 pm https://t.co/LuaTcdICXd #Birkie2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcLAllen Also this https://t.co/KgsllufNS2  And this https://t.co/Tqq6s6ro7O  And this https://t.co/IgNNGsnF9R  I am not alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesusSunbae @BTS_twt @ShawnMendes BITCJHSHSJAHSJSSH I BOUT BROKE MY NECK HAVING TO LOOK AT TBIS TWICE I WAS LIKE W… https://t.co/uCfLsdJs7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spitting truth as he always does.  @common is LIVE now! #unitedwayaap #leadwithaap2019 #mentalhealth #leadership… https://t.co/mlWA19ahUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[life is way too short for bad vibes @ Cawood, Kentucky https://t.co/bkCZ5NApx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Vanya can’t see that this guy is up to no good. They both dumb #TheUmbrellaAcademy]]></document><document><![CDATA[starting this week off right with a dance class at @ODCsf thanks to @ClassPass 💙🌀🙏🔛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another EPIC day! #parkcity #vacation #wishiwasaskibum @ Park City, Utah https://t.co/1BrHPrLivf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Presale on my upcoming album on my go fund me: Each $25 donated gets you a Vinyl copy here: https://t.co/TfKeGYXc2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s work.  Happy Thursday 🏋🏻‍♀️🙌🏻💪🏻 @ Golds Gym https://t.co/3ZHSc2P7Ec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanDreyerNBC I can solve your pancake issue ..Calvin wd love this! Pm me an address I’ll send u one on me! Sent… https://t.co/FjO9zFa7dw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krshelnutt They talked about it all day 😀😀 They even used their choice time to continue their drawings! That’s a h… https://t.co/TxeUitdqXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: hmm wonder what this is about   *scrolls my tl*  Me: ah there it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[We just whispered across the room telling eachother that we love eachother. And with that. Good night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our song “Mr. Blue” premiered this morning.  Thanks to @SoundofnowMusic for the great review!  You can listen here-… https://t.co/kFw39i9M4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[DYK the Ontario Travel Information Centres hire summer students to help promote Ontario’s tourism industry? Recruit… https://t.co/s2kzacCuCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanFillion I think you're HOT! My son loves all things CANADIAN including you. Castle was awesome, I'm still ma… https://t.co/89IzDSCbHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KVanValkenburg @the_woke_yolk What’s the over under on how soon CD mixes up Jumeirah and Jamiroquai]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t sleep because I keep coughing and the coughing hurts since I did a killer core workout the other day, and I… https://t.co/7AmfAUfgmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to pour my cats food in his dish and poured it in the garbage. My mind is not working today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristenwhit @yoursweetguys We’re traveling every 2 seconds anyway we might as well lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rawknrob @realDonaldTrump All this time , Thanks, I was wondering how they had Killary A sure win in 2016!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is 2:30 in the fucking morning. Why are my neighbors playing fucking mariachi music so loud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg!!! I meant to say lip not lil... and thank you girl I wish I had the talent for make up as you do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Quatessa8 @veelighted7 @50cent React responsively, you can’t take  care of your people behind bars, remember that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandomMess_0 @jpodhoretz @NRO @rkylesmith It's 1 perspective. It's not the end of the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the hair gets in the way; a solution minded woman!😳  I just found this video on Dailymotion https://t.co/AeQPFXQuQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phillip70856934 @joy31608 @RenagadeGirl @TheOralBuffet @RudyGiuliani @kerrywashington @ScandalABC Oh, yeah, becaus… https://t.co/cQlRD7kzp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Customers get mad if you don’t give them a senior price, and they also get mad if you just guess it and give them t… https://t.co/ahLLj395Je]]></document></documents></author>