<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ealepping It is virtually impossible for lawyers to name names of judges they will continue to appear in front of… https://t.co/WQaXnOEHpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna get in the pit but these little girls are playing around and I don’t want to ruin their time cause I will really hurt someone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceAgidSF @LetsGoWarriors @1jordanbell Call it a hunch : Bruce Agid = Warrior Fan?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t stop thinking about how me and Allen met almost year ago but how Thomas Velik came up to us with a vacuum and… https://t.co/ppGg9BuR6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccblueyes70 @IndiaEaton not sure but the whole they boo'ed me make it seem like she thinks everyone has to like her. get over yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're wedding planning, make sure to set a realistic budget of how much you want to spend than stick to it. Bre… https://t.co/ToqIXRUVtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Norm_Farrell That's what Bloomberg thought then, now we and they know it's spec and foreign nationals and crime and more...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the day I graduate so I can move to a place where it never snows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meredithdclark So many things to say: but for qual. Go for what makes a qualitative study of quality (validity, re… https://t.co/Yxv4MlKIek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great #sagaftra podcast with @NinaTotenberg and @ericspillman — relevant to this moment in history. Thanks Presiden… https://t.co/PrHfXcJOYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go placidly amidst the noise and haste. #mondaymotivation #desiderata #loveyourself #begentlewithyourself… https://t.co/Yoo1ulpMiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can never get him to hold still! @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/wdopQTpcGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's when she locked the door and called police.  When officers got there, they handcuffed the boy and took him i… https://t.co/ziEyZn1rn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parvisani @HISTORY Women choose what to do with our lives. If we choose not to go into certain professions or indu… https://t.co/iXqsLXi3DG]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW this morning: Hartford police say the responded to a stabbing on Franklin Avenue https://t.co/0UTH8qPlJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[quiero darle un abrazo a sabrina y agradecerle por haber compartido esa canción tan personal con nosotros no dejo de llorar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BunniHopper1 I loved watching him. Still watch it till this day. R.I.P Steve Irwin u may be gone but u will never be forgotten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND to further bolster my point, a quote from W.E.B. Du Bois. You simply train players in the medical establishment… https://t.co/uBCy6z4qMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my students argued that in  #faulkner’s #aroseforemily (spoiler alert) Emily kills her almost-lover because he was #gay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[laughter is free ⛅️  . . . . photo creds to bae 💖 house creds to toya.chunks @ East Los Angeles, California https://t.co/athOxkg0Gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doors are about to open that no man  or thing can shut! Trust Him. Believe in Him. #Repost trustgodbro ・・・ Amen if… https://t.co/g0p2AqpvhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a $50 gift card from work and guess what I’m using to drink @ the rodeo Wednesday 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusanBranagan11 @PlayingPolitix @h8Wankmaggot45 @hardhouz13 @HoarseWisperer @HollyResist @ida_skibenes… https://t.co/dYNjJrndoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmcgee32 @Brandi_Mathis84 @LaDonna42356652 @LateasaH @adam011977 @OttoJohnson3 @HomeDepot5085 I learned so much fr… https://t.co/zxw2Cut81o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Day in Sonoma with Mama.  #date #mama #beyond #blessed #precious #memories #family #love #beautiful #day… https://t.co/YE0RuibF4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great week in the Windy City ... Until we meet again Chicago ✌🏼 https://t.co/UJJA0NJnX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aug1405 @1stLineDefense @lolly7777 @buttersflykiss @Notyomamma2 @Jimmybo62868157 @RedWingGrips @sappermartin… https://t.co/zxuUk06lKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women's History Month day six reminder: like, seriously, womanhood is not defined by biology. If women who have had… https://t.co/jY4kdCPHFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz It's sad celebrities have to live behind walls. No one should. But , things happen. Bad things. And we m… https://t.co/chjnW5RiSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[They lost my support for good now. Now more will I buy their cds or sing their songs. They are not Christians]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedayofsteve @Khallion I adore her art. Even cosplayed as her Rebel Girl one con]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonidockter @BruceBochy @SFGiants @scottostler @geoff9cow @DrDinD @DouglasCP @sfpelosi @GareBearEsq @CranorE… https://t.co/xk9FaMMmy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When you do your strikes, imaging what you are hitting in front of you. This is your chance to get away from a sit… https://t.co/g2bUA7MKj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and George were fighting all day because she scratched my face at 4am and made me bleed and I got home from work… https://t.co/aM4hq5DXtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #StrikesMakeChange on @TheTylt. Teachers are trying to preserve the soul of public education–the time for c… https://t.co/LzAgqbezTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala Haris is going to crash and burn for this one:  Harris said in a statement announcing the legislation that T… https://t.co/1yOcHl5Stx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m Stephanie Hickman. Middle school librarian. Love reading books, teaching big kids, and being a MOB (mother of b… https://t.co/yJVk4XOdFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottcwheeler Pretty sure my in game hosting rights got traded to Barrie]]></document><document><![CDATA[The party finally started at the LRT stage 2 technical briefing. Joanne Chianello: “can you define ‘scope’?” Chris Swail: “More stuff”]]></document><document><![CDATA[somebody need to get me out this damn dorm asap i stg i can’t take it no more]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Cats steal hearts, not souls. Liz Collins https://t.co/8xOHteq9en]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from Daisy! ☀️ 🌼💗  #yorkie #teacupyorkie #daisy #yorkiesofinstagram #swfl @ Cape Coral, Florida https://t.co/2SPmDlKqN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WelcomeToErf @LittleMissLizz That would be a reason to not kill you unless you did not have thin mints]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to have five teeth surgically cut out in an operating room instead of a oral surgeons office because I have a bad heart I love life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@221beees I doubt I’ll be awake much longer. To be fair I am still sick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe @MeetThePress @NBCNews @CNN @SenSchumer @SpeakerPelosi @senatemajldr @SenGillibrand @KamalaHarris… https://t.co/mZlLrLVj9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Whataburger Little #piggiesue lookin’ for her Justaburger patty fix. 🧡 https://t.co/KPqlzTTjC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to even mention the retarded men who are holding these women back lmaoooo. Get ya own stop tryna live off your… https://t.co/7Ld5ORg4Nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Varsity Softball ⚾️ battling against Eastlake HS.  Go Big Red!! https://t.co/fFqGfm8Dvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have horrible communication skills and i’m so insecure                                          if i see somethin… https://t.co/MgXlDyWgHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the win! @keselowski @Team_Penske #xfinity #daytona #nascar #NASCARRacingExp300 https://t.co/6O4KnlJeng]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad jeeps have waterproof seats. Left my window open last night like a scum and the amount of snow inside my car is ridiculous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[no one has time to butter bread like that at all @colton you are right just eat the bread how you want #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really dnt be missing chicken, beef, pork allat like I thought I would!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming across one of those Zoltar fortune telling machines was probably the coolest part of my night https://t.co/eUkrWPGwnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another event in the books with these two...  #vista2019 #revsunshine #bdistyle @ Carlsbad, California https://t.co/77r8FgBTnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that makes sense, they’re sweet.  I’ve heard cows go nuts for pea vines]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad my order finally got shipped. @phora didn’t think I was gonna fit into my gear anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @TedCruz has an idea on how to fund President @realDonaldTrump's proposed border wall... Make El Chapo pay… https://t.co/PhUmVIl2Sc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams! Happy Monday 😊❤️ https://t.co/K61Ft03fWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markus_miller40 @jonasbrothers @3ddi3ddi3 The love never dies 😂 #fanforlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KezhalDashti What the What 😱 this will the song was the worst thing to wake up to #nowimreallyup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rita_S__ @HananyaNaftali @TWITMO_INMATE Whatever lady, tell yourself whatever you have to . The Jewish state of Israel is VALID and real.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @RichardLui That’s why I love @MSNBC . Richard stepped in without a hitch and had 3 great people on the… https://t.co/znohviduCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please visit our online store and like us on Facebook!👍🏻 #WanderlustHemp #HomeopathicAlternatives #CBD #CBDUK… https://t.co/GXQhhlOw5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InvestorPepe @TalbertSwan First your "facts" are way off. Send me a screenshot of that statistic and I'll need mor… https://t.co/3aoFzJFKlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸Con Sue Photography and Design🇺🇸   🇲🇼Like our photos...Follow our IG 🇲🇼  🇨🇱This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 🇨🇱… https://t.co/xa8TO02owy]]></document><document><![CDATA[☀️Good Morning Beautiful Ppl #goodvibes #goodmorning #goodmorningpost #goodmorninginstagram #goodmorningquotes… https://t.co/0qbh1nkxXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should try DoorDash, it's an awesome food delivery service. Get $10.00 off your next order when you sign up wit… https://t.co/0rSTFcGeWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurasessions10 Nothing makes a mess like popcorn, those old maids fly around and never, ever pop.  I found out re… https://t.co/Xcp18xEpuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMurphy @NJDeptofHealth I would like to read some tweets regarding spending cuts. Our taxes keep rising in NJ an… https://t.co/IY7Zq73XJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[And once these socialists (which inevitably leads to communism) grab control, THERE WILL BE NO GOING BACK.   And it… https://t.co/ZpOrHKqbpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[When BMTH said “We will never sleep cuz sleep is for the weak, and we will never rest til we’re all fucking dead”,… https://t.co/USo6LOaWkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity So the princess has spoken and every one has kowtow to her seriously]]></document><document><![CDATA[BTW my SIL has been watching the GBBO and so she has sucked me in. So we all know how I’ll be spending my time off starting 3/6 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyndacloigman I hear you. But still too many wonderful things to read for that to be a worthwhile philosophy for m… https://t.co/rYzBYl6hY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these new videos of dads changing their baby’s diapers and feeding them veggies and stuff and I am overwhelmingly attracted! 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArudanIsMe It’s funny that I have no idea what this about yet I can think of a few people who are like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lbenny92 Yeah thinking you can just put me on blast like that...damn 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the best thing an athletic coach ever yelled at you.  I will never forget the time my basketball coach yell… https://t.co/zl5Na18XZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hermanos Venezolanos! Inmigración acabo de anunciar que el consulado estadounidense en Bogotá va tramitar las petic… https://t.co/yqFcbzB82D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rarely have the chance to hear our radio team (always watching the game). @jamieseh @reneingoglia @jerryosports are… https://t.co/zVRjKbzYZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mojosusan @MichellBasler @Commandtechno @marieluciesecr1 @teslabros @marvelwonderkat @WadeAndersonPT… https://t.co/JO7O9hlLPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[And stix and stones may break my bones but words....  Show how ignorant people handle a losing argument!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This leave I’m taking CANNOT come any sooner. I want to be a normal civilian again when no one asks me SHIT about the fucking Navy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will note that the only guy I was in love with was a November Scorpio and we’re still friends. But we’re two Octo… https://t.co/Pwq5RCLGYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone take my god damn phone when I’m drunk wtf is this I have no idea what I was trying to do here https://t.co/FSR74wRns2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we turned on, tuned in and dropped out*  *Only for a bit. We’re back now. https://t.co/rEpiDCciK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[So windy! The only bird flying was this #eagle at Delaware Lake! 🦅 @ohiodnr https://t.co/QjUeG3v9kb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The photo was taken seconds before the switch was turned on... Amazing wind tunnel @NASA_Langley]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what you call #progress and #positivechange in Coffee County, TN! Makes me very proud of the new administra… https://t.co/D0U7wglKsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not take people’s kindness for granted, and yes, that includes your own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay - The @BlueJays are on TV ...oh happy day!! #torontobluejays #theboysinblueareback 💙⚾️💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[when i was little, i would tell all my stuffed animals bye before i left, and would remind them that i was coming b… https://t.co/GOgo1Rndjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsJCP @ClassActOrlando @TaishaMPerez @sliktoria @GuapoHenry @JoseV29 @ThePassageFOX Rolls for Roles! 🍕💫🎭 Because… https://t.co/BsuNzRAxvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton you gotta quit while you’re (barely) ahead #TheBachelor https://t.co/b8L5br1Hlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GIMiddleSchool working on their equations and inequalities videos! https://t.co/qMaz1qlxIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need something tooo watchhh on Netflix cause I definitely don’t feel like doing these tbh’s lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rugbynred @Jamesb40595620 @msdusa @PaulColby2 @Chihuahua1900 @kathrynresister @keanothedog @62WalterP @stuffbusted… https://t.co/5Hboq8yJJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Generals Salute to Nimra Khan!!! We are so very Proud of You and We Know You Will Continue to Be a Great Example to… https://t.co/Hkrw7cciE0]]></document></documents></author>