<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s a Flash socks, Venom shirt and Brooks Ghost kinda day. https://t.co/nFJ2Uuijgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MurcielagoLust No melee... Those arrows that take armor off X 3 ... 😃👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took Madear to see Madear one last time on the big screen @tylerperry missing @medicdiva1979 #familytime… https://t.co/SVNRnvgeUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJD1953 @ProudResister @senatemajldr Vote him out!! Come on Kentucky get your heads screwed on correctly in the name of GOD!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeahCartel @strom_annette @SaddleUpPeople @DarinColville @cpw_Numenor @LA_Karma1 @Mandalorian_Ren @jhgurf… https://t.co/D8gETF7Pg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleSandy355 @boomcloer Defender beat him to the spot, however, he turned his shoulders into the offensive player. Block all the way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@football2990 @Dispuesto2018 @JLHB33 @Chivas Al tio pelagatos solo tonterias se le ocurren]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ms_Riley_Guprz @WestPoint_USMA I was thinking 1861 through about 1877...]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lovely piece by @GolfweekNichols that reveals the drive, maturity, playfulness, generosity, inner strength and un… https://t.co/QKk9cOamPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thigh gap, puka shell necklace, snake bites. She does heroin and mtn dew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBAMemes Two words for this shit... Detroit Pistons #keepitoldschool https://t.co/HeYuHz5kFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ksh_bash @AliBHamed It was implied that we were discussing career success. Uncommon career results tend to require… https://t.co/aQHEfph50L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMPyper Lol. They’ll go BAANANNAs (Build Absolutely ANything Nowhere Near Anything)]]></document><document><![CDATA[one of the greatest moments of my life has been flooding my head all day and it makes me really happy and really sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jekrb Nice. If you want a level of abstraction or need form validation I’ve used “react final form hooks” and it worked pretty nicely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember ,it all started with little gestures, Less Chief Wahoos around the park, then none, then finally NO Wahoo… https://t.co/Wp3T1cyhnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tbhardon90 @crawford_cam95 @Chet_BeebeBNN @dearolenicole Where the hell was i?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les pagan por eso... NO creas que es de gratis o por buena onda y el tiempo aire que utilizan lo donan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willyshaf82 @MikeToldoRLP @MikeSullivan They are trolls man.  Everyone with eyes knows why UM didn’t get to the li… https://t.co/bJQk1cZRtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s nothing to do with food, it has to do with telling us what (in every form)to do.  Because, they know better th… https://t.co/hl2niGoqqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deadass if the Flyers lose tonight no one talk to me for at least a day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marianalongo11 @MariaCorinaYA Por supuesto, en las últimas presidenciales yo no llamé a votar. Pero ¿Por qué perdi… https://t.co/pohTuiYOW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good pooch - maybe I've got a dog biscuit... #GhostbustersLines * #BPS making their rounds in the building https://t.co/RBQA3YeIWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ginger climbed on me to get her ears rubbed. A reasonable expectation after catching and killing her 5th gopher in… https://t.co/cpUXsy5zmj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DynastyOuthouse @TylerGheeNFL @srstulljr @TradeAddictsPod @BrianHarrFF @Stoops1990 @MyFantasyLeague Mack?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen222 @realDonaldTrump You wouldn't know the truth if it slapped you in the face. You are a habitual lia… https://t.co/ZvV56H7Oeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MACNAISMITH Rainman is just trying to send the message that you shouldn’t vaccinate your kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldKutney @DrKateMarvel Nils-Axel Morner has studied sea level changes for 50 years and the effects of climate… https://t.co/4pqcZcwnxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend's task: figuring out the easiest, fastest, and/or most hilarious way to get ordained so I can officiate my friends' wedding. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Lakers logo on LeBron’s chest kind of ruins what would be a classic picture if he had a Cavs jersey on...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterLorrie1 @RepMaxineWaters WE said no #Individual1. WE said never #Individual1. But there's the electoral colle… https://t.co/KhqthSYSWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CentreCountyGov is making great strides with new voting machines as we roll toward #ElectionDay Check out the late… https://t.co/wjzlCYP95w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even when you dont get to accomplish anything you do in your day. Still give thanks for life bc it could be worst… https://t.co/aioPq1uS9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[No need for tricks, in my element....TBT ...#heroesandkingz #entrepreneurlife  #quote #positivevibes #lifequotes… https://t.co/UrVWlAC2nE]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/I11t3G7DG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cambridge, MA: SALVATION ARMY CHURCH BIBLE STUDY @ 0945AM. https://t.co/EVSt9wRRHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I TRIED so hard to like Hennessy cause that’s what I thought niggas drink, but I have my limits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people ask me for an “Android Charger”  Peasant I have iPhone https://t.co/7fD6BRok6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 am drive time Put this on and just hit those streets 👍 @TheMidnightLA #nightmusic #drivingmusic https://t.co/SnziMdp9k1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlakeDuDonis Interesting... Never thought of it from that perspective.  @ShaneLaflin @RayCwell100 @situsflip any thoughts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starphoenix26 Klobochar doesn't appear to really want to fix trumps mess or do anything to fix the messes our peop… https://t.co/IA3mHJcLoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cropper01 @Aulari_ALR It looks good Mark. Looking forward to the finished product!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAYLAPARX Yes. The universe works in mysterious ways, but what happens in it is what was meant to be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey so question. So say kap said i didnt want money and did expose the NFL. What would have happened than? Or bette… https://t.co/gtd0GVdpk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan We’ll know nothing. I’ve resigned myself to sitting in a room when I’m 80 and hearing the big revelatio… https://t.co/0N1CH6W5mY]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi do you or a friend need somewhere to live in philly?! pls come my way I have just the place!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite TV lines: " It's like teaching a halibut to put on socks." Harvey Bullock , Gotham]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bwreed @IlhanMN The topic is a humanitarian crisis in Venezuela NOW and she is attacking him for something that ha… https://t.co/zABrqFgl8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Variety In other words, Trump said he was attacked by two women in vagina hats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obstacles can’t stop you! Problems can’t stop you! Other people can’t stop you! The only one who stops you is yours… https://t.co/NMR9nW6wzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@n8sager @Jonathan_Dunphy “FROG PUSSY!!!!” - Faith Goldy (Doug Ford licks his lips like Moe)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren The liberal hate on this post just sums up who you really are “claim to be all about the constitution o… https://t.co/gMYffYIsHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennisPrager @JudgeJeanine Amazing job on @JudgeJeanine.  I love her and you were great on her show.  Thank you fo… https://t.co/nH73wj9S5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFLonFOX That one week in 2010 when the Vikings had Brett Favre, Adrian Peterson and Randy Moss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for all of your accurate weather predictions “discount Ben Affleck” as we call you in the station 😂 but s… https://t.co/7M4jeJnfFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr No ice but i-c:Y A-Policy in question NoTice NoLice I hope NoYesDice NoYesMice NoYesDice NoYes Vice… https://t.co/rdwtEQZ7Rc]]></document><document><![CDATA[What you do in this situation is u just click the notification tab And don’t read anything keep on tweeting https://t.co/Pl6ITJhQP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you pass a bill unanimously in 2002 and then 17 year later it gets turned away by 44 dems.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do we think about this ND state football player showing up to The White House wearing a democratic socialism p… https://t.co/DaCCLv6SYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder. Don’t stop at garbage and expect to order. 😂 (at @DunkinDonuts in West Haven, CT) https://t.co/VYH7XVNaoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just some quick bullet points reading through {John 8} this morning,I encourage you to read it today!   •May our he… https://t.co/ly4UsO8QTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s at least 5 shots from outside the top of the box. Only one tested the keeper or was even close]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started working with @augustrigo when I first got in the biz always been a genuinely great dude but it’s crazy to s… https://t.co/CZP11phQKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rardk64 @RyanStormrage Free == Easily   I watched a raycevick video about nightfire and had to play it for myself… https://t.co/5Vd6u9Yrjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now, Israel, what does the LORD your God require of you, but to fear the LORD your God, to walk in all His ways… https://t.co/a0CRwTwdUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending $1000 a month on dancing lessons and not telling anyone so you can just very casually bust out some sick m… https://t.co/PWeaSOGlEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!  Turley is a pretty good damned writer!  👏 👏 👏 (Clapping @JonathanTurley )  Why Trump will win the wall fight https://t.co/EiYf8GwonP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gosset41 Isn’t that the Dallas side of the news? @Gosset41 keep doing what your doing, before you came along, the… https://t.co/gLd31mn3qJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even a cursory look at @realDonaldTrump's Twitter feed reveals that he is still the same man who bragged that he co… https://t.co/3vdKR4cMQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spaceliontobi They have to raise the ceiling and turn down the lights.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@speakingmanners @CthulhuBen @evilref @XIIHangedman @char_stokely @kimberlykane @ZakSmithSabbath @sbeckertweets… https://t.co/UowOlnVPxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Aeropuerto Internacional de Fort Lauderdale-Hollywood - @fllflyer in Fort Lauderdale, FL https://t.co/5PnzLbsOuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Staggs_87 @NBCSPhilly Pretty sure the penguins did that last night. 😂😂 🤢🤮 . Good one though!  .Original!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The left does too often suspend disbelief in such things. And the right does also, the latest of many being the “na… https://t.co/kkQ4tXP0Ir]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a strong appetite for the day's approved outrage that's troubling. Also, always wait for the unedited video.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this momo shit is getting out of hand stop retweeting that bitch i am not trying to see that scary bitch on my timeline]]></document><document><![CDATA[AAF:   we only have money for 1 team uniform  Kaepernick:  I’ll play for $20 million]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayKnight25 Word is most was deferred to age 60, not a lag it offer. Best offer was from the Dodgers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/lvCCnWWvhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaroldAbend @salesianprep @coachnatesmith @Prep2PrepSports @MitchMashMax @CalHiSports @CIFState @CIFSports365 She… https://t.co/VXV4J8r8Vk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darth @annamerlan Puppy 007 says that would be entirely outside operational pawameters. Uh oh, he’s said too much.… https://t.co/ByQHjCu7AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scooterbates4 Scooter! I thought you were out chasing Russians and old tax returns 🤣 , the hoaxes and nutty conspi… https://t.co/wDeFjxaQUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ShekinahGlory_ @_iShotTupac ITS NOT.   I aint say HAWK A LOOGIE AND SPIT... come on now lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[$25,000.00 Share the Riches Gift Pack!  Play Free Scratch Cards!  We Could Both Win Big! #ShareTheRiches]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Unfiltered IPA by @LockStreetBrew @ Lock Street Brewing — https://t.co/OLoZmqr9xP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 They will only speak on the record if he drops below 30%.  Cowards, all of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjane87 @jbouie In David’s defense, I think he understands and might even intend the insult to a certain degree. H… https://t.co/0fKVar1jkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[cant believe we’ve been together for over a year 😩 and i’m still just as sprung as day one 💞 https://t.co/NwOK1SIaGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrnkrkptrck I woke up, stared to come downstairs thinking every light in the house was on... I was pleasantly surprised!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayedrepicazo @88lunanextdoor ANDRE ARE U FINALLY JOINING AZN TWITTER LMFAOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CHIvsDET I go with the Red Wings. My dad’s best friend the piano player George Sahagian was from Detroit and my mo… https://t.co/ryw960iIWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaggieRicker @krusty627 @VassyKapelos @AndrewScheer @realDonaldTrump And break the law as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok banda a ponerse las pilas #RedAMLOVE  #RedAMLO #RedAMLOvers #AMLOnoEstasSoloMexicoContigo #AMLOELMEJORPRESIDENTE… https://t.co/ZeB9g6CyIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGF91 La cuestión no es si el norte ya era más rico desde el siglo XIX sino si esta diferencia se acentuó con las… https://t.co/OpfY9f5Ziv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lincoln Regional Airport (LNK) - @lnkairport in Lincoln, NE https://t.co/K8o8ZMjnPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all the women who fight the good fight...we honor you today. #whitestone #queens #bayside #pizzas… https://t.co/n4rUYbgE6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #IT jobs like "Full stack developer" at Robert Half Technology in #FortWorth, TX.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Housley is a fucking idiot. Worst coach I've ever seen. Is this guy literally trying to be fired? You put bogosian… https://t.co/4Q8B9F5kM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WIncRebel @WrestlingInc I adored this, they played to the same dynamics they have on SNL as a team and it parallel… https://t.co/pb1ILHXJY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love martial arts so I think @RyankPotter and I would have a fun match...then he would turn into a tiger and I wo… https://t.co/nnx1lrMtud]]></document></documents></author>