<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber And the big old Karma bus is coming for 45!!  Praise the Lord!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I think of how badly I want to know what happens on the bachelor I just think how much I’m sure @colton… https://t.co/94uziWhKTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[when i watch the blind auditions on The Voice and the singers family starts crying when they get a chair turn i sta… https://t.co/85wuhz6Zv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign the petition now to tell Congress: Pass universal background checks! https://t.co/cPoPveLQwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to this amazing woman right here!! Cindy, you have played such a large role in my life over these la… https://t.co/aXGswcn0V8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Ulta Beauty team! See our latest #Cosmetology job openings, including "Brow Waxing Expert", via the link i… https://t.co/MmGOLjjBaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[PIT 👉🏻 CLT // Looking forward to seeing our Champions Advisory Board members for our Spring ‘19 session and the ACC… https://t.co/cYsfZQ9F76]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on my way to Washington DC for ACOG Congressional Leadership Conference!! @ACOGOhio @ACOGAction #2019CLC #Accessls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bearhandsband @WALKTHEMOONband @themillandmine My friend @TheCraftyTwin6 saw you recently and said you were amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No folks: I am not his another crash or short time girlfriend. Very long story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenna12022960 Just because people agree doesn’t make it right. It’s called opinion everyone has one. But it doesn’… https://t.co/8wYdBEgkiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casie190 Thank you. I really wanted to show y’all. I loved yours and Pearl’s. ❤️🐾❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So popular... time to restock the #40s @ Detroit, Michigan https://t.co/kooFiNjtml]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didnt mean to say "more often".  Pretty sure I havent seen any episodes that involved physical violence.  If anyt… https://t.co/pU7fi8nwRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[God shows himself in such different ways. Just to remind you he’s always watching]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giancarlo1985g1 @sadrbot @tedlieu @realDonaldTrump I’m not saying that at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Motto: I don’t work for the Algorithm, the algo-rhythm works for me (me functiona algo 💃🏻) off to #werk https://t.co/8oLGq97JjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to turn those clocks forward so you’re on time! #wateachlead 7pm PDT Sunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nedryun @BugsyBanks That was amazing. Two babies weighing less than a pound at birth show the true calling of Doct… https://t.co/RNr9NRQx4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@good_shit_daily @matthaig1 Then pick a non local indie. Any indie is better than Amz. When I haven't been able to… https://t.co/iMhOQNcEfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Independent and its curatorial concept made a good fair this year. Read #judithbenhamouhuetreports about… https://t.co/GmaH6kMg7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all the fans! You made this win possible! Much love for the Bobcat community! https://t.co/D7Hu32bP1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdoolittle @realmahershala What an amazing actor and a wonderful man. He’s incredible]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Coach @CYWrestle_KD - it’s been a fun two years watching this program rise! The energy and commitment to e… https://t.co/yu0AFX8RL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump Representative Eric Sewell is as mentally ill as his counterpart Adam Schiff these two… https://t.co/Njio9qENUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rejectedjokes @donaldglover @RobRiggle @sarahburnsie @Ben_Rodgers @eugcordero @issanatesmith so good ! i wanna see… https://t.co/WX2Nl5PdY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[UGH @Metra at LaSalle St station again brings in second string night managers who don't know how to park a locomoti… https://t.co/9jq4S11nIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2019 and bitches still can’t figure out how to do their eyebrow 😐 smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[It never gets old... I ❤️ these trucks! #steelcase hyphnstudio #whatsnow #hyphn #steelcasedealersrock #… https://t.co/9psRYkt8y5]]></document><document><![CDATA[No what is sad is that you (GOP) keep lying for this President. #CohenTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[McCabe Said He Was ‘Very Clear’ With Congress That FBI Was Investigating Trump https://t.co/ElHfE1dbwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never liked outings. If it's not about food or me socializing with people I partner with IM NOT GOING.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“when you look at me, and the whole world fades....I’ll always remember us this way” 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nuunhydration A2) smoothie with protein powder, collagen, frozen fruit, a splash of OJ, water, yogurt and chia seeds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you everyone who left me a testimonial!!! If you haven't done one yet,feel free!  https://t.co/bKX1j8DKFl https://t.co/dD5Psmd5UO]]></document><document><![CDATA[And by “seeing” she means ... @kwetoday was trying to go to sleep on the train, and I walked by and excitedly kinda… https://t.co/RPA9Q7AANo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awww they’re like soul mates. I hope she forgives her one day even if they don’t become friends again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 @alexcooper81 Why would you kill babies I hope something very bad happens to this guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using clips of @OneDayAtATime with my #MiddleSchool girls during advisory to have some relevant, funny, and real di… https://t.co/O0UiXOxLOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can feel myself getting sick quick. it’s fine :) everything is fine :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GracelandBSU thanks for a fun evening of great Karaoke and some new found stars. We/I need more of these!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ufolou He wasn’t wrong. You’re not making me kiss who I don’t want to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya just as shitty as the people you talk shit about so stfu w your hypocritical shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hallee_haybad @ELGL50 .@lib_seguin @bridgetdkoz @SavageLaura @CarlyLorentz @heypamdavis @ayshmonroe (and more) and… https://t.co/mOQOagGCEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherlyholmes @latimes @latguild Congratulations!! We of LA are SO lucky to have you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the record and FWIW, my extremely Republican grandparents were warm and supportive about me transitioning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom has ignored my calls 2 days in a row. It’s like she doesn’t even love me anymore!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sballenger3 @TheDemocrats From the Republicans You got that right liar]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RedForEd: Parents, Teachers ‘Scared’ to Confront Unions | Breitbart https://t.co/AUmDEdPgxF via @BreitbartNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods you are on acid @khloekardashian used to have so much respect for you but it’s your b… https://t.co/PcUWMxzOmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@livingvalley1 @JuddLegum Close st. Joes,  it would be great if we had a law school here (wishful thinking)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coding workshop at 7th Annual AV STEM Conference for Girls!  @avuhsdistrict #STEM https://t.co/EhCYAa4Cce]]></document><document><![CDATA[No se me quita esta tendencia suicida de cruzar la calle sin voltear a los dos lados.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi familia y amigos tienen 365 días cada año para demostrar su cariño, amistad, respeto y amor. https://t.co/wMQPM81Nj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want something from me I promise you dont need to call me 100 times. If I said I’ll do it, I’ll do it. Chill tf out]]></document><document><![CDATA[My colleague @JNRutherford is speaking about this pervasive issue. Chicago tweeps, who wants to go? https://t.co/zLWvi3fDlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[My teacher let Taner go to class with me because my babysitter decided to quit. I had never felt so anxious because… https://t.co/3RpZaWRs8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you know me, you know that I love skincare routines that are simple and perfect for those on the go.  Thankfully… https://t.co/1GilYKZZiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am the procrastination QUEEN today, holy shit. I’ve had my laptop open for hours, this not-so-giant task before m… https://t.co/kRnWNku4hl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesomeness!!! Questions: 1. Location of classes. 2. Time/Times?? Thanks!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdawsey1 @ToluseO @costareports I will tell you one thing I didn't know, some white people are so evil and vile th… https://t.co/bCVdtb8Uie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crackersnatch @EdKrassen Receipt for what?  I know about the receipts.  My tweet was clearly about his lying about… https://t.co/WauYospdey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker @DavidNakamura Don’t worry—there’s always war in Venezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[my cousin really showed up to my house cause I wasn’t replying lmfao I just been having my phone on do not disturb all day sorryyyy 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[After this weekend with our daughter's soccer team this quote from Mia Hamm seemed very fitting for a little Monday… https://t.co/kmMLlWEkFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always see tortoise crossing signs at fl.stateparks , but never came across one until today! @ Lake Manatee State P… https://t.co/zATYIbwZG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kahlerboybk @wildest_rose_ My husband had a similar set up. He ate pasta, chicken and rice, casserole, tacos, you name it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PostRoz @DavidCornDC  @chrislhayes @maddow  This guy I have seen in clips on Fox I think not 100% sure but his wif… https://t.co/93M9jdW4XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never stand in the way of anyone’s happiness... Rather see you happy with someone else rather being unhappy with me #BIGFacts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @LindseyGrahamSC @senatemajldr I’m #TeamVoteThemOut ✌🏾 #ByeBoys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjoelpimentel I know the feeling , I lost mine two weeks before i started my freshman year in high school. It wa… https://t.co/gkO3IWWKjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[um we have a delay til 10 but what about my cel nav test at 08???? i genuinely studied and was ready to body that t… https://t.co/hiZZEmMv6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just waiting on @lukecombs to do a full cover of “Don’t Close your Eyes” by Keith Whitley. A girl can dream 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews The aid will be given to countries where @ivankatrump is applying for trademarks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lastly, I want to give special mention to these Super Talented Brothers.!! @8thdaymusic have been getting Great Sel… https://t.co/MLfphsGOxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 990 can be one of your most important communications tools. #nonprofits it can tell your story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know you got older when this doesn’t describe your summer anymore HAHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IHSAA1 @FishersHighSch2 @HSESchools what is wrong with you?!  The culture of not backing these young women is flat… https://t.co/QpFXJZnZ1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Onett_Draws @IGNxLOL @monsterprom @Crunchyroll Literally competing in a field with over 100,000 active professiona… https://t.co/5PVzLFYXl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @realDonaldTrump @TheJusticeDept Sarah you were one of the very few people reporting on this all the way from the beginning]]></document><document><![CDATA[this Osprey has caught her prey... who is still alive... as you can see the Osprey has the prey in her beak...… https://t.co/i8PowTNNVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarlZagoda @JonahNRO I didn't see the tweet where he mentioned the dog is sick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeliz123 @Rich65k @SKenneke @lynell_mcmiller @CliffMcClain3 @CliffMcClain4 @hill_deryl @UPSSafetyNTexas… https://t.co/cY8ejATTbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve had @DribbleUp for just about a month. I’ve seen huge improvements in my daughter’s footwork and her ability… https://t.co/x0ptcSejgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are currently four kids missing from Scarborough as per the news @CP24..not ONE but FOUR kids.. Where is the… https://t.co/nVYY9g4gW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pookman_ The whole first 12 minutes of that show is absolutely iconic. Freaking game changer omg! The harmonies, c… https://t.co/0aW1KkPwOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[St Michael, the Archangel, defend us in battle. Be our protection against the wickedness and snares of the Devil. M… https://t.co/2yuCcBcSsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @kimguilfoyle @jussiesmolett @RichardGrenell You know it will be the dem who cried wolf.]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Koechner at the Tacoma Comedy Club! @ Tacoma Comedy Club https://t.co/R9FoTk2qgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatchSumZs @raleys @natomasdaily @natomasbuzz Checked in with @SacPolice sounds like it was a call for two custome… https://t.co/1HusWzmWNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing evening celebrating Black History with talented artists. Spoken word by my little sis @Iamjemeni,Sm… https://t.co/naiDwczDhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMcFaddenWNDU @MMcFaddenWNDU Well deserved Maureen! You will truly be missed. Thanks for sharing your journalistic… https://t.co/cVsng4cNkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this #Healthcare job in #SantaFe, NM? Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Bi… https://t.co/NVjZ9yBhft]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump I'm so proud to have you as our President and God Bless you for all you did. Keep fighting the lous… https://t.co/qF2J2LQYNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew the second he posted his most recent tweet there would be tweets like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeefBeerNBuns @realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Have you kept up with politics over the years ? OMG the parties have been… https://t.co/y8TMJ8sMYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your work not speaking you shouldn’t be either lmao has ya lookin dumb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoDrunkDrivers I’m so sorry to hear this. Drinking and driving is never okay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree they are just as wrong....that shit damn near worse like damn you just letting this happen to your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annoyingyang_ @meenayolanda For those of you math majors: that’s 10,000 times less.]]></document></documents></author>