<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hope your bone spurs don't keep you out of Vietnam again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw this on a Jeep at Starbucks today...crocheted tire cover.  Sooooooooooooo many questions... 🤔 @ Northwest Oklah… https://t.co/QyOpbetu1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[For an episode I only 2/3rds paid attention to, when I did, it felt jumbled and disjointed at times. Idris Elba is… https://t.co/XsKoFemoWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me pone siempre de cabeza esta mujer @KennyArroyo pero desde que la conocí hace dos años amé su talento y carisma.… https://t.co/vssJnjyxq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2000. @bobdeuell geared up to challenge Hall so Hall invited him to shadow him for a week.   "I'd be less than h… https://t.co/HMqJDffq4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alice swam in the Minnesota Regional Championship today. Grandma came to watch. Now they have a break from swimming… https://t.co/FWdxmtROyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luciandrade Eu passaria aí, de boa. A rapaziada tá ficando muito frouxa. É só passar, não precisa de agredir nem nada. É só passar!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joseph_johnson7 😇@Mach1academyva😇 @CoachSteveDBU 😇at University of Tennessee today 🏈💪🏾✅👈🏾 https://t.co/xqfIwSjg2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharoShane Definitely “tall”, not “tall-ish” but in the dating days, as a 6’2” woman, men would check my shoes for… https://t.co/5UyiMd8YXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a L'Impératrice - Brassin Spécial (Bourbon Barrel) by @troududiable @ Île Perrot — https://t.co/EFRg9sWrLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kyrie is a joy to watch though. I look forward to when he’s not a Celtic so I can enjoy it more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fistbumpfriday #crossfitopen2019 @ Transform CrossFit https://t.co/pRaTOvTFpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is this housefather charactor! One thing he needs to show is respect for the members of committee thaat are not… https://t.co/X6dACgYPY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re booked up already from Jan 29 ~ #03Feb2020!?!   You Chicago @cubs fans sure are sure about that next 🐼Bears… https://t.co/5PM6Y9JbHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Small world!   At dinner a guy I used to work with came up to our table to say hello.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonmouthGovNJ There is no fresh county air by exit 100.  The smell from the reclamation center is horrible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to the newest ranger love the hat #maga https://t.co/1arcCNlPNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo cute,💋jayne good morning happy Sunday have a wonderful blessed day you rock from John in Manhattan ny 💓💓 💓💓… https://t.co/kOTV7ZNyCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brewskidude @Dawgsfan34 @abparrish083 @ALiferGaDawg @Deblg1G @Betweenthehedge https://t.co/qVAyEf0yy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the birthday celebrations continued in the most wonderful way, courtesy of the beautiful and insanely talented… https://t.co/BVyUTdHdWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elizabe75855947 @shiralazar This is actually something I’m glad I figured out many years ago. Whenever I get reall… https://t.co/WAh6YmdXBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blkgrlpoet Congrats!!!Make sure to close the deal by finishing strong. You have many folks with you than against.… https://t.co/YeTb35kxuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[just found out Jonah might be quitting😔💔 what am I even working for now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPaulYall My whole point was this BULLSHIT shouldn't be posted or shared.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetUpESPN @espn @JalenRose @mspears96 I'm with @JalenRose on this one. We have become so quick nowadays that if a… https://t.co/bcGOnj1K6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phnompenhpost The quality has certainly risen since I purchased my “North Fece” backpack at The Russian Market in 2002...]]></document><document><![CDATA[While trolling for coffee this morning, I grabbed a photo with the (hopefully) next Mayor of Chicago...Lori Lightfo… https://t.co/J0mpejBvQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Controversial ZSFGH billing practice that left privately-insured owing thousands could be banned - San Francisco Ex… https://t.co/IWxffRNELv]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need a sugar baby to spoil with $500 as your daily allowance credit card #SugarBabies #sugarbabywanted… https://t.co/965tlPQW0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nucgirl75 @GabeWhoDat Silver cellophane wrapping made it a coin flip whether you would get stuck with a dry cinnam… https://t.co/ksPQhaCYi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frankacy I don't think I'd switch to vim, BUT I'd be interested in reading about it as an alternative to Xcode]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went back to work and the gym today. I feel accomplished and want another vacation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Micheal Cohen met w/ Adam Schitt's staff for 10 hours in recent weeks, speaking to the sleaziness of both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rogers only wants the Jays to make some easy money for the owner, without putting much money or effort into it. Cer… https://t.co/Nt3fNYYjEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging downtown this morning! Winter and rain in Iowa. Have a warm weekend Waterloo.  #winter #waterloo… https://t.co/IvhKTMunyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackHe02774267 @DavidHaydnJones @Heike251 @severinebond1 @CastielsAngels7 @KetchFiend I was just asking because I… https://t.co/dgiBqTHzLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some decent finds for the week. Think @markmartin knows a few of these guys. 🏁 https://t.co/0MxFemAwzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Now God himself and our Father, and our Lord Jesus Christ, direct our way unto you.” 1 Thessalonians 3:11 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajfromhouston @JoeTalkShow @ConsrvativeVato @Debber66 Count my blessings daily for being  born in the greatest cou… https://t.co/XHyfV8xQ8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dsmolansky Y ustedes cobardemente dejan desprotegidos a quienes han salido a apoyar la ayuda humanitaria!! Cuántos… https://t.co/OwFIz4JQJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[That does it for disk 4 for the 2nd half of [UBW].  Tomorrow I finish the series with episodes 24 and 25.  The day… https://t.co/40p6z1tYMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UGEplex Shadowrun deserves a series following a team doing heists. It would be great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarcasticSadOne Are you counting in dog years? https://t.co/XmdrYZCxHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some more photos from the night. #BooksmartMovie #sxsw https://t.co/cA51rMUkwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[DRC (ICYMI): Key questions UNT faces heading into spring practice: No. 4 -- Can the Mean Green continue their trend… https://t.co/kyZxJDPEJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsKellyPierce @chrissayssoo_ @ladygaga I am interpreting she is using a trans women to cause her hypothetical ex… https://t.co/Ieul8UBDQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We will not and cannot accept a world in which half of our African American students go to schools that are underf… https://t.co/T4E3WjHbO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be running long distance again. Not going to run any races until 2021 because I'm in school but definite… https://t.co/InWXAtcc9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[you are exhausting but I love you so goddamn much https://t.co/VGf1u2lUSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone just announces to a room full of people that they basically only want to do the bare minimum required… https://t.co/uaDpypQYvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyEssary @TheFalcoholic Sad part is if this was Aaron Rodgers the public narrative would be the Packers blew… https://t.co/BQ3Yo2omAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PaintBae just like #SaltBae but with paint. #ctfu @ The Gun Range https://t.co/UAO9UdzaTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the way, all flatters (false praisers) are COWARDS. You know that, right?? They hide behind them. Wake up Donald to the real world!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nifty inbounds play for Spruce Creek, but Oelkers’ short jumper bounces out. Sandalwood up 53-51 with 1:05 left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The number of ladies who wear shoes that would make it difficult or dangerous to disembark an airplane in distress amazes me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coreyandreasen I can't disagree with you at all. I'm guilty of jumping on tweets that hit my trigger spots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This case can “comprometed” him. Que porra é essa?. Isto deveria ser “this case MAY COMPROMISE him. O “may” se apl… https://t.co/ReCVWdDXNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SithLordAR Wake up, your girl has breakfast ready. https://t.co/5otVdJ1cPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the ones that have already gone bankrupt because of his incompetence?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bwill1130 Not gonna lie, this pic looks like a really good mug shot 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyberieus82 @AaronLemingNFL they tried but it was too easy for Ds when he was in.  He will find a place, we will find a better fit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So is Luke May really @talkhoops or @DrewFranklinKSR ? I'm getting conflicting reports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it so hard for my husband to OPEN the hamper lid instead of leaving the clothes on top of and next to the ha… https://t.co/DP5GUqq8uu]]></document><document><![CDATA[this girl in my night class burps all the time and she just burped in my face bro🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillTufts What about the racial profiling the turd does against white people or does he not know he's white! SMH!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lot of great stories from #MFLA but again there was no space for casual players. I thought a Magic Fest would cater… https://t.co/0PudGXLGiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn this is a good collab.  Enjoying this after many different styles. Easy drinking - Drinking a Hand It Over by… https://t.co/k5yKWchzcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking into updating my picks  Remember integrity, track record and public service  #Halalan2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[There have been more signs that this thing shouldn’t be made. THIS should be the final nail in the coffin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AirlinesBs @MotorsportsBeat You’re really Aaron out some BS with that tweet  😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chatting here in 15 minutes...To A T video premier at @youtubemusic   https://t.co/HZN4iCkCml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalleVonXXX HELL YES!!! #BonerInspiring #Goddess #Perfection #DreamCumTrue #DreamWoman #MyFantasy… https://t.co/2UC7LffzR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who are you in discipline and fellowship with?  What a poignant question, and a foundation to enhance the Transit… https://t.co/Dg9IqPy9Sa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TessFowler @GoGo_Picnic My go-to fall/winter drink: One bottle spiced rum One bottle of butterscotch schnapps Pie… https://t.co/6XKVwkpGGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was already on campus and class starts at 11, but went home so I could 💩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenniferarce01 @L_wendy99 Lo haría pero no me dejan dormir tus mensajes lamentándote por tu mal de amores]]></document><document><![CDATA[#malibu soothes 🚁 #droneviews @ Malibu, California https://t.co/dmaArfWTEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMatthewThomas @jfairchild13 @Julissa_Nicole4 @Baca_Nation @TheKylerMurray @PCnowisthetime @NFL @LAMARJACKS0N Exac… https://t.co/4WFPRX6C0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had the drive to write the way @lexaarosen does to make starter packs I’d serve as valedictorian at Harvard Law #latenightthoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Loyal To the Grain by Froth Brewing @ Froth Brewing Co. — https://t.co/ZkMr6xBdNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1PatrioticBitch @jeffbailey69 @JewelsJones1 @Jlowe1129Jill @voelker_frank @Lmchristi1 @ish10040 @Jali_Cat… https://t.co/H26uK1ercw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxSportsWest @OremOwlz @joadell25 He’s 19.  I say AA for at least 1/2 the season.   AAA in July.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShellyFromCali Looking good very nice definitely BIG TIME hot and awesome oh yeah!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuheadJones @ThinkingPython @_BottleCaps @woodyBIGGUMS @LongLiveChris @ldj1988 @jaypopdizzzy @MannyGalan_… https://t.co/i20zZfPfzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always great to give back to my high school! Thanks for having me @mrhs_athletics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came back to this... I wonder who??? Barrett? Brosam? https://t.co/OJW4X5jBDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ford my dad drives a 2003 Ford Explorer Sport Trac, and on his way to work the engine of his truck blew up on him.… https://t.co/noFaN3wrbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who put this show together? It's like Someone said "hey let's get some funny people but let's annoy the audience an… https://t.co/x0hkdfPfXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PierceParisXXX @NicSaharaXXX @RomanToddNYC @pman43 https://t.co/PUAQYaoo0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then the #311Cruise 2019 gets announced. We’re all in. We head back for another dose. And we get so much more than… https://t.co/hvEhyn642I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jinngonqui I have to disagree, only because I've been on committees where we do seriously engage these documents,… https://t.co/0U9eC93EvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀🏆 Congratulations to @CCHSHoops... the 2019 @CIFSDS Division I Champions. @DrBean14 with the game-winning layup fo… https://t.co/2FONeyRZyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be assured, my current Oscar speech clocks in at 30 seconds, four thank yous, a solid banger of a joke, and a charm… https://t.co/C9hEkw8811]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brockwilbur Hahahahaha I’ve never been, please describe these scintillating scents]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s happening at the #Daytona500 right now is like the last minute of a basketball game being delayed by 275 tri… https://t.co/mewO50ffr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congress considers making it Daylight Savings Time all the time https://t.co/Y6X89SKUcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nickelodeon is bringing back all that oh man the 90s kid in me is back!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@15schmidc @GreatMidwestAC @maloneathletics You were awesome and such an inspiration Collin!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time you think it's ok to tweet/Facebook/email this to a professional........ Don't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DREWBICE @HiMyNameIsSeton #MahershalaAli will win the Emmy for Best Actor tho hands down]]></document></documents></author>