<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Designed to keep you warm and dry in rainy weather, the Duster WP Field Coat is a waterproof, wind resistant, and r… https://t.co/MZGCd0v25u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Yet, as of today DHS has refused 2 support employers who insist on a legal workforce.… https://t.co/9S3mSKHMbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I walked into tonight’s @wsfcs board meeting expecting a melee. There were a few sharp moments, but by the end of t… https://t.co/0LuaHngsx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NolteNC @kansas_sun And the president said (We will build a wall and Mexico will pay for it!  FAKE NEWS along with… https://t.co/Aawua34zdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@victoria_at221b I’m disappointed. WHERES MY ANIMAL CROSSING?! WHERE, NINTENDO?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isolating myself more and more so mfs hear from me whenever .. I’m always there for people but no one ever make sur… https://t.co/tr8HIbIGCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OaklandTeachersStrike might be over but protests continue. Got this message about a student sickout. Looks like to… https://t.co/Wm3qRcjvfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @MrSwansClass to post covers of 7 books that I ❤️ No explanations no reviews. I’ll challenge so… https://t.co/EBZw0GlLpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sweet grandson Grayson. #blessed #GodisGood #grandma #chooselife #sweetangel https://t.co/nvvRgpUziH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The nomination deadline for the #Huntington100 is ONE WEEK AWAY! https://t.co/kiUVj8Oafd https://t.co/ZkIFQ8BGHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleyhollabakk I would love to hear an example of this so I could relate super hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[... when the smell of cigerettes remind me of dad..... sigh this will be a long journey :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lock your shares up at 0.60 burn the shorts and flippers. $BRKK is going to give us huge gains]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharleyMoss1 I love killing Time!!! Better man and burn one down are my favorite Clint Black songs that one is right there with em.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Devin   emeraldkailoni @ Texas State University https://t.co/hoNrNg1eRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take our shame away from us, Lord, and make us rejoice in your saving works. May all who have been chosen by your S… https://t.co/t2QVDUECTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So enjoyed your speech yesterday -- 2hrs WOW‼‼time sped by- "Sir my father always said - respect a… https://t.co/yk1e4eF8uK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to fall asleep after that nightmare of a dream I just fucking had.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz  deleting your tweet doesn’t take down as you can see , we will retweet this until you are charged, cens… https://t.co/wzr8cHBflG]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Belonging to a church is a crucial element of living a good, happy, healthy life. And this phenomenon ripples out… https://t.co/7SQVJRgag9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kihyun dancing to Tempo not once, not twice, but 3 times on Idol Radio totally made my morning!! Thanks for the TMI https://t.co/IRnyZmFtDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalReporter @QueenVicMirror @chrisshipitv @guardian And handwriting experts as proof.  Princess Di did not have… https://t.co/H6nb4l9Sh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessiGronsbell @SethxDecker I was just thinking how cute you look in these! So]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProseGarden_HJ Is your tooth that needs a filling bothering you? Find out how much just the one filling is. Do one thing at a time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come home from my best friends house and find my other friend in her underwear at my place with MY fiancé… https://t.co/qAxkl3Mnxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#beauty #updo #wild #hair #redcarpetlook #hairbyhare @ Rancho Palos Verdes, California https://t.co/eLY3DUA7p2]]></document><document><![CDATA[my boyfriend is the best human being alive. thank you for coming to my TED talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do I find out about tickets I bought and making sure they make it to me on time? @TMFanSupport]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitches sayin book me for prom but they makeup don’t even look good on themselves 😔 no boo not the move 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm leaning towards China. I want to visit a sacred land there called @Starbucks. - @FeinbergFOX5 👏👏👏👏 Let's go Jason, I'm up for it. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highlight of my season this year was sitting in the same row as @weddlesbeard's family. His daughters kept trying t… https://t.co/8WWXBQN7Xu]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey bby @SeaveyDaniel I LOVE YOU SO MUCH AND I CANT wait to hug u and then we get married and laugh in a certain someone’s face HA HA HA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please listen all the way to the end (it’s short!)  You don’t have to be a school leader to heed this wise advice.… https://t.co/NZBMZoX4XW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going through my closet and I have SO. MANY. CLOTHES how did this happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Name this school. Too easy? Fair enough...What year was it built?🤔🤔🤔 #OSDFriends #GuessingGame… https://t.co/goyNp7iN7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[me:  harlee: up until my senior year of high school i didn’t even know you could smoke weed i just thought it was something you ate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LTavarezECISD @TechyJD @Aggie_Tech @ldomsten @TechECISD @RJTechy @JaimeMi50367314 Yes @Aggie_Tech 🤪🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[i too aspire to announce the birth of my firstborn and self promote my AI research https://t.co/2hiTx9RF9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me looking at myself angry that I didn’t listen to Melany for the 192719818th time https://t.co/2ZsojFwvgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliflute I know faculty members work hard to finagle things/budgets/etc to bring in guest artists and I like to be… https://t.co/7hMTsWSxJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No one lies more than you do! I would believe Cohen over you any day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davismaples34 Also he said “a discussion would be made” not on how to murder the baby but actually on end-of-life care]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was just made fun of at work because I didn’t recognized queen latifah. She was asking for hand sanitizer and I h… https://t.co/9DCD7o7KBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@superinspired67 @thedoorgal @subtextiel @Hailee_RN So glad you're there to represent the rest of the Family who can't be there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Better Path to Universal Health Care by @jamie_daw describes Germany’s UHC model: “This model ensures that all ci… https://t.co/iw5nst0KyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hellboy919 @SmMarwood @stevecourtney79 @scifielements @Wembley138 @MaraRanger @darth_swlove03 @i_stielow… https://t.co/a2PF5WUaoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cowboyneok @GMinto @CharityMeads1 @GovernorKayIvey @VP You know what, God will show himself to you one day so I'm… https://t.co/biYVuFr9hq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve apologized to ONE man in 2019 and that was on New Years Day I’ve met my quota for the year 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re a complete BITCH that USES PEOPLE -and- you surround yourself with SCUM! Good RIDDANCE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 31st birthday to my best friend Brittany 🎉🎊🎈😊❤️ I never knew how much I needed a friend like you in my life u… https://t.co/bbkEOx6toR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet Trump's rump! What do you think? https://t.co/pHyZxK8OhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not sure you heard me right the first time. Aviation camps of the Carolinas is considered an educational Journe… https://t.co/rwg7h6uQ5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excelente noche e inicio de semana @HitsFm1061 me pueden poner la canción #DeberíasEstarAquí de #RíoRoma, por favor… https://t.co/9bAu4RkaN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Septembers_Song @corneliagracchi @JeanO_Appleseed @IanThom01 @charbhardy @SbredsFarm My father’s parents. She was… https://t.co/PgKJzkluh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Resorting to quoting racist children in your quest to stifle the press]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaclynhill I honestly thought that series was a joke the whole time and when I realized it was real I was like....… https://t.co/aq5lwmHqNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RavenEyz Oh ok. It was a little confusing as to what initially happened.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir WHAT LOVE? oh! The love of OVERBOOKING EVERY FLIGHT!!! #greedy #worstairlineever]]></document><document><![CDATA[SILVER AND WHITE HEARTS MAGNETIC FRAME https://t.co/GAYqwqlxDj #ZazzleMade]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I said stay in the house 🏠 Carl” #wscruise #tompayne #chandlerriggs #twd https://t.co/2IsVUyox8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan you may feel angry and feel you represent suppressed people, but I feel you could be more effective if you u… https://t.co/Lqizg45vcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Theres nothing else that gives you such adrenaline than trying to mark a calf as the cow is trying to eat you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jarrodmjohnson "Got To!". Just think about The Rabbit Song! https://t.co/SdzqCpH4sb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland North Korea changed from rice to potatoes and that's a very unusual cultural change for Koreans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gudvibez I just saw that, he hit 8 other cars on the street, po'baby man... 🙏 For That family]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NoBorderWall #BorderSecurity #NoWallNowNoWallEver #CBP #NoWallOnOurWatch   https://t.co/21X3RngsQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LunchLady420 @TheRyanAdams Do you read or watch the news!?!  Google Ryan Adams and see what the buzz is about!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SundayTings 😘🌱💪🏼🐣🐓🐄🐖🦃🐠🐶🐱🙏 #endspeciesism #speciesism #animalrights #friendsnotfood #vegansofinstagram #vony… https://t.co/zunuvFglCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaybeware "Freedom of the press is guaranteed only to those who own one." AJ Liebling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing my headpieces on #offset and his kids on these photos by pepwilliams for the his new album.… https://t.co/dmkEEOIXpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hinch said the “young guys that everybody will immediately go to” Whitley, Martin and Bukauskas are not options for… https://t.co/Woq092XqXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the @bowlingball weekly contest. https://t.co/PG8mhxRkbn #52Weeks52Winners]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good for Gaga for shutting down the rumors of her being in love with Bradley Cooper. They’re actors and they wanted… https://t.co/mehFOFkxRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you keep telling someone they are hurting you and they keep hurting you, it’s your problem. Set #boundaries.… https://t.co/tZVmYGahU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OffTheTriBoro Looks like I will also have to go to High Branch the next time I visit. Also, brackets are the best part about March.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are we just now acknowledging the imprisonment of Dr. Walid Fitaihi by the Saudi Kingdom?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdkliebert @ESPNRadioNOLA @Gkatt_17 @Public_B_Enemy There's bookoo laker fans in the N.O FAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barracuda_Bella @JugularGrasp They cannot escape the overwhelming evidence of their involvement in sedition. This… https://t.co/IYOVK5JFXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posted withrepost • @hey__sweetie__ 🏡 🍪 🎥 💕 . FOLLOW @hey__sweetie__ . #heysweetiecookieco #instagram #dessert… https://t.co/5V93CZfIrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all rather have money, love, and happiness over your health lmao trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonicFox5000 I lost so many brain cells trying to read and understand that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi, Jessica, PATINS specialist, technically on vacation and doing lots of self care, but taking a break from my break! #PatinsIcam]]></document><document><![CDATA[A party where everyone has to teach a mini lesson on how to do something mine would be making quesadillas]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I told myself don’t get attached. But in my mind, I play it back, spinning faster than the plane that took you.”… https://t.co/Idw53jrWLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not going to the #Oscar2019 tonight? There are plenty of parties to go to. I’ll be at 3 of them, including the… https://t.co/eDhZar4A2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande OMG, I jus downloaded the *Arimoji* app &amp; I'm in love! Y ya gotta be so damn cute, @ArianaGrande❓ Love u LOTZZZ 😘🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[as it turns out, trying to tell these stories/musings to darling bf while he’s literally 99% asleep is not the best… https://t.co/e56gO7D2RL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aw, It’s My Park Day falls on the Saturday I won’t be in town. I was so excited to get registered to volunteer :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidhogg111 challenges current @TheDemocrats Presidential candidates to speak up about gun control and gun violen… https://t.co/6Dfg46TMbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mndarnell @darcjai  @BryceDarnell   - 13 degrees windchill -30. In the northland]]></document><document><![CDATA[This year for my bday I’ll be in Costa Rica playing a gig. I’m counting the days. However I miss my girls, road tri… https://t.co/tlj0Bai6R3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look I am trying to rest and think.  You are taping me, why? #pureentertment #pets #bichonfrise #resting #randr @ W… https://t.co/iWXKN4GVHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realCalebLawson Thank you for following me Caleb. I agree with you about the Emergency and his re-election. I trul… https://t.co/1Cxi4tHuB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s funny is that sometimes being right is scarier then being wrong .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCDOTPress Seriously, would it kill you guys to light your roadways? There are deer all over the side of 95 just w… https://t.co/evKNmpxxUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could cry I'm soooo excited!  Thank you a thousand times!  @ThomasRhett is my favorite!  @MelissaBotelho8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is kind of a piece of shit y’all. We love Vegas and he’s picking on low hanging fruit making himself look… https://t.co/jayCUIakLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there an unhealthy amount of times one can watch #Bridesmaids? Asking for a friend..... #sofunny #IloveRhodes… https://t.co/VnCseNAuZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickyDavila As my Brit husband would say I’m gobsmacked. When will someone stop this treachery? Unbelievable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was at South Oaks (psychiatric hospital) my social worker (female) said I’m more feminine than many women. F… https://t.co/bXq2lODzoq]]></document></documents></author>