<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Satosky24 @JromanJuanroman @maximitodiaz @DeportivaManana @YOHANNA_NUNEZ buenos días y bendiciones para todos! Ya… https://t.co/s67YTCl2yM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wyoming, Oct ‘14, during the filming of my short doc, “Chasing The Lightning: The Working Musician’s Life”. (🎥 avai… https://t.co/WG8ranKkF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bot 4th: #Sooners 3, Dallas Bap 1  Walla draws a 1-out, bases loaded walk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chiephtian @TheValuesVoter Have you ever been to that area of Texas? I lived there for 16 years of my life and I c… https://t.co/BGFORvRwH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the greatest Intercontinental Champion of all-time @OfficialHTM on his announced induction into the #WWE Hall of Fame!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicalwire I’m guessing Hitler and Goebbels won’t take any questions after this propaganda laced bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Valentine’s since I’ve met Maddy that she doesn’t get me flowers 🙂 should I cut her off? I think yes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to file @CoryBooker’s Marijuana Justice Act https://t.co/0cdP9e4JFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My theme song, Drunk on A Plane  dierksbentley   #DierksBentley #DrunkonAPlane #BurningMan #UpOnTheRidge… https://t.co/HWdGK4NMF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RalphNortham thanks. now the 18 years olds  just have to  get roommates to buy alcohol AND nicotine...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCatnipSultan @rdrhwke @Serremmy @ehgreenie @Jetsta812 @REDECLIPSE15 @WhackadooPress @IrisFoxNYCGrand @Dbargen… https://t.co/2ChloOQfje]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Hollywood casting couch is alive and well. Explosive report implicating the Chairman and CEO of Warner Bros exc… https://t.co/bnG5TOL95y]]></document><document><![CDATA[A second knockdown for Doumbe, who ran out of the ring thinking it was a KO. Wow. This is nuts #GLORY64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonechols @KimberBlodgett I don’t agree with you on this issue, but I genuinely appreciate that you almost always… https://t.co/1ew7MGADnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vas al oxxo en la noche por unos chocoroles bien perron y de repente te topas a esta pareja así viendote desde lo o… https://t.co/cXrw1NTsDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Blacks will find it much harder to play the race card now if they’ll okay with this. Apparently the… https://t.co/5eaiGN5jEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The whole secret of life is to be interested in one thing profoundly and in a thousand things well. . . .… https://t.co/YrrC9JpYD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pelicans and Grizzlies are literally trying to lose games for good draft picks. And lakers can’t even win those games mannnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@6abc Why did the lady shooting the video hide her face what does she have to fear?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @dbongino @RealCandaceO @realDonaldTrump WHAT DOES IT ALL MATTER?  If the world is going to end in 12 years an… https://t.co/7MY7G8pTjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if I told you @WholeFoods has the better breakfast tacos, while @CentralMarket has the better coffee? https://t.co/Kmmx0q0CzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdomenech @mschlapp Fuck you Clapper! You lied then and your lying now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillKassidyy @DanielJelley @blairsbananas You’ve got that big 🍑 very 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee We can’t stop c#a women from killing a baby, because it’s her body. Now the wacko Booker is tellin… https://t.co/qWaSaa55Ts]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOREVER AND ALWAYS #WADECOUNTY  #ThankYouGod 🙏🏽🙏🏽🙏🏽 3️⃣🐐🔥❤️ #HeatNation #DWade #OneLastDance  #fannypackswag… https://t.co/mQN17hRyBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finn found his way through this first time... he is a maze master. Call him Finnataur @ The Children's Museum of In… https://t.co/SWhKGKXIJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[18.30 min/mile. only one more training run then I have to do a 5k. @nuunhydration is still triberry #nuunambassador]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sebcourtney @Kimbchr @MissCTUSA @jmg27_janet @Kitkat8298 @ZillaStable Hope you feel better...lots of fluids! 🐴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennbeck Rep. Ilhan Omar is a Muslim extremist. If she cares to dispute this it's easy. I can disagree with any I… https://t.co/xCt27jLY9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkNagi Takes an awful human being to wear a Witten jersey and a Kentucky hat]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chuy's Barber Shop in Monterrey, Nuevo León https://t.co/AOCeeRncCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my boy @TyeOrsund10 for making the North All-star team. One more opportunity to play high school football baby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing all the people of Wales happy St Davids day love from New Orleans my baby has her Dragon @visitwales https://t.co/mWlveypFZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just wanna get you over my way bend you over side ways , do it to ya 9 ways last in it for 9 days 🌝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zerogspot @hockeybtch I should have seen it, she was Xx664232  man do you know, @hockeybtch well, it's not her fau… https://t.co/RTlvpFZYsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babuyagu @BobTetteh LoL you Alex and a few others are the only ones I bother listening to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayRow63 @CandiceHare_ @keenelandracing @KentuckyDerby Bounce back to what?  His debut showed he can run a big num… https://t.co/OGFswdyENC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimPhi80 @JoeGiglioSports @Phillies He has 14 hrs in 179 ab at CBP . That’s a a hr every 12 abs. That’s work out t… https://t.co/5ZNFiBgOaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chefjoseandres do you need a +1 for the Oscars? My DACA was finally approved this would be a great celebratory gift :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton What ever happened to "what, where, when"??Journalism is dead! Activism has taken over! It's becoming c… https://t.co/Pfu7oWnxim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @StCollinson For such a bombshell report, I’m not hearing any links to cAlOoShAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#woollybugger #flytying #flytyingjunkie #bassflies #bassflyfishing #flyfishing #bassonthefly  Get this fly -… https://t.co/GGyDrEytJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[NightLife Event Photography  @allswagga   🔥🔥📸🌟🌟 @ Baltimore, Maryland https://t.co/BjSxCjuyUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great friendships and great relationships generally start and begin with somebody else’s mistake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mak_enzie0 @kelseyycm @teal_colby @DrLeanaWen i never said get rid of pp, i said the problem was abortion. and the… https://t.co/Xl7sWnZRuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity It is a beautiful illustration in real life, of real immaturity.  If she was only smart, she could be effective. But no...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't tell how happy I am to see my children's excitement. First time of many to come!!!!   No puedo decir lo fel… https://t.co/Q2GVbHCZyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temp: 62.3°F Wind:0.4mph Pressure: 30.006hpa Falling Rain Today 0.11in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump If they are going off the rails about an f bomb , then what are they really saying and hiding about tr… https://t.co/zyHNuTqA0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danncianca Thanks Dan.  Ur feedback will be sent to the developers.  I too like it and feedback will help drive fu… https://t.co/Ae7KrAnTsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelHunt237 Goofy, but still better than most of the CGI crap, which would make it look like a video game. I sa… https://t.co/rH7Bc0XCCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsNanonano @OpenBarATX Yes it was a rsvp thing https://t.co/R2ThiSkBLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hotcouponmama .@hotcouponmama does $95,000 send a strong enough message to future organizations to not do this in the future?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took a picture of this girl tonight and when she opened her phone to get my Instagram i saw that my ghastly pictu… https://t.co/ZWeapHvNmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReutersVzla @NicolasMaduro Y estas? Ladrones, #doral #noperdon https://t.co/cXzZP3VPGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregbauman1 Guys were lucky to get a hand on him. At 13 is UNBELIEVABLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachMiles From one guy without much of a filter and a sarcastic streak, it's no big deal to me. It was clearly sa… https://t.co/5DyYY4KDAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realRostell @OmarKelly @KingJames @AB84 @steelers Brown is the best player on the team, prob the best they’ve ever… https://t.co/7z0PUCVk5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dazy_Daze @its5ant @nisaaa_torres @NicoleMoudaber @CharlottedWitte Yea I need to make a trip specifically for CHIC… https://t.co/TgT2SIIS3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 10% started throwing punches late last night and decided to stick around to the wake up.  So what?  Zero bearin… https://t.co/xtqZHE9fkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:51.1°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doubles lineup for the Coogs: 1. Kendall-Woseley/Tairyan 2. Ndindi Ndunda/Sophie Gerits 3. Phonexay Chitdara/Jovana… https://t.co/eBJhlzgCvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, Pantera, for the loud meow IN MY EAR at 7am which woke me up. 🤦🏻‍♀️  Hope you’re enjoying your breakfast th… https://t.co/Oba2qIZTLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonSpake Phlebotomy is the process of making an incision in a vein w/a needle.The procedure itself is known as… https://t.co/5GuYubGYN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Corey5771 My favorite part is that FanGraph’s projected record for the Phillies went from 80-82 to 84-78ish. 6 million/win/year 😂?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davezatz @Philo Hulu is working well for us, but for the wonky interface.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the #NCAA #basketball rage again?  #Zion #Williamson didn’t have to go to #Duke and the publicity he has receiv… https://t.co/dpARFSD1Ua]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think turning text messages into twitter and Facebook comments is the last straw. If you need me send a smoke signal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching ‘McQ’ with the great John Wayne.  “Get some foam on this thing! I'm up to my butt in gas!”  https://t.co/KrraKB8oOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@connorjessee Don’t do that the humidity and hurricanes will be the death of happiness]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my culture and my people. Can’t wait to see @robynkonichiwa on Monday in #Boston]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikePalmCirca @GUnit_81 I’ll give my own RR in Esports Tournament play for the weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/X7jabVnYrs  Play stupid games.......Win stupid prizes.......  #isis #ISIScrimes #Syria #isisbrides]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Taco Bell on the corner of Lexington and Larpenteur is closed. Wonder what will become of it. Anyone remember w… https://t.co/Y8T7fTWzBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for a  Great March! #StPatricksDay, #StPatricksDay5k #PuntaCana #MonthOfTheIrish enjoying a… https://t.co/zszHzsW2j7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulsiGabbard @shipman96 Ms gabbard do we the people get dividends from all our bailouts?  The past few years we ba… https://t.co/0W2bEZPd4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabriellaSibaja @RyanScottGraham I wish we had a huge house for you two to move into]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inittowinit007 @Jenn198523 Says The Victim Of A Hate Crime!!!!! I THINK NOT!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's nearly 1am and I'm looking at men's leggings on Amazon and am mad that they're all sporty. I just want some comfy pants, dammit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jwxrkRxskf We have a Verizon Customer Service Phone Number 1 (855) 431-9111… https://t.co/4lthO32899]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff No, what's absolutely jaw dropping is that given the blatant hypocrisy and pedantic whining of your… https://t.co/xmszHaAW21]]></document><document><![CDATA['Goodnight Sweet Prince’: Jason Priestley posts touching tribute to Luke Perry https://t.co/8fvxdn3bVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[With #DiceTowerWest finishing up, it's time to wind down and just have fun with friends. Starting off with… https://t.co/12X1vUkRi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[late at night, a few drinks in, had good convos with Tuesday even if i just CANNOT stop talking, but she's a sweeti… https://t.co/XoEg3DlRUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do girls find the exact tweet to retweet on how there feeling at that exact moment?!?! Because honestly I have… https://t.co/xjAseXDX5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell yeah @badreligion this new song kicks ass. One of my all time favorite bands. Looking forward to the new album https://t.co/40YeWZKGBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 1.0 mph SW. Barometer 30.102 in, Steady. Temperature 37.6 °F. Rain today 0.04in. Humidity 65%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hunter's Day of Hope (@ ADPRO Sports Training Center in Orchard Park, NY) https://t.co/kthcSumP8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Эхх, а в Москве случалось дорога с работы домой занимала 2 часа https://t.co/CvihgjVy2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SONOMO @DonaldJTrumpJr Not required by law.  Sorry. Will Nancy, Chuck and the other Dem party goons show theirs?  Yeah, thought not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaraDuffyCBS12 @TheHondaClassic @terihornstein @sabirahrayford Beauties!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNEWS @FOXNEWS You stormed out like a child getting s… https://t.co/bjjjNjgBlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[S2d52: I legit just learned that today was ash wesnesday, so no using the devils USB stick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rudykyle @ShoweyD Yes, i will watch higher quality basketball when it doesn't interfere with the Flyers]]></document><document><![CDATA[The US has offered up to $1 million for information about bin Laden's son  https://t.co/UimRfgc9KS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teslatunity @Tesla I think the reason they don’t is that they don’t want EAP as an option at all anymore. Until FS… https://t.co/MjI466nHmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facts hate females who got dudes and be airing their ass out for the whole world to see.... have some fucken respec… https://t.co/5FIQiXwI2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robsaucedo2500 You don't want to know how many black-and-white striped shirts I have bought, hoping to look someth… https://t.co/KhVLhlH0RQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The correct answer is “neither.”   The other correct answer is that anyone asking this question either doesn’t unde… https://t.co/Kd6kohT9Lq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kazzooom brooooo i feel this so hard i’m like wtf is this boring ass shit SMH i believe you could make some super… https://t.co/GLv3SwUcd5]]></document></documents></author>