<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@phambitious @TraceWall @nbhdgoods Also why I think @mrsharma's thought on the future of holding co's is spot on -… https://t.co/C27X2u9RIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 Sue the damn School Board fire them and take back our Schools Sue the hell out of them we have free sp… https://t.co/9Y0TdFMzck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cindytjshared Yeah you saw what he said right?I couldn’t believe too.Well yeah he does now,before I didn’t kn,yes… https://t.co/U7zybQQsaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Coach D!! Thank you for teaching discipline, technique, life lessons, and making me swole nole :) yo… https://t.co/JjDObEPg4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders If Bernie Sanders wins the primary there must not B a repeat of 2016! Get past it!  beat Trump! It's… https://t.co/6p7klP9JVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister Congratulations!  I am a single mom of two amazing kids. Both are, smart, determined and very indepe… https://t.co/e4WLfflHDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vistayouth_c3 High school Bible study starting at 7:00 tomorrow night after @OfficialCISD @CrandallSports baseball… https://t.co/PUsB31bVed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dracaenawines @CaththeWineLady @GailBenzler @Cbp8Cindy @jflorez @SteveKubota @ccatmpt @thatsVeryKari @simplysallyh… https://t.co/ULsHRgD1Al]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bentleycorvette @CBSBigBrother If u get it I’d just be sad I can’t talk to u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msmorgan1968 How cruel, poor pup`s the owners did not want him after the accident,but glad to hear someone(Katie)… https://t.co/qbJzkAwCYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free form is forced to air religious show 700 Club and their disclaimer:  We dont care if you watch this show or not]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just pulled up to @McDonalds and the lady at the drive thru said thank you for choosing Wendy’s what can I get for you 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@State_Champs one of the best concerts I’ve ever been too - and that’s staying ALOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMO102324 @DigitalBlunt_ Sanford &amp; Son is my all-time fave even though it has no lyrics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker keep the party together...after we have a nominee, the party MUST be united...my fear is that Dems w… https://t.co/dYfzmrld5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindhays @DalaiLama I’m a she not a he, but since 1st grade my name has been confusing people. 😸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karaswisher *That's* where you got your rock star aviator sunglasses look from! https://t.co/kb55oaZrur]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came up with a new hashtag that I’m really excited for tomorrow and I feel embarrassed about being excited about… https://t.co/IJlmaFay7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SagittarianMind @jakesastrology was an identity crisis at first, which taught me not to attach but rather entertai… https://t.co/Qm5PMOnsvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[City-building is serious business.   Mostly.... ➡️😂  PS - I work with the best people. 🙌🏻  @civicactiongtha… https://t.co/qvlWPlVYX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Church that wants to get bikers into the Bible brings a warming center to downtown Bangor.  @WGME   https://t.co/zUZZIpMNx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are the country's disaster. You owe us 10 billion for all our money you've wasted you worthless pos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadisonKittay I can too but stop being a twit about AOC.  Jealous much?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This is not what the @SalvationArmyUS stand for!” Resident of #SalvationArmy retirement community speaks out! Says… https://t.co/f10NIJa1fY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish companies would just state in their first two paragraphs of #earnings press releases the revenue and the net… https://t.co/OmnNLQpa5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is NOTHING, about you, that is not miraculous! @Kerrick2 @TheDavonLee @wearefaithATL @racquel_butler https://t.co/nSCvfSgYXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so true!!! Thank you for being a sane voice during this insanity!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosemoczulski1 @BxglL @72cricket @MrsSpuds @CSonafelt @sharon_schwan @sannbs @RidenerTina @ACog1984 You too Rose!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited to do my make up tomorrow but not excited to wake up early to do it 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iranian foreign minister steps down from his position via Instagram. We are living in this kind of world, folks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, if I tried this with SK she’d tear me to shreads. If you know my cat then you know😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love to laugh. kar wants a tiffany blue accent wall with black furniture.... I think white will look better...… https://t.co/lTUEdbW2oE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great head start to #ValveDiseaseDay last night with over 200 guests learning from our experts @MHIF_Heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Macman912 @NicolasColodiy @okello4101 @Roseann74 @dennison_bryan @Lorrainbutler @PaulDeveno Yessssssss team! Keep… https://t.co/vTIfwg446T]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby girl’s birthday party is this weekend, I haven’t missed a birthday in her whole 7 years of existence. She w… https://t.co/RjyGqI56k2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waltshaub Dear Walter, you are doing exactly what they want. We all get dicouraged but you are doing something imp… https://t.co/H0doqfimZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little bit of my work before my baby showed up to say hi peopleeeee. https://t.co/VVzJaZOVn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KP06108051 @IAmmSlimmm There's nothing wrong with your Eagles room. 👍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein GREAT! When are you going to protect we the people.  PRIOTIZE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw #FightingWithMyFamily. What a great, heart-warming film! And not just because @therock is in it. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living through 9/11 as a kid and now rewatching tapes of GWB give such strong speeches about patriotism and togethe… https://t.co/hIiZeknKUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, poor Rachel Maddow. She's got information overload for tonight's show. #trms]]></document><document><![CDATA[To book a reading go to https://t.co/h9pJ7TLNdy or call 937-971-8518 or https://t.co/UEPuH6donE @ Xenia, Ohio https://t.co/OzCcBaOH60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shawn172510 @gr82btnvol @madsatan6969 @The_Fool_Monty @Bubba_Henson @HippieVol @DollyVol @MelissaFincher @magnumCJ… https://t.co/nApBfihglM]]></document><document><![CDATA[But people say @ManCity don't develop 🤔. Kids a straight stud. It's too bad he didn't want to stay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Port_Charles1 @animalover65 That was an imposter Rick! #ThatIsMyStory #RedeemRickWebber #GH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aixum_ an identity that consists of experiences unique to those who *identify* as being a woman (a gender), rather… https://t.co/bGCqwJtw05]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super pumped to share some AMAZING new innovations at the #CX main stage keynote today! The team has been working o… https://t.co/0VUHSq2bg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RillitoRigata @docrocktex26 Don’t you know-  Jane’s probably still “working on them.”  I think they’ll reveal that… https://t.co/grCtApaxmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs .@usminority This is POWERFUL!  Again you’ve hit it out of the park.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sooo mad all these changes came late! He should’ve put on rlc and higuin from the 70’ #CHEMCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarenMorris #GIRL has been the song that has led me through what has been one of the hardest weeks of my life. I k… https://t.co/bBpYA0FK4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you recognize this we need to reevaluate our friendship. @ Edgewater, Cleveland https://t.co/s9OsNagGIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s petty as fuck but I especially love curving models (yes models plural and yes this is a humble brag)]]></document><document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion: kevin jonas is the cutest jonas brother. like HELLO https://t.co/l2Kp34s02U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 35: Celebrating a successful, delightful recording session with Secret Breakfast and Blueberry Boy Bait… https://t.co/L26rgT4yZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @lara_polk to post covers of 7 books that I love: no explanations, no reviews-just… https://t.co/L1XBKcOLOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Fun @949WOLX: Our #BrainStrain #trivia question continues from =Friday= -- this AM w/McGaw at 7:30! And a new deli… https://t.co/bwQVVI9Z7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mr_e_guy @H2VisaConsult @archwaylawncare @ChadWhorton @kevbrog @DouglasConley13 @SecNielsen @SecretaryAcosta @realDonaldTrump @USDOL Bingo]]></document><document><![CDATA[music hits different when you listen on vinyl with the lights dimmed in your bedroom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because if you are me in 1996 transplanted from a tiny town in Indiana to college on the east coast you deffo say t… https://t.co/FtWhoHfaEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @DonaldJTrumpJr I love Fridays. The giddy anticipation of Junior in cuffs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have a terrible cold so you’re bumping elbows instead of shaking hands. #mepolitics https://t.co/hp3MZ30dry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yolo County EMS is preparing for Cache Creek to flood tonight. Please do not drive if you can avoid it, and stay safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Public Policy participating in the #GTDoggoneThankfulForOurVeterans Dog Photo contest. Here is Sadie, one of our ne… https://t.co/mEGB3hD8oi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist I love it that young people are getting engaged in politics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shuffle Your Summer Wardrobe with Sublimation Shorts this Season https://t.co/hgSFcWbm9E #SublimationShorts… https://t.co/FQqnaFdDEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interview with Gary Gagnon, @MITREonCampus CSO by @marcom_mary #cybersecurity #glamour #RSAC #sanfrancisco… https://t.co/6E86Pvd6Jz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending 💖 this morning to all of you doing a warm-up routine or working out even though you don’t want to 😎 #discipline #routine #excellence]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOAL TO THE @Arsenal! (2-0, @Aubameyang7 69' – P)  #WeAreTheArsenal🔴⚪️ https://t.co/6HblsZuMn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! @mer__edith tech employees have a right to know where the tech they are building is being used #nytnewwork… https://t.co/mmwCrJ7mjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody @FortHoodTX Please everyone in vicinity let’s send this soldier home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a black stewardess just called put everyone on the plane and I'm 100% here for it..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well here’s number thirteen for the democrats.ive never watched a democrat debate,but this could be funny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ligar para hospital, Bahamas cruise, pagar insurance, pagar sunpass, pagar crédito, marcar facial, consulta dia 6, remarcar testes 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGA96825 @RepAdamSchiff @ColemanLynn05 Oh and follow up question if you think homeless is an emergency wouldn’t m… https://t.co/noLk9zBdV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy tan acostumbrada a dormir con mi precioso que sin su brazo no puedo dormir pero por darnos lo mejor todavía e… https://t.co/HYSAo2cCid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to kick Monday’s butt 👊🏻 What projects are you tackling today? https://t.co/ScGlXdLEMX… https://t.co/Uyp8yCCFCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments You can take this to the bank.       If the tables were turned and this was Hillary Clinton investi… https://t.co/IdhPyOXmiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time on @atlandco this AM! More pics to come. I love this show because it’s all about the Happy News! T… https://t.co/thv3wEHJxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perrynoble I believe some of you replying are just more examples of the problem.  People are dying and going to he… https://t.co/IgZPay1iRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my one &amp; only @justinbieber ❤️ https://t.co/a4bIl8On9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations are in order for Niki Kelly with girlsincofbaycounty for being given the #humanitarian award✨🎉 Than… https://t.co/Gspc8SfinD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every year we run a red carpet between our apartment and our neighbours @cathyclyke and @sugithvarughese down the h… https://t.co/LAVSICCTHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reviewing all of my hygiene classes/units I need to take and i just want to cry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosLuisRivera73 @emastromatteo @jgamorin @bugabea @mvdsister @RamelaCarlos @nelpold @mariososa29 @petche64… https://t.co/XVWOHbHAr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of the #NationalEmergency  It’s serious folks! https://t.co/bVecdA4izW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @TheJuanWilliams Juan is only on the Sunday panel  b/c they needed a token idiot!! 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catswithnohope As a rule Torti's are an odd lot. Have has a few. But, they are beautiful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Comicsandcats Ha I was thinking today I might as well wear my car to work with all the cat hair I have on me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its 320 am. I need to sleep. But I also need to play........ fruit ninja]]></document><document><![CDATA[Olive Bistro Midtown@1050 Juniper St. Check us out #atl #Atlanta #diningout #atlantafood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian @kkwbeauty #MondayMorning Please support my daughter Reality Winner who is serving the longest priso… https://t.co/hgXV8Phhkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Measles alert: Chicago Midway Airport passengers warned they may have been exposed - CNN https://t.co/q5SFdWkAzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay here goes...I'm looking for caring supportive friends. Particularly members of the #SPNFamily. I have some but… https://t.co/IyLRk2MiOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my coffee creama drink and won a free tee-shirt! https://t.co/jiShV8R5Ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakepalmieri I’m leaning towards the mayor and local officials,trying to sell how safe their city is,because I kno… https://t.co/D8Yby1E8gv]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's just my opinion I've seen what they've done to my children and they need to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pizzahut y’all definitely suck at delivery , it should not take 2 hours for a pizza 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late post, but congrats to the @ChargerMBB for beating West Alabama and advancing to the @GulfSouth Conference cham… https://t.co/mZ4GZOp0Jl]]></document></documents></author>