<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Welcome back @WWERomanReigns ! #RAW it’s time to get to work and reclaim what is yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best game I have ever played. Right up there with Slug Fest for the Game Cube]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gotta get it done like everyone on the court almost looked like they knew even on the @ATLHawks were going to l… https://t.co/4g0NlCmnd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@surfnutsc2 @RepSwalwell @realDonaldTrump You have nothing to break about antisemitism and racism. According to Tru… https://t.co/5exbr01iGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noturpalsis As an adult you’re showing your maturity by informing them you’re no longer interested where as by not… https://t.co/XAqXV9Z7AG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PMRF_ALLSTARS @TheRealDIGGZ_GC @Complex Wow blame the victims family? The parents defiantly messed up but you fina… https://t.co/5MI7vztDom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mad_ship @courtlewis127 I'm curious how many dm's you got of dudes' balls upside down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AspireLAschools instructional Rounds @aspire @AspireInskeep @dersaroian https://t.co/JNmTLBRcTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[College  are run by ideots who care about money  they dont care we get it we are all setup to fail after high school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ONILEONA @mirchilly Lmao chilly the boss, u gonna have to grow a Ross beard to talk that shit bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkinSawyerr TALENT IS NOT EVENLY DISTRIBUTED EITHER - otherwise i would be lebron james or kobe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMikeVea Sorry to hear brother. Hope you have someone on it for tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker So now our president is going to have his name on houses of prostitution?]]></document><document><![CDATA[but I can hide it when I’m all dressed up. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . #arianagrande #instagay #mensfashion… https://t.co/F80GdqsMcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Parker5675 @VivTeach @drevil_philippo @tomradman @hintze_steve @LittleMissFlint @realDonaldTrump Bwahahahaha!!!  T… https://t.co/XREMGVo7r7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottyP_Math Yessssss!  Still a class and professor I speak highly of to the AP students at my school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SierraClub #HumptyTrumpty was obsessed with a wall But he couldn't get Mexico to pay for it all When Chuck and Nan… https://t.co/4KAFgQ5Lor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefDOutlaw Recuse yourself and let an independent party investigate this. Then resign. You are a joke. And it be… https://t.co/XksFEUrn4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCWorldNews I have a couple of stories but I’ll keep my mouth shut or no comment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brother when you start making a good amount of money, you’ll see people from the trinches come out the blue.#besafe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @AP Happy Friday Bob! I love to watch the mighty fall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldAShults Is say they made the right call, then. But...Can't take away the experience, bruh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metasynchronic @0xKruzr @imisspoundsigns @ShelleyElwood @TheBInstitute @cheerful_ExGF @ianmnoone @alicere @Rutho_… https://t.co/jzlLLWpeqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please do, at least up to episode 3. That’s where the show takes its turn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisonhismac @LinkedIn Haven’t seen that one, but I can tell you that drop down menu and on LinkedIn don’t work o… https://t.co/RtBxEzrNk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I landed safely but now this Cali-boy had snow to deal with! @ Kansas City International Airport https://t.co/MTvZil75GF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just 400 miles from Portland.  Look at that beautiful trolleybus burning 100% clean hydropower.  Meanwhile in Portl… https://t.co/nijbbg5GjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overtime in Virginia. Virginia and Eveleth tied 4-4. Catch the finish on https://t.co/IoxXdFTKvd right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Female talent need for new pov site in Vegas paid gig dm me if that you thanks 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us and wish a Happy 17th Birthday to @BraydenHolbroo2 !!  We are so proud of the young man you have become and… https://t.co/Ki7jaW0iuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so sad how many women can relate to this (based on the comments) because of horrible spouses. I feel so happy… https://t.co/xRkG2MIWxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished a GM2 stronghold. Took like 45min. My Storm and 3 other Colossus. Got 5 masterworks and one legendary. Unf… https://t.co/Ue9UVHNb4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NHLBruins now 15-0-4 in their last 19 games. Longest point streak in #NHLBruins⁠ ⁠ history since 1940-41 when B's… https://t.co/97Ydk7ol8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 293: An Ode to Alita; Battle Angel... #alitabattleangel was a movie that I was very surprised at how good of a… https://t.co/HyGBVnf3Yg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stewartsc @instrument Cool man! Gotta check you guys out. Hope you’re enjoying PDX. I lived there in the 90’s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theygone238 @gijoefan82 @TheFullForce Aw! You’ll probably regret that decision!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarleneKeener @TMURPH88 Conservatives have to out bully the bullies on the left. It is not typically a conservativ… https://t.co/1A419Fbq4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[GDP as an economic indicator is like using number of tinder matches as an indicator for dating success.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can you be an Uber driver and work knowing you smell like dog vomit and your customers are gagging on your musk in the back seat?]]></document><document><![CDATA[People automatically associate experience with improvement. Reality is frequently different than our natural assump… https://t.co/pteX6NTFjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m such a fuckin jerk sometimes like I see it.  But it’s sad because I’m such a deep person and Id like to say tha… https://t.co/Bg05azWEFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the worst when you’re mixed race. Do I put Hispanic or Latino? Do I put Black (not Hispanic or Latino)? Do… https://t.co/q7qMR1jodl]]></document><document><![CDATA[After watch Texas play #1 ranked LSU in person. Texas plays with so much heart! They do all the little things! I love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a long weekend with The Paschels! This couple has a huge loving family and extremely excited becoming first tim… https://t.co/dOplguqryP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTN24ve EL LUNES EN LA REUNION DEL PRESIDENTE GUAIDO CON EL GRUPO DE LIMA Y  EL VICE-PRESIDENTE PENCE SE VAN A PON… https://t.co/QfDX13OaUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr I think that is what America has been saying about your CRIME FAMILY. You been running around commi… https://t.co/fPcC9BPwEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrote this piece a few months ago for @courierpaper 🙏 Appreciate the opportunity to share the uglydrinks journey th… https://t.co/QQUQEE9M8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Losers always focus on what the winner is doing. https://t.co/c6mNuBfJvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This new Dolly meme is not funny. Stop it!  Also me: https://t.co/VlXWDoV6zT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to hear former Senator  and current member of the Santa Clara County Board of Supervisors, @joesimitian at… https://t.co/rNyUyPydr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3coltshandicap @GGFracing Sal's. 50 late pk4  R6. 1,2,5,6 R7. 2,7 R8. 4,6,7,9,10 R9. 2,3,7 $60 good luck… https://t.co/FdZfcfZs1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aguilleramirez Omg YES! El que me regala esto, bitch me caso I have found the one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer @joncoopertweets I’ll go out on a limb here and say that the Trump kids get far more attention]]></document><document><![CDATA[I at least only fed one addiction today... and it wasn’t dick. i’m so proud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcfunny @Lovelyy_Jules Ralph you are one to talk..what you do, sends unsuspecting parents to willingly trust their… https://t.co/oHOheqjno7]]></document><document><![CDATA[EmJ and Momma are off in AZ  for a soccer tournament so it’s just P and I all weekend long.. so let’s start it off… https://t.co/uhJOhBosqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday morning! Awesome week ahead!! Let’s be kind to one another! #fitnessinspiration #sprinttriathlon… https://t.co/I0YdtyCpSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Taxdude @JimCarrey Trump is a lousy President. He's the worst President we ever had. I don't support Trump at… https://t.co/2Lt111blD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Valentine service last night with our Future Chefs in Action.  @ACHospTourism @AlgonquinColleg https://t.co/Zy0xzW39Be]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJayTruth18 @shondarhimes @maggieNYT Feel the same way. Hard to watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday Night Stream! 10 Days till Spring Training! Let’s continue to grow each day and have fun! Enjoying this new… https://t.co/vTXGTpALVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Merlin3ks @stevenewing @roadshow @VolvoCarUSA @gwestr Not even hybrid (I don’t think). Volvo was originally suppos… https://t.co/ytpnXyqnYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeff_gluck He gonna get a turtle shell shortly and start chucking them aroumd]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2018 “the Department of Defense spent $2.3 million crab (snow crab, Alaskan king crab, and crab legs and claws)… https://t.co/y4esFdwq8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[A different version of yourself exists in the minds of every person you meet throughout your life. From one to the… https://t.co/3wgYzsZQHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just have to ignore your head and your heart and go with your gut instinct. Today I made the decision… https://t.co/Mw4YaRF32Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NieceMotorsport @RossChastain @TruNorthNA @WhereIsPaulJr I’d love to have one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr Donald Trump: Si te dejas intimidar por los Rusos ,por la opinion de "LIMA"y de las charlatanerias de MADURO ...… https://t.co/kK7MCq0ynT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QTRResearch Either side is made of people, and people, of course, are prone to error.   The timing of those mistak… https://t.co/QmjpqYdxYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southerntexasc1 @EdKrassen Actually, I have no problem with police shooting when necessary but I honestly cannot r… https://t.co/w9HEZK1ti4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Lime Junt by @memphismadebrew at @memphismadebrew — https://t.co/sfnliAlnsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom I am 50 and still use Mr. and Mrs. for some of my friends’ parents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #DreamMaker herself @cbeteta on the power of tourism and California’s position on the cutting-edge of sustainab… https://t.co/LRCZHn0xY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadNerdCorp @923TheFan Sabemetricts had him a top 10 in WAR. And that was in a off year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sooners 27, Iowa St 29 4:19 2nd  Oklahoma went down by as much as 9 but they have clawed their way back to within 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your significant other is busy today... sorry to break the news but you are the side piece 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RuppSara One of the strongest I’ve ever known! Plus there’s an army of folks who stand with you!! Let’s take care of it!!! ❤️💪🏼❤️💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum You could run police tape from one end of the border to the other and Trump would claim his big beautiful wall has been built.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're absolutely right but it's bigger than that. We in the DCFS/CPS reform groups have known for some time that C… https://t.co/rJoYdkZyxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanieEastwood @trevbrowning No need to stress! Check this one out https://t.co/ajyKoZfKp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Jurcik Yeah Jr. is not a power 5 player whatsoever. He really doesn’t bring anything to the table. Avery just… https://t.co/OepTlgUPVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen live Monday night, 2/25, 8pm central, via #wslr as I discuss the @HoskinWarner campaign. Councilor Warner an… https://t.co/1I3vgvcf6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Assyria_news Assyrians celebrate today the exhibition of their beloved king Ashurbanipal at the British Museum in London.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lot of honorable mentions here though: Tyler O’Neill, Dex, DeJong, Girsch, etc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cfitzfox How about poor Defense  they just don't look very good and Paul George shooting sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems like the Man has been shopping at the same store as Uncle Shinsuke #TheMan #WWEChamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SedanoESPN @minakimes We were on WIC so we only had this. They said “it was for kids” https://t.co/JtflMAy7pM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBlankenshipWSB @KarenMintonWSB She is definitely going to be missed, But she definitely deserves to enjoy a new c… https://t.co/5DmQtGmkrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is fulfilling and rewarding when you get to spend it around motivated, kind, and courteous people who enrich i… https://t.co/T6hBfil5QC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jansinclair9 looks like Clapper is hearing footsteps. Perhaps Hillary is "looking into this". Uh oh...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@intranautt Did you say the same thing when Obama put kids in cages and separated   them from their parents? No, bc… https://t.co/u4Z7QvvFtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Details from #protestnoun #torranceartmuseum through March 9. Ripple Effect  artist talk this Sat 3/2/19, 3:30pm...… https://t.co/PhOhbWeSBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Just Entered @BiGGsGolfTalk #March #Giveaway 2 WIN a @TitosVodka Prize Pack from @USGolfChallenge ENTER! @wcuebas https://t.co/F0bXvTDnrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveDuFourNBA @SixersAdam You know who also shoots from the side of his head https://t.co/caXebx3Qhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[All set up for a great day of learning tomorrow at the VFW in Maple Lake, MN. Room for both 9am and 1pm sessions!… https://t.co/YMuPBi92tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course you know, they can’t take over the government without the illegal vote. This is one of the most obvious a… https://t.co/UnNfhlSflW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now there’s a pair of liars if you ever saw any. Smiles of pure deceit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where we see the longest stretch of @TripleH not being Champion since he stepped into WWE 7 months]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrangeFunnies @BreitbartNews I guess the photos and videos of the crisis are fake. Government troops firing on pr… https://t.co/INc6wv6D67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiveAction Just remember when Nancy Polosi is givin an award THE MARGARET SANGER award just remember Margaret Sang… https://t.co/luPMqg3tRC]]></document></documents></author>