<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m a big fan of Eric Decosta, he learned from the best. This shows early in his GM career he makes non-emotional,… https://t.co/gaTjlPfh0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abc15 Thank you to everyone involved in helping give him the burial he deserves and special thanks to all serving… https://t.co/cuM3XQobYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnszim Glad we have this support for you here! Praying, praying, praying! And a added bonus ... purring cats ...… https://t.co/btGqL6Xszy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never not watch that video of Glenn Close assessing Billy Porter no matter how many times it comes up on my feed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump so you want to take funds from the Military, instead of fixing their horrible housing conditions f… https://t.co/lBMNJluhwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chiudo un altro grande viaggio... 29 su 30 #NBATour https://t.co/c13j0CdKs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a year! To some of you that’s not a lot but know that I am not easy. I am easily annoyed. I am bossy and… https://t.co/Ei4rb5RpC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amorfatietlux I tagged my daughter earlier when I saw this and she responded “heathen children are gross.” 👏🏼👏🏼… https://t.co/WakqgyFCUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbrleigh Thank youuuuu!!! 😭😭😭 it is my first time in disneyland!!!! 😭💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNPOPULAR OPINION: McDonalds sprite throws cheese on your baby while wearing vans that land right side up and it ju… https://t.co/82OkMYULCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol literally told ma dude a joke ab Kurt Cobain high fived him &amp; said thanks and walked out 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonOfManAndGod Why Jesus. You’ve grown your hair out. 😀#TaraAnnMoons https://t.co/gtF8GWvZdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raticorns @PrettyBadLefty @SenSanders Yeah #BERNIEGOHOME @SenSanders what we see in Venezuela is a result of socia… https://t.co/8PePkvOGFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feelin’ blue? Wake up with @SubrinaDhammi @nealestano and me and we’ll help you see the sunshine and blue skies ahe… https://t.co/enEzE20rov]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little taste of spring on this wintry Monday 🌺❄️ #hyacinths #springflowers #wintermeetsspring #february… https://t.co/v2V2oZYGqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SunsetBlvd sidewalk ... #hollywood #sidewalkart #mydayinla @ Pearl's Rooftop https://t.co/1E05bukllJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep at 1am yet I’m still barely waking up rn.. it’s a gift or a curse idk the difference]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Oh,  trust me they are never done!  As long as Trump is blocking them from ripping us off We The People can suffer!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re a farmer when you’re comparing vacuuming your beat down living room rug to cutting a field of hay t… https://t.co/jigG21Cguu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JAbudayeh @illhanOmarpress If you just change God to Allah, its probably Ok with her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Mother  immigrated for me to become educated, and now I’m almost graduationing from college 🙏🏽🎓 and make my moth… https://t.co/fTNfq74RVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ItWorks #Loooooove $200 worth of product for $59 ♥️♥️ https://t.co/PFZIQyEQnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrumpiGramp @parscale @realDonaldTrump I heard 7 to 8 thousand at Beto rally. Keef keef.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aniyaj12 Lmfaooooo I really do hate it here but it is cheaper 😭 that’s the only pro about it but yeah I’ll most likely just transfer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arrianna_Planey I'm finalizing my diss now on Urban renewal and health provision in Detroit and EVERY TIME I have… https://t.co/8OUsGerdFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[i walk around like everything is ok but deep down i need some head. : 📷 robhawthorne @ Beauty by Benson https://t.co/SXwacRu8W5]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Fr. Brennan... he’s died. I’ve  forgiven him. As far as other people suffering from addiction, suffering from the… https://t.co/QC3X0QBqhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHaydnJones @CreationEnt @cw_spn When is Ketch returning??  He's been mentioned in a few episodes this season,… https://t.co/XINOloHZMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cajuncocoa @ryangrim @Ilhan @SteveScalise @AOC @IlhanMN https://t.co/rXXean0Tue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids teaching kids how to create a Kahoot #CREpln https://t.co/GOgX4PMq74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieathena @snapwilson I’m reading Twitter in the hotel bathroom and my daughter thinks I’m losing my mind. In here giggling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathanchait @SarahKSilverman Remember when we had a president with a smart brain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone convicted in the future for any reason,  upon hearing their sentence, should shout out: "what the fuck, Judg… https://t.co/deXUoOa2MX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RKelly arrested for failing to pay child support https://t.co/TEc1chjqLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlavorOfTheWeek Oreo Caramel Churro 😋 Dulce de leche cake with an Oreo bottom, filled with salted caramel, frosted… https://t.co/fzBSJQKtcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spicy-juicy #turkey-feta burger; scrumptious #harissaaioli#lodgecastiron #eattheworld #nywca @ Upper West Side https://t.co/F6n89H88BV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @RealJamesWoods What or who are America's indigenous people??  Why do we pay taxes for those who won'… https://t.co/BppcwkizCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some are beginning to believe they have no voice in government because of Trump's election. When they realize elimi… https://t.co/tPX65u7lmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[OPEN HOUSE ALERT! 11 Crapo Street, Marion, MA SUNDAY, March 10, 11a-1p DO NOT MISS this opportunity to live in the… https://t.co/9T2idPzurd]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're all in tears with @ladygaga as she wins the Oscar for Best Song! https://t.co/qyCricQrQT https://t.co/bNhcku4fj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SockeLinke @LeoRules1 @WheresMyArk_23 @BillNye @AOC Well liberals are hard of hearing facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just 😐. And no, it’s not just poor word choice. It’s indicative that THIS WOMAN does not (at the very least) have… https://t.co/pZPWf1kkL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Jay! Extremely excited for you!! I have no doubt you will GO DO GREAT THINGS for Florida’s students… https://t.co/B11vxe3Zf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dream comes true🏀 I got the sign and took pictures with my favorite @Slimm_4.You are so handsome and cool during… https://t.co/szohe7bdss]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of the impact engagement our students have in Chicago! @UChicagoPGE @ChicagoStudies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryJoPehl The work you and Bridget do for Rifftrax is my favorite thing about Rifftrax. My mom and I were dying l… https://t.co/vDerXhS7Tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pluggedd_ People are not going to sell their houses knowing that their quadrupling in value in the next 15 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well Hello there officer Nolan 😊😉No one could 0lay this role better than Nathan. https://t.co/EGpAu2Ydr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jrprotalker No it isn’t but Happy Birthday anyway. You so are so admired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kaptain_Krispie @mjs03093641 @ZandEDad @ScorpioNan71 @peggyzab @greyeyed87 @maxi_fabulous @pippasykes154… https://t.co/H6gANtZH2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same reason why we wipe front to back is the same reason why ya shouldn’t double dip 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwayzeeMartin Somethin bout them gold diggin baby mamas 😭😂💀 I needed this]]></document><document><![CDATA[I flew in this morning and have seen four innings of baseball... But I already know that I LOVE #SpringTraining.… https://t.co/h8i9heGSYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@S_TIAA Hahaha: from now on I’m judging outfits from the get go, if you can’t match we ain’t no match https://t.co/zO6PJwtK7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 That's entirely possible. He's projecting an energy of desperation in a way that a guilty man who is… https://t.co/3zG5PZbAJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 @ABC Your President knew exactly what was going on the entire time and, hopefully, you will be replaced b… https://t.co/sRETBvyPbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewartMcDonald @mikercarpenter We should have done the same immediately after the 2016 election]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCChicagoMed Dr. Rhodes had better be prepared for the most dangerous surgery ever!😈 I just can't resist this. I'… https://t.co/9R4M6qL9gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisJDWatts @Dyoel182 @TLatshaw @sportingindex It’s a sport, dancesport is a thing and the athleticism of breaker… https://t.co/cXx9roohBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 Glenn Beck is a squirrel. I guess he doesn't know any real men if he thinks trump is a role model.… https://t.co/fNihaJV4DY]]></document><document><![CDATA[time to waste time online shopping &amp; never actually buy what’s in my cart 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[My birthday is in January.   Just sayin'  Happy Birthday @CarrieMuskat😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megynkelly Nope!  My husband just made them in our InstaPot. Turned out perfect!]]></document><document><![CDATA[you should be allowed to hit the people who ride lime scooters in the street instead of the sidewalk. this goes dou… https://t.co/V5h0BaiAEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're absolutely right im going to do the right thing and vote for Donald J Trump again! 2020🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Misophonia so hard, I had to throw my watch across the room. Second hand probs. #Misophonia https://t.co/BZHpYyPPK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This song gets me so hype for when I see my boys in NOLAAAAAA @warriors 💙🥳 https://t.co/kMAD7zPYQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Imagine what these women could have done with Twitter,” says author Rebecca Boggs Roberts speaking on her book and… https://t.co/x1DwM5bWBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: @MHSGirlsBBall1 senior standout Sammie Puisis receives her McDonald's All-American jersey. She is the first… https://t.co/ionCD0PZvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza You’re the biggest hypocrite ever!! Pelosi seek immediate help!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and run 🏃🏼‍♀️ #Happysaturday  #SaturdayMotivation https://t.co/zz7rbUd1Im]]></document><document><![CDATA[@koolkaryn @busbee_deborah @elder_jodi @LadyInHats @simplyemc @Idclair @ladyred1956 @heckyessica @FishFunSun @AOC… https://t.co/iE1YwhrYY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Razzolate Black screen ranters because theyve got no hope, nothing to lose ➡️ alpha]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear some ppl laugh at some shit that has me?? on fb.This post i just saw really got me heated.Esp when i have g… https://t.co/qLDl1TjrQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phil500 get the sea world animals that don’t belong there rehabilitated and returned to the ocean]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serious question, Do you floss your teeth first then brush OR brush then floss???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tam_camilleri Okay it’s literally only happened to me once and I love her and we’re still going strong and I have… https://t.co/yMGfZWirBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLynn_XoXoX This week is the 30’s, 60’s, 40’s, 60’s, 30’s &amp; 70. That’ll probably be completely different tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelindaHoward4 @ChafeXcream @gotailwind @SPIBELT @XOSKINUSA @oofos @topoathletic Gah! I got knocked over by my pup… https://t.co/UYArCbVHaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELP!!!!!!! I don't think I will survive this. @Hiyaboopers @fredsfam @kayb625 @JasonFischer77 https://t.co/YGnIbUaPQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s do this #writenow #gratefulwriter #Scrivener https://t.co/O4rEpQiZti]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a little snap shot of yesterday’s fun competitions to end the quarter! Who will the winner be?? We add it up t… https://t.co/ZHMvcVYRUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update positive to being in the hospital: bomb a cheese toastie at 2:30 am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Year of the Boar to Miss @TiaToony! 🐗 you guys will hog wild for her performance 💛 Coming in April to… https://t.co/BffWeFkfRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kelli_Fields @birthdaysmatter I enjoy being on the frontlines, so many people are forgotten out there or don’t hav… https://t.co/08GOh2aDgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolegelinas The mayor of this city does NOT have the middle class or our small business owners in mind. He has o… https://t.co/UHUO6PSUmj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Athens #GA +954168 #realestate #realtor https://t.co/g8rrbW3lGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which one are you? #kidlit #monsters #swag #peanutandmoe #picturebooks #buttons https://t.co/lfd4liIzi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[We compared the physical characteristics of the Sun, Earth, and Moon then practiced using Earth’s Rotation to find… https://t.co/RR9AaRaAhE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I know why Bradley Cooper’s wife was acting like a fool https://t.co/SqpU0uX2Wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[For good men to stand by and do nothing while evil men spread and grow their agendas and philosophies (brainwashing… https://t.co/LrqHaT0AGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1plantman @RepMaxineWaters Follow you so you can fleece me your a criminal your the emphasis of all that’s wrong w… https://t.co/ktgnSp2Dzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My greatest creation, this tiny human teaches me so much everyday. She opens my eyes to the a whole new world. To s… https://t.co/08J0lWH6PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunsopeningband @DunnSdunn2 @PranaPT @LenMacPT @TheSteph21 @DerekFreshman @BrandonPoen @HETpodcast @acapt2… https://t.co/u7LMhTqXwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I have an unhealthy habit of continuing to be friends with this girl on Facebook that I knew six years ago,… https://t.co/G3MgDPfrRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many Mantle cell patients out in the community will benefit from social media for all our clinical trials offere… https://t.co/kY1wjS3Btt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bestfriend: “_________ was the biggest thotiana you EVER messed with you. I’m so glad you’re done with his ass” Me: https://t.co/ngjOa80WMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi , Pelosi needs to be removed she is unable to do the job. She is a disgrace to our Country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Finn_American @__CassidyRae__ @DogsBCool @NikkythaBee @bromsisa @MAGANuggets @establishmentno @leslie2sing4u… https://t.co/Tc2X4Zfxhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0hbebe @GusSmyrnios @ChallengeMTV FYI CT brought all@the drama in the begging and middle of this journey called th… https://t.co/gbiwEC340m]]></document></documents></author>