<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JJWatt @DerekWatt34 @gabriella_watt2 @_TJWatt Uncle TJ, very Cool Name. Get used to it 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't think the commentators on this first hour of @UPonMSNBC grasp how dangerous Trump's CPAC rant was, not only… https://t.co/mJOswpWjOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of the reason I play Civ6 is to enact “alternate history porn.” For example, here’s a Dido domination victory… https://t.co/gQhISzqKq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our paper on the role of #relationalvalues in shark conservation, science, and management is out today! #openaccess… https://t.co/xsFXcYOqPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because sometimes you just need to keep it light... @myccasa @Public_Market https://t.co/2IkPY8IZxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FerrellCarson With no Mariners I can’t see the Indians in person so no. 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who's the best supporting actress? I voted Regina King on KABC OTRC. What's your vote? https://t.co/setFeAkd4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pearlandpetal The only consolation is it’s my alma mater. I wish they had had hockey when I was there. Not that I… https://t.co/BMUlnZjeY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who supported animals today by purchasing sweet treats! 🧡🐷🐰⚖️@HerseyHuskies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Wolfhound Double IPA by @CaptainNeon at @captainneon — https://t.co/CSezslZrd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[in this day + age, the world is set on fire 🔥 by alpha fe(males). @irisj_styles  Happy #InternationalWomensDay to a… https://t.co/eagVpImuLm]]></document><document><![CDATA[“i’m here to make ur life better, plus ur cute so i don’t mind” BET BRO BET #prettyprivlege]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder Woman a stick in da mud. Her personality trash &amp; she was a hoe. Had Batman &amp; Superman up her ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azzamac17 @AuthorLMurphy You know that mansion we all get when we go to Heaven....well, yours is on a back street… https://t.co/YVWap54BS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to know how to upload a video to Paul Mooney or Eddie Griffin I am a 56-year-old African-American and… https://t.co/n1x6voWUSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidhogg111 @marcorubio Oh Marco, are these your thoughts and prayers for the children killed in our schools? Do… https://t.co/eQggxdS401]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JashSayani @JesseDraper There are a lot of unique challenges to working with government. Gov Tech companies need a… https://t.co/cVVJnwf3Y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@l_tucc He shouldn’t be. The longer we wait and the closer it gets to the election the more Dems will be blamed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Helflower I'm glad he has to pay court fees after losing yet another idiotic lawsuit.  Someone should send him ins… https://t.co/dvKjmuaeFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of y’all a parents didn’t teach you to flush public toilets with your foot &amp; it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those starting their weekend early, stop by Hope’s peanut booth this sunny Friday morning! Hot boiled peanuts a… https://t.co/lfvu4CtHoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drfraud19 @DianeMariePosts I think you have mistaken my level of intelligence for yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why everyone hates on raisins. They’re good &amp; an important ingredient in trail mix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiding in Plain Sight: PAC-Connected Activists Set Up ‘Local News’ Outlets https://t.co/DM9udavWj5 # via @snopes]]></document><document><![CDATA[...I start with email because that is how you find my website. That is where you can purchase any service or produc… https://t.co/Y7RhTV40A1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @JohnAsplund1 : post an album cover a day for ten days that would make up the soun… https://t.co/TDLdwrvCaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does it mean that the US has hit its debt ceiling?  https://t.co/cTT18KuBsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rnelson0 @GOP @GovHolcomb @INDOT And won't release the funds that ARE there so our Mayor's can use them to fix the infrastructure?? #]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardinalDolan. I am humbly asking for your assistance to help keep Mary Queen of Heaven Catholic Academy in Brookl… https://t.co/YHHkrUteXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A strong country has an intelligent, knowledgeable leader. You sir are not. Boarders are secure wh… https://t.co/tdcQ1RsDO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanineMaverick @jasonagastrich @ChevJustChev @Beedge @keithboykin Yes most likely..... I muted him, he's not one t… https://t.co/8uJnbe25ek]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just walked into a class and sat down and realized it wasn’t my class...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another #fat fucking #WhiteSupremacy male who’s just hating and probably mad he can’t see his own dick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh I'm sorry but is this supposed to be funny? Cos it really is not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dermatologists are a hoax and estheticians are highly underrated! Estheticians get you're skin right naturally, whi… https://t.co/xpGZhkRIwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity In the meantime over in Saudi Arabia,  the Saudis continue to torture American detainees.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Let's talk about the reason for the Genocide in the Middle East. https://t.co/ZuNdb9vrB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3atAkUvTxR  https://t.co/RmvQ9LZYdB  https://t.co/dMW9hZ1Uca  https://t.co/x2PnMO8pqy https://t.co/RjKWPEP9A1]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s already on daily nose drops for the rest of her life (which is really fucking expensive btw) but it looks lik… https://t.co/FwEoODy5Bn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voy captando que en la escuela que trabajo todos, TODOOOOS te saludan y te desean buen día 💕 espero y sean así también amikos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreaNRuth @JayCaruso You DEFINITELY need two. I seriously want to get some but my husband thinks they’re the sam… https://t.co/hzCXeIA2qS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanObeidallah 🤣🤣🤣 Good that’s what she deserves. I have no pity for these folks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best pizza in Birmingham -  @SliceBirmingham   Love your new location in Vestavia!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Schneider THAT'S so true Mr..@John_Schneider I sometimes get overwhelmed with just signing my recording contr… https://t.co/ET0lUxCTQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually out and about during the daytime on a weekend and now i don’t know what to do with myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Cardi said “your pussy basura, my pussy horchata” I felt that. 🔥 #pleaseme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breezing through my 50th Birthday Party To-Do List like a champ! #Tots #50LetsGoCrazy #PurpleParty #80sGirl… https://t.co/AfKbiy7ibG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días..., SI, en mty es un día lluvioso y de mucho tráfico pero no olvidemos ser agradecidos y que si nos emp… https://t.co/EXfM5olJ3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who can do this color exactly? Dark roots and all! 🤔 tag your suggestions preferably not too far from my hometown b… https://t.co/tbO28OH1A5]]></document><document><![CDATA[10th Annual Ohio Human Trafficking Awareness Day-Ohio had gone from being a State without any protections for victi… https://t.co/NzTsUj90bY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we go back to last night!?? @lukecombs was amazing last night!!! #RodeoHouston]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexander keeps looking for the best Fat Tuesday's pawty! I think he found it @keithezeiler  He met some really nic… https://t.co/kznvIclwRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I said on @Playlikeajet1 podcast—Humphries would be a big target if I was Jets. Young—big upside and would compl… https://t.co/UhQQkFTk9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see @Lifeline519 set up in @WhiteOaksMall. A reminder to make plans to donate wherever you are. It’s one o… https://t.co/U7DM89s7yz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Com’mon Kentucky!  Let’s get this guy voted out in 2020!! @AmyMcGrathKY @DNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This BLACK HISTORY MONTH has been a wild ride hasn’t it? @ Brooklyn Bridge https://t.co/WsPrb65swx]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve moved back to our normal section surrounded by all of our friends and all is well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just in: Saturday’s are for the moms #🦞szn @ Houston Heights, Texas https://t.co/vggCpbyaji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorrtaborr “Colton is a total douche nozzle...It’s not good for my soul.” -Mom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@URBANWONKENOBI @BuzzFeedNews How awful &amp; embarrassing. I continue to hope that our allies aren't paying attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This very important work on streamlining adverse event reporting will improve the process of drug development proce… https://t.co/g32eukUyow]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want right now is a truck load of canes and tons of tattoos. Is that too much to ask for????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lynette Watkins crossed 1 Mile to GO!. Time 02:17:08, pace 11:23 min/mile, est. finish 9:51 am https://t.co/BcPKErwf9u #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to land a job like "Material Associate Atrium Health Cleveland" at Atrium Health? Applicant tracking systems l… https://t.co/2meyYd9Xcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[What better place than Atlanta, Georgia for @jacobcollier ‘s rendition of “You’ve Got a Friend” and for laying it o… https://t.co/4qGIakxXv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickyDavila Ill bet he was staying at trumps Den of Thieves,Liars and Sexual Predators otherwise known as Maral… https://t.co/I9pVjKNjf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t I ever go to sleep at a decent time? It’s not like I need 8 hours of sleep a night or anything...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@____Biaanca @Banana_James13 We bought another tv cause he really wanted it and shoes he can wait just a little longer 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw I really think it's unnecessary to consider DOJ rules as the rule of law. I don't know who/what they affe… https://t.co/KxvAwwlV9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/nvNn4GqT3J  Our Amazon Phone Number is 1-855-431-5111  #amazonphonenumber]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you hate when you’re sick with the sniffles and when you’re better your nose is all peeling from the irritati… https://t.co/vNjFQY3YbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[So i just pressed that little square button at the top of a YouTube video and the video began playing on my TV and… https://t.co/mZaKDvNFRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[all i’m gonna say today is.... people who make tiktok videos have a lot of time on their hands to do so]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite gifs I've made of a couple. No matter where you are, I hope you're surrounding yourself with lov… https://t.co/r6CqfNKQ37]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing night in The Cassell!! Hokies win (again) over Duke at home! 🏀🎉👏🏻 @ Cassell Coliseum https://t.co/mIDG8IH1sa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deport Maria Gabriela Chavez, and send her back to Venezuela. https://t.co/5aLJOPSefC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo the line to get through security is so long I’ll just miss my flight. It’s a sign to stay in Austin]]></document><document><![CDATA[have not been able to stop watching the umbrella academy since starting it today ☂️🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone doesn’t do something how I originally and consistently do it, it makes my skin crawl and I want to scream.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hangin’ with my girls on the helipad! @JPS_Health @FortWorthEM @feminemtweets #StrongWomen @bharti711… https://t.co/SHKPsKMD3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have standards today, so all you fuckbois better watch out! Or at least wait until tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[The highlight of my Tuesday is automatically going to be @MichelleWESH 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth.  Categories limit.  We all are on the same ship &amp; it could sink...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The HORROR, I cleaned &amp; washed my car without checking the forecast &amp; it’s going to rain this week 😭😭!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me watching all my friends leave for warm fun places over spring break. https://t.co/mPOTsoCyif]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched instant family tonight. Expected to be silly. But actually was really good! And definitely moving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lupeintransit I get a different kind basically every time I go to the store 😂 but I’m happy with any flavor of Che… https://t.co/emyQHYGf43]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys always want to help was my hair. That’s a form of intimacy that we DON’T have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinnPatriot @willithesaint @randalthom Omg. How horrible. So sorry for his loss😢🙏🏻💔 Hope the  person gets caught for this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if someone gave me a dollar every time I have heard a hydro and an iclicker fall in class, I’d probably be able to pay off my school debt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJenniferMac hi Jen. I just watched the recent video on Juan. I get all the other voices being John but I hear n… https://t.co/B3Hvbp5Xaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best PD ever! Encouraging us to get on our phones🤣 learned so much today. Thank you @gcouros #CCSDLI19]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going to  miss you LA. . #LosAngeles #thelastbookstore #la https://t.co/3XKqEmWhUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sun beginning to rise here at the press site at KSC. Yes, we’re still here. https://t.co/rKoaSIcbKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love  it but I know many of those Chinese girls!  Too funny! This has to be Nancy Pelosi's name too! Wins 1st place… https://t.co/DBAi5AQzsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love little off the beaten path bakeries. Look at how good everything looks 😍 https://t.co/k9b7vv6Xsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok i see why landfills/trash dumps are not easily seen by the public but it makes it so easy to completely ignore t… https://t.co/nHFtTgoHsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your favorite Business Fraternity returns with another professional headshot opportunity 📸. Come join Kappa Chi Cha… https://t.co/wVv95KsYfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get physically ill when @cloakzy doesn’t remove the exclamation points in his locker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cabinet48 I’d just like to note that you’re really easy to talk to and I always love running into you ❤️]]></document></documents></author>