<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@andylassner @realmpolowin POTUS Probably ordered a Spanish omelette but hold the Spanish at omelette bar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bethel AME Church "Spelling Bee Participants" @ Jacksonville, Florida https://t.co/bmQ6rOF3s8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m blown away every time I get to be a part of a Pelotonia event...such incredible community and so much passion.… https://t.co/lqtMnZ1rki]]></document><document><![CDATA[No te preocupes por la UE. Son unos ricos venidos a menos sin ningún peso internacional ni capacidad de lucha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will buy Harper jersey if this happens... #notadodgersfan #youcanquoteme]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here come the Padres. Cade Rees three from the top of the arc and it’s 42-30.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how many adventures @nikki_manly and I go on after 12am, and Trevor just sleeps through it all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSSacramento Wow!!! What a pair of “cuties.” Love those tattoo’d eyebrows... Hey, give these lovebirds a break! T… https://t.co/E3vxwaKcfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Pictures Of The Day – 73 Pics #mirth #lol #smirk #funny https://t.co/dnFqreJqyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeTFinance @secupp They have no shred of shame. CNN is has even less if that’s possible! But hey you wrote someth… https://t.co/EMz6YTwFOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[An obscure BOA #767 from Bolivia @iflymia, a successor to LAB. https://t.co/MII2o61sPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mientras no le den más poder a la autoridad, estas cosas seguirán pasando.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3GsoCougarTown @F3Greensboro @F3See_Thru So it’s just YHC. Heading out on the ruck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chicago O'Hare International Airport in Chicago, IL https://t.co/VeHpVfHt30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump False that's only of the Republican party 52% overall 32% approval I call bullshit !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone thing Trump will be as upset with this  as he was with a Muslim-American Rep? https://t.co/Dgto4IdOJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToraChan23 @EdLatimore Depend on what you mean by “forgive”.  Ie.  You don’t have to let someone back in your life… https://t.co/iBn5X4U248]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchyGallo 2ns in points when you get all that is time and on first line, makes it easy.. but it's if you think i… https://t.co/buU5hBZR9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Traders #Investors hear financial market commentary from a 45-year #Trading pro &amp; analyst. #Bullmarket -… https://t.co/4Suc7FztQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan 19 retro's Air 27C's. #footlockerkicks #becausesneakers @ West Palm Beach, Florida https://t.co/cGSLiK8RdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adammccracken You know what man I thought you had replied to my tweet about leagues not taking trout #1. That thre… https://t.co/dAZkzMDwIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinHart4real amazing what you did for the little man with amazing artwork]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is absurd. If they fight this, I will be canceling my @Spotify subscription and getting @AppleMusic. #Spotify… https://t.co/EcCFQa4zlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post 4 films among your favorite films   Eternal Sunshine of the spotless mind  Pulp Fiction  A league of their own… https://t.co/WnQLE87GFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TopOfTheLine__ Lol dude gone get got sooner or later. Snitches never make it out unless he leaving the U.S]]></document><document><![CDATA[And a reasonable @realDonaldTrump quote: “I encourage Americans across our country to take advantage of resources t… https://t.co/XdDeC9ZNvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[When faced with the reality her best friend has gone missing, Noma must exercise every skill the swamp has taught h… https://t.co/uFYwXDJYcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heldyourpride Need to start seeing more around here too so that’d be perfect! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eunicorn_77 @tinacurcio_ Yeah it sounds like a great idea until so many of our great memories we’re building are r… https://t.co/QxbamRWgIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nigga got KO last yr by Ronaldo on late pk goal &amp; same just happened wit Rashford]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quote of the century! @ Cambellton Road Sw (9623) https://t.co/kdU1BGalu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christian Psychic and Catholic Parapsychologist, Angel Guadiania… https://t.co/cvoK2dFKMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Birmingham #creativewriting #Alabama #literary #writerslife #WritingLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz You seem strangely familiar with criminal behavior. https://t.co/x10SBhor7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden @UDBidenSchool @jmeacham What examples of his vices are they talking about specifically, Joe. Name them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting on a tuxedo shirt gives me the #superpower of always being able to order the messiest thing on the menu.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SONADORLIVESON @danny_buder @Black_is_back5 @cancunbound2022 @cowboys20041 @My57ChevyBelAir @Mharris888H… https://t.co/NbyvaaUxQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valgreen660 Thanks Val! Would be awesome if you could 🤩 Hoping for some friendly faces!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza WHY AM I SUDDENLY SEEING SO MUCH OF THIS TRASH ON MY FEED?]]></document><document><![CDATA[JD, so very sorry for your loss. My prayers are with you and your family in this trying season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_neto We should be speaking to end-users and performing a needs analysis before recommending any tech.  Too o… https://t.co/b3JLCbZGQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rossbossk @flystl While Chicago is in desperate need of a new terminal layout and modernization, (no matter the co… https://t.co/UT0bvxREOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life takes me away from Twitter. Probably for the best. I figured I would start another thread. @ErikOnSax,… https://t.co/2XMnrM4bMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpTicHitch @OpTic_Scumper Hey Scumo what’s your favorite movie with dogs??? Bee Toe Vin... https://t.co/W8L0kBo84q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess it’s only fitting that now Nats fans can hate Harper as much as the rest of the country already does]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet Oh hell yeah! Mine has changed dramatically since I am an immigrant here on papers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If #DeathRaceForLove came out when I was in high school I would have listened to it on repeat like a million times.… https://t.co/Lqgxx58Uta]]></document><document><![CDATA[What people who finance human trafficking "deserve" is way worse than a misdemeanor arrest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the national debt will cost us $7 trillion in interest over the next 10 years, according to @pgpfoundation… https://t.co/3ayfAdH68s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4Squeakerpaws What the actual fuck? Usually you have to be dragged kicking and screaming into the world of the liv… https://t.co/vsfLA4sRxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that, softball season is underway! #GoBigGreen #EvenStrongerTogether @ Choctawhatchee High School https://t.co/yiW3AgyA2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Perkolates @NothnButAGThang @CoreyMoOfAlief @Jay_Edward It’s getting Spicy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the day when your church seems to be falling to pieces #GC2019 go out in the kitchen and bake banana bread for t… https://t.co/IgsmxRgsxT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CantankerousCMF I know I sent him a happy birthday earlier.  20 years old was 30 lbs ago for me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost Bad move I feel field too crowded already. Bernie Sanders good man. Would make fine President. But times ha… https://t.co/6xV18SmyEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[So animalistic behavior of this so call democrats congress racial behavior. My dog behave better than her.💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tangela83955834 Wow tyler is really coming out of his shell just thank Angla getting that every night sorry just saying lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredNBCLA This is all BS. Last seasons records have exactly zero relevance to this season. Who really knows what w… https://t.co/tOJjqtU1WH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamnickrogers Put the giant teleprompter in the back of the hall so I could read along, and we're getting close. A… https://t.co/fGythPfIfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever nabiscosnacks came up with this your #thedevil and #evil   THESE MAKE YOU WANT TO SIN EVERY MINUTE OF THE D… https://t.co/Nt000V8LWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#onthemoney with @BeckyQuick  deserves a larger platform.  Highlight of my weekends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcuslemonis Next episode in Lexington and you didn’t call or stop by? 😊   #MissedTennisLesson #NextTime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Keir_Starmer What is more gaulling is why is this money being made now? Austerity has hit people hard so this move… https://t.co/1DzgLJQKAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Purdue once again will enjoy a double bye in #B1G tourney, clinching it since Wisconsin lost at IU Wednesday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @MichaelCohen212 @RepAdamSchiff Just sick! Power grab any way they can get it. Also allowing illegal voting to be ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fawfulfan I’ve always been told that when people are struggling the best course of action is to pile on not provid… https://t.co/rVvbWY6r91]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKZhou I actually saw it on an Instagram birthday card the other day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[(L-R) Sean Timothy Brown, Bianca Stoker, David Youse and Alexana Thomas in Dezart Performs’ production of “White Gu… https://t.co/UbmJ9qV9ej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, I did. None of them were stupid enough to try and flip a car over with their bare hands. So we didn't have to… https://t.co/SQLJlxsMdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now @CollinSexton02 has joined the @Goodyear party 😄 He’s signing 📝 and taking 📸 for @CavsWGNation!… https://t.co/EyQVLXimXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think the Björk lyric tht speaks 2 me the most is prolly that one near the end of Bachelorette where she says  “a… https://t.co/LUkqEb0qmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smileyt22 @StableGeniusRN @nypost You know nothing about me. I’m no Bernie guy. I don’t think he should even be in… https://t.co/2E6VAkx3GD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasmineLouvenia Here you goooooo😭 lol ... I doubt all of that https://t.co/uzQQlTTAAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[look mom, I made these!! ✨ huge thanks to my friend billyritter77 for hosting private classes, so fun to try someth… https://t.co/0VRhzSnAkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning - All Rye City Schools will open on time for Friday, March 1.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is another of your BS statements! Stop lying now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wolfpackamk @mo_kaba3 That and a nickel will get you a nice warm cup of ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler Hope everyone else has noticed that almost every item in the stores have gone up? Great tax scheme wasn't it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019, day 70  3+ pages, so I’ll hit page 90 tomorrow. Final stretch to the end of this draft. Will cross the finish… https://t.co/vu27pQSIqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like listening to some addled man in a rest home, fixated and obsessed with one thing that’s trivial and weird… https://t.co/qfbLF9ih7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiTownSports @jetpenguin @lv_teacher @EmptySeatsPics @MLB_PLAYERS Would any fan be ok with whatever company hired… https://t.co/yhiP2DcJND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosG52413131 @migrantsaid a few reason the U.S. is exaggariting  the crime and the American made Ms13 gangs in… https://t.co/OdaLOSMfg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LikeA_G_ Bro you give Hawkeye like at least 7 arrows she has no chance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh this is fucking crazy @Apple your next don’t make me move back to a galaxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little update of what happen yesterday with my Ex she did text I did not answer her back and she has been messaging me all morning ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VenZenix Zactly.  Which i truly wish was a word.  Even kind of looks bad ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flagstafffilms i spy ernesto natali @baseballhall @RedsMuseum @cammillerfilms #redlegnation https://t.co/gXZz13YNeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the discussion @susanranliu - big shifts ahead. @WhiteBdAdvisor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSun The time to decide whether you want to have a child is before they are conceived, once they are born, they… https://t.co/FOO0B1YOvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwbh @teddygoff @nycsouthpaw @AOC They want to make her the next Hillary Clinton]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinnyRebyak @marklevinshow Wow, there is almost nothing in that entire statement that is even close to the truth]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Tangled Restrooms are the best loos you'd ever find in Magic Kingdom. Still wished Disney would make an entire… https://t.co/fFiCRgr66t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RearAdBsBlog @BizNasty2point0 how many times have you seen a team have 2 own goals in a hockey game?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MercadGabriel Puro coto. LOL. Me imagino. Ya me fijo Chava cómo te pusiste jaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finishing things off after an intense final, emseefour is your hyperxesalv #SuperMarioParty champion once again. Co… https://t.co/xaWzGNMlqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronrachelmom @MorganOrtagus I’ve always thought the same thing. Way to much MAKEUP. None of the other ladies on… https://t.co/M72LYO1bkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just added my name to @pogoblog’s petition to demand that Congress vote to stop President Trump’s end run around… https://t.co/fhItOJxJrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Filipenses  4:6-7  6 Por nada estéis afanosos, sino sean conocidas vuestras peticiones delante de Dios en toda orac… https://t.co/YSQDCGCOKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpbcOnline Yeah, I agree.  He could have done it already.  So he obviously has a good reason for why he hasn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The countdown has begun: 0️⃣6️⃣ Days      #Nephmadness 2️⃣🏀1️⃣9️⃣ 👉🏼 Save the date 🗓 March 15 https://t.co/dZWjlG7jLj]]></document></documents></author>