<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@HardballChris Opinion shows like yours are not news, not journalism, they're show biz. Famous pat liberal pundits… https://t.co/Ky100PBNtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chilling at Dusk til around 10pm tonight (2/21), I'm going out of town for the weekend, come support my trip and sp… https://t.co/z0dL37pX4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because YOUR Happy Days DESERVE a BEAUTIFUL, FRESHLY BAKED and GORGEOUS Dessert!!!  Our Custom Desserts feature the… https://t.co/0uDqRs9ofn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @mre6th and I, along w/ others, for Session 2: Tech Playground on March 18th! Hands On Time with some engaging… https://t.co/KQiZV8N9HC]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I got switched to soprano for the musical and I have never sang soprano in my entire life 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch at our intimate bar with a craft cocktail or wine &amp; Meze. #OscarsRedCarpet #Oscar #winelover #cocktails… https://t.co/HB5HubHIsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandmhateglee listening to this week's episode of the podcast. I remember why this episode has more viewers than t… https://t.co/WnB3nwLrz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So cute! Loved seeing @MirandaSings @ColleenB123 in @wreckitralph 💄 https://t.co/oVJX9QBo37]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book Review: Hitting the Books by Jenn McKinlay https://t.co/4GPhHuBIhA via @jamescudney4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t get invited to the party, ehhh? Maryam has a PSA. She said please wax your eyebrows. It’ll change my life...… https://t.co/XVyt67hsRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FajrAbdelnasser جبتي من الاخر والله.. الناس بتفتكر ان احنا عايشين في جنه ميعرفوش اللي فيها]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a white Latina I grew up in a culture where colorism was part of my psyche, I’ve had to learn its dangers!   “Qu… https://t.co/aBSCxQxz9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you had told me, as a cub reporter for the OC Ranger back in 1989...that I would be the chair of the Kitsap Coun… https://t.co/lJaiLQ9q80]]></document><document><![CDATA[House passes public lands bill seen as a win for conservation (Via @JuliannaRennie) https://t.co/zff2QXkR5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[💓💓💓 #poetry #poetrycommunity #valentine #poet #yogiyesi #love #lovepoems #instapoetry #igpoetry #blogger #wordpress… https://t.co/WXZkoto6MI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charging station availability? Beta testing for App? @Tesla @elonmusk @ANYONE WHO WORKS WITH/FOR TESLA. Check out… https://t.co/VgtOHG6por]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 Worst Feelings:  Cheated on.  Over thinking.  Being lied to.  Heart broken.  Not cared for.  Losing.  Scared.  A… https://t.co/8dvr7W4Q5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I AM GOING TO PRINT THIS OUT AND MAKE SURE I DO THIS EVERY TIME ... @shawnmcintosh’s “initial data checks” list… https://t.co/KO6XTWaVLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Danced w @MaeDosela &amp; @Tessence01 at Fat Tuesdays!  Been a mad min since we hung out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnpklake Things I’ve Learned  •Cats are indeed assholes  •Immediately after “saving it’s life” it still ran into… https://t.co/bSQZQ4Ipda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to my kitten, who has been loving and full of purrs and snuggles during this week long sickness ordeal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m lucky-always had buyin w/admin @NISDSteubing. They let me do my thing,even when I don’t know what I’m doing! Th… https://t.co/J64THLc3gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope they have better luck than us declaring homelessness as a state of emergency. Our mayor and his gang of elit… https://t.co/DdBCooGPXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#leaf #leaves #shadow #light #shadowplay #snow #snowy #snowfall #wintery #winter #winterinontario #winterincanada… https://t.co/sgm3Bqsm6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KreepyKimSofia @AOC Maybe if Hillary wasn’t a low life corrupt, immoral politician and person who is not in jail t… https://t.co/GtWDaNvezY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman @missmayim This is truly sad.  Yet it’s ok with you that we also killed 42 million babies last yea… https://t.co/FhHZKBOT50]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Lol!!!!!! Soooo funny!!!! How about his suspensions and behavior report!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoppinmama5 @bedevilme666 @SealeyGerald @Libphobic @gator4kb18 @trumpAngel45 @NahBabyNah @KevinMFerrara @ShellyCov… https://t.co/lxOcIOuljU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi tonight has truly been the best night of my life and I am so incredibly happy. I feel like I’m in the clouds 💕 https://t.co/pgTd9SJKdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[High profile #SF public defender @JeffAdachi  remembered for working tirelessly for the underprivileged. #SFMayor… https://t.co/V85FZQYKtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was a bank teller, I ran across the hyphenated last name Lynch-Blackman on a check.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @OversightDems @HouseIntel So you are taking a liar under your arm.. oops, my bad, I forgot.. you al… https://t.co/ELBmLJwNGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiw many illegal campaign donations did these Chinese execs give to her for Trump?]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Gainesville, FL #SupplyChain job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: Unload Associate at Lowe's]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does it say it’s 5:51 am on the screen 😩😩😩 and they keep saying it’s 5:51 @fox5dc #FOX5MORNING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizzhartman HE REALLY SAID THAT HIS BATTERY IS LOW AND IT’S GETTING DARK 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[people who talk non-stop at gigs are rude. Disrespectful to the artist, disrespectful to the rest of the audience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhondaj123 @MSNBC @MaddowBlog I bet he thinks his hands are gargantuan!]]></document><document><![CDATA[citing officials familiar with intelligence reports.   The countries were the United Arab Emirates, China, Israel a… https://t.co/VEmFgKwBsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvaShadowgirl18 Thank you!! You too!! Enjoy your busy day; I'm finally ready to head out for my walk. Slight delay… https://t.co/65wtNO28RW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscar movie block day 2. @kristi_milbourn out for a work trip so it’s just me. Really missing nsibirwa_24 today who… https://t.co/lwr7rgG5wN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Enough. 🔮 By Bobby Jones #2015 #artmodel #artisticshoot #artisticnude #bobbyjones #constanceplumley #zaftig… https://t.co/biNuhSAQwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes yes, that was very clear...some Repubs were just so into their rage they never bothered to listen...he… https://t.co/9HNPRWkUPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#stop #crying #sad #hard #here #tell #hear #scary #help #listening #need #want #stay #feel https://t.co/RW5U2zdbtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJacieMaslyk @ISTEMLN @Rdene915 @JaimeDonally @nankr1120 @dailystem @ReneeWellsSTEAM @STEMigo @JustinAglio… https://t.co/jsOEpuVLB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@softpxrn Weeks?😐 that's nothing omg and I really can't stand you or your gif choices 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The people here are so kind, nice and helpfull wow. Dutch people can definitively learn from this. Got so many comp… https://t.co/JR7jAnP2m5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@illogicalnick @rachelbret13 Once in composition seminar, a female colleague of mine was showcasing a piece she had… https://t.co/nl5V52tuhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAN it feels good to be doing better than the people who did you wrong 😋💕✨🌈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched @Dianodrama's video about American vs. Irish words. All thats going through my head now is the Funky S… https://t.co/kUHkka9mQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope all of my @rushtheband friends in Canada are enjoying @MythBusters Jr on @DiscoveryCanada!!! GO!!… https://t.co/KmSsXiYNxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allisonmpreiss There's nothing slick about it. It's a man explaining how, over time, his experiences, education, f… https://t.co/MOoawdzXcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few more folks should be ticketed as well. It is sheer laziness to not clear your vehicle prior to driving on the… https://t.co/Sjfi7WhQ46]]></document><document><![CDATA[PERHAPS A CLASS ACTION LAWSUIT-FLINT RESIDENTS VS CITY OF FLINT, MI. CITY HAD PLENTY OF TIME to rectify this proble… https://t.co/UMug3yJqw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews The democrats have been using a lot of understanding for racism lately. Ilhan is from a different pl… https://t.co/4oc7gQR2ou]]></document><document><![CDATA[What better movie to watch on International Women’s Day #CaptainMarvel —a movie about literal QUEENS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just want to wear your “Cece Mana Dress” ... it’s warm out right? 🤦🏻‍♀️😂 #outfitoftheday #ootd… https://t.co/MoHv0H82i1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lightbulb #picsart picsart #lamp #lampshade @ Cypress, California https://t.co/PDxWciwoFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katebilo can you say last snow of the season??????  💕💕💕💕💕.  PLEASE https://t.co/v5hMG6rYFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on my face🌹 #botox #lashes #brows #facials ~~ message me your business, body is next 🌹❤️ @ Dallas, Texas https://t.co/r2OtW6CoLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever wishing that coffee would actually wake me up and give me energy 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday nights are for AGR and my girls💕 #latepost https://t.co/na5fKGmp0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you consider whistleblowers ”yarnspinners” no one should listen to anything you have to say!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMGoph @CapitolRomance if the diamond was brought back, I feel like we could work with that ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Dude your age is showing🤣😝Joking . Ask me how I know...]]></document><document><![CDATA[mmm. looks like a good text to pair with Jared Sexton’s Amalgamation Schemes. things to keep in mind as I’m revisin… https://t.co/b6aerZ3Anz]]></document><document><![CDATA[my research lab group members trying to figure out what to say/do/participate when I decide not to do all of the wo… https://t.co/eLiqi6hf2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoriLoughlin @hallmarkchannel Joined the #Hearties movement tonight.  @hallmarkchannel]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the Dream we all grew up on. Living in peace and enjoying and learning about our differences and similariti… https://t.co/SYStJEhVES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patricia_Traina What are some source sites? Lol and thank you for the advice! 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if I get Thomas a puppy for his birthday and then just take it for myself? He can’t get rid of it right? Like… https://t.co/twozRRj5dI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex8Calvert @RuthieConnell @mishacollins @Alex8Calvert You were fantastic in tonites episode. Lately when SPN end… https://t.co/a40o4OKw0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starrizborn @HeadCountOrg @swingleft @IndivisibleTeam @realDonaldTrump And all of her friends...they can pre-regis… https://t.co/jp0DpwONwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astudyinsnoggy @vanetti @shcrlockhouse I did enjoy Texas when I visited years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vauxtheox I would like to make a formal petition to make George the Bird canon now because that is wonderful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to teach class in the city... I looked up.  In a state of overwhelm with the challenges life throws one’s… https://t.co/SRRG4PvphB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing the love ❤️ Buying or selling your home ☎️  Jo 647 518 1984 https://t.co/T62A9zs8ML ☎️ #luxuryhomes… https://t.co/VxggsZIBQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the 7 Day Book Cover Challenge from @julieresua23 to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations o… https://t.co/faZlmr3FjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@312Gina @RightHookUSA @JussieSmollett 1/2 Jewish? Omar will have something to say!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Cardiac Cath Technologist - https://t.co/D0AUQ6q7eJ #Healthcare #Rogers, AR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally how this is going in my house with Him https://t.co/wdAzFgBSo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a newscast I heard that's not congress's Authority their Authority is to write law not go after people. Especial… https://t.co/NKkQFdOKc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allisonbravo99 Sorry I purposely hit you in head today thister.. forgot you had two concussions won’t happen again :*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be nominated for an International Dance Music Award in the best female artist (Hardstyle) category!   👇🏻… https://t.co/IKtSFQpVza]]></document><document><![CDATA[✮ ✮ ✮ FLASHBACK FRIDAY!! ✮ ✮ ✮  The things we go through in our youth can either leave you broken or toughen you up… https://t.co/fUsvml1fhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MDeskaTTU @RoundRockTim @KingBobbyWdlnds @dkdeberry His 162-game average is 37 bombs, 29 steals, 121 runs and 105… https://t.co/1WCDZsjV7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Agree... We need a huge turnout!!  That includes the old white folks, like me ( My candidate is HARRI… https://t.co/hjoAZEDsIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the funniest Buzzfeed of all time....quotes from bartenders....this is sooooooo accurate #mirth #lol #grin… https://t.co/5ZSU2ImCHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleasant reminder curtesy of Jimmy Johns.  Stuff is not why you should get out of bed tomorrow. @ Seattle, Washingt… https://t.co/VXRztKChti]]></document><document><![CDATA[crazy to think 2 years ago i was dating someone who genuinely scared me and that’s the only reason i never left.… https://t.co/oR8aU9MZrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t see Captain Marvel till Sunday, so these are the steps that had to be taken. https://t.co/5ao9gWG16N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suzanne Anarde talks about the importance of cross pollinating efforts and the power of leveraging funding for cata… https://t.co/mYstVXL4uF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently running 87 heading to Inola for a team roping on this fine Saturday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 I have one who went into the Navy 21 years ago and is now stationed in Spain. My daughter who is 21 m… https://t.co/wX5jfeec31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AprilDRyan @PhilipRucker @matthewamiller @HeidiNBC @emilyjanefox @Dr_CMGreer @MichelleBernard @DrJasonJohnson… https://t.co/Yj6hIcJt33]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me channeling my inner @coachjfranklin while everyone else houses a cupcake ☝🏽 https://t.co/kpna0K4DR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrimeCreator2 @theColor13 @tee10202 @AboveTheBurgh @HeARTofGod99 @2newearth777 @davidsodell @WILLOWOOD2… https://t.co/H6X1OCD5Hc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RURiotSquad Yes indeed the students rocked the RAC @RutgersMBB https://t.co/TQANXCxtdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RikRankin I can give you great Nashville recommendations, if you’re interested. It’s one of my favorite American cities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People really out here questioning me when they should really be questioning themselves...]]></document></documents></author>