<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'm nervously buying outdoor patio storage containers so my landlords dont get mad at my dog's diapers and pee pads… https://t.co/E3QZX8fZ9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just applied for an individualized major in Entertainment and Spectacle Production, and @ladygaga was mentioned n… https://t.co/i6uGjLBa50]]></document><document><![CDATA[@red15blue @cjzero @PFF_Eric if you want to call a blind shoulder check in the open ice a "hit for men" then go pla… https://t.co/Jh0csCcnnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a scuba diver and life long surfer, I have been fortunate enough to come into contact with these lovely mamma… https://t.co/y6UHMOCxTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrndAdmiralJohn @junkyshane I won’t fight you over that, but I’ve had outstanding bbq in Memphis and SC too. I’m also a pork fan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did not watch 90210, but I WAS a fan of #LukePerry in #Oz - STILL a top 5 HBO show - better than The Sopranos (fi… https://t.co/ZoYO0R47y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd is intent on destroying @TheDemCoalition - Democrats SHOULD NOT appear on @MeetThePress - his panels are… https://t.co/Kb3IuZRG4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will itblend? @ South San Francisco, California https://t.co/nTXgClSTmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another story about the horrible political landscape unfolding in #Venezuela. The aid is waiting—let it in, stop th… https://t.co/PpxiMVv3nX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinM_NFL I don't think any of those guys falls to the #Titans at those spots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conrenaissance @JackPosobiec So far I've only seen Jack's examples - not saying it can't be the case but I don't k… https://t.co/CVTsqfcsoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Catuchee I wouldn’t argue with delirious Caroline about Pokemon Mouthfeel jsyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffkilburg @thekudlowreport You know who else loves Larry?   $ES_F , that’s who.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump @GOP Republicans like em dumb. Cuz facts don’t matter to trump dummies. Trump dum… https://t.co/RigCnWUseO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Obscurus_Lupa You look like Debra Hari circa 1980 going on stage at CBGBs to sing about martians who eat cars and then play guitars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve Carrell will play Justin Trudeau in the movie https://t.co/JCZlyq6mB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@resplendicity @RavensRulz @AlexInAir @SouthwestAir You are correct.. it's the 737 Max 8... I have been on one or t… https://t.co/mIjeJWyyvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro who cares if Coby White was was a dook fan growing up when MJ was a kid he was a state fan and now he and Nike… https://t.co/xLIzTJEMY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey all . Anyone motive the inability to move to quick plat etc, until how to play? Super annoying. #Fridaythe13th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta @trumps_feed Always .the innocent little kids get hurt more than the devious isis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 Easy to say yes but as someone who has climbed towers (not as high). You start to change your mind at the 100 meter level....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perpetuating an embarrassment because he cant admit he misspoke #TrumpLiesMatter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/MwzTJmePq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outside of Geist, #Mizzou’s freshmen guards have 13 point on 4 of 13 shooting. Puryear’s also gone quiet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianZahnd Happy Birthday Brian - I’ve never met you, but love your books...and your music tastes 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kill Your Workout  - Credit to this post is to musclemonsters - When working out it’s important to get in the zone.… https://t.co/aM1zBRxdUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning my a.m. crew. @SexytotheNorth @katspaks  @abc13houston @ChelseyABC13 @ABC13Elita @TomKochABC13… https://t.co/YkRgC7lb6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aledemar1M @trish_regan @DanielDiMartino THIS WILL FREE AMERICA FROM this enemy to continue to destroy from inside… https://t.co/eVVGW5Aa33]]></document><document><![CDATA[@El_Universal_Mx Con ése obtuso pretestó se quieren quitar la responsabilidad de dar seguridad como gobernante, lue… https://t.co/al2LanG5gO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, on their behalf, Peter. One day, they will remember and appreciate you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The article states clearly inspire of the headlines that non-citizen cannot vote in federal elections. You, like yo… https://t.co/BnzfyvEuuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joannasmith131 @TheBigCrunchTh1 Since FLA’s ‘stand your ground’ law's adoption not only have ‘lawful’ homicides in… https://t.co/LuLpEDuHKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be performing Thursday March 7th @ 7-9  material from my new social justice spoken word book Exposing Politi… https://t.co/Q6va26nYKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC That’s how the GOP roll. Foaming at the mouth during their Nazi convention: “Lock her up.” They are the one’… https://t.co/HzZvVzocia]]></document><document><![CDATA[chuckle with me for a bit. If you are the oldest child be honored. It means that you were so awesome that... https://t.co/cxryOD4QZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we're looking at here is a hockey style clinch. He's creating space by grabbing and stiff arming near the coll… https://t.co/Jrnwh2jZPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy anniversary to the girl I can’t stop following in love with @OliviaLake96 you’re absolutely amazing! Love ya babe!❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattmikalatos Gerascophobia is a good catch-all. Basically the same thing. 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philosophrob @Donice88 The people are eating food out of garbage trucks...but that's what you want here in America! Stop crying pajama boy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Rolling Meadows Bell Tower in Rolling Meadows, IL https://t.co/MwCnBEoQV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayoMogundipe yo my phone is somewhere inside your place, I believe you know who has it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unreal  Really really unreal.  Quite amazing the system works and is happy to restore games for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@we need a social platform unlike Facebook and Twitter that is fair to all sides. Facebook and Twitter are blatentl… https://t.co/Idad3iUO54]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pouyalilpou @JewelzWinnfield It really is fifty fifty tho u got that on the money!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just seen someone rockin a velvet green du-rag with the cape out...this generation is doomed lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want a #pixelwatch!! Android Central: Google to reportedly launch Pixel Watch, new Nest camera, and more in 2019.… https://t.co/gOZyU6pB1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@21Street12 @vivien2112 It's a hand That rocks the cradle It's a motion That swings the sky It's method on the edge… https://t.co/IPnABmRc5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeriedadT @Orlando65837117 You led me to the very brilliant @SeriedadT I'm wild about him Thanks from the bottom my heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to dklayhay for these great pictures. Very talented. @ Wichita Falls, Texas https://t.co/NXvxdRcQVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[99% of my friends are car people so this was oddly refreshing and funny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Valentine's day was ok I was all alone to myself having fun without woman in my life and I am still on vacation… https://t.co/jYLdFiVNNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been the same since I loved that h*e Haven’t been the same since I lost my bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeSherman And then the R demanded AGAIN why they weren't turned over.  They aren't even listening to the answers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latinpopwer @RMScanal @Madonna @ArianaGrande @ladygaga @katyperry La que vino a mencionar "la más talentosa" fuist… https://t.co/WSq067MjQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KanelandHoops you guys were phenomenal all year, you guys were so fun to watch. Congrats on a great season, so muc… https://t.co/6AVwClGnuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t disrespect @kanyewest we are witnessing history and that is a fact]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyFriendCamilo @berniemoreno The lowest paid FTE of @CityofCleveland makes $15 as of April, 2018. I was happy to p… https://t.co/bsOD0INfwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorge_guajardo En ocasiones es difícil pintar la línea entre ser propositivo y ser ingenuo.  Le pasó a Maseca, a C… https://t.co/AssUSnzCKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @WSJopinion That’s California our politicians are total Nut Jobs and Do Nothing For California Unbelievable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sec1968 They are going on a overpass down here in the City of Peachtree Corners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to hear @sportstalksc back on the air in Spartanburg with Kornblut and Smitty. Smitty did a great job with sp… https://t.co/fx5k31JjFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Views wnydowntown @whotels @ W New York - Downtown https://t.co/pnc8MKjQmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dan_Fitz23 @aireste You guys are giving those guys WAY too much credit. Kobe made those guys look good]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night, I got a beautiful email that contained the three most romantic words I've ever read: direct deposit received.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We didn’t have one Top 10 Beat Writer in the APSE Awards this year. We had two. Well deserved for both @BW_Jones an… https://t.co/uJhsaOGi6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leggo #Fsu #tribe20 🍢🍢🔥🔥 All right bruh let’s load up the under armor game with a bunch a #Noles]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the sad thing about your comment is you're serious https://t.co/2ICMU0ELDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaysonL56 @daverosenthal27 @RU_Knighted_18 For us just win! I would be estatic with a .500 or better record and the NIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sammmidd Neither are you guys, just got smacked at home by a 14-14 Rutgers team.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenHigginsSD @usdmbb They must’ve played punch-out before the tourney!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ERTraumaJunkie @bhawkesRN Someone other than a conscious, dedicated nurse would have these dreams less often. A yo… https://t.co/MBbDQ2vvO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't be grateful enough that God allowed me to adopt this loving girl. Always #adoptdontshop. https://t.co/hGIl0DgFTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My NBA East standings Predictions for the rest of the season  1. Toronto Raptors 2. Boston Celtics 3. Milwaukee Buc… https://t.co/RcVcS6fRcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sommervilletv He's beheading people in the street. and calling his schoolgirl wife antisocial. Yeah Ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@W0LFM4N92 @Vext6 @JenLFer03 @realDonaldTrump Seriously, screw that argument. How long a law has existed has zero b… https://t.co/ejbLSqykZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leslie_bern @SPSSI @nitopconference I forgot that you and @meenzwell were friends until I saw she liked this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TechRojo That *doesn't* break the bank. Like around $200 or less. Isn't OnePlus like $400-500?]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Stanton: broken clouds, 59°F 44% humidity, wind 3mph, pressure 1014mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annwprice @EvaluationMaven I vote for Carolyn's suggestion: a query! @c_camman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Search me, O God, and know my heart! Try me and know my thoughts! And see if there be any grie…… https://t.co/Mj2OgZ3foI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mheathumbach @whoop Are you still @Garmin free or have you gone back? Set my Fenix 5 down today and put on the… https://t.co/Ur8IiktdgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to sit really close to an s10 owner so I can charge my iPhone through my pocket #SamsungEvent]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son just matched!!!! He’s gonna be a surgeon. Long road but the right one for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatsjonsense @ronnyk "try anything, measure everything" is particularly good strategy if the search part of your… https://t.co/SZI45Clw0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steigerworld Well, for one, I do (have a clue, that is).  If you mean politicians, I certainly could list a few an… https://t.co/6vIHGsqbUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HornsFan29 They typically are. It’s usually a very relaxed home crowd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cautious, careful people, always casting about to preserve their reputations...can never effect a reform. — Susan B… https://t.co/86qcWsQS9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akaFayaven cigarettes for breakfast came on a minute good ass song miss you homie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nevspins Hey! The only one I’ve come across that’s close is Anathem by Neal Stephenson. Alternate universe where t… https://t.co/Ui8DguFeLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeatSauce1 Of course I have to comment on this...Did you have to giveaway your ‘real’ Rolex or earrings— “dangly”… https://t.co/PmXTYnEyn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LA_SocialistRA That's NOT the right answer, and that's not going to help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#radiobeach #bimini #realbimini #blue #watercolor #water #sea #tattoo #tattoos #calm #beachlife #lowlife… https://t.co/Y0jVgxi9GJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian BLONDES👑🇷🇺Women Are The MOST Be In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝😍😘 https://t.co/StUo3MQRaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlyweeks @AndrewScheer and the @CPC_HQ probably support this type of abuse but I bet that they won't comment on it!! #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidG_theMLG @BeckyLynchWWE Word! I believe it! I'm in the 60-70 range and there pulling in fast now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TRHLofficial I helped a Girl Scout troop with car stuff. That way they would be safe as they learned to drive]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @GeorgesMusic in Springfield, PA https://t.co/WGfjVLny3O https://t.co/mzAcvVE3TZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinnieWrightTV I wish the would here in Arkansas my god we have tons of potholes remember you were here #flattire #frontendallignmemt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting warmed up for day 2 of #southernpremier @DynamoSwimClub https://t.co/OJnFsImIb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[[IAMLIGHTSTAR1111] sings Dream On by Aerosmith, what an incredible voice on StarMaker! #music  https://t.co/xCaUfEgRGo]]></document></documents></author>