<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[lmao do y'all think this was a stock photo, or did they take this picture specifically for this headline?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctanner3 @Serremmy @Havoc_70 @Wuwugirl1 @my3monkees @CaptainComput3r @ChrisBragdon @somethingfun08 @misspunk63… https://t.co/y0DdOQRu3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I pray each day and night you and your mobster family will go to jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick fact Flash Card #4 #PelhamProudforEducation https://t.co/LjgovpK4mI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salt dough map planning has commenced. Give them guidelines and let them dream! Can’t wait to see their territories… https://t.co/0f8tuoqbe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s March 1. I have 14 days to apply for 15 jobs and I haven’t written any of my essays for said applications. PANIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @ecklund93 for joining @CreightonDSL this morning and leading a conversation about #NASPA100! https://t.co/ItrdaGRRyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelT_45 @realDonaldTrump Each day that passes make me wonder, what the hell is wrong with you people????Everyd… https://t.co/fWne8xGPVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlaccseedAmeri1 @TwitWiter123 @NevetsNonnac @kzshabazz @tonetalks @JordanPeele How can we increase the numbers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[That piece of high literature inspired by Steve Harvey stupidity https://t.co/5z72FD8mx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madea Haven’t missed one yet! By the way, I crack up every time I hear the announcer on the movie trailer say “hal… https://t.co/4YzM4CwA3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[i been doin some research n it turns out that i am, in fact, that bitch https://t.co/zxp1AwP50z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me reading every article/listening to every conversation about the #JordynWoods/#TristanThompson/#KhloeKardashian d… https://t.co/Z9NP1PMlfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u come at me with "plans" I expect you to follow through #JustKnowThatHomeBoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nouveau tunel de la montagne #universitedemontreal #photoarchitecture 📷 @ Université de Montréal https://t.co/urnHlXPBNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urbiewankenobi I know dutch bros does . But I never seen restaurants do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1:My opinion removed, homework is to review the day’s learning &amp; provide additional practice for Ss. #satchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monica_redondo @Cinthya_Cadenas @soyMargarlto *empieza a buscarlo en amazon*]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @tedcruz... it is time for #TERMLIMITSNOW Join the fight and support Ted's constitutional amendment --… https://t.co/OpzIGYX7tt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharlesPreston 10 over here (age 27), four of them unpaid internships]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to hear @roxystriar give Umbrella Company a shout out on #ColliderLive because a good friend of mine from e… https://t.co/vnSsPhTzMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please read this thread. This is why we work so hard to understand school shootings but also to publicize how rate… https://t.co/AYE2gdPO1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to all and 💥 💥 💥 @PwC_Canada @ByronBergren @jenn_cordeiro @jessicamacht @monaghiami @dingle… https://t.co/cN1axq7Cqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TubeTimeUS This is great! Does it have words pre-recorded into its ROM, or does it use phonemes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey,  Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/LzEWYxn6Lf… https://t.co/wobwpWSuy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast of champions! #preparedmindset #foodisfuel @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/rk775EJnMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[yall ever work a double and make under $300 and just wanna cry bc yeah same]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night in St. Paul @Sannehfdn #Gala4Goals. Minnesota really knows how to show up strong for the kids. Well don… https://t.co/FMK1OOh1rI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the absolute best valentine I couldn’t ever asked for! I’ve been in such a happy mood until I got home and he… https://t.co/DRYOwKZYLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day 👭🏼 I'd have to say that the best outcome of becoming a blogger has been all the bea… https://t.co/fjZiGhJcKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/24 @PoliticsProse 3 PM, D.C. w/ Jeannie Vanasco 2/25 @booksaremagicbk 7 PM w/ @melissafebos… https://t.co/78xTw5VcLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot about standards and the great work of the @iaeaorg by @UnderSecTc, but sentiment seems not to apply when… https://t.co/eIAX7dhfwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help!!! No puedo sacar al #HP de @maluma de mi cabeza!! Literal mientras como, manejo hasta cuando duermo!! Ya solo… https://t.co/6qLHOoNukG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone has a birthday coming up and this would be perfect. #JustThrowingThatOutThere https://t.co/DUtmmDNe5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu If you loathe President Trump, which it appears that you do, then it’s a given, that you’re ALWAYS going t… https://t.co/JlR0IyVTiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Letterkenny is the greatest dialogue ever written in television history.  Fight me, 10 ply.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if swmrs actually go I’ll be so happy cause Roy Blair’s show is the same night as swmrs wks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kate_macatangay ( TBT to not knowing what the object on the floor by your bed was and using your video camera ligh… https://t.co/dZgQzH1dDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brettsavidis Compensating for something?  He actually didn’t build anything.  It was done through another company.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeepsBurgh all I heard was *fart noise* *fart noise* *fart noise* so obviously he made some good points]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re hoping to assemble this 3D printed prosthetic on Monday!  We wouldn’t have even started the project had we no… https://t.co/8lFPnaZj3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[You do not need to care about your friend to still be friends. I have a friend who calls me slurs every 6 months an… https://t.co/QJhsnaz3MU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Cinemark Theatres for Greta in Somerdale, NJ https://t.co/bFt0VmD3h4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so proud of this kid, all the kids who run, and the families who make this club possible! #runhappy… https://t.co/i1UlqDdbwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mescothelioma This sounds like a great intro to a short story of memoirs. Can I ghost write 4 u???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Binge watching One Tree Hill on @hulu  and I always forget how incredible @katevoegele is until I see her as Mia 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I just woke up Levi out of a dead sleep so he could touch my ass. He slapped it, kept his hand on it and started snoring again. MY MAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cirque du Hopefest Gala to benefit @HavenHouseSTL https://t.co/nd4P345WPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX MONSTER IS RAPPER, SINGER, SONGWRITER, PRODUCER T-PAIN I WILL NEVER FORGET THAT VOICE.  #ThankMeLater😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decision-Making Matrix @CPI_Training. @Tabitha_Dudley1 @Chantel_Pearl https://t.co/Ldg80YdKxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Pakistan and India Keep Fighting Over Kashmir https://t.co/IgceeQfLwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[my legs hurt so bad thanks @MeganBrazier  i’ll die trying to keep up w you🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Laura Voeth and the Tolucan Times for a wonderful review! #hollywoodnt #castingcouch #metoo #timesupnow… https://t.co/Xb4Fz9R5Pe]]></document><document><![CDATA[As one of those #older #Entrepreneurs. I appreciate this #post. #unretire #startup #impactinvesting #aging… https://t.co/udtWKgRIvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's so sad more and more radio stations are dropping his music.. just speaking for myself I will never stop listen… https://t.co/7X68jCrFWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[⠀         (\__/)     ⠀  (•ㅅ•)      me driving the SAFE 　＿ノ ヽ ノ＼  __   bus at 2am  /　`/ ⌒Ｙ⌒ Ｙ　ヽ     ( 　(三ヽ人　 /　　 |… https://t.co/k9n4ABOLOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m done doing everything to try to please mfs. just let ME DO ME and move the fuck on with it. i’m not being sad abt u anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi! #WatchGotham everyone! #SaveGotham on your schedule tonight! This final season is on FIRE! 🔥 @Gotham… https://t.co/w9DhiTr0I0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chadwick_Moore @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews Chadwick, I absolutely love when you are on @TuckerCarlson  You ALWAYS do such a fantastic job 💘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miramardesign @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Just go away. You are way too extreme and negative for me to waste time on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warming up before my AcroYoga class and practicimg for my Daily Challenge Pose!  Felt really stiff; I can tell even… https://t.co/8m8zvyNRIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nishawrites gym, shower, soup, father brown on bbc, murder mystery novel. far far far far better than 95% of the parties I’ve attended]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralHospital @MauraWest This relationship is disturbing. Very disturbing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw this today. It is so true. ❤️ my scholars. https://t.co/FHefLE27vG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been to many live concerts but it’s a close first with @tobykeith at the @ford centennial thingy we went… https://t.co/Sa6PmAmOwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 more days! My @giantrace preview is up on the blog https://t.co/VHcJPdHXtb #GiantRaceBR #BibChat https://t.co/v5DordmWwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi guys i woke up early and I’m at the gym :) this tweet is more myself telling myself I’m proud of u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drdrew @greggutfeld @GregGutfeldShow @PlanetTyrus @KatTimpf CANNOT WAIT TO SEE DR. DREW!  I miss him! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[prediction, dumbass Democrats make Bernie the 2020 democratic nominee, who then loses to Trump https://t.co/2rjLqaO1Id]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been real #aafs2019. Awesome meeting, great presentations, and great to catch up with so many forensic science… https://t.co/KPnVvTWhWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Thoughts #madaket  3️⃣ days to 6️⃣5️⃣✅💪🏻🙏🏻 @ Nantucket, Massachusetts https://t.co/vcXBwrlfZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tah tah for now #EmpressOfTheSeas, it has been an adventure, wink!  Cheers to Cast 6, wishing you all safe travels… https://t.co/gU0jKplbvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyD3315 @ColoradoEagles Piece of cake for these eagles another win is all we want go eagles!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch Why?  He's undermining all that is good for U.S. and funding anything bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wintermute_exe They are financed by exhaustion, it seems. I have often retrieved my Sad Desk Lunch at a subpar spo… https://t.co/eJ7mujiht0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed out to Toms River High School North to help @AttitudesInRev spread hope and good mental health. 4th year in… https://t.co/p3kORVTZzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scenes from a Topanga music night. Feeling blessed and emotional over the fleeting beauty of moments like this. May… https://t.co/TIms2oQyQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girrrlllll.... if I’d ever received grades like that @LawrenceUni? ...you in danger yo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comfy from head to toe in the Nile Dress - hood down or hood up - paired with my post-apocalyptic Pixie vest… https://t.co/n9l9tjquBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find someone you can be corny with together.   Find someone who makes you snort uncontrollably and laugh like an id… https://t.co/fbMCmHWbtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DirtyMoMedia @DaleJr @iRacing Who thinks my son needs hired to create paint schemes for iRacing? He also races, sp… https://t.co/ahLlufo5j2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec You are doing an awesomely amazing job Sarah!! The American people see and understand the ridiculous anti… https://t.co/IIkQ5Fsk8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJTaj @RepAndyBiggsAZ @realDonaldTrump The illegal alien lied and thats ok?  He took a life when he shouldnt have… https://t.co/ifvdZITArF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senior lefty @yosoyjfong was named SCIAC Pitcher of the Week after a dominant performance against Texas Lutheran la… https://t.co/WzSNQpqhOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MandyBa48181836 @NO1GifQueen @collinsp1960 @LadyTi88 @DebbieRumsey1 @APabloIsForever @Lou_S_Stools @linablue… https://t.co/ssqsqbYcSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIERCIEL Something I was thinking about was what if she died ala FFXIII or was overthrown by the Astrals (like int… https://t.co/IXA6ot27m4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hawryluk_Hive Select jerseys will be available to bid on during the game on March 10! You will be able to find the… https://t.co/LQaklOqk2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomsofMaine @StanLevenson @craignewmark @HoraceMann @donorschamps @StephenAtHome @UPS @37people]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AtTheHalf: @DuqMBB leads the way with a 47-41advantage over George Washington. #PutEmUp/#DukeTheProcess #WearRed… https://t.co/mFOQTMVlrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have a platform, use it to stand OUT...to have an actual voice. Not blend in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening now, faith leaders of Sacramento and from all over the state are gathering ahead of a rally to call on… https://t.co/gWHF4PDfSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir THANK YOU .. JUST SOLVED MY LOG IN ISSUE AND BOOKED A FLIGHT FOR  $11...i had so many unused points!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m wondering davidnova7 if SpikyPoo (his Grandma called him that) remembers the little people?!  @SpikeLee CONGRAT… https://t.co/UM8N49AhVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely. “E Pluribus Unum -  out of many, one (the motto of the US). Keep that motto in the forefront during thi… https://t.co/WMmZ46wUxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[aye this was me at cgp... you’ll be aight. if you reall wanna have a ball, mix those two with 4loko and a splash of… https://t.co/X3s2TeK5YR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KwikWarren I picked strawberries, raspberries, all kinds of things plus worked in a hamburger joint to get my first car.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s party time my friends! Now let’s go dance!💃💃#slatenyc #clubbing https://t.co/evqacQA6Uh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting a group at hssu dedicated to helping bring awareness to mental health among young women 💕.. . I know h… https://t.co/Tkvsr7CQFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’ve joined your UPC, agreed to speak at nurse residency classes  while still working your floor full time,… https://t.co/W7UNVHiWkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissamtripp It's how I express my thoughts and feelings to the world. 🖤]]></document></documents></author>