<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What happens when you tell the Frenchman’s bartender that the WiFi doesn’t work?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You spend your whole life trying not to be like the person you envy the most. And in the end you become so blinded… https://t.co/uBSGt16Z66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluekel Heard a valedictorian say that during a high school graduation speech unironically. I felt embarrassed then and I still do now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔 how cool would it be for @stance to create a HWC Jersey sock based on these @Bucks jerseys? #FearTheDeer… https://t.co/i4QIovLZx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryan_leblanc @towhey Every single day. And the negotiations NEVER involved anyone but me and the prosecutor. No p… https://t.co/lZPKIYhYUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[And like what, a selfie? Sure I'll just get a heavily edited filter to make me look pretty and also makes me feel g… https://t.co/1EZUSgjrRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are people acting like $2B isn’t a shit ton of money. You know how many people $2B could help?? A lot more than… https://t.co/lycpLK6xb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard there was a national emergency at la frontera, so I came right away to do my part. https://t.co/IpsnTpLhIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealGFD finally used my #Titlesist Duffle bag you all sent me.   Man does it hold a lot of clothes for s trip.  Thanks again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michaelgh040 @Ezidi2 It looks like Yazidi People look Similar to Me !! ? Sincerely yours me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petercoffin PETA criticizes Irwin because he wants what they profess to want,  but people actually liked him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally gong to see my favorite band in the unverse  tonight. @ Ukrainian Culture Center - UCC https://t.co/QrS0wzwbGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fix NCAA men’s basketball: 1. Quarters. Everyone else plays quarters.  2. 1 advertising TO per quarter + 1 between… https://t.co/FR07GjOMEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I trust everyone had a great Oscar weekend and a great begin of the week. moetchandon @EatWinsome @hwood_roosevelt… https://t.co/q6rO9YE0fI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our after-hours Crisis Support is back starting Monday, March 11th. @kingsatwestern and @WesternU  thanks to fundin… https://t.co/qwAB6A9KfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalFFAWeek has ended but I’m still missing my team   #WAFFA https://t.co/snfklcj8Ns]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to write my monthly technology/computer column for the Forest Ranch Post. Any suggestion or trending topics you would recommend?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good life is a waves crowning crest​-rolling in a majestic-moving moment-of full formed-white cap crescendo/Becom… https://t.co/t3BBJsenKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“O Lord, in the morning You will hear my voice; in the morning I will direct my prayer to You, and I will wait expectantly.”- Psalm 5:3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to boston and called “Ni**er” multiple times by black people ...I just can’t imagine what white people be saying Lmaoooooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@overtime @kobebryant Man, these chicks are bad-ass!! A spike from one of the girls, would explode your face!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @realDonaldTrump Thank you @LouDobbs! Continue to dwell on @realDonaldTrump's responsibility to secure the borders!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PokemonGoApp I'm going to stick with team Mystic https://t.co/45pnOlmwE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanCasten You might want to take to your colleague about some of his own Islamaphobia https://t.co/MhU9fe3Dx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPaigeWWE I'm looking for it at the UA theater in Brooklyn Court Street but it's not playing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cambridge99 @adamgoldenberg Bingo. For me, this isn't a question of whether undue pressure was exerted, it now spe… https://t.co/fNUhX5tqGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtandrade 😢😢😢💕yessssss ahuevo que llevamos ofi juntos hahaha que tiempos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robert_in_MN @ForteCatholic @pursuedbytruth I know brotha. Just Messin with u. I’m the same way. All about fightin… https://t.co/0dcnrVdmkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealNickAldis @RealNickAldis there are some things that never needs to happen and that is @TheJimCornette with coffee in him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sneakers4Kenni I'll have more on that once I'm back from Germany. Had to reset for mental health reasons. It won't… https://t.co/b3CMy4dnZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part 2 of my Alamo tour. Long rifles, swords, knives, jewelry and religious. #dad2summit #sanantonio #tour #history… https://t.co/mVjcilOY57]]></document><document><![CDATA[No cause I'd live my life in fear over slipping on a potato chip or some dumb shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation @RepAdamSchiff @realDonaldTrump Ask #FullOfSchiff about this guy! @margbrennan https://t.co/YkyhMuFz7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kiera wants to bring Kailyn, Eddie, Stef, Damien, Anthony, and Maki in a room together and see if they commit to ke… https://t.co/yX1hSDLA2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are non-wealthy minorities who went to jail for drug crimes who are screaming right now about how light of a sentence Manafort got ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattlspurrier @nsarwark @Galt1138 @aaron_m_wright @FlowInTheDarkXX @LibertyEricRI @LPMisesCaucus @ThomasEWoods If… https://t.co/2cqraZkW2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[APRIL ACT✏️ The April ACT will be given at VWHS on April 13. Students need to register by Friday, March 8 at https://t.co/OZl1m5PEz8.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NASCAR making an impression on @barstoolsports &amp; @stoolpresidente. Nicely done @austindillon3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano How could he look himself in the face when shaving each morning? He's suffering from… https://t.co/bXkvG3ZXMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterSupport @jimcramer  This is always @jack and #riptwitter idea of innovation.   Put lipstick on a Pig.  It i… https://t.co/i0AooBH81o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump IvanKKKa, are these jobs in the coal industry, like your pussy grabbing daddy promised?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having an absolute blast working with Steve Martin and Luke today. #lions ashonadawn realestateminutelasvegas glamo… https://t.co/VxGimMcDEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Exactly... We're not talking about Paul Manafort here.  My Observation:  There are good liars and th… https://t.co/rMLlZHuG7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shrugs contract/retract.. makes sure you hit the posterior side of the traps. https://t.co/FlveYGI32U]]></document><document><![CDATA[RECORDED EARLIER: ”REPORT OF FIGHT AT RESTURANT” in SLIDELL, LA. - @SlidellPD | @OfficialLivePD #LivePD #LivePDNation #LivePDWatchParty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ilhan Ersahin, Juini Booth, George Spanos at Nublu, December 10th, 2018. #ilhanersahin #juinibooth #georgespanos… https://t.co/CxtTyWWzUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benehmke I think they’re serious about using him as needed. Comps: Hamilton and Matt Kemp come to mind. Prob forge… https://t.co/8KLYZkNBMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Granma de Cuba dedica una pagina a Cohen,y omite todo cuanto sucede en Venezuela y lo peor es que creen ciegamente en Cohen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mainstream Hip hop is the worst thing ever. the most dangerous trash ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picking up 540 right here in Vegas.  Going to Kansas City then Evansville Indiana for the night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @SlayerMosh @chriswaslight @Truth2Dj @The_DNELSON @AMERICAOF1 @imaxmeon @MargaretMcgui16 @BrettHuntoon… https://t.co/1jderl299k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlatEarthCity I’ll I see is a horizon that in some shots is slightly curved in the bottom screen. Your own experim… https://t.co/ja46qDofAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take your best guess and you could be off to see @TheEllenShow ! #FreshMornings https://t.co/6cVpV2f84p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Remdelarem @MikelleStreet The fuck cares what the hair is lookin like?! https://t.co/6cycUHgiY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @littlesexbuddha @milanamaylove @missjojokiss @AbbyCrossXXX @ScarlettSageX @akaDaniDaniels… https://t.co/tVIu6gxK6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianxluong And you were going to stop being my friend if I texted my ex with thank you, next...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @JonSummersdc This is an emergency...Democrats intend to bring the illegals in to the point our exist… https://t.co/HKioI38nUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustMuteMeNow There’s so many @Kaepernick7 supporters out there the @nflnetwork ratings are way up since he left t… https://t.co/6qZWrWYE4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[RJ Barret with the self-nutmeg to set a screen for Reddish with the game tying three... that’s something else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JorgeDCG Ser de idiotas que nada está bien. Si no va por qué no va? Si va por qué va?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch, the only person you're keeping my account safe from by doing this is me 😫 https://t.co/6VjqKOsZu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brock 49, Colorado City 34... 5:36 to play. Wolves on a 7-2 to run. #BigCountryPreps https://t.co/7Y4C0gx9jG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know who needs to hear this but Do it for the culture man, uplift and spread love over personal satisfaction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petition for Gaga to scrap “Shallow” at the Oscars and perform a mashup of “Why Did You Do That?” and “Hair Body Fa… https://t.co/LklAn38EEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contract is on their terms and they can structure it however they want without giving up any draft picks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZaherToumi @pattynece @DrSRPWilliams @DrAlberga @JAMA_current @YoniFreedhoff @UConnRuddCenter @DrStuartFlint… https://t.co/n08r7NAlNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino The left has become increasingly bold and violent, supported by the media praising the fake MAGA racist h… https://t.co/sbRrrlE0kN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, props to the cameraman in black, grabbing that jacket off the ramp while still getting the shot!… https://t.co/0cZskPqD98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum Why do you have no remorse for the Iraq War, NK, or Iran? How?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@huntercody30 @CroixBoy @MSpencer1010 @undisputed @DaTrillStak5 Two finals MVP over Lebron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esto es el Feminismo un Cáncer social!! Esto defiendes @tv_monica que a tus compañeros los agredan? Por eso es que… https://t.co/eFm9JoItu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Week 2 of Men in the Trenches Lineman Camp, it was so much fun and I learned so much today from the coaches, met so… https://t.co/rqW5eC8yJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwrjd @charliekirk11 I don’t know the lawyer speak for it but the new laws take precedent over old ones. The law i… https://t.co/9XjzV0hbFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mas_fifi @lacabritafifi @FifiLibre @AlyeriV @oct_bolloa @DenisseBasarell @DoraPatricia21 @germanmexico @OmiBeGood… https://t.co/uqSxCe71IE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@victoriajcoe @Melady2000 @henrybearspark @penguinkids Can’t wait for their next adventure!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liking the change I made to this beat the other night. Slide 1: original. [Swipe] to hear a preview of the verse I… https://t.co/bRrkHM0VWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fired up for this young man! He has worked hard and it is beginning to pay off! @TavianHobson keep grinding!… https://t.co/uKSaNKyuNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnTheCard @W_W_Unicorns @Bigpawsonapup @withjohners_pod @RantWithAnt @fowl_original @Omega_Luke @PWPNation… https://t.co/9ddrtM3SIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just bought AF1s cuz @chelseacutler and I need a walking tutorial girl. But plus side is I’m now 6’4.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@topper_fan Yeah I know they are down 2 of their best players...but DAMN!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help make it happen for Funcl Wireless Headphones: Affordable Awesomeness https://t.co/QvyJ1ZeoXo #indiegogo via @indiegogo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, @hqtrivia is all about Taylor Swift tonight... if I don't win it's gonna be hard to "shake it off". #dailydadjoke]]></document><document><![CDATA[East Hartford girls basketball leading Newington 25- 15 at the half #ctgbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand people who read review after review before watching a show/movie or listening to new music. Make… https://t.co/4nXVPjBK3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/48ge80a9st At time of #Ebola crisis, #USCongress approved one-time, 5-year #emergency supplemental spe… https://t.co/KzSmW70zpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FransedeCastro @gialloqueen @FromMadhouse @SkyCinemaHorror @DawnOfTheDee1 @creepybranson @horrorbulletin… https://t.co/jFvyC1tWFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was never a penalty but this ref has been a disaster all game 🤷‍♂️ ....and justice 😂😂😂 #ArsenalTottenham #PremierLeague]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Congratulations on making this guy never pay attention to anything you have to say ever again. Keep on killing… https://t.co/m8UDbmK05j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senca Event Management Design Linen Gallery Soirée Chair Decor #art #photography #justgoshoot #iphonephotography… https://t.co/XmuqASeJcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandicarlile @TheEllenShow @FSMaui It didn’t start last week. I saw your you at the Austin City Limits Music Fest… https://t.co/ZVwQqYcdJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#5deMarzo #Sismos #PapaFrancisco #HoyconMhoni #MartesdeMhoni @mhonividente 🧿 @ClubMhoniFans @magdaproducer ✨📺🔮🎬🎥… https://t.co/KdD3UyiS5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[In addition to defining whole new classes of immigrants  The Iran “Deal” The Pairs “Agreement”  Now I don’t like th… https://t.co/1tct7aOAYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whiskey  bent  🎧 I'm Not The Devil by Cody Jinks on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/fKFd0rPMPU https://t.co/Wzo7oprzMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW TREND ALERT: The Trump Bump. Market Growth, No Recession | Read it here: https://t.co/WzbsgBfwZ5 https://t.co/3I3Fr0x3We]]></document><document><![CDATA[Were these guys really self-reporting their penis sizes to some Viacom PA when filling out the paperwork? Was… https://t.co/zT8S3k2PNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen I bet you do!  Hell if the President endorsed Robert Francis you would prefer the other! Tick Tock ! I l… https://t.co/RcGs1m87dV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrookeGrimsley I started at Bradley in 2000. It’s now 2019. We’ve been to ONE NCAA Tournament in that span. We/I need this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Larson was the real winner of this race with the day he had to finish on the lead lap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickWinkelman Honest appraisal in areas where we can improve (speaking for myself). Takes time to build relationsh… https://t.co/odruBHER8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpTic_Scumper When you expect no reply 😂. Was just trolling for reply tbh]]></document></documents></author>