<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Rashida Tlaib’s Demeaning Remarks about Lynne Patton https://t.co/XEizu1HSBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allen58VoteBlue @BlkSantaX @AllanMcHz @MrsblksantaX @CIAnderson3 @AussieDebBell @pfarrside @PauletteStrick… https://t.co/DPTC4gsqCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way #WrestleMania seems to be forming, I think the friend(s) will be heavily entertained. I'm showing non-wrest… https://t.co/ZogZ52Fr0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dedicatedbitch #lafitnessbeverlyhills lafitness #newdaynewme #purelaughter  @LaughterLearned @ LA Fitness - BEVERL… https://t.co/1P9qo6SLeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today and yesterday were just perfect days to just roll the windows down, play the whole "Band on the Run" album on… https://t.co/nnvTqssJrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This album takes me back to the bus rides home from 8th grade hoops games bumping this on my Sony Minidisk player 😂… https://t.co/WUuamBtrEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Society will brainwash you into thinking you supposed to live a certain way because of your skin, or upbringing, or… https://t.co/cq7chqyPoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming up at 11 on @WRCB I’ll be showing the path of the deadly tornado outbreak in Georgia and Alabama hour by hou… https://t.co/Q1xvTOVXrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobRobledoBA @Asael_Ruvalcaba @PrincipalSJV @DrJerLowe @MrCourington53 @literacy_kim @RyanBJackson1 @EastwoodHS @LSkae @danielmedinaCMS 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizabethraine @devinforparks @KevinLovesDonut Why do parties need to endorse in a single party town with ranked c… https://t.co/oPOxTwFoi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeatrizGMuller Sra.Beatriz. buen día. No se deje llevar por lo que le comentan en la calle, quieren utilizarla com… https://t.co/hl5X3onkRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine getting to air commercials for your show on the USA Network, during ad breaks for Chrisley Knows Best or wh… https://t.co/AN3u9p3kZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait till they get older and start answering back. You’ll be running out the house. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i know im peaking in my mental health rn bc im actually unsubscribing from all the spammy email lists im on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hola Los Ángeles 👋👋 #californiaroadtrip en Los Angeles, California https://t.co/wbi4UaXKb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Were is all that money going? Do you or have you ever seen a polotician living check to check. No none of them do.… https://t.co/tvIY3a2VvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dipping our #cups https://t.co/r2V5KVhpv6 #Word #bible #Jesus #Christ #God #Spirit #Faith #love #grace #poem… https://t.co/RIFGkyDEKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam Schiff just cares about covering up his lies! 10 Hours of coaching did no good. Lock Him Up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t been this excited about a project in a while 👀 Can’t wait for @MeanGreenMBB to be back in the Super Pit for… https://t.co/ygx56vaoKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nanis_916 Completely agree with you. So much of it comes from the media though... everyone seeing these models and… https://t.co/VavwPhuyo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr  Day after your father leaves office in 202 for you have to run for president]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy CHD Awareness Day! #1in100 @ Oleo Acres Enterprises https://t.co/cb2rN2eUWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveGators4ever Probably a better day than what I just saw this plumber have. He pulled his bicep trying to lift a heavy water heater]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially his complicit Congressional supporters who are in violation of their oath of office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Fleet are currently Padreing!! But as news comes out those days are numbered!!! Let’s hope !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash Menendez? What a MORON! The Schiff and Swalwell of the east coast. He is lucky to not be in jail!]]></document><document><![CDATA[B2: Reilani Peleti crushes a solo home run beyond left field, giving the Wildcats a 1-0 lead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaShi_DaShi I would leave they ass! Not because of the food but because of the description! If they lying about wh… https://t.co/HH4NY0mK9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance Not true of trump wasn’t president and HRC won the election the democrats and left wouldn’t care a… https://t.co/Hltz1nSET4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizadushku It's only gonna get worse as th IC's investigation gets closer to his family, and ultimately him. But Judement Day is coming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJARiley @HITMANWarrior23 @lake_1423 @hoopscoutmedia @ARBballRankings @ASTSprts @42_sports @maverickludgood… https://t.co/FZwa76G2ah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Revised Wknd Prvw ATR @TampaBayDownsFL 9a-12p @SiriusXMSports = @DRFMcGee, @NTamm1215, @AwayTheyGo, @DRFPrivman,… https://t.co/5wwzScfLZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to go to king of the cage next Sunday let me know I get free tickets it’s at the Ontario citizen ar… https://t.co/X7Ltpp9gk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaySekulow Can you pick out the "pro-life" vicious, greedy Republicans and the liberal Democrats in this presentat… https://t.co/9I3qLkQ40R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just stood in the middle of my apartment and silently screamed; how's your Monday going?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CCESColts Kindergarten did it again! Super cute Bremen Town Musicians Concert this evening! Thanks to @CCES_AP… https://t.co/Llqkm8LCJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me get this straight. We waited two months and endured all the 2.26.19 tweets in anticipation for a self-procla… https://t.co/9vsyPAJzPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought in my wildest dreams I could go on without a drink. But one day I said enough was enough. I was tir… https://t.co/A8XzLxuUeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kuhl_USA @stance @merrelloutside @patagonia @thenorthface Renegade convertoyble pants enthusiast. Skar Merino wool… https://t.co/TwS6AnI6DT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keira Knightley our gere making everyone question their sexuality https://t.co/cvYJkOv0is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCKatie Wait until next week @ottawacity warning Tuesday and Wednesday when transport caravan arrives]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that a yearbook photo of  @adamfgoldberg in the @SchooledABC opening credits? #wellPlayed https://t.co/QlCsofMIBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone on the left acknowledge why the right disagrees? The left, who fundamentally believes in big government… https://t.co/QqLZzeK4lQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really hoping ASIB doesn’t strike out but even so, I would be really happy to see ROMA become the first foreign fil… https://t.co/6iJ71dyzUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[For my birthday wish all I want is a new left leg or legs... bc I know I’m going to end up in a wheel chair before 54]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a wonderful truth, however it also ignores the problem of exorbitant tuition.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradyBacon @KyleLarsonRacin @XiaXianna I have NO idea what you are talking about 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[It never ends! USADA could literally test everyone on my team everyday, and someone would still accuse us. 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_thaWRIGHTway then i also remember not everybody is invested in you unless you’re read as brilliant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up this morning and realizing today was supposed to be an off day.   ...I woke up at 3:45 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Houlton leads George Stevens Academy 46-26 with 6:22 left to play. Looks as if we could have a new Class C North ch… https://t.co/kT27EWBUa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I picture this song playing while I’m at a Hawaiian festival in line for my shaved ice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always Trippin chorus. Bae why you trippin... #RYMEZ #alwaystrippin #whybae #idontargue #stressmeout #mighthaveto… https://t.co/Ygcob75Ejx]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW! I’ve been sick in bed the past two weeks and was starting to get very down. This news definitely made everythi… https://t.co/EaFrnIKKwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[hahahahaha no. this spinning off of amerie’s beat and all i thought about while listening to this was her song🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddiewhittle It’s just all about how well you get on with someone.  That chemistry that cannot be predicted.  That THING]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avg car price last year was $33k! Insanely high and way beyond most people's means but if you're gonna blow that mu… https://t.co/6uDJczEvCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can anybody explain why some people on the far right have the three gold stars in the Twitter handle? I know the re… https://t.co/2udvuhwqrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 "I the Lord search the heart and test the mind, to give every man according to his ways, according to the fruit… https://t.co/6YPaUE49TG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WeNotMe ... new time for tomorrow... 2:30 PM !!!!!!!!!! #HappyValentinesDay https://t.co/anH3gDGatR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edwr96 @Bill_Seitz @Benaskren @BlessedMMA @robwhittakermma Thank you yes we are 🤙🏽🤙🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is your pick for the Larry Flynt Freedom of Speech award? Call the Hotline now!! @JerryLawler @HeymanHustle… https://t.co/CK7btugp9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my 23rd anniversary at my job!! I love what I do and I’m surrounded by wonderful people. Thanks #Lifetouch and #shutterfly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @AmericaNowFirst In her face again . Dumb Bi*ch never learns 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TsGladysa @lithium66 @Tgirlfan69 @indo_waria1 @indo_shemale1 @jockosrocket @waria_highclas So Sexy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lack of the caution flag this year because Danica isnt racing this year #NASCAR  #NASCARGoesWest  #TicketGuardian500]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sadsaviors @tomdelonge He cant because his hair is prone to cutting itself.  ..✂️✂️🗡🗡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @Truth2Dj @SlayerMosh @chriswaslight @The_DNELSON @AMERICAOF1 @imaxmeon @MargaretMcgui16 @BrettHuntoon… https://t.co/M2bkmydMvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can build the wall AND have El Chapo pay for it... @tedcruz's #ELCHAPOAct is how. Stand with Ted Cruz and add yo… https://t.co/c6vreh4ukg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 86th Floor Observation Deck in New York, NY https://t.co/eimXoSdJwt https://t.co/K2tVJwwN4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber_Support I wasn’t trying to use Apple Pay. It’s not my default payment. How can I change this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Season Premiere of @switchbacksfc football show in the books! thanks to @Shanetane and balla8_11 for joining me, gr… https://t.co/FrtRM8sFjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Linden Yard Fleet Operations in Brooklyn, NY https://t.co/7twwORZ7lP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of our little Malia (on the right) and @Miss_Sugg1st class at @FEShseIN for putting on an art show and addres… https://t.co/4m4Zp0GDit]]></document><document><![CDATA[These numbers sound right. And not because we have said 50-50. 😏#Think2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missmiafaith OOOHHH NOOO TORTUROUS...MUST BE A LIBERAL OWNER-HA..JK NAH PROBABLY A PRO-RIGHTS...INCLUDING BIRTH OWNER😉🙄🤨😅😃🐣🐶🐕🐩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@datechxtremist @NukleaR92 @Techlife32 @youo082501 @holman1124 @yordyords @ttwiitch @ivaylo_belchev @sherifhanna… https://t.co/9cjTi1C5WU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family came from Cuba in 1958, fleeing tyranny mysteriously they are Trumpers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day, Another night, Another fuckingbattle in my mind, a lot of love, a lot of hate, a lot who want to see m… https://t.co/m1JE6XS6vV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hungry? In Northville, MI this morning? This might help! #Breakfast #Northville #NorthvilleMI #Food #Foodie… https://t.co/jDb78O4jYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @SenWarren I have to point out the obvious: #Bernie2020 has been doing that and it never stopped him from rais… https://t.co/uqjZwKreCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rubinafillion @AOC @SenWarren @SenSanders And nearly half think they pay too much in taxes. Hmmm, who do ya think… https://t.co/IWoatuCnrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayPea2018 @keyboardman100 Of all the people that replied, none of them agree with you. success rate of zero. that… https://t.co/W1wtQx9F8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few days late but Happy Anniversary ratiobeerworks !! • • • • • #Ratio #RatioBeerworks #Denver #RiNo #CraftBeer… https://t.co/Npp0p7c1nU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klcombs95 Doesn’t make the list, while ATL sits at 8. However, Chicago comes in at 8th worst in the US. https://t.co/aA2K2eyja9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrxChad Thanks Chad, me as well sir. ‘‘Twas a rough night yesterday for me. Just kinda reality kicked in. Yet it w… https://t.co/lSa1L8oa90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeLibby2 It worked fine against Capone. And Capone never left prison. At least not vertically]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @DanAbramsSXM Show with @danabrams, @TomMorrisJr1 &amp; @Sean_C_Larkin is LIVE!! - @SXMPOTUS | @SIRIUSXM 🚓👍📱😀 #LivePDNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great! Hopefully they’ll find out about https://t.co/EzRffTECzU where many such petitions are being compiled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s ok for people who were once part of your life to just be part of your past. (no, this isn’t about you)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ringer @ktjazz14 @fosterdj3 Screw nba AND nfl ...  let’s make the games less physical... cause that was never an i… https://t.co/AwNzXGvBx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is your adventure buddy?  The one who you can’t leave home without?  Mine is @arharleybabe and always my… https://t.co/QSZQYUqmdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinsonWoodrow Saturdays are a good time to play live if a little far away .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oneday... 🎧 Incredible by Future on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/uBxN46dUAC https://t.co/bsDWIqNmsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll call you Mommy after you shoot me outta your womb, take care of me when I'm sick, and prostitute to make sure I'm fed and clothed...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The product placement on @DrPhil is just so ridiculous it’s embarrassing. I actually used to respect this guy lol.… https://t.co/E3OYOzSlOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Wow...no more @cnn , @MSNBC , @CBS , @ABC. , @NBCNews. ...only @FoxNews will survive in the next 6 years? . . #sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realRoseIzzo @tomgreenlive @CBSBigBrother @CBS @nypost @Kato_Kaelin @AOC I'm all for it. I say bring back tom green!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesignationSix @TheRynheart @Arbys @Starbucks @McDonalds @Applebees @redlobster @IHOP I’m out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Were you able to complete the chocolate-eating scenes in one take? #loveromanceandchocolate @hallmarkchannel @IamLaceyChabert]]></document></documents></author>