<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics @Top_Sergeant Who the hell IS this KY hillbilly??!! How did he EVER get elected??!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who reigns supreme as the quintessential Hollywood heartthrob of this era?  https://t.co/Vd9HMFPeeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is awesome @DHarp100mH! Growing, birthing, and nursing a baby is a billion times more commendable than having… https://t.co/AZ0xSq22BK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I volunteer! I was once between the ages of 8-12 and am an experienced skater! 💁🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaysonjenkins10 @horiMahato @RealSaavedra Exactly, do you think just maybe that is what the Dems want?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Ilhan Omar your impeachment is inevitable.  Immigration fraud is illegal (marriage to a sibling to obtain him… https://t.co/5Q1SfbGTRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love city girls. But I love Jt. Caresha Ight but JT is where it’s at. Caresha could’ve been locked up😭 #freeJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greencapt You’re the sweetest, but I DO ask them for their support &amp; opinions &amp; such]]></document><document><![CDATA[#orgy #orgymusic #prettyinkinktour #seattle #showboxsodo #band #concert #music #tour #againstthegrainphotography @… https://t.co/o0FYgz73h3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_Legend1976 I talked to her yesterday. She needs to speak with you privately https://t.co/JU5TVIgtBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RohitKachrooITV It is unclear? When these waves of ISIS brides to be and aspiring freedom fighters started, severa… https://t.co/eUCTCQJ4HA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Charlotte, NC? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/PkpTvmcY5v #Sales]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Brain* 9AM: fine  12PM: a lil hungry  5PM: hungry, but still ok 11PM onwards: HUNGER HUNGRY FOOD Food NOm@NOM brea… https://t.co/b9rBEh8pFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nelsonthenupe1 😂😂😂 you was, I just thought about you when I saw the boots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw into an apartment that had a plant corner with special light fixtures, and a Peloton bike and honestly it’s peak DC millennial.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely kills me when someone thinks they know someone based off social media. Just because you're a mess who ca… https://t.co/3lvbGFtt6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[.my Favorite Band, Out Of Israel. Very Happy to Wake to @YoniEliavUS  &amp; “Funk Medley 2016”. Thanks to My DJ… https://t.co/TOa9zsrCtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just in...Harrisonburg High School Blue Streaks Band Assessment results: (drumroll please) straight SUPERIORS.… https://t.co/zsysVSzybk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @realDonaldTrump Maybe the problem is you didn’t know how to be a president!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm playing this at the animal shelter where I work and now I have perplexed shelter cats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning, when I ignored my alarm too many times, I almost skipped my class at @ilovekickboxing ... almost. So… https://t.co/PprF5KcVdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepLizCheney your hypocrisy is astounding when your president has protected and has been racist, antiSemitic, anti… https://t.co/zPRAv7gHL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gary10173 @realDonaldTrump No you would rather support illegals with housing, food stamps, healthcare.  What a moron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed! Glad @DomEnergyVA could contribute. 1st phase open this Fall. Thanks to @MarieAlbiges for sharing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspired by the most amazing room of #RadicallyGenerous females that are funding phenomenal female entrepreneurs. T… https://t.co/1XLIZpFeVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t sleep. I’m wide awake and I’ve tried everything but running a mile. Hopefully exhaustion kicks in soon beca… https://t.co/gtPla3bUYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickABC13 “I never heard from the mayor’s office.” *you didn’t contact the mayor’s office *you contacted Public Wo… https://t.co/qDDJ6BcH5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beauty of the Ozarks lies in how easy it is to imagine days gone by - roads traveled by horse and buggy, travel… https://t.co/a4O9kwcSkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna give someone’s son the world but I’m always taken for granted 😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill Cosby in jail  Priest just Moved 2 ANOTHER CHURCH 2 RAPE CHILDREN AGAIN Is JUSTICE EQUAL  @ToneXComedy… https://t.co/ISMMZNU0Pa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took a nap at 3PM and set my alarm@for@tommorow just incase. That’s the definition of college]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Earthjustice @LADWP @MayorOfLA This is so awesome. 👍 Meanwhile #POTUS is still a shill for the coal industry 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect engagement❤️ I couldnt be more happier it was all caught in pictures! #4MoreMonthsUntillWeDo #Engagement https://t.co/V7TEJgM7Be]]></document><document><![CDATA[falling asleep cuddling my pashmina + watching planet earth = a great way to end the night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kates4cubbies @slwein @MrFrankShirley @george4593 Kate, you might be fortunate enough to not have experienced this… https://t.co/7pEf7Ge0Bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abalsd Credit for this should go to @LSTupdates and all of @kpmcentee hard work gathering and sorting the data.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's Grateful Thought: Grateful for opportunities to help others ♡ #TGT #todaysgratefulthought #bepositive #thinkpositive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAGS_Lucas @HVHSOfficial @elizabethtonhs 🤷🏽‍♀️ he just said no.. it was between quarters too.. people always compl… https://t.co/oMZxRDAsWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[only Brad Pitt wears Tom Ford and Yeezys like Brad Pitt https://t.co/bgzYjGczw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarySpot @MitchGarver @kgib44 @whatwouldDOOdo So thankful everyone is safe, but how scary!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolsports @SLynn46 wasn’t an O lineman but a linebacker and played middle school basketball once...has the re… https://t.co/HqOZXs8ffS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wvwcswimming #bobcatsonawarpath #mecWINNERS @ C T Branin Natatorium https://t.co/UbgxJMsPUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to If You Want It To Be Good Girl (Get Yourself A Bad Boy) by @backstreetboys on @PandoraMusic… https://t.co/GhFxsm3mRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jonas Brothers came back together and the SS Wildcats are going to state. WHAT A WEEK IT HAS BEEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@criscyborg Baby has no fear of the lioness  @Amanda_Leoa #CyborgNation #CyborgVsNunes2 #Gofundme #3mill let's make it happen!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans will lose with this platform in 2020.@realdonaldtrump, thanks to your gag rule, millions of people who… https://t.co/nMOizf7lJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's Wrong with These Photos?! #funniness #laugh #smile #merry https://t.co/p30x8m88Ph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Math homework tonight: $300 million divided by 10 years, four of which are healthy = where is my glove again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Papi for your teachings and guidance on keeping our traditions alive ❤️ #coahuiltecan #texas #native… https://t.co/sxvoRDfcPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday’s sunset was absolutely beautiful...cold, but beautiful. https://t.co/pH4t0tJzKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad// the soldier pics are really cute but they're just making me sad bc I'm a dumb bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Samantharhill This is why you should never talk to strangers or to anyone for that matter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honest to god can’t get over at how incredibly handsome @benhardy0291 is 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beautymechanic_ like it literally makes me nauseous idk how people watch that shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[I of course have to join in on celebrating National #LoveYourPet Day! Here’s my little bestie. https://t.co/V46hvgn1n6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajonsiegirl420 @Artizzahn @JonnyRotten1714 @SweetlySmiles @Carreenv1 @rustman_the @laurajax1 @james_bong13… https://t.co/napYfF8uj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjmclaughlin So frustrating..... especially when you find out it’s a bigger problem then just a local pharmacy. It… https://t.co/PwUGQ9C0Ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sug_knight Girl you think hey soul sister is bad. Try the album afrer California 37.  So different from their old… https://t.co/ZfEumKFdBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I were to get Dragon Writing software my work would go from "She crept closer, watching the water drip down his… https://t.co/0Xe9Iozwq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sox_leo @jluna56 @cindymccain @strathglass7982 @michellemalkin @SenJohnMcCain Do you think we can become the hands… https://t.co/rdwHEKo6nY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thereisanocean @mainedcm Hahaha how many times did she show that she care? Boracay blog, Valentines letter.. jusmi… https://t.co/nf93LCAzRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[alright every time i start bein a lil psycho i know it’s time for a nap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please RT to spread the wordNSC staffers privately shared evidence of possible illegal acts by Trump administration… https://t.co/4NY6h1RLId]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 1941, war rages. She has dreams of a seat on the NY stock exchange. But she’s fallen for her boss. He’s destined… https://t.co/hvpu1m93zq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkSalter55 @NicolleDWallace And let’s not forget @IvankaTrump lied, too. They are a family of liars. #Deplorable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bus update: Two buses to MK in the last seven minutes, none to anywhere else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timwagner66 And your mom is looking down upon you saying that you could never disappoint her]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope my dog doesn’t have to get surgery 😥 everyone please pray for my baby 🙏🏻🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perdón por ser esa persona que grita “bebesita” en la oficina, no lo puedo evitar 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinRoberts @JussieSmollett @danabrams @sunny You too are a victim of his crime. He tried to use you knowing you… https://t.co/REUmsVyzUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am going to be the person who brings the heating pad to #ACPA19. I don’t think it will be nearly as popular as… https://t.co/voFwRXhk15]]></document><document><![CDATA[گفت‌وگو با آناتولینماینده حماس: هماهنگی ما با ایران در مقابله با چالش‌های مشترک «عالی» استhttps://t.co/Pvij1uG01m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askjillian Sending u a tight hug...love u attitude!! U are a bad azzzzz!!!! #friendinmyhead #Prayingforu 💕🌼🌸🌝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 15th Birthday to my beautiful first born, the one who made me a mom and challenges me everyday. I love you… https://t.co/Vl7MYRQqXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super pumped to be back in #Roswell this week at @TheLibertyNM !! https://t.co/ClzbQcD6fJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATT You guys suck ! Have brand new phone and have no service at home most of the time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @FirehouseSubs in Portland, TX w/ @treylexisdad https://t.co/0bxReVJPw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is literally the dog and cat version of this Marylin Monroe photo. #greenwithenvy #sojelly #envy #pug #cat… https://t.co/YtN8w1ahT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget we lose an hour of sleep At 2AM on Sunday. So Saturday night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Artists get the most direct money from merch sales so if you love the artists, buy their official merch]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just told my roommate that her disabling her Twitter is hurting our friendship and I’ve never seen such a look of sadness on her face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bd is honestly so annoying saying “I’m NOT a parent” when I’m the only parent that is actually present in his life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact about me. I LOVE collecting coffee cups. My cabinets are too full of them so it’s a struggle to not buy an… https://t.co/c6kABJlfJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot to post pics from Tuesday advancing from zone but we have district tomorrow!!! https://t.co/IuUTjjjhdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now the paczki are getting filled and powdered #yum  This batch is raspberry @NTVNEWS https://t.co/feZIEOiH6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarvemupJames Whoever came up with it is right.  The term 'pro plague' fits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crisayelin @royito_oh @diariobasta @Kaffievillano @telenovelo @NovelaLounge Hay gente del espectáculo que no acept… https://t.co/SlsWYfifVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp There can't be a resolve when this administration won't admit there is a problem..... SHAMEFUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnakeOilPrez Well there is Donald Trump JR who is running for president]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and pup watching the breakups... @colton @BachelorABC @BarefootWine https://t.co/De8Lyyv501]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamilleHammer lmao they gotta try every filter and post allllll of them too 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samanthayi @maushoo @andreyi Anybody else up making up impeachment scenarios? 3:04a]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so damn over the Creed II movie commercials when watching Sec plus. It’s been done into the damn dirt. Stop it already, Sylvester!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Service Honor Guard consisting of @AmeriCorps (including @AmeriCorpsVISTA &amp; @AmeriCorpsNCCC) members,… https://t.co/0ASfxd3Ihp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mickeysooner @TheVOLColonel “Captain or no captain: right now we’re just two assholes lost in the woods.”😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WineFoodGuide @TheSavvyChef1 @WineCheeseFri @DivaVinophile @jflorez @_drazzari @SashaEats @jimofayr @damewine… https://t.co/n4SAueN90K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesHMcLaren Answering your response tweet to me, @JustinTrudeau has also done this in only 3 years. It's a parti… https://t.co/U5edwRYRN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDunlo @PAMSPanthers Whoa!  I’m not sure my adult-level of self-confidence can handle this...but up to the attic… https://t.co/N88CMHwiY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[A generation in BOLD pursuit of King Jesus. /// It’s a wonder my heart didn’t actually explode this weekend. 🤩… https://t.co/sCkLcfFJF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[*my son to me as we are watching #HowToTrainYourDragon #TheHiddenWorld* That's the Hidden World 😌]]></document></documents></author>