<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Buccees then the highway. Back to the land where dreams go to die.  But imma make it look sexy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As some who suffers from anxiety, some people's anxiety rubs off on me, making mine worse, and those are people I c… https://t.co/f6SIRPYfGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker Once a criminal or crime boss always a crime boss and criminal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonCarbine @glennkirschner2 @MDMJD @maddow @NBCNewsTHINK @MSNBC @WhiteHouse @FBI @CivilRights @CNN @AP @thehill… https://t.co/jeEf1wY11E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch with an old friend. 友達とランチ。  #lengthwisebrewing #chilisize #ギネス認定の人 #221センチ 場所: Lengthwise Brewing https://t.co/5FHrY1vFdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[A👏🏼MEN👏🏼 never again in MY LIFE will a guy control my life like this. This shit is abuse and it’s controlling and i… https://t.co/y59xkaoKEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[welp @Morning_Joe nails it. "We can talk about it" (we just can't actually DO it) FFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good to be with others of like minds. #stjohnlutheranchurch @sbegemann @AnthonyBegemann @Adamleid]]></document><document><![CDATA[#grateful #love #blessed #happy #gratitude #thankful #happiness #inspiration #nature #travel #success #summer… https://t.co/Ocyf2eON2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me hype myself up cause a bitch is finally feelin like she gettin somewhere 👏🏼👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timing has never really worked out for us. Things are happening at a really crappy time. It's potential for good st… https://t.co/XcRm37zFxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously. This would be a GAME CHANGER for the work I do with teens 😭😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just food for thought... If dumb Donald aka #45 did not hang on every word that came out of poisonous Putin's mouth… https://t.co/ITdjOwRwBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gebr71 @JohnDePetroshow I just never thought we would become so uncivilized]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalloryLPickett @NWSBayArea Thanks @MalloryLPickett ! I agree that averages may become increasingly meaningless wi… https://t.co/QhBbtgsd96]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get it... why would I fight to find parking in CCNorth to purchase a book https://t.co/4Cp3DcvwJe would shi… https://t.co/PRtAz6wzLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwayneklein @RoyalRogers Absolutely ridiculous to perform like they have this year and then become incredulous whe… https://t.co/imDz59gp0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gaialor95blog @TwitterFood I understand and respect people who have celiac .. it is the ones who don’t have celiac… https://t.co/UVY0swAn78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando Rio Roma dice “eres la persona correcta en el momento equivocado”... I feel it 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @SenateDems Does he know anyone with that much brain power?  I doubt it, h… https://t.co/GsPpWssDJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day Two! First time in Duluth for me... totally love it! 💜❄️#northshoremn #springbreak2019 @ Duluth, Minnesota https://t.co/O2HWnLvv0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msmariapreda Aww will you tell them I said hi and tell Mister luca that I said he’s a cutie and that I love him an… https://t.co/k2xSOs56p0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWitherspoon It sounded like she said she was quoting someone. Do you know who it was?]]></document><document><![CDATA[very openly eating canes while studying at starbucks... forgive me father]]></document><document><![CDATA[That breakdown @rkelly had I kinda don’t blame him for it. How would you feel if you got millions of people judging… https://t.co/YJAa9JNTpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNMcGee I agree. I have wanted her to succeed because of that.. but it’s just not happening]]></document><document><![CDATA[One last look before Bill shoveled #minnesnowta #snowmageddon @ Minneapolis, Minnesota https://t.co/Yx6JE995qN]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this happened today.  Thank you Rev.  #nosepiercing @ Pittsburgh Tattoo Co. https://t.co/z8o89FUqp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[ive decided im going to giving up coffee for lent.... coffee you will be missed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vcspalon @realDonaldTrump Always has been before.but @realDonaldTrump  does what the hell he wants. PS- hope REM sues the hell pcmfot,]]></document><document><![CDATA[He might have said his name was Markell but that sounds like my daddy 🤔😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[one of my babies today came in with pigtails so then all the little girls came to me to give them pig tails and my heart soared]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bersi_ Straight up. Johana pulled out the GIF and I nearly passed out but didn’t want to make a scene.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Safely landed. One of the bumpiest flights I’ve bern on but all is forgotten now! @jetblue #sxsw (@ Austin Bergstro… https://t.co/hADFzWlGYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannaASanford @UW_MBB @AustenEverettFD @David_Crisp31 https://t.co/wSTNZ1Vytw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was in 1st or 2nd grade trying to be all tough in my jean jacket, some mean girl walked by and took someone's swe… https://t.co/EXl2COQqf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi @BarbC1947 😂😂😂😂😂  I'll bet he is nominating himself.   What a loser.  What a big f'n loser.  @Sen_JoeManchin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandzBobbi @ProudResister @realDonaldTrump I don’t get it either. This is all mentally exhausting. 😜😜😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissAromatic @ladydrac1111111 Don't just stand there. Help me take down these clothes for Christ's sakes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gzusscripes1 @brainwashedur @Betterw05759703 @joefaz @realDonaldTrump @CNN 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a privilege to sit at a table of active and engaging women and rep girls in our community with… https://t.co/369iA5ADbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN This guy is a rigger why would you go on TV knowing what you will be asked Like what is the rate of taxes the… https://t.co/e3BEp5PZLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstebanSonsoles @TobiasMenzies @amaranta75019 @kbaryaacov @Lizetteagenbach @Lornesgoldhair @MargieWhitby… https://t.co/zyKur0nakH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiovanniSTriana @DemriScott Negatory, captain. Red pepper flakes. A far superior topping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You don’t seem to be hurting financially now eh ? But you want the rest of the country to live by the rules of… https://t.co/ALzL0KzGIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt CASEY rescued by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from Po Village #DogMeat #Farm #SouthKorea   She is very sweet and playful… https://t.co/h5PRTh7LBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Trudeau disappointed by #JanePhilpott resignation, interrupted by heckler at rally.   Hey Justin! 😂 https://t.co/LFE6s7NTLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fox12oregon #Fox12Unstoppable never ending winter https://t.co/0bqpLA2egB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soupelina @KatyMontgomerie @luddym @JuniperTheSloth If you lose to a trans woman for a medal. The trans woman was… https://t.co/VabRdqCGV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougDavidsonYR @EBraeden Are you back for good? I hope so. Y&amp;R fans have missed seeing Paul and you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you everyone for saying something kind, and my son also appreciates it💝💝💝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyResist @TheRickWilson I am clinging to this also. I can’t envision a former AG protecting Trump. But, then, I remember Rudy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my days be soooo long and tiring and stressful.. which is why I call my mom everyday lol I be needing to talk about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best part of my job is when other people get to see the awesomeness of our students-athletes. @ODUWrestling… https://t.co/J8eRdCNLJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Dirtier than the Hudson”- LJ #classic #figures #cocktail #delicious #dirtymartini #vodkamartini #rhodeisland @ Bas… https://t.co/d4RJpA9ngM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The establishment against trump and his agenda includes republicans I’m not sure how people don’t get that this rea… https://t.co/4u2fSlWHHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leewwiisss22 I’m not the one who wants a milkshake https://t.co/XdSU0Ui0Rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the first day I saw you on that piece of wood in that barn in Medina to this last day when I told you I would… https://t.co/pfnqsGHA54]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beccahallstedt I sleuthed it and you should have your invite on FB. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattbrode @MonsoonCon @Gregtucson @SirlinJohn @jperez1690 @StephWeaverTV @WaldrefWeather @KristenKeogh… https://t.co/KcSCvQW3wv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imbecisa Acordando às 2 da tarde e sem comer desde ontem fica fácil né 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photograph this Again- First taken last year, second taken all the way back in 2010. :) Used a Nikon for both but d… https://t.co/KWgqDeKYch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellzBellzzah @RobertJohnDavi @GiselleSmith19 I'm for hitting the streets!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we talk about how Main Street will always be the first runway I walked]]></document><document><![CDATA[#love #yoga #hanuman #instagood #photooftheday #spirituality #healing #mogulinterior #indiangod #yogainspiration #… https://t.co/VEVo9p4RNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[We always resented our moms for making us go to bed, but they were right. Thank your mom for her service. Texting h… https://t.co/FcvxvcK5K1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, last one!  Hilarious!  Enjoy!! #EddieIzzardTour  Eddie Izzard  Noah's Ark Sketch From Stripped https://t.co/WKnzVPAfRi via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Captain Save-A-Hop by @FullCircleBrews @ Dunbar Brewing — https://t.co/wW7XZS2jUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greg, my Uber hero in Portland, waited while I went to two stores to solve a wardrobe malfunction AND then contacte… https://t.co/k891lZWsrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom texted me saying that when we’re in Georgetown today that she wants to go to the famous steps from The Exorc… https://t.co/GyLluIi4L0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Postcards are going out! #RealEstate #MedinaOH #MedinaOhio #WelcomeHome @ M. C. Real Estate https://t.co/GE6OZg6qEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day!!! ❤️ Hope you are off to a lovely start!! I’ve been stuck on red lately which fits right in… https://t.co/j1Y0OfniYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge not least you be judged.  But remember.  Your opinion of me is none of my business.  haaniy5252 #repost… https://t.co/0clJYHe4QP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenlgeiger1 @kingmanmarie39 @MSNBC Keep waiting for more voters to notice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComedyHeather Sending love to you and shooting daggers at the insurance company.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so horrible!!! This is in no way funny at all. Kids should NOT be seeing this in their videos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Browse Encyclopedia Britannica Quizzes https://t.co/CvBKyAJj6h via @britannica]]></document><document><![CDATA[I called it from the start! Joey is The Rabbit! I have been an NSYNC fanatic way too long to not recognize that voice 🙌 @realjoeyfatone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wcnc why can't people buy their own cars with they money that they make legal.  It may take a while to save for it… https://t.co/tGp9lxP7LX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain The View constantly cuts you off.i guess they don’t value your opinion. Joy is a rude miserable woman… https://t.co/JDziaGKElE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamToque8 @BringerOfRain20 Awesome, it is fun to see him crush those balls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agent: Ma"am, I'm going to have to pat down your crotch. Are you sensative anywhere down in that area? Me: https://t.co/zs4Npszf03]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland finding the black boxes may be tricky because they could be lodged in the mud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh NO, it can be ending so soon. Only about 10 min. left.   #CrosswordMysteries @hallmarkmovie]]></document><document><![CDATA[girls with super long hair who cry when they cut off 2 inches know how to fight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA When I was a prosecutor, I would dismiss a case if there was no reasonable likelihood of conviction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing is more satisfying than coding something and having it actually work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cause parking garages have good lighting? Not bad for 29.  . . . . . #instamakeup #makeup #makeupjunkie… https://t.co/aXMCPyBWdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @BFlyBeauty2 with get_repost ・・・ So excited “TODAY IS THE DAY”queensofcurvesswimwear will be having its 1st… https://t.co/wTaISCNKxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePassageFOX I love the show. It’s great to see Gosselaar back. Saniyya, you rock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennis_tabella @SerpaPserpa2004 FIRST let’s save the baby humans! Pro-Life! Pro-woman! Pro-child! https://t.co/1oxQQz7Nkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Weeknd - Sidewalks ft. Kendrick lamar https://t.co/5igAXX1Sy5 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ange_kh9 @TonyRobbins Damn Ange! What a day to remember!!❣️  I hope @TonyRobbins wasn’t to turned off by… https://t.co/K6gVrne5sA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump #WilliamBarr_Is_AG? Oh, #MrImperialPresidency? #Mr19PageMemo? Mr. @nytimes? @WSJ? Hey,… https://t.co/eHwZV1cyzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can spring break come any faster ? I’m ready for Florida and to get tatted up]]></document><document><![CDATA[back in the day if you had a Avi that wasn’t you they called you out to be a catfish I sure hope that shit is over now  *avi isn’t me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BartleySandy @TrueDetective @HBO So true.   I have had to back it up a few times to see what he says]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tvton #hospitalinfantildelascalifornias #25años en Televisa Tijuana Oficial https://t.co/fjPNvPZVyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some {touristy} things from Portland so far! 😜📚😋🍩🌤 https://t.co/ltxa1Mb2zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[AT BLUNCH 😘🍃👩🏽‍🎨 🎨 CannArt Culture Art Show Miami is brought to you by blunchevent Miami, a celebration of Art and… https://t.co/iCkANu4Nc0]]></document></documents></author>