<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[One year ago today I received my bone marrow transplant from sax_bro1234567890 Today I’m am so so proud to announce… https://t.co/LAhDH9ie3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[I, along with @mgulledge, will be headed to Montgomery County for the C3D8 girls final between Lutheran SC (23-2) a… https://t.co/adcwDqfIEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrichhcirM @SenDuckworth @POTUS Yeah, that’s convenient... but to lay that issue at his feet, you also have to rec… https://t.co/UUjmdbKTTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MFBeltrones @PRI_Nacional Con edad para merecer,dirían nuestros abuelos. Ya es tiempo no de la tercer edad; sino d… https://t.co/gTanDDwavX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Winkky I got to pull up with my own product or you got allat handled?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real Giants fans can careless about Pablo pitching. This is supposed make everyone smile and be excited. While the… https://t.co/GEIopBZA5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Labatt Blue by Labatt Brewing Company at @barclayscenter — https://t.co/0ULWcz2VyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had to type a list of all my devices with their software versions  That took a while 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShinGokaiRed @HalfTangible Not really surprised by this. Social workers have enormous power over families in the courts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy juega @FCBarcelona x @realvalladolid x @ESbeINSPORTS LIVE con @Jaimefmacias #BarçaValladolid 230pmET-1130amPT los esperamos!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This feels like a bit of a ripoff of Olivanders but should still be pretty cool https://t.co/NOHwC76iIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perlmutations This entire thread is full of fan boy sycophants. The slobbering over Obama is really gross. Perlman… https://t.co/jSiIjXvzpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to philly @Bharper3407 can’t wait to celebrate down broad st with you! #Phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[2016 undeniably had too many bops that are still highly played today 🤷🏽‍♂️🤷🏽‍♂️🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[India says its forces carried out airstrikes on terror camps in Pakistan  https://t.co/BvWB5OzSMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“[Pompeo’s Statement] was extraordinary [..] Set aside the perverse incentive that countries with nuclear weapons w… https://t.co/8690RFaVIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lbjamesharden It wouldn’t be so bad if they at least had a none of the above option.  I love Harden but you could… https://t.co/bV9qdKr2jY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We won a 75" TV at Costco today just for shopping, so shout out to them lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 CPC kickoff. No big previous winners at my table and the two big stacks are to my right. Only negative is tha… https://t.co/4LyRJukVcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drivelinebases @esim3400 @SBriend97 @PitchingNinja @OneGun45 https://t.co/s9SPVTsqtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had such a fun night at the #beauxartsball. Thank you to everyone who came out to support such an amazing organiz… https://t.co/wL72kptlSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im a good ass workout partner, I need somebody to match my energy so we can kill shit in the gym!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hgills16 All he has to do is stand and listen to someone speak and I'm loling all over myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Undeniably my favorite Digimon. He desperately needs more spotlight officially. Great job!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a ride that heard a P!nk song and thought it was Britney Spears and started talking about her lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michperezof @EstadioAzteca Un verdadero aficionado no abandona por más decepciónado que este , todo equipo pasa po… https://t.co/TtkIxONa8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone answer this for me in all honesty. do i be looking good or do i be looking ight or just be looking plain ugly?? 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rsmithecu @F3LilMermaid @Asbypirate @F3ENC @Asbypirate crushed it. #qJuice was flowing!! 11’s, then the PAXpaid ou… https://t.co/bpFlcAPAMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @McCluerNorthHS and @NerinxBBall from last night district championship game in Robert’s Gym. Goo… https://t.co/1bgc8KaWps]]></document><document><![CDATA[19 DAYS until Prettu Little Liars: the perfectionists and I. Am. Screaming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Princeton sparkplug Ballard, pt G, fouls out with 2:21 left and Tigers down 3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Devils need some top talent help in general but especially on defense. #NJDevils]]></document><document><![CDATA[Depression and anxiety will always be a roadblock, preventing me from being the person I dreamed of becoming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One one one!! Mom &amp; son. #FBCGFLC #HoopLife #TheNathanChronicles @ Kettering, Maryland https://t.co/CFfMcWavOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waltshaub Please provide names of those receiving kick backs from Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlantSync @CecilUforia @mcBrinkincine Regardless of a changing climate the damaging effects of road salt, sunscald… https://t.co/mWjm8YtMp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoddessofGrain @TCHedger @FatF1nger Having a hard time following along @FatF1nger blocked me https://t.co/PRhXZcC4UK]]></document><document><![CDATA[payge always tells me how beautiful I am and she makes me feel like I’m the prettiest girl in the world and that al… https://t.co/RAGjQ39ieE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go home duckies!! @BeaverWBB is tops tonight in Corvallis @Gill_Coliseum !! #GOBEAVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatrinaPierson I will was just named the CEO of Smollett 2020. See ya at the ballot box Kat. We are gonna kick your ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering if Attorney Laney Davis wrote the Fictitious Story Michael Cohen is reading before Congress.  JUST LOOK AROUND AT THOSE IN CHARGE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oooh and i got coats, hoodies, lotion, body wash. Im set for anything homestly 😂 i just forget to bring shit back inside the house]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jthomas3001 “Some people later told me I was ranked first among the apostles...”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think if everyone stop looking for racism in everything things would be better. Like not everything deserves a re… https://t.co/1gMJ9BfHYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just looked at the best picture from the last 5 years and it’s the worst best picture in the last 5 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I would’ve pushed myself enough so my son could get quick lil lessons like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewGillum you have all my condolences on the passing of your father! My winter family supported your governors… https://t.co/KclvOVnAPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Supermoon, 2019's biggest and brightest, will light up the #sky https://t.co/CKoBVYPnhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchellJensen7 @dimarzo_chad @tammigaw @AdamSchefter @DukeU That’s his choice. He could actually attend classes p… https://t.co/H5jqP9Ka9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am out working chasing around bugs and mice in the middle of a snowstorm. Jeez I'm glad I didn't go to law school or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I cannoooot wait til this overly sensitive/triggered by everything era is over]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiero sexo oral con contigo amor bello a love ❤ me gustas mucho sexy boy Hot simpático blonde 💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great graphic showing how the top companies have changed on a global basis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrFan @dmewing47 Let me start with one of my rare WTF! First, doesn’t Trump know that Independence Day i… https://t.co/t1aUY4aXtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite NBA fallacy is that players openly recruit each other after games by holding their shirts over their mo… https://t.co/sT1RMWy70b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning!!!!  On the way to see Mac McClung and the Georgetown Hoyas!!  Life is good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[MISERABLE drive to work his morning.  Yuck.  Due to the cold rain this morning...you all have my permission to call… https://t.co/CkZSaSfs9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[This!  From the Manafort sentencing doc. A US Congressman??  Who could that be??]]></document><document><![CDATA[List goes down at 8pm. We start with the jokes at 8:30pm. If you want to talk about how UNC swept Duke this year, w… https://t.co/TlsSDGo9Ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGitsVanessa2 @UCandu2 @maryjanesosexy @Mierdafavorita @KendraGirlsonly @Follow_mee18 @Real_Whores @candi_smyles… https://t.co/jQGk6xhIBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissaclaireb @marrowing I was going to suggest https://t.co/MUSr58EaOR but the type you mentioned is a steal! It… https://t.co/7hJqoh3p7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryleynolin @ellawedergren @sportsgirlkait @madilynsiebler you need an around the back start 👍🏀😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ViaCheri @MckeehanCarolyn @JayDog335 @GovMattBevin @reposborne It would help to have a Governor to push the legislature to do so!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanBitterman witness intimidation by a MOC is like jaywalking these days. Sad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter’s class is having a Chick-Fil-A party for Valentines Day.  I’ve got to get over there... I can’t let her do this alone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You woke up this morning with a purpose. Let’s get up, get out and get it done. 🙏🏿 #Blessed #GoodMorning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nwsgator @kidkapital @AustinLieb I tend to like companies that use debt strategically... but I don’t buy the notio… https://t.co/PKO5mm7Gk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont forget: The Trump admin. barred transgender individuals from being service members of the U.S. Military.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derchadmeister This is true. She was uber enthusiastic and held up fingers counting them off and everything. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daechu6 Nah we just flat out lost. The ground passes they played were off target as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @TSA at @Bradley_Airport this morning. From curbside through security in 10 minutes flat! #tsaprecheck #mustbearecord]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her: Have any plans for #ValentinesDay?  Me: Nothing in particular. Go to work, get a drink, cry intensely into my… https://t.co/NBhY9GZBx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my oldest sons wedding day.  I’m excited to welcome my new daughter into the family.   Yes, it’s 4am. https://t.co/UxlWFqez6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[😇🇳🇮Nicaraguan Francisca Ramirez, small business owner, and farm workers leader leader in a Press Conference in Ireland.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss NICKY! https://t.co/iCpaNr9rNn The White RACE German BLONDES👑🇩🇪Women Ar T… https://t.co/b2vJIIQJn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bexofeasttex I mean really doesnt mean much when he could have done that to make it seem he is not racist lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like padre is for ppl in high school, I feel way to old for stuff like that😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remove slug Dems from office. Vote for Republicans to continue to #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJFURMANIAK There isn’t a “boost” option btw. 😉 Just straight up monitoring.  Here’s a velo chart from one of our… https://t.co/mVcTEeQM9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or any time within the last hour of being open. We just wanna go home ://]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surely innovation counts toward greatness? Or does one have to be great technically to even be in the convo?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@palmercharlene1 @rsanderlin @Susan_Hennessey They don’t care. The rule of law has never applied to them. That’s for only us little people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[J'aime bien la citation qui dit que le chien aboie et la caravane passe. Ou plutôt les chiens aboient et la caravan… https://t.co/MqoIzxAtkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:30.3°F WchillLow:30.1°F Wind:0 mph Dir:--- Baro:Rising slowly Rain2day:0.00in Hum:84% UV:0.0 @ 02:30 02/22/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMT Please put last weeks #4 @LaurenDuski #CostumeParty back on the 12 Pack Count Down!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@t3hthirstydog I mean, they traded Mack and what's his face for two 2nds and now getting AB. I'm shocked, it's turning around lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Morning Bill ! 80 Foot tall- 80 foot tall, that's how Big, I want my wall. make it Big , and make it l… https://t.co/iIIkSVB5k2]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gonna build a wall on the east coast now @realDonaldTrump ?   https://t.co/U7SLX9YgSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to train your dragon the hidden world (@ Edwards Ontario Palace 22 IMAX &amp; RPX - @regalmovies in Ontario, CA) https://t.co/Hv6FcmT3to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump approval by voting Republicans is at an historic low of 41%, 75% say Trump is dishonest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @IvankaTrump Or maybe the WWW house? WWW HOusE is legA-L tender for A-ll debts public And privAte WW… https://t.co/zVdWjSDbNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a great Southwest Santa Rosa Health Action Chapter meeting yesterday. More and more collaboration happening… https://t.co/ddhgEjlOKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That has become very obvious particularly CNN, MSNBC, NBC, ABC, &amp; CBS &amp; WSJ &amp; WAPO. ARMY STRONG.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The greatest poem ever written about Batman already exists, Neil https://t.co/Vg5saixeZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The loneliest donut. . #freshfromthescanner #filmisnotdead #contaxt2 #streetphotography #portraitphotography… https://t.co/RYo30oqktW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stizzthewiz @CjWilson850 I know you a young buck, but Rickey Henderson was a problem too!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiptw @UOJim "Despite denying this was a problem for decades and shooting down even moderate solutions, we demand… https://t.co/uELP94yw5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@La_Ney_sha Probably not, but hey, as long as it makes you happy that’s what’s important!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Psalm 46 5 God is within her, she will not fall    God will help her at break of day...  Lord Almi… https://t.co/sg2lFGHnu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 805 Blonde by @FirestoneWalker at @wipeoutbar — https://t.co/vil8nwmvRD]]></document></documents></author>