<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@lizcabrera55 @darylnelson01 @realDonaldTrump Resign from congress. No muslim will ever support Israel, not as long… https://t.co/R20aeN6HM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trail awesomeness in Wasatch pow! #bigcottonwoodcanyon #utahphotoproject #utah #wasatch #utahgram #utahunique… https://t.co/g9TqsdXEFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gwen Stefani🎙 at Zappos Theater in Las Vegas #gwenstefani https://t.co/tOQzIqmLdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys I can’t more strongly discourage you from attempting to run 4 miles the morning after you stayed up until 6 am eating bundt cake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Shows and a new look.  • Pints at the Round Table | The Chris Renne Show • Spotify | Apple Podcasts | SoundClou… https://t.co/uQaLHBJxxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coryprovost I'd imagine they'd order a pizza delivery for the the booking station.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylansmith_15 @DrPhil @DrOz @Oprah @JennyCraig @What I gave up! Best idea yet! Focus on other things!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sold a bunch of #comicbooks to like 12 year old kids. Always make ya feel good when kids are excited to read your b… https://t.co/cB2HwZonia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @CNN Lock stone up lock stone up lock stone up lock stone up lock stone up lock stone up lock stone up lock… https://t.co/npTPE5Z0zh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video: Watch the workout that earned #FSU QB commit @JeffSims_10 QB MVP of the Opening Orlando regional and an Elit… https://t.co/vpiUEA1P2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dadbaddy @debbiepalm44 @zypisfy @zapher134 @SoberHootOwl @MichelleNewDay @BiblePoop @PrinceOfAtheism… https://t.co/O5JiYFT1DR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Offset speaking facts ... I didn’t meet my twins till they where one .. I didn’t know if was they Father]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TysonGamblin What grocery isle did you buy them on? Dry shelf = pantry Cold shelf = refrigerator #puddingproblems @TysonGamblin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lowe's is looking for teammates like you. See our latest #Retail job openings, including "Merchandising Service Ass… https://t.co/lvrxmulsED]]></document><document><![CDATA[What could go wrong? Rules Relaxed for Banks, Giving Wall Street a Big Win @TakeOnWallSt https://t.co/30iObYExmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sorry #moron - I already have something to do on the 4th of July. It’s called the 4th of July.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanRaanan That’s great. A nice kid. But can he throw a medium range ball accurately? Jury is out on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Afternoon at the ballpark @ Peoria Sports Complex https://t.co/TWIY6M4Tro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily Encouragement from God’s Word: God’s redirections are not a distraction. @ Oakfield-Alabama Baptist Church https://t.co/XWvZbavwPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve just been thinking about this and giggling all day I fuckin love these kids]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when my prof assigns a paper weeks in advance and I wait until the last day to do it!!! Ugh my mind!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a while since I’ve been on here and it’s a bit too cold in the shop still so I thought I would show off t… https://t.co/Ggb1yquc1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX35David @Fox35News 2) ...act choreographed by Hannity and  the shameful president  If Alan Samuel Combs were he… https://t.co/t9AuG9s4tS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mobster Don embraces a Hitler tactic -“tell a lie big and tell it often”. It’s a diversionary tactic to distract th… https://t.co/qGGmEWZm17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Construir destruyendo es una mala fórmula, columna "El Juglar de la Red", por Rafael Cano Franco @CanoFrancoR /… https://t.co/LDyOJRcNWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mary Anne Marsh: Trump, not the border, is our national emergency https://t.co/XJxaIwKUpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flyinointment11 @CoolCatCarolena @KinvillePaul @gollum1419_g @mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 More likely had a favor d… https://t.co/4zWbj6Fxbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Streaming Right now!!   @OfficialUGWA premiers the complete #Jungleboy @boy_myth_legend Vs @DaveDutra match from… https://t.co/3x4qhq0kDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GTechYJ @AJCsports Actually need to move the Tech game to once evey 4 years and add a SEC game ro the schedule.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EklecticRose @TitusOneLuv @StanleyRoberts The interior of a store isn’t a public area, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sneak peek from a photo shoot for the Anderson Conference Center. This pic is highlighting the amazing florals of… https://t.co/eSqMa2JTpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcmillan_photo @sdw @sandofsky @halidecamera So what can I do with my right arm and hand till I have my carpel tun… https://t.co/5WaLhlTTWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beat the Turtles. @ Coastal Carolina University https://t.co/Um0eEbLPha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSSportsNet what website is showing the UMD vs UND game since BB game is OT?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kendricklamar I hope there will be a Heart Pt 5 coming. I need 6, 7, 8, 9 etc. Please...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anpalacios5 @TSteegeNFL There are tons of reasons but if you are going to be to ignorant to understand you never w… https://t.co/zZvDOdlaNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No que quien la tiene más culera, Santiago Solari o Nicolás Maduro. https://t.co/9dObAOzhKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Soldier: “ I am a Soldier,I Fight where I’m told and I [WIN] When I Fight” @usarmy  #CoffeeTalk #1st☕️… https://t.co/54AMruvCut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Taeler_Hendrix It solidified Daniel Bryan’s reign, built up Kofi, and made history with a memorable women’s tag te… https://t.co/T5lFc6xvPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MW55 I really don’t like your work in the booth. You sound like a tween. #bemorelikeBenny Grow up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OkiTimes @cellmavin @zappafaye @lhtetrick @TammyJaben @JonMontag @JohanBBT @Just4BeerLovers @wolv54b1 @cedarflats… https://t.co/h8J8e66f7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonPuckett20 to be honest...I was entertaining friends,drinking bourbon and eating Cheetos when I saw the final… https://t.co/2C8J5AxZ9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que bien la pasamos. ☺ #BocadillosCafé #WinterSprings #LiveMusic #MúsicaEnVivo @ Winter Springs, Florida https://t.co/Cs0vuaa7Sn]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the biggest attacks on my life is when one of my friends said “christian I bet you were one of those those p… https://t.co/n6DHkbHau7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shyannesellers3 with 28 points. Reminds me a lot of @TwinsburgTigers' legend Ashley Morrissette. No one can take o… https://t.co/EimATFKdfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I listen to music constantly on @Spotify and often check out artists' bios to get more info/sense of their characte… https://t.co/yfvE41LKQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had the sickest dream of my life, lemme try to fall back asleep I have to be up in 2.5 hours 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmplifyPhilly @atxconcert @djjazzyjeff215 @DjAktive @joshbwc @wxpnfm @sxsaviors @SXUnofficial @SXSWHIPHOP @OpenBarATX 🙋🏼‍♂️🙋🏼‍♂️🙋🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I need to get an actual squad because these fandoms do t appear to have common sense sometimes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DowdEdward He was forced to stage a poorly scripted crime, to dramatically lie and to enlist willing media to prov… https://t.co/ARmnDAyydT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biglesp @bplraspjam It’s a great kit - I saw your review, ordered two and made this https://t.co/MkbSAwsJF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sean McNeil 55 pts (Sinclair College School Record) https://t.co/GmjtHx1XWu via @YouTube Copper high school.🏀🏀🐾🐾🦊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Linguine pesto with chopped tomatoes @ Davenport Lakes, Davenport, Florida https://t.co/q46BbpVmXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicky_A9 Nick? He has a girlfriend and a daughter with said girlfriend... but having said that I could give a flyi… https://t.co/luOGtkv4sJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found a quarter here on my bike ride today @ Herndon, Virginia https://t.co/fQyosX3g6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are going to expect you to live your life a certain way do to certain circumstances, but it’s your expectati… https://t.co/SazSyVFNe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDaniel2033 Worse signing ever. Come on man we can’t have that bad juju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeblow745 Help is available. 12 step program called reaching for reality. Please save those puppies !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real quick, I love my sons Oki and Tama. I love you guys, you’re so cute. You guys are just as cute as you are annoying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@activist360 @AOC @WaysMeansCmte @RepRichardNeal DJT jr is too stupid to rue the day. I hope he getz hate fucked in prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuimos campeones primero en tu canchaaaaa 🎶 @TigresOficial  @luis_beto8 https://t.co/kpeSUatAKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mountain Jam Vol:3 by @roadhousebeer @ Greeley, CO — https://t.co/RqlL9kmPKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Search me, O God, and know my heart: try me, and know my thoughts:  And see if there be any wic… https://t.co/dQYt8eyDdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morrisonicpod @lawyerdogg @graysonson @turneresq @thesocceresq On permanent hiatus now but it was killer while it lasted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VitalVegas @VegasTweetsInfo Far from matching up.1st off it’s listed on W Flamingo Rd., 2nd it reads North Las Vegas..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powers at be are doing to anyone who doesn’t agree. #communism #Liberlism #FreeSpeech #CENSORED @librarycongress ne… https://t.co/xjyen002FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on my first day pride look and oh bitch https://t.co/kc4v9YhbAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goallllllllllllllllllllllll!!! Dylan Thelin crosses it to Sam Daw for the Header Goal!!! Varsity Boys take the lead… https://t.co/fRW3sIkJg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunterLJohnson @CarsonEW24 @AlabamaBSB @coachbrucepearl That’s very generous of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmellon The gloves are off Mellon! I’m telling you, Bubbly is delicious. Who cares it’s PepsiCo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trevor_porath @AaronPeck USU student media? You know Josh Witzel? Awesome kid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JudyChicago &lt;agreed&gt; @ Institute of Contemporary Art, Miami https://t.co/u5pa0opVUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perlmutations @Change We should never forget, nor should we cut the compensation of the first responders. Keep fun… https://t.co/EJIkLSsJK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJohnKatko How about hateful comments against women, non-Christians and blacks?  I would hope it takes those into account as well???]]></document><document><![CDATA[And Bryce Harper wasn't even in the lineup today! #Phillies https://t.co/LlZO81b4LN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The birds chirping make it seem like it's a nice spring day outside... except it's 34*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tercer avance de @Radio_Zocalo #Noticias. Envían a atención psicológica a joven mujer que denunció por violación a… https://t.co/GLtnKtBUVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[See? This should be taught in grade schools. It's easier to teach gun safety with fresh minds. @NRATV @DLoesch  https://t.co/py3y2YJu4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: "It's legal to eat your dog if it dies of natural causes."  Bartender: "One IPA coming up."]]></document><document><![CDATA[the real question is when is @Bharper3407 gonna ring that bell @sixers ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timrabonjr Me during the presentation tonight.... You had ONE job dude. https://t.co/uvVT8Av7Iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might play some lottos tomorrow, but if there’s not a clear direction, I’m out until next week. I might position… https://t.co/nJFp68MLGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@22anddmean @thereddempress_ Nigga im receding, talk to God about that one. Lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best thing about working out in SF gyms is working out in old man sweats while your surrounded by ppl who look like Tron characters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrkambN @guffsafc73 Well that's not leidens problem as some would suggest (not saying you are).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimBridenstine @MarsRovers Rest in peace oppy!   I bet 50 years from now, someone visiting mars with a  brush will… https://t.co/1oF3e2b52g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Souf_Oaklin Ohhhhh...dip that Antoon’s pizza in some ranch and make it edible!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoJacksMBB @dauminator24 Congrats Mike! Very well deserved with all the hard work you've done]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForsythSports Coaches understand it but the schools and communities don’t really get the importance of winning the… https://t.co/rkq8X0tN4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexroze6 @LouDobbs @RepMattGaetz @realDonaldTrump Another corporate loyalist voting for trafficking, teen prostit… https://t.co/YmZjALXYrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sanders doesn't care at all about the progressive left. His vision for the country centers HIM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Texas_Dexter He doesn't care one bit that his feathers aren't colorful yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nada como amanecer con la familia feliz #Amo estos momentos aquí con mi. Papa. Y mis sobrinos LQM. Franklin Palacio… https://t.co/qWoVVDgCQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netter48 @Gypology @midtownexpress @thebeeeez @henz_mark @43324FAN @chevychevelle48 @munk_craig @CamilleCindia… https://t.co/e7MWri1Hgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe @GovChristie Christie had to take a swipe at Cohen - what a prick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noahsebastian @mista_cocks Well this is one hell of a slightly extreme representation of the Conservative Republic… https://t.co/iniYKHTzoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your @SDHSAA State B girls tournament officials! Thanks to a great group who loves to give back. https://t.co/mNO5BtvJzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @1010XL @Ballou1010xl Having flashbacks of big sports news breaking in God's country. Welcome @NickFoles #dtwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also if anyone is in El Reno and wants to bring me some sweet and sour chicken or something I’m up at Redlands’ Royse Ranch starving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to make sure that you ever get close to my children. Dont want you to influence them with your diseased mind… https://t.co/Up7NIhLki9]]></document></documents></author>