<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What do kids do now that there seems to be no Red Cross babysitting course anymore?just wing it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MimaWrites @OaklandPublic OMG! 😍😭 The best surprise! https://t.co/14dRcRpWfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the story of McCrae Dowless, Mark Harris and the election scam in North Carolina district 9 is told I hope the… https://t.co/koqGM6kjrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@___Leliane___  #SHOWNU #ShownuBombardment #BiasBombardment #MONSTA_X #MONSTAX #MONSTAX_Alligator @OfficialMonstaX https://t.co/GlwJIC5rf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[last home game @ 1🏀 come out and support for senior day🌪 @ Lake Erie College https://t.co/z66hEEeaEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[just saw a truck with a “pussy hunter” sticker on their windshield. I want one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I let my cat lick my hand yesterday. Now my skin looks like I stuck my hand in a food processor...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dramarty @RealityAshhole @ReedwiththeRead Why is that woman drinking wine with a straw?]]></document><document><![CDATA[See that face?  That hound will be my boy soon. His name will be Sam. Help us help more greyhounds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Catheri28125754 @EISDMemorialHS @EISDofSA @EISD_LMS I LOVE the new books!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritAirlines crazy how I make an airport purchase and I am forced to pay another carry on fee!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catswithnohope Sorry you have to wait, thankfully you have kitties to keep you occupied 😍🐾🙏💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was having a great #MondayMorning until I visited @usps @USPSHelp at Bryant Park, 23 W 43rd St, NY, NY. The posta… https://t.co/JZg2spOHAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @dnewhook16 and KUA team on winning the NEPSAC Elite 8 tournament!!! You guys were amazing. https://t.co/k9w3pDRNUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBS @NBCChicagoMed @ChicagoFire  I’m Atlanta with direct tv and your channel is blinking going dark then the chann… https://t.co/F4nlJyG33C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also shoutout to @EAWTCU for dealing with the Brussels sprouts and potatoes for me bc I feel like trasshhhhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran’s “The A Team” is the opposite of @the1975’s “She Way Out”...if you know you know]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m using my phone without a screen protector and let me tell you... https://t.co/qtmZg18F9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[GROCERY SHOPPING WITH MY NEPHEW N MY MINI ME💖👧💙👦😍 https://t.co/TkKF8OiC72]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristenD82 @ClayTravis "Aggressive Misogyny?!" What? Bless your heart 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just signed a @theactionnet petition: Ban trophy hunting of polar bears. Sign here: https://t.co/0uGTZJbSTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the opportunity to be inspired by @NiceBikeMark today at #LIM #LIMSposium2019 what a fabulous end to two emotio… https://t.co/MtQ9tUKPtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmysawtelle @RickBatemanJr @BPCCCavs @JSawtelle4 Absolutely! Call 318-678-6015 to register.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nckhui @WCPSS @apexescougars @BriarcliffES @cary_elementary @NorthRidgeES @westcaryimps What is the proposed new time for West Cary?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am voting for @Orlando_CityUK in @TheFBAs for #BestInternationalCreator 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JgSpeight @Reason_Rouser @TImeTurner128 @Olle7Ho @AtheistRepublic Issue is, men dont get to even call it rape, like it says.]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorte. @ Terminal B - Newark Liberty International Airport https://t.co/7Pa89rwjtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wljohnson714 Yes it does. If he runs maybe President will adopt the name for him lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDice @AOC I'm sick of you jerks treating AOC and any woman as they are incompetent. Clearly she is not. What i… https://t.co/y25VpXqUa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chezumk @a_mess26 @ClarksonUniv When I lived in the dorms that cost $12k a year the basement used to flood so bad… https://t.co/jdVi4hJ7DZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie changing the game and making Colton guess if she likes him!! that’s the thing about them tables, THEY ALWAYS TURN😈🌹🌹Yes sister! ha!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @brookevroberts2 have a great day pretty! https://t.co/1GUFvVsZpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOS! @PaulasDonuts our Paczkis are gone! 😩 Please send Fasnachts 😜#DonutEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khamill908 I’m trying to stay as bundled up as possible lol but I’m still freezing! ❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty sure @donlemon said that people who work on morning news shows are not “real” journalists tonight as he… https://t.co/sKPkQuK0FB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow No immigrant who hasn’t fully assimilated and actively supports and advocates for jihadists should… https://t.co/aPtJRBeOER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casspacheco__ @sabrinaiglesia 40$ over 400$ for the trip is a MAJOR DIFFERENCE .]]></document><document><![CDATA[a very crossed @sebastian5tero: i’d still love you if you WERE team edward though]]></document><document><![CDATA[“un pañito con alcohol te va a curar” at this point Im taking any suggestions]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to watch my favorite movie, with my doggies &amp; my candle on 🥰💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[just got a massage and then couldn’t stop shaking. my midwestern body be like “WHAT DA CRAP HOMIE?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomMommyNurseRN @CNN @CNNOpinion You must be smoking crack to come up with that bullshit. 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJPaultjeD @SJB6991 @GraphicsPhd @Game_DevBot @GraphicsPhd is killing it everywhere with the support!! https://t.co/snleajL7wR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA @DonnieWahlberg @NKOTB I just saw it on #NKOTBonGMA  in AZ!!!!! Awesome. I love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are save the dates a thing? Do people actually care about getting those? Lol asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaircaseWhitt Omg I just got why people used to call them brothers...in my defense I refer to Tanner as Tanner an… https://t.co/XeDWIieKr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can everyone @ the President of the United States bc I don't think he gets it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ja0nuy おはこんばんちはです〜。雪が降ってます! 家には問題なく帰れそうです😊　家にパソコンを持って帰るのが重いのでオフィスにいましたが、五時に出る時点で、フロアでは最後の一人でした😂本日もよろしくお願いします!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting a chuckle out of @adamjapko. #designinfluencerscon fun to be a part @white_good @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/3FlEreM46r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reb_452 Yasss!!! It’s over!!! Thank God!!! They both agree!!! 😂 https://t.co/LjyQt33e2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hmgarth14 @GeneralCattis @AndTalitha My dad had Alzheimer’s. After he passed I was glad to have had time with him.… https://t.co/meKx0qeZPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[He admitted he has some trouble hearing the proceedings-strictly to help him hear the case]]></document><document><![CDATA[@numberjoon @saItkath don’t mind me im just here to flex https://t.co/IeId18KBIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacgregorRucker They were too busy trying to pass their corporate welfare tax scam and attempting to repeal Obamac… https://t.co/YXQ7W1cK3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and then came home and did the dishes while i cried just so that i could feel like i accomplished one (1) thing… https://t.co/dzue285zlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson Hell with the nay sayers ...You know in your heart and mind you do your best..and that's good enough… https://t.co/6Zu0Jegj1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathanarussell @DeRouenMgmt @Pastor_Madeline My guess would be thin John 3:16, skip 3:17, double-down on misinterpreted 3:18.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You aren’t gone see black people outside at all at MSU until it gets sunny😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ljpearcewriter Finishing something. It takes time to gather myself together again for a new start.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsJeffHudson @Rowdygirlinmt Fallowing you just for that. The man is a blister upon my city of origin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a continental bfast rn and thinking to myself “man I would hate to work at a hotel......” ...........y’all I work at one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher @realDonaldTrump looks like a kindly grandfather. You look like a pervert. You have a dirty mouth. Who s… https://t.co/YCd7ff7MUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKornacki Steve you need to take into account a lot of America does not have access to REALLY WHATS GOING ON I… https://t.co/RsHArBUKqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bishop Luers Basketball Sectional Pairings... Sectional 23 Class 3A at Bellmont... https://t.co/E2u9GnEA8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToughGuyMankas @Tonithecat32 @vroberts9 @BloomNight2 @lynda3035 @fluffybasil @deborah26449389 @sharon_cantley… https://t.co/XmJhJQTveO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarah_Morris12 @melindajonesart @RedMillES @RMESPrincipal @NclKeros Yes! We have the most magical bathroom now!😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DontCallMeAnt I LOVE that place! I stock up when I go visit Mom in Athens 🤣😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just the tip of the iceberg...we got incredible input through the @ReachNCVoices platform. Thanks for the p… https://t.co/3sQPWm1egF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofiacomenta naoo! to estudando só! fico em san diego até sexta e depois vou encontrar a minha família em LA e dep… https://t.co/aPNaKMYVxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is saying that someone lied the same as calling the person a liar, as some media outlets have said? Please advise.… https://t.co/LRQAirG2Ym]]></document><document><![CDATA[list price for that drug is more than triple the price that Novartis gets in other high-income nations. Novartis sa… https://t.co/1r1KSHOAe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thank you President Trump! July 4th is America's best holiday. Don't hypocrite haters know Obama/C… https://t.co/VYQeAMtScK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took me almost an entire year to get my #Venmo account reopened... You'd think it would be a lot easier to gain access... Geesssh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please let me know why I’m looking up prices for water bungalows in Maldives at 2:30am when I can barely afford gas… https://t.co/l4s3y79ozQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibertyU @WilliamByron @TeamHendrick @Hendrick24Team #LibertyU24 🏁 Hoping to see William put the #24 in VL this season.  #Go24]]></document><document><![CDATA[@souljaboy @MelaninFaves Drake a grown ass man who don't give AF about what nobody got to say and can laugh at himself lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofeyahhh @Highdee95 Wait that's a Wednesday nothing on the weekend? 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reporting live this morning from the White House. https://t.co/olFxroRZxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher Then, we cut the power and cable TV to the White House and the new president takes the limos and Secret… https://t.co/2w4bldOup2]]></document><document><![CDATA[a guy really hit me with the line “I would recognize that smile anywhere” last night. Is it because? that smile is?… https://t.co/ViErpXt9EQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang amusing. #funniness #giggle #smirk #funny https://t.co/HyjhzaXTRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we did a thing... only by the grace of our Lord and Savior! #Godisgood @Lennar @aubrey_eudy 🏡🙌🏼🎉🥰🙏🏼 https://t.co/gmjJq47J97]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/17/2019: This photographer, Enzo, did an amazing job on this photo. @ Baldwin Hills Crenshaw https://t.co/ZaOj1B1fmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpereyra1952 La hija de Chávez es una de las mujeres mas ricas del mundo, que solo visita a Venezuela para que el… https://t.co/rIcp9EwgoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5 of 7 books for 7 days challenge! Nominated by @TheOfficialMrG . My students and I are in the middle of this i… https://t.co/5GTXWlRd0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SundayDiana @jax_persists @BarbaraLevinbb Well I know the Blessed Mother and she is the greatest! https://t.co/YQnHUFb5Ak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their desperate for votes. And absolutely don’t care about the American Citizens who pay their salaries.  They are… https://t.co/PCJXSNxvPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCG_Health My daughter has a painful neuro disorder. She feels like a drug addict, deals with depression and socia… https://t.co/Sfe91cD8ST]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been challenged by the one and only @ymarquez_07 to post pics of 7 favorite books, no reviews needed. Each d… https://t.co/4GRIg5FJAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoungAndTasty @nelgbtc @SienaCollege No, it's the Transgender symbol. ♀️+♂️+⚦=⚧ https://t.co/Nm19o1mwGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk who needs to hear this but,  if a guy wants you, he will make it happen. they go after what they want. at least the guys i like lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning dog walk views of the Roebling Bridge in Cincinnati/N.Ky. This beauty was the prototype for the Brooklyn Br… https://t.co/tXuJfeOsZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lbfirefighters @longbeachpd @longbeachfire @LBSu @csulongbeach Congratulations, Long Beach Firefighters!! Captain… https://t.co/Q0aEuVyPDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally did this w an afternoon class this week - from the dentist’s chair!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whtabtpineapple Well, I mean, I saw the first one when I was a kid. I feel like that is good enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran a good game but a shitty few confrontations between players and I am still up stewing at 2 am eating bad Wendy’… https://t.co/d3m9Yhs2x1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaffAndConquer @yogawithadriene It’s a little thing that makes your smart tv smarter.  I use it to stream YouTube to do yoga.  🧘‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oceannhills Thank you. Following. Can’t wait to read some of your content.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a La Petite Mort by @Super_Mead at @rjstadium — https://t.co/pEeQ34qCTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re having a Summer or Fall wedding when sunset is later in the evening, I’m definitely going to ask you this… https://t.co/z5l39qXWBx]]></document></documents></author>