<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Z- laughing I thought it would take a while C- they don't understand the mirror.  They do not understand chaos.  Th… https://t.co/BTTyxbVlcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s absolute chaos in the Carrier Dome where @SAatSU is expected to be giving away 500 free tickets to the Syracus… https://t.co/K2jMYixV96]]></document><document><![CDATA[Considering Alex IS the Mind Power Host; Positive Thinking and Good vibrations can extend a person's life. KICK ASS… https://t.co/u7rKZHtdns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BikerFunk @ZackMeisel He’ll, I’ll take average compared to what he had been.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cloudyskies #rainydays #sanbernardino #california @ San Bernardino, California https://t.co/O0oNCu9Igv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilisncz @mikeHeiser77 @hayliexcardoza @jayydentweets I present to you, a pupper https://t.co/w91qD5Rxk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so mad i didn’t have an ugly baby i would be roasting tf out of her 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlieBEERS10 That’s a good idea. Yes sir probably didn’t have a clue or it just never showed itself till you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DroppinTheMitts @RedWingsFeed @detroithockey96 Who replaces Jensen on the Wings?]]></document><document><![CDATA[S. Craig Zahler was not impressed with UNCLE SCROOGE AND DONALD DUCK. https://t.co/QhiBEqmZCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though he’s not coming in, we’re gonna wrap up some red velvet cake for him.  #ShootYourShot2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget about #Selfcare for #SchoolPsychologists during #NASP2019 #Spinning #GetIt @Amy_Patenaude @Flywheel https://t.co/oB9TcLymXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#skyfitsheaven @4WTC #skywriting #LookUpNYC #downtown #watertower #silhouette #manhattan #NYC #NYCweekend #home… https://t.co/Ov3JmN1Bwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a lie. @TheHannityShow needs to be investigated. @FBI @RepCummings @RepJerryNadler]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMattKnicks @JordynneGrace Well luckily I'm still here to give you the scoop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The English Govt still think they own the world: UN court rejects UK's claim of sovereignty over Chagos Islands https://t.co/fD1CRwVPhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TroyAle52891286 Maybe this is just the tip of the iceberg!!!- https://t.co/ZEv77jKZPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe it! This is why ex Scientologist slam Scientology!! Free soup and smoothies!!! It’s dastardly!! 😬  Feel b… https://t.co/9MAPDnUZPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[25lbs down. 3lbs to go before @sarahnelsonfm bribe kicks in. #newlaptop #weightloss #myfitnesspal #diet… https://t.co/S0NlofrFzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sergiy Derevyanchenko vs. Jack Culcay in IBF title eliminator on April 13 https://t.co/RkvzgZAxYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realhartman @Ninjabros72 There ya go! Hope ya like it! https://t.co/tr2eDV3YGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn You are telling people what a low life dictator said.senator Cornyn like it is something people should pay attention to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nancy says: “There’s no emergency and turn over your guns.” Lol 😂 This is living “Proof” that she really has totall… https://t.co/Ji7RKPaC1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it’s layover time 🙄 (@ Chicago Midway International Airport in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/oUFx2eSKvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlmcdowell391 @butzsecs Our set list from the @Metallica show! #MetInLouisville #worldwired]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't forget to set your clocks forward one hour for #DaylightSavingsTime. Republicons, set yours forward one hour...and fifty years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyscof #fluoridation Must be kickback to our politicians. Whistle-blowers Please~! https://t.co/EqtUMqdYAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Triple Citra Daydream by @OtherHalfNYC @ Heisler's Custom Services — https://t.co/4Qlx9R2EZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday! The Converse Chuck Taylor All Star sneaker is celebrating its 102nd birthday this year.#realballers https://t.co/kC4yXSxUl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the hell is wrong with the New York Times: seems like a great idea to create a friendly name for stalking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Failed two #pokertournament and lost 2weeks pay. Extremely disappointed in myself. I can blame being unlucky in imp… https://t.co/GiWO4UxUyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham remember when the least among you would inherit the kingdom. Was that before or after your fabulous events?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Leeshha Happy Valentine’s Day boo boo! Hope a 6’0 bearded man knocks you up today. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still on my weather rant. Siberia is having amazing weather compared to Des Moines!! 🥶 👿 @ Lower Beaver, Des Mo… https://t.co/npeHZ26Ftd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fahrenthold Just an old reminder of a warning about Mar-A-Lago: https://t.co/o21WG35NfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The recreation hall in Covina Park is packed now, filled with concerned residents. https://t.co/042VOCLLXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Jefferson, North Carolina https://t.co/SNOy8NVKDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[And when I say “disingenuous” I’m not referring to people like Tucker Carlson who are wholesale grifters, I mean le… https://t.co/DOw7r859I4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when people would post photos of dumb ass shit and say they’re adulting. “Went to go buy cereal, because w… https://t.co/Q6ss4ZxgMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGreenblattADL @ADL_NewEngland When English is your second language...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out in the woods this morning!!! Got to take my son shooting for the 1st time today! Great Target Practice! So far… https://t.co/LOa5oicBvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @iThoughtful If it's so bad why aren't all the SAS flights one way to the USA? https://t.co/6tMvwwzOrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once upon a time I was a hoe, I don't even wanna hoe no mo' 🔥🔥🔥😍😍🎼🎼🎼 @lizzo #onrepeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good series for kids, especially if you like pirate-themed stories. @ Orange, Texas https://t.co/UDal2qeX6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BroadStHockey @Simmonds17 If they had to trade him I am glad Nashville he has a shot at the cup now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenzhuscott Also in OP an unclear double negative: “slowdown is accelerating” should read “sales continue to decelerate”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he was seriously about the rings at this point in his career he would have went to Philly. Us lakers fans were f… https://t.co/d8npJ34VH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andybuege @SportsCenter Wouldn’t have shot that many 3s had Zion been in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apiecebyguy If it’s to lose k like a nitwit, he has succeeded beyond his wildest dreams]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hablando de provocar la tercera guerra mundial... A este pana no le basta el rollo que se viene para el 23. No, el… https://t.co/yjiWlHdgSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callherdiana Either her pussy ain’t tight like she said or his dick small small]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaj33 You are such a class guy. To raise$ for the education of kids is so worthwhile. I worked as a nurse on the N… https://t.co/HzZoeeTXcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The blur of Green Race... #famagogo #gorilla #greenrace @ Green River. Saluda, NC https://t.co/FFLg8TtVqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Kevin Hart latest to join Netflix’s stand-up boom with new special ‘Irresponsible’: Comic Kevin Ha… https://t.co/AxLvaCQMhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaithCampbellJ1 @katheri64795347 @clydesconnect @cbeaux @PrinPeta @Greg_MarineLab @bate_char @RayRayEdwards19… https://t.co/uplhdkGc6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hoarfrost by @bigtimberbrew @ Big Timber — https://t.co/CvC1KdX0Nx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirnuthi @MattTremblay8 @Skip_Estes @smayranderson @dan_reynolds Probably a water thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having babes will make you feel this even deeper!  Happy Valentine’s Day babes. Let’s fight for love! ❤️🧡💛💚💙💜🖤❤️🧡💛💚… https://t.co/k9MWvgld6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[First things first: do not disturb sign goes out immediately upon arrival.  You don’t need new linens or towels eve… https://t.co/5owXkHFYfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AFineBlogger @KeithPowersNYC @CarlinaRivera Not to mention the many realtors who won’t even answer the phone or of… https://t.co/KNruGGaewK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stir fried rice cakes at Sura Eats are stupid good. https://t.co/fyLQKdcURq]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was an epic tease from Amy, Maya and Tina of what could have been. So good. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like @fairfightaction is readying a full-court lobbying press on voting rights issues. #gapol https://t.co/mYu5Jg5TdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Evan_Flood Douche bad flex after giving up numerous 3s.  Then missed free throw.  The act is old.  Kid is a punk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mona made it thru surgery, they were able to close a lot of the wound which is amazing. I'll go pick her up at 430.  Whew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fred is world class never discriminate. #MUFC_FAMILY #mufc @manutd @MUnitedNewsNow @mufcfredthered @nuno_fredthered… https://t.co/l7T3uzxJWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Jackson finally see the truth, While we all know he's gone and can't return to defend himself. it's amazing… https://t.co/pcHKBHLz66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonSouthwell @GuyFieri Sorry, everything is wonderful.  Get with the program.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday Night LC Wrestling Fundraiser with friends! @ Total Sports &amp; Entertainment https://t.co/uczBbWKum8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of seeking meaningful ways to circulate wealth back into our communities, our extractive policies are forci… https://t.co/feTOC2M2MJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrodyLogan This @SteveAtwater27 guy would slay the lion...lion would probably run the other way. Kinda like Christ… https://t.co/e84CMaTpFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having trouble getting the crowd into the music whilst DJ-ing tonight. New strategy: play the worst music ever. Mam… https://t.co/AxYvPi12is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @phucccumean I bought one box before this shit went down. Is it too late to buy more?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateDawg8583 Idk if you ever check twitter anymore but DM me, it’s 21_NYG_21, from the old forum days]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took a nap and now gym but there was no pizza in between? 🤔 good Riddance]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m probably not on list to meet @taylorswift13 next Era!! But one day i will   @taylornation13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mario_trigo @NYNC214 Morning bro be back there next Sunday 4 days in big D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosedixontx @AppSame What manner of Democrat-liberal- progressive-socialist-abortion 💩 creature is this now!? @GregGutfeldShow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emily Gerrick speaks about how DOCs receive financial incentives and in some cases actual “kickbacks” from contract… https://t.co/bjAiuUP45N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 10 #SanFrancisco #49ers from1965 on.  https://t.co/GYXQHDZ99m … https://t.co/V44BpDOFZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day to this special lady. I’m inspired every day by your laziness and your ability to sleep anywhe… https://t.co/1wXT8UTb5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjammingh My current and previous managers are women. Work in a large food manufacturing company doing IT.  Half… https://t.co/3fS3fv3Cvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSS98Rock I'd rather see Sabu and Mick foley, as old as they are hit each other with light bulbs, chairs, and barbed wire]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrBrentTaylor @SarahJacksonSJ @styling_reader Have you read The Boys in the Boat? One of my favorites.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In this episode of INFILL @loridroste from Berkeley gets the housing problem! We need to build housing for both cur… https://t.co/B5mlDNbBv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leewelshman @Rockbmi @JamesFl @tuxford2 @Chris_F_Griffin @matthewd_wilson Yes, please! https://t.co/yB5JFU1JPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haverhill leads Pentucket 1-0 after 2 periods at the Newburyport Bank Classic Finals. https://t.co/kuA8eda8kd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweeFTF @WebberFB After you make it big and take care of your Momma... let me hold $20... 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help me save children’s lives!  Every dollar counts!  https://t.co/qTtpdL7v0i #stjude #stjudeheroes… https://t.co/yN2hdTc0cT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterbakernyt Was he injected with something by the guy in the green coat?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mom looks like a beat up Bruce Jenner bruhhh. One way not to get ratings!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Martin Yu crossed 13.1. Time 02:02:08, pace 09:10 min/mile, est. finish 11:05 am https://t.co/NNZgwBXIOF #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump BECAUSE OF ME, IT'S NOW 2019 That's the higest number year EVER, much higher than Obama !… https://t.co/VicLlru3hL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carey Price: You are thorn in my side, but you have brought joy to my heart and tears to my eyes.  You are a kind abd caring soul @CP0031]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was at Walmart, if somebody asked for something I'd go to the back and walk to the other side of the store. Fuck outta here nigga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WarOnTheRocks I understand that the Bundesrepublik Deutschland is in the process of adopting the ostrich for its coat of arms...]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all, you gotta try this! It’s soooo good and sooo hard. And tag someone who needs to try it too. Thanks to… https://t.co/9g2oIUVNEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jim_utter @KevinHarvick @keselowski Specially when they were showing love for @KyleBusch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior  SARAH, We need your VOICE!! There many people that are voiceless!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peep Jesus at the Official Bad Art Museum of Art. https://t.co/IPJRmsiSFU]]></document></documents></author>