<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Extremely accurate. College orientation is hell on earth https://t.co/ZnXdNH1kOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 11 of no cigarettes 🤗🤗🤗👌👌👌 quitting cold turkey after 9 years has been an actual bitch but im so glad I did it. #QuitSMOKING #cigarettes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bringing education stabilization grants back to 2016 levels passed the @NHHouseofReps in a 268-90 vote. #HB177 #NHPolitics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to bump into some members of the Florida Delegation yesterday at @NACoTweets  #NAColeg All working hard for F… https://t.co/NvRIEcfiHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bowling alley serves the best cheesy cauliflower bites! #food https://t.co/r3kfU3ghyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[You had me at "generously buttered noodles."👩‍🍳 #WinterStorm food! 🍗🍝 Stay strong #midwest!🌬 🌨💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time we are all home 😂 @kdotwilliams @kshearin1014 @simply_shay3110 @kpaigeh07 @wholtgordon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using inverse operations to match solutions to one-step equations #6thmath #CPrepHartford https://t.co/c6DZWZ7VEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You can’t call him an asshole because he doesn’t have one.. you can call him an ostomy!” 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incase anyone needed a reminder... it’s costs exactly $0 to not be an asshole :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_NattyP They may be better off without you as a friend. Students I know with spelling disorders work harder than m… https://t.co/0Q8BP2TglH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristelAdnana Chrstel it takes time what to 2 say about your television father kristoff how he was and a good man… https://t.co/NQfDRGZltn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried, I’m somewhere into the 5th ep of the Kominsky Method and I can’t finish it... 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao on our way back from Austin me and Ethan were saying to each other that the other person sucked a lot of peen… https://t.co/OozCeAFSiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peachlimeshake Yeah... It's weird because i almost feel JEALOUS sometimes that i don't get creeped on and that's a… https://t.co/fMn5ZBC9E9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having loads of fun at STEM Expo at Bethlehem Baptist! #STEM https://t.co/yHbCIbugVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bornabrit1 He believes every frigging murdering thug around the world except U.S. citizens. He is not representing America just himself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olliethevast I love my phone. When I initially typed out destresed it autocorrected to destroyed. Which is how Hux and Kylo destress. XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dizzymom64 @amicah1 @OrenIShiKiddo @kaci150 @Aug1405 @SealeyGerald @RL9631 @JeanneInTexas @Crunk5454 @FLMel69… https://t.co/D5pWFC23Eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you soon Miami 💫 @ Wynwood Walls &amp; Art District, Miami https://t.co/hBqtzjTMtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesHellen7 If you would like to soon ok talk later got to go I will be waiting on you for a few days to chat bac… https://t.co/Uu1coP5wZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OWNTV .. This is the first #FixMyLife that had me yelling out loud!. I wish I could hug each and every one of them… https://t.co/zsXSwMYRL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheddarLynn @pamdobs @colbej @TamaraGary5 @LaraMcC53585805 @CraigBu68569857 Yes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One for the record books @PatDonahoeArmy joined SGT’s Time tonight. @EighthArmyKorea is STILL my very favorite assi… https://t.co/93Mnj8GM3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope these young @whitesox players see the crap fans are talking because we didn’t get Manny and play with a chip… https://t.co/cALM2Hq2YJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A night to remember! #50thbirthday #chaz #malibu #birthdayboy #happybirthday #sober #friends #instamoment… https://t.co/0BlIxig5Qw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: do we have any chips? Sister: We have carrots  Me: https://t.co/XbLtsrYUN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Cole trying to describe anime*  Cole: Man fuck these hentai games  Me: uhhh what  Cole: You know. The gotdamn japanese cartoons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holly Dude that looks like something that came out of a @neilhimself novel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[:) (@ CVS pharmacy - @cvs_extra in Lyndhurst, OH) https://t.co/BoWlucDszV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SP19hockey My articles said the team would never play permanently at the Coli. I stand by that. And yes, if you sa… https://t.co/ZGWNX7EgRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely cannot read anything that has been blurbed as “fiercely intelligent.” Visceral nope reaction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Documents: State trooper shot by 11-year-old son because video games were taken away https://t.co/9WhCk5j29U by LAU… https://t.co/frEPAd1ZPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[No joke. I walk in muddy river banks for fun. #adventure #pnw #flamingo https://t.co/GcvyL4zksr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#snowpocalypse2019   It’s really pretty (kinda scary), I gotta say the best thing about snow is seeing everyone loo… https://t.co/Rp00OSLD1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@historyinmoment Is that really Strawberry Shortcake sheets?? Oh, God, a vision that I can't unsee just made worse!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let#me#help#find#your#home#sweet#home#orlando#homesbyvanessag#  https://t.co/YPufig3YPZ… https://t.co/O4pY4tb36K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TassajaraRd @LaurenBaratzL @StephMillerShow That is exactly right. They supported the orange monster with zeal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are an A**HOLE in one! Could you just stop it "FORE" one day? Please!🏌️‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Clean Sheet for the Mighty Hatters!    Thank you Hatters Defence and the Keeper guarding the goal!… https://t.co/RcVEXDmVzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you samba_lover2 for these great shots that capture the joy and alegría do samba. My heart was happy tonight.… https://t.co/bVsGURiDoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beltrandelrio @Imagen_Mx En NYC Pascal, atentos a la diana, ¡buenos días! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liz74117654 my aunt is the lady above the red head and that’s her boot over there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magnitude 1.8 #earthquake, 25.4 km NE of Eureka Dunes, CA https://t.co/PRrwz1awex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoshlyInc Flying home from beautiful Sanibel back to Chi town. Relax on plane?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying a new place out for dinner! @elbowsmac #ElbowsGilbert Pesto MAC n Cheese for the win!! @ Elbows Mac N' Cheese https://t.co/JBszf9eW0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the Zombies will agree with the Court.  Please Rep. Schiff we need ADS running telling the truth! Play SNL... B… https://t.co/wzR0Ze8gBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright @amahnke I have binged on the Amazon Prime program, but I’m only just now really digging into your podcast.… https://t.co/qp1q43xIP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calumsbadidea @MostRequestLive @TheChainsmokers @5SOS #5SOSFAM 😢 #whodoyoulove https://t.co/opYnlhheP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it has to do with @realDonaldTrump and his supporters they're all in and you make up stories about Trump and his… https://t.co/x37vnrZo4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks a lot Thanks a lot  We don't want our honourable PM Imran Khan's portrait on your Dirty walls 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[No veo ese noticiero. Se de que pie cojea la Delta. Nada consiente ni imparcial. Fue sumisa con AG he hice zapping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a game!!! #KingsVsCeltics 🏀 #WithACelticsFan 🍀 #SacramentoProud 👑 #WeAlmostHadThem 🙄 #KyrieOnTheBenchToo 😝… https://t.co/LevHrLEWMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoraBarbiery @LastresPepe Será que la llevó para ocultar el abuso sexual de algún familiar]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’ll heat up My leftover calzone I made yesterday,&amp; eat that for breakfast when I get home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar @DrDinD She needs to be fired before the end of the day tomorrow. Who hired this opinionated wacko????????????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry didn’t even write you a note! Was so mad I didn’t mail out sooner. Just watched Abducted in Plain Sight, twis… https://t.co/mItIijwf5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[They didn’t want to get the earful they deserve. So they don’t get my vote either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IDODI (DI) competition day - My SpiDI Sense is Tingling. #WeArePDY #shesasenior @ Pike Delta York Schools https://t.co/WEkTKVfR6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebsAllin @MichaelO1711 @benshapiro He could’ve ruined 2 totally innocent men’s lives if they were unlucky enough… https://t.co/msGjNSor3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[OKAY I’M ABOUT TO TAKE OFF AND THERE’S A HOT GUY NEXT TO ME WOW IM BLESSED SEE YOU SOON LA AND HOPEFULLY… https://t.co/bOOHWjtPzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[2018 had some good moments for me. I finally left my job of 10 years. It was toxic but in the last year I had a new… https://t.co/TSGY3DPWYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go vote. Have to have fb though! Help these hard working kids out! They represent the state of Kansas! Spread the w… https://t.co/jHK9EHBGNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compass Santa Monica // Trying out a phone booth @ our newest office in #SantaMonica on Main Street! Super fun gran… https://t.co/Jkd4YKa3ZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MotorCityMadness #WEARtheBEAR #GrizzGangVsEverybody https://t.co/nFaWvbEmXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Astro_Nerd_ Yes, please do! Also, check out @EVNautilus for some more ocean exploration/NASA collaboration. Went… https://t.co/ngRCMpGUGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@disney__tasthic I know your anxiety is telling you someone is mad at you. But you’re okay. Even if you do make a m… https://t.co/yIKVdOjlHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just told my representative to terminate Trump’s sham "national emergency." Will you join me? https://t.co/wrL6yFSXjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogenaLSpokane @thomaskaine5 I have heard those words at a wedding as an adult and every time it made me cringe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glutes 🍑 and Abs 🙋🏼‍♀️ what more could you want 🤷‍♀️.  . . Jokes your program should be well balanced however most… https://t.co/yvNakyn396]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahBurris @SeamusHughes Theres probably more POS in our armed forces who are just like this guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thanks to all the gentlemen who barricaded me from being seen while peeing on the platform. I am winning unemployment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“sometimes you’ve got to let everything go— purge yourself. if you are unhappy with anything... whatever is bringin… https://t.co/DMJVMcjcZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work is hard, but my best friend is always there to support. https://t.co/ngUgYfsJWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryan_mansbarger came over for a couple hours today. all we did was study on my couch, but my heart is so full that… https://t.co/Jo2PkvYsSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KylanKnight @P_ebers and I watched four seasons in four days when we first moved to the dale 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[They let them play SO much in the first half. It was glorious.   Did the @NCAA call the refs at half time complaining it was too physical??]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Pelosi did not single out alien Omar for criticism that was no different then trying to explain  That Harvey W… https://t.co/iXn6aVK44X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grumpynurse74 This is every nurse break room everywhere; why can we remember a million things on the floor but not… https://t.co/LsK6WdLtqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The advantages of being a woman artist.  (On display at Gracie Mansion) https://t.co/0jDBGpZ3s6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so glad. Men and women should know in no uncertain terms that they have betrayed our Nation and they have NO R… https://t.co/SgYQRLOju9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish someone would tell their future baby daddy to stop calling me private 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to chuckle. 20 Funniest Ultrasound Photos https://t.co/GvfZLx9VH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[you sir, are quite fine 🤩 @ Greenville, North Carolina https://t.co/Ey92EOpup5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students helping students! ❤️ #BeAWarrior @WarriorsNMS @Norwalk_HS @eastview_89]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bionicanadian @IreneWoodbury @lennar_my So happy to hear that! Right on! You definitely deserve a you day 😁...you… https://t.co/47CjkbN5FL]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a sweet surprise from my work peeps! Thank you for thinking of me! @NakiaPitre @MsAuthier @MsStephDouglas… https://t.co/B0c92ZxVld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making inferences. Diving deeper into location and resources. @gchribar @ctroxell https://t.co/2K4O5ZkxVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Oh, what joy for those whose disobedience is forgiven, whose sins are put out of sight. Romans 4:… https://t.co/GMkGLfBqYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will I ever be able to run without 21 year old guys honking at me??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again you have it ASS backwards listening to a lowlife wannabe news reporter Hannity .This is a country you are run… https://t.co/snn8UPOoU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USATODAY Me Jordan is so Vendective he knows like we all do that trump lies so he's a liar per mr Jordan!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi I’m Carly and I cry every time @MarenMorris Girl plays on the radio.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Mark Franke from @relatrix for the opportunity to share with fellow @tspra members how we are using Relat… https://t.co/zX0ZzqHKwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Streaming on #YouNow and #twitch for the first time since I moved places! GRWM at 630am PST ✌🏽 YOUNOW- K3chocolate 💚 TWITCH - k3dance 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shotglass1 @kkerrrigann sorry, ill try to dumb it down next time. maybe ill just video it so you can *here* it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdanClay Baby mama was 19. Terrified of cat carrier. She walked up to it meowed and went in. We drive directly to… https://t.co/IhNOGLk11n]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always a great day to give the gift of life! @SCRedCrossBlood @RedCrossSC ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The memory of visibly shaken Feinstein informing us of the murders of Harvey Milk and George Moscone barely able to… https://t.co/35YfSlG8t0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@domchappelle @EnergizerHunnii He ain’t random lol he was a child actor]]></document></documents></author>