<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I used to go to 10-15 movies a year. No more.  Not interested in seeing a bunch of so called super heroes or disgus… https://t.co/P9S9vvE5sJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennyfactor This was my reaction too but I figured maybe I was missing something. Also amusing that past protests… https://t.co/dZ9l7cqoZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealBookSpy @Connellybooks Just concluded Dark Sacred Night. Ballard and Bosch made a great pair. Maybe they’ll… https://t.co/0cpMhPvaR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilevin @AnnRudich Hey @HowardSchultz that sure do smack of extortion(also found in the Capitalists Dictionary).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoberlyHoops @IceColdJones_ Sorry guys..... Was looking for some defensive clips for a coach &amp; ran across this! 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgentPjr @KristySwansonXO @larryelder @PatriotMe1 @IngrahamAngle @PlanetTyrus @bennyjohnson @thecjpearson… https://t.co/jsqMkcocjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be on the rocket ship with an incredible crew! https://t.co/wY8CXl1sEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GePeirson @amteve The Conservatives will do no less than what the Liberals are doing on electoral reform. #ndp #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 hey remember when @SarahPalinUSA claimed she was "the boss"? Me neither.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I knocked up Natalie Portman, she would never leave my sight. I would master the art of not blinking so that I d… https://t.co/gD6m3FoHAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @MSNBC I thought you said MSNBC was "FAKE NEWS" and "UNTRUSTWORTHY" so why should we believe this.… https://t.co/ydZGQjUJKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchyD @CCampbellArt I cherish Bill Burr. Maybe it’s the whole “angry Irish guy shouting about idiots” thing. I d… https://t.co/ypRaCxNctE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrwells82 It actually tied in to the mythology of the originals in interesting ways]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DenaliKannapel If it’s one of those Bic Round Stic Blue pens then I leave an extra $ or two on the tip &amp; take that shit. Sry not sry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking of Smollett, I just wanna say hi to my bae since Eves Bayou, Journee Smollett ❤️ https://t.co/swkGhV9xN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindachilders1 @TheMicheleWojo @PalmerReport @johnpavlovitz @krassenstein @EdKrassen @ida_skibenes @funder… https://t.co/Y32wwrZwaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Partying with your buddy Jeff Epstein - we all know what you did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexdalton95 @Bewyds @GoVeganWorld @vegansprinkles7 @plantbased_Bee Signed]]></document><document><![CDATA[God loves you! I love you! Refocus! Get into his presence before you go out into the world! #prayer #Praise #Jesus… https://t.co/BKks4tfIcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[NASCAR: Kyle Busch post-race quote illustrates lower series debate https://t.co/qEUzROcNBj I think the Fan's need t… https://t.co/XzgQdZZCuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[When They Spill The Tea On Your Co-Worker 😂😂😂😂 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/edYzFIUSsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check it out. My first solo performance in 10 years. Come join me for an evening of jazz and more. Plus great food… https://t.co/b86wH2J3Gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@logical_tinker @Phredd67714463 @StandUp4Brexit @BillCashMP What we would contribute could be saved by reducing our… https://t.co/apeFvmeLv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCAR_Xfinity @NASCAR @DISupdates @JEarnhardt1 Not like the truck I'm afraid! I think tomorrow will be like this… https://t.co/h9v0uPXDi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_HadleyGamble Moring Hadley ,I hope yr feeling better , I want to wish you Happy woman s day]]></document><document><![CDATA[during the second coming i hope the “trumpeters in the sky” mentioned in the book of revelations is actually just a… https://t.co/BcnlLGYuqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlcieslak @AshleyJPL I have two of my Book It books still on my shelf 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is feeling a lot like a, “Brett needs to be fired because he can’t manage the end of games” game]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you got kids I’m just suggesting as parents or guardians we need to just pay close attention today and be on extra aware alert.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queen is the most overrated band in Rock history right along side the Beatles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump @senatemajldr @SenateGOP This is what open borders and multi culturalism is doing t… https://t.co/9D8VwIVmnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lostinjonestown @Wisconn_Valley haters gonna hate. You will see Foxconn will raise the bar on environmental standa… https://t.co/BIkqPYyM8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m cool if @miketirico is on the call for hockey going forward. Well done, sir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillKassidyy A Good Night to the sweet princess Jill Kassidy &amp; hope you Dream of your Birthday wishes to come true tomorrow ❤️💕♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews American exceptionalism is now in the face of all Americans - exceptionally pathetic.🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hot date 💁🏻‍♀️🔥 God truly blessed my two boys with the best mom, and me with an incredible girl. @ Hot and Hot F… https://t.co/x4VDtgJoFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels good to be lost in the wrong direction #coloradoliving #coloradosprings #northcheyennecanyon #7bridges… https://t.co/L8xD9nroUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prior to sunset pics of the moon reveal all its beautiful seas and craters. A few minutes later is just a big white… https://t.co/AXRdDpWkql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeGromen The beast must be starved.... Implications... yes, but bitter Medcine is many times required to heal patient.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterZeihan Hadn’t seen this before, I guess I knew it in my gut.  One thing stands out in my mind is the need for… https://t.co/BuOYKtojNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fongs Crab Rangoon Pizza May just be the 8th wonder of the world. Simply amazing and never gets old. #fongspizzadsm… https://t.co/4Ws1jQe3JS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Star is born... I snuggled my wife as she asked me to watch this... I now thank her not knowing Dice, Chappelle w… https://t.co/eshLWD8O7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeoffGljiva This event doesn’t work for our schedule and we informed the organizers of this last week. I’m always… https://t.co/Bs26Onsy25]]></document><document><![CDATA[The eagle has landed! Add nice weather and $$$ on the street = GREEN! @shawnatspg @anewton_SPG @VIPwireless… https://t.co/U1MzNjdFZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Episode #2 of "Albright Access N247RU", On this episode we cover our Post National Convention Staff meeti… https://t.co/0zmZESb2Hc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We gonna pull up old tweets of Zach Collins being #MAGA and saying the n-word aren't we?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again, it is very hard to stay “in front” of the bad actors out there that are trying to steal our data, but we ALL… https://t.co/6gGgwgMUm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[☝️Pasos para un estilo de vida más saludable:1) Buena #nutrición. 2) Actividad consistente. 3... ¿Cuál es su número… https://t.co/Ldnk6NE2h7]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEEL YEAH!!!  unc_basketball #uncvsduke @ Chapel Hill, North Carolina https://t.co/hrObkLig8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Atlantic Aviation PHL in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/9Ui0NEFlFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have they approved all the photo radar and double school zones for speeders?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikethemiz How come at house shows you wear elbow pads, but not on tv? I think it'd be cool if you wore them all the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta My point was you choose his death date to bash him! You can care for animals without being assholes! Want to… https://t.co/wpw7YsGkKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I live right across street from the Giant in Shaw. Heard 4-5 gun shots around 11PM. Looked out my window and viewed… https://t.co/1avpHVHyvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timberwolves laying an absolute dud early against the Kings. Not very encouraging]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you close your eyes and focus hard enough, a half empty jar of Ragu spaghetti sauce will appear in the far left… https://t.co/PAGHkAXrgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#2030ispossible #riseagainsthunger #wwjd #ibelievemumc @ McKendree UMC https://t.co/CLUNzpWaWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The2ton @MLB Do you have eyes to see? The ball enters glove OVER THE FENCE...and he flies over...no catch IMO but… https://t.co/P1qKg7SK9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol how come everytime someone touches the piano they play the 2 chains song 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anhadrepooc @willin_mac I'll be fine thanks, hope your daughter recovers quickly 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump I feel sorry for your patients.. Do you say this bullshit to them when they come in for a check up.?]]></document><document><![CDATA[imma keep it real with u chief today was dumb sad but imma keep it moving]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry to hear about #NASA #MarsRover #OpportunityRover but I think we could’ve spent $400 million better than to fi… https://t.co/abgtJUlNrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BottleShop opens in 2 hours!!!!  #FirstAnniversary #NewBottles @ Chapter Two Brewing Company https://t.co/P7v0vPbZNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[💯 there no better feeling than after a run!🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️  #carpediem #greatnessawaits… https://t.co/TjqT7KS0Xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aprilrenae @MeghanMcCain So by her reasoning it looks like her dad was judged after all of his warmongering]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuchyB @juanvillorio1 @SamuelHoyosM Cuanto extraño a mi presidente @AlvaroUribeVel versión 1. El q no sabía de coa… https://t.co/BIIyHpAKlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amaiyah saw her first fight and I think she liked it a little too much 😳 my baby got hands like auntie @tyanamari… https://t.co/4Pel5MDv8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm pretty sure this is what love looks like.  Especially when it's served up especially for you.  #getinmybelly. @… https://t.co/OjmlF79tZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ozkar88922981 @DougPlagens @OfficialCrowder @560WQAM Great meeting you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight fire - Drinking a Skies of Wonder (Batdance) by @FortGeorgeBeer @ Craiglandia  — https://t.co/6evz3EaBem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SloSHO @argusmattz @ORUAthletics They’re always fun to listen to. They typically hire local folks to fill out the… https://t.co/G2nO3auIYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tell it like it is. Dodge cars are NOT worth owning. (excluding challenger/charger/viper) prepare to lose $$ and… https://t.co/ajl7IEUe9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewpyper @janetsomerville Coming back from Spain, a customs agent stopped me in New York and gave me a tough ti… https://t.co/A0bF9VwAUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sooo glad I don’t or ain’t fuckin with no hoes I’m Waitin for my lil thang 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevehernick @GoodmanHoops Yeah I would boycott the best sporting event in the world because 2 non factors weren’t invited.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will Barton hits a 3 and gives the Nuggets a four point lead, 112-108 with 3:49 left. #MileHighBasketball #NBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone know if the developer/integrator is still in business and/or is the govt still paying them for this disaster… https://t.co/KW0kbtY7On]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen grape jelly is the secret to any cocktail snack. Lil smokies, meatballs, uh.. that’s it really. But! So impo… https://t.co/YD9HGbOP9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoldorinAngst @Neoavatara Where was he when the dad came to his decision?]]></document><document><![CDATA[House Committee on Appropriations Subcommittee on Article III meet today to go over Decision Documents. #txlege https://t.co/OrsMcENCRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[CRAWL is playing #LIVE at the Atria downtown Oshawa tearing down the building Valyear is up NEXT #LocalTalent… https://t.co/IpF5FfPPxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uncswimdive Praying for you Coach Rich and you family hope you get well soon 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter Sara is covering the Alabama tornadoes. Apparently she was also on CNN in the middle of the night doing… https://t.co/NjRpSdfAQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markdaly362 @Winners786 @MC_squared_ Really helps me understand 1933 Germany. I'm not saying he's 1943 hitler but… https://t.co/quUslN03LY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReuseRecruiting @RadiNabulsi Jake smart ass comments from radi  isn’t a form of payment no matter what he tries to… https://t.co/psHryimeK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope, it's the subculture that deprives it's members of the most basic human needs. Satan wasn't grinding on me bef… https://t.co/IJ6x32bQDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller @JBaker31826004 @RandPaul Just when I start to like you, you become an asshole like MCCain]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fairly confident I saw the best experimental music set I’ve ever seen tonight. Werner Dafeldecker + Valerio Tricoli… https://t.co/JeH0wDcq7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would jersey Italians be jersey Italians if they didn’t have a 20 pound or less dog named Bella?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gavthomp remember the days where we would do this with pillows in the living room?  #offthetoprope]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m done with nba basketball until Miami gets a superstar or Lebron gets AD and KD]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I wish I could post on everybodies IG v-Day posts https://t.co/VrDRtXgtcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyond stoked to have won this @cainforge tattoo machine yesterday from the @bleedforacure raffle slctattoo_convent… https://t.co/TtSfeKTn8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Raspberry Blackberry by @SerpentineCider @ Serpentine Cider — https://t.co/VrHdCuaefL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevBoutMula If it was me then I’ll take ownership , start of the year he did not show me anything that showed it h… https://t.co/PGJiK6bury]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaseballJeff1 @evaelle @Mattealc I’m an eternal optimist. None of his injuries appear to be long term so I’m hopin… https://t.co/r21lHMKFiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antipodesrex @TheRickWilson @MollyJongFast Have you ever been to a book festival?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blue Out tonight at 7. Buy a shirt or call me to borrow one as my tshirt drawer overfloweth with them but come in b… https://t.co/k6jij7jJ2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2INTMD8 @rudd_jason WTH? Does the governor enjoy a police escort when he personally delivers your takeout  to your home?]]></document></documents></author>