<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Tell Them We Are Rising: The Story of Black Colleges and Universities - this month’s social justice film at St. Pet… https://t.co/w4589O7YJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noellemarie_w @lolesports @100Thieves @SabbyrinaW @Nadeshot 💙💙💙💙💙 https://t.co/2Up0qHWkEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[why the hell does the Ventra customer service close at 4:30 ☹️ I need a new card bc I lost it the day my new pass s… https://t.co/yG7dUpDkYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book mail! My copy of #SCALES by @ANConway just arrived! @owlhollowpress @literarycounsel https://t.co/oecT1WptXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My B train, being held downtown at Columbus Circle, is either going on 8th Avenue or 6th avenue. The conductor keep… https://t.co/oxZUA30Ku5]]></document><document><![CDATA[BEFORE SHE KNEW HIM by @PeterSwanson3 is out in bookstores, who is running out to buy it!? https://t.co/DDeHmGB7Jw… https://t.co/wA7Zip8Lq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommates friend is already referring to herself as an aunt because her sister is pregnant which means the baby is “alive” 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would find her more genuine if she redistributed her own salary to her staff or back in the neighborhoods that su… https://t.co/idRAfW5mAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0AOwwY3P3L  #AceFrehley "New York Groove"  #Kiss solo album #ClassicRock #classics   @derkacz_mark… https://t.co/INMbsP2z7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mastermind7864 Yaaasss. I am unthrilled over a couple that have thrown in their hat, but I'm gonna shut my trap an… https://t.co/oaWajDruAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@desiree_camus sitting at your house on a Friday that no one was doing anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowToGetAwayABC #HTGAWM do u think they will all finally get caught! Stay tuned next Thursdays episode!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@and321run @SpecNewsATX @GrittyNHL Dreams do come true! https://t.co/BTpFyDs7b3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StanysBujakera @VitalKamerhe1 Même Vital a attendus avoir un bon travail pour se marie mais toi tu n’a rien et tu veux te marie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Againsat Helen Mirren’s dress, Jason Momoa’s suit looks like it was left on my dash too long. (But was it...?) #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love books and movies for a LOT of reasons but my favorite is probably how richly I get to experience a scene lik… https://t.co/PMOoNTxjXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Tatum straight up snatched Durant's soul midway through the third quarter” Knew I was watching something special l… https://t.co/HtnRpC8Avb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Courtne29435960 @BuddysBBQ It was good; I just would have gone a little lighter on the sauce. 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HilarieBurton  Sending prayers to this little man and his family as he fights this dreaded disease. I’ve just begu… https://t.co/eN4MnMqoe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Venezuelan ambassador to Russia has said Guaido is a U.S. puppet trained by a Serbian group that “exports US-fr… https://t.co/U5fijdTLJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[These always make me angry (as someone who wants to work with animals hands on). People are shocked when animals ac… https://t.co/5TkZlnoGYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Mr. Eastwood calls, you better answer!! Such an amazing memory where I was blessed to not only do the casting… https://t.co/YQlGLn8cUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marketing Class underway!  Let’s Get Moving!! @ Coldwell Banker - Timonium, MD https://t.co/EpT10Zxhy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, yelling: I HAVE ANXIETY stacy, also yelling: THAT DOESNT MEAN YOU CAN JUST POOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today at the Legislature, we heard from Tim Hogues regarding his appointment to the position of Commissioner of the… https://t.co/W7x2nc0Kmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best tip I heard today: “Your role is to stay in your light.” 💗💗💗⭐️⭐️⭐️ #staylit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I will stand up for this.  I’ve said for awhile I think it’s tertiary syphilis.  After this past week, I am pret… https://t.co/apZ4dnmrNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The “apparent” apparition in this pic is no camera gimmick but a flick in the here and now and the wherever that’s… https://t.co/xmME3gZ3XK]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are pics of me Harlem Shaking from last night https://t.co/EDSvKIxd4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Lambda Gamma Omega, VB Chapter of Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority Incorporated for celebrating Black History M… https://t.co/Lpey5vpFdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daver2956 @senatemajldr Yes and that’s two firm promises. He needs to keep his word. He is great with the judges b… https://t.co/Nhu0S4Gmv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight #findom! I have a 10 hour drive ahead of me tomorrow and I expect every single one of you losers to enter… https://t.co/8LDI66uIwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsmnkrrh @BriBabeShante 😂😂 Thanks!! Yea that's how I felt at first too, but I think at the end it was more about s… https://t.co/wncujD8pzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Commander_Kzin @GeorgeTakei Best idea yet!  And his construction force is already there on the border...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshlyeKyle God bless hun hope they all get better soon push those fluids ❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I really hate my job. This weekend was one of those times. #icunurse]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that the Ss wrote the questions! @Sharonsobal1 @CheccaMirags @KMallon_HTSD @JenMarinello @MissEduTech… https://t.co/NaCXmlGIcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[you really was trying to turn me against my friend and I was blind to it☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I learned from @SPCEliteInvite   1. We needed this kind of tournament in February  2. @FSU_Softball is a POWER… https://t.co/nklG4DFak0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had a dream that I walked in on my man sleeping with a guy what does the MEAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbartley6 Marcia from Atwater CA #TOSA new induction mentor for new teachers; making carnitas tonight #tlap https://t.co/6dViMnrERS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo who wants to buy one of these jerseys for me at auction after the game? As someone who suffers from cripplin… https://t.co/3wtPUkwkG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[First @jeffreyswisher saves my life and then he turns into Billy Bob Carter]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s love when she mentions coffee three times in the same sentence involving evening plans 🖤 @heeeeyimemilee]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Oh wow she’s way prettier than me...”  “No it’s only because she’s dressed up, I bet she usually looks like a rat”  Y’ALL I CAN’T W/ BECKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so sad and I really hope that @uglymugsie is able to secure an exception. #sexwork]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WebbAdams3 @DougJones So not true. Obviously your blind support of this admin. Won't be swayed no matter what is f… https://t.co/RSWrwABdyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ironically, you may be more related to your marrow match!  The cheek swab you return collects your HLA (Human Leuko… https://t.co/HSr8EfVcMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not where I want to be but I’m further than I thought I’d be!    At 18 I didn’t know if college was even going… https://t.co/VyWaGQ8FuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[No but forreal, my neighbors are always fucking... the people in the apartment next to mine and then the building i… https://t.co/K9ckkx57lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patricia_ann4 The sun is a big help. The trees were loaded with snow and now they're almost all snow free.😘❤️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy 18th day of birth to my best friend since the beginning love you forever 💗🔞🤘🏽 https://t.co/lMDyYdjvvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Duh, he thinks we’re all idiots that believe every word coming out of his mouth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Susan_Hennessey Fox is purely entertainment and an arm of the RNC. Fox is not news media entity by their own argument in court.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelzegler @doddleoddle Me when I sang this during a recital and I knew like two people in the audience]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two awesome kiddos having some fun and supporting their school! @ClubHill_Cougar https://t.co/YHpEJVgT1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just re-listened to "I Kissed A Girl" for the first time in like... five years and I gotta say, that shit still holds up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMartinSJ Yes, it's info like this that shakes ones faith.  It's not easy being Catholic. But, I cling to the… https://t.co/gwhi8Zsasv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WX1BOX brief heavy burst of snow followed by current frozen mix in #Assonet 32°]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec Are you at least doing your job of being a mom? Because Christ knows you sure as hell aren't doing the job we pay you for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Allen19 First off it’s not red. And you’re more like a ritz if we being honest 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[First One Tree Hill and now The Vampire Diaries....what is your issue @netflix]]></document><document><![CDATA[ugh yes let’s pray on the decline of someone’s mental state to get the REAL tea out here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKyleMorris @MAGAPILL The worlds going to end b/c @AOC said so!no experience whatsoever regarding politics,scie… https://t.co/6ppW6yuxX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me before coffee and me after coffee. #DetectivePikachu https://t.co/26RySPjJf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“One day you will wake up and there won’t be anymore time to do the things you always wanted to do. Get that new jo… https://t.co/4otNxnWgda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandyincanada @2kewlabs @Axolotl_2019 @BloomNight2 @lynda3035 @Marina935home @ColobusFelton @MauSupercat… https://t.co/FXBYebZQjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This facility was brought up yesterday by Sen.Shelia Jackson Lee on closing the Detention Center,and blocking a sec… https://t.co/gBmGhypcWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone 5 years older than a millennial: *smugly* I just don’t get kids these days. Memes? Huh?  Me: fucking christ… https://t.co/VN42w464Bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I talk THE MOST shit when I’m out having a good time with my girls. I’m occupying his entire inbox with “y’all” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making the World Beautiful 1 Fabulous Diva at a time!!! #pixiecut  #DiamondsandCurlz  https://t.co/kVHXUWVmCR  ••••… https://t.co/njsCjE4agc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catturd2 U could call it “ The biggest turds in the litter box this week!” Lol! 🤣😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the #ctleg hearings with @MomsDemand and @CAGVNews supporting #hb7218. We can do this. #Enough #EndGunViolence… https://t.co/qYDTeAyh2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seattlesparklee That’s how mine started lol but then my water broke and it was horrendous lol you’ll know what you… https://t.co/dGDPXFiY8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joanwalsh Are they looking for an address so they can pull another Waregate heist?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Track 2019 begins! This is how to get it started!!! Go Logan!!! Go Hurricanes!! @Logan_s_22 https://t.co/ORlptzspem]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told Ariel that I prayed that @KaceyMusgraves would sing some Selena and SHE DID! I can die happily now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xoxoains_ Aww I miss you more 💓 I’ll be home tomorrow for spring break!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar How can I buy a ticket !?? I missed the free ticket but I have to meet you!?!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just asked @eveewing about her thoughts on Willie Wilson and yeah he’s all our uncles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The key is to never let them see you coming... #masikakalysha #AllTaidUp #Agentsofla #Vh1 #wetv #GrowingUpHiphop… https://t.co/yi8o3fkO5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[“the universe has a plan. sometimes it’s a really fucking gnarly plan, but nonetheless it still has a plan” - @ArianaGrande]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time at @512studioslive last night. Episode coming soon! ✌️❤️  📸 mrschelsealewis @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/ufPPR6I9KF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okRobGrant Yes yes and yes! One of my favorites. Thanks for the reminder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I prove them wrong by doing my job to the best of my ability, which speaks for itself.” - Torrie McAfee 👏… https://t.co/hCTIt62s3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2002 Congress enacted a farm bill that further reversed the 1996 reforms. The law increased projected subsidy pa… https://t.co/YniaXzxYYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Perrymanimal Well I brought my family’s desktop lol it took up the whole desk in Creswell 😂🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find your breathing space and hold on into it. Inhale. Exhale. Freedom.  . #RileyandJax #BehindTheScenes… https://t.co/WtMJlXkWBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Are you going to be ok? Can you get a friend to record you Live ? We pray you will be ok https://t.co/T731JjxZ3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mental health of our teens is of utmost importance.  #EndTheStigma #mentalhealth #mentalillness… https://t.co/lDj46PG9Ns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lesdoggg I may be a middle-aged white person, but you are my spirit animal, and my goal in life is to be as confid… https://t.co/4K2JXMCZ2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Federal Judge Rejects Accused Troll Farm's Claim That Mueller Singled Them Out for Being Russian https://t.co/08Ex5WNT4f via @lawcrimenews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anton47492193 @Bozesgirl66 @sheri_lynn95252 @social_stars Aww thank you Anton! I hope so!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow White and the Seven Unemployed Dwarves #OcasioCortezChildrensBooks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BriBagwell To quote the Fluffy Guy “I didn’t know they made your size!” 😂  Don’t let unhappy people get ya down!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicbinga Mama Cynthia going on and on? Not letting something go? Now, that may be genetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mta bus 6073 on the m15 didn’t stop at 94th and 2nd it drove right past!!! The bus driver clearly saw me as I wave… https://t.co/6owTzXJbmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The District Attorney’s office says this is a case of domestic violence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Motion Dance Competition is almost here! Visit our website and get registered today! 🎥 @mrledee @ Acadiana Cente… https://t.co/ZXrRCC1S7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madali lang palang sabihin na wag aabsent pota, pero nakakatamad pumasok kada 8:30 then gigising ka ng 5 🤦🏻‍♀️ kasi… https://t.co/T70Gd9v2Kz]]></document></documents></author>