<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[- Jesus isn’t against treasure - he’s against false treasure.  - Every $ decision is a spiritual decision.… https://t.co/QPOpU80GWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheezborger Cheezborger Cheezborger. Always wanted to try this. That SNL skit is one of the best of all time https://t.co/NXWeHpo1qN]]></document><document><![CDATA[1992  #GodofAbraham  #Legendary  #Writing  #Google #NWO  #Tumblr   #jeffdavisshow For #USCongress  District 10… https://t.co/4iR1iABFzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Connor_Bennett3 Order them now and you should get them by the time you can hoop again]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Class Divided (full film) | FRONTLINE https://t.co/wbdVAGYnOs via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PepsiCo @ethisphere @iamcardib now how about this looks like Pepsi is a blessing darling]]></document><document><![CDATA[My job has me so used to the cold that I’m sweating like crazy in this 38 degree weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgsiegel @dmorey (And also, artificially propping up the NBA middle class isn't inherently necessary to the health… https://t.co/Kpk2JOwXoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eriktorenberg Anecdotally, visa renewals that friends are going through now seem to be much, much, much slower than in years past.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CocoDaBear @kirstensaidwhat #BBCan8 @kirstensaidwhat and @BBCANMikey do an all star draft and pick teams without t… https://t.co/J1L2qPBRON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelAlexandreM @silvioluiz Kkkkkkk @RedeGlobo ta cada dia mais piada!!!!  MAIOR TELEJORNAL DO PAÍS @jornalnacional… https://t.co/QqbISVYKmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to visit April 6 @WCU_FB @CoachRWright 🙏 https://t.co/B2bUqBWBYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great show tonight seeing @floggingmolly for the first time at @pennspeak !!  Great place for a great band!!! https://t.co/zlmLpvUL89]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShotsRangOut @ValeriePrimros4 @SpeakerPelosi @TheDemocrats @DrSueDVM @lenlucas46 @tgradous @ChgocadChic… https://t.co/F7yNEwuU1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex__Pitti Hard to feel sorry for those who finished college and going to make  2-5 million dollars in their life… https://t.co/NKTN2ikSVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is humorous. Robin Williams - Life in Pictures RIP 8-11-14 FUNNY BEGINNINGS https://t.co/V77hqdU2Pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also... “Right Now” by Rihanna is very unnecessarily loud. I think it’s up in the ranks of “Obnoxiously Loud and An… https://t.co/FSpLjID8nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Wednesday morning WAKE UP call! There is a time for every season! #WakeUp #ItIsTime #Ecclesiastes3one… https://t.co/ilJSWrzC9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barry is winning me over by the week. Now all he needs to do is prove that the Florida game was more than just a fluke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some rescheduled #Sooners baseball this afternoon. DBU and OU squaring off. On the mound for OU is 6’7 264-pound fr… https://t.co/Ysjnn8cexR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mafia_summers @reinaldoazevedo Se tivesse 1% da inteligencia do Casoy o @reinaldoazevedo  seria um jornalista.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayawiley Putin rejoices as Lyndsey and Trump undermine America's sense of right and wrong, moral authority, rule… https://t.co/JVrChbX3kS]]></document><document><![CDATA[We've locked picture on our 1st short film of 2019, "NO PROBLEM."  So very proud of this one and everyone involved… https://t.co/PJyr5b3AMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[More like dirty filthy pornographic dreams of you....in various positions and outfits]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RealClancyBrown at this point I feel like you’re building a Seth collection :-D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christworedior I will find this guy and chop his dick off, I don't tolerate that rape shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @egrittani for the pic from last night at freetimescafetoronto @ Free Times Cafe https://t.co/mDafp6pLXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is out of control.   Does this administration not even understand basics: that without bees we have no food???… https://t.co/UCRJI2EoV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well well well, hello Becca! Becca who? Exactly, beccawhodesigner 💥.  Check out this beautiful silk Parksquare, the… https://t.co/pQQJ8g9BWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at St. Paul Station (DART Rail) - @dartmedia in Dallas, TX https://t.co/A2onFyGsWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeZimmersEars @lno09281978 @GregTompsett @Notkiba62 @diegojuarezs12 @celestealbone @only_flip_flops @egoltz… https://t.co/M9A6goBIg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s fencing being built where there was already fencing. This was planned under the Obama Administration.   But… https://t.co/Ki5OTvo1Se]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of ya’ll is fat, ugly and unattractive, but that is ok. just be yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misterkristoff Seeing as how I'm supposed to be 2/3 done with my next book by now, though in reality I'm only abou… https://t.co/1xnSXOEQmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doranimated @BernieSanders Has this guy ever worked a day in his life?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WesternMEwx Will do Mike!  Rain now.  I’m at Adams Corner (Goose Rocks &amp; Oak Ridge).]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got some gloves and a domino mask, again in brighter green. The domino mask is where I like the exaggeration the… https://t.co/EDLWTCkz2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing day on my Instagram follow at AKAPAD13 Two of my idols rolled through. https://t.co/bXnTM7s28G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenuineLeighJen @HowardSchultz Yeah.  I was going to recommend “The Paranoid Style of American Politics” but figur… https://t.co/Pmy40566MS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m an oldster in Mass. and follow @drawandstrike, @RealJamesWoods, @STUinSD, @DineshDSouza, @realDonaldTrump of co… https://t.co/YWPzswhB3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@dandeluce This is utter bullshit and you should be ashamed as a reporter for peddling this kind of regime-change… https://t.co/15gZbG3GXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sam_Rasoul @GOP For some of us 🐂🐮 are our business. Thus cows = working families.   Massive increases in energy co… https://t.co/Fc15FNmsk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antoniomazzaNYR @ChampionsLeague @TSN_Sports @Sportsnet Driving now... still in ot ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amazing thing about #AOC is that she has no clue how utterly stupid her ideas are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[whole dam squad on a party plane headin south CATCH YA LATER WEATHER WTH 🌨🎉🛫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseGavin1 @ChetsTeam Good point. May have to be addressed at the PL meeting Wednesday night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djadamscott @FerryCorsten @iBluestone @alpha9music @grummmusic @jordansuckley @apex_presents @leocasagrande]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrBoringJustin Why does Rock Steady remind of something from Its Always Sunny?  Like it should be playing over a montage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaileyPittipat @washingtonpost It demands we love them... and we do.  You know nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldAShults @seanmccoy Wild Don Buggythrush is gonna have to get cut]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if AOC believes the crap she is saying.  Maybe she’s a product of the public education system.  Regardless… https://t.co/VA5Ny1wZKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tony Vehon Owner of Weichert Lake Realty celebrates 60 years! #weichertcourtneyvalleywide #realtorlife #weichert… https://t.co/5yCGhAsv4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevin_2LadyGaga Very powerful performance Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I its Sunday and Daylight Savings time the Sunrise is at 7:36 a.m. and Sunset is at 7:13 p.m. https://t.co/gg9eNViW2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MangaCast Boy do I know the strength of an Imperial Stout. They can lay you out. But so good and tasty!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @Chrisman_hoops coaches and squad for their win today!  So proud of you guys... keep it going Saturday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @LeoDube ! Please follow all these great patriots. #BuildTheWall #MAGA #DrainTheSwamp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blue Point Beach Plum Gose cans now available. https://t.co/hxoBNNBVjw @BluePointBrewer #BeerMenus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames I hope you enjoyed passing Michael Jordan on the all-time scoring list by celebrating it with strangers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Travel safely friends. You won’t find this girl on a Boeing 737 max until they figure out what’s going on! 2 crashe… https://t.co/U2awIu236R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Sean can you explain McCarthyism in better detail on your show tonight. I get the jest, but I cannot r… https://t.co/pkcRfUJE2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a King of Shoals by @crookedcan at @raglanroadpub — https://t.co/rWmLWLqmPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielbrown777 @RtR_YHWH Put that up on Politico ... CNN  ... The People of God know the Word or they're are supposed to .....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me Kristin and AJ look forward to this night each year!! Lots of fun, and a chance to try new foods! Thank you… https://t.co/BBDlEXZj8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSlaughter33 @KathyGNorris @Bananabang74 @EricTrump 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂........ infinity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hazels and Huckleberries! (Hazelnut Nut and Dark Chocolate Bavarois, Huckleberry gel, Hazelnut praline, Chocolate E… https://t.co/67OgNaZ4L5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Albany Georgia!! See yall tomorrow night! @ Harvest Moon https://t.co/CfW12kAXVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SepulvedAllende En realidad sepúlved Eres tremendo enfermo mental el pueblo está pasando hambre necesidades no hay… https://t.co/2MkNltihqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must put the Republican party on stand. We must start investigating the Republican party in a whole. For some re… https://t.co/GsCJiTsoUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNK!!! Congratulations @USMAN84kg #Lopers4Life  @UNK_Athletics @loperwrestling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shitting on @DaneCook and his comeback tour is the most hack thing ever. Like the dude or not, he launched standup… https://t.co/B2IPeZ3dVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @senatemajldr the problem is, wanting those who are not considered as citizens allowed to vote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ghost in the darkness looking through  my soul's window glass. I vow  not too look  at what's looking  back. This w… https://t.co/EfhRZYTVeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Revival”                        come out to abilenebarandlounge on March 23rd. #fortherecord #jackwest… https://t.co/3PHwqgKJyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SUBjectiveMMA I get ur point but don’t we want to see fighters make more money? We want to see the fighters get pa… https://t.co/eqiKnHExlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheOrville is quite possibly the biggest piece of shit of a TV show I've ever seen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allmighty_O I am also. Nooch, in the last year, has become a pop culture phenomenon. Dude is going to ball out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Rancho Mirage, California https://t.co/Wj34pxRj8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s going to be interesting to see the contract difference between Bogdanovic and Kris Middleton this summer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WOMAXO @Sowokeitswoke @AOC You must not pay attention or listen to the show. I give it to the Right all the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#repost It takes nothing to join the crowd. It takes everything to stand alone. #beseparate “Therefore come out fro… https://t.co/brRqZkL7dL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anybody really want this a****** in the White House? https://t.co/CDUU2jUOKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pay close attention to who needed the close direction on a fucking harmony— and then turned to Dorinda to give her… https://t.co/0a4o5ktR57]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toney2020 @LadySif2017 @jomareewade @fenrir_71 @saltymom51 @DragonStone1963 @LiberalVenom @Unconquerable… https://t.co/CCUk4qZ1Xq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Foodiechats @Thrillist @BodegasLan @Attems_wines @CesariniSforza No need to spend big money in good wine! Ask your… https://t.co/KM5BMAGTYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will California’s bullet train be derailed by a waffling governor and a petty president?: A little over a decade ag… https://t.co/1ZNDbjOvMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimesilverman @AOC The telecom companies you just mentioned compete heavily in many sectors ... therefore they are… https://t.co/zqyP07vM5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zwash300 Want to look at the new data (midday)...check out my #podcast later this PM for details on both systems!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tesla What is going on.... Do you actually think any of these through before doing them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I'm kinda new to this ultra violence stuff and @GCWrestling_ #TheySaid but whose Nick gages manager? That dude just screams money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For anyone who's following along at home, I just retired from Google as of today ,, wow! I have no real plan of what to do next—any ideas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber Here you go.  500,001.  And I’m not a bot.  I’m a straight-up gangsta.  A straight-up, 48 year-old gangs… https://t.co/v0cF77sia4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodzillaMendoza @YuriLowenthal @SupSpiderTalk Don't you mean https://t.co/FGvIZBnjWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place Song Spotlight  Featured Songs for February 19, 2019  Hippie Death Cult - Black Snake https://t.co/w2O0kZ4ZDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenVaderr Facts! I love your profile pic but I’m still a BIG Kakashi fan. https://t.co/WbiDbaxMed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattJonesRadio He’s not doing that. You know that. You know the barbarians are a historical fact. Quit trying to further divide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@david_caughlin @TheRickWilson Repeat this.....Dems are the party of Slavery, Jim Crow, KKK, segregation, minority… https://t.co/df9qV347QC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Several United Ways follow up on #UnitedWayChat by creating @TwitterMoments to share their contributions.   Scroll… https://t.co/QPWaPXxsXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday morning reflection: Lost in the MAC championship to a well coached and talented Flint Hill team. Didn’t make… https://t.co/FTT0sLIGhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Search me, God, and know my heart; test me and know my anxious thoughts. See if there is any offensive way in me,… https://t.co/vclche0plA]]></document></documents></author>