<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Padres can I have a 300 million dollar contract now I can kinda still play]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BFinnegan @JCole4VA @jessfosterva @ronnierossva @SallyLHudson @JK4Delegate You too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hottest take I’ve had in years, 7 Rings bangs. Will be discussed on our podcast, tune in]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieZipperer @RealJamesWoods @AdamSchiff Same weak jaw and no neck.  Reptilian.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggiebrinker I always go with the regrettably unable to attend option. Delicious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you know how my neighbors went to jail and one went to hospital... well I think they are back together or some s… https://t.co/dhbMe2Uh6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wonder how my personality would be if I never started dancing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catzmiaou @DirtyAlarmClock @Chris_TOMP @ejscott I think that there was an interview where Charlie Cox also mention… https://t.co/FKDh5nqWxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night, I saw light at 6AM.  This morning, there's a little light getting into @ThePressofAC.  It's happening. https://t.co/01j6IcbqDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where There Are No limits on Your Dreams. #SHIFT'19 @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/6GJzsmyNcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirkajoseph I actually went up to SoFo with some friends. Was packed and pretty fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BisonDynamic @TheHoopCentral Ok yeah if he gets 49 and 15 for the last 20 games we can give him Roy]]></document><document><![CDATA[These dinner is for my birthday #HappyBirthdayToMe2019 🎁🎊🎉🎈🎂 https://t.co/KEKQXU6g5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game 2 is about to begin! #GoBears #TCSBears #OFSAA #basketball @ London, Ontario https://t.co/pXMYnKwE8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Final5Linemen @DrakeMetcalf60 @EarnestGreene_ @Nofoafia77 @Taiheeeem @77jwilliams @koreyforeman54 @LeshaunBell… https://t.co/ngbwbg2POa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it can happen. I hope one day it happens. But a Pull Up episode with Kanye is needed. Not only for the cult… https://t.co/CUnG5PDaFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[can someone tell @jbalvin i want to sit in one of his studio sessions... he be drop’n BANGERZ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a Pretzel Pride State Weekend! Boys wrestling, Girls Bowling, Speech.  #pretzelpride]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rustyrockets retweet for vets! 11% of homeless are veterans. with ptsd and mental health issues. Venmo rob-donley-… https://t.co/0SmTypybYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish someone would look at me the way the dinner guests look at @McConaughey playing pool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Hudson @maggieNYT Sloppy tweet for someone who writes on deadlines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE we need better a better guest host for #WrestleMania35 dude was an idiot on #RAW saying Wrestleing is "fake" t… https://t.co/pED75FQ8EF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeasideScribe @KamalaHarris There was no power grab. Congress gave Presidents the authority to declare emergencies… https://t.co/8dWStiKUT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 25th amendment, surprising to many people, is very legal and very cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UMassAmherst is now ranked higher than North Carolina State, Virginia Tech, Michigan State and Indiana University.… https://t.co/W54NMZ68JT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sucks being 38 and seeing shit u hated, like camo pants, come back into style w 23 yr olds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahNRO You are almost as popular as Pippa &amp; Zoë ? Happy Birthday to you and Good Luck to the ladies in the finals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattcoss78 Proof: If anyone has ever doubted eastern Iowa and the MAC conference as both elite and bowling powerho… https://t.co/j7yag1yXgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good , now I have another reason not to go there that isn’t because the food tastes like shit. https://t.co/AwDi3H3KNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My date from the other night hasn’t texted me and I’m honestly so offended like how dare you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylanpetersedu Sharing his experience and expertise in #gamification and #studentmastery using the @Classcraft pla… https://t.co/hjsKG6jeGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have never looked less forward to a premiere Celtics game as much as tonight. There is no hope in sight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite moments from last night. My mom playing simon says with some of the kids. No video games, no com… https://t.co/jj0OI9Zuad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chriswhitsett I know right? It’s as bad as probably any other low cost airline (aka absolutely terrible).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Mr Skin dot com for your lifetime achievement Oscar  https://t.co/kkt6qMLDxa You did so much for a generation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsburlzzz His parents should be fired from their jobs. These people are racist and to have a 7 year old doing thi… https://t.co/fzq5kfkYNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @GiantTVNiagara and @balsommike for having Adam and I on! I’m excited to hear the final result :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@passantino You’re such a Great reporter...let’s hear you refute with facts rather than try to ban speech.]]></document><document><![CDATA[95, 21, 38, 12, 10, 41, 8, 19, 36, 37 are all now OUT of the race.  #Daytona500 | #nascar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicken wings on the big green egg, taco bar, and cold beer. All good ingredients for a successful Daytona 500.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m subbing for this guy’s Mom. The kids think it’s the coolest thing ever that her son is doing what he’s doing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[that was the day I found out that women like to fight a lot more than men at parties tbh  Most men really just be i… https://t.co/LTeKYD7Mqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @RobinhoodApp and we'll both get a stock like $AAPL, $F, or $S for free. Make sure to use my link.  https://t.co/tVhwBZUqnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carpshaw @TheChadColby I just met with ACG consultants out of Princeton IL and they seem to be the real deal!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/nAcCG2ZQEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there is a bubble in the economy right now that nobody is talking about it is probably these clowns. Assuming al… https://t.co/Zu6YAqrGVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty is looking for talented professionals to join our amazing team! We are hiring in Long Beach, CA. If int… https://t.co/eo46zmax5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited... Here’s my poll question... Who is your favorite #GameOfThrones character? . . .  #GetUpDC @wusa9… https://t.co/cy8owwhkTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't you just hate it when you can't block a Troll before they drop off]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll probably treat myself to BDUBS tomorrow because I’m my own Valentine and that’s where I asked myself to go😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 They aren't trying to take either. Just asking for reasonable and proper use of both!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chavez came on as CEO on Oct. 1, 2011. She was paid $98,000 for three months of work in 2011 out of a salary of $39… https://t.co/5qnmC5crIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karrie56383927 @agueros_henry @Pamogram @DFBHarvard @ILMFOrg @AOC That comment is racist and classist. Just saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StocktonAlexus They are the most special conversations. You keep those moments with you forever. 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y-  why hide this from the world? C- I have no video.  I have been fighting demons and you want my worm hole knowle… https://t.co/hdZPFAI6ab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stuttsy @artdeco82 @MeltzerSaidWhat Mitchell Rule &gt; Los Conquistadors]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to APUSHer Evan W. &amp; the rest of the mockers! Way to shine!!! #SCNPride]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monicaaespinoza @lindseybwashere People can only see what is front of them don’t think about the consequences of the future]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YesWeCan4Us @B52Malmet @ddknyt @NYTBen @MarkLandler @MarkMazzettiNYT More than one got @IvankaTrump is right in this mix as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse was so much better the second time around, I’m just going to stay watching it 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattyJenks @SamoanJYandall @GalGadot @brielarson Great sentiment. This is why I don’t delete twitter. 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems like getting rid of the filibuster would increase the volatility of public policy, more than promoting any… https://t.co/Wx4xOniWKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chuckles152 I did for about a week or more after a hurricane. Summer time not fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast at @SMTF_Cbus at the Arnold meet up, see everyone at the expo tomorrow! #morphogennutrition #mntakeover… https://t.co/VR36oQjqqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to wish a very happy birthday to a very lovely young lady who I absolutely love and adore and am a hug… https://t.co/AF3Z7BTruv]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the winner for the “most ironic tweet in the history of Twitter” goes to.....    CC: @ClayTravis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nfldraftscout @ConnorJRogers @mello  What do you guys think of this trade Jets Deal pick 3 to Steelers for pick 20… https://t.co/U4pQpvVr9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fourmeows Mom read she can freeze them individually and give as a crunchy snack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spotify @spotifydesign Is it possible to request to be able to rearrange my list of playlists? I have playlists ra… https://t.co/qX8R2h4G5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrantHile Sometimes you’ve got to know when you’re a shade of who you once were 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[there is beauty in simplicity 🦋 @ Kings Beach, California https://t.co/0Ej9oYtdDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayo they really paid Soul Train dancers in KFC chicken😂 a damn 2 piece.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3Miyagi @DreddCNC @F3DOAH @43feetPodcast @F3Nation Is it @F3RoundTable topic you can discuss and share?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ask all of the players who have fought the league over medical care. The protest movement has been a huge prob… https://t.co/MO8Z8SRG46]]></document><document><![CDATA[White girls obsessed with movies about lovers with chronic diseases damn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tictoc @AOC @BillNye CIVICS. CITIZENSHIP! Bring it on @AOC. Why the HELL isn't every member of Congress talking like this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaEedge @SavoieEagles @JennyChanRemka @mrsdelby That’s my aunt on the bottom right of the photo in the blue shirt!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I realize I need to stop trying so hard to cheer people up. It makes me depressed after a while.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilyMarsWrites @philafelines @Barbi_Twins @ersle @PeterAskin1 @BrendaPerrott @morgfair @KittyLibFront @MeowMiya88… https://t.co/BLoGuIGEuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CEDVersion2 They way they are currently playing would you?? Maybe a backup goalie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great game @vcu_hoops  #vcubasketball #vcuhoops #WeRunRVA #sportphotography #photography #CollegeHoops #ramnation… https://t.co/jbk3gT63fQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanadaFP @cafreeland @RalphGoodale @BillBlair @csiscanada @CIGIonline  @MercedesGlobal Have U informed consulted w… https://t.co/xZtQxjH7yf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir How is it possible to earn points while flying on points?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Building a wall is a CAMPAIGN PROMISE not a national emergency. Trump is declaring an emergency because he wants to… https://t.co/67Ti5sIhfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s some math, the median wage for High School grads is $30,000 ish, the median wage for college grads is like $… https://t.co/rJcplMJyn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArseQueef It’s really cool. I love how different it is from Crit Role, too. Very different styles and they both wo… https://t.co/3vKh9tCd0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goatadamsOKC Any elite QB from the past 10 years could succeed in New England]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickjonas @joejonas @kevinjonas It’s 1:37am here and I am jamming out🔥 #sucker #TheJonasBrothers https://t.co/GXsfkTl6C6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Panther did have a great score, but the fact that it won the Oscar while Hans Zimmer in The Dark Knight didn’t is beyond criminal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread is worth reading. Whoever can propose a credible solution can get elected President in 2020. (Draft… https://t.co/yzY15PsubV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/bTaky5SpgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skinner is healthy!!! Holy shit. @MattBarnaby3636 was way off, but I didn’t think so myself after seeing replay. Looked brutal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He was one of those guards who controlled a game in a lot of different ways, with his scoring, passing and his clu… https://t.co/KYOhBcLdH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LBarbs35 I grew up with Queen!!! Music today Sucks Compared to the 70's 80's. Just watched Bohemian Rhapsody the other day. It was great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatePickowicz That’s a pretty niche tweet. Translation for the rest of us?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvesBaseballSTL He is one of the greatest closers of all time with years yet to add to his stats. However he also… https://t.co/q2bxmCUkkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pelosi if you want seperate powers to function try doing your part instead of acting like a criminal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why must you lie sir? Why? It is absolutely no problem that a person misspeaks while talking, ever… https://t.co/TOn7gfFPD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not necessarily agreeing with the message, but this is still funny. @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/ULvHprdsmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I’m listening to the YES Featuring JON ANDERSON, TREVOR RABIN and RICK WAKEMAN Live At The Apollo, I’m reminded… https://t.co/JWzVDrEQEV]]></document></documents></author>