<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett lied to police before during a DUI arrest. Signed a citation using his brothers identity and was ch… https://t.co/Z3Ho4qdbP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperBookUSA @ViewFromVegas Will there be any contest for the first two days of the NCAA tournament this year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating #wonderwomen in my life and around the world, especially my #mom and #queen 👸Jennie Harrichand ... you’… https://t.co/maPYKcsMGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every YEAR...it’s the church of baseball, we are born again into a new season of HOPE!! Best of luck this year!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eakayamusic I’m listening to your EP on my drive to work this morning. I love every song! I’m going to have this on repeat for a while. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[This State of Emergency is unconstitutional &amp; a gross abuse of presidential power.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cena de matrimonios, gracias por sus oraciones. ¡Dios es muy bueno! en Iglesia Evangelica San Pablo sitio Playas de… https://t.co/URQK0hsjYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[my two braincells telling eachother to go to sleep https://t.co/AdhSns37sD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA @RealJamesWoods @michaelstrahan @KenMatthews so GMA, how come no story on why police have to be very cautious… https://t.co/cxsWgQ6T3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Climbing in Ouray Ice Park today. Beautifully cold conditions. Contacts froze in its solution while we slept in van… https://t.co/MxOD2mGRjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Microsoft release three new seasonal wallpaper packs for Windows 10 https://t.co/oV7cWUhHhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was trying to go for flower names, but lilac is my favorite color so I figured I’d name my dog lila... i also rea… https://t.co/2qOaYFL6Tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[We out here again!!! Burn bisshhhhh burn! 💪🏽🥺 @BasecampWeHo https://t.co/Fqi2RvOA4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Infusion A: Peanut Butter Chocolate Coffee Porter by @hoppinfrog at @hoppinfrog — https://t.co/ozX27fNMeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao pro golfers who play in the best conditions all year long whining their asses off about “mud balls” stfu and p… https://t.co/RBUdX2wgX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notalexpfeffer Oh damn, back on Twitter too I see. You’ve just completely cracked huh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rach_Ryz I’ve found that generally if they say that jokingly, it’s still not a joke. They mean it. I could go on and on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There’s a spot to be had — and someone’s gonna get it — so it might as well be you.” @SheaSerrano]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does the door and floor have to be so loud when I’m sneaking back into the my house]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Holli_Rox @the_amish_txtr Listening to the podcast. I would tell her, all that you can amass money, fame, power en… https://t.co/R7SONTNBvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSN Bahahahaha the stupid bitch! She got what she deserved. Now halfwit, was that picture really worth it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel @JMUOSU You just did it again. Nobody is lecturing refugees from totalitarian regimes. Buy *you* are c… https://t.co/TqPjmpj5cu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise Movement paid McConnell a visit today. The hashtag for this is #OilMoneyMitch, they’re taking aim at campai… https://t.co/VqINfx1Yb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RondaRousey @RubyRiottWWE @RondaRousey I really liked your Sonya Blade look. I tried to recreate it..What do you t… https://t.co/ekNctFTBCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[REPORTING: Oklahoma City office market: Stuck but not stalled #CRE https://t.co/TR92H3zxSC via @newsok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyParrillo @RayGun0231 “Loose”? Well done, Master of Rhetoric. The debate bar is low on Tea Party Twitter, ain’t it, Voltaire?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you struggling to get a tighter core?  Try this #coreworkout as a finisher to any workout...  10 to 25 lb.… https://t.co/ENrzJESvCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consternado por la partida de la gran actriz #CristianBach ,que en los 80s cautivó con su talento,belleza y gentile… https://t.co/3RcfitJjSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends would have made me do 21 rounds of 21 shots within 5 minutes.......okay you got me.....its me I'm my fri… https://t.co/EmiaplNTcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr  Davis has helped out his Yale University Law School classmates, Bill and Hillary Clinton, includin… https://t.co/Xw5ee28i6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarketWatch Very UNAMERICAN and WAST FRAUD and ABUSE.  Protect USA from DRUGS, HUMAN TRAFFICKING, HEALTH/DESEASE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alainapinto @AmakaUbakaTV @KaitlinMcCulley @KimLucey @kekevencill To a very special news crew, wishing you all a H… https://t.co/EWjq9OBrN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames @NBATV @BleacherReport @GrantNapearshow #Sacramentoproud #NBATwitterLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarceeH2 Not jealous....they just showed who you always were....we have moved on....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLeavine @kaseykahne @mattdracing @ToyotaRacing @JoeGibbsRacing It’s ready for the Earnhardt Grave Yard for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePlumLineGS @JaneMayerNYer Try reporting something that's not 2 years and never went through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ContrarianShort 😂😂😂WHY IS THE MARKET SELLING?!? IT MUST BE THE SHORT SELLERS! STOP THEM FROM SELLING SO ONLY LONG BAGHOLDERS CAN SELL!!!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbara79167636 @kimmyifuplease @joefaz Where do they get this fuckhead from?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Jarrett Culver for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/FMjELAtNE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarryArnettCG @dhorlander @fanofrockytop @JasonFinleyCG @CallawayGolf How long do you think it’s going to take for… https://t.co/LIBprmf9lg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DustinMulvaney @SaveTheDesert @cody_a_hill A late thought: Start with all the public parking lots and rooftops.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is one of the reasons that Pence has no business being the person that takes Trump's place if it happens to be… https://t.co/F6sZL8kkOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @SouthwestAir no #wifi on this flight to Phoenix for #WLPC. I may know a few people who could help fix it...the… https://t.co/M5dBzqb6Wm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cycle continues.  #dotheknowledge @ South Orange, New Jersey https://t.co/YEsf3bHmxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was watching Hulu last night and I literally had an add in an add Jesus Christ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In one of my most special roles, I support principals.” @vpriceless Leaders draw us into a narrative that guides u… https://t.co/EVem5HFX8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FEFecuador Perdon. Pero este senor ha fracasado muchas veces y todavia sigue de tecnico de menores. Les deseo suer… https://t.co/Y1U59gMOkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[just got my drone yesterday so expect me to have the videography game in a head lock this year https://t.co/88o4Ybst2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[And as far as aged animals go? I guess Bubbles isn't THAT old. But man do I feel bad for this senior citizen chimp.… https://t.co/ob4920S2d7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woman are just as bad as men. You agree to lunch. I drive all the way to Dallas so you don’t have to drive. You tel… https://t.co/XwNc4M05RM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reverse Pyramid Training.  Day #15 - Legs, Shoulders, Abs. #BeastModeLifestyle👊💪💪👊  #HealthyLifestyle🙏❤❤🙏.... @ Pow… https://t.co/qWHQWeAJhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McWhorter_67 You know how it is 😂🤷🏻‍♂️ Down on the sideline getting cold as heck some nights]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cyber metrics ruined baseball. Mother fuckers turned sports into accounting are baffled when America’s got talent o… https://t.co/huM52cqMgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are so many smart people, how do they come up with this shit? It’s great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm...I’m starting to think I forgot to post something hours ago...Oh YEAH! #VamosTigres]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoaquinCastrotx @Sifill_LDF @realDonaldTrump How about a resolution to terminate his presidency !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pacelattin @DonaldJTrumpJr Do you idiots actually read this shit before you press the reply button? Numb nuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cleft_Music @NC5 @AP Ask the PEOPLE of El Paso!! Or ask Beto and his 100 supporters that showed up this week... it… https://t.co/3NMf8vrIRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a very long week! Time to bring it to a close. G’night never never land.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when you get up close to someone who you thought was beautiful from afar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OdyReturns I don’t blame America for all of the worlds ills.  We just need to do a lot more leading by example rat… https://t.co/inAwNAQdsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[... oggi è' festa degli innamorati ... anche se e' scontato faccio gli auguri a tutte le persone innamorate come me… https://t.co/W5KYX6hx83]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s make it a productive week people! You can reach your goals by being kind. #CoachSgro #EmpathicLeadership https://t.co/DVNyOuOSus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BballCoachMac @CoachCollinsJMM Right on the nose.  The point guard is an extension of the coach on the floor.  The… https://t.co/k1GV34vHiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RehabAllStar @CoachHoover Great job Justin Hoover his personnel QB coach for the last 8+ years!!! #spinit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect time to need a OT for the Bills. Some decent FA options too. Flexibility for them to get upgrade there for… https://t.co/mHAj8NH6yL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siempre estos opositores mienten para recibir ayuda monetaria.Pasa lo mismo q en Cuba alla los gringos se cabrearon… https://t.co/ki1KyENaEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YulieannaDuran @had_rebel419 I’ll definitely come by soon love ! Hope you beautiful souls are doing well💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MATTERhealth A great example of established and emerging companies coming together to make a difference… https://t.co/nEaC8ooLPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨😄🚨  The first time I did a ring muscle up I was excited to add the movement to my competitive "repertoire." I was… https://t.co/8KsxK6fGOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Trump lawyer Ty Cobb calls Robert Mueller 'an American hero'  https://t.co/bEBYvQAvB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #CrookedTrump #LockHimUp #VietnamDraftDodger #Dishonorable #LockHimUp #CrookedTrump #ImpeachTrump… https://t.co/Ih6PnbwvDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Libertea2012 ISIS sleeper cells abound and it has already matasticized into other regions. Thousands of ISIS warri… https://t.co/JL3VpMecay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some more pics from the @ameripolitan awards. 😎🏆🎸 #Ameripolitan @ The Guest House at Graceland https://t.co/1fSmgMKbnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team tell us whats really in the meat you sell to people...... ill wait ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brenna__brown this feels like the type of thing you would do... https://t.co/RkK2jjt3LC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game day! Prepping &amp; testing @espn college basketball graphics. 🤙🏻🎨🏀  #GraphicDesign | #VideoProduction https://t.co/f9SoWq1ebN]]></document><document><![CDATA[🅰️🅰️🅰️🅰️🅰️🅰️🅰️🅰️🅰️🅰️🅰️  Making Some Moves this Weekend in the A. Need to Connect 🔌 with the Movers and Shakers.  Pl… https://t.co/qQlJDI6Bfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DmitriiZelenkov gorgeous indeed, great meeting u on Twitter, enjoy my latest horror film review 13 HOURS IN A WARE… https://t.co/FSV0epV58W]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all animal rights activists who feel pet ownership is slavery, come talk to Bo....but wait until after his nap p… https://t.co/TCbaWo43fD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always say @luchalibreaaa is best company out there but w @Ozsuicideaaa @vampiro_vampiro on commentary it's even… https://t.co/eSPZPxIojh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arista Extends Hybrid Cloud Networking Solution for Microsoft Azure Stack - Arista https://t.co/gGSvatbwkF via… https://t.co/3iB2fDw2I9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The welterweight division is so stacked. You gotta go Usman vs Colby for the title. Would love to see Askren vs the… https://t.co/qnG3NqgRp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its getting to that point when my family asks for kids. And in freaking out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I’m pissed that I have to wait another two months to go to the lake]]></document><document><![CDATA[We do the same... only out of a 4-3 ... it is a way for us to be multiple while maintaining simplicity...:… https://t.co/RepOgDwXjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christopher Wren died 296 years ago today in St James's, London, England age 90, astronomer, architect, St. Paul's… https://t.co/QAhvCasoH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord, Thank you for ever-increasing faith; I can have whatever I believe without any doubt in my heart. Father, tha… https://t.co/vu9MqHb9ub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @RepDanCrenshaw @SecNielsen Good for Rep. Crenshaw for standing up against the Administration’s lies, propaganda and distorted truths.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigDaddyBoone98 Asking is the first step.  Hit me up if you want some help with the “interpretation.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estimado Andrés Velázquez, la narco dictadura se le adelantó: paralizó totalmente al país para demostrarnos que al… https://t.co/gt4Qy9TZOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got the #win !  @UCLAMBB holds on for the W. #GoBruins #Pac12Hoops https://t.co/OQoOwRojQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeensCa @Thor4306 @RazorPack65 @GroupHomepage I know I'm seeing them too n won't retweet them. People don't watch… https://t.co/ZRIivL2NQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at base lodge bar whitefish in MT https://t.co/EZWERhYUAI https://t.co/tmlGNyV2Da]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VaticanNews Interesting. I wonder if the pope has ever given any thought about the souls of these "poor" people?… https://t.co/pYVHNgVMmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good times lol or getting Charlie Horsed and coming g home with bloody kneecaps from the turf or dry grass👎🏽👎🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Persian military invaded, they heard about the gold, the teachings and everything scared, Africa was almost rob… https://t.co/yNk29orxnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard a radio commercial for a Family Dentist who practices, "faith based dentistry."  Thats funny, I don't remembe… https://t.co/fq5Lh1jgZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irduxbury @stephenfry @RichardDawkins @center4inquiry No. Check Campbell, The China Study. The data is there. You've  been misled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How stupid can these ppl b they got my phone hacked read and see everything i write but didnt think the government… https://t.co/DkukM5H1H5]]></document></documents></author>