<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@kaileamckeehan1 I feel ya girl...I have to be up in 4 and wide awake 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌫🌫🌫 What do y’all think of this Master Bath transformation I designed?  . Swipe to see more and the before tub area… https://t.co/HpS9con8Fs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Night Karaoke! #thesetwo #shallow #love #sundayfunday @ Backman's Neighborhood Pub https://t.co/aZEgn1GYpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[and of course the popular kid who everyone swore had a third nipple, wrote about that for an English class fiction… https://t.co/Tf5IesFPvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never sleep tonight and i gott be up in &lt;4 hours for work. Not even just work. Weekend work. Which is by far worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People treat Facebook like a platform for narcissistic press releases haha and I swear anyone who starts a Facebook… https://t.co/2ntCPJHyat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only do we fear death, we fear suffering as well. We all desire to prosper and to live a good life. In the OT,… https://t.co/wkrHRL9aM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baad_kittee @joncoopertweets @JoeBiden @KamalaHarris Apparently 243+ years isn’t enough time for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @EdKrassen Brian, your tweets are so welcomed and stirring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pray that @dansmyers remember what he told me last night cause I’m really looking forward to August 🙏🙌🏻 @DanAndShay @ShayMooney 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You wish POS. I am loving all of the prosecutors in SDNY, Washington etc. your crime family is going down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me driving with others in the car is a whole different person than me driving alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little ballet to end a great week of rehearsals 💃🏼 #RoyalTalent #JewelOfTheSeas2019 #JewelRound2 #MiamiCityBallet… https://t.co/ua2mgh41fc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFienPrint There was a Porky's / Kentucky Fried movie appeal to The Happytime Murders I enjoyed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferAydin She did so good!!LOVE YOU TONS JENNIFER!! You are WELL SEASONED NOW!!@RHONJ👛💄👄💕👑 @JENNIFERAydin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traceyram @NDP I think there was no route to save some of those jobs despite every effort.  Sears has closed its d… https://t.co/UJ9ZLHTwna]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mardi Gras 🎭 | #MardiGras2019 #TiffanyCaines @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/iy9eKiCGTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[EARLY RELEASE!! #imaverystylishgirl #wrappingpaper #linkinthebio https://t.co/7qCzu8CnQe @ Durham, North Carolina https://t.co/R4psGIhBZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTBD1 We hear you! We have an LPM Alpha coming up. Will PM you the invite...]]></document><document><![CDATA[WCW - MEEEEEE!  I have to honest “IG BABIES”! Social Media is EXHAUSTING!   We are constantly bombarded by images o… https://t.co/cMZK429Q2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitRECordJoe I held a snake for the first time  Saturday night! https://t.co/7FQ3axUUah]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is just a bummer when a girl – human or dragon – only exists to inspire their male counterpart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monptitchou Would send this guy your way if I could! 😝 https://t.co/iI7tOyQ0x6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wareslab @pastramimachine I just started drinking coffee a few years ago. Still hate it, but with enough cream and… https://t.co/J2l0dAIsk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kailah_casillas I love how u list ur part of Lohan’s Beach Club! U for real need to take that off or add Fired to… https://t.co/xNftVHnInl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been so excited for workout clothes and for the gym. Thank you @Gymshark 🥰🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still confused how there’s no good boba in sac they have damn near everything up here]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC folks should all tune into @InsideCityHall w @errollouis tonight. All the Amazon reax!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, BirthriteStrike!  You don’t want babies?  Thank you!   We don’t need more of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning!☀️   . . . . #willowthecat #willowthepillow #willowthepillowcat #persian #blacksmoke #cats #cat… https://t.co/rIZcMLymRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a cousin on my dad’s side that plays football.....and idek him....but I need to get in touch with my dad’s d… https://t.co/JDpTRsEeZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PRETTYMUCH you guys don’t need to explain yourselves, but we can’t wait for what you guys have coming 🤞🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Craving that type of drunk drunk where I’ll wake up and not remember what I did the night before drunk drunk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonDemersKTIV4 I  used to drive in that mess everyday from Sioux City to Orange City in blowing snow, blizzards an… https://t.co/8ZE02bvQWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wynton_Mohorn @KingJames @blackishabc @funnyblackdude @MilesBrown I liked this because I'm from Chicago and grew u… https://t.co/FBCsJjSU4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherA9 @Mamabear0772 @TheTinyTomboy @Frigga81 LMAO, exactly!  Perfect GIF 😁💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@24thunder1 @Trailworker82 @krassenstein Your hired...the position is yours as long as you promise not to obey the… https://t.co/R9tQczu9PV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehailstorm_ For sure! We’re all busy and the poll I went to only had 3 computers open, so if there was a wait th… https://t.co/dFoHLypMm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bachelorette weekend for this sweet friend of mine. We love you Rach! 👯‍♀️💍🥂 @ Downtown Chattanooga https://t.co/2JgxnL1lfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve really been so busy lately I’ve had no free time, so don’t take it personal if I can’t hang out with you 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so cold this morning I forgot to say good morning. My coffee was ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Not like Barack O didn’t overuse/abuse executive power! Just about every day of his two terms!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandallKingBand @RiverRoadIH @TristonMarez @michaelasgio @sarahgracewood @morgancarey21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimsMom3 Kind of crazy they were filming at The Washington Monument the day of our #FakeNationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awkward silence after Pence mentions Trump in speech - CNN Video https://t.co/8Pf5k2KNOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Donna.  I was born to be honest.  My age is still uploading. I like to go with it. https://t.co/txejMbYHiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@godishermes imma call out everyone’s annoying asses if i stay on my phone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join @JasonWitten and definitely call @tonyromo!  We miss you @DeMarcusWare! #DallasCowboys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo...one of these days I'd love to read a memoir from @taylorswift13 Well I'd read anything she writes really..… https://t.co/otsjSWMZjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryan65039 @cvpayne AOC knows far more than you credit her with and your misogynistic treatment is at your own peril!]]></document><document><![CDATA[最近最高裁判事になったカバノーに比べたら良い人に見えるコーエン。逆になんでこんな人がトランプの悪事のお先棒を担いだのか疑問なくらいだ。これも犠牲者と言えるのか？]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyDelmarvaNow @lukebroadwater Cool. I’m going to start working on a list of state laws that I think my county shou… https://t.co/ii8F03rdj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliyasbars Didn't she tweak her groin recently?   Also, shout-out to my phone for auto-correcting "tweak" to "twerk."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lill_rene bruh, it's the same side..but  i wish i had two good sides. yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micfrd @Ludokine4 @Jacquiecharles @WhiteHouse The question is what’s black Ops what’s doing in Haiti?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomensDay: 4 women, including myself, washed our faces and completed our nightly skincare routines in… https://t.co/OQqzoHgUwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthPark #DrNowzardan needs to intervene #crossoverepisode ? #futurecastmember #beefcake]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone can drop off a handle of whiskey and some fruit and maybe tequila that’d be nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun night with my mom and sisters walking down nostalgia lane ~ 💕⚡️  #disneyland90snite https://t.co/srHcfVtQyl https://t.co/JHWPTVT8gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahKohut @ilikedags17 @Axels15 @RebeccaBuck @sppeoples I work at Northwestern in HR and our building is right there. I knew it was a lie]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Shallow’ is cool and all but have you ever heard ‘Always Remember Us This Way’ ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the most recent issue of @ArthritisDigest! https://t.co/5oX3uwD28l https://t.co/SikiBIK0zV]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the oldest strains around, and still one of the best 👌🏼👌🏼🌬🥰 #ogkush #indica #landrace #love… https://t.co/9GBimH7oDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[you think that the  moon landing was a hoax???? trust me..  i was there! https://t.co/qgUaR9VsmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on circuits with our 5th grade buddies! @KStrzempka @Grandview_Elem https://t.co/OLCciTwcyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I'm speaking into exsistence for NM5 -Single debut top 10 -3-5 collabs (Ari, Bey, Jay Z, Post Malone, Lil Wa… https://t.co/P59AIfJGu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanted to put it out there that I wore some super cute camel boots today that I bought even though they are ki… https://t.co/WTNK0tjdaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tras asaltar a un taxista en la colonia Lázaro Cárdenas, Víctor,  de 24 años,fue detenido por elementos de la… https://t.co/buteuF9AD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well... @ChickfilA  decided I didn't need the top of the biscuit. 😀😀 https://t.co/8dN6cMQSCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janielkawaii2 @MisterPreda What do you think happen I @JoeyGraceffa And @MisterPreda weren’t getting married for a long time🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also have to find where i left off in GoT because I passssseddd out 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CGProgram I even saw parents from other Clovis Unified schools come out to support.  Yes, we all have our rivalrie… https://t.co/5bkhy5NlSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That’s a #nationalemergency not your ridiculous wall... #guncontrolnow #childrenbeforenra #stoptheinsanity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @AmericanExpress for winning the Breakthrough #CX award - well deserved! @lmalalanne #QualtricsX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arich424 or throw a fit when you were winning so I turned it off before you actually won]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GwinnettSO @JamesCraigmyle @gototheshack #LivePD #LivePDNation #shenanigans]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sing the #lord is my #strength #God ❤️✝️🐦 #music #givethanks 🙏🏻 https://t.co/ykZMq97CIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Women’s Day 😍   We want to celebrate this special day with our brand value - Women Aspiration 💋  To share the… https://t.co/nXuaEslCQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[As for me #VisibleWomen, I’m Carol, I was the level producer on #GodofWar @SonySantaMonica and I previously came fr… https://t.co/lXB6TLvwph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbirn1 I wish trump would just go away. STFU. He’s just a nasty cancer to our democracy! I hate him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope it’s not wrong cause the thought pops into my head at least once a day!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cannot wait to get this fucking hair fixed. Still have like 3 weeks to wait and I’m dying. https://t.co/gjreSviel3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This link is fascinating.  Students can view works by M.C Escher, read about his art process and even produce a dig… https://t.co/A1TEpqA5Sn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worlds collide!   @eorlins @benry26 brotherhood forever ✌🏻 https://t.co/zIfFBkoU6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattkir36512104 @KamalaHarris There are already background checks on voters, ignoramus. You have to show proof of… https://t.co/Y3GSZSTVP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[An edgy cut ! #hairstyles #mohawk #edgyhaircut #edgyhairstyles #mohawkfade @ Cutting Edge https://t.co/tloBzOKqLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my website https://t.co/RzzCJbKxvc and pick out some bling today https://t.co/OWIhHnw6Yk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cameron’s performance (@ Ashburn Elementary School in Ashburn, VA) https://t.co/XCQPREcF7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I visited @mediarchaeology lab, and I had this privilege to work with this amazing stencil machine!… https://t.co/o9XX0ldZb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are your choices a reflection of insanity??  What actions do you need to change? #goals #reflection #Accountability https://t.co/N8BG2afSer]]></document><document><![CDATA[He can't it's not in his nature to tell the truth. Let alone prove the truth.🤣😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[In other news how am I going to find 4 hours to critique this Joe Rogan x Alex Jones podcast invu. This is longer t… https://t.co/z9s19TOy3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton @adamlevine @kelly_clarkson @johnlegend Is there a rule this season that only @blakeshelton is allowe… https://t.co/R3a2FiHrMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you of your favorite artist comes out with NEW music and it's Frriiidaaay 🔥@dustinlynch #winning #RidinRoads]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching 1st graders how to code.  #technologyskills   Tech experts and lawmakers meet in support of new legislatio… https://t.co/dazTdn8NcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[CITY OF #LOSANGELES, 400 VOLUNTEERS PLANT 182 TREES 🌳 IN #VANNUYS https://t.co/4mFjK2L9PF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Huawei connects rural America. Could it threaten the country's most sensitive military sites?   https://t.co/FeFkV6N0O7]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@fawadchaudhry responds to @cher MoU has been submitted: Upgrade to #IslamabadZoo Training Staff &amp; #FreeKaavan… https://t.co/t6Jucgg8aZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam your not allowed to turn one mister stay 2 years old forever stop growing up @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/vDMAHIY47K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salsa Street Mexican Restaurant... OMG. This is authentic Mexican food! #salsastreet  #mexicanfood @ Randhurst Mall… https://t.co/3ikqtCzn8R]]></document></documents></author>