<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@survinmama @jack_608 @kidrev2 @IlhanMN So by Sherrie’s reasoning we can’t trust trump because he’s a liar and we c… https://t.co/gmwJmbwoXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobThomas @KenMarino Can’t wait for next installment of #VeronicaMars 🙏🏻💃🙏🏻💃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz Bunch of fake news anything to discredit the president and you of course]]></document><document><![CDATA[we went through the door in a record shop and found a chill jazz bar https://t.co/XICk7rFb73]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @ThomasRhett this is my third year trying, and I could really use a "happy birthday" from you on my 18th🤩🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PineyElem in STEAM lab it's Free Build Friday! @Colmenerohisd Kindergarten meeting all our essential skills… https://t.co/OuSyAgG3BF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman Hi Mark, Would you like to get expensive battery charger case for your iPhone 6 / 6s / 7s / 8swithout… https://t.co/xjZmRgPQn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been  picked  on periscope  because  what I  look like  and  said  things to me bad names  again  I'm soo  sick a… https://t.co/WCqtvHsGPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotSonOfGod You were suspended for giving fake spoilers on the walking dead? Unbelievable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God wants us to be the best picture of ourselves so that He can do His best work through us. Pastor Spencer Jackson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for enduring this #tidyingup day with me. Twelve hours in. I’m done. Everything is on the floor now and I am… https://t.co/SS8hnlqlDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, we were so lucky to have the @FtWorthSymphony come visit us! We learned a lot about folk and classical music… https://t.co/uviavnhgkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a vivid dream I forgot to pack my suitcase and missed my train.  Lucky me.  I have something to overthink all day! #psychology]]></document><document><![CDATA[#explore the many #benefits of #cbdoil at the #daretobeawarefair in #alvernocollege on #april6. #hempheals  Details… https://t.co/IOP7l8cZ4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sc saw it first Y’all I’ve been feeling myself 😌 https://t.co/lreZtyp2Kh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally found the song I was jamming to on @siriusxmu ! @therealkurtvile https://t.co/BB8UzbCZ9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramonGpascual @SnowRMCF @realmadrid @7Sempiterno7 Pero quién debe pararlas? La prensa que come de echar 💩 al RM?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The special reveal of our One Book, Two Schools title -every class had a letter to spell out Charlie and The Chocol… https://t.co/RFyqpbjefw]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big round of applause to these @NewLab partner researchers from @Columbia, @MIT, @Cornell for providing us new… https://t.co/cHFbV4XnuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah... so much better then blaming it on the fiscal irresponsibility of the democratic run state.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayChpJones Did anyone who signed realize  they voted to suppress freedom of speech?🤦‍♀️ The whole damn thing is rotten to the core...]]></document><document><![CDATA[最近都下雨不能出去玩，只能在家一邊看電視一邊吃東西囉XDD 今天的下午茶是冰醉豆花～～ . . . . . #food #dessert #tofupudding #instagood #weekend #食べ物 #デザート… https://t.co/CWgAhUluyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pid_gov "I did not even think about the billions of deaths" said American service member now because of what Dunfo… https://t.co/kLKary7VEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading out to watch my first #marathon ever! My girlfriend is running in it today. I can’t wait to have this exper… https://t.co/KxtNMWIdDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flynnrita149 @ForgedInFur @FeralelFeroz @timzmom @DTrump_Cat Beautiful! Wow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @DrJDrooghaag   I am so #grateful for your kind words. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LannyDavis @RepMattGaetz He should not be allowed on the House floor or in any Committee hearing. He should be cen… https://t.co/zYy0ZATJFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemolitionDan @rsshootinggirl @MichaelJSams93 @KathyMu87484671 @shearl_d @SkyviewKevin @KamalaHarris I would like… https://t.co/EemiAmQ1lD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I continue to watch depressing movies when I know I already get too emotionally attached and can’t stop crying 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joshua_4_WA @XoXo__Kellie The Bernie Bros are at it already even though the primaries haven’t happened. Maybe have… https://t.co/ZYAkUOhYZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT IS 80 DEGREES ON THE EAST COAST!!! The west is honestly so trash let me tf go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnieSchultz @SenSherrodBrown Nothing but respect for both of you. Thank you for your service. #ClassAct]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happens when you have the #flu and your @LaSalleMBB is playing at the #GolaArena? You watch it on the special… https://t.co/WRPfKQX8PI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just sent out a professional email that ended with “I am apologize”. I’ve never said anything truer in my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A really interesting concept for #leadership #fitpro Here's why work life 'fit' -- not balance -- is important | Bu… https://t.co/gsfEJ54Xsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[When life gives you lemons #embracewhoyouare #lemons #mixnmatch #beunique #locketsherpa #origamiowl #livinglocket @… https://t.co/yPTIBR99Rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmdj04 Thanks! The 10k is the easiest! Lol 😂. But it definitely felt better than the half]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s still a little early to pick a primary fave, but @PeteButtigieg reposts pics of supporters’ pets. I’m just saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeep_Familys @steelecreations @THEJeepMafia @XBullofficial @KrawlAmerica @Legendary1941 @toxicoffroad @wve1022… https://t.co/elQhGePcFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is plausible that the responsibility of the Rohingya had been delegated to The Organization of Islamic Cooperati… https://t.co/EtLQBU7obJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This tatoo is so beautiful #tatoo #beautiful #Love #art #tatoonana @ Bonney Lake, Washington https://t.co/QcFvVALqsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpsAMoron00 @benjaminwittes @qjurecic Remember, Mueller is a nothing burger. Can't find collusion, when none exists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel was brilliant and I believe every needle drop was specifically meant for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The realest facebook memory that has ever existed. #kittenlove #catmom #furbaby #kitten #cat #kitty #purr #meow… https://t.co/6m9DlpuLKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[So awesome to see @SummitCoffee so bustling this morning! Love being back “home” in @DavidsonCollege and seeing the… https://t.co/p4qSieKpVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stjamescheese @skooks @panarmstrong Agreed, dump em in the wetlands for the sludge to stick to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone who ever laid in my bed knows for a fact I sleep good every night 🛏😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of “President’s Day,” looks like #GDNY is doing a deep dive into what makes #Residenttrump click!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePerezHilton But are the telling the truth? There's going to be a bunch of them coming forth bit they could all be lying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Hey Matt Gaetz, does Mueller know you are on Twitter drunk, and threatening a witness?… https://t.co/2HUtVIKqor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar @TheOldOlaf There’s not even words for this! Really. A man personally responsible for killing many of his… https://t.co/t3gRqPEDO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anarfea And I agree, that threading is the way to go for long conversations that need nuance. I’ve read some of th… https://t.co/kEVkrlPa3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want my entire body 2 be covered in icyhot and tiger balm https://t.co/MB13iFA9GR]]></document><document><![CDATA[So inspired by @DrBurkeHarris and her passion for addressing Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACEs) as part of a heal… https://t.co/ndn8Q5FReo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you started the Journey? Amazon: https://t.co/F5Dgka5KDP CHILDREN OF STONE 1)Voices in Crystal 2) Going Forth… https://t.co/XcUfuRPzFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods There resentment now. Its unfair.  This has to be corrected now. I remember during past Olympics, R… https://t.co/yzJVt9uuxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarrySDailyEC @Harry_Styles @KaceyMusgraves #BestCoverSong #StillTheOne #iHeartAwards @Harry_Styles @KaceyMusgraves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost 38 weeks pregnant and loving it!  My baby is almost here! rcvwarrior and I are beyond grateful for this bles… https://t.co/gOeoxLHC6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mood for today as I ran out of the apartment for class https://t.co/5rV4RIteri]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheProfitCNBC The owner of the wine shop probably put the wrong address in Google Maps. #embarrassing]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to present with these fabulous ladies at @NAISnetwork annual conference . #NAISAC https://t.co/IlUqStCAgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raindrops... Inside the Apartment!!!  A G A I N !!! @ San Pedro, California https://t.co/jPK6flr2nk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Counting down the days ❤️❤️ #epcot #drinkingaroundtheworld #family #mysons #excited #disneyjunkie #disneyfan… https://t.co/outEQ6Jlpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[As Organic Farmer for our small family farm, I agree 100%! “Consumers who choose #organic food to protect themselve… https://t.co/vysLx6cycP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fine. Go on. Move to the euro calendar. I’ll finally create my long-awaited full-length cascades flag fleece blanket coat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsolomonReports After the Mueller prob is done AG Barr needs to open up an investigation of what happened with Hil… https://t.co/CCBwrw5hm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonMarduk If you fall out of tree make sure you got head gear in case you go head first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was wondering why the gym was so packed today...It’s free pizza day 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grace is #VASE ready! #lastvase #sadhappy #senioryear @ Cedar Ridge High School (Texas) https://t.co/ZQvzFbtsKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mix - The Muffin Man | Kids Songs | Super Simple Songs https://t.co/ClDolgmqzg via @YouTubeqñfdfifilglopñ ñ was o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate buying something then seeing the cuter version at the next store]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebraMessing We need to fund public schools. This is the party of evangelicals. To actually believe outright lies,… https://t.co/3eg2e1teAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/zOg0trJ048]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/uDmQo9gNSV  We have an Amazon Phone Number 1-855-431-5111  #amazonphonenumber]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at West Orange - Pleasantdale Section in West Orange, NJ https://t.co/AkIzv4baWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[LV has been so overused on everything to the point that it’s starting to be tacky. make it stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My therapist: you can’t just deflect feelings with sarcasm and humor   Me: Are you saying I’m not funny? Bc I once… https://t.co/Takaou9RMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Sarah Palin mask still getting good use 10 years later. Sweet dreams, everyone. https://t.co/AJUG1klgBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all he chugged one faster then any of “country boys” can ever do. sheesh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Long ago, psychoanalyst Leonard Shengold wrote a book called Soul Murder wherein arbitrary edicts or a… https://t.co/Zsa7RXBWDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amó hablar con mi novio 🤩 y más cuando sacamos temas de negocios y de mi trabajo 🤩🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garthbrooks with the tour starting this week and all of the folks from the 90s coming back, are we going to see… https://t.co/lIPtcYoOZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂  Why did this show up after I tweeted about Trixie eating off the floor???]]></document><document><![CDATA[was eating pringle’s without looking at them and they started to taste funny and i looked down to see: mold then re… https://t.co/f0eTEZajcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juiceone3 @andraydomise Sending solidarity because I also used to work with dogs and the worst part was dealing wi… https://t.co/kDNKMyelb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethingaround @Green_Mt_Girl Haha ohhhh! That makes more sense. I thought the issue was wearing the ashes in publi… https://t.co/eCCL815Ab2]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤗A magical thing happened today! The St. Louis Children’s Hospital has approved the funding for The Fantasy Kids Le… https://t.co/3nTcLBQh92]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danwarren6 Happy Saturday Dan! Here’s how my day is starting and here’s my view. https://t.co/TckkAVOWDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $60 Spotify Gift Card Offer       Enter Your Email Id And Complete A Simple Sign Up To Win $60 Spotify Gif… https://t.co/0rPcahXYgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s here... #worldpololeague #newbreed #newera @ Wellington, Florida https://t.co/VO1CUT4wR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sutter At Dawn https://t.co/jweFInFCYi via @http://twitter.com @salon9 #salon9 available at Salon 9, 9 Maiden Lane… https://t.co/uaP33W4r4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dailydaysspoilers Wed Feb 20th #dool #days  @1CaseyMoss @matthew_ashford @billymflynn @KateMansi @LamonArchey… https://t.co/5BSQwDAjJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @JoeBiden @realDonaldTrump @VP Saying something nice about Joe Biden is not the same as saying som… https://t.co/uAXHghN3QP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uhhh.... y’all didn’t tell me that Elle went all the way to Harvard for some boy to take her back...]]></document><document><![CDATA[i implore you to look at the things people write in the guest books next time you go to an art museum || found at t… https://t.co/tkq0I0fE3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[“... and role tide” LMAO go dawgs but love u hannah beast #WomenTellAll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner If Republicans help Bernie win the nomination,  and they will brag about it,  I won't be able to support… https://t.co/s2VqI4JIVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people say “sure” so much in podcasts? It’s like yada yada yada. Sure. Blah blah blah. Sure. Abracadabra. Sure...sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga @MarkRonson @Wyattish @killRossomando @iBradlycooper @jasonhalbert @BrynnCartelli @KelseaBallerini… https://t.co/fVJrWm9Bdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg ppl in the workplace needs to understand this.. also the ppl you fuck with, need to know when and when not to b… https://t.co/G5nrMlWozZ]]></document></documents></author>