<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WWE: .@FinnBalor?is all HEART. The #ICChampion does everything he can to crawl back into the #ICTitle Match against @fightbobby?on #Raw!...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@igabemarino @hotnosferatu Bitch u forgot it!!!!! I literally gave it back to you last night!!! But you fell asleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vajazzercise @steph93065 @AOC #YouveBeenBrainwashed #VotesArentViolence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JrThatcher Maybe. I think we are just alienating everyone right now. On this topic, I’m one of four people still mad we abandoned TPP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone wanna gift me 1000$ so I can buy A piece of drum gear that only benifits me? I thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson @LunaticRayven13 @SenatorLankford The same guy that was so upset about the firing of Comey. He said… https://t.co/ju4CfB8v38]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho @AEWrestling @TonyKhan @TalkIsJericho @VinceMcMahon Furthermore @IAmJericho @TonyKhan went with Gabbert… https://t.co/ppBNImoEdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[2-0-1-9...3rd song on #RoadToARolex is called “Black Murakami”. So, @takashipom is an incredible visual artist. He’… https://t.co/9X7X7avT6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stanford and Oregon play very difficult schedules this fall. Advantage:  Washington.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did this on our channel as a BroVsBro Challenge with a twist. Come check it out @fuegobox #chocoloco… https://t.co/UFp8NXrdBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for an #insurance agent/broker in #Connecticut? https://t.co/njgMtW4lCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillTrumpYou @DoggoJoshu @PolitiBunny @CassieDupras @AOC The other thing that rich and powerful people do is get t… https://t.co/mAsoQc3L8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jimmy Johnson tournament dinner was by far the boujieest event I’ve ever been to and Joey and I spent most of t… https://t.co/kSHxROjufE]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We think the issue of whether they use a term like meat is a proxy for this bigger issue, which is that the meat i… https://t.co/Yr2m7b6E5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenScala4NY @RCNconnects Love DirecTV Now; it’s fantastic and only $45 for so many channels + HBO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTimpf Anymore than a mouthfull is wastefull. You go Kat your perfect as you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gustavofdelc @LeonKrauze  - @lopezobrador_  descalifica a todo aquel que esté en contra de sus desiciones y muy ma… https://t.co/9krHJ4cnGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Hauser knocks the ball out of Johns hands, and then throws a lazy pass to Howard, the epitome of self destruction]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timwoolleyracin @Racingwithbruno @PaulMattiesJr Claiming system penalizes trainers for taking care of their horses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kind of wish I could watch the Women Tell All episode with @demi_burnett. Looks like it will be full of fireworks a… https://t.co/SaRKbXzOw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a view from my desk! #mobiliar #swissnexsf #enjoy https://t.co/INsCic58Bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnerRichard12 @AdeleCulp @marchmadness Just Incase you were wondering we haven’t played Pepperdine yet, but nice… https://t.co/C2xRgQh8sN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@regwag2003 For ppl who talk about 'policies' they're woefully ignorant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Officially the last time I come home, my own “friends” robbing me from my own bottle. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keybank is the absolute worst bank I have ever had the displeasure of dealing with. #pissed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost as excited as this pooch for tonight's #storiestoscenes! 8:00! Rozzie Square Theater!!  #riot #riotimprov… https://t.co/F1Cl83YEbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is the list of my top 5 favorite shows on tv that I have watched with multiple seasons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at San Francisco International Airport - @flysfo in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/vaVa0SIQyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[SEXY SMOOTH  SISSY  GAY FEMBOTTOM FAGGOT LOOKING TO HAVE SEX WITH MEN. I'M JAMES DI MARIA FROM WEST WARWICK RHODE I… https://t.co/WJbfS0V7jA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think @bigaljack broke Ag Twitter this week with a simple picture of all his screens in his planter tractor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirginiaSlim67 @Whtnbourbonguy @thedailygallop @fairgroundsnola @handi_capper @theyreoff ARKANSAS!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[PBIS is effective, if used correctly...using it to excuse behavior and not work for improvement, well, that's not w… https://t.co/rWvSN8bWNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw that Shane Dawson conspiracy theory last night about Chuck E. Cheese and now that’s all on my TL today.… https://t.co/yTSXRDw7RZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey, I’m enjoying the new video @jamescharles 🥰 https://t.co/8kQV2bajcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Other - Dude, I wasn't that drunk!You started petting my cat saying 'LOOK AT HOW SMALL... #mirth #tee-hee #smirk… https://t.co/tLngEvnkOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Merrick777 @johncardillo Wouldn’t want to add to the Clinton body count!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carter Mahaney pulls up from mid-range, 17-10. He scores from a lot of tough areas and opens up shots for more traditional players.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackbooshwa @ScoutingLLC @nfldraftscout @CodyTalksNFL @ZackMooreNFL @seniorbowl *Tytus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NARAL I just read the bill. It's straight forward and simple: A live born baby is a person, and consequently a pat… https://t.co/As8Wtl0nI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny to see there’s twitter trolls and all of their “mean tweets”.  Haha.  What a bunch of hacks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CmFalz @7News I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quincy HOME Day1 USA… https://t.co/wiqfwDToGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @TBoneWFNZ let's make a bet, if the Heels win you drink from the mug tomorrow morning 🤣 https://t.co/nr9cZjLwtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me and start your day with Morning Brew, the email covering the latest news from Wall St. to Silicon Valley.… https://t.co/cFDyCOUvDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It isn't the burdens of today that drive men mad. Rather, it is regret over yesterday or fear of tomorrow that rob us of today. #Hastings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MIHouseDems @gretchenwhitmer Stop with the platitudes and fix the roads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Bob’s new show “Videos After Dark” debuting Tues, 3/12 @ 10pmest on ABC!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grantcohn It would come down to what the price is, and how could Shanny use Ross. When healthy, Shanny could, imo,… https://t.co/fDvkeCBfjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby Atreyu Drewy has been found at Eldorado High School. Father of boy says he is “ecstatic.” @News3LV https://t.co/eawGoxEVeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women internationally is the epitome of grace, strength, success, and love. #successfulyou #internationalwomensday https://t.co/0cCE5tJzDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4tammiem Yes it is criminal. And this must be changed. Enough is enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian Love you Khloe.  You are kind and beautiful.   Don’t let anyone hurt you and don’t look back, only… https://t.co/0K2a1DpCHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patriotdb @Tia6sc @POTUS @VP @FLOTUS @SecondLady I read the tweets by the so-called Patriots. Wishing harm on ever… https://t.co/igVgkbltgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[These jackets by @ACEEngineering are awesome. ACE Engineering JK Lava Jacket Overview Video https://t.co/EnYeDcGChg… https://t.co/ndpsw8m6lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh... Brad got me faded last night. It's a miracle I got home, on the D train no less. Fixing me some crab cakes a… https://t.co/1OBQbYCVM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling for government retribution against entertainment programs is how you make America great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pubs from the National Judicial College: 1) 'Hydrologic Modeling Bench Book' 2) 'Water Science in the Courtroom'… https://t.co/TA8RdS6MdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom said if I make this face long enough it would stick, I guess she was right.  #model https://t.co/gLMTaMJOLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oOParkerOo @GunFaceP @realDailyWire But I thought there was wage inequality? Now all of a sudden you’re not down for a pay day!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snippet: “I wanna go back to talking about Hilary...”  Trump dude: “well wait hold on...”  Chick: “LET ME FINISH”… https://t.co/8ib9lIHQFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was strain in Joe’s voice tonight, so I simply asked what he was thinking. His response...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimMartin2011 @AngelaBelcamino @realDonaldTrump It won’t dummy he will never ever resign why should he America lov… https://t.co/bz2PhzPbVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QBsMVP How would you like it by slingshot or or fat guy jumping on opposite end of a see-saw.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kaishu_designs @weezer831 @ThomasArena9 @MrDane1982 Either way it’s wrong. Brothers and sisters, let’s not let sem… https://t.co/f2Cp7IQC86]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CornerButcher @georgewrighster You right he would literally fucking stab him. Love that tough basketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailySabah One muslim terrorist is calling another muslim terrorist for help calming tensions with a nation that i… https://t.co/qD6rAB9cEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever had this idea some company better collect up quick. That person is a problem solver everyone wants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to meet some of the coolest local business owners. Let me introduce you to Fouad Nakkoul, owner of Heel To So… https://t.co/xLsEN7aPHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@developerjack @chendo Vega 56 has 3584 stream processors versus 1280 on the Vega 20. Plus it has twice the HBM2. A… https://t.co/OZpNt8XRff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShiftParadigm @kellyhines @MarkJWestpfahl @inclusionchick @LindaAmici @clairecummings @jchandlerteach @Oggs26… https://t.co/B1NVXQYJlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to receive an invitation to the 304 Elite Camp! Looking forward to competing! https://t.co/zacx7svJ7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my name is Patrick, but Starbucks wrote FATrick on my cup...are they trying to tell me something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans make no sense, Vol 3:  They’re doing everything to destroy Cohen’s credibility, and he’s literally sitt… https://t.co/P0yboT2E3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Sasser is talking about balancing resources for Venezuela students and support for native born students... Did I mishear?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mid_madness They shouldnt have to win out to deserve it. If they lose to uncg at home or at Furman, they should be… https://t.co/y7Zl4eZ6M9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Fastest way thru adversity is straight thru it. “ @LewisCaralla            Love it!!! #WW #neWday #BookerT #goWild]]></document><document><![CDATA[KU changed them halfway through my last semester and I don’t think I will ever forgive them for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[May your values come full circle in each continent and country for generations to come. Rest in power, Tata. - Ma… https://t.co/xXOKQVRl2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanCronk @jhoffman Oh hell yeah we even got cronk on this one what a world]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope @DaMFunK approves   #CherylLynn #Preppie https://t.co/KCd6nUNSHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My god I'm so fucking frustrated right now.  I've spent over a grand on battle Royale, and 26.99 multiplied by 4 fo… https://t.co/HfjfyyGQOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINISHING UP MY PLACEMENTS ON LEAGUE TODAY, ON STREAM!! STOP BY AND WATCH ME GET CARRY BY THE @andaharu! https://t.co/UEKVwdSd0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty successful evening for our little team. #TSPRA19 #CampCommunication #CelebrateKISD https://t.co/bJsro2sAbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_EMdeJong @reavo7five @SinBinVegas @RP_Quigs @JesseGranger_ I was told it was available]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonKelce didn’t know you endorsed a restaurant?? https://t.co/RZ46kyndDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vaccinate yourselves from hate and physical aggression. It serves no purpose for good.  Use your God given abilitie… https://t.co/pQXa2xbmhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimAdamsGeo @iAmTheWarax Are y’all telling me this outburst occurred in a college class? Wut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetJurgensmeyer @jonasbrothers 😎👍JET-MAZING!!! https://t.co/tR5dxM5i2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if I’ve had more coffee or beer in my lifetime.  Has to be coffee, but I’d maybe like to see the numbers (probably not).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colossians 3:2 Set your minds on things above, not on things on the earth. This week, whatever situation you walk i… https://t.co/i69gSy5aiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PadsFan4Ever And I could do the same to yours and you could do it to mine. I stand by my opinions and I do a lot o… https://t.co/aq0x1MHmIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollyMinor11 Empath, emotional vampire🧛‍♂️.. . Typically the "Black Sheep" in the family is usually the most empat… https://t.co/XwXBo1rQPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AcademyRewind @TimothyPG13 finally listened to the latest episode and that was an amusing 2 hours of arguing. I th… https://t.co/depqbkflbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time got away from me and this is the best I can do for the Cake Eater Championship #TheTourney19 https://t.co/Wn4T2GG0Cx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DinosaurDracula You bring me a chill and nostalgic buzz feeling as strong as when you were doing #Xentertainment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mridleythomas @MagicJohnson @lacountyparks @LACoPublicWorks @LACMA @CDCHACoLA @HerbJWesson #LAUSD’s lobbying contr… https://t.co/7NKztnDueT]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: @Bharper3407 may or may not be signing with a unnamed team for an undisclosed amount of money for a speci… https://t.co/Ktx666DWIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLambert15 Congrats to your Dad in his retirement.  Heard your shout out on The RBS and cow bell by @TheRealTRizzo… https://t.co/mm4IZZSobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuniorGrande88 Yeah but I don't really notice him, he's kind of like a tick. Tauras can at least have legitimate c… https://t.co/7qYDAa3LTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before there was "I Confess", there was a movie priest who kept things really quiet: https://t.co/h1BCY6gENq https://t.co/VdZ4kims61]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m excited, are you? #SandboxDemoDay #7weeks @FinTechSandbox @MoodysAnalytics https://t.co/Zgx8UXt9TK]]></document></documents></author>