<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Like it’s gross and I’m sorry but OH MAN HOW IS SOMEONE ALLOWED TO LOOK SO GOOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Excelsior por que terminar con el mas internacional y productivo con nada se reemplaza]]></document><document><![CDATA[This brewery continues to impress - Drinking a Cryptic by @somethingbrewco at @FirstDraftDen  — https://t.co/vwGbObmZW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeRepNY @SportsCenter Nice try. Get the facts first. You're in for a big surprise and not a happy ending for Patriots haters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachkruse2 Well said...agree too. With the back drop of not making the playoffs, BG should have the support to tak… https://t.co/pXBNx9TfGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are unable to attend #church  so to the #snow we watch #passion2019 message... today it is @ChristineCaine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ispence_ It was 2016 or 2017 either way it was when you Alexis and Ro were always at lock and key lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[After driving through Pennsylvania and West Virginia, we're finally back in Ohio. We'll see you this evening,… https://t.co/lCxkhdZnkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill McKibben is right! “The beauty of the Green New Deal is not that it’s shiny or progressive. Its beauty is that… https://t.co/1Y8vbfqgKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KUSINews @GavinNewsom  #InternationalWomensDay  Sanctuary Cities are the Gateway Drug of Socialists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAalsma @RobMeyerIII Drop one of the afternoon sessions and have a time to meet with district and digest what we l… https://t.co/A1zDpOAgsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Busch is so cold, when I got it out of the grocery bag from grocery store, my corn was about to freeze....… https://t.co/puhy6d4mHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Walsh12358754 @RobertPRoehm @NTU What has happened since then is the further mergers of ISPs and media companies.… https://t.co/WUt4tY36AH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also Cate Blanchett as Katherine Hepburn? Fantastic https://t.co/8kd6GXi2IX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that I’m back in the Mile High City, I’m trying to get rehydrated for the next few days.  It will be needed. https://t.co/4WpZXrfakY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Containers and @cotufa82. . . #DeveloperCommunity #GDGTriangle https://t.co/ZQpyFEeUVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Rocky Mountain Way by @JoeWalsh on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/gAx1jDAQfd 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iancharlesbaker @Top8Games Still haven’t watched it. Been meaning to for years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@educurious2015 Why give the kids (NQT’s) a false impression that it gets better?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boardwalk_11 You guys rock! I love the DigitalPour display is great!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It shouldn’t matter what people think about you, what matters is what you think about yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiotRSL @lucaswmuller @sirveaux24 It doesn’t help that Petke has seemed quick to put people in his doghouse in their defense though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SOninesJensen But how are they read? And to whom can they be sent? If you hold them dear?]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you do 99 + 47? It's all about perspective. #T3Learns #T3IC @pwharris https://t.co/lmO7J4XQkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ShuOuma_ Yeah it’s a wonderful feeling. Going through all these emotions and making a difference because this sho… https://t.co/vs64UbpnuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes...I will dodge showers to play #golf in #california today... I am apparently the only one. @ Paso Robles, Calif… https://t.co/s4ghrnwt8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsbpd84 @MouradB @max_domi @shawz15er @CanadiensMTL Ppl can make mistakes with numbers...big surprise another arrogant Leaf fan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Torranceisbest They suck as super heroes I’ve never taken an Interest I can barely sit thru the movies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sistertoldjah Pretty soon it will just be 2 men’s sports and I will not feel bad at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolmswain @realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter No it doesn’t.  She’s full of herself and will end up on the Comicon tour by 2020, if she’s lucky.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to a great friend. Enjoy your day @Ajbarber_ https://t.co/GPHcxSzNR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephMajkut @limebike @DDOTDC So dumb. They at least should be 15. If not their normal capacity of 17.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New @USAGym president/CEO Li Li Leung was a managing director in both the Beijing and London offices of Helios Part… https://t.co/1QfWmHvS7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somewhere my ex is out there asking people if they want to hear a joke about ghost... they answer... she reply’s wi… https://t.co/CjGsBEgEgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meteorologist - 40% scattered showers today.  Guess that means 1 Inch of fucking downpours and trying to find Noah’… https://t.co/DgNyA9yGS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackTheJobber Don’t feed the trolls Jack. As #RTruth’s idol #JohnCena would say, “rise above hate”]]></document><document><![CDATA[35 years down and 20 more years to live according to my family history combined with my lifestyle choices....30 if… https://t.co/cpvEp2yKUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Our vision is to be the innovator of a new mobile experience.” — DJ Koh, @Samsung (holding the #GalaxyFold) https://t.co/mKfGydshY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peteb52 @OakCityBrews @Brewers @HartSchool_SRM I’ll see what I can do for a fellow #CarolinaLeagueDuke]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of working going on out here in Denton.... one of a kind. #offszn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Officer reporting suspect "still alive, still conscious, still holding a gun in his right hand."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo que voy hacer el viernes va a cambiar por completo y espero que esto que tengo en el ❤️ ya se asiente]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Drink enough water. 2. Eat good food. 3. Work out. 4. Prioritize sleep. 5. Always have an appointment with a doc… https://t.co/K9VGQIBBlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee RIP Pat may God Comfort his family.   🇺🇸Governor, have you considered having CARMAN on your show?… https://t.co/XdE2GOmT5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Francisco Franco? No, sorry, that would only be one.  We would have to say “Dos Francos” to make a complete set. 😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pensacola Day 2 #sunseasand @ Pensacola Beach, Florida https://t.co/TdLu3rik9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atlanta!! I’m hosting another great lineup for COMEDY AND COCKTAILS @CityWineryATL!!!   Tomorrow 3/6/19 8pm  It’ll… https://t.co/wZFnUWnXDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnPsaltis @MuellerSheWrote The outright contempt leads me to believe revocation of bail. Never mind evrythi g el… https://t.co/6bHhz0kc17]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't think Mark Carney makes things up, says High Commissioner @SusanLeJeuneFCO, referring to Carney's positio… https://t.co/2LssISNQq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly surprised more faggots aren’t at Berlin already for this Robyn after party 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[After yesterday I am so happy I got to watch last night, VOC is so good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DollyVol So much better than throwing cheese on a baby's face. Our dogs would love a pancake to the face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chameleonthot i’m about to MAKE MYSELF BE omfg i can’t believe i’m breathing the same air as you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Buy a presidency. Buy a judge Buy a entertainment network (Fox News). Can't call it a journalistic outlet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CadenBraylen I mean realistically at this point everyone has been exposed to some form of Symbiote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEUniverse: Happy birthday to @WWE ring announcer, @ItsJoseann! https://t.co/9mCarJZLFw  https://t.co/WIXdx2dJTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Michelangelo__ @NBCNews I think Obama pulling our troops out way too early, leaving the vacuum for ISIS to take o… https://t.co/ihMahz0876]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcinthelibrary Good tweet. Thank you. I was on the right side (against the anti-Semitism)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m seeing the second LEGO movie tonight and they are showing a trailer for the new Kim Possible Disney Channel mov… https://t.co/uux0nyBVGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrownieLB_1 @StormHour @metoffice @itvwestcountry @ILoveCornwallUK Happy Valentines Day !]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Webster Schroeder High School for @SecVBBasketball A1 semifinalis. @mendonbball leads @EastridgeHoops 78-49 with… https://t.co/qQ6SQ2NKS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go check out My track Listen to Wes1 (1) by Wesley Deguerre #np on #SoundCloud https://t.co/w1Eq5HEOrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@congolandoll @hoesferatu No, but I do expect every human to believe in human rights.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DraDianePerez @LibreriasGandhi @libreriaporrua @solosanborns @amazonmex Gracias diane lo voy a comprar buenos dias]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ask me and I will tell you remarkable secrets you do not know about things to come.” Jeremiah 33:3 NLT… https://t.co/N5dL0QixPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blake from Workaholics, Demi Lavato, and Noah Cyrus were all at a Butterfinger Emo night party I just had to film. Weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lame that @sternshow would go thru the whole @memetwalker vs Rat Face Brent IQ test betting segment for an hour the… https://t.co/1XwyjfyY1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[So if I give up paying taxes for Lent, if the guvm’t comes after me, will it be religious persecution?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most at Fox challenges Juan.  I don’t mind listening to him making a fool of himself and exposing the hypocrisy of… https://t.co/D9WTUyuIj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jperricelli_ @GMEN23MNB @ridgeback2002 @pmurph790 @EmperorMara Getty was offered a 3rd and 5th for LC last year now he walks for nothing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was great to see so many positive people who made it to the CCR3-III special session board meeting tonight!!  Th… https://t.co/AyIfgq07FO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradleyTBs @santaanitapark The old mentality of ... https://t.co/riWgZdqGLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your crush is in the same room as you and you’re trying to play it cool #GlennClose #OscarsRedCarpet #oscars https://t.co/AeThEZuI7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UncleCharlie50 Fair enough. But in a dispute between owners and players, the only people to truly suffer are the f… https://t.co/Qe2FVEpf3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSMT88 @f8kcensorship @MorozSteve @RIP_SW @JesseKellyDC And you're saying they don't know of this equipment you ta… https://t.co/5SuTTYWPRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Patriots WR Free Agency predictions - CP84 re-sign, Devin Funchess, Kevin White, Dorsett re-sign]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes it's like ,,,,, Keynedy,,,,,with a little long brains,,, https://t.co/yIo3CKEOlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does #TraitorTrump aka @realDonaldTrump keep LYING and LYING and LYING and ... The latest is saying that Sen Ha… https://t.co/8Chp1O17B3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DancerOnFilm @SkotArmstrong I love the viciousness of Taylor and Burton in this.  Bette Davis in Little Foxes, times 10.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AClarkHHS I presented Nearpod yesterday at #NCCE and I used the idea to gather everyone’s email address upfront an… https://t.co/h8bsv4qeg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IntrovertDeb Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now to wait about an hour to see happy death day 2!!!! I am so excited to see this film!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcharvie Been here many times and it’s always a nightmare to get in and out of]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tdave I am an HM3 beast, hope you find someone, happy to help; roughly 7k cases on my HM3 back in the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bresnan_Bear @cmclymer @BernieSanders i'm fine with it, too. he's going to be so overloaded with unanswered questi… https://t.co/OgaErMicBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[University of Kentucky’s DanceBlue is a 24 hour dance marathon to raise money to fight pediatric cancer.… https://t.co/ALo1QdFdM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally the first day of nice weather and my crackhead neighbors aRE already HOLLERING]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT A NIGHT!!!! The senior lock-in was a tremendous success! It was great to see @WHS2019Lions have a loooooong ni… https://t.co/dhyi8zB8Lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂did he start the national anthem with “WELL”?!!!! #anthonyhamilton https://t.co/lBlgUKascL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bowlesian @VANS_66 @ledzeppelin Thank you Andrew like the tweet was less than an hour old and they’re already sold out lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in Irving, TX, check out this IT Infrastructure job via the link in our bio: AWS Engineer at Cognizant #EC2 #Java]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what #TFClive Twitter badly needs?   A game to talk about. Thank God there’s one in THREE DAYS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You trade with your neighbors. That’s what you do,” U of Minn’s Edward Usset. We agree. Mexico is Kansas ag’s #1 t… https://t.co/TsfivBjWdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tom_tml Is there a Three-pack of pitchers that count as a one puck-up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone at my office told me they were coming to a show this week.  I'd like to formally announce my resignation from comedy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YyzkevinBull @fordnation Bumper-sticker slogans from the sticker king. #ONPoli #THUGNation #DougFraud #Deco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teddy and I are out on the west coast supporting the @NHLBruins vs @LAKings at the @STAPLESCenter. Lots of #Bruins… https://t.co/drJ2txVD9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[No way Cook isn't worth $9-10mil per given these TE deals, Uzomah, James, Kroft. #Raiders]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SFIGVegas bound.  Who wants to talk #Lending #securitization #blockchain and #crypto?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyschiavone24 my son Dylan and his best friend Layla says please keep doing the podcast.  How could you disappoi… https://t.co/mW5dzG1Qoh]]></document></documents></author>