<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jleetorres11 @DallasWriters Yay! It was so fun meeting you and getting to know more about your goals as a writer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard that celebrities are not allowed to leave during award shows. Which means they have to pee in their seats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prayingmedic @Antoinotabot Start with your security to elevate their guns!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@binge_mode I just now started S1E1 of BingeMode: Thrones and yesssssssssssssssssssss #ForTheThrone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude. @LateNightSeth and his writers are KILLING the game with that Trumpized version of “We Didn’t Start The Fire”… https://t.co/4kbMMBfn4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shop @LuxeNior they have amazing work @ Detroit, Michigan https://t.co/1qqxu5FYVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[【買付1日目 ニューメキシコ州アルバカーキに到着】 https://t.co/nlnnL4xKl8 https://t.co/q2KoFzvwzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump held 2013 Miss Universe pageant in Moscow. The venue was owned by Aras Agalarov, who Trump had done business… https://t.co/EmADVYfdQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really just pulled myself out of bed and showed up to work 4 minutes late for them to tell me I’m not scheduled t… https://t.co/z9HHv0jkHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AFASusannahEWR Were BFF’s now. Follow each other in Instagram. I told her to go after her dreams. Tipsy, jet-lagge… https://t.co/mBoONNLKhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[LONG PAUSE around liability for providers....@CindyFriedmanMA suggests legislature can develop language to address… https://t.co/y10vMVnKcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SladeWentworth @numeri33 Love that!  Can I steal it for some of my family members? 😃🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kid just sang" I gotta grinder ,I gotta bong,I gotta dildo ,I gotta thong"😂😂😂😂😂 WTF 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to be fucking w u a year plus plus b4 your number gets saved 😂😂 cause i can’t deal w that maybe:]]></document><document><![CDATA[People get scared when you can speak other languages. @FLOTUS speaks 8! 🧐😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @mcspocky @monkeyface__ I did not know that we are required to answer DM s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Well? No answer from Melania because she doesn't know ANYTHING she is a Stepford Wife!]]></document><document><![CDATA[17 dias pra eu abraçar minha mãe e meu pai e obrigar minha irmã a fazer massagem nas minhas costas em troca de ouvi… https://t.co/hdPShn1rUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE ABOUT TO ROLL UP TO THIS LIKE WE DID FOR HANNAH MONTANA @organicjelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulBracken61 @ThisIsROCK2019 Oh! I thought You were looking for a sugar Mama!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenziDreamBigTs I have relative in Macintosh,  Alabama.  I hope is safe..  🙏🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just pulled my belt off my pants &amp; it sounded like luigi’s vacuum when he’s sucking up the ghosts]]></document><document><![CDATA[I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS. Why Jussie why????.... I don't understand why he would fake this. When there are so many hat… https://t.co/Qz9VqFhIcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia says Thank you, America!  They will get what they want from Jared and we get another nuclear foe. Than… https://t.co/DoAVJhrYPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[She needs to go back to her village in Minnesota. I heard a token is missing.  https://t.co/ZMuoA8tQOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the Oscar’s!  I thought that this years was the best show in many years!  No host was wonderful and made it… https://t.co/1oJiFt3xB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told warriors right before we went on the floor that we didn't have anything to lose, but we would sure have some… https://t.co/ZZ7pO59R4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dos tickets for sale for the sold out @QuinnXCII concert next Saturday at Mercury Ballroooom. $40 each OBO go enjoy it for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pauley_jessica I think we should stop before this gets too outta hand https://t.co/tkz1ouLyWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecenterspeaks @RudyGiuliani I think it would be a tie Rudy and Lindsey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ensenada eres bien chula aunque tengas un trastorno climático múltiple https://t.co/ChZanLLfad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably my favorite CCR song ❤. Listening to Long As I Can See The Light by Creedence Clearwater Revival on… https://t.co/TcrwLZwNPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[i also worked out in then and they are 10/10 the comfiest pants to work out in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMANGO @TSRStore @EldoraSpeedway @DannyLeBlanc24 @dega_boy_87 @KCJO_LABMOM889 @spyderrider63 @18RowdyNation… https://t.co/kkCQdPBWUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Being up-to-date in the meme economy.” @andrewgrojean identified one of my biggest time sucks. #smckc https://t.co/HkYtpfYM7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radmaggie 🤤 Excellent choice. Those are some of my favorite things too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried to Venmo @Giaa_Dub $6.34 for my McDonalds and I really am a dumbass huh? https://t.co/6YZYuC6PpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moment when you realized you have your WiFi off for the whole night https://t.co/JgsN9AtWrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sounds exactly like dating men who have issues with their mom/sad or have been molested as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed BeeElleEssss! How can any WOMEN WITH BRAINS SUPPORT “dt” NMP ‼️❓⁉️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodo The Best Video for 2019!!! What a happy boy. You are a Saint.  Thank you for what you did!!!!!!! ❤️🐾🐾❤️🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrishell7 I want to know what Kate's gonna do to Jordan when this is all over! 😎🤔! You won't trick Kate but once! 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine Leave it to a failed TV Hispanic judge to try to use this as a "fake news" story. She's like a piranh… https://t.co/w91JdlRkka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He would say any kind of vile, demented spew, knowing nothing on the subject.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Situation is that someone is like having an argument and straight up screaming and cussing hella loud outside the building lol smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbascom69 @bennyjohnson @TPUSA Your depiction of this scenario would also dictate that Nick Sandman from Covington… https://t.co/uRBPj5PgAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found Stay Alive and I’m so excited cause this is legit my favorite horror movie 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poroshenko Скільки б не намагалася. #Україна🇺🇦 не піде назад. Тільки вперед!🙏 #СлаваУкраїні]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THAT_G0MEZ Thank you! Ya I’ll come visit you two and baby 😍 I’ll probably not be able to come out until after I fi… https://t.co/2U5ShWFa2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ITM_1997 @DoctorWho_BBCA Some people don’t like to hear it because in their eyes Ten can do no wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melanie_korach @aweninspiration @tracyscottkelly @DrMaxineWalters @fablefy @mraspinall @GrundlerArt @SJSaragusa… https://t.co/gl4XhZBgBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump no podemos olvidar a nuestros hermanos  Nicaraguenses y Cubanos los vamos a liberar también]]></document><document><![CDATA[We both worked hard and I am a Veteran but need both Medicare and Social security and as a Veteran with disabilitie… https://t.co/NepSO0P2FX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethaniapalma It's part of one of the many hobbies I relentlessly pursue to stave off existential dread in the evenings]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember a recorded conversation with a female GOP senator in which Nunes explains that he fully understands what… https://t.co/oSXyEbi8ck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudyWilliams123 @DonaldJTrumpJr @KamalaHarris @JussieSmollett https://t.co/hwiLZR3poD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennycohn1 @robreiner I refuse to watch him destroy all that is good for another 600+ days assuming a new pres wil… https://t.co/XiEn7Zewdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je veux faire plaisir au fils de quelqu’un ptit dej au lit session spa fait par moi ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmicataGbR Nice! Your cosplay looks great so far! I met him in New York. He’s a good person :) please tell us abou… https://t.co/LAt4u4aD5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougJones @MalcolmNance From news reports, he is conflicted. But, I guess we just take the word of liars?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on folks we got to get #SweaterMan trending. #LivePD  @DanTheBeepMan @OHFCSO @thehicklife @Sean_C_Larkin… https://t.co/w8OqyLEDIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bennett_Kavlick happy birthday to my third roommate!!! Sorry to miss the festivities this weekend! I hope you have a good day! 🎈]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry, but as a Christian I don’t agree with this. It’s not my life. I was raised to love everyone no matter th… https://t.co/ON3CBkSN2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SteelersFan_7 @Steelersdepot @AdamSchefter @RapSheet @TomPelissero @AKinkhabwala They have both said it]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO. EXCITED. Seriously, I'm such a Disney nerd, watching this gave me chills. 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halloran_john @AmericaFirstPAC @seanspicer @IlhanMN Isn't it time you get off his Twitter?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brightly50 Wow LVP was her only friend last season,  now she has Kyle and she thinks she's all that. NOPE! Team LVP all day!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish i can send out a PSA to my whole class to tell them to just not come so we don’t have to take this quiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he's one of the very few close and long time friends of T-rump. What does that say???]]></document><document><![CDATA[👉 Ready, Set, Go! 💪#ChooseHealthy2019 #FindYourFit #TLSslim #TLSslim21DayChallenge #TransitionRadiance @ Frostburg,… https://t.co/iTX4ZA0Vq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikWemple @TuckerCarlson Still in search of a story that goes with your ending?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying, thinking about my Papa (Paw Paw), grandfather on my dad side. He’s my only grandparent left. I love him so… https://t.co/yf3Tug4Haz]]></document><document><![CDATA[New favorite word: Phubbing (snubbing a person in favor of your phone). https://t.co/MR3APdGdaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeleMage @EscoBlades Yup. Then they'll go back home to their big houses and talk about what an enlightened experience they had.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Trumps wall gets a National Emergency. 72,000+ lives get no media mention, no emergency funding, absolutely NOTH… https://t.co/jLaiwz14uG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mitch McConnell @senatemajldr , you have allowed the @GOP to become Jim Jordan @Jim_Jordan and Mark Meadows… https://t.co/abLKmcColA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once again sarah has the audacity to stand and insult all Americans by spewing the lies she is being paid to say. T… https://t.co/vgxWs6Lsli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain @IlhanMN Meghan, I really feel for you for the loss of your father, but you're so beyond your lane ri… https://t.co/5LxHHUXxuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RomanReignsNet @WWERomanReigns can't wait to see him on Nickelodeon. welcome home roman reigns]]></document><document><![CDATA[first source is literally the worst bank to bank with. avoid at all costs. WHERES MY MONEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i promised you something , doesn’t matter if we’re on bad terms, or if we don’t even acknowledge eachother . i w… https://t.co/exwpQip0FZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlabasterCogs keep your eyes peeled for unique, quality, and rare pieces in antique stores/online/second hand spot… https://t.co/qjqnVSGnXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Better update your resumes Zirconia and Polyester! This gig is almost over😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Going with the Soros lie again junior? Just low class no class]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #NationalEngineersWeek! Checking out the fun #engineering activities going on at @CMOST_Troy - online @WTEN 🧮 https://t.co/UdxIBnBuhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamSimpsons on @TyltEnt—‘The Simpsons’ is my favorite adult cartoon https://t.co/wylyjhnfQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way these past days have been it feels good to get in my car and sing at the top of my Lungs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly And you used to be a good newsman. My grandmother liked your work. Then you went to Fox and lost it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dreezydreezy This Month In NY Rocking The Mic. Nails By:@vwreen @ Engine Room Audio https://t.co/Xty36ogpg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1011WNOE @LukeBryanOnline thanks for playing ❤️❤️❤️ What Makes You Country by Luke Bryan ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/evH16CE7zo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForeverMeatloaf @brithume I guess you don’t work or you would have noticed many tax payers received tax breaks this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helen Mirren is breathtaking. If I look half as good as her at that age, I made it.  #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drag show in LA—first male drag entertainer I’ve ever seen. “His” name is Landon Sider. Hilarious! #MarysWeHo… https://t.co/6q8wyHCiF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anon_decoder America will get our country Back. We are Victorious. This is God's Plan. Proverbs 21:31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slyturn Take the tweet how you want. Just know it peaked at 63. https://t.co/cqBAVoIt1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traditional school day and calendar out of sync with the times https://t.co/CDLpFGlgaW via @EducationNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally hit 500 followers on twitch from streaming and I'm honestly really proud of myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill Hader didn’t have to go hard in this photo shoot. He could’ve just stood in a blank room and do nothing, but h… https://t.co/bs5ZSODGHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught my cat playing in the toilet 🤦🏽‍♀️. I understand she’s still a baby but WTF. Had to trap her just so I could… https://t.co/N6XE5AEKJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DJohnsonPGA We have a national emergency should trump be watching golf]]></document></documents></author>