<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[In 2009 Obama offered stimulus package to states $$ for high speed rail! Fl Gov.Crist turned down offer. Only two s… https://t.co/NWIQQvdDi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAnnualBB hosted by @shamieranderson &amp; @realstephj #blackexcellence #oscars #theannualblackball… https://t.co/d9crq0RI3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a terrible, unkind obit of a fascinating woman. What the hell, NYT?]]></document><document><![CDATA[How a Texas Director Finally Brought &lt;i&gt;The Iron Orchard&lt;/i&gt; to the Screen, 50 Years Later https://t.co/wah1ST9K4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[ThankU! @MichelleforBOE for lending a hand at the food table. @APS_DSE Parent Expo 2019#DSEMissionPossible… https://t.co/GkSUL83pJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytgraphics They are not real republicans they are democrats saying they are republicans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@techinsider @businessinsider Love this cycle elevator !! Great design for homes as aesthetically pleasing to the eye!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#shegotthem #breds #on #igotthe #vapormax #nikies #jordanbred #airmaxvapormax #airmax #nike  #downtownriverside… https://t.co/ktnGHtCeyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilia_suze @lillianmcrowley Sorry ma'am - the US has a wild pig problem &amp; it will be on all menus for a long time.  Have a nice trip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OTellMeMore Is that supposed to make me not hate on him? Lol don’t check my other tweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes and @GOP has let the Dems get away with their double standards without repercussion so now the American people… https://t.co/b7PcHxCvCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogerHarper16 @ALT_uscis @FLOTUS @Nicklaus4Kids https://t.co/PuXhuTaRfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTA no L trains or 6 trains today?! I assume you’ll be reimbursing us for our monthly metro card that we don’t get… https://t.co/lttYpOCC9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 Gun violence, a looming dictatorship, children in concentration separated from their parents]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really gotta start buying groceries so I don’t have to look up what’s open at 4 am]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a serious question .... am I the only person who likes soggy cereal? Everyone thinks I’m crazy when i tell them this 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally thought I was going to die this week and I woke up feeling amazing so if I comment some happy stuff on… https://t.co/aaZfoIRC0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder what that would taste like poured over a bowl of Lucky Charms cereal...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BronxDAClark announced her support of the Driver’s License Privacy Act A3675 and S1747 this morning at the Equal A… https://t.co/2Y1GbdtdTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotImpressedUS @KTLA The only time you get to communication, is at the PAYPHONE. How many Finance offices do you k… https://t.co/BoCtIIlFSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh, it’s so annoying. So dangerous. Be lucky if you have good vision 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little vintage barn elegance? We got you.  . . We listen intently to what you want to create for your wedding day… https://t.co/H51JaQjWQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[[#PostWorkoutSnack] #sponsored • I have finally gotten my appetite back! And just in time for my Thursday two-a-day… https://t.co/9FAXVA23KG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rivergianna1 Yes would love to someone needs to book is either NYC or NJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fortunately, that’s extra fuel for her!!! Thanks for giving her the complimentary platform!  Go @AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @seanhannity @senjudiciary Yawn. 😴 Pentagon says crisis on southern border is manufactured   Ameri… https://t.co/gDiCQrbeL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaVNeri Good morning Angela. Thank you so much. Have a wonderful day.😘❤️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russellcrowe I am so very sorry for your loss, she looks like she was a wonderful woman ~ ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElleWibble @Momof2in1year @LA_Karma1 @CIAnderson3 @AviFlyGirl @ScarletAvengers @bridget_joy_ @CharismaMolotov… https://t.co/o0SS7ae46n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDugudichi Cockroaches, they scurry back into the dark when the light (truth) is turned on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is just around the corner so I thought I would take one last run in the snow at #swissvalley 👀I’m just glad… https://t.co/eTZ9Hy3grB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheMcMillions Hmmmm. Imma try that. Witch hazel is the only thing I’ve never tried.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Changing my life with this company and products.. #clean #natural #guthealth #antiinflammatory #immunesupport… https://t.co/Pui1mhYEOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittneyThiele Awe I was going to say come visit me at Carmel mountain]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Lakewood Ranch High School Basketball Team! #JackStrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthemRespect @ArizonaKayte @Sen_JoeManchin @SenBobCasey @DougJones ShAme on them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BasedPoland He killed millions of people 🧐 #Shame #Stalin #Doctator #Communist]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dumbo #worldpremiere @disney #timburton #colinfarrell @ Dolby Theatre https://t.co/kQwnt0FDHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be too hard on yourselves. I don’t remember a single thing from Econ 101.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KallMeKhlifa2 @_carolachavez95 Where we going? I’m ready for my third vacation]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t ever sleep in on my day off because I’m so used to getting up and this is bs bc Cody is sound asleep all co… https://t.co/bKhCyLChSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Team #THD6315 🥳🎉🥳 SASM Sean @seangarvey88 and Specialty DH Regina getting recognized by DSM Scott @Scott_Key_HD… https://t.co/eQIhnCtpvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[somebody send me money for postmates i have an addiction that i can’t afford pls send help 🆘]]></document><document><![CDATA[bite at the constitutionality of the pardon apple,” Meier said.  Bolton, the district judge, already determined tha… https://t.co/mvNtapapuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[My point was don’t you ever be doing the most for someone who ain’t doing it for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Monsters University &amp; my toddler yells out look it’s MICROWAVE (Mike Wazowski) 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bikergirl1964 @realDonaldTrump Instead of arguing with you, I want to tell you I’m sorry to read you have cancer a… https://t.co/QRt6ifZoAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been every corner store’s favorite customer since I was a freshman in high school]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent teacher and leader professional learning focused on K-12 pathways!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many thanks to @NASA_Wallops for hosting a fun filled day of #Moon2Mars education @NASASocial   So much more innova… https://t.co/AXCC7dzKP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So incredibly proud of my son Taylor who was honored last night @LLSNatCap as a Student of Year. This class of amaz… https://t.co/RQD51f6pFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANK YOU PRECIOUS PRESIDENT TRUMP.  HALLELUJAH! GLORY TO OUR LORD AND SAVIOUR JESUS CHRIST.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too sick to sleep well, brain too cooked to think clearly, these purposeless hours of tossing and turning and simme… https://t.co/BBcK7BOvjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home with the pups after a great workout. So happy with my progress. #LAFitnessLifesyle (@ Chester Valley Trail - S… https://t.co/fcIPhHABq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think we should begin impeachment proceedings until Mueller completes his investigation.  While recognizing… https://t.co/Sw0UVs3wHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time hanging out with great friends this weekend!@EstepSellsHomes tempeperreira daniel.perreira.980 bri… https://t.co/R0O07vpBDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc ifnimnin lorain or not I will drive all the way to Mansfield when it’s time to have the baby because that’s where i wanna be]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for @survivorcbs premiere tonight! Here are the tribe flags class 5B made today! @JeffProbst  #Survivor https://t.co/4mCmPSmNiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence The wall is a complete waste of taxpayer $, is shortsighted and sends a message that our neighbor to the… https://t.co/2ZvCJmVaYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been having super scary dreams and terrible sleep for the past 5 days wth going on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wishing_Wells19 Thank you for GETTING IT— I’m confused at the blandly benign reactions of my classmates. Like, I c… https://t.co/PqMVxVKGJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano I would love to see the Americans who do not find this embarrassing. It truly appears to be a satiri… https://t.co/Wu1o5mtijr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madShana @enelra5 @nm9139 @Cricket6 @hannadjh @Mountaingal456 @Fridaygirl1969 @mia_nj @pm3900 @ThePhightins33… https://t.co/QBIL2Y4hpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Forklift Warehouse Replenisher" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about these typ… https://t.co/YONoz5Io07]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels like i haven’t been in my bed in forever how much I’ve missed it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenofliz4rds I love your discourse server. I don't know any other fans of #rottmnt ... I didn't feel alone. But… https://t.co/tjZEgHUcAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @OversightDems @HouseIntel Cohn is a liar and a Felon! Please go to bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know what I did to deserve Bailey but I really thank God for him everyday]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an intensely beautiful hike up Mt Wilson yesterday 😍 So much water, fog, rain, snow, wind... Loved every momen… https://t.co/faXIGbefGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian West calls out fast fashion and opens up a convo about imitation  https://t.co/ssUcmc51pF]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say no one likes you when you’re 23, but I’m feeling so loved❤️ @ Mia Italian Tapas &amp; Bar https://t.co/onPVRawIP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Launching into our curriculum on change management for the @acgme #BacktoBedside project members - @DeweyLovesNeuro… https://t.co/vGiQlOpvno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chugsnation619 1 chicken has 4 limbs so it is ethical and saves other chickens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance @markknoller @PressSec @FoxNews @realDonaldTrump The electoral college is all that matters so he won]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preacher, Baker, Candle Stick Maker. Only God knows❤️❤️❤️ Happy Valentine Day. #SharingLifeLessons]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great dinner with great people at a great restaurant #apollogrillbethlehem #oldfriends #fabulousfamily @ Historic D… https://t.co/5Us9baUXgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite rainy day past time is reading. Here's a plethora of amazing reads that are new today at The Perky Nerd… https://t.co/yV2KKBf4dL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wheelerright @rebeccajshafer @itsCoriRosen @ryanscottstetz (Had to grace Twitter with it too.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland The United Nations Genocide Convention defines genocide as "acts committed with intent to destroy, in… https://t.co/J3yqGDXvx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having said all that, if it DOES come down to Sanders v Trump, I will vote for Bernie. In 2020 the theme is #Trumpmustgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister She lives in LaLa land she gets her so called facts from her boss who makes up his on false fake new… https://t.co/24jTBwlq2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt_the_thew   matthew: *exhaling for a long time* “pssssfffffffffffffffhhhhhiiiiiiiuiuiui”  me: “you sound like a deflating pool raft.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nofilter #thatssnow #saturdayvibes #ohitsnowed #carcovered #workoutchallenges #spinherewecome #LA… https://t.co/SQGHPpawNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NCISNewOrleans @zadegan what 's Lucas Black like as a person, he seems like good mannered human being on the set of "NCIS:New Orleans"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes a very sadistic way of teaching students but this method worked for me because I hated the pain he was having.… https://t.co/AxO2rKzM7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because you are married does NOT mean everything is "ours". Put the speaker bomb down and walk away, and you m… https://t.co/8kRvNM7RhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoyArlanBrunson @DonaldJTrumpJr Ranked last in a list of Best Presidents and this was a conservative new outlet reporting]]></document><document><![CDATA[All formal plans with acquaintances for this evening were canceled. Thank God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've noticed that a lot of people are so fucking judgemental when a black woman has a large family. So what she has… https://t.co/aqYKVuk3JC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is this Lady?! That “He Touched Me” was gorgeous! #ElvisAllStarTribute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealFact19 @BressieDiana @KamalaHarris This analogy is incomprehensible to lefties    They usually do not realize… https://t.co/hygGEwl7So]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachCelano Best snowball fight ever?? Velocity of a snowball by college baseball players 🤣⚾️💙💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lyds_campbell Eating dinner and drinking beer in a bar that showing it like live sport 💁‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radiomonroe Nope..nope..I think I was right the first time. 😂😂 I sware I'm usually not this cognitively challenged.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThursEastwood Cut them out of this and move them around the outside and put yourself in the middle in a “bubble” b… https://t.co/7rJidDtdEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LBraun1912 Right! Hilarious that a mispelled tag went viral &amp; hasn't been corrected]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 How about a woman! That seems to be the only assurance against this crap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beerguypdx @RJellyman @JonMontag @DRE_Go_Fish @ephoustonbill @badhopper @RealBMaxwell @lhtetrick @OkiTimes… https://t.co/5QaVr2hcle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got floated to the surgical unit today and let me tell you.... I should have brought a book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contact Congress NOW! (new bill to save puppies) https://t.co/gFLF1EStFr via @Change]]></document></documents></author>