<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@itssMelii That bmw probably gets pulled over a lot for not having a front plate. Nice buns tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[stk prices so sensitive to the s/p futures.. makes it horrible to trade]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryDilbeck @DeepStateExpose Obama made sure all of the Somalians were put into one district so he could have Muslims in Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s weird how people who win the lottery say they’ll retire and relax. If I won the lottery I’d spend the rest of my life in school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancywgonzalez I didn't know about the salad......now I have to go next week!]]></document><document><![CDATA[New, New Years resolution: no more missing concerts/shows for no good reason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone new  #rawosyters #thisis40 @ Mariscos Sinaloa https://t.co/qYGbCSQU0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is a “fact checker”? Seems like they’re just coming up with their own opinions with no supporting facts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leanin' up against one, watchin' the vibe Forgettin' all about the stress, thanking god I'm alive  #AroostookCounty… https://t.co/h5Xymbgw5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[My story tonight from Southwestern's win tonight over South Ripley  https://t.co/GQoYZRzGd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Defense Raptors are:10th in pts allowed-108, 7 th in FG% allowed-45%, 9th in 3 pt FG% allowed,34%-8th in TO’s fo… https://t.co/VBQt4iVWU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penelope7usa @AnnCoulter @CPAC Seems a bit short sighted oh well sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@homelaber @VM_FrankM @vExpert Hey! You’re going to give me a bad reputation 🤣  I wonder if I can decline Val’s application …]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌧 Freezing rain is still being reported this morning in parts of Sussex County, including Sussex Airport. Watch out… https://t.co/7Vg860ToWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC My mom worked three jobs and raised six kids. Imagine the pressure she was under. In all the while paying taxe… https://t.co/tte7t8mjHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m like half asleep watching Planet Earth for the 3rd time. Nature is fucking crazy. Goodnight y’all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lazy Magnolia Sweet Magnolia #craftbeer #sundayfunday @ The Lion &amp; Crown https://t.co/MEIuQGaSE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[RVX has arrived! This week, join a who’s who of social media influencers and national media to discover the best ne… https://t.co/03OTH44Exl]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASUNTO DE TIEMPO, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/VSg2lMSJxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now she’ll never win one, just being a woman isn’t intersectional enough these days. She needs to pull a Dolezal, a… https://t.co/4EJZSCXluJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How To Make A Baby With An Air Pump [7 Pictures] #laughter #lol #grin #laughable https://t.co/THADvBXAr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hectorgilmuller, mis mejores deseos de armonía, salud y éxito con motivo de tu cumpleaños 🎁.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 No one is above the law. Sitting President should be subject to indictment. The Constitution provides… https://t.co/dhYsL3BWE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredoPhss @As_TomasRoncero Aaaaah mis disculpas, el mejor defensa de todos los tiempos con el que ha contado la se… https://t.co/6clmb8zqHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm...I’m thinking more like Israeli.  McCabe: ‘It’s Possible’ Trump Could Be a Russian Asset  https://t.co/T2q5D05Sp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before a packed auditorium of angry residents, Seneca County General Health District votes to issue an intent to de… https://t.co/LV3pg4e9m1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las rocas ígneas extrusivas se enfrían mucho más rápido que las rocas intrusivas. El tiempo de enfriamiento rápido… https://t.co/7Mn50MGTVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The religious right has changed. And the Republican Party think they are the religious right so they have went so f… https://t.co/06ERG3EbtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaneKithier    Your son is playing so well and has an incredible future in front of him. He already embodies what… https://t.co/zt7gDjlbhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[De una cosa estoy seguro Vamos a servir la mejor #carne disponible para @sonora_gprime sonoragrill parrillaurbanamx… https://t.co/pbYGZqKoT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE every single song on Head Above Water. Thank you so much @AvrilLavigne I love you]]></document><document><![CDATA[When's the last time a top talent was traded at the deadline and ended up winning the Cup? Was it Jeff Carter? I'm… https://t.co/oXga3LsKdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are 2,043 billionaires in the world...9 out of 10 are males. At 3 minutes:  https://t.co/r6wUghfxYr Their wea… https://t.co/DfoTpqvLKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[NY Mets ace Jacob deGrom responds to criticism from Yankees' Luis Severino https://t.co/dzO53b2wAl via @northjersey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turns out I’m an idiot and should’ve listened to everyone who told me to go the doctor a month ago for this confirmed sinus infection]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adaniels33 It's really that bad. The refs think the game is about them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner You are one to talk. You have yet to tell the whole truth since before your redicul… https://t.co/46uYvpo0sA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spurrier: Dundon entered after original AAF investor backed out https://t.co/CFQjsBlSkI via @ProFootballTalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for all good men to come to aid of our country!!  This stupid bullshit from democrats has to stop!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Fitzcarraldo by @rockbottom at @rockbottom — https://t.co/HJp8yKG6hy]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBC you should be ashamed of this article. Until you call out Donald  for his words and attitude I suggest you cut… https://t.co/8lkeXlshz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codeblue87 i mean spinning up a commerce business that replaces lost ad revenue]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨TONIGHT 🚨 I'm hosting @bajasharkeezmb come get your #SexOnTheBeach with me 🌊🌊🌊  #VIPTXT 562 282 3198… https://t.co/aK3kJzC9F5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving for our local St. David's lunch. They mean well, but it's usually a little boring. Making the boys go with… https://t.co/QQT2K6oycM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sunset looks like Broncos colors. Must be time to go to bed bc I'm SLEEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImBuiltFordTuff Dreadful decision. Rosen has three more years on his rookie deal and then a relatively "cheap" 5th year option after that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it too late at night to have Crosby and Hornqvist reacting to Kessel scoring as my "mood" ... as the kids say?… https://t.co/zAcjnoYOa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gomez163 @Slate I said at the time that he spent more time around 12 year-olds then 12-year-old boys do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ja ja, wow!! Biden is not going to run for President, and I know why? He is old and and marry 2 men after having a… https://t.co/FtNMtoh6xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vann also flopped big time with 40 seconds left to put VCU back up by one. But at the end of the day, the refs aren… https://t.co/OuUoU6tWg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking News: Seen today , another “Hold My Beer” joke. It is believed a bunch of people still find this funny and original.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FyodorFish Is it not playing SF?  I thought the Metreon (at least) picked up all the big Chinese movies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoshaLinster Facts ... wish they would leave each other alone and go be happy with they new people lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Companhia aérea britânica declara falência e cancela todos os voos https://t.co/IzJLHe1xUK #Brexit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Phenix Street who scored his 1000th career point on Monday night vs. Union City in the district champio… https://t.co/31Y0zdwuUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@97Darion Lowkey coulda been had it 🤧 im boutta start hoppin on it tho fr lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson If we can just keep him there until we re-take the Senate and WH, then we can make him persona non g… https://t.co/1pt05YtX3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StPatricksDay5k #CorktownRace! Going to be a windy day! #TopOfTheMorningToYou! #LuckOfTheIrish Team… https://t.co/buCpqn7TlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinBartels2 @RapSheet 31 year old AB would be a MAJOR upgrade over Coop..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Planes, and now trains... (@ Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport - @atlairport in Atlanta, GA)… https://t.co/JahaV26YrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll believe it when I turn into Johnny Cash and my son turns into a Dale Earnhardt https://t.co/5Of1HpOf1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what happened when Putin named his horse "Donald J Trump"! @realDonaldTrump needs to watch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManWestcoast Wasnt green book the " qhite guy sees racism" film?  Guaranteed to win]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU THINK IM PLAYIN  #work #workout #gym #snow #cold #russian #single #buff #savage #dope #parkour #nike #samshapo… https://t.co/KOTRKUXxg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mañana 8 de marzo, día internacional de la mujer, leeré poemas en el kiosco de Chalco. Iniciamos 3 p m.  https://t.co/rQZ2943eBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@90sWWE This happens anytime I bring up 1986-1994 wrestling while @ATLMike2007 @TheFFRealist @DanSiegelUnCut are ta… https://t.co/BZRNSWNySU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Noah would play one week for every team. He will become your fav player if he is on your side very quickly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge shoutout to @kalpenn  for capturing myself, the Crypto Castle, blockchain technology, and cryptoassets incredi… https://t.co/go9G7b0FV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReyLeonVzla @NicolasMaduro eso han hecho muchos, hoy sancionaditos y sancionaditas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect day !!  Get out and enjoy it!! 🌵📸 🏃🏼‍♂️☀️⛳️  #wakeupaz #wakeupscottsdale #fsscottsdale #fourseasons… https://t.co/matY2lqH10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEUniverse: Get you someone who treats you the way @SamoaJoe treats the #USTitle. ?? #WWEFastlane… https://t.co/p9BTn6H2K1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNobleMan45 @_therealcomb What are y’all doing now? https://t.co/beArjyHk7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LL_cool_Jace 😂 what are you doing now anyway? Hope you are doing well! WDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swampynomo Dude we’re done here. This is my Twitter. You can talk about whatever you want on your Twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RionaMcArdle Would you be willing to send me your dissertation? I’d love to read it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J2XCK Where did you use to check? I’m curious I might check mine, could be worth financing something dumb like an… https://t.co/llY4I1DwI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“people don't regain most or all of their lost weight because their bodies effectively tell them to, they regain mo… https://t.co/LjwZg29XEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roomway @sportingnews Butler missed six times to Zags' zero. Made two F4s, three Sweet 16s. You're gilding your ar… https://t.co/Sx3Q23tKOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanteYeh @JJcolemanMD With ZERO benefit in any outcome measure. Supported by mult other studies of trophic or hypocaloric approach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF?? The Deep State is countering FOX News against Carlson and the Judge. I hope that #QAnon addresses this. I hop… https://t.co/SLxLZZH0Ej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATT Wait, I just saw a commercial from Verizon saying the same thing.  T-mobile too.  I guess they are all the bes… https://t.co/e7P7ABJPaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottEweinberg @80sAllOver #Silverado - hands down my favorite Western of ALL TIME ❤️✊🏻🙌🏻.... and it STILL HOLDS U… https://t.co/w9ZVK9MXLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiredofit16 @Guidostrong @getnickwright He didn’t nor did he understand them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their early films made when they were still conjoined twins have sadly all been lost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_Van_Mama @VSB39 @pattibacchus @CarrieBercic @HastingsCommCtr Thanks for the thoughts. Yes, modifying spaces is o… https://t.co/xCox8n8y0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[My beard looks gross and tomorrow’s Mill Fest. Oops. @ Ervin’s Dairy Farm https://t.co/sLIFUZDA4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilovejiujitsu These are the guys that think Seagal can actually break people’s necks with a chiropractic adjustment]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't say this often but I agree with President Trump's on a recent matter. The Alabama woman who joined ISIS sho… https://t.co/zqrEo8y3Vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Leader McConnell we Americans are becoming more and more disappointed in our Republicans in Senate an… https://t.co/jJVWazbJxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE HOLY TRINITY OF CAPITALI$TIC PRODUCTIVITY 1,) Land, Materials, Building = the Capitalist 2.) Salaries = Workers… https://t.co/vjIp0eDqJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shittt y’all wanna see all my cuts and wounds Ive gotten because what I had to dealin wit? 😂😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nigerian_bros I didn't use the word "insane." It is ridiculous, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gigirules7 @suziday123 @LoriMoreno @AlikaHope @momo_sandiego @Jessicasquared9 @JustJane2019 @JustMyTweet… https://t.co/bHp05akPOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoo boy, NC State vs. Wake is gonna be even more awkward now with Currie (He was the AD who tried to hire him at Te… https://t.co/Phn92QwQup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissUnivers0 No te preocupes por lo que piense la gente de eso no comes cuídate y feliz martes saludos cordiales,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto @NevadaJack2 The biggest crime was allowing her to be here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BKactualPodcast More fearful of his abilities, I took this from a safer vantage point last year. https://t.co/2zQK8G16cb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HIIT #firstthinginthemorning #kickinmytail #goingforit #healthychoices #weightloss #bodyinmotion]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stink, therefore I'm Spam- Rene Descartes #MapOfTheSoulPersona https://t.co/qoqqSUZN0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhutnguyen13 @Toni_Scurlock @DOJgov Oh yet another Russian so now at 27 Russians charged, and 2 Russian companies https://t.co/LQ3vKsAIYq]]></document></documents></author>