<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JoshMonkwords You saw an indie comic book movie and didn't bring me or dad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BYUbasketball The sad thing is, no one is surprised the team tanked tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My genius wife made me #universe shot glasses for my bday! #Cosmos #space #NASA #resinart #resin https://t.co/RXY5LXByB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlienart @AdeTheux I don’t need 100k to like your posts Todd... but if I did you’d probably like me a lot more! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[3. For your calendars: I will host a live debate on The I ❤️ CVille Show featuring Lloyd Snook vs Michael Payne on… https://t.co/dcKAV4k0Et]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VIXEN @TheVixensworld @GregLansky @AVNMediaNetwork @avnawards @AEexpo @RedTube @redtube1 @AngelDarkBlog @ButtmanHD… https://t.co/lhmA1rLBK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BubbleTitos Really? I didn't even know he was on the verge. Have I just not been paying attention?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@koby24beast But you've been counted by the One who matters .God never discounted you family. #LetsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenSchweigert @DozaEric I know! And it doesn't get better with age. That's why I haven't been involved with anyone… https://t.co/jK9MlcjXVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why post a video of yourself doing lines of cocaine. You think its cool, but it's NOT. People need to keep that shit on the DL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFDWrestling Saturday 2/23/19 Licking Valley DII Sectional  Championship Round  285lb Cole Potts Lost 2-5 for 2nd… https://t.co/pUBBYVZVtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come to Salon G in Hilton Austin at 3:30 today for "Building Just Systems for Safe Schools" with @hechingerreport… https://t.co/ni4grYxf9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DollyVol He once told a story where he got an orange for Xmas one year as a kid. That was it, an orange, and he sa… https://t.co/BxHR1C5WRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickCassidy_ Looking good 👍 Big question was it as fun as running in a #RCFGT3 around Daytona?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So good to hear that former ASD Cape Town graduate Ethen Sampson has signed for New Mexico United FC.… https://t.co/gwdvWlGRAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just gonna say it, United should make a bid for Firmino. If they can make an exception for Paul Ince, Bobby Cho… https://t.co/aw4t2unj1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[#weekendrecap📸 #secondstop hero_voguehairstudio_lucan hero_promotion_page #blazersandboots @ Queens, New York https://t.co/DaaRbXiUKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllcapsDcboyz @moneymouse74 @Starrbryte67631 @redsfantexas @GarDolphin733 @lisaponyexpress @DollyDwyer10… https://t.co/FSduWQ4lTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IL0VEthe80s Back to Future wins the gold and Top Gun takes the silver. https://t.co/iYxhpSEvjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be sure to tune into the @sports_ctv show tonight at 7 PM.... #TripleJPickemChallenge https://t.co/MUMK9p1BKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riotwomennn @NorahODonnell @ScottPelley @60Minutes 3. To wealthy Gop donors who caught a massive tax break at the… https://t.co/zwijKVffWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrLupo Just do a reverse Nickmercs Cam angle where it's just the bottom half of your face instead of top half]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruinsBroadcast @BVNitehawks @BorderBruins Come on boys, time to dig deep...thanks for the shout out last night Ke… https://t.co/ooxBusKhvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddssSchu Chew gum for when your you take off and land. It’ll help your ears pop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travistritt Alright @martystuarthq, you’ve heard from @Travistritt. He says he’d love to tour with Marty again. Le… https://t.co/6nTgUFRm0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RSun82 They are right, not as beautiful as Tomi Lahren you are gorgeous.  She's not even in your league!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como va a salir NO, DONDE VA A CUMPLIR CONDENA YYYY, YYYYY espero sea en GUANTÁNAMO, al ladino, justo al lado]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obianuju Well she would also argue that everyone in America has the right to a period. Period. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive said this for a LONG time when we continue to let everything become acceptable bc “love is love” at what point… https://t.co/YpJV59qlwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so obsessive about my nicotine intake that since I got my sourin air (cooler Juul) I’ve never let it die. Not o… https://t.co/Rkhl8lVGmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @DonaldJTrumpJr As Michael Cohen said , Donald Trump considered Donald Trump Jr. to be the least intellige… https://t.co/86tRUCOIpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[El vato que está narrando y no se le entiende nada con Luis Omar Tapia creo que odia a Dembele hahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Quillette @analogfusion As a liberal, I’m not surprised. A private company formed by any party members without che… https://t.co/Gzbh4moOsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outlawscalper We asked 100 women if they would date me. Here's what they answered.   Not interested..... 😂😂😂 https://t.co/vupOFHlnon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2Freelancer @cspanwj My guns don’t cause “ moral damage “ Besides that’s considered “ infringement “]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished an interview with @hightimesmagazine for @greenfeverfilm. Stay tuned for the article.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty stoked for captain marvel. Just need to decide if I want to return my extra ticket, or find someone to go with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to everyone who retweeted Candi's photo. I'm very sad to report that her body was found about an hour ago… https://t.co/JQd37EgjUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QTAnon1 That’s got to be a tough gig being the mayor of the least moral place on earth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddZolecki By not getting this done before Arendo signed, the Phils probably cost themselves $25 million over 10 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NCCBasketball I mean.... it’s gotta be Tommy Koth for 30 points tonight right?! Or Will Clausel!? or Maybe they both just hate Elmhurst 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRATV Have you visited your Russian spy lately?  #resistNRA https://t.co/HDcj3UI7KN]]></document><document><![CDATA[After one-@TravisHoops leads @HISDAthletics Sam Houston 17-16 here @CyWoodsHoops Gym. @RcsSports @FBISDAthletics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every where I look when I google #Qanon...MSM, @Wikipedia, or any #FakeNewsMedia say”right wing conspiracy”  Why no… https://t.co/raxqeQ5Mks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reverendofdoubt @Rick_Pescatore Yup! They diagnosed him with cynanche trachealis, from Cullen's nosology. Took off… https://t.co/RiawVPHOol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big shout out and a Congratulations @Ben_Howland @HailStateMBK and all on coaching staff for the victory over… https://t.co/Du8mS6UVgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely ❤️ when every person who has ever piloted an aircraft, worked in aircraft maintenance, civilian or mil… https://t.co/oiI60tviMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for walking in with me to Snoop Dogg ❤️ @ El Tropicano River Walk Hotel https://t.co/Izx4bscAnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benbbaldwin @SeahawksMachine @karatemanchan37 @JasonCheathawks Did you ever projectile yak in the middle of a lift?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamEdwards She’s so domestic. She can cook for her New York Communist Communes..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffreygoldbIum @scottmelker Also, if there’s any way at all I could get you to record a ‘Happy birthday Samantha’… https://t.co/MtByMGg1ZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can have anything you want in this life, but not everything you want 👤  #alternative #artist #mix… https://t.co/oCBdkhhtRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s my deal, I am not a fan of Drafting Kyler, I love Derek Carr and want him to succeed. However if they’re GOI… https://t.co/4uTpGIlSRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyTownsend11 @ldelpuerto @TheYellowSheet Was a reference to the fact that the #RedForEd band repeatedly played… https://t.co/EpKKrVIOZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[BD leads 61-54 with 3:20 to go and the ball @WendySkibinski @WayneTwpSuper @squire16 @MrSamuelNGC https://t.co/LdmzPoy2vF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAndyBiggsAZ @realDonaldTrump Seems to me that gun violence and school shootings are a much bigger problem.  A s… https://t.co/8KQzCpmlLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one:  Me to my crush: Hey girl I won't be able to talk to you for awhile. I'm giving up sweets for Lent. 😭😘 See you on Easter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First night back in #mancave feeling rusty but loving the chance to #playmusic and loosen up. @ Dogpatch, San Franc… https://t.co/86NNb9Vk9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@llchristyll @nils_gilman I got jobs at Idaho State and Princeton University within three years of each other. I ha… https://t.co/d1kYPprTsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's o🐟al. Let's do this thing.  3.16.19 @ Howard Knob https://t.co/OP80U05ewU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardWellings @Barnes_Law Drag them from the castle and fire up the guillotine?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulycham @davidaxelrod @realDonaldTrump He'll have to take a stand soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 18 might be playing harder than usual at @ChubbClassic as the wind is right in the face of the golfers. Tough way to finish.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CosmicSCryptid @MRasky @ndrew_lawrence I haven’t watched Fox News in 10 years. But I keep getting accused of it. I… https://t.co/Dcp2q8UQhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rabble smell blood. They will destroy America incrementally on their way to national socialism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So what you saying is you didn’t accomplish anything.    The art of the deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waters, the only constitutional Power of the purse to protect, should be Protected from you and your party. You and… https://t.co/Woz0avCBWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo this shit deadass got me weak she deadass eating Larry the lobster out this bitch 😂😂. I’m over here thinking how… https://t.co/eHijdGniIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most times in a residence not permanent, with a short lived experience around mom, poor execution by dad... https://t.co/aXfX4qPLY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendaGPrice love you mama B. Hope you have a great weekend and I hope the weather up there is half as nice as it… https://t.co/yEobLOdo27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leonardo DiCaprio’s disgusting dinner surprise was peak NYC: https://t.co/MLLAXBy6rL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@etuck495 Anybody over the age of 35 looked at this and fell out cuz they know the craziest dude walking this planet still Iron Mike 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeywaywannabe @PalayeRoyale Yes, Chicago has always been so wonderful to us but we couldn’t find a venue in time… https://t.co/cPdU4ZMHYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyKillerTV1 @DaveVescio I think I'd get a migraine and vomit trying to watch from that close.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackNtheOldRays Thank you! She’s on Onyx this year and they are so ready for this weekend!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnieChave @MikeJ_A @Erraticscc When I played we had 3 comps. 50 over league games and a couple of 40 over cup com… https://t.co/UOv42o7Pek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DontBeSnsiitive They really watch anime. It's quite common among alt-right accounts. Twitter is so much bigger now… https://t.co/WP9Uz6HbdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly... #CaptainMarvel just didn't do it for me. Felt like it had identity problems, and no real great characte… https://t.co/x2zcvsKAMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conn Dam spillway of Lake Hennessy, Napa Valley CA. 2.29’ spill depth #CAwx #dronephotography #napavalley https://t.co/qB8GaTucOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rex_rexchapman Both. Block first (reporter was  moving, wouldn't stand in and take the punishment, tried to ole' i… https://t.co/Lp16g0uLKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The coworker that only listens to buttock is side eying me SO HARD right now. https://t.co/NYKam2cY8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoardEveryday @ChrisDooB @dcc1018 @BrandonHRojas @_gaming4justice @TheTableTopRev @G2Summit @_stefanier_ If we can… https://t.co/MCrpxudqYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo que más amé de cada noche en Las Vegas: los rótulos, las luces y el neón 🤩  Fue un ejercicio fotográfico super i… https://t.co/LX4jzraJS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny thread in response to MIT’s “hipster” article. https://t.co/F7IX89rEee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta noticia estan interesante como cuando  Usain Bolt quizo jugar al futbol profesional ⚽️.  Que seguramente no ti… https://t.co/J67Kl4LuaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drdrank @FelonStonk @NotStockPricBro @ElonBachman @FredericLambert Sure , heck it was published at Marketwatch on… https://t.co/oh5C7gfdAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited for @captainmarvel , the reactions to the movie have me hype. Hoping to have a new movie in my top 5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 True Heroes, True Angels...  And the twelve gates were twelve pearls; every several gate was of one pe… https://t.co/ZLs3khW3v3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The BQE serves the same # cars in one day as the Lex Ave subway line serves during a rush hour, he says.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rmoran4446 @NickCannon Its not derogatory or racist amongst the BLACK community, being that they took a racial slu… https://t.co/cCIgjgLAEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donato's goal in OT gives Wild 2-1 win vs. Blues https://t.co/0wqHJI6RKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buttpraxis Like we seriously don’t deserve trains. Did we use a cheat code in the 1800’s to get them? I think we used a cheat code.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WokePapi 🚨 NEW VIDEO ALERT 🚨  Deezy Blast kickin w/ #TDXMedia follow his ig @kushwater ‼️💯 Check his interview bel… https://t.co/ElmeJORCn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much gratitude percolating through these boyish veins.⁣ .⁣ .⁣ .⁣ Lost files. .⁣ .⁣ .⁣ .⁣ .⁣ .⁣ #nightlife #nyc… https://t.co/03hZvP3sC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[That loud “DANG IT!” you just heard is from all the people who hate the time change, but now have to fight to keep… https://t.co/tnnvfTepjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hellotybeeren If I could fix mine I'd let you know how!  And just knowing you are out there supporting people and doing what you do helps]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just as fucking stupid as saying socialism is bad because stalin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaxReformExpert @AOC Not a trump fan, but remember when people and the media were slapping Trump around for saying… https://t.co/o1e5X4ohTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that the read aloud is over, Mr. Billy is conducting a PD session on how to broadcast live online utilizing You… https://t.co/c06564l6z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling so good and finally living my Peachy coral Prince fantasy! itsmekittykatkat did such an amazing job bringin… https://t.co/ocpNIO9Lxa]]></document></documents></author>