<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@semodough loving this arbitrage. either way i'm long celg if it falls apart, sales and patents looking good]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBC News - Trump knew about email hack, Cohen tells Congress https://t.co/VRAxrCEh66]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of those times where I need someone to talk to. #FUCK #MYMINDWANTSTORACEWHENINEEDSLEEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump You seem to be a very unhappy trouble person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly guys, for the first time in a really long time I can genuinely say that I am happy with my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elsie_lachlan @99poguemahone Many faces of Kauffman the therapy dog https://t.co/HFEjNiTlJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first Southern baseball game today has been moved to 4PM. Per @SouthernUsports]]></document><document><![CDATA[GM economist declines to comment in detail about auto tariffs. “We have to wait and see.” #mfg #autos @SMEMediaNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Koch Brothers Announce Plans to Intervene in GOP Primaries in Support of RINO, Open Border, "Free Trade" Republican… https://t.co/GkronQHhib]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien As bad as the movie was...it winning was worse. The academy learned nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladsit76 @waters1117 @pbalyta Well...we should do a session together next year in Dallas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LobsAllDayy @josephwoodall99 @NYYDJ2 lebron has missed over 15 games, and those guys had to win games- couldnt. ko… https://t.co/HcYAEXAZAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you miss football when you’ve been watching the Combine basically since you woke up this morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abortion's not a tissue issue. Abortion's a moral distortion, choosing death instead of prenatal human life.… https://t.co/KKP54RLWVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gen Z and Millennials see bigger role for government https://t.co/kVo5peIDuU https://t.co/MekcdiKQfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamJPfeffer WTF do we live under a monarchy? Time for a peasant revolt! We laugh about how silly kings and queens… https://t.co/L4vJ3zfzkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence @KamalaHarris Terrence is the best funniest you got me rolling brother!!! You have me laughing all day 😂! 🇺🇸🇮🇱☯☮✝🚂😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[We show throw a fundraiser for @CoryBooker at @huntandfishnyc Maybe getting a ribeye into him will help get his moj… https://t.co/c4FX2AUbfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once or twice a year Mac does something to surprise you. This is one of those times. Good idea. 🤔👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lmax97 @feekhai @Hazz I forgot my favorite photo https://t.co/8QzfroiUu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @RandPaul isn’t this more important than what Democrats might do 6 years from now? Support Trump now &amp; change the law later]]></document><document><![CDATA[@disarmingfilms @michaeljkellyjr @HBODocs Congrats! Look forward to watching it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am thankful we have a President who will protect its citizens from the invasion of criminals, drug dealers and il… https://t.co/302wcCWVx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommyjoe5587 @NBC12 Yeah, I heard NOVA will have more snow than us in CentralVA. Do you have a picture??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachTHardy @LoyolaMBB Hey coach, after Coach Mo and the @nuggets win the NBA Championship you might want to invit… https://t.co/UacNNLbEKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carreteromolero Found this link, on the apple site, too long to paste the steps https://t.co/CA5torEFFT I hope it helps]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATL Bihhhhhh... @hyperdenim 💁🏾‍♀️💁🏾‍♀️💁🏾‍♀️ *As Well As Me Tryna Get it Together...🤦🏾‍♂️* 👓 @westwardleaning  👕… https://t.co/tFfTPHF2U1]]></document><document><![CDATA[MMC Softball takes game 2 from #12 Freed Hardeman with score 14-4. Go RedHawks! https://t.co/KzkX4OtyRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep I definitely would say that their both in Love or HEAT. https://t.co/dTHhCcRFAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tdsb Thanks. Sorry to bother you with this question. My son’s school bus was 15 min late this morning and I want s… https://t.co/HBmlCiDPRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1fishfan_72 @EJFootball Love the guy but don’t want to see him in Miami. If we were one player away then maybe. But we’re not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DA: Yoakum students, faculty lied to grand jury about locker room vandalism https://t.co/SqGaEOPb35 via @vicadvocate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kavanaugh shows his stripes on Supreme Court's 'shadow docket' https://t.co/MxeSZJGmrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some refresher terms for Black History Month.  Prejudice: an unjustifiable and usually negative attitude toward a g… https://t.co/EC1lz3f9UZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the greatest city north east world…incorporated this day in 1837. #Chicago]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son's favorite player. Every game we went to last yr he would just yell for @ScottyJetp4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your VIP tickets before they sell out. Free Admission before Noon. $10 General Admission after Noon! Don’t miss… https://t.co/IxpJqd5uxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday and everyday is #womensday. 💃. I am proud to be apart of a community where women can… https://t.co/XfuQgEhvoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mans had the best 5th birthday, my little turtle boy https://t.co/Hqkxs6rXrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susie_meister Wrong! Jesus wouldn't care Trump is signing Bibles. At least the people are picking up their Bibles… https://t.co/M0QB2797WN]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad to see these colleagues in Byzantine studies recognized by @MedievalAcademy for their fabulous work.… https://t.co/bjipYUfSvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEmilJay @KrisPLettuce If the second part ever shows up it's something]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenYomtoob  @netanyahu  So, when we were kids, Ben and I had this blood-brother-pact to go explore the Bermuda Tri… https://t.co/Ge7v16J7MX]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: ‘Google train?’ Caltrain puts naming rights up for bid - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/6MrQexKXWl @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our playoff run continues this Friday at Catoosa vs #3 ranked John Marshall at 8PM. Winner advances to state! We ne… https://t.co/FFnvWO525E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewsricci I’m still pissed First Man got shafted in several categories this year...it was out of this world an amazing movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFagan1987 @YanieYampier @ricardorossello This lady is just like the rest of the people, complaints but no new fresh ideas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Not as much as John McCain or John Kerry. They didn’t use Daddy’s connections to stay out of Vietnam, as you did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 2 @OmahaMBB is the highest remaining seed in the Summit League Men's Basketball Tournament as @GoJacksMBB fell to @WIUMensHoops earlier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, the game isn’t going so great, but it s a great day to watch a game!  #letsplaytwo #smttt @ Pete Taylor Park https://t.co/8EmAFJCbgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCJohnston14 Dog it’s still Madrid till I die but that man too shwifty with the ball at his feet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaiDavisPoet Sorry I wanna say we but got me personally it depends on the situation but I’ve never had a sex sessi… https://t.co/6dSHLrbVSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nature’s way of showing Trump that LGBTQ is totally cool. 🌈 🤡 🖕🏼 https://t.co/wyW9hj2bc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson The same garbage people who think the world is flat, 6,000 years old, and snowballs mean there is no… https://t.co/CURqj703wc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 We’ve heard that several times, what and why were they 13 national emergencies? Was it the drug abus… https://t.co/0OYT4PkkRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the he’s not getting any younger line well no shit I m not getting any older to be miserable either 🤣😂🤣 or i… https://t.co/x9Z68LMxTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson @LindseyGrahamSC You have been involved in hush money schemes and that’s NOT how ya do it.  Tell us h… https://t.co/mzkWLoPe69]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upgrade your colored@stone to #Csarite, a beautiful #colorchangegemstone that @bijules has collaborated with. This… https://t.co/fSnulS7UjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JediFett @emcsweeney1215 This is the picture of the light bulb going off. Everyone has had this in their wrestling… https://t.co/JTuVyxxWP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was Jeff Bezos the weak link in cyber-security? https://t.co/fPqfvd1ra9 just move HQ2 down to I-20,  SE of Atlanta… https://t.co/rzbQGOo2Pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dad’s favorites were Shane, It’s a Wonderful Life and The Music Man. I’m pretty proud to have those three as primar… https://t.co/HQzeArQWHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JooosieB Grattis! Snart är det omöjligt att fotografera en kvinna utan att det finns en mobil med på bilden.… https://t.co/XlU2NIDC8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[The definition of "Choices!" Here's my recap of #DragRace #AllStars4Finale for @vulture: https://t.co/63LwgGzRjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senior in high school, makin some grown man boss moves. 🙌💪✊  #graphicdesignGOAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Catalyst_Campus in Colorado Springs, CO https://t.co/1dX0IYI1Z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add my new single "Never Change" on Spotify: https://t.co/D2zvGaVOK5 (powered by @distrokid)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Southern Promises by Thomas Bradshaw. Mar 11 - Apr 14. TICKETS IN BIO. @ The Flea Theater https://t.co/DduvYj6PKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOW ABOUT THAT PUSSYCAT 😻  #OLIVERIO #OMNIPOTENT #OMELETTE 🍳🥚  #BODYBYROCCO 🥰  TRAIN W/ME 🧠💪🏽💪🏽  #FAT LOSS 💦💦💦💦💦💦… https://t.co/pI5G2htpTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today isn’t looking like a good day in Philly sports. We let Foles walk to be a free agent (nothing in return) and… https://t.co/7pUONK8rTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[dont be mad cause of my time difference. the fact that i'm gettin dough and im ridin different.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Axelrod is saying by having the convention in Milwaukee, they are trying to show they haven’t forgotten abo… https://t.co/JqRvXZ54WU]]></document><document><![CDATA[As stated in the article....62% of those that responded to the survey said either they wouldn't know what to do in… https://t.co/kKGp008Z6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great partnership with @womensfundindy @Marion_Health &amp; @IPSSchools 👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @JussieSmollett Heterophobe 😂 I’ve never heard of that one! I’m gonna have to use it. I’ll give ya credit. 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesAALongman @ABCWorldNews Screw her! She helped kill people, is a treasonous POS! She married 4 ISIS fighters,… https://t.co/RwRAF2TxYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#backintheday Pre show picture of me Gettin’ ready to take a ride on the King Doublebass (Red/Black Burst)… https://t.co/kCDwCIvxZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Craig1140 @Ben11486471 @Lilpoo404 @globalnews I didn't say what you have here you are making things up like trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cherrynchester @DeanPerl1 @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson I sense you like Donald Trump about as much as I do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess I’m making a new insta since my ex hacked it and is messing w all my stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honey I can see the root so keep showing off I am able to notice that well. Seriously my god go see my hairstylist… https://t.co/HMz1eddMup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WINsconsin026 @The1998jj I played at VA Wesleyan. We played you guys in the final four in 07]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travestibanu2 @traverbeynon @ShemaleSurfer2 @Ts_Lolita @IloveShemale44 @PassiValerio @pic_poster @rickstwit12… https://t.co/COVr2afSMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[All accomplished in one week! #prolific #meded #medtwitter @MayoMN_IMRES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Don you need to stop ok no one is listening to you anymore , you ran as this outsider and turned i… https://t.co/lkRG01njir]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I want to “laugh” at posts, then I realized I’m on twitter and I can only “heart” things, which is okay,… https://t.co/3VH44tc8MK]]></document><document><![CDATA[We actually powered through!! @ Rock Springs Cafe https://t.co/bW3K65M1aM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews Looks like women get rewarded for fucking and getting pregnant...whats that rule in states]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bvmper @MisterAssEater Lmfao cause i been trolling so much. I need to start chilling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steady Eddie. Gelnovatch was a key piece to the @ACCMSoccer championship run for @UofLmenssoccer. #LsUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[No joke my dad moved one of our security cameras above where my cat usually chills and has been periodically checki… https://t.co/rzgWolxZvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @Nokomaq Toddler trump will loose the election this move is just more rope to hang himself .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Still@dont understand  then why you aren’t pushing to change these laws that are crippling and costing us… https://t.co/5RwVSKWPyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickFoles Thank You for the best sports year of my life!  Good Luck #PhillyHero]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kiskiss08 @DeniseMTarHeel @SoFreshlyFaded @KayGragg14 @goheels1984 @UNCSwtHrt @tbyrd423 @TarHeelBruin… https://t.co/5mYP1dxPn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP Isn't that part of the Muller investigation? That hasn't been proven nor is there any evidence of such. I hope… https://t.co/ktk6YJMjHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Undercoverhist Karen Vaughn was member of my committee and she was very important to my generation of (1) historia… https://t.co/qC0ntsQ1LX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPUSA does your organization take positions on issues or more so just freedom in general?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TWlegion Lets just pretend he needs this to make the cut. I’ll say he misses and then he drains it to prove me wrong again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biagcomerci @Sportsnet Haven't beat us in almost 2 years, but I'm loving the effort https://t.co/KWOdY3XjJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dontyoudarryn Emergency escape plan Alpha, go! https://t.co/2R2GkJoScA]]></document></documents></author>