<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I think it's hilarious how @Poshmarkapp got mad at me for posting a picture of nipple stickers for sale and then th… https://t.co/egPuPAO9dk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnamaeKElliott Yes, that was the 1st thing I noticed. He is good, and Brian May has still got it! 🤘🎸]]></document><document><![CDATA[This @DavidGrunfeld photo made it onto @NOLAnews More shamed refs with @theharryshearer plus @markchildress as “Mr… https://t.co/Ip1oxVphbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[AIRPORT LIMO SERVICE NEAR ME (703) 459-9666 https://t.co/woqh7PKtPV https://t.co/dSMz4VVLis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rucoschools As a Rutherford Co parent why is schools not closed or on delay? It's pouring buckets and roads are fl… https://t.co/Bd4Y1Xse5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going solo 😎   Here’s a song for you… SOLO by JENNIE https://t.co/gVxNpsR8n7]]></document><document><![CDATA[not even 30 minutes into valentine's day and I am already not looking forward to seeing all the oversized teddy bea… https://t.co/xC7I6uOOvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read something that said to look at God as those who look at their King’s and Queens in foreign lands. How you se… https://t.co/ywq7Zqz2HY]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Craft a Brand Manifesto [Guide + Examples] #pr #iabc https://t.co/AzJeljzDwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like spending Sunday morning in bed alone listening to a thunderstorm. (This is not normal for WNY in Febru… https://t.co/QdrATPGfAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonOfManAndGod I’m just wondering if We need to review Revelation 13. Maybe? #TaraAnnMoons actually thinks it’s hi… https://t.co/FH2bgbVUJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@311DCgov @DCPoliceDept  @DCPoliceTraffic @MayorBowser   @popville Why is this car ticketed? Please tow! It has bee… https://t.co/0ybVlUb46u]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘The Breakfast Club’ Became a Must-Stop Spot for 2020 Democratic Candidates https://t.co/DGDYxBL6jz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCWthrWatchers @LisetteVogel Wish I was in springtime.  -7 outside Blech]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all really be letting guys who have less than you in your bank account hurt you ? Can’t relate 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ghosts walk the secret halls at Union Station. I think they steal my lunch occasionally https://t.co/IbvLZq9IjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[OKAY SO — Your girl wants a Brazilian but is HIGHKEY fucking TERRIFIED of that pain; after much research, I’ve conc… https://t.co/HaHNFTgB8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza I'm going to put this out there..Cory Booker. Same week this "attack" happened he announced his run f… https://t.co/XG9wZoUVNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the follow @LSookarry love the very handmaids-ish profile photo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dedicated to my amazing friends who run marathons. Well, I thought you amazing until I read... #funniness #chuckle… https://t.co/vHHT8SHro2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jedemoxie @LenaWaithe @TalentiGelato That’s a supernatural power right there⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoticiasVenezue No le pueden poner un tapon con cloro en la boca a delcy  y cia anonima e inclyan al maduro aese uno bien grandote]]></document><document><![CDATA[A ti te sale muy bien mentir, pero a mi me sale mejor hacer que te creo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelicahale You are amazing, adorable and so talented. We will be hearing you for a long time. God Bless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SNHU_Softball Great job ladies! So proud of you! https://t.co/uHgV3JdrSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 facts about turmeric  1. The curcumin in turmeric is what’s considered “the” part of turmeric with so many healt… https://t.co/CMyzarINTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@filmdirectorAMi @charliekirk11 What happened to Otto is horrible. But we have to find a way to get him to get rid… https://t.co/YqCPec44wK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just let a boy who told my friends I was obsessed with him come over and watched him beg and tell me how much he’… https://t.co/81BKYeZdbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished Body Blast #3 this morning to complete my exercise goal for this week!! 🏋🏼‍♀️🏋🏼‍♀️🏋🏼‍♀️🏋🏼‍♀️🏋🏼‍♀️🏋🏼‍♀️… https://t.co/KyX9fjCxrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 20 Best SomeEcards About Love &amp; Relationships https://t.co/M53pG2MqOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#singingtruthtopower @_DiggingRoots @folkalliance @ Fairmont Le Reine Elizabeth https://t.co/rlTI44G4Ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am now patiently waiting for this Khloe &amp; @JeffreeStar Twitter drama. https://t.co/f6pe4J1BWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loulouartguru I get that. I keep getting ads on Facebook about clothing for plus size women and how plus size wome… https://t.co/Qqz1fpPg27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieF @edcampnova @ThatsWightman @timstahmer can you help? When and where is the next #EdcampNoVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I end up having to sell my car I’m taking the sub system out and putting it in my other car 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyciuum @JahnyaNovak We can exchange st con, as long as they’re different 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexGaskarth @Jordynraelove @AllTimeLow @JackAllTimeLow @riandawson @iamamerrickan @nbcsnl challenge accepted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @laurads_laura Here y’all tell her! https://t.co/Tg00Hc1Skc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DiamondandSilk Our great President walks the walk AND talks the talk. Keep up the good work, sir!… https://t.co/f9fIkYWOXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[i did this one time with the movie remember me and had my heart broken all over again 10/10 do not suggest that shi… https://t.co/J3wrPXxbl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GangstaDatabase @shaunking @AltUSPressSec @MarkMeadows @RepMarkMeadows ...that he's been keeping a secret...]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyways. what do y’all wanna be when you grow up? i wanna be a therapist specializing in substance abuse and stuff like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayoshock Bc marriage shouldn’t equate to whether or not u take someone’s last name - but me personally I getting mine hyphenated]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday morning with my fellas @ Ragland, Alabama https://t.co/8sQ8aP3abr]]></document><document><![CDATA[She asked them their classification as she’s doing this. The students were sitting according to grade level.   Out… https://t.co/0G9WJZfKAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vpisano @LoriSECAggie @UACoachMurphy @molly_fichtner @ULM_Softball @AlabamaSB @isabel_pisano @catherinnee22 See you there!!!!❤️🥎💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh what a great night of celebration! Happy Birthday Ernie. ❤️ erniebochjr  ab_neh13 #openhouseparty @ Norwood, Mas… https://t.co/06LTMCDXJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#humandevelopment #aging WRAG by WOMR podcasts via #soundcloud https://t.co/C1BjVrTomY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of March 4th #dool #days  Thurs Mar 7th  Brady pressures Gabi to team up with him to take down Stefan .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rpondiscio @caldis I am on vacation next week—surely there is something I should see! (last year we caught 'Black… https://t.co/E241Bt8P1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seven Hills’ senior Greg Kalin is the state runner-up in the 100 yard butterfly. Badin’s Luke Paxton finished 6th.  #cincyswimming]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffFortenberry   Please  #Cosponsor #HR961/The SAFEAct/#Protect America’s #Horses From #Exportation For… https://t.co/ebG8A9qjGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Do they realize how few people they reach on billboards. Versus Teitter that reaches millions in minutes. How… https://t.co/xIJ2HQGzB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[ugh saying see you later to this is so so so so hard 😭❤️ https://t.co/VhoeekHPax]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are not a burden we are a model!  I look at a School Board and district leaders who have forgotten that what we… https://t.co/RASM7KD8id]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you think one big thing is being accomplished on your wedding to-do list, but it actually unfolds 10 more secr… https://t.co/ATPnWkZ604]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @maddow  love watching her she explains everything so clearly and dramatic!😁 #TrumpCrimeFamily #ImpeachTheMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talktoomuch51 I can't watch this without crying.  It exactly how I feel about anyone he's with . I'd give anything… https://t.co/YDxk9yzSg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where do I find friends like this lol whereeeeeee https://t.co/Kzr1JqSLjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[OCEAN CITY, Md.- Springfest's much anticipated line up includes Grammy-winning artist, @leannrimes .  The "How Do I… https://t.co/vlDUV5TfHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[GBB HT: Crete 22, North Platte 11. The Cardinals built on their lead in the second quarter and they’re now just one… https://t.co/z70t7VPdda]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas brothers getting back together has literally caused a universal alliance. All i see on Snapchat is everyo… https://t.co/TB3rQJON7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let us therefore strive to enter that rest, so that no one may fall by the same sort of disobedience. https://t.co/BIVsDkZ3Kt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hit a PR and put up 30s for 5 tonight on shoulder press, slowly....... but surely]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timhaggs I'm sure that's probably similarly good at containing germs but also...now yer tits are covered in snot? No thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When asked for their favorite Chicago skyscraper, Lightfoot was the only Mayoral candidate to pick Marina City.  (E… https://t.co/YjK5uJDIDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙈🙉🙊@TheDemocrats who ignore facts, then call on endless investigations since DJT won election @realDonaldTrump did… https://t.co/iDlaTMU1lq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wellll...at least we moved off Smollet for an hour. Kraft Breaking News has taken over the airwaves for last hour.… https://t.co/ISvGttdOet]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally kid y’all not!! I almost burnt the house down when trying to heat up a Chick-fil-a sandwich with the FO… https://t.co/RcyyfVbkCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are all better together! Whether it be a friend, a family member, a boyfriend/ girlfriend, or spouse it’s easier… https://t.co/jjga0ar9rk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve reached a point in life where I will literally do anything to support and help my friends be happy and success… https://t.co/xQ2cZcbBei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradFothergill1 I like the point you are making. Although Andrew probably could not beat up a female with her hand… https://t.co/ap9m5F128I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MimiTheProblem Bright ass foehead shawty had to turn my phone down 😂🔥💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAOC @SpeakerPelosi @KamalaHarris @SenSchumer @SenFeinstein Shame on you. This is real. This is America being at… https://t.co/doDxKQzv69]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which family will build the tallest tower? @McMullanElem #MustangSTEM https://t.co/rLFqAPWaXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LRT exactly! Y’all was doing the absolute most to Demi Lovato. Sis didn’t even say anything mean smh 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t ask for anything more. I live for moments like tonight. ❤️♾ https://t.co/khGoRriJDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home sweet home (@ Kirkman Home &amp; Garden Center in Bloomington, IN) https://t.co/RnHl8qFcAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day to all the generations of women and their good men. Pictured two of my favorites th… https://t.co/07S0B0eNlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think I can reserve this seat? #55Strong #KillTheBill #SB451 #NoCharters #NoESAs #HereWeGoAgain https://t.co/Ddpx2Y8g06]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Viviane6677 @PucciaPatrizia @enriqueiglesias @TereOrt51687394 @ElbaklySami @janaplauen @SimySemsem @gabryluce… https://t.co/QcE8LnAIrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluegrassep @gbbcountry If you’re an asshole, you act like an asshole though. Not a good look for coach K.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaviota330 So her owner left her with a sibling to go in the service...now the sibling dumps her? Pitties are PTSD… https://t.co/Izix81xpKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbagump324 I'm still waiting for one of those babies! Getting bigger,too.  Ah, they grow up so fast.p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARodriguezABC15 Too Funny!! But I prefer the 60’s...I’m s native AZ’n and I can’t take the heat anymore 🤯🤯🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[All fun and games until Miss B thinks she needs to interrupt my TVW viewing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jen_Z_2017 Love you Sis!!!! You are an amazing woman and I’m SO PROUD of you!!! 😘❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing to it but to do it!! #10k #rundisney #rapunzel @ Walt Disney World Marathon https://t.co/dEaARM2dtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouAintABarbie @TevinsAGenius Both y’all buggin. U can rent a HOUSE in Georgia for like 850 a month!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've always thought "I was wrong, I am sorry I hurt ______ and I vow to never intentionally do/act that way again."… https://t.co/p0DTjdBJrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIs4Tardis Good taste. I'm fond of all the classic Doctors - I started with Pertwee due to reruns - but Peter has… https://t.co/FTRg1hkeaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mitch_Reames @GlobalPRMolleda You know I’ll be asking for your input as we build this sports comm curriculum. You’… https://t.co/TUgkCBjfJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ll be up early helping you navigate this latest storm! Join us at 4AM!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theTrackQueen ‼️‼️‼️ You actually say the funniest things around people too....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our tape sculpture metaphor for redesign highlights the important role of #StudentVoice. Oh.... and not being afrai… https://t.co/td4FxvtIjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connoisseur 😎 Lemon 🍋 Skunk - An MC Fave SunMed Strain 🔥 🌿 | The Maryland Connoisseur 😎 . . Happy Valentine's Day 💝… https://t.co/hgzS8B2Uum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sedallas @Glinner @MavenOfMayhem @Martina As a scientist I find your assertion that the TERF position is scientific hilarious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My @kroger pharmacy here in town sucks...waiting for the @Walmart pharmacy to fix their mistake. Seriously I called… https://t.co/JMQjDuGGBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our own KHS senior, April Wilson, organized a Black History Month Live Wax Museum!  Love watching our leaders show… https://t.co/wziqv2gH26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames @JaMeS_CLAAR our childhood is not fulfilled if we don’t see this together]]></document></documents></author>