<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan Looks like he even cleaned those eyebrows... Lol.. great pic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@westward2009 @justicetime @AriFleischer We have to wait till Mueller report. Then all sh*t will hit the fan with declas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your donation is greatly appreciated!  https://t.co/HDlXCBHBEI 💜#lupuslife 💜 #transplantlife 💜 #lupusnephritis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WOWK13News I like the dates but I foresee students losing some of their days for spring break and the Christmas ho… https://t.co/hsinGgiVQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WHOAINSANITY @ABC All the people in China making her shoes????  It didn’t help the US.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Researching at my favorite Barnes and Noble. #ankh24designs #ankh24designsillustrations #fashionillustration… https://t.co/E5AbX8GUGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I needs me a care package like this @SDJBeauty that u sent @coffeebreakdani love it. Like she said love when brands… https://t.co/6bGZl5CrWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel the need for security, safety, grounding? This beautiful Mala is hand-knotted with red jasper, garnet and agat… https://t.co/RpnvdrkHmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My vacation for summer was approved!  And it covers my Goo Goo Dolls concerts😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmalinesadie @SchittsCreek Right?!?!?  Need another 30 minutes for this show.  Can this be arranged? 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell @WhitfordBradley If it made sense, everyone would believe it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dadogcosmo @cnnbrk @donlemon Don Lemon, you are as bad as Jussie over your hate for Trump. I cannot believe you still have a job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dansinker @Chronotope I can’t tell if you’re joking Dan, is that the midwestern nice coming thru]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBenShade @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @DonaldJTrumpJr @seanhannity @OliverMcGee @EdKrassen @krassenstein Q sent me]]></document><document><![CDATA[i really have the best boyfriend. I couldn’t ask for any one any better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidOAtkins Careful w the generalization...I'm X and ...i'm seeing a ton of my contemporaries condemning and appalled by both]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well...people in Hawaii aren't shoving their children into storm drains anymore as missiles fly ...so there's that.… https://t.co/CA0ZmtgOg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best part about interning for @HOBCleveland is getting to see artists I never would have seen on my own. Today’… https://t.co/puh0n7daGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad: “wow Colton’s got a lot of clothes in that closet, if I was on the bachelor I’d have to give Tommy Bahama a… https://t.co/7Rfdufr4cs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to know what gets old? Old people thanking me for my service/saying it takes a special person to work with spe… https://t.co/xNRjMuTopm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kingtuff and crew being at home in #thetroubadour he never disappoints and think that’s a great club for them.… https://t.co/fgNeaucpeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I slept in my contacts last night and had them on all day today and now I can barely keep my open :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk My car currently for sale located at Wheels &amp; Deals Santa Clara if you know anyone interested in buying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkilahObviously It’s damn fine as a ballad, too. DAMN fine. https://t.co/x9HeKqso1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safaviaa @UofTDRO @pmcancercentre @RadMedPM @Sunnybrook Congrats and welcome to the @UofTDRO family!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband is a reporter. He is for the people, of the people. And, Mr. President, he is not the enemy of the peopl… https://t.co/3sTqEhicyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano What man? Say his name Alyssa hum you can’t because I’m sure you wished his bs was true that they were Trump supporters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTSPhilly A great weekend for you guys!! Can’t wait to see what you’ll do in Hershey 🍫🍫🍫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congress and Senate, are you going to sit idle,  as The CEO and Friend of Trump is going to persuade him to fire Da… https://t.co/fB5sF7w4EK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My, my. Comey’s notes could “adversely” affect the pending Russia investigation.  What could they possibly mean by… https://t.co/4fsNJRCtH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hop this is true, all other states should make that a requirement for ALL candidates ( otherwise it may not stand u… https://t.co/sKuDyxFEne]]></document><document><![CDATA[i could wreck it if i have to, but i’m the wreck so what would that do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really just want to buy @KailLowry’s books and lay in bed and read all day. 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[In recognition of International Women's Day, we are celebrating one of our many amazing clients, April Moncrief, th… https://t.co/eCYRnyFEd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethMaitlandDQB @KingMinos777 @YRInsider Wonderful!  Always glad to see my favorite Abbott back in GC!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So guess i can take my time and wash my hair and sing in the shower lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my Pastor @fhunscripted. @friendshipwest Day at The Capitol.  #FWBC https://t.co/ALk2VqIJXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Esta mañana filmamos @CronkNoticias!  Puedes verlo y mi historia sober el conflicto venezolano este sábado. 🇻🇪   T… https://t.co/EveNIqomtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday everything irrelevant except big heart 😍! @ Irvington, New York https://t.co/KoLvzrcaR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW: thick snow covering Huntington Ave in #Boston 6-10 inches expected #NBC10Boston #necn https://t.co/Fe3JTXYACN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Theres so much to do before tilly's surgery and things I've gotta get 😅 guess tomorrow night isn't relaxing but cle… https://t.co/5y9jl1xlWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[021919 - Above Your Head A beach umbrella and crystal-clear blue sky at Disney’s Castaway Cay #fmsphotoaday #fmspad… https://t.co/ykAHE16hTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austin Mayor Steve Adler is here #icon #SXSW2019 https://t.co/hVD6ndR3Hk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, Twitter is the one social media platform where I rant the most. For those who are following me, just igno… https://t.co/nVQ0sb8UrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time my roommate says hello this is all I can think of https://t.co/5zzvdO1KWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[do y’all remember when grace house beside hobby lobby used to be a movie theatre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg @LindseyGrahamSC I will hold on to hope, it is the best option available.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremiahjw Cool is a mainstream institution and I’m too unique for that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Hes going to work on the 2020 campaign. It's not like he's working with an epiphany here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 692 SW Everett Court #PortSaintLucie #FL  #realestate https://t.co/nfuXrc9YNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Share the magic of reading. From now through March 31st - for every “Shellie” (selfie with book) posted with… https://t.co/o4AWqdu0Ts]]></document><document><![CDATA[W @womenwithgifts  E @_BPDiaries_  E @AlBell42017  K @simplykatricia  E @MadiDearson  N @InspiringThru  D… https://t.co/SxePKbZTa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1936power @paulsperry_ Republicans are not who they used to be. I am a Conservative and angry at the GOP for losin… https://t.co/7vhyzmawNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies, if he ain’t defending your name and who you are as a person then please find a new man. Trust me there’s me… https://t.co/r26pRLtUcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missjessicaww @TheView @sunny Joy &amp; Ana Navarro are the only ones who stand up to her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to be a powerful chat for sure! Hoping my @VBGifted @vbschools friends join the conversation! @brandongifted… https://t.co/sd4KmbXaTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorglenn504 Also! And I’m not a shot shooter so I just be sitting around like 😐😐😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bedevilme666 @MAGA2ARIGHTS @Stephen57036680 @KathaleenHarpe9 @monkeyMagaKAG @DoingRight1 @DallasBrownin16 @Dbargen… https://t.co/Zf1ZmoAEC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stand a bitch who tweets their personal business and exposing their bfs or friends. Or girls who post every… https://t.co/OlA33ggzYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GitRDoneLarry Larry, does my husband buying a new larger TV count as his Valentine’s Day present for me when he wa… https://t.co/rWcrdAtIKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rev_elliott @ThePolarJ @CynthiaNixon @JoeBiden @mikepence This is why we need people like you out of political pow… https://t.co/hntjioRAYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[i been waking up everyday around this same time and it’s starting to get annoying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Whales and other marine #wildlife deserve quiet oceans‼️👍🏻❤️🌎❤️👍🏻‼️ PLEASE TAKE ACTION NOW to PROTECT the #Arctic… https://t.co/1odukN5COe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nós poderíamos ter tido um Príncipe na Vice-Presidência, mas por causa do Bebiano acabamos com o “bobo da corte”!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence @trublubeliever Absolutely! These Repubs have no morals or conscience. Cohen is holding up greatly. Jorda… https://t.co/atbK18ZtxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 1:32am which means it’s Valentines Day. So Happy Valentine’s Day if you need me I’ll be listening to @5SOS son… https://t.co/GtLnbjxujQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was me when my daddy and uncle use to rap in the laundry room 😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great turnaround for @TUOWLS_WBB to even finish 6th in the @American_WBB conference just such a tough way to lose t… https://t.co/WCRD0mlgjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomItForward A15 Not only do I not mind but it's actually my very FAVORITE way! Sometimes just  touch of salt.  Th… https://t.co/q1ns0toNgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDilanianNBC I think the term pathological liar. Is it hereditary? #speculation #inners #maddow #trms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mvno4 mike where are you?? youre not back yet, see any plays? can I call you man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Priincessbella I can’t wait to see you! We have to hangout as soon as you get back 💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CindiMadsen @LBrownRoberts @clairepmarti @drslayton @ccannonauthor @AmalieHoward @LegionofJen @beth_vrabel… https://t.co/ijwE1d8j7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend was amazing. @fatbellybella had me radiating &amp; vibrating on the highest frequency of love 💕 #hello… https://t.co/kKVg8d3JhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanWuori @SupportEarlyEd @ZEROTOTHREE @RhianNAEYC @NAEYC @childcareaware @kbstevens Are we getting to the point wh… https://t.co/QaR9LCZqhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so excited about our new product launch and want to help all of my friends, their teens and young adults (12-2… https://t.co/qMTbhUjlrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Last Ship was excellent. Unfortunately this is as close as we got to Sting. Fantastic weekend with the Banases. https://t.co/CPHwqLbCBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just two goofy (season ticket holdin’) goobers. 🥜 Happy birthday, BB melisserr! Love you so much and I literally do… https://t.co/onW9NkyVTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, walking the only red carpet I will ever walk in my life 😂 #SXSW2019 #sxsw https://t.co/TxHPdwN5T1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I napped 3 times today and I’m still tired. Why??? https://t.co/NySlIKp8fU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister asked “how do you spell Somalian?”  Lydia:I think it’s “Ts...”   Me:🤦‍♀️... wait, Lydia what did you just… https://t.co/51XF462U9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me @ @shxyreneee and @haleycaprisun_  for being the realist and also supporting me and bs tweets 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra I don't understand how they think.  A baby born alive after trying to abort it tells me that's a stro… https://t.co/gglEAltp6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReelTalkQuays @ladygaga You and Bradley Cooper had me and my daughter in tears last night!!!! Such a beautiful and moving performance!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My acid reflux wakes me up in the middle of the night to just make me fuckin miserable. I find that quite rude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KJensoncreative Aren’t they? I’m always surprised with what 10 year olds can do when given the chance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gerrinnesmac @letgolifeflows @pkamla1 @LavaletteAstrid @Adele47018578 @TanRob22 @Mike6Truth @jill_magnussen… https://t.co/rUfp336kaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[saw a new primary care physician today and i love her so much. she saw on my paper work that i smoke weed and she g… https://t.co/PhveA4jARA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_mireyahMOLINA LMAOOO 😂 A buffalo chicken salad will never taste the same if I’m not eating it with you :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawsynElizabeth *10 year old us after hitting the final pose like https://t.co/BanHv6Y2oe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Roland Archer just enjoying a beautiful drive through the country and came across your banner. This brings back… https://t.co/FQ2T4O2ZJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCMcLaugh @PintDiaries My sincere condolences; this world has lost a bright light indeed 😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this happens at our wedding, I’m immediately asking for a divorce. Take note @DMyers1590]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just slept in for idk how long without an alarm waking me up for the first time since I’ve been back and it felt… https://t.co/gKLxKrifg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Dr Snyder for a leading us in great discussion today.  Appreciate the invitation for collaboration.… https://t.co/Fk1ezs5SWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[some days I sleep for 12 hours and some days I don’t sleep at all   what’s going on man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for brunch!! (at @BlackeyedSallys in Hartford, CT) https://t.co/SVlyX57X7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshRamsay you guys looked like you had good fun tonight; more so than other shows I've been to... good on you!! y… https://t.co/84lVd65YUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at LabCorp? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and informatio… https://t.co/xcMVI5SG7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[She should just pay me to be her best friend I’m already out here fighting for her and idk her 😩🤣🤣]]></document></documents></author>