<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Perhaps-unpopular opinion: on the whole, the professional “conference circuit” is a horribly irresponsible mismanag… https://t.co/OMaRrzVfUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @TedCruz has an idea on how to fund President @realDonaldTrump's proposed border wall... Make El Chapo pay… https://t.co/pLlbW4OJ69]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍😍😍 Bom and Joy's Love Photo Booth.😍😍😍 @ Courtyard by Marriott Oxnard Ventura https://t.co/VsVM6EoHlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMarkPantano Calling Good What Is Evil And Evil What Is Good. Isaiah 5:20 Woe to those who call evil good and go… https://t.co/diIHu2i8Wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drdrew what we need to go and do is pursue the “neutral mind.”  This is what my psychic friend has advised us all… https://t.co/aUTcRJdzDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[well another impulsive decision by jared &amp; I https://t.co/1I6D7uy0Rm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping the #TVP will be cleared for tomorrow’s commute @CityofLdnOnt  - it was a bit of a slog today 😜 #frostbike… https://t.co/oPDyySOlSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@open_mix @matthewjdowd @mschlapp Yes, but how many indictments so far?    It seems like they have something to hid… https://t.co/VSf24cKWKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally hit 5k on IG 🔥📈  This stuff is too fun   Just engaging with other like minded individuals 24 hours a day 🙌🏽… https://t.co/Gr6mcKXA3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnycatholica @KathySchiffer @Michael_Voris How many times have we hear the liberal claptrap, “We’re all equals… https://t.co/XXduXPIHMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought this had to be a parody account . Our draft dodging president is a joke. @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been going to the same bodega for 7 years but tonight he asked me if my boyfriend ate ketchup.........]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stan Van Gundy looks like someone who can live off nothing but steak, whiskey, and cigars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mviser Feeling good about being fucking brilliant compared to the dumbest billionaire in America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to find my way with the Damned and so on. Thoughts? 🤔 such a great song but not typical of their library and… https://t.co/e8CV3IJCfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN You’ll be able to reuse that statement with Trumps name soon.Karma doesn’t judge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggiebrinker I'm partial to spending 4 full hours "planning" to roll out of bed and go to the gym]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg wut they retroactively fixed it right there *in* my tweet is this some kind of divine intervention? Are you the… https://t.co/dYJBJQKZlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBrennan You still flapping your lips?  Mind over matter traitor!  Mind over matter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenKolke @gretchenwhitmer @NoShamePeriod @RepDebDingell stfu before u get dick-slapped b*tch w/o a profile pic - n… https://t.co/yhufOUkbrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The highest level verbal jujutsu ever displayed on JRE was @Timcast tapping that lawyer from twitter over and over and over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emsthxtic @ndaynn @prisnatics Yeah I agree, I think he could’ve handled the sitch better though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomensDay, Utami Hayashishita, Stardom's "big rookie" holds four championships including the "Future… https://t.co/35zhWQFrT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 13 of #MWE Mac Miller Blue side park. Amazing and outstanding. His flow is great and the songs are great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFStradamus So I watched the last episode twice, first time I thought it was dumb. The second time I was a crying… https://t.co/czs7Iyrpfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterkessler Wait till this week when you can go see everyone in shorts before Thursday! Now that will be attractive!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pelicans again show grit and fight but fall just short of the comeback.   Oh, and that comeback happened with Anthony Davis on the bench.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatiePhang OMG its #TacoTuesday and @PaulManafort is still rotting in prison. https://t.co/NxoifMamyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How can there be Presidents Day when you don't have a president?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeoDiverDown @Quinceyjakarii @LowBlackFast1 @halillgutierrez @adrianiaaa @cKentclash @robbedy @delwilliams I think… https://t.co/eleevkgsCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ball to the wall behind home allows @k_robinson20 to come across.  10-1 Alabama B5]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of 3 @FHLadyRangers 31 Bedgord 18 @TheWizOfOz11 @calemillig @TribDemSports #PaGirlsHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow the case for collusion against Eric Wynalda grows! Biased PRO refs can’t let their golden goose, these Colorado… https://t.co/vwGKQuxShQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RetireMeASAP Nobody is. You have to win a best-of-three first-round playoff series to do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnAsplund1 @ScottKuffel @UJHPrincipal @UnitedBand304 I’ve accepted the challenge from @JohnAsplund1 to post an a… https://t.co/7lxl7gF2ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snoopdemidogg have you ever made vape hash oil? So instead of butane I just use a resin press and triple distill.… https://t.co/0orgoUqIHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Westin Los Angeles Airport in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/SRAJL4tBgb https://t.co/OnB1esxBDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antidominionist @deuceohsixx He's a Seattle area conservative radio show host. He basically just complains about e… https://t.co/71gHJJCMKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Umbrella academy on netflix might be my new all time favorite on netflix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @CanesBaseball on @WVUMSports , Add On Some More Runs Fellas!!! 🙌🙌🙌🙌⚾️⚾️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RollTide Swimming 🐘🏊🏻‍♀️🐘🏊🏻‍♀️@kensey_mcmahon @FightingSpirit https://t.co/IlzJl0Z7nL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @mb_butterfield to post covers of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews. I’ll challe… https://t.co/mcg8QqxWFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 6, I have accepted a challenge from @KyleGetter to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations or reviews—ju… https://t.co/gWdywXdK2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SXUnofficial @SXUnofficial365 @KVUE @fox7austin @cbsaustin @statesman @AustinChronicle @CurbedAustin @KXAN_News… https://t.co/5gSSOFsvCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The WCC Super-Ladder Round 2 is done!  Check out the bracket, courtesy https://t.co/WRdK6XmnNl! https://t.co/PY1l2wxLW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not Mardi Gras without #kingcake @ Chambersburg, Pennsylvania https://t.co/1lLq3fhN1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fresh #justbecause #roses for my #queen and the #princess... don’t forget to let them know you love them, no matte… https://t.co/dBvGmJ0aK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[ON-AIR: #ALLCAPS AHL affiliate seeking 9th consecutive win today. @TheHersheyBears lead @LVPhantoms 2-1 at 1st inte… https://t.co/WpMIsGrh6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would Kim Jong-un concede anything when Trump is working hard to break the United States-South Korea alliance?… https://t.co/YeiwUZefAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blake65Griffin @keeley__duncan They know we pack that thang on us https://t.co/Y2JhV7H95N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made sure to take my time and get the most I could before claiming my prize.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish the wind would pick up a little so I could fly my kite. #itsaneagle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add another honor for Rock Island @QueenBrea_1 as 3rd Team All-America. https://t.co/zMcRGEp4Pl]]></document><document><![CDATA[White gay men are some of the most racist people on the planet. Periodt.  We want the world to accept and respect u… https://t.co/y5pZ8s0Jsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jon Vitale scores 14 points for Jonathan Law, but the Lawmen fell, 65-59, to Hamden high in the SCC Quarterfinals S… https://t.co/K8uTBfmrf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My Kingdom is not of this world.” We need to learn to respect and appreciate our differences and not become the di… https://t.co/keXRvDfkeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunset I #montrealairport #yul #giglife #headinghome @ Maple Leaf Lounge https://t.co/bK5EV7SKZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoopscritic He said all 29 teams are on his list. It's amazing how the media seems to be working for Boston. Geltz… https://t.co/HM3xXHFphI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate that spider/possum video more than anything I've ever seen in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this review of Justin (Licensed Massage Therapist) on Google Maps #OnGoogleMaps  https://t.co/JsFA0a8KUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@numeroun0_ Hmm. U wanna eat in good vibes. Just do Ricardo’s. If u wanna sit n have a nice great meal. Steakhouse.… https://t.co/YTZYGiKaaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrizzyDrew94 @FatKidDeals @9princesss If I win you can have my airpods broke boy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion is a NPOY caliber defender. With him on the floor Blackshear doesn’t have half as good of a performance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No charges filed against cops in Sacramento’s controversial #StephonClark shooting. The case roiled Sacramento. And… https://t.co/islw1iRffa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dasertine @realDonaldTrump I thought Jussie would be smarter. I don't know why I would think that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@best_utica I've never seen so many bricks in my life https://t.co/7jqqFE8lCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaKNewton @MeganGannonTV @mynbc15 Meanwhile you can find me in Montgomery. https://t.co/sPUZ4UJzEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @realDonaldTrump Trump’s Minister of Propaganda. Goebbels reborn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobCruz09 @DavidEckstein22 Pretty damn good teammate too! Correction, great teammate. #NoOneWorkedHarder #NoOneMorePrepared #STLCards]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DustinT11 Incredible. They beat the shitty Magic team after being down to them late. Really got me with that one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters Again, Auntie Congresswoman Maxine Waters For We Can’t Be Anxious For Anything But Through Prayer… https://t.co/GEuKcJogw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomNovelly @TMobile @Delta @JohnLegere Glad you’re getting service that cheap! I have @TMobile and my service is $75 a month]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsHopkins96 The renegade Hopkins tosses grenades into the status quo of life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rainfell_key Ooof. I’m so sorry for your loss, hon. I wish I could be there to hug you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandallOtisTV And as a gay black person with a decent singing voice, i am sending my headshot and resume to the pr… https://t.co/RLs4BoUczZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@utahjazz Give it up to the effort though. OKC doesn’t want to face us in the playoffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd @SenRonJohnson Why don't you ask the real question if it's a National Security why is Trump playing golf… https://t.co/xTQEMyprgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Search me, O God, and know my heart; test me and know my anxious thoughts. Point out anything in me that offends y… https://t.co/YnhkM97c30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeelPoliceMedia was it really necessary to sound that alarm on our phones all the way up in Ottawa as well? 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good sweet potato fries are lit but most places don’t make them well. More often than not they’re over-cooked or mo… https://t.co/e6QC5xdCa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kalebhorton here's the trick: kidnap the oil magnate's son and then start doing a podcast with him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @SpeakerPelosi @AOC @AdamSchiff I don't even even need an investigation to know that fact I can se… https://t.co/EF75e6nnbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is farcical. This must be why my ex spend so much time in the bathroom...no wait that is... https://t.co/QMnaPo7w88]]></document><document><![CDATA[Them taxes hit different when you gotta include your business earnings 🥴🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reneemusicus @DiamondandSilk If it helps u cope with losing so bad to Trump, Renee - believe that garbage. Have a… https://t.co/MuWbDTuglk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeHarrison you are so missed. You were brilliant, and the world desperately needs millions more like you. #HappyBirthdayGeorgeHarrison]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ride inside Spaceship Earth teaches us the full history of human communication. It starts with cave paintings a… https://t.co/2XZcEYxg6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl Hey while your at it, can you ask him if he ever filed that police report? You know, the one he said he… https://t.co/RKYFK1TQDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! God is working miracles! Bring the lost. It’s all about souls! @RealRodParsley @davidcrank]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the same shot happen to me all the time and they go talk shit and block me in like wtf bro, like grow tf up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steamtraintime @Ariphon @bnacker Now I want an actual Gospel According to Danny Ocean movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look forward to the day graduates from Hillsdale College are more desired to hire than the Ivy League Schools]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 6 #LasVegas #Vegas #Talent #ThePlaceVegas  #SpankyHayes  @ImSpankyHayes #SugarBearEntertainment  terranceflow… https://t.co/1LcN70gIhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonCross00 Yeah, somebody reminded me of the Cup Noodles and I *do* remember a bit about that. But the Coleman s… https://t.co/yATmeehTm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Arrogant idiot is right James, its how the dems think, whether they have been in office three month… https://t.co/S8wguMZZkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DKPghSports @dlolley_pgh @CarterCritiques @HunterAHomistek @Dejan_Kovacevic @btsteelcurtain @SteelersBrazil… https://t.co/XcYrmCHJfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaKasparian so. Since you support the Armenian Genocide, you also want “White Christian” genocide?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m convinced when we find Jesus again the community will find the church again.”🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill I have not realized any benefits of the so called #TaxReform &amp; so called #TaxCut👎🏻 @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/rodkQtfD5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bubble bath is always my go 2 when idk what I want I’m fw the matte on top this time (new go 2)]]></document></documents></author>