<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If anybody threaten to put money on my child head OH BEST BELIEVE you will get found and dealt wit. Tf .. you don’t… https://t.co/l8I43Vi4UZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikeggibbs Definitely check out A4AOntario - it's an autistic run advocacy group, some of them are autistic parent… https://t.co/F7HV6xfcU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeBryanOnline @ClayPageMusic Kinda reminded me of a young Curtis McNeal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st Birthday to my sister, @jessirank3698! I love you and I’m so thankful to have such a hilarious, kind, an… https://t.co/KDcdbOz05Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to be a woman and seek a sex change operation. This will be my third chance to have the surgery and I’m… https://t.co/79f6zOBeJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chriskrokshow Because Trump is the Devil. He doesn't have love or respect for all people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incase anyone needs to hear this: your feelings are not invalid, your emotions are real. You are valued.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y luego esta él. El que se queda cuando ya todos se han ido.  El que te va ayudar con el ziper del vestido.  Se que… https://t.co/9MSQNFaJmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that expense really an investment that will move you closer to your goal? It's time to fly!… https://t.co/f1iyoHxMzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@houseandhens I don’t want to bombard you with advice because I know that can be frustrating but I have clients wit… https://t.co/Q30jMvaZtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonDeSantisFL Happy 174th Birthday Florida! God bless us Everyone! Amen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days, I have my life together. Other days, I forget everything- including my sandwich. Luckily, I have a sweet… https://t.co/IqhsmNZreO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatSoOnika Lol, that’s not a mv. But okay, don’t stress me and my Nicki stanhood like that ever again 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I shouldn't be surprised but there's a dude in a headdress at the @Ottawa67sHockey game https://t.co/88IINmn9Wa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TWBDimash #WorldsBest @dimash_official @WorldsBestCBS    You are the reason I got on tweeter...you are the reason… https://t.co/bxgbWxtJkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoloresCatania @Andy @BravoTV honestly I would watch a show just about you &amp; Frank being roommates]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dude, where have you been? They’ve always had fireworks in DC and celebrations. Get your head out of your ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love how much they love to read and learn together! #curriculuminnnps @nnschools https://t.co/jCy1k3I5iR]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a stunning turn of events.....I sang words in the RIGHT order tonight😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben Carson thank you.  President Trump is doing a great job,  Wake up people]]></document><document><![CDATA[After being down early 8-0 RHS Boys basketball get their game going and have a 14-8 lead with 1:58 left in the first]]></document><document><![CDATA[WEIGH IN: Do you think the Space Force headquarters should be here in Florida? https://t.co/4X64N8JzGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[How the fuck you do me wrong? Left me for a nigga that wasn't worth it like me. I put in work to be with you, he ai… https://t.co/c1R2fwRqqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefShady_ I showed my mom this tweet and she gave me the most concerned look and then continued to laugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does Disney own part of Netflix too? Because if that's the case then they might not be able to pick up the show… https://t.co/uSrfHCJZIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @BenedictMPWhite Wow! @SenWarren big liberal socialist wants to go after the internet giants if she… https://t.co/ogyUNv69Ev]]></document><document><![CDATA[ORIONS BDAY IS IN TWO DAYS CANT WAIT TO OVERLOAD HIM WITH BESITOS AND ALCOHOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas_Duncan All their names are the same - hard for me to know who is who.  This is the one who keeps marrying b… https://t.co/mFFoDuJipE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@globalnewsto And they are going to ignore us - notwithstanding. Let's NEVER give up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_vndrue @FutureDodgers I'm happy baseball is back but also sad. Very very sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the baby shark concert starts at 7, but bedtimes at 8 https://t.co/1TxXKyxN6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @cmikegoodwin @realDonaldTrump @KellyannePolls @DonaldJTrumpJr @EricTrump @SenRickScott… https://t.co/HctPUzRkhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OANN @AndrewsHarley That’s a violation of THE US CONSTITUTION!  Does pissant Cuomo think he can just ignore the un… https://t.co/nYfHR1cRiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spyscribe The progressive ones?? I finally invested in good ones this year and I *love* them. Truly airtight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertBeamon Yeah hopefully you make your money back if you sell it. Or you can get commission for recruiting peop… https://t.co/JptGiVdlpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My morning run view went from yachts to sailboats ⛵️ https://t.co/hiSsEb7mHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look how my Bowser head turned out! #bowser #cosplayer #cosplay #supermario https://t.co/v0eiqI76lL]]></document><document><![CDATA[x3. Trying to run the cranky away 😬  (I’m not really sure it worked, but if nothing else, I *should* sleep better t… https://t.co/dzDhWcq6vM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just need to keep telling myself, “One more semester.....” https://t.co/y0ZXdZSXqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissadderosa @Newsday Completely irresponsible to talk about the tax cap with no mention of the impact on school… https://t.co/n8hGy0zpsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom tries so hard to be a good person but she really is just an absolute savage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollyhoodshay “dOnT BlaMe THe GiRls fOr HiS aCtIons” babyyy that couldve been avoided if you never gave that old ass man a chance]]></document><document><![CDATA[This nigga I work with doesn’t do any fuckin work but he sure can talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[take time to grin. Windy..... yes, but lots of creases and wrinkles too!!! sweet and precious basset hound!!!  ps,.… https://t.co/bLSgSnt7o9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Knights Go!! - Drinking a Mango Cart by @goldenroadbrew at @tmobilearena  — https://t.co/OdJTyk7qWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherrig108 @SUPERGOCHOo @jaimemiserachi @guiller25136814 @happy02013guy @PattiBrookd @BeatriceLacy @Lunarteddy… https://t.co/s1tPp4XUrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone tell drake to take notes. produce a song from another culture then you help the people]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Openhouse tomorrow, Saturday March 9, 12-1:30. Best location in highly desired #millspondestates #stjamesny… https://t.co/Wc6HJ3zdJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I got this little foxy lady and I’m so in love.😍 I’m beyond excited for this new addition to my family and I… https://t.co/4bP0NaH3be]]></document><document><![CDATA[The female version of a circle jerk is a group of women going around and admitting that they are all intimidated by each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OttosGrove You all who are saying I'm clueless, you're the clueless fools. Please go out and ask all the students… https://t.co/FLCYRWTwu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are we on the bingo board? Are we getting close to coverall? What’s happening]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would this country respond to a crisis by victimizing it's most vulnerable citizens? Drive them to death out of… https://t.co/232ZmNmJP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You're not getting it are you?  I didn't have to do this means, I could behave like the past presidents who did nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_F_Kennnedy We deserve a Congress that is not bigoted,  biased or anti-semetic but, we don't have that.  They… https://t.co/hzIWgOYtYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lordt I am being TESTED on this 6 HOUR flight. Sitting next to two humans who are SCREAMING about how much they lov… https://t.co/gKAGosdHxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally did a yoga workout on the @onepeloton app. Good chance I’ll be doing yoga more consistently now. #fitness #fitnessaddict]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for cheering me up tonight, @DrDogMusic. Always a good show... see you again soon!! 🖤🎶 https://t.co/fN3hoWJAhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guy I blew off last week: where have you been? Me: on vacation  Him: yeah I can tell you gained like 5lbs  Me: *smi… https://t.co/CQc8N1TSfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to get up but golly my bed is warm and comfy @RobertDowneyJr  @SKeynes1  @williammoseley @TomHolland1996… https://t.co/HCAYjM7J8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneFallenAngelM No, I did not.  I am interested in the answer of People around me. Like the leader of study last night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wavy_Nights @x_Reign @phorever_boujee Omg the little boy in the front is soooo cute 💕💕😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for “Cold Pursuit”. Hopefully this doesn’t turn me into a homicidal maniac.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sober February is over, the sun is shining &amp; I just finished my last nursing final ever!!! https://t.co/HaSlVwJmuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who says #internationalwomensday has to last only one day? We still celebrated in Zumba®️ class this morning at vbp… https://t.co/qiTiI9B5Pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beth_farrah @sarah_forgey @lilchickhat Never thought to bring it up! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boyfriend let me borrow his Navy northface jacket. Really cute how he thinks he’s getting it back sometime soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LassiterBrian What a tragedy 😥. Hope your daughter is doing ok - a lot to absorb and process]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GOBankingRates Best Banks ranking will help you choose the ideal bank for you. Check it out! #BankBetter… https://t.co/peDliNAD4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[train your hair’s oil over time.   your hair will start to adapt to your washing schedule if you’re patient with it… https://t.co/NBTOwG96v5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nagwala stress ko forgive and forget na ka agad 😊 #ADNForDaddysGurlWithALDEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianaartsy It does!! Especially cause I drink so much of it like I don’t get hungry and I don’t know what to tell people 🌚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @ericswalwell I don’t use my COPD inhalers because of the cost.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve now been in Seattle for almost 6 full days. 🙃  I’M FINALLY ON MY WAY HOME!!  (21 hours after my original flight...!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The scraggly extensions might be out but i'm not! New Paris map in OVERWATCH! Lunchtime stream starts at 1230pm EST… https://t.co/m3QXqf24Tv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainbows are magical reminders to look at the bright side. #lookathebrightside #rainbow @ Salt Lake City, Utah https://t.co/q4KtFnlbwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wackyvorlon @selinazawacki @hackaday @tindie @Regorlas @socallinuxexpo Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, and this is kind of weird and specific, but if a show is set in CA and they show a New England dairy brand (H… https://t.co/XaV2fmFsZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdle2963 This is all you need to know that @TheDemocrats know there is going to be #NoCollusion it’s a #WitchHunt! #WastingOurMoney]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; Brennan advances!! #wediditforalewags #harvey @NISD_FineArts @bearly_scripted https://t.co/DXymTOFRqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all should’ve just saw my face when I read the text u received regarding Machado]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babyname_maven @drfixus Many diseases can be inherited and have a genetic component.  While others are more of a “… https://t.co/2CoXpKAvBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you really care about someone, you would never be able to hurt them. Period.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Spend It (Feat. Young Thug &amp; Young MA) (Remix) by Dae Dae on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/xGSzKqTQda]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @acwahlert to post covers of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews. I’ll challenge s… https://t.co/oCj0uBIUx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ordered! Can’t wait to dig into #Platform @CynthiaLIVE! https://t.co/ktIcPWozDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnitedPeoplesTV I assume Greenwood is just traveling as he's just coming off injury. Would be ballsy to start them… https://t.co/oKhFhAtfCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t realize how good this song was until i was in my feeling............. forever stanning a QUEEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to win a women’s hockey game: flirt with the girls on the other team to throw them off😏 #elmira@3 @ Murray Athl… https://t.co/04hzUYuHaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing elderly couples who’ve been together forever makes my heart melt &amp; makes me so emotional. ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeDWerm @brandicarlile @amandashires @MarenMorris Great idea. I’ll make one for my office]]></document><document><![CDATA[date night! | @TheTableBakery #deliciousness #asheboronc #ncblogger #datenight #butfirstcake #ncfoodie… https://t.co/ZF3dsC55mA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Future is a god among men no debate necessary 🤣🤣🤣I know they was tight 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday at work we had a meeting and the Vice President asks one of us “anything else to add?” And this guy respo… https://t.co/9iBRVud1LV]]></document><document><![CDATA[A quick reminder : You serve a God that is not afraid to fight &amp; has never lost a battle .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I would say it's time for you to #UnsuspendMother__Gaia but you were late for that weeks ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know the green parts of a radish can contain more nutrients than the radish itself? 🌱 Try making this Radis… https://t.co/v2kMrAke22]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No...your presidency  needs to come to an end. What's  collusion? I thought you and Rudy told us t… https://t.co/wJMQFw3x4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[The small things are all that matter in the end. 🖤 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/soCXqoSWMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[5) Does anyone else fine it odd that @RepAdamSchiff, the Russian Lawyer &amp; Co. all met with #GlennSimpson of… https://t.co/kcgxCRMAyb]]></document></documents></author>