<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DappyAndNana Working in restaurants I would imagine they’d have to treat the kitchen the same, but it doesn’t sound like they did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliaDavisNews That'll be a chess master move for Putin, trying to decide how best to exploit evangelical Trump supporters in Russia..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Who are you, must be the ground hog, do you not see what's happening]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao got an ad for some pipes and i fell into the trap and bought one. Send help plz...]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want to do in life is stand on a stage, and sing/belt out music to my heart’s content...but I’m too scared (n… https://t.co/iA9DQZjoPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paxuco5 They create mini versions of themselves, and cycle keeps repeating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Propaganda in plain sight. All the press should walk away from this farce of a summit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmillaCon So ready, have alarms set because I won't get home till 2am and then need to be up to buy them! Super excited 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Sunday evening...yes it was still light (compliments of DST)...also got a little QT with all my boys...ready for… https://t.co/YvFSlkuFNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It has begun! Fat flakes falling outside the @wpri12 studios. Team weather coverage starts at 6 a.m.!❄️❄️❄️ https://t.co/wPEqdvLeZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning and happy Saturday. This morning inspiration for you and food for thought truly 🕉🐉 @ Pennsylvania https://t.co/iHauULEYkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to say I do love the look of freshen fallen #snow . Not necessarily a fan of the frigid cold. #sandwich… https://t.co/0ZJlg4u9JN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had so much fun promoting positivity and kindness with @thumperproject today at the WBCA Grand Parade! Thank you so… https://t.co/hn8PQLkbjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Miss Junior is making a PHENOMENAL impact. Truly the definition of a queen and servant leader ❤️ #myasu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottHech You could explain how the judge in Alabama got away with admitted voter fraud twice. Then things like th… https://t.co/iz50uOSgaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this is what you think marriage is, you either need better married friends or a different spouse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not showing up to nobody funeral that treated me and who ever else like shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rey_Sistance @lfkraus @AryaResists @EmmaFrostResist @JadedCreative @ellievan65 @LunaLuvgood2020 @B52Malmet… https://t.co/YCUbwFbC6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are trusting a university that fundamentally misunderstands freedom of speech to educate the next generation of… https://t.co/ytrzCoWrda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working the night shift to get this one posted since ive been slacking😬       What have i been up to lately? Well h… https://t.co/KK3thyl18x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not gone lie, hurts a little. Feel like its hard to breath at the moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[rewatching grey’s anatomy for the fourth time and I find myself really appreciating george o’malley and his story… https://t.co/R2QAoC7csc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC We could of but instead I called Mcshit and got you cold burgers cause no chef wants to cook for the WH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @Groupon why send me a invitation only email and not let me participate in it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@11thHour Thanks, @BWilliams, for being the sole @MSNBC evening host to mention #Bernie2020 - it was a record-break… https://t.co/WJOEkxPq6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrlandoSilva17 So they open one by my house and i looked up their ig and saw him their, I’ll send you the video on ig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@infinityscotty Omgosh I was listening to his cd in my car the other day and I said seriously this should be his ne… https://t.co/EiuIEWqelk]]></document><document><![CDATA[remember when the phrase, “planes don’t just fall out of the sky” used to be true? just awful. #EthiopianAirlinesCrash]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRHeritage @HeritageES @douganjo @abbrake @MsDobbsClass @BeaubearTerri That is so POPPIE GREAT!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reality check for my #WW ( #WeightWatcher ) Friends: #Panera Kitchen Sink is 38 #Freestyle points or 800 calories!… https://t.co/hxUhfWdabh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrewingTalent @aplusk @LetsFixWork Yes! Maybe my family would finally listen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlowersAbstract #hypnotique (February 2018) by @sdekouadio #art #abstract #AbstractArt #abstractartist… https://t.co/g0dnVdQdAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WileyPostKHOU @StephKHOU Wiley!! You made it!! 🎉🎉 thanks for taking one for the team 👍🏻😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep seeing so much shit like this whether its about the jacks, shawn, wdw, other artists. Im so sick of people a… https://t.co/JIDqzIX4yR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @_CARTERDANE @alex_mecum @BruceBeckhamXXX @adamramzi_xo @corykanexxx @Beaux_Banks @TeganZayne @TheWesleyWoods… https://t.co/KQfsJN5hMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just ordered 8 new coffee syrups/creamers.. someone needs to stop me.. but pls don’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shegoodfam_ And my original point is , that’s your employers job . I’ll always tip , but it shouldn’t be set up th… https://t.co/BFJ3GM4zTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seoul Songpa-gu District Mayor Park Sung-Su: Seoul Songpa-gu, Korea, Shut down the illegal dog meat farms,  markets… https://t.co/cyeZJRSjqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a long time since I have reached 18,000 steps in one day. Thanks canterburyumc ‘s confirmation class 2019… https://t.co/6fQ3d7pvJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome conversations happening in this session about toxic course combos with @dknightVT and @DustinGrote at… https://t.co/kqzXtCYNar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laying in bed snuggling with my two favorite boys. But all I really wanna do is get up and eat the rest of the ench… https://t.co/75m7iYhLuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish instagram showed you which account unsends their DM’s https://t.co/2rsTpN6jo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sprague716 @amypenprase @Sophronisba @brianschatz Or Adam Schiff as AG.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the becoming-commodity of the human and the becoming-human of the commodity as related by that renowned dialectical… https://t.co/iTcpMbDxLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 down•3 to go! So incredibly proud of these students ❤️❤️ I am so fortunate to be a part of such an amazing show,… https://t.co/z3xLI44ehd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmazonHelp Amazon Brand - Mama Bear Diapers Size 5, 124 Count, Bears Print (4 packs of 31) https://t.co/njl6ifRA3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so fortunate to be born on the same day of greatness man ever!! Happy birthday Dad! 💙😘🎁🎂🍾🎉🥂❤️LOVE YOU EVERYTHING… https://t.co/YqRhTttw9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azbrumb18 @tyizar @ZooWildlife ???? I don’t get this?? A woman was in the wrong here- nothing to do w/ the owner,… https://t.co/tGiMa6C2R8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go get him Sen Schumer. Make those Repub Senators show their hand. #BlueWave2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[А почему молочные продукты – это так плохо? Меня батя до сих пор заставляет кефир пить, когда я к ним в гости прихо… https://t.co/2cBhZYdHBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This squad needs to be put to bed, they don’t compare to our guys @tpinsonn and @alantwilliams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You should never let the word deranged slip through your lips or tweeter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SiriusXMFLY Just a practice BUT we’re listening to you guys on the hour and a half ride to our tourney Saturday! Gotta get hype]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Good. He needs a rest with All he hast to put up with like NBC news, ABC News, MSNBC news and CNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put them back over the fence so they can Rob, stab, more American tourist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbouie Getting rid of Citizens United and unlimited and secret cash donations would be a really good start toward… https://t.co/wEb26CRk0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristiancrespoj @nikolibertad Deberiamos meter a Maduro y sus soldados en un cuarto y torarles adentro varias lacr… https://t.co/aId04KN2b2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuzakiTheAmazon @jennnufer I am truly sorry for your loss I had to help my own companion dog Scooby go in 2012 and… https://t.co/njxLlBAvqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Today was a very satisfying day” Attorney Michael Avenatti and his client Stormy Daniels played a big role in what… https://t.co/HL8e11W6je]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to 11 year olds talk about how their boyfriends were being “big jerks” for talking to other girls on Vale… https://t.co/LHVWnT3uSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also the AAC &gt; Big East in 2018-19 from top to bottom and it's not close. #Big5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dw4ua We’re all Birminghamians now. Lol. #ForgeOn Doing well. Hope it’s good with you back in H-town.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last minute trip to the Kings game! @ Staples Center https://t.co/KMz55WeDPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows No, what's remarkable is that all of you -- except for @justinamash -- were intent up assassinating… https://t.co/lszZEGYuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Miami Candidate Vanessa Joseph for City Clerk visiting First Class Enterprise. It was an unforgettable meetin… https://t.co/JzNS12XN0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yassss!!! Alllllll day YASSSSS! This is awesome! @RyanMoodyHCPS your staff rocks! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarnellDaHustla @GrimKim For what it’s worth I imagine I also believe Lil Juicy should be free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of those nights you tell your grandkids about.. too bad I want a dog 🐶  . . . Thanks so much to thebandcamino f… https://t.co/53gd48ojXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I ordered food and didn’t get silverware cool...how am I suppose to eat my food now 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Indeed! God bless you and your family. May he watch over your travels this week and guide your tho… https://t.co/ncj3z6eLSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Stuart, FL? View our latest opening: https://t.co/4HbDMGH6Hn #Accounting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonofbuns @BarrettBrown_ @JonathanLKrohn @AdrianChen I can confirm that possibly sooner is viable 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤷‍♀️😢🤦🏼‍♀️🙌🏻😑💀😢👇🏻 #Truth @ Deer Park, Wisconsin https://t.co/SsdMn4x4Ol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalaikaJabali Wonderful informative &amp; educational article.  Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me tell you something, when I started working @GenworthMI I was new to the #industry and knew nothing about Non… https://t.co/wZ2wYh3G6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexanHealthCare @Envision_Cares @BeckyBP Y’all are in Network with UHC... which is about 30% of the Texas market..… https://t.co/xjrewlpZ92]]></document><document><![CDATA[“your debt is your responsibility” LOL all my ut mutuals liking this still have their parents paying their rent so]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have really been liking my new store- I feel good things coming in the future #0081]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @EasternHS Lady Ramblers on your Championship win today! #PrideofCapitolHill #Ward6school]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes, everything's okay at school! I just pissed myself. - Danny Sexbang]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe @cspanwj Will you promise to leave America if we decide to elect a Socialist Candidate?  You won last time but… https://t.co/EP1frNjfO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Focused on regaining range of motion by stretching and riding my stationary bike. @arizonasuncats]]></document><document><![CDATA[Via Qur'an English https://t.co/Uvmv0o74QF(petition for Earth's inhabitants!!! https://t.co/qdR2CbU18E]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXPERIAN for help is a JOKE PEOPLE!!! I’ve called on different ph#s 3 count them 3 and was NEVER offered a HUMAN BE… https://t.co/Hz9sa3ggrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NPC #NYFW #Pier59Studios #ChinaDay @nyfw @pier59studios @ Pier59 Studios https://t.co/w5SdJNwH79]]></document><document><![CDATA[You kill it, you grill it? New California bill would let drivers legally eat roadkill. https://t.co/K6NSx7YFZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennonDoyle @GilbertLiz I NEEDED that.  Have been toying w the idea of bangs (I have NEVER like myself in bangs) Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets That would be a microcosm iof what’s going on around the country.  Thanks to media outlets such as… https://t.co/PE94K8bS83]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two right lanes remain shut down in Oakland, EB-580 at 98th the crash involving one fatality...updates all morning on @KPIXtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next time you attend Holy Mass, remember you are there with EVERY soul in Heaven also, including our Lord ❤️#Catholic #Lent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just in case anyone was wondering, the best decision I have ever made is joining Greek life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paul,  what about prior Presidents that called for national emergencies?  What if Congress continues not to do anyt… https://t.co/UA5c35hAkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking I don't think it takes much to scare Meghan...In fact, she probably jumps at her own shadow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanYeagerPA @BernieSanders If he was so interested in advancing civil rights why hasn't he done a single thing in… https://t.co/vOVUgsY1KK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@headius @WildMindAles @HellNBlazes Come to Orlando and we'll head down there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelicitySmall1 @sedallas @Glinner @MavenOfMayhem @Martina No. It really isnt limited to psychology. You are woefully misinformed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buses loaded! Leaving for the Austin airport headed to New York! SMHS Rattler Orchestra! https://t.co/w27rXzDIwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grand Prix! Downtown St Pete 🎉🏎🥳 #dtsp #grandprix #racing #courigans @ Saint Petersburg, Florida https://t.co/x9ErKnvwIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing it looks like lost weight from someone is such a confidence booster]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrisracefan1 @DaleJr88FanNate @JLee418 @georgia242011 @ToddTPrice24 @JudyJ31830202 @laura24fan @YouTube… https://t.co/lTCm31DgkX]]></document></documents></author>