<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KOAAGrant @PengoSports Well it says “Lawton” for Oklahoma, so clearly whoever made this list is deranged...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEHaden1 @FatherSciarappa Um No. He is not. Actually adding sex into that equation is the Gnostic view. And the heresy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@growingwisdom chances of getting out of Logan to LAX at 6am Thursday morning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like this picture represents the 5 stages of me watching my last paycheck go to all things @OldDominion 😂 Go… https://t.co/oME7lVKsGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geograpologist @theAAG Met her in Belize recently and read her dissertation. Has just started teaching when 2005 f… https://t.co/tiZgnSu4x3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love our students. I love our school. @LetoHighSchool is a special place! ❤️💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alm siento que 24 horas son muy poquitas para todo lo que tengo y quiero hacer 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thing I looked at my #Twitter feed. I forgot about #DaylightSavingsTime. #timechange #INDIANA https://t.co/Ur5onuz78k]]></document><document><![CDATA[2. ANYONE can get tattoos for ALL kinds of reasons: expression, “I just like it”, memorial, ANYTHING. he acted like… https://t.co/vf5CiWbFNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow White enchanting your timelines!😘 🍎#DisneyPrincess #disney #disneyland #snowwhite #princess #colorpopcosmetics https://t.co/HFYUG7mAYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder why every time I watch a @ReelBearMedia Instagram story, an oreos ad plays right after 🤷‍♀️ #oreo https://t.co/c6nBn2jdVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good times at the @spitshockey game on Family Day!!! #familyday #hockeyfights #ohlhockey @ THE WFCU CENTRE https://t.co/7gKcRuMem7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from healthyaging  -  Friends who work out together, stick together! 😉 It’s #NationalWorkoutBuddyDay. Tag… https://t.co/0y2ZI6DYof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh boy...cohen sueing TRUMP for legal bills! SHOULD keep TRUMP and the boys busy for awhile!  1.9 million dollars!… https://t.co/Y7ICuxJLrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I. This Kardashian-Jenner family drama ⠀A. Involving Tristan and Jordyn ⠀⠀⠀has solidified the following ⠀⠀⠀concepts… https://t.co/81Fkw2BVe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diamonds are nothing when I’m rocking with you Diamonds are nothing when I’m shining with you @beautycon… https://t.co/FVF5ZPmbne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsHlymbicky This article is super practical and full of good info! Excellent for parents/guardians, teachers, caring adults. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume "Ahead of the vote, the bill’s Republican sponsors and outside anti-abortion groups lobbying for its pass… https://t.co/Vk7H0bxDFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland   David Letterman's EXTORTION story https://t.co/8q2Js6dMLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy me tocó ver la despedida de unas niñas y su papá. Ellas viven en Reynosa y él acá en Monterrey. Fue de lo más t… https://t.co/xJPtI7y5Kf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFoongLim @yelmelnobrainer @425suzanne @bamboozlebros @mattkindt Yes we are supper excited to be bringing MIND M… https://t.co/IwUnLy78Ml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrs_ARockstar Do you girl if you've done it before #bb and enjoyed it I'm sure it's done beautifully it's definite… https://t.co/1xapSNvqYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[You tell me you’re not like them, to give you time because all this makes me vulnerable but the more it develops the more fucked you look]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don't like just anybody's grits unless Mesi or my granny makes them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 11 players from the Springdale boys basketball team are dressed down and warming up. A good chunk sitting in t… https://t.co/vv3FmRXMlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I turn on the tv and immediately hear some niggas stole 20 guns. I gotta move out of this city]]></document><document><![CDATA['And I want a moment to be real Wanna touch things I don't feel We want to hold on and feel I belong And how can th… https://t.co/ibJ8DCRDLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheaBrowning https://t.co/WcbY54mnSu  Agreed @SheaBrowning   Brave 3 year old with angel-parents fighting it right… https://t.co/D2qAodnqLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews You are the most disgusting creature ever to walk this earth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@czech1_2_3 @FOX9 Kids, yes they are great at stealing kids for profit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[First two weeks at new gig and I accomplished quite a lot. Besides banging out some code, I got to participate in s… https://t.co/XlrQXQOnxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister tells my nephew she can’t buy him Jordan’s and expensive sneakers anymore . Nephew : it’s okay mommy TITI buy them for me anyway 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmdesoer But do you love your 10,000th follower more than you love me???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had a dream where I had been replaced as Quatermaster’s voice by Danny DeVito. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#computationalthinking activity in @WVEBeagles PreK class! @SBISDEdTech @BeckyHagan1 @mahabirs1 https://t.co/79YbYFrxFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNWomensRights I believe that all women come together and demand global changes involving rape. Why is there a sta… https://t.co/h7Ocpbcqgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just saw a video of people repeating holes and shit with ramen and i don’t think i’ll ever be the same]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kushner is in Turkey and going to Saudi Arabia next. Nothing to see here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the kids I babysit started crying cause he just wanted to cuddle with somebody I-]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao omg mia is watching nailed it and I just love her so much because she does @nicolebyer voice and it's just amazing. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally dream of being old and having my own house with lots of dogs and snakes and a sphynx cat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magicandrew @NickPacilio @AOC @BillNye @JordanPeele https://t.co/9otmAnB5yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RitaZonius @MingHinCuisine @IABC @IABCChicago @paulfuriga @susanda @SueBooth5 @AMKrzmarzick @cjmayse @BethLegateGR… https://t.co/6JCKzHlD2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just made a friend at the airport because of my @OutdoorVoices leggings 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[The whole “you don’t know what you got till it’s gone” bullshit, no you know what you got when you have it, you just miss it once it’s gone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grow_Supplies https://t.co/EgNcJi8VCh $750 for 5 plants.  TO medical patients.  Wat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aUSAFVeteran @BostonJimmy67 @realDonaldTrump You can dish but you cant take it!! Typical #eyeroll #boybye your tim… https://t.co/GTMxbbeAs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gotmel_1 @antione_harris 1. I was sick with jaundice 2. delete this before god sees it and sends me to hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine That is actually funny that they say not to run. It means they know Trump will win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Collazo474 @karenslinn43 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @ClockworkHamma @Iluvinspireu @MyEngland2016 @FRISEEMYRIAM @Jimmysimmonds1… https://t.co/4ovX2AihY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day for @OdessaCollege #baseball. We are @utpb come watch! #njcaa https://t.co/CvJpIKuvPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sophomore year of high school vs. sophomore year of college. 💚💛 @JordanHasay https://t.co/ccswHAnLsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[First official snow day of 2019 for @TheHiveInCC #snowday #bringonspring]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know I never understood when you love a guy sm and give them your all they’re assholes to you but when the shit… https://t.co/uRJv2KtyJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sweat don’t understand how some people can be in relationships &amp; fight all the damn fucken time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish to be completely feminized including male to female transgender surgery! That is what I always wanted! The d… https://t.co/hoToiTBD5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[She doing her shit and this was my fav performance. Cause she wasn’t twerking or none of that. Nice choreographed d… https://t.co/yByH2NSJLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAIT WHAT? Lol here we go.. I’m already exhausted 😩 @Humasound fill me in on what is real here ty love! X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatsVeryKari @Starofthesea007 @FionaMorgan79 @ccatmpt @Dracaenawines @simplysallyh @GailBenzler @CaththeWineLady… https://t.co/V7ikMJnv6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen ♥️ #maulmayhem #becauselife #thisissome #tatscoffeevacay @ Eldersburg, Maryland https://t.co/JpS967ghWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaronNefcy Is it me or is baby hainious adorable!! https://t.co/PrqFR2ev6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[The comments from these so called "celebrities " are beyond disgraceful, but sadly also predictable! It shows clear… https://t.co/K4cS8wPYHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[u ever get so high u sit and stare at something, like a blank wall and then when u come to you’re eating animal cra… https://t.co/6X13OTAjA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sugarwits We don’t exorcise our demons.. we find out what kind of beer they drink and invite them to a crawfish boil. #frienemies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapehartJ Don’t hold your breath to hear anything from him, Hannity, Ingush, Carlson, Nielsen, Pence, Pompeo, Grah… https://t.co/eXCXhhYzs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertfr69 @Mivasair @SpeakerPelosi @splcenter @MazMHussain They've been absolutely awful to her and her life is b… https://t.co/rGzsQpyuLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soar high  . . .  #disney #disneyig #disneygram #disneylife #disneynerd #disneylove #disneyfollow #instadisney… https://t.co/skhTzRpjqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sr71538 This is awesome....we need many resources to help with homelessness. Its such a large problem that needs f… https://t.co/HWeTRBMcyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[At an alarming Rate I have been asked the question “ How you going to go about getting rid of all the excess skin a… https://t.co/Tb4HM3ScSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @scientistTonya for spending your day with #3rdgrade We loved hanging out in the #starlab with you!… https://t.co/6LdghmAwtx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carrieunderwood how are you out here belting and in heels while so many months pregnant and not out of breath? I c… https://t.co/Wj8QGATlIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, @JSloanRISD for the recommendation! #RISDconnects https://t.co/9pB37elaE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dermot Kennedy said ‘what if the love you deserve is the love you never find’ and i have not been whole since]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump Our Country is at the lowest it’s been since the Civil War. The division speed by… https://t.co/VSAyPzDiQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to get better at something you can’t be the smartest person in the room. Seek out those who show eviden… https://t.co/VtojjF8Eq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scyian @Megan__Cutler @DKTaylorLane @jennyrglover @winter_cecily I love arguments in writing, too! Especially when… https://t.co/Hr8M2VY1mV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I completely agree. I am fortunate enough to be able to rematch the series. I was a mere child when this iconic sho… https://t.co/iYcRm4LpoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The relational context from which #Jesus gives us commands has changed. Commands now come from a place of love, pos… https://t.co/Y0V0gFLNVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t tanned since high school. However, I nonetheless chose to tan as I have run out of all other options at being hot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasChance @USMCTexian Oh, thank the heavens. I’d have to call Character Flaw on that one 😉 https://t.co/kOuEfc4yg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[If i didn’t have a child I would be a flight attendant. My girl has been doing it for years now. And I’m jelly af]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Stay Alive by @_josegonzalez_ on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/881w3f0IIb https://t.co/RMmXWCc6Bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days I wish for pitch black silence. Other days I just wish for a shaded area. Both days I just hoping to cover something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's some over-quoted, over-hipster-designed things in this list... but there are also some great pieces of...… https://t.co/4Y5atmhSec]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students of any level will enjoy the challenge of chess at the STEM exCEL Chess Club! Students will learn the rules… https://t.co/SMh6qXZ9MW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if the kids who faced Feinstein about climate change, realize they will no longer eat hamburgers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Competing views are one thing but blocking qualified appointments is dirty politics.  What in heaven’s name is wron… https://t.co/89ckHYpOBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I open to find this DVD, twin of the very same copy I received this evening. As I was carrying it up the stairs thi… https://t.co/TSC4TZAmIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Están platicando la mamá de Mateo con la mamá de Valentina. Hablan de la mamá de Regina y del papá de Maximiliano.… https://t.co/cqg9JaOaX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[These little babies at their first @the1975 concert in Brighton in 2015 didn’t know it yet but in the year 2019 the… https://t.co/YsnjEumnDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeeMiaRoll @michaelsafyan I love that. As a blind person I too am tired of being inspiration porn. I’m abducting t… https://t.co/5PKMOHViKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAvaArmstrong When all groups Democrats proclaim to protect are caught in the ugliness thats rampant from their P… https://t.co/AdkFMrAx6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched a guy go into the bathroom then turn around to look at the sign to make sure he was walking into the men’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day! I’m currently debating which single from my album to drop next. Which song of mine… https://t.co/Uxnu3gxAOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me at 32 being the young hot cool mom when Haleem is a high school freshman while everyone else’s mom looks like a… https://t.co/Nj98JmwwT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith kevin, my all time favorite smodcast is when you guys analyzed the book of pooh’s outro. here’s to… https://t.co/mlZOSQrxEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Whole Foods Market - @wholefoodscincy in Cincinnati, OH https://t.co/qiNU3rSCyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Mexico state legislators don't represent US. The new governor promised recreational https://t.co/LRQ2ktaY4x Col… https://t.co/rWz8ihj0ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments This is a crap bill and everyone knows it.  If I was the President I would never sign this bill. Ev… https://t.co/O0dBgcnyUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you had never had a meaningful relationship with another human and it shows. All jokes and personal feeling… https://t.co/GzLeAoKCTR]]></document></documents></author>