<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@nbvenom @alegvilla1 @tumbaburross Es que sus mentes ya no les da para más , por eso dejaron un pinche cochinero, y… https://t.co/Eq1EtHgOQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all be talking that positive shit online but be toxic as fuck in person]]></document><document><![CDATA[She hit the gas and baby, I don't wanna ride slow Haul ass, it's me and you all weekend long]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just some of the local heroes from the Ellerslie Volunteer Fire Department in Harris County, GA.  You are truly ama… https://t.co/zYIYBunbQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamTommyInLA I was afraid to say Wienerschnitzel but yes!! You are sleeping on Del Taco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraJayXXX I need some pussy and or a blowjob tonight I'm horny and my dick reminds me of a tree limb always hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie’s trying to be nice and let Colton down easy and the dude was beggggging for her to love him back.  Hate to see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk can you pls send some “Not a Flamethrower”s to Nebraska. they forgot how to plow the streets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blueeyedbuddha @danielworkman Fair enough, but then why are they going out of their way to NOT mention college soccer on the website?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh I think you did an excellent job of highlighting why its use would be appropriate. Thank you.I think you… https://t.co/LiME2hofxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will Chicago State reach 10 by halftime? Stay tuned 🤔 #WACtion https://t.co/wcgEErfWWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SGottliebFDA If I am correct the use of opioids to effectively  reduce the severity of chronic, severe pain has be… https://t.co/ZhEMkc5NJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just love this pic ❤ The old pics on the visuals were a treat! #RobbieLive #RobbieWilliams #LiveinLasVegas… https://t.co/P1OrpJxwfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz #DiaInternacionalDeLaMujer @erifontana @AguCasanova @Pilarsmith https://t.co/KiqyggBceB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drewmorrisUK @TheHooksta @Buccaneers @NathanHuff_ Big time!   Congrats man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steam_games @madrugaworks Can you guys please put rust on sale like please I really want to play it but just pleas… https://t.co/DFoT368rFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr No commits about a Coast Guard Officer blotting a terrorist attack but you found a story about an i… https://t.co/cssjRxpjKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is really pathetic is that there are always people who are in an audience who are actually more historically i… https://t.co/OjFBwMyPw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Octavia Spencer is a terror in the MA movie trailer  https://t.co/c5GJBIxVlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AristeguiOnline @JanaPalacios con tanto "ingreso extra" que hay por ahí quien en su sano juicio renunciaría a un puesto de gobierno .. ja]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm pretty positive about everything going on here. This is some visionary stuff for a lower league club in the US.… https://t.co/bqcEEj97kZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrlandotheCooke @MadeleinaKay @manbearpig9282 @nickylep @WeNeedEU Well, you just made my point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sjm23_ @Guti_O9 Mine last me all day at work lol I work 8-9 hours a day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jhonata76190805 @diegosaviola10 @DptesSinTapujos Ser Visceral es facil. NO es acerca de una Nacionalidad, es de un… https://t.co/9Qgec4VSSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliawb St. Louis. But I spent a long time in Athens so it’s not entirely new.  Tallahassee is tiny so I really li… https://t.co/GHuLx3WMql]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rebranding is everything 🥂✨✍🏾 #menswearblogger #menswear https://t.co/Iy1HBglNkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GePeirson @CBCNews Oh that's fair I just wanted to build on that and make it a double whammy, even if clumsily]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully Deionte Thompson drops to the 2nd round so the Cowboys can steal him]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Tuff rides those 8 seconds for Lane. 😢 I’m not crying you’re crying! #8Seconds]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/14/19 number 109 Aftermath by The Rolling Stones. Came for Paint it Black stayed for the angsty loneliness vibe. Thanks Mick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachGelb What's up Zach! I just saw a report that is not getting a lot of attention in the media when it should, b… https://t.co/OWKrlpk6xN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashley_malizia That’s what happens when u don’t get them from the plug🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started watching #UmbrellaAcademy on @Netflix and it might be the closest we'll ever get to Wes Anderson doing supe… https://t.co/eeB5DFyVG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HtOwNzOuTLaW713 @big_john819 @NombreEsJustin @lyssah_a @alegriselle Kevin right after the game ends https://t.co/9zRGNSi9tb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex_segura I think this might have been the first time I read a comic and realized it was well written. https://t.co/0aJtTlkIT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omar, whose father was a Marxist should know a little something about dictatorships.@Ilhan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should just change my name to LMFAOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO so i only have to rt shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[File suit for slander. 1st Amendment Rights come with a responsibility.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CDuts98 @Sue_Hylland @uOttawaGeeGees @The_Fulcrum FYI, I think you are forgetting the @geegees_mgolf OUA Champions… https://t.co/JRsTAFJPBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuesta pero hay que seguir, #mondaymood Y Seguiré hasta que las cosas sucedan, Quien esta conmigo?...👇🏽 @ North Mia… https://t.co/bbGwzmJM4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[True growth comes when your decisions are based on multiple point of views and not just the one that benefits you at the time....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBNNews @ChickfilA @12s @zumiez @AutZone @BernieSanders The campaign is voluntary. The #SandersWilson2020 campaign… https://t.co/l57fuelsut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allidoisowen @jaredlholt @shtpostpodcast Did he book and cancel on you Owen???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking : Trump to roll out “Party Night” for the evening before New Years Day !!! Says it will be to celebrate th… https://t.co/QUFRWZEkWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ERAZNOYLACHOKO Simon keremos otra temporada de mi madrina la choko porke es bien ponedora aber si pala otra tempor… https://t.co/n3cTeeelGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustJeremyHeyYo @Ox1073 @MissLovebat @RingFalcon @Walk_With_Elias @Fireboy987 @LoganMeador99 @TheBarryPotter… https://t.co/ftnJZHY5II]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn’t post your entire trip to Vegas, did you even fucking go? #WhatHappensInVegas #EndsUpOnSocialMedia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmywagz353 @buffaloves @Bulldogwgr This is true and I wouldn’t even say completion percentage. I’ve seen both of… https://t.co/YFtvYnsfoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big Home Weekend ahead for @XavierWBB Providence tomorrow  on National 📺 and Creighton on Sunday w/ @kwf_kwf for ou… https://t.co/LN6N8ukCe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiChargerz Full form lol. Man. Save the money, give it time to get good with claw and you'll be gold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Breaking News:    No jail for teen accused of torching a caged cat. Judge orders community service instead     Via… https://t.co/r4GGIfLUd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone know where I can find jeans that will actually fit my waist/length??? I always have to buy 30-32 and th… https://t.co/FfhR7erhv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t deal with problematic train conductors this morning. @SEPTA @SEPTA_WTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maasyy i hadn’t done one with them, but booker is really fun to use and i bet ayton is pretty raw]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/XjD1rwL5em]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my assistant w me today. @ Ulman Foundation https://t.co/bHx22DR431]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eriklutz And Science can not “prove” anything...  but it can provide evidence.  I am living proof.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These fucken Peace's of fucken shit forged over government documents which is a capital crime it violates everythin… https://t.co/BWfnls9XAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for Bernie in the 2016 Dem primary and HRC in the general. I won’t be voting for Bernie in the 2020 primary… https://t.co/KyXAR2l4dA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The spliff I’m gonna roll when I get home....lmao https://t.co/CDEbLoi8Tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[NCAA baseball - Schroeder Park  End 3 Rice          3  6  1 Houston  2  2   0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFMarrufo Vini en 2 temporadas va a acabar en la Real Sociedad o algo así]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PittsburghInsid Raiders are most realistic. Can’t even imagine the Broncos doing this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorfolkKnights Kids need to realize that “waiting for a [next level] offer” means you’re likely a backup plan for… https://t.co/M2zVosGroU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to thank my visionary leader @rhowardbrowne for the ability to breathe air &amp; get dressed this morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught in the Snow * * * * * f/4.5 || 1/250s || ISO 400 || 51mm #sonya7ii #sonymirrorless #thisisnewyorkcity… https://t.co/HUF41Q86lH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Honda Just bought a Modern Steel EX-L from the awesome sales team at @IndyPenskeHonda  Oh, and a #Ridgeline too. T… https://t.co/DCYxRYNy4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HCaballero @DuilioDavino Ó Carlos González de Pumas (traído por Necaxa). Al parecer en Aguascalientes sí hay buena inteligencia deportiva.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Seven Saddles by Grove Roots Brewing Company at @red_door_wine — https://t.co/1doqn2dMv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @rhsmrsapplegate to post my favorite books for 7 days. Each day I’ll challenge others! Day… https://t.co/2D87DW1TkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[alright, you millennials who have never taken econ in high school or  know this is economically NOT FEASIBLE at all… https://t.co/TUy6e5ksXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andrew Hamilton let me on your podcast I’ve been doing some groundbreaking research on how B.O.F.A. movements in Lo… https://t.co/7RdTgz5cJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimeJumper319 @shwood @NightAttackShow @JustinRYoung @brycas Is he standing on his chair yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travisakers #SaveDemocracy  Now is the time....... https://t.co/vHxrTn5aSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard @PALucier If sixteen is old enough to vote, as the #libtards would have think, then it should be old en… https://t.co/JVVaczG4HN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsbyarshistory @CNUSD I appreciate your insight and spending time to help us. https://t.co/DJgHSBTou2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afreedma The "Doomsday Glacier"... gotta love climate scientists, so academic and unemotional.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thing we're getting the real criminals off the streets...... Wtf bro....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump What do you think the Republicans did for the past 10 years...Benghazi, Emails, IRS bias… https://t.co/1zNdLrNEB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make your smile change the world, don't let the world change your smile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I need to account for in NYC vs things I can barely keep track of in the bay area in the winter:  Bay area:… https://t.co/PNx34FrQHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Chicago! :) #Sunrise 07:11, noon 13:01, sunset 18:51 CDT (UTC-5), March 10. Day length: 11h 40m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this is key. She made her decision but was still open? This needs more questions. Which was it? A closed decisio… https://t.co/ztQC5Mz4eo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s missing a comma and an exclamation point but I am 100% on board with the excitement and emphasis. Herbs, baby!… https://t.co/tjYknfK2Mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaylyTVOficial1 @BaylyTVOficial1   Vergonzosa la actitud de Jaime Bayly.  No tiene el derecho a insultar a un Vene… https://t.co/joU36HTMFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[El perdón de Dios es asombroso. «Seremos saciados del bien» estando en Su presencia. Él te da «esperanza» y «alegría»]]></document><document><![CDATA[20 years ago I helped lead 30 Days of Prayer for Canada with leaders like J.I. Packer, Christine MacMillan, Father… https://t.co/fbK5rTQDTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribebrowns @jrock521 @jeffhalaparda @JOEish94 They should try going the rookie QB route next....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhobicCarrot No I have the station but since I’m technically out of the market I don’t get the games instead it’s… https://t.co/WQRSq6fCWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LyAHandmade @C104Weaver @Country104 @HunterBros @jamesbarkerband @MacKenziePMusic @jojomasonmusic @DaveHartney… https://t.co/2h4gHFRcaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xaenie @GarrettRWang @AronEisenberg Hell, LaForge was promoted 3 times in 7 years.  Lt jg, Lt, and Lt. Commander.  Sorry Harry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday  #janetjackson  #icon @ Indianapolis, Indiana https://t.co/3HX3vaSE5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new Basquiat exhibit at The Brant Foundation was wild. Apparently there’s a piece on the 1st floor (not shown h… https://t.co/1ieaLF7VR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[George Navarro three no good, John Smith offensive rebound, timeout Hoopa Valley. Warriors down one, 9.3 left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the honor of co-producing and playing on TRILON - a time traveling record with @michaelshrieve and a bunch of… https://t.co/qgBBzxEvE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drug Pricing | Patriot Act with Hasan Minhaj | Netflix https://t.co/tZ96hzcBHb via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bringing Heilsgeschichte back.  We need an English equivalent.   That’s all.   #Saturdaymusings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I got an 87 on my bio exam??? YO. I’m gonna FUCKING cruise to an A. LETS GO]]></document><document><![CDATA[So that is hilarious to me because this super nice woman at @Delta was ordered to basically try to scam me out of $… https://t.co/MWcmbDBobV]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Final Tn Flight High School Tryout is 2-5pm today March 10th at MTCS in Murfreesboro.   *Fielding 7 high school te… https://t.co/T5pBKBAEgT]]></document></documents></author>