<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Fanny. Vintage Dior #celestialblue #jadoredior #hautecouture #vintage #50sfashion #gown #vivanteline #christiandior… https://t.co/gtj4Y23qv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethFratesMD @Havenlust Awesome Thursday morning @BethFratesMD @Havenlust     👠👠☕️☕️🕊🌻🌎🎼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else get in this mood where you just wanna go out and buy a bunch of shoes??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanbpeterson She’s a one of those select feminists that is not open minded and thinks she is right about all th… https://t.co/clGPfFs7xR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg this song! Im literally shook rn  #ColdInLA https://t.co/on6mg9L2i6]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are kicking off March with our new Gratitude Campaign! We have teamed up with Lily’s Place located in Huntington… https://t.co/blDlMSjMRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Eleanor and her bf came to see me yesterday on our Opening Day of business. ❤️ Thankful she's in my life and alw… https://t.co/9KwXDrkmUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big scoop, a gun can fire if you pull the trigger, not just any gun a Glock. 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 Damn libtards]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofyoule Hier encore j'avais oublié de te payer esti Jamais vu ça va faire un peu de ménage dans la vie   😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TereOrt51687394 @mali_kervannn @mich_onelove @Viviane6677 @Alcioni5 @gabryluce @roberta_lanzoni @evakoosiglesias… https://t.co/Ps0HZLNHmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahum;  better check this out. #andsoitcontinues #ARMORUP Patriots; Be aware; Wolves dressing as sheep are everywher… https://t.co/S4aWFToroo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dana4bama @tidalwave7705 Yes, now I can't argue that, plus it's a better tourist spot....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valley St. Patrick's Day parade steps off next Sunday | https://t.co/Essx9guqiz https://t.co/fUcdpZukgs via @twitterapi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Don’t worry.  Saving the world NEVER involves adults.” -CRYPTID KEEPER #MGLIT by @LijaFisher (@MacKidsBooks)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eathbound420 @DetroitLove88 @Twitter @TwitterSupport @TwitterDev @jack @ReneeLibby2 @SavaAnderson94 @AstridWinegar… https://t.co/SaTgfWBcAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump-Kim summit was cut short after North Korea demanded end of sanctions, Trump says - https://t.co/jZAyY6j8UB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can watch this 9,000 times. 🤣 #SchittsCreek #foldinthecheese https://t.co/Z3yDxT0Vza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning meeting location #ilovemyclients working on destination wedding article❤️❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/marI3vQWFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onelastkick71 That is so weird. It sounds like a blood clot. But I assume they have done a doppler ultrasound]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayharrington3 great episode last night! Deacon has a new baby girl. ❤ what a great episode! 💓❣💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Otto was returned abused and this  dictator who has had his own family members killed states he didn’t know an… https://t.co/ITAIUIn20S]]></document><document><![CDATA[*dining at hooters*  Nobody:  My best friend who breast feeds: I wish someone would tell me some shit about breast feeding here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epoch_awakening @notch Can’t wait. It’s been a lonely 17 months. Pretty much everyone I know thinks I’ve gone crazy. 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlanetTyrus @CoryBooker That’s so big of you Tyrus (ha ha).  I’m going to go ahead and judge him enough for both o… https://t.co/h8voO99TVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is #DonaldTrump so obsessed with the media? The #TimApple thing was funny and just a slip of the tongue but now… https://t.co/nsoPEcpXck]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 100+ year-old brick rowhome is about to blow over. That’s some mighty wind wolf out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about Bernie Sanders becoming a real Democrat and maybe he’ll have the whole Democratic machine behind him. So… https://t.co/9j3VIUs9Ea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't we have a copy of Obama's order to then UK Foreign Secy Boris Johnson...ordering FiveEyes "allies" to wiretap… https://t.co/hxM1ClsuoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@virtualpenny Hey there rock star, I see you out there, making a name foe yourself and increasing your influence 🤜🤛 #swayfactor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewartHaasRcng @ColeCuster @Jacob_Companies Almost!! Heard Kev n Jimmie....good job]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOLD! Bright and Sunny Unit with Skylights  If you want to make the best move of your life, let us work for you!… https://t.co/3l4h5JWgT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pdazzleliscious I did..I'm at my limit .but some days it goes down. I hate to drop people. Seems like their my friend🌏✌💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Beep beep.  Tooting my own horn again.  You're a conman and a cheat and this makes you look foolish and desperate.  Sad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning’s beautiful sunrise over the PNW. #pugetsound #olympia https://t.co/6N4uUR5o9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[R.Kelly has finally been indicted.   Thank you to all those who helped to make this happen.   I stand with all surv… https://t.co/ugt7AQ4q41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaviota330 Poor boy!  He’s so gorgeous!  PLEASE HELP HIM NOW &amp; SHOW HIM WHAT LOVE IS, PLEASE💔🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[A forever bop! 💖  #Repost 70s.80s.90s_music • • • • • • Level 42 - Lessons In Love  Lessons in Love is a single fro… https://t.co/RNZAsKOodA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Over 3000 people died in Puerto Rico due to the slow response by the Trump administration after the hurricane last year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandsmartin @essencefest Still trying to glorify himself. https://t.co/RYtM0iLC8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[At q and a at hammer theatre for Joe All Alone @ Hammer Theatre Center https://t.co/yL3a32K9Ql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaPustorino @SonjaNi41294318 @AGuirado5 @queenandadream @DanielaSantannn @danielalippke @MBryant122 @JuliK317… https://t.co/1yaapMWowP]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Bowdoin College student was taken to a Portland hospital with second-and third-degree burns following an early mo… https://t.co/PMJyHZr5aT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come join me at 10AM EST!!! I am going to (try to, lol) describe the mentality and shift into this 5D reality. I ha… https://t.co/HycJF8LlTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ready for this year??? @kelsieeeeeeee @AliBueche @trevorlandry22 https://t.co/MJA7jDjpYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyRainbow You should offer Master Classes on “Throwing Shade” and “The Art of Snark”.  💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game day ALERT to all parents and/or anyone else you may know who is arrending the game tonight at Veterans Memoria… https://t.co/FUnMqjXDIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the wilds of #QueensNewYork 2 see my @theshakesforum buddy @tylerjmoss kill it as #CyranoDeBergerac, oh an… https://t.co/mUGVZhZu9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DDJOY4TRUMP We think alike &amp; must follow each other !! I've got you !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Feminism isn’t about making women stronger—women are already strong. It’s about changing the way the world perceiv… https://t.co/YkFmH4LXE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberBarbe omg that reminded me of when we were on our way home from the mall of louisiana one time and we were bl… https://t.co/Kg0E97ZdWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebJHull @HonkyTonkJew Ur worst is somebody else’s Best-right now!  I love this dynamic w science &amp; humans - do u?  $bayry $bhc $hlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neillmal1 @steph93065 @realDonaldTrump No they aren’t mean they are smack out liars!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@candikahne @charliekirk11 Me too, I can't even get my own family to listen to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamRomany Watching now... a few hours late. 5 minutes in and you've got me bawlin! #AMillionLittleThings #bestshowever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__SoulFlower nah sis.... detangling and wash day alone is a chore. Buying products to make your hair manageable ca… https://t.co/mZez8R5IFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie: *trying to break up as nicely as humanly possible*   Colton: I’m not going to stop fighting for you, even i… https://t.co/HfpMh7WwNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thom3700 Lots of Harper merch, but no Harper. I also haven’t been looking that hard!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GilbertReyna4 @OscarBorderTeam @MLealTX @KENS5 @AdiGTV Yes please. Is there any way you can mail some this way?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zuccarello36 #NYR Heart, hustle and soul. You are so missed. Heal up and hear us cheer as you lift the Cup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @WDWToday with the marathon happening this weekend, will MK be as bad as it was on Saturday? It’s our last day… https://t.co/bMmxRiGOcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Via amandaumek Sin palabras ! en Broward County, Florida https://t.co/uEa35MPlwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedapperdiner @UPS Oh man! I think I just heard the door slam and a big truck drive away! Fingers crossed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Clayton #CA  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/ilxp9pD8xq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that i have no one to argue with, my life is getting kind of boring 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another Saturday night in beautiful #ogunquit ⛄️ https://t.co/e3Ugc1OIsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[KD ain’t come to compete at all tonight he trickingthe game off for his future teammate Kyrie I need this nigga off my team man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once when my then-high school aged sister was refilling a man’s water he grabbed her arm and pretended to cut it of… https://t.co/lftzb29lW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in too careless of a mood and these beers aren’t helping take my phone before I say some dumb shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[We do not want her here. She made her beds, three, i think, let her lie in them. She gave up her rights wben she jo… https://t.co/jzSNKbLQdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillJPoe I could, but she doesn't look like she's going to be much fun...]]></document><document><![CDATA[How weird, I had a dream about her last night, and today, she liked three of my pictures. Haven’t talked to her sin… https://t.co/ZvY6KaDsUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlliniWGym @BigTenNetwork Is it on TV @BigTenNetwork? I only see the replay tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blown away once again by James Bay. Absolute talent. #Jamesbay #electriclight #concert #themetphilly @ The Met Phil… https://t.co/ojAzDu9OIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a show for you… Larry's Loungecast  am listen to this right now @lorenzabraham12 @McJuggerNuggets… https://t.co/h5uRhOsrnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re dancing all night with morningstardj CLSQ ‍ Chapel https://t.co/9brqDvhc14 https://t.co/M6m7WtylHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Therefore, behold, the days are coming, declares the LORD, when I shall send to him pourers who will pour him, and… https://t.co/xCOj3snMZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 Okay listen @norvina1 I’m a baby mua but I love ABH and makeup so much. Even if you just got some tips fo… https://t.co/hsRa5TNPGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad asked me if he could sell my car just because he wanted to put an add on Facebook that says:  “I’m selling my daughters soul”]]></document><document><![CDATA[NIH apologizes for its failure to address sexual harassment in science https://t.co/645jsj8IAt via @statnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darryl_parish @aaronLebeahm Of course! Haha not as good as the first one of course, but I still liked it for what it was.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“i can help whosever next” is not grammatically correct and it makes me SO MAD when anyone says it omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomBrinkmeyer @fox32news Well, you did ask for more education. Happy Valentine’s Day. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSAWWeather What are the records for snow on the ground in Wausau. I’ve been looking on the internet but I’m not finding anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a big day! Excited to continue my soccer career at Bryan college!🦁❤️⚽️💛 https://t.co/RDKOV5sRX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@dbusiness Thank you for covering the Judson Center Family Health Clinic Ribbon Cutting.  @MedNetOne is so proud t… https://t.co/sM3nfDBUUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoodandTravelMX @MusorSonora @YeeAurora @VisitSonora Que estimulante su apoyo para promover @MusorSonora y que las… https://t.co/KX4Ve7lc7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylanmsmitty He gives humans a bad name, which is quite a feat, since, Earth itself could do without us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m literally only a couple assignments away from being done with school yet my motivation is at its lowest🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roxyroller99 @hicusick I thought of Abby in that scene too - from season 1.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like the cemetery there and then gone and back again in what seemed like moments]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Montanablowhard Was it the dude who gave you a good review, because then you’d have to do them a solid. 😂🤔🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much awe and respect for #JodyWilsonRaybould for speaking truth to power. ✊🏽#cdnpoli #JWR #SNCLavelin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouiseMensch Buuutttt... CNN, MSNBC, MSM all report using illegally leaked info via illegal anonymous sources and… https://t.co/U62GGX1Fop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FinnBalor appreciation tweet cuz wow he’s amazing https://t.co/MepN9sz2lt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you Stan Adam Lambert PLEASE follow me!!! I need more glamberts in my timeline ✨👑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goldenteach Thank you! @e_mcguire_ nailed it with this cover. GORGEOUS. I love it so much too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup but they were trying to be a stunt queen so I just cancelled the whole relationship]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te interesa trabajar para reducir la brecha de género en LATAM? Tienes experiencia en investigación y en desarrollo… https://t.co/8NvQOD0MAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 YET, how many real Americans read or heard that! Re: state run media]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fadwaaaziz @KSpringsLions THANK YOU!  I was hoping you would see it.  ❤️]]></document></documents></author>