<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@VinceMcMahon vice wish .com sell your see stuff on there so better get stuff wweshop or wish]]></document><document><![CDATA[struttin’ it at the 91st Academy Awards 🤩 . . . . #oscars2019 @ The Oscars https://t.co/oaNS87AXUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm seeing that also that's why I've actually been just not giving them credit for making a mockery of the USA also]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DishinDays yea but I make a point of not reading that stuff because I dont wanna know. I dont want to stop listening to u guys too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ron_fournier This Jewish atheist can’t wait! Presents! Gifts!   Will there be cookies as well?]]></document><document><![CDATA[the “throwing cheese on people and animals” trend needs to stop im about to delete twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna say that if you’re my friend and you saw my tweet earlier and actually checked to see everything was o… https://t.co/2tk2kIpwgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Just_Say_Snow @Softykjr I don’t know about you but I want to see wins! https://t.co/CQPLOgIfHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que estas imágenes siempre estén en los recuerdos de los HDP que tienen secuestrada al país.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could actually smell how clean my sheets are because I love my detergent but my nose is not working anymore☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eileencostello Awww thank you!! I'm looking forward to drawing him more 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgetBAdkins @LambertHS Ooooh no, do you by chance have the lab you’d be willing to share?  I love that idea!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zigmund_Fraud @SueQuez @jkellyca @badzoot7 @doritmi @BarbaraMcK42 @EmmaGPaley @boglethemind @Rosewind2007… https://t.co/t9aPhBEdoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now this girl from Ohio is using me, a Kentuckian, for proving her credibility as being someone from a place full of illegal exotic animals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks. I've been a vegetarian/vegan since 1986 and have used protein powder for weight loss and vitamin fortificat… https://t.co/DAqyo4Hwq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Self reminder: I will not allow my self harm scars determine what I wear this Spring/Summer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFis87569576 @CarolVernon7 @IlhanMN @AOC @JoeBiden @dccc @TheDemCoalition Because they’re a freaking #cult]]></document><document><![CDATA[No sir! The NYT is a well respected newspaper with an immense body of work. On the other hand, you are a hack, a co… https://t.co/YHmB1Wjm8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mornin  #bodsquad check in @holidayspecial @roadhouse1176 @StacyShadows @bcbwinchester @nekkidblaze @bcbwifey… https://t.co/WoJxZlkeEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanStevey1 @PardesSeleh @TulsiGabbard Umm. She was for getting proof, not for getting a hard on for taking ou… https://t.co/EOZnWCadiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brrrrr 😳 #SeriouslyLovinThisWeather @ Valencia, Santa Clarita, California https://t.co/XoHunS6NgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the best thing I saw all day.   @andyojones I know it’s raining, and we’re delicate Californians now, but c… https://t.co/4e28aSn1oP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @BetoORourke Sen Graham, shouldn’t the money be spent on the highest and best uses?  Like maybe re… https://t.co/rjce7nHEqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Tyler Dill. I don't even know how to describe what he just did but it looked impossible. He puts Narragansett… https://t.co/8knUc4O9LR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland These.  Carol Feeley recommended these and I plan on adding these to my diet. https://t.co/Ycd0ewFQYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LPWhitt @ItsMeSveta88 @RepMaxineWaters Deutsche Bank and cooperating? @realDonaldTrump is probably crapping his pants. ✌🏻💙🌊🇺🇸👩‍🦰]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother 🙄🙄🙄 have me walking around the neighborhood during a damn hurricane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToutouleNtoya @SueThotz @MsFarinas #TruTalkEdu https://t.co/Jlx1e9WuA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[which are the initial basis for the growth of capital from trade, have a very long history. The "capitalistic era"… https://t.co/Rnr4QgzikJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi @indayevarona, I read your article. On Thursday at @AJStream, we discuss the case against @MariaRessa. Could you… https://t.co/05eO9TVTzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweetness 💙 #blueprintphotographystudio #bppclients #bppfamilies #maternity #babybump #maternityphotography @ Blue… https://t.co/x0YNCUjBYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lucky Strike - @luckystrikwdc in Washington, DC https://t.co/kgeEu9RM5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Butterfly_3376 @sharon25lb @livilouboo @boxycharm @ipsy I had 3 ppl dm on Instagram1fell thru she went w/someone e… https://t.co/eobGS2hnzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[One strawberry at a time... order yours today! #lips #redlips #strawberry #chocolate #chocolatier #chocolatelover… https://t.co/tKYiVQUbH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting on my girl Liza to have a margarita with me https://t.co/q1aCq7Tl3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinterJolt @SuperGerbil @ComicBookNOW No, not a better choice....it's very rare for movie to change characters and… https://t.co/MTygScMnKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wheels631 @Josh_Macri @Buster_ESPN @dschoenfield @esotericeric0 Those were players in my youth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[By my friend @shemaiahng Ash Wednesday: A Holy Day I Yearn For. https://t.co/0qMxjnojuV. 📸 @corpuschristipp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WNEMTV5news Who would do that too a poor defenseless animal. I hope they are caught and put in prison for a very very long time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop laughing omg 😭😂@cassmarielang @ebzaharia https://t.co/YCZFI9vETS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy with a good skate #figureskating #adultfigureskating with a silver in my interpretive. First competition in a… https://t.co/rJR8GuFIQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marycmccormack @JoshMalina @Richard_Schiff Just got to the “West Wing” episodes of my binge watching of… https://t.co/uL2ozoAnZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This one’s titled “Bitchin’ rooftop deck views at night because I had to drive back to the model unit after getting… https://t.co/GjKloT3gS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Here is a copy of Patti Smith’s latest book” which thank goodness is purse sized. I was not going to mention I had… https://t.co/F7UREX4Aax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tennesseine @BernieSanders Bernie started out strong and credible, but he crossed the line when his criticisms of… https://t.co/DciBVOQWm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Elyse for some medical appointments at the Mayo Clinic in Jacksonville.  It’s a wonderful balmy 84 degrees her… https://t.co/Pb9eb5lzCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch men be fathers &amp; enjoy it. Manners (southern men have this lock)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisalexander_ @thepbg Please send me that information. I got a stack for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing self made about Kylie is her face. Nope, even the doctors helped her with that...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FromHuronOut @_SJPeace_ @AOC -Mocking the disabled https://t.co/p0vF7Ras9T is none]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜#Snowmageddon19' 💛.  Keep it going #Viksnowfight @lshs_sports @LSHSConnect @BaldVikingAP @dhayman77 @docfank… https://t.co/TpfiDbvuN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[“THINK ABOUT US” by Little Mix is such a fucking hit. THESE GIRLS HAVE IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[a woman mistook me for a high school junior today n i kno im getting old bc it made me so happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[now i want some cookie dough, should’ve bought some when Jordan bought some😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[I put iced coffee in the cup I normally have water in today, so every time I go to take a drink of water it’s actua… https://t.co/KAtgHcBhgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Princess Bela is ready to #run @EasterSeals_SFL @SOFLHC proudly representing @MiamiDadeCounty celebrating… https://t.co/pro4tVyfpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shop Now With @IIAMYRB now!!! Follow @IIAMYRB for more young rich boy videos and pictures and music drops @IIAMYRB… https://t.co/DNa8ptwUY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been up since 5:30 in the morning plz don’t come @ me sideways because im not a morning person ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is interesting! A Spanish #Anglican! Also might be good to get that recipe for his syrup. Because if… https://t.co/iSkeTO1X18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to meet my LA-area friends on Tuesday! Will YOU be there to join the #HumansFirst conversation?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Seek a Doctor, you are processed by evil.👅👅👅👅👅]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cats decided I should get up at 4.30 for my 8.30 flight. I guess they wanted to make sure I had my good tea befo… https://t.co/ftTQ3LJiSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[its hitting me so much when i’m alone like i don’t wanna be alone right now :( but at the same time i just wanna let it all out]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m here for the growth and expansion of black businesses! Support! Support! Support!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me during a hyper manic spell of my undiagnosed mood disorder https://t.co/GH4qIFIHOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help Reece hit his fundraising goal!! #dreambig #stjude #noonefightsalone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bloodjetpoetry Gonna make a shell out of poems &amp; live there in perpetuity]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @joanowei and I walked into our classes today after 3 weeks https://t.co/izQsv1jXDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello and good morning to my followers all Nathan Fillion Castle #Firefly and the #Rookie fans I hope you have good… https://t.co/zuYMQdaVyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pink Twilight Zebra was inspired by zebras and pink magical skies.  In my dreams zebras frolic free surrounded by p… https://t.co/yeFF0zgrnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddiMellencamp Congrats! It’s so nice to see a truly healthy role model on TV!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay...Yes I'm partial!!! But this is the BEST Amelia Earhart ever!!! (my niece Amelia) ❤😊🎉🛩 https://t.co/MNlrF4IKg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@econokafka Siempre supe que AMLO era un Dictador Bananero solo por como habla. No me siento traicionada porque sie… https://t.co/KiREHqrlg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never met anyone with the same taste in music as me besides Albert. We. Are. Twins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CW_Riverdale and  #BeverleyHills90210  R.I.P Luke Perry you will be missed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a great day for Region 1 JAG-K! @JAG_Kansas Congrats to all of the students that participated and thank y… https://t.co/6pkpcyj8Re]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone take out Kyle Busch on the first lap so he has no chance of winning this race. Please and thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to learn how to drive. And get a car. So I can do more of the things I wanna do be myself 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekevinryder @clydetombaugh  @kevinandbean can you all break down this crazy story?! Got my head doin some mental… https://t.co/0xXhdwZaPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So it starts... @ Festival Pavilion at Fort Mason https://t.co/VILcapcbxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is damage to the Zadra construction due to high winds at Engergylandia in Poland.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t be the only one just starting #GameOfThrones⁠ ⁠currently questioning why I didn’t jump on sooner?! I’M HOOKED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manmanBrigitte Шавло. Туда тебе и дорога!😈 Чего ты хотел? Прийти с войной к соседу и чтобы тебя там встречали хлеб… https://t.co/XiQ2r4R4Gb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tflater @Darlene_Zoller I’m realizing now that a hammock may be the answer]]></document><document><![CDATA[This show has given me so much hope! I’m shocked that they would only do 10 episodes. It seems like a slap in the f… https://t.co/OTjNK3j5Jm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just went to deposit all the money I made this weekend, put the money in the ATM, processes the request, tells me t… https://t.co/CfNtPNa3Qn]]></document><document><![CDATA[wearing pigtail braids to remind everyone that I am in fact NOT an adult https://t.co/JUW6Uh5puP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m catching up on love and hip hop Miami and I’m confused how tf these grown ass women would let a man that loo… https://t.co/HFmiBpeKH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meeting strangers at the bar and then becoming besties by the end of the night will always be one of my favorite past times 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProBootyLicker I did and shit got better but it’s a process brother I won’t be truly happy for a few years]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great showing, SV Science Olympiad!  -Jayming L finished 5th out of 37 schools in the mission possible event -Devin… https://t.co/oxWkcO4hZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mullets are back and I am obsessed 💗 @dan_danburda  #mulletsofinstagram #mulletsrock #babybangs #ontrendhair… https://t.co/mTuaL2j4qC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kirbyb619 @ToddGloria Two of my zucchini bread fans! I feel like I should a zucchini bread party at my house. It s… https://t.co/TeL2fwvi84]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breyeschow (who is “big deal in the Presbyterian Church”) came to talk to our youth and wanted a selfie! Magic!!!… https://t.co/bbnSzMAxBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#datenight #tacopanda (@ Taco Bell in Brea, CA) https://t.co/SV5UDY78Zt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaltonDover3 Great job with that #KeithWhitley song. Absolutely beautiful. #Dontcloseyoureyes #voiceblinds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Have you thought about why these people are fighting Trump so hard because they've been there 20 30 4… https://t.co/x5cBZkxi2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnpavlovitz This is not the first time Trump has hugged the flag. What a bozo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Uber, why do your drivers get to make a passenger wait 10 minutes and then the driver cancels the ride? Accord… https://t.co/6SKYbl4byv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newbies: What do we mean by HOD, HOY- HOD=High of Day, many see this as Bullish.  HOY= High Of Year...also Bullish… https://t.co/8jMGv6vvnW]]></document></documents></author>