<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Kareem Abdul-Jabbar Puts Memorabilia Up for Auction https://t.co/iAR9LV71DL]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one cares about Duke-North Carolina - @GolicAndWingo - Maybe you should learn hockey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oswguzma Es mas facil que se robe la oposicion, los dirigentes y posibles candidatos .la mayoria tienen cuestamien… https://t.co/ZMXKRynlQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiveFrmCarolina @DeniseMTarHeel @Jessica_Klee @SoFreshlyFaded @UNCSwtHrt @tbyrd423 @KayGragg14 @TarHeelGirl93… https://t.co/URnKgIoccU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReggieChatman @Mar1on_ Marlon omg I dont know if you’ve seen this yet but wow. https://t.co/BevI2zLWrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@persnicketyweas @PamKeithFL @ScottsdaleBubbe @JavierLandes If they illegally enter the United States they are criminals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PROSPER ISD GREATNESS IN BASEBALL WILL CONTINUE AT ROCK HILL https://t.co/v3oQyjgJ3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can quit trying to control me, I am who I am and I’m gonna say what I want. If you really loved me you would lo… https://t.co/Av9Tj1WPmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re read this platform post again because of @patrick_oshag tweet. Great reminder and it’s how we’re building @okta.… https://t.co/6TWILGRqHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spinoff is back Friday Race 2 Tampa. Johnny V up. https://t.co/7LtBwqT1eA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRather I think my teenage daughter is old enough to remember that too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @GregGiordano1 to post covers of 7 favorite books I have read: just the cover in n… https://t.co/4U6At4LuIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw Knock Down the House, doc directed by Rachel Lears. It was inspiring! Check it out when you can. AOC is a… https://t.co/ac1ZTqiQI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[OPEN HOUSE: 995 Stuart Dr, Pottstown, Pa Sunday 3/3 from 1-3pm. #realtor #OPENHOUSE #MONTCO #HOME #luxuryproperty… https://t.co/bhdws2VNI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear US comics,  (@michaelianblack @AndyKindler @DougBenson @marcmaron @GaryGulman @Reddsaidit, etc...)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will be chasing saves on WW.  Couple old boring HR hitters  Few trendy SP  Yelich Goldy Xander Scooter Peraza  Nell… https://t.co/PkAwTknvna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clutchcurryback @Blake340_ LOL. hey man we’re 3-0 vs GSW this season and we would’ve beat them last year if CP3 do… https://t.co/tkwY6FUxR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sa_da_tay_ @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Cappitown brother, cappitown....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burgersub Ah yes the toll lane project that expands I-95 directly to a major Hogan Company brokered greenfield dev… https://t.co/OtW8QRXlDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A girl is sitting next to me in calc. Send help, my left leg is starting to seize]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today: @kittykuopoker “ I remember you in Venetian, we play table together” Me: yes @kittykuopoker : u say Kristen… https://t.co/DMYA9MK15E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMBichotte @agounardes @DebbiAlmontaser @BOENYC @MarkTreyger718 @JustinBrannan @NYCCouncil @DianaAyalaNYC… https://t.co/24XHlfl0x2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes @TGowdySC @MariaBartiromo Russia scammed America, that's for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has NASCAR become so expensive that protecting the car takes precedence over being competitive?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HFrazey @laflaneuse Yes I had to stop and stare at all those cakes and chocolates. Very impressive. Was there on a… https://t.co/zGU2y9S092]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey! Someone I know IRL won an Oscar! It's the First time that ever happened, I think!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Otto Octavius   . .  Our challenge going strong! The bad guys in the spotlight this month. Tag your toy-photos… https://t.co/7vz6dwFj49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WVUFLU Is there nit a difference between speech and action? Physical violence should be repudiated IMHO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LiT Event Photography @allswagga #KennyBeanPhotography #Photography #Nikon #ATLANTAMODEL #PhotoShoot #NewYorkModels… https://t.co/SamVtlxVTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our love ones get sick some times, not from Divine purposes, It's just to help us to live a more intense life! @ Du… https://t.co/ZRzKzllN9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricJorgenson Hi Eric, We would be happy to help your friend to work on his/her WordPress development project. We… https://t.co/MC3Z6UuqgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pueblo now down 30-15 to Sahuaro with 2:24 left 2Q. Warriors allowed Desert Edge 26 points in a 48-26 win on Thursd… https://t.co/sYE9VYsmzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisHines21 Only problem is his game hasn’t really evolved from last season. Today showed that he is a real asse… https://t.co/PdknVLbrf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexicru46779143 @TGirlsAddict @lithium66 @jockosrocket @Trans_promote @PassiValerio @adultparody @DaveKohenn… https://t.co/W7cXzNFkzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#clamchowder #yum @ Disney California Adventure Park https://t.co/5syGGGYOVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This final paragraph is like the last-minute sting setting up the horror movie sequel.  https://t.co/0zZHpykthY https://t.co/C8OAd4sdAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little man one of 23,000 plus I stand united with all parents against this injustice. #justiceforallautismkids]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’ve been seeing this Pancake Bread from Trader Joe’s going around social media (thanks @hotlinebalingit!) and I… https://t.co/UbqWQR87wy]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this day in history, 03/02/19. In 1944 at the16th Academy Awards “Casablanca” (pictured) released in 1942, wins… https://t.co/x7N40Hfq9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning to everyone especially our new NXT North American champion https://t.co/Fmt3O1U2dp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got excited when I saw @JERKROPE followed me.  I was then saddened when I realized it was not a list of jerks and… https://t.co/cwW4lCoitR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleArbour when I see you in your boots you remind me of Felicity Shagwelll From Austin Powers the Spy who shagg… https://t.co/UfVt1HlPa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#savingsam I know this is my 2nd post about Sam but please understand, she was recently diagnosed with stage 4 lung… https://t.co/zRWOGI45Ki]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a cool, damp, blustry morning west of Wytheville VA, Glenn Wheeler and I stumbled onto the source of global warm… https://t.co/N6XFEvfFgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw Kavanaugh did not succeed in hiding what he really is. Indeed, he blew his cover to the point that Justic… https://t.co/WSUxVA6dBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to blizzard conditions,  NO goalkeeper session today at 1PM! #campshutout #HPG #UWSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world is a vampire - boy were the smashing pumpkins right #mschat good thing for garlic and holy water 💧 https://t.co/mxLI9bqYCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered to WIN the NEW Corsair Wireless Harpoon RGB Gaming Mouse AND a MM350 Mousemat!!! You can enter too; click… https://t.co/GBWMa1hgs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twerring Looking at setlists from their recent shows and honestly I don’t think I would. I’m probably also more picky with their songs lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpeterman619 @RealJamesWoods You are in one. Forever on phones. About fake news. Its in ya schools, not on the new… https://t.co/yejgyHNkho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to meet you and hold you in my arms 😘😍  2 more months!! https://t.co/ptr0ZJahci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avon's Cade Robertson wins 7-2 to advance to the consolation second round at 120. #LoCoMats]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chance on Ultralight Beam Jay Rock on Money Trees Rick Ross on Devil in a New Dress Vince Staples on Hive Pick a An… https://t.co/IUmfsJmnhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disguising the way someone can take advantage of a smaller nation’s infrastructure and resources to get exposure to… https://t.co/Ld6f6jJpxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starbucks drive thru (9-10 cars); I decide to go inside (1 person ahead of me); All 11 (sarcasm) cars beat me!… https://t.co/7hXT48M3VR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time at #SUFU19 catching up with friends at the @CleClinicUro alumni dinner! https://t.co/vPhZd6AeIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But as we were allowed of God to be put in trust with the gospel, even so we speak; not as pleasing men, but God,… https://t.co/rx0IbvSqWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rivian how can we connect!?  The Outside Experience is perfect for your truck!  https://t.co/Tqo7l1Rs9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the west coast, which they refer to the best coast, I’m a wildabeast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robertfritz33 @JenniPrickett @cauzin_trouble @LowellMiller17 @OnTargetFishing @RapidRiverLures 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had 2 arguments this weekend where I think the other party is just flat out DRUNK!  Argument #1: Paul George i… https://t.co/EEByA9YCxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seaside Village board president and another resident both urge larger capacity of pumping station for future separa… https://t.co/htphr9mJMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[That camera that sweeps alone in turns 3 and 4 is my favorite for the sound. At least until crank it up comes along.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ anyone send me ur fave Spotify playlists or just fave songs because I really need to revamp my driving playlists]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magastorybook @RealTT2020 @BreitbartNews This evil unbelievable bastard Cuomo needs to be thrown the hell out of o… https://t.co/StQ7taic3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASA @Crystal_Fishy @Space_Station The last snow day we had here was, I think, 1972.. so no, not today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t get any replies on this, so is there an argument to be made for keeping those FTA included in the formula?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN He is the most gullable baffoon in the World.....he is a disgrace to our Nation. Our apologies to the Warmbier… https://t.co/4iGU3ivql8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta stop taking breaks from the gym. Be coming back looking sore asf. But i gotta work this Mardi Gras off me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Tyler, elected as vice president in 1840, was the first man to accede to the presidency because his predecesso… https://t.co/2pBEmcACgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/IHObGlx3UU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I CAN NOT GET #CuzILoveYou OUT OF MY HEAD. @lizzo YOU HAVE DONE IT AGAIN AND I AM HERE FOR IT!   So damn pumped for… https://t.co/jyk82Pe1Yf]]></document><document><![CDATA[For whatever reason both Finland and Sweden use this kind of neoliberal shill sliding-scale subsidy system rather t… https://t.co/EFC6Rx31y4]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is tomorrow yet????? Iron vs Apollos.....excited for this matchup then Sunday Commanders vs Hotshots.  @TheAAF https://t.co/ZmM917IDr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle has bounced around a lot and probably just a cover for Jr fake divorce just to hide his assets when h… https://t.co/kjkiIlew9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why we say yt people know absolutely nothing about Hip-Hop. Nothing but culture vultures who were introduce… https://t.co/HN1sJd2JIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waitwait I want to walk and talk with @lukeburbank mainly because I’m a Ten, and if you don’t know what that means… https://t.co/IncGzmfKRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[BS and Crap flinging are always trending so Tweet with Huge Boots on , Caution, and Facts ! Also your non reply is… https://t.co/vq7z7b9Wq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also lulz that @YouTube marked the video as not suitable for ads cuz it may contain controversial content? Algorithm fail 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leslietfj Instead of attacking Bernie, tell me which Democratic candidate for President you like and why?  Be positive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMB @adamnash Not really. The consent decree hurt the web. The only reason the web revitalized was because Google… https://t.co/ljOI15Ao0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jon155 Super nice photo update.  Your last one was tight. Better to give than receive.   Work it out again Santa a… https://t.co/LTfK1xyako]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cars #california #garagelatino #petersenmuseum #orangecounty #photography #instagram #photo #clasic #classiccars… https://t.co/gVabEwPC6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the five-year anniversary of the best screenshot I've ever taken during a Michigan game: https://t.co/HHJc0NvNQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/ #ProfessionalServices #Engineer is how I started my career. I was a biz major and self taught developer. I never… https://t.co/eftra9ysfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow why is it that HR 1 received not one Republican vote today?? BREAKING: The House just passed HR1, wh… https://t.co/Sqv8x7qnmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow https://t.co/qwoXMAsNR2  #bodybuilding #abs #gym #pecs #nipples #gaymuscle #muscles #flex #flexing… https://t.co/aIUxPTz0My]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meggettonian @Cardinals @CardsMagazine Felt compelled to create this visual for you. https://t.co/ObLkk1FaOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Shell Game by @kanebrewing/@jackieosbrewery at @2foodiesinlove — https://t.co/3CQWbj1eW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richard2355 @catorano so 2%-10% paid 32.2%  That is the group that gets absolutely screwed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ate at the @SaveRoscoes where 50 Cent got shot in the face. Surreal experience]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theRealKiyosaki #amazon says my copy of #richdad poor dad was delivered today! Almost walked out of my job to star… https://t.co/s0nai9w2bF]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t. And even if you think that is needed, Domi is out there and can actually skate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus he's a wonderful Offensive Line Coach. Happy Birthday Hall of Famer. Steeler Fans still lovin you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @SpeakerPelosi @mattgaetz &lt;—- he apologized, only because he is scared tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXERCISE for @selfportraiture #selfportraitsunday #sps #exercise #lovethesnatchfoundation #lovethesnatch @ Burlingt… https://t.co/XsquWUiwaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm still mad about the Edgar tweet.  I know at least two that have that hair cut. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then they adjusted it to just 2 hours- I’ve never before had a delay get BETTER after it’s announced, only ever wor… https://t.co/sUTZxTJsMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC The Girl Scouts even though some of them may now be boys or want to be boys have been infiltrated by Planned P… https://t.co/z4Cbky9Fo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IESTroutman @CCC_GR And I would have the same conversation with them as I have with you.]]></document></documents></author>