<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@debbieratto79 @realDonaldTrump @SpeakerPelosi Go into the room and talk to johanson and Brian.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amy doing Jakes under the breath “whaaaat” 😂 spending too much time with a person really does cause you to pick up… https://t.co/QtmuFrzAvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t get me wrong, I WANT kids.. but I don’t want to bring any children into this world when I’m in so much debt a… https://t.co/mw791IrQtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CroHardcore @DogfartNetwork @Brazzers @JulesJordan @naughtyamerica @EvilAngelVideo @LustArmyVideo @XFREAXX… https://t.co/VPBboOcZmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHeartRadio Stray by Grace Vanderwaal is so beautiful and so powerful, can't stop listening to it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge demands answers from Roger Stone on book that could violate gag order https://t.co/OYbRJ1JhfH via @politico]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrossingBroad Ok Kyle but like, lease? Bryce emphasizes he wants to be here to LIVE, raise a family. He’s not temp… https://t.co/RsRKPrY3WG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I click on a trending topic #NationalEmergency and this is what I see... not one POV from a Republican! Bias? Ignor… https://t.co/lxPiRbx4WY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cait_Parker85 Sometimes I can’t get up from bed cause of the pain from my sciatica 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#blocked i am not going to arizona to be with my family. Id kill myself first.  Pass that message along to laura tu… https://t.co/C3bsbPvN7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump @SecretaryAcosta I listened to the whole interview a while ago and could NOT beli… https://t.co/K0BnqxbvrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenHowe Commodore Vic 20 with a cassette drive. We coded our own games and saved them over my Mom’s “Saturday Nigh… https://t.co/RASAVmeHrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was one of the #toughest days I’ve ever experienced as a business owner...#butGod  No one said it would b… https://t.co/kiCw9zAlCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@That20Twin_Twin Hell nah. Lol I don’t ever wanna experience that shit again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Madamefigaro Oh dear tit job under boob saggy leather not good Kimmie-kins not good @BotchedTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amym1972 @joshgroban @JenniferNettles ty we'll be at the Verona show.... was just hoping &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mermhart Miranda Hart, not only are you one of the, what I call, world’s funniest people, you are also a good and… https://t.co/K03MDALYsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 @SunStandsStill6 I accidentally hit Mark instead of Jordan. Jordan is the worst!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellen Degeneres Quotes -  I love this one -- it's more touching and true than... #comedy #giggle #smirk #jolly https://t.co/T3BVJ60KTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danko89 Ya sé! Nada más nos emocionamos a lo wey 🙃 jajaja pero se me hace súper divertido toda la locura del fandom]]></document><document><![CDATA[_ᴜʀ ᴅᴜᴅᴇ ᴘᴀᴛ ᴄᴀᴜɢʜᴛ ʀᴇᴅ-ʜᴀɴᴅᴇᴅ, ʜᴇ, ʜᴇ, ʜᴇ 👉🔥 #SHYGIRL #SHINY #LATEX #RUBBERDOLL #LADYINRED dramateurope darkaeu de… https://t.co/fg5LqW4FI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My poor dog after only being out for a couple minutes. He's in for the night. @ Houghton, Michigan https://t.co/7AMeerqKFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonnieJohnson This stayed in the headlines thanks to the LOCAL Chicago news media. They did ALL the work. MSM just wanted to preach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t let #nhl slide now that basketball is back. @JillianSydney has you covered!]]></document><document><![CDATA[update i FINALLY saw him at work and uhh let’s just say he looks good in red 🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeniseARubin @nvygrl1 @UROCKlive1 @ilan @Ilhan You have that entirely backwards 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free House -- what a great racehorse! Fell in love with him at the Santa Anita Derby when he looked at me down that… https://t.co/q4zqW78rWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omar Apollo/Manwolves/Jamie Isaac/Joji/Moise/Tyler Cole/Matt Monday/Caitlin Russo/Baro/Jasper Bones/Yeek/Banes World/Raven Lenae/Bakar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Article I, Section 8: “Congress shall have Power…to coin Money, regulate the Value thereof, and of foreign Coin.”… https://t.co/izSqhvrFGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nunca le había echado tanto amor a una ppt como hoy ahora si a dormir amigos 😴😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[love life Gogo westhollywood barhopping cardib teamiphone mylord Chapel imstephaunelite WATCH:… https://t.co/urYeMNPw49]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you wondered, it's really cold outside.⛄🤣  Thankfully, I'm back inside warming up and writing while listeni… https://t.co/5012esdvh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things are just ludicrous. My dad did this for me once but instead of a gift card it was a... #mirth #chuckle… https://t.co/YJ0Eild91G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2019Jefery @catvalente @najwazebian @AOC @KamalaHarris @SaraBareilles @BettyADodson @Adele @motherwounded… https://t.co/ib3mbb142H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it justifiable to spend $48 on these? I think it is https://t.co/HnJo2YAcHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @KamalaHarris @ewarren @PeteButtigieg @CoryBooker @JulianCastro too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great start for this hard working group of young men! @PatMyers1221 @GoLeopards]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made eye contact with @gwenstefani tonight - and it was bananas. 🍌 #ImJustAGirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz you should walk away, crawl away into whatever hole you came out of]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise at the farm this morning @ Smallwood Farms https://t.co/3pFURIJDav]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to go to Kokomo with me tomorrow to Book a Million to help me find The Great Gatsby??? 🙂🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also. Bullies. Who the F has time or energy for bullies? Bye Felicias. https://t.co/BBbFHhkyr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sxdoc @realDonaldTrump President Trump is a great President, trying hard to fulfill his campaign promises.  Normal… https://t.co/pW3wG91P01]]></document><document><![CDATA[being a care provider for your grandpa with dementia, alzheimers and parkinsons is not something i recommend for an… https://t.co/XSpctdtn0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[The importance of prayer. @ Temple of Praise Ministries https://t.co/2EKpLPPfFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doginturtleneck @mamajagger WOW ur so right about that dying part bc rmemeber that time I got in a fight w/ Matt h… https://t.co/cxTR5BWEUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this #InternationalWomensDay Did you know that the first woman to receive a Ph.D in Computer Science was a nun?… https://t.co/Smgs6rPZuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 2 more days to VOTE VOTE VOTE!!!!  https://t.co/aUtvKkAHsH durantmainst @smbizrevolution @ Durant, Oklahoma https://t.co/PGXQNVsvuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ruthmkb @Tintie4 @a_picazo @acoyne Only if you actually *want* to work things out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope you all like Maryland basketball. Enter at your own risk in March 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP critize Ilhan Omar as anti-semite. She's not. She has no beef with Jewish religion. She has a problem with mone… https://t.co/10fcq954Y3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corpus Christi Community Council of PTA’s teams up with @CCISD to travel to Austin for Texas PTA Rally Day. We’ll h… https://t.co/YsSR0deZ0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok remember the snowman @JaisolWX made Saturday? Well veteran #7News reporter @Byron_Barnett made the one in the to… https://t.co/7YJLhjoY7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[The barista at Starbucks just said I have clear skin annndddd we need more people like her in this world]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I should be watching the #Oscars2019 but my bed is calling my name. 😴 Goodnight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No way, Congress should support our President, You work for the people, who want the Wall 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to beat the “mom” and her boyfriend to death now.  Aniya Day-Garrett suffered stroke several weeks or even m… https://t.co/upL5qyMciQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gkokonut i can't believe this person has 2,400 whole followers who are seeing their garbage views, gross]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristanpagliei It’ll be 7 (yikes) years since I graduated this year and I think about “show, don’t tell” everyday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Senator Nelson and all others involved successfully pushing SB 3 WITH the amendment to add librarians. We… https://t.co/fha47sRd7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can call me Marvel, Marvelous, Victorious!  @COPraiseIM @pocah1675 @MoonNicoleBush @DrJinCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nate added me to some steps challenge on my Fitbit and I am so fucking determined to beat him. Therefore grayson an… https://t.co/hwUpnixvZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleebb21 I live in Minneapolis and don’t eat donuts/bagels or drink Fancy Coffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ICE19 I’m here and ready to mingle with some amazing educators!!! Come by and see me tomorrow!! #canvaslms #lms #edutech]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have asked my landlord to stop charging me rent because sometimes we have nice conversations about the lavender I… https://t.co/YEJSoGKiH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask, 'why isn't she part of this working group, or committee, or meeting?' - @so_many_amys on how to build the en… https://t.co/RVp7huF54N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mat Wow wow wow I’m drinking way too much salt juice smh https://t.co/3S4iYuSG3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonicaRunge11 @grhluna24 Yes, I thought all that too at one time. Then I listened to autistic adults and examined… https://t.co/3xLZF6nErD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory YEAH. THAT'S BC THAT'S EXACTLY WHO THEY R - STUPID GULLIBLE RACISTS!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX @FOXTV @donnyosmond is #peacockmask, @MsGladysKnight  is the #beemask, and I'm almost certain the… https://t.co/anWh9OEjcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh I hate those days where I can’t keep my eyes opened at work to save my life 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeccaGuido @hallmarkchannel @BGrossbardProds 😆😆 such a great scene!! #AOMH #AOMH4PLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I helped a 17 year old girl find her way back to her hotel room just now and she thanked me like 10x for not leavin… https://t.co/y05Eqxo2RS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschroder326 @seanspicer @extratv @SecPompeo @KellyannePolls @SarahHuckabee Who cares Michelle! No one care if you watch😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you hate me so much why tf are you concerning yourself with what’s going in MY life ??? hmmm someone’s a lil https://t.co/1P3xzs3luN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maotechno @escouadeEDU @CFORP Merci pour cette belle causerie! @maotechno @Bourmu @monsieurhunter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RapSheet vs @AdamSchefter on this Antonio Brown to the Bills thing. Who is right??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew that the Las Vegas murders were part of a false flag.  Thank you for shedding light on what was behind this… https://t.co/S9k5lyGwxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're singing all these songs in your head, you know you're a Grandma #ilovemygrandsons💕 #babyshark #family @… https://t.co/b58Kf3npoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShadowhunterBks I actually just finished it for the first time last week 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let us #celebrate #all #women not just today but #always #happyinternationalwomensday #strongwomen 💋🥰👩‍🦳 @ Union Sq… https://t.co/VzHrmBBxCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[This! One theme I picked up today: focusing on how we can truely uplift (not just point to the problems with BYMOC)… https://t.co/Ike3GonKwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SofiaG2015 is seriously my new favorite party buddy other then my girls 🥵🥵🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read Across America Week in PEECH, Day 3; WACKY WEDNESDAY!!! https://t.co/7AnRQnE5cc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paul Rudd - he looks so handsome in this pic and his sense of humor makes... #funniness #lol #smirk #jolly https://t.co/nBTR9U7O9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[annoyed because I have 2 classes and 2 meetings all back to back and I have to pretend I’m not in a horrible mood today lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anybody know how to fix this technical issue??  #Mimi #catsofinstagram @ Mimi's World https://t.co/n0aaLVPKqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me something I don’t know about you 😏#NewProfilePic https://t.co/RPmhA5v5fz]]></document><document><![CDATA[people ghost me all the time out the blue. shit b going good and then one day they just disappear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best friend has two days off work while her kids are in school and she’s blowing her ig stories up with all the… https://t.co/WDgLR4Tr4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sxdoc @realDonaldTrump He is, indeed, the best President ever and continues MAGA in spite of the hate spewing liberals!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATRlXXY It sounds like me but I’m 99.9% sure I made it back from the cruise? 🤷‍♀️🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌲Con Sue Photography and Design🌲  ♥️On-Location.... March 9-14, 2019♥️  🌲Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌲  ♥️This… https://t.co/niP6kvnQcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh I can't wait to get back to Tennessee where I'm not sweating constantly]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much movement in libraryland these days. What are your favourite/most effective ways to on board someone or to b… https://t.co/0AYQQ24Mrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Trump asked Gaetz to threaten  Cohen ..note that this tactic was exactly what Cohen noted yesterday--- have othe… https://t.co/qitfLkYWDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueClawG @lauren_huesing All right! I'm here for it. Let's hit zero yall!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacycosmetics Catrina 1 palette   @shopedenrose Lashes  @benefitcosmetics Brow contour pro  @gerardcosmetics Every… https://t.co/Kfxq4tlYcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#R10leaders getting started in a non traditional way D.E.S.IG.N. Thinking!  @JonathanKegler https://t.co/PnMFWP9QoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[VENCE EN AMISTAD CON DIOS @lilidegalindo * * ... Abraham creyó a Dios, y le fue contado por justicia, y fue llamado… https://t.co/MRiqDeWoQ8]]></document></documents></author>