<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Seguimos un 100% con nuestro presidente interino @jguaido. Que Dios lo proteja.  Estos canallas desgraciados lo qui… https://t.co/CiVbMIkE6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feels like I need to sell my organs if I want to afford healthcare in America...of course, though, would anything b… https://t.co/q2SGwSuY6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @maddow You have the support of many people - keep in touch with MoveOn and similar groups and we will… https://t.co/BylV4CBjTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I folded laundry that was sitting on my bed for two days. Someone be proud of me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jack’s band, Sidewalks, has the privilege of playing at Irving Theatre tonight, opening for Speaking Suns and other… https://t.co/TDAGq9ptBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaNordWx @hbwx @laurynricketts @TenaciousTopper @amelia_draper @dougkammerer @ABC7Brian @MiriWeather. Martins… https://t.co/2ulBAEAuyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrookeKnisley @trello @RipleyHQ @KristenVanNest @msexcel I tried to use Trello but I ended up discarding it. So it… https://t.co/ogTBrtri5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little art lover enjoying my postcards at @artistprojectTO #artlover #art https://t.co/BJEJdLpFOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VABVOX Get her this sweet and gorgeous book about a family of elephants welcoming its newest member. https://t.co/5401bclAUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A moment of silence to honor those who died in the plane crash in Ethiopia begins the opening to the Commission on… https://t.co/EUc7dFIhg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really enjoy making a delicious homemade meal after a long day of work👩🏽‍🍳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg my entire yoga class sang happy birthday to me this morning! 🧘‍♀️ 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of preaching buzzwords like “empower” and “celebrate” how about start using words like “promote” and “inves… https://t.co/wiCx3teIwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaceyMcFadyen @marlenakayj i say this shit constantly, it’s hard to find an actual feminist in this community.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarsMovieMag, Please Write The Story About The Great Late Kenneth Tobey👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👍🏾👍🏾👍🏾 https://t.co/oPOcxUxtXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LandWaterSummit I reviewed "The Bees in Your Backyard" for @storycircle and loved it. Also Xerces Society's "Attra… https://t.co/1qWO69lsqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My babes! Help me out here...hit me with your reasons why the concept of “it’s his word against hers” in matter is… https://t.co/hfqhHDmbm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loll what is happening??! I just received about 20 friend request on Facebook 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephRider13 At the fancy candy/ice cream store, the fruit-flavored drinks were called phosphates. Central Ohio, 1970.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost time for church! 9:30 this morning tune in LIVE for morning worship with Senior Pastor @jamalhbryant… https://t.co/jWnqPrRbQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julianjaxxxon i love your honesty.  i love how you get yourself grounded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got word that ICE is releasing 530 migrants to @AHouseElPaso today. This is the largest single day release in… https://t.co/wmPr0yiM0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 @ronbeatyjr  Your mama should’ve told you it’s not OK to jump off a cliff just because others are… https://t.co/sulxBPDlm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you here with me? Just looking out on the day of another dream. Well, you can’t get what you want but you can g… https://t.co/tmzSsErqxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paul_Flores44 @nicolebyer @NailedIt @FoxNews Oh my God, get a life, you big baby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oddCouplemusic They got him on video saying he stole the dance, anyway. Lmao 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillFigel @93XRT Likewise! Thanks so much for hanging out with us @93XRT Salvation is what we offer 🎼]]></document><document><![CDATA[What just happened?? #advancingtocounty #AnimalSciences https://t.co/oveEn1hcsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chazebration @KatieofCode It’s like an uglifier but, like, a starwar-fier!? I’d totes use that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly Khloe probably got paid more to do this event than Tristan gets paid an entire season. 👑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outlander_clips They should have deleted part of the Star Chamber scenes and leave this in. The episode shows Clai… https://t.co/6H8140J1za]]></document><document><![CDATA[... y’all I’ve been managing my pain without any massage or chiro work since SEPTEMBER.   I’m getting a massage tod… https://t.co/aUCjRF4zu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legs in the air, he’s eating you and sucking your dick https://t.co/j7VaUQDXrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @_lexgotnext_!  Words can’t express how proud I am of you!  Continue reaching for the Stars but keep… https://t.co/KCIR5I2YUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathyliveswell tonight’s dinner was inspired by this tweet. 😌🍔💁🏽‍♀️ https://t.co/yE1g8Fec3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are stuck in the hospital find the biggest Fancy Nancy doll you can find to make that girl smile!  Someone… https://t.co/oRfbR9W8Ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that we are 500 pages in to my criminal law book and we’ve read everything but one chapter should tell you… https://t.co/65oqWw31rB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bust out your visors and fanny packs! Taking a trip down nostalgia lane tonight — FLASH BACK SATURDAYS with… https://t.co/4gAwBmV0Bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @shaunking You are an amazing woman. Smart, eloquent, unapologetic in your beliefs, unafraid, you are what we… https://t.co/So5XWduIeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[i swear this is literally @sonnierae1 in algebra y’all. I’m in tearsssss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kim first. Putin first. Erdogan first. Netanyahu first. All Autocrats &amp; dictators first before America.… https://t.co/g5jsvbWGwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening now: Tump meets with Kim Jung Un. Behind the scenes look at press in Hanoi. Watch live on #abc13 MORE:… https://t.co/iEE9Olzjbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SontaranPR I'm driving in tomorrow; should I be ferrying TP and other supplies? 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[the look on a professor’s face when they can tell I’m understanding a concept &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear future husband,  If you come home to me jamming out to Warrant and Twisted Sister while I make dinner. You’ve… https://t.co/E3hrrQfAXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must protect Ghost!!!!! Weird or not weird to have Ghost ride a dragon w/ Jon Snow?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tayshia’s dad: “you can’t just microwave a relationship”                                  Tayshia:… https://t.co/0VZFu2O5g8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somewhere a retiree named Gertrude has a banging sonic adventure 2 chap garden huh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Experiencing major #FOMO with all of the amazing #SXSW sessions going on. https://t.co/6THbuxnBfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[But then I finally come to Cali. (Not to see her but to see my friend) Mind you I’m in Los Angeles but she’s manage… https://t.co/tEL2Oqtp3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[No cavities, again! 🙌🏼 To say I’m proud of this little guy is a gross understatement. He’s been terrified to get X-… https://t.co/tkhJvtKwwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited @rhettandlink are coming to milwaukee in june i’m gonna haha CRY!!!! 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chemical spraying our skies at night while we sleep with poisens so we cannot see what they are doing. Making manki… https://t.co/3gWL4ZaoLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Obviously 🙄 was given grades to pass to play football... same old story... both of them]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew I was gonna regret that long nap after work earlier smh #WideAwake 🙄🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[you see, i wanna give you some smart ass comment like “oh bet she’s enjoying that...” but ya know what, i’m gonna n… https://t.co/9pRdhqVsMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 🎂 Cynthia Bailey with many more blessings to come🎉🎉🎉🎊🎊🎊🎈🎈🎈🌹🌹...from:Cynthia Howard...Macon,Ga.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss from watching you and the whole gang on Saved by the bell @MPG @MarioLopezExtra @TiffaniThiessen that was on… https://t.co/pAGwEAeozK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finish this sentence... #NationalDayofUnplugging #11Alive https://t.co/0TNMsTmAgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoloresOfCourse So they are selling his art collection! ?That Warhol type painting of George is kinda ugly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Señores @Avianca, así como el aleteo de una mariposa afecta el clima al otro lado del mundo, ustedes me afectan tre… https://t.co/FFDEKuUfnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending the christening of my newest godson, Parker John Williams https://t.co/Q53lWPKyDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uterly frustrated today. Just when I think things are gonna be good I get surprised!!! 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WallisFashion #WallisWeekend #WIN I like look number 2 the pink one!! Thanks so much for the chance!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We breathe in what the trees breathe out, and they breathe in what we breathe out. Always impressed by the beauty o… https://t.co/s5E9cpO51g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to have a blast at #GNOSEF @ Tulane University https://t.co/71xliOBK78]]></document><document><![CDATA[An important read those who tenderly care for aging loved ones.  https://t.co/n9KczhiqGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got a gnarly ass bruise on my knee from eating mad shit at big bear yesterday, oops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You seem like you can’t sleep. Sitting up worrying about Cohens testimony?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The movie: “The Choice” will have a good hearted man crying. Great movie to watch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 21 degrees and these hoes in shorts. Wow. Hoes really don’t get cold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaV579 With my 8th graders, I did a shoe, cell phone, or a quarter. Everyone returned the pencil if they gave… https://t.co/AhqSHJcTjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NELLY161076 @miguelbtrevino @SanPedroNL Comparto tu opinión Nelly. Ojalá y nos tomen en cuenta. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaternityCourt and @TWIZZLERS is the reason I'm so sleepy in the morning. EVERY morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJ_Miles I literally was like welp it’s Friday tomorrow I can sacrifice sleep lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have Herpes...what I also have is a phenomenally strong mental, spiritual, emotional and physical well being!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisDJackson @ABCPolitics @jonkarl When trump said he lied about everything else does that mean he just admitted to hitting his wife too??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also it is wild that y’all can make a joke out of ex girlfriends and play them up as crazy meanwhile your homeboys… https://t.co/RCqmREUaoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[proving that the enviable work/life balance is possible. ☝️It is AMAZING what you can accomplish with a little wine… https://t.co/2pgSWDr6q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Idiot doesn’t belong in Congress???? She’s so rude &amp; classless &amp; dumb &amp; a bitch!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InfamousAlmost @joncoopertweets @mattgaetz My same question indeed, Almost Infamous!]]></document><document><![CDATA[can someone from the future just tell me what career to do and nothing more and I’ll be set]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopularPups Just one touch was enough to calm down the baby, this is positive caressing so important on the health… https://t.co/4KDSVnNOkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a true blessing when you can say you have friends 👭 and it’s even sweeter when that friendship has lasted for… https://t.co/brAEL5taUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @steph93065 @realDonaldTrump Not watching him or Shepherd Smirh ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayleyraee1 @madisyn_young03 @slycoopster How is she racist by pointing something out ? Y’all wanna #maga but the… https://t.co/0FvNgDRbpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOralBuffet @nikoCSFB @BernieSanders @TulsiGabbard @McscNetwork Bernie was cheated! Period end of story! Look at… https://t.co/M0XJIaUeV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Hand already touched him. He’s infected gotta throw the whole face away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was able to shower without seizing. The weather is nice.  About to eat and hang out with all the homies. It's a beautiful day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BasementCatERE @usatodayopinion @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows https://t.co/n9xcdks1dM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Would you rather be a @Yankees fan and own the state of California or be a @TheIowaHawkeyes fan and own the Star B… https://t.co/c8dR2veEiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love kitty cats &amp; yes this is true!!lol👍😎😳🐱 https://t.co/jZz13RB86F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WireAmerican What do you idiots think an online petition is going to do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jack (well my son jack) who loves to read @TheEconomist.  Remember when we sang Mariah's song in the car and we ha… https://t.co/zzivTIrueV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bunkybun @globalvoices @haloefekti @lilith2u @buell003 @Communista2 @KittyBhagat Fucking children on a lethal playground]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I was born waaay earlier just so I could have the chance to see queen live 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TayshiaAdams Tayshia, you are the greatest. You have the biggest heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT  Catch me at The World Famous for All That 90’s with THE QUEEN of PARTY theonlymayhem performances by barbi… https://t.co/1Jsr1Cb35b]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tobaccofreenj @NJPN @TobaccoFreeNJ with colleges from across NJ and multiple out of state colleges as well.  Worki… https://t.co/GbYNtfVDmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSaraMiles_ dying in thigh high heeled booties for a 16 hour shoot that is still filming rn &amp; im cold, tired, sick, &amp; hungry]]></document></documents></author>