<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TokuChris @EmperorBigD The behind the scenes on both are more fun than the actual films]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Graham wrestlers placed: Champions:  106 Nolan Gessler 113 Trace Braun 120 Dawson Show 126 Chris Kelly 132 Nick… https://t.co/yx8sEfapif]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronlopresti I buy based on artist/writer or IP. A good cover also draws my attention. 3.99 an issue is pretty steep for a normal issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is wrong here?  The activists who told these kids there are 12 years to stop the end of the world, following th… https://t.co/H1iljeWbMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckReising Remember Kyle Van Noy? Misused and miscast in the Lions defense? Gets traded to NE and becomes a very… https://t.co/XeiiNrOWEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s an idea worth considering, move #PresidentsDay to the day after the #SuperBowl. “We should simply move Presi… https://t.co/Aax13TNJye]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quite the view. I just figured out my retirement plan. @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/MZhBdyVPKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t been tweeting much lately. Been spending all my free time catching on ECW TV episodes from ‘97. Thank you @WWENetwork]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can this be better offense when he clearly travels, not once but twice!?! 🤦🏾‍♂️😡👎🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[A night of upsets???!!!  What’s gonna happen now???!!!  Who wants to see Anthony get this!!  Let’s go!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueMattD15 @TitansMCM Please to god let the @Ravens resign him but I think we are going to let him walk]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do I alter my closet items to prepare for DC?! Like the REAL cold is going to happen to me again?? And I’m CHOOSING this?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Falafel for lunch (@ Dabke Lebanese Cuisine in Mc Lean, VA) https://t.co/wj9DwKXUpv https://t.co/3zDFp9Mw0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KGWNews Money for school would be great. Unfortunately all the bonds and measures that are usually passed always g… https://t.co/PCznMbpQOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamonRoblesJr @MesquiteSmoker So that's what that song is about!!! https://t.co/9Va8z1gIuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alcoholic brains are assholes a lot of the time, even in sobriety. #alcoholism #sobriety]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sasshole @calimelissa @saracrump @QuinceMountain @BlairBraverman sigh...   ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amo que me aparezca a que le dan Fav mis friends porque así me doy cuenta que tan enfermos están 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just became a contributing writer for @RespectMyRegion thanks to @therealjayping and @MPyreP for adding me to the team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro I used to wonder how human beings could perpetrate evils like the Holocaust because I believed people w… https://t.co/TssghDpZZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhondacrain4 @chuckdiesel7474 @RealJamesWoods I am sorry for your loss. They become members of the family. Lost my… https://t.co/6Ddhm9TnCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is situational insomnia a thing? I can’t sleep for my life the few nights before traveling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HWP_IV @WalkingESPN14 @VOLUNTEERS_TN @CharlieDaniels Loving the game it is not over yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheMerryWriter D2: After taking a Creative Writing course in college. Afterwards, I changed my major when I transf… https://t.co/G8WV3hcG73]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twin with the best backcourt in the country @TyreseMaxey @chrisharris_2 https://t.co/dprBX47ilf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rex_rexchapman I love how the smaller dog started licking himself as of the big brute did him a favor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Mark Hollis. #1980s Talk Talk - It´s My Life https://t.co/NPtELZy64i]]></document><document><![CDATA[She should, at a minimum, be removed from the Foreign Affairs Committee!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This @SJCHSBBALL squad is one of the most Dominant Programs I’ve seen.  Can you say DYNASTY‼️💯‼️💯‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m gonna get my postpartum and grief doula training as well. Hehe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning training under palm trees @nsu_msoccer #trainhard #dreams @ Fort Lauderdale, Florida https://t.co/1zSeyTVr0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrienneOfSnark_ Did they come before or after Sarah Palin.  I thought she was the first sign of the apocalypse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[our new record is done . BUT it needs a few sprinkles and whip cream on it ...WEBSITE will be up in few weeks. reco… https://t.co/DAsA9Zs8g2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having fun at Springfield College staff night at the MassMutual Center! #FunaplentyInSection20 @ Springfield Thunde… https://t.co/1ti8D3MrwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rakeem Nathan Nuñez-Roches is a Belizean Garífuna defensive tackle for the Tampa Bay Buccaneers of the NFL.  He was… https://t.co/34pm8kF65B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrstone4 @kron4news @moniwelz Check out my song:  “Snowing in Vegas” https://t.co/9cB6kgI6aT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pero es que el presidente no ha tenido en sus premura un diálogo. Solo  parámetros tenemos que conseguir que son: c… https://t.co/cChNyNYf2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wxstjxhn @itsss__kat Yoooo super proud of you bud. Knew you would get it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimMWeber I voted Walker only because UCONN had lost 4-5 heading into the postseason and then just went on a roll.… https://t.co/IeBtPge7zl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smoking the first meat (pork shoulder) of 2019! I know I’m a pansy but it’s been too damn cold to cook outside!… https://t.co/qdmXLhpRnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dad in his happy place #family @ Cooper's Old Time Pit BBQ Austin https://t.co/00SndxRU7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@builtbydoozers @MarkJGrimaldi @dickersonpike @jaycaspiankang Yup, those two seasons rock in NYC. They're  the only… https://t.co/mlSXq09sOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serious question. Are you at least aware their plights are jointly negotiated by the unions they will eventually be… https://t.co/ouHJc3I5t8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AthleticsCCHS @gmhssports Now that’s really really classy! Much respect!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McCurdysComedy @tommycat I'd love to come tonight and have a distant relative with a birthday sometime in the futu… https://t.co/O7grsEz4Fy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first 7 performance videos from #noiseknowledgeconsortium are live on my YouTube (link in bio) . NKC  is a mont… https://t.co/9RQ72j7Q94]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IL_police Praying for his full recovery - refuah shlemah.  We stand with you Yisrael!]]></document><document><![CDATA[falta que salgan a decir,si no fuera por la revolución Bolivariana no habrá regresado la luz jamas y nunca.. imbéciles]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted to take a pic of the box score in 2k showing I made a 3 with Ben Simmons, but my friend decided to hit qui… https://t.co/KUIzKVVITL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyDiComo @JamalCollier @JonHeyman So Jamal: Arby's as @timbhealey: Chipotle?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fabricar2003 @ConversaAfiada Talvez voce acostumado a ver os ministros do STF como Gilmar soltar Tucanos, queria q… https://t.co/MhIIr8FGqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s some more. Few finishing touches / adjustments. Ugh so excitedddd for photoshoot! 😍😍😍 https://t.co/awEF949IIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[great event at Paper Crane featuring Andrea Tafelski, Jim Stewart, Danny Piechocki and Tatsuya Nakatani @ Paper Cra… https://t.co/96TutH27BF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanLSittler It's a very good point! Of course, it's also in that seems to be changing - I think I wrote letters f… https://t.co/CIYUSDfnfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoupleNexxtDoor Btw, what is "Reclaim Sex?" I tried goggling it, but I got very little help and nothing definitive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One down, one to go. Lengthy changeover coming right up ... #IAmHere (@ Dallas Fort Worth International Airport in… https://t.co/5E1OVw35Et]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to them St Aug boys. Y’all deserve it after that hard earned win. Goodluck  in the championship bring it back to the 504!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TangleF23 @scalzi It’s not that hard. Turn on autopay full balance. Tada! No debt, plus a bit of cash back depending on the card.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBC @guardian @csmonitor @washingtonpost @maddow @latimes @haaretzcom @sltrib @USATODAY @dwnews @lopezobrador_… https://t.co/JjjJJDzFyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto I stopped watching them especially Mika &amp; Glassless Joe ever since they took their obsession personal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allayva @therunchat @salguodmai That is important!! https://t.co/xkThbuxH93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iandschultz @JimCapsCup @AWallace39 I can see them maybe tinkering with it if they aren't getting more scoring fro… https://t.co/ApzGaFmyjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to my man Gary Martin and his Susquehanna Township  (suburban Harrisburg) boys high school basketball tea… https://t.co/Km2tcqsVFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PBrennanENQ Alexander not game fit, sorry. @LedeManu18 needs in at half.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebHarlow1 @hobbsisme It depends on the sport and the socioeconomic status of the athlete.   Some sports don’t g… https://t.co/CgTEMYctuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@premierleague @EASPORTSFIFA I dont have that kind of pack luck... who am I kidding? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I would be doing a disservice to his legacy if I didn’t also mention Kemper’s work shooting 1983’s “Mr. Mom” *a… https://t.co/AL00oU0HCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshtwist @fanatec @ForzaMotorsport @Formula1game @kellabyte Lots of them. Just no for Xbox 😁 Have to go PC for that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG.  I’m coining my own German word to explain something: Frustmusingressing- The feeling one gets when watching m… https://t.co/LJt6BKRINv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I love Alex Trebek. Even in the face of a grim situation, he's cracking jokes. A true Canadian/American treasur… https://t.co/r3oAYT8j8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PBandJPod @PeteButtigieg Here’s the link. Lol.  https://t.co/bXg892LUAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlyByKnite It’s honestly tough to watch cause it’s so cringeworthy. But yeah watch it for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronbeatyjr @USRepKeating You have no “God given right” to atttack (or to attack by insinuation) people on the basi… https://t.co/AiJijK5jTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is it! #TrueConfessions is back with @mulaney, Pete Davidson and Jimmy! 🙌🏽 #FallonTonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMr_Sharpton Gotta tell you it's been far harder to be a conservative than it ever was pitching in the big leag… https://t.co/nwrQIhzf5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[#myburgerlove on MY Birthday! Thanks guys. 😝@myburgerusa (@ My Burger in Saint Paul, MN) https://t.co/R4QgJVxTQ6 https://t.co/w6Pvu8RNuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheila_Copps The order of law is at issue #JWR decided there was wrong doing.  #indigenous jobs? (job loss consequ… https://t.co/9h3JmUbpys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBellaBosco Is it time for this? @truTVjokers https://t.co/6JGM4Donlr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LVSportsBiz @lvlightsfc Ask the Knights if you can put a @GoldenKnights sticker on the front of your book 📚💰💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenjaminSWatson Excellent idea. I’d watch it. Duck dynasty mixed w Kate + 8. Wonderful Watsons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yeah, like solar power tech. Oh wait, you killed that with your idiotic tariffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelSHolley @celtics Kyrie lost this team when he didn't show up while injured to support them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trae Young’s last 15 games 30/8 26/8   23/8  28/9 27/8 10/10 19/5 20/11 13/7 22/14 16/11 30/10 23/8 36/8 36/10 But… https://t.co/dLTzzrIybm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Past out last night but god was looking over my shoulder and my truck after I slid off the road into a tree🙏 thankf… https://t.co/ARNulRP8Qf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul @tastelikehaggis NEVER DISRESPECT A NATIONAL LEADER, EVEN IF HE WAS A MURDEROUS ASSHOLE. THE CURRENT 'ANAL ORIFICE' DOESN'T LIKE IT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, this Washington Establishment Neo-Con just called himself a classical liberal on the stage @CPAC . I’m praying… https://t.co/9YupzitoPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinReynoldsTV @Big2_Sports Puppy&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;baseball. Both are great but.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Mr Vice President.... not a chance I. Hell your ridiculous border wall will happen !]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is being the first D1 softball player to ever hit the HR cycle earn you Co-Player of the Week?  Hope the other… https://t.co/eecXvZ6azG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZionW32 likely out for Saturday's rematch against @UNC, but Coach K expects he'll be ready for @theACC. #ACC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Maybe all the actors should get an Oscar, just so everything is fair.... Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I was in the mall yesterday “we” still going crazy in saks and neimans 😂🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AritAmana @blkCodeCollctve @MomsCanCodePgh @DCFemTech @BekahHW @wesbos @WomenWhoCodeDC @ASpittel @littlekope0903 H… https://t.co/WgQCXHZDxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DroidsTV This is the only time I will agree with you. Yeah he ruined it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys who barbell row 135 with lifting straps on a smith machine then lat flex their tiny ass back in the mirror suck the biggest dicks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not getting married anytime soon But I hope she likes Lifehouse Hanging by a moment .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Why is this a story? It’s not like any of them will vote their conscience, they will fall in line behind… https://t.co/7y7XOwVZoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@exploringelise @livparz @noelle_parziale What can i say, my #Squirlies ... THIS makes me prod to be a #Longhorn… https://t.co/UHbE2vNcZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[At long last. Now I know which side to pick here (besides, India is the one buying oil from Maduro)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Tom Osborne; his greatness as a ball coach is matched only by his character and integrity.]]></document></documents></author>