<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Andrew McCabe and so many others were/are right about Donald Trump.  He cancelled INF Yteaty. Exactly what Putin wa… https://t.co/Ytbc5M8YEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lexa com Triku didn’t appreciate being killed off for “some spice” and neither did Lincoln]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think guys know this but this girl won’t settle for less anymore. I have zero problems cutting you off without hesitation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PadmaLakshmi @ManMet80 They should be forced to resign on their own accord.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Trump thinks he's the only liar out there 🤦🏽‍♀️😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old Nashville has been on a slow decline for a while. It’s officially dead. #ripgoldrush #rockblockforever… https://t.co/h7C5O7RDHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlakandBlack @43a6f0ce5dac4ea @fredcuy1 @Tafkao @hr4tvausnz @LindaDHoward @montaguethecat @AussieGen4 @CrankyRake… https://t.co/q5pIF4Iyjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved representing @DailyBrew at the #SJSU @prssasjsu Winter Career Fair! So much fun to go back to school, if only… https://t.co/oeGfPnNNMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[MACHINE TRADEMARK FROM CHINA          TO: "We the People"   ----  IF WE DON'T SCREAM LOUDER THAN WE'VE ALREADY BEEN… https://t.co/drvM0ZjjY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_thinking_funny It was all nice for me, even the rain! I came from snow-covered Eastern Washington😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oregon is apparently the land of 1,000 artisanal ketchups. I’m not pleased about that, but so far I’m also not disa… https://t.co/tllsD8SFO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisarinna I’ll take the Nice fun Rinna who doesn’t attach LVP and stir the 💩 thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Kids today. "You are so old"(me 46) "What are you like 30 or something like that?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was greeted by this rockstar on my way up heartbreak hill!! #tpsprepares #ilovemyjob https://t.co/MyDubvGLrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“All reports indicate that it is safe to drive on the roads.”-CCSD #8NN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frostgirl11 @NGDAverk @darker_dearie @AlliCamAllison @tweetNorvena @hjhollis93 @VillainPeterPan @Danielle21A… https://t.co/LrMUYN0ICQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone wants to watch @SimplyAJ10 play for the DBACKs, I have a spare room in my house.  We can go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summa cum nothing!!! Volume does NOT equate quality. His lies are obvious and predictable! 3rd grade level certainl… https://t.co/GmWjkuqq2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaded Sardines cooked with lemon, rosemary, garlic, oregano, and parsley. A small side salad and some cooked pota… https://t.co/YBhq16UiuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama Glad no more RIOTS SINCE YOU LEFT OFFICE GUESS TRUMP WONT PAY THEM TO DESTROY NEIGHBORHOODS LIKE YOU DID]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS Between your deficit numbers &amp; rocket man inspired, I'm ready for a long coma.]]></document><document><![CDATA[La forma de gobernar hoy de #LopezHablador es una combinación de priísmo setentero, con el marxismo que se enseñaba… https://t.co/CYd1OacepX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 @PinkPinkpetunia As a health care professional, I have been obsessed with HRC since 1991, especially he… https://t.co/Ap8R5jS0Lo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forcing a religion on your kids is wrong and dont be upset when they grow up and join another religion or become at… https://t.co/6wGFTU0mLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suziday123 @SLHLuxuryHotels @always5star @RoadtripC @RoarLoudTravel @MyVirtualVaca @TravelAtWill @RickGriffin… https://t.co/khZWF5REvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling supersonic, give me gin and tonic. @ The Rabbit Hole https://t.co/OkTi5y9yxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu acordei às 9:30, são 14:35, não comi NADINHA até agora. Mede o mau humor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahaha. What a bunch of numbnuts. If you can't cope then you should take ur meds. #TrumpBrokeTheirBrains]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanukioriginal 笑 あと、ファーストネームはイニシャルでラストネームだけ、かつM.D.だったりすると、もはやこの人は存在しないんだろうなと思ったりも。]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danidiaz73 Yeeeiii!!! Muchas gracias, les mando abrazos y ya les estaré contando qué tal va todo ✌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[That sucks. But it doesn’t change the fact that your play in no way helps autistic people. When one of the “poor pa… https://t.co/rjsH4GqcsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealScrambledYE @SusannaLHarris @UNCeship @Ph_D_epression @johndchisholm @garyvee I apologize, I spelled your name… https://t.co/NheucJFj0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello yes i’m depressed as hell but at least i’m depressed at disneyland 🙃🙃🙃💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DirectionersRok @itsavarose_ @Complex I don't want to fight either I'm terrible at texting. If you go on Ava's twi… https://t.co/WtIeo4R8ij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scrolling through Twitter this AM has my brain going. Stay tuned. May or may not piss off some folks with my opinion... oh well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alisoncook There used to be so much more 😔 Now it’s like 3 publications]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Imagine the Earth As A Rhombus by @StickmanBrews/@HiddenRiverBrew at @hiddenriverbeer — https://t.co/AwGvxl3NGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GISRockstar @nextspaceflight @johnkrausphotos About to post....ummmm....it went 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dropped @Jaquebooya and katecowper88 at the starting line of the #zionhalfmarathon and drove to the finish line. Go… https://t.co/ISnorwJyOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[For someone that never drinks, it takes way too much alcohol to get me drunk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FiddleSabre I love it because my Dad, who was a Buffalo city kid always wanted to be a cowboy. He’s 76 and I think… https://t.co/Ets8Bvvmkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: NYC just instituted groundbreaking new legal guidelines that would make it illegal for any workplace or scho… https://t.co/oFfpyscZtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance Does Donald Trump control our country's entire budget?  Can he just give away our money?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Golf is so old white man No one will be playing it in 10 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump I can’t believe a president said THAT! A PRESIDENT???!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tictoc @splcenter Wow... you’re strategic timing won’t work this time.🙄🙄🙄 https://t.co/nAvbXAEyxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#c89robandmegan #toomanydrinks #touringwithrobandmegan @ Reif Estate Winery https://t.co/oXL1zMHkHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing thicker thighs come in clutch for is warming my freezing hands, I’m over this cold weather.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter Maybe he should have supported the ACA and Medicaid expansion. https://t.co/uEq7WGjg0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[| Everyday style | 🌿 This is always a go too look for me, so easy and classic! My sweater is under $20! These black… https://t.co/Ares5XOtY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Valeriad90 @caitlin__cara @justkate0910 @NatalieAsorey @EricaGeorge My top favorites are @HowIBuiltThis,… https://t.co/6KabaHZCUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[3:15 &amp; I’m watching YouTube videos of people trying Disneyland food #wishitwasme]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Augusta, GA #Legal job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: Staff Attorney at City of Augusta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, @mkhan1969! Looking forward to seeing what you do with your new skills! #Python #geospatial #dataviz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportShelly paid a visit to Neblett Elementary this afternoon. Inspired kids to keep trying. @swhorowitz… https://t.co/DQ9NI7ZuVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge calls new hearing on gag order after Roger Stone's inflammatory post - CNN Politics https://t.co/Wwj74NBhyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonaldAbeyta @JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump 😂😂🍊💩🤡lock that piece of 💩 up impeach that. 🤡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman Sick, sick, sick. He should be castrated. Pathetic POS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Gosnell: Murder, Abortion and the Movie You Weren’t Supposed to See via @PhelimMcAleer https://t.co/nNc1JfG3rM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catebatman @kyouryokusenshi @rainknight It’s always been my head canon that’s he’s loaded but never wanted anythin… https://t.co/I4F1HzZxar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Author Vi Keeland wrote, “If you want to know where your heart is, look where your mind goes when it wanders.” . .… https://t.co/ccpDCSh9md]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys don’t understand the amount of happiness I am feeling to FINALLY meet my best friend 😭💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Back during the war, when @realDonaldTrump was fighting? Oh hahahahaha, that’s not what you mean at all!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latinmassuk This did indeed hsppen in the states.  My St. Louis, MO 📺 station broadcasted where you could go for "drive through" ashes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MSN @muhriyahhh remember that lady in the hospital with my mama?  That made her stop smoking]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Cheetos 2. Barbecue Lays 3. Cooler Ranch Doritos 4. Regular Lays 5. Fritos  6. Nacho Cheese Doritos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sexi_Red6 They’re doing great! Send me ur number again, are you still doing that thing u sent me? Imma text you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been so at ease and unbothered about something in my life.. literally no tears to cry and it’s great. An… https://t.co/QHpezVMckX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenryLouisGates I can’t wait to see this episode. Great list of guests! #FindingYourRoots]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadJynErso @acagoldsmith Ya that's why I didn't even conceive of it without this post- but who knows- maybe a hid… https://t.co/5NmBGNDgcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dariusrucker Beautiful day for the Arnold Palmer invitational https://t.co/LhYYzOEGAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was last month’s winner and that gift card for coffee hit the spot on cold Chicago mornings! #PantherPRIDE… https://t.co/1iq4QkVbZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big winning from the night...Jackson and guinea pig, Dylan with killer glasses and other cool stuff....AND my Beani… https://t.co/A2McA8JcV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twerking too much friday night lead me to having to limp because I’m sore af 😂😂🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rodrigo Andrade &amp;  Juan Martin Nero Grand Championns Polo Team. World Polo League  Wellington, Florida https://t.co/2sUBoSVGt0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time  The old question of time.   We all have 24 hours in a day yet some of us still say we struggle with time. Tim… https://t.co/LG9OUN0AQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @LindseyGrahamSC @Lagarde @MorganOrtagus Incestous puta go away]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it begins! #CRT #CRT2019 @ron_waksman @JackieLGreenMD @ChetcutiStan https://t.co/MfxwhIT5LN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBsBeasties OMGOMGOMGOMG ITS KILLING ME THAT I CANT SEE IT BUT IM SO HAPPY ♥️♥️♥️ https://t.co/cDBzxfa0Aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stars were shining a lil brighter, tonight  ✨ https://t.co/eCZeCOZMnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to survive as a single mom, with no child support or family assistance, and raise a strong, healthy and compass… https://t.co/5YNq6XMbDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[So next week’s episode brings back the Miss Mystic Falls pageant #Legacies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corrcomm @CBSNews 7 hours ago they are still posting this garbage?  Lord help us!]]></document><document><![CDATA[NASA will send an all-woman team on a historic spacewalk on March 29  https://t.co/psUG2wov5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another crash, this time on 495 NB in #Milford. Two lanes blocked after EX 20 - debris all over roadway. @wbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gracyy_c y’all I love ❤️ your life is my love 😍 now please thank you 🙏 please let me know if I have any thank for… https://t.co/i4JfsXZxuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pura vergonha. A nação rubro negra deve estar revoltada com o clube Flamengo. Pelo pouco caso que fez no tribunal c… https://t.co/tqvwe6o6tY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uhg... I'm about tape a dryer sheet to my dogs ass...  So every time he farts, there will be a slighter chance it could be tolerable.... 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every athletes instagram story right now:  Nominated by Ashley I nominate Megan, Brittney, &amp; Katie!!🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is he in office? Can you move to the Central Valley please in Cali?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RzosaJune @Speedee19 @hessbrass @mattrob74779817 @RepAdamSchiff @AOC if you think the caravans are full of nice po… https://t.co/8vZofErK97]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinproudusa @WanderlushVibes @CNN You don’t seem either educated or open-minded, Kevin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope my sisters &amp; friends know I think about them all the time. no bs. I just be so busy. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot wait for life to work out, and for my soulmate &amp; I to be happy together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATT @JanelleMonae @NBAAllStar Really bad company making it impossible to get internet!  They will not talk to me b… https://t.co/bwaGvD2iur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rudepundit They will get raptured up and everybody else, Jews included, get left behind.  Actually, it might be really good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @jetrotter I beg to differ—we’re just raising awareness of her socialist agenda!—And her hypocrisy !!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitch_Pink  caught this on stream and I thought it was to cute 💕 https://t.co/TWbsGmo5iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScanCouver Lower back spasms. Can't move well. Flared last night while unpacking.   First time since alone that it… https://t.co/tsxW1H0sZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Kim knows that Trump responds to flattery so he has poured it on and it definitely is wor… https://t.co/TUHhEBKU4D]]></document></documents></author>