<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This reflects poorly on ALL the citizens of Virginia. They aren’t speaking up nor taking action. Therefore, we can… https://t.co/YohiAahKEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WVUhoops, @CoachHuggs  once a Mountaineer always a Mountaineer!    I live in Pittsburgh but my team always will be… https://t.co/s8tnmhLSHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerjbjohnston Leafs haven't made a cup appearance since there were only 6 teams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I meet someone new, I never listen to them when they tell me their name. Causes some issues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swansblunt Unfortunately when someone says something  to you, your mind stores it away.Others say I love support y… https://t.co/shZ5dt2z8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIFE IS SHORT! If you don’t know Jesus there is no better time to know Him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 2018 Indy 500 was the probably the most boring compared to recent years, BUT it is still 20x better than the re… https://t.co/SvqgPnGLpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been so fortunate to be mentored by talented, brilliant women in my PhD and career: @ITS_UCDavis’s Susan Handy… https://t.co/tDDAAHYpwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurnettRM @startrekcbs I have no idea (and not a lot of faith) in how the Spock story is going to work out but Ans… https://t.co/IDzKHImgra]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your bestie comes to visit you from Boston, you’ve got to take a pic. Yes, it’s to look like this. @ Los Angel… https://t.co/FaII3Qt5p0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KRowan15 @mitchellvii @FoxNews Would it shock you to learn that Muslims also believe in God?]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 Cx making out on my furniture they better go get a room @ Amsterdam Bar And Restaurant https://t.co/f7wVFXIEIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow this is excellent. Wish I bought more than one. Didn’t realize the ABV was 10.5% when I got it! - Drinking an E… https://t.co/ZblqHsez8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Witty Belgian Witbier by @SavRivBrewCo @ Savannah River Brewing Co. — https://t.co/AwCbuX2Esf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexandraAnne72 @SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump @SpeakerPelosi She's a stupid idiot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobmaxon @ryanhanrahan looking like a solid inch of pure snow for once in Manchester!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Launching Tuesday, March 5th 2019 at 10pm EST All-New Radio Show "Asi Viene El Sandwich" via @LaMezclaDotCom… https://t.co/CYYPxh4ezV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier this week I attended the grand opening social of the new event venue @520onthewater in Downtown Sanford! Th… https://t.co/oPHxhx6hh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow is collecting and visibility is reducing at the Lawrence service area I-70 eastbound. https://t.co/11Jxi0ljem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President, the failed fast train project in CALIFORNIA? Isn’t that where these politicians are… https://t.co/wO1vmw7dTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper Helped along by Our Former Dear Leader's Contribution of $11.2 tril. All of a sudden, the… https://t.co/WvmVuzFCeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[...when a rep-rig gets repoed. Lol Just saying... @ America/Los Angeles https://t.co/NXkMu2JRmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[mom just texted me that i’ll have two fur babies waiting for me at home in two weeks. i’m so ready]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo comprando online por el feriado de #PresidentsDay https://t.co/h7MDvFB0Lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do love when two security forces meet in plain cloths, identify each other as the threat, realize what just happe… https://t.co/4nSkG0kisV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebron has played over 100 more games than MJ too. In a league where defense is rare. Nice try tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magi-Whirl 2019 Gala Public Show 4/13/19 info at https://t.co/4aXDatDdEU #FamilyEntertainment #Magic https://t.co/h9j7J4yrjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm supporting Children's Miracle Network Hospitals Dance Marathon! https://t.co/CCtvhkanEF via @DonorDrive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaz_KY @rgunns Zero chance they didn't intend for the media to go crazy with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeyhemLauren Well good 4 you! I'm takin' a dump, reading your tweet! So what's next!🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw the incomparable @PaulNicklen speak this evening in #Phoenix and was awed and moved by his photos, videos, and… https://t.co/EIuXrS999E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to get our worship on #Walk4Water Sunday #HLChurch @ Ham Lane church of Christ https://t.co/zAHNtYMSTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny that you said 6K x 3K. Which makes total sense. I had been reading it as 6K for $3k. @marcoarment @siracusa @caseyliss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta make it back to these games next year! Been about a decade since my last OHSAA state tournament game... 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yellow-bellied marmot sketch study. Do you have a favorite animal that lives in the Rockies? Have you even been to… https://t.co/vXDG0nGvJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Changes for the #OleMiss starting lineup for Sunday:  - Gindl to start at RF - Servideo back at 2B   Gunnar Hoglund… https://t.co/zQDflYYAMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCrawford70 @boozychef That's really cool. No one in my family ever used one that I know of. Looking on Amazon, I'… https://t.co/TSdI63RZNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickDaKick @KjellConnelly @RutSpence4 @robmtaub @DiamondandSilk @realDonaldTrump @POTUS His people think trump mag… https://t.co/FNP6AsQSXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattsdriscoll @JM_Murf @thenewstribune Yep. I read both of those, on my to looking for the coverage of the address.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ianfisher86 Just caught up. Wow. And here I was starting to like Carmella hahaha. Crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come to think of it, the cartoon was probably my first introduction to Beetlejuice]]></document><document><![CDATA[You wanna know what's sad? You can give everything you have to a person And you can be perfect for that person You… https://t.co/CzcUukxoWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy day @ #thebestjukejointupnorth #sledding @ Lavigne Tavern https://t.co/wnP1jGYEQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RowenaMonde @oldtimer1968 Better, we had a bad bull, he got out police in our yard, we loaded him, but scary, big… https://t.co/xMxpewxprv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for sharing the impact of @PLTWorg across the nation all the way to Alaska @dlash09!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I am noticing a bit of a pattern here: brutal, corrupt and murderius Dictators are good and should… https://t.co/E3629XGGKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @ResargNivek @jennerific713 @realDonaldTrump Kiss ass I see! https://t.co/vGyl88VQCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhpostman @zacko343 @itwaslibby @TimBallTim @ChrisannDawson @darlad99 @threatsr @FridgenW @SRowe1978… https://t.co/UKhauynpQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[En #IslandOfAdventure #Orlando #Florida 🇺🇸 con Mi Sandrita @sandri92 https://t.co/v7efVUiKpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoblinShop @btv_25 @lancgal @jbendery @NRA You got such a wonderful way of saying they're fucking liars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetterkennyProb All dressed bud. #Buffalo #Letterkenny #NoProblemsHereBud https://t.co/Mo9PlulyhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngryBlackLady Who ?  Do you mean the daughter of that President who was erased from history ?   Don’t care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Bronze Helmet by @SpartanBrewpub @ Spartan Brewpub — https://t.co/mRMJMTWmVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MunicCK Take the kids ice fishing while you can  https://t.co/BeQOHF4cw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Ja Morant for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/b4OZb41JYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Hour with mrgustafik ! 🍺🍺🍺 #californialiving #birthday #notMYbirthday @ Nick's Restaurant https://t.co/Q79JN89UCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old retired Euro player is on the opposing team!?  Oh no's!!!!  #UniteAndConquer #HailUnited #ATLUTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[“North Carolina's elections board Thursday ordered a new election in the nation's last undecided congressional race… https://t.co/a4lChidCbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green Lantern armor had some set backs. Will try out a template so I can learn how to make some better armor. Will… https://t.co/BXwFWmFRcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/y8G9B2HRrQ #iamkingspydamann #fedsqad #atlantahitmakers #whereskingspydamann #totallyawesomemystycman… https://t.co/yWdE5ikM0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most players when they decide to leave a team, just leave ... Antonio Brown is burning every bridge he can before h… https://t.co/9Hc8EXMSAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Are you with us?’:  Bloomberg calls in his chits https://t.co/wQgdow3iDw via @politico]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow along on @Genius as you sing my debut single “Zealous” https://t.co/ll7gM2XYog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GmanFan45 @MarciaHallThom1 The biggest reason was that he thought this charade of his would "put him on the map" b… https://t.co/CIGnUtVsLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican circle https://t.co/E4Zvabpcc2 wonder Jordan looks so at home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’ll have all the block-rocking beats he can handle in the thereafter. #Prodigy #music #hrmusicshare   https://t.co/mUi5aJwYcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a rider, to go down and slide up I hope you can handle a shift stick, babe, cause you gotta drive it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green New Deal? More Like New Green Deal lol they are trying to figure out a way to milk new money out of the American people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dropsofjmw move??? i mean, of course. i’d be able to be out there with you 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro there’s nothing worse than getting stuck behind a family that doesn’t know what they want at @ChipotleTweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some photos of the amazing rainbow stretching over Casa de Shamhausen yesterday. https://t.co/mVV7PSgV0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom used to make these all the time during the summer 😩 add some sugar on top]]></document><document><![CDATA[They don’t make them like Kobe no more. Literally had a bunch of guys from the Local 24HrFitness as his teammates.… https://t.co/0usRQxsKEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smkeena49 @r4iderz4life Those moves you mentioned probably have zero effect on Kings W/L record, not sure I get the argument.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleMeagher1 @_Philly_Talk @Nelson81 @EricBogart1 @Phillies @gabekapler How about now you stupid fuck?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmacharlotte I want to rub your legs I want to rub your arms I want to rub your thighs nuclear weapon boner I wan… https://t.co/Ua6uLhYCFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[bishopmooreathletics  @letsgohornets  osvarsity #BishopMoore #Hornets 🐝 #Orlando BOTH Girls and Boys Varsity… https://t.co/L2rGcw7XAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the smoothest, or the quickest, of flights, but #NHLDucks are on the ground at #LAX. Quick turnaround, with… https://t.co/11kkF7TwLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heat were down 10 to start that 4th quarter. LBJ, Chalmers, Birdman, Allen and Miller were on the floor together fo… https://t.co/BEuF5pBv3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[This like the 3rd or 4th time this year I went triple aluminum so thanks or the support]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apopey Which might be one of the better things that could happen to them - and English football.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emily_Welford @peggybvick we are so done. y’all will never find me with that piece of junk again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Count not the days. Rather make the days count 💜 #happySunday #goodVibes #carpeDiem #quotes @ Chez Weggeland https://t.co/jgody5hg7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewdugger4 @BarstoolTenn 26 minutes into the game ky was only called for 6 fouls and had a big lead, damage done]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @RepJuanVargas Just because someone else criticizes someone’s remarks doesn’t mean that First Amendment r… https://t.co/7LwWJjoeKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff I can be fired for stealing a pencil from work and yet tRump can do the most despicable, unethical,… https://t.co/UgffZeDGoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanS27441765 I was in the Marine Corps reserves. Did a 7 month tour in Al Asad Iraq driving resupply convoys. I… https://t.co/urUNBM3MLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The directors hanging out or working. Either way... damn they all look good! @ALL4HNW  team always thinking of bett… https://t.co/Sf11BtLuwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiveFromLiz @daveweigel @SherrodBrown Student LOANS aren't "free money" and, as a self employed carpenter, I've be… https://t.co/ltnMX26nLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricChandler4 @KevMan4Real @SpeakerPelosi I call bs no way a native Americans get forcefully kept from the polls w… https://t.co/LpBUgq4zsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe I haven’t seen this movie yet. Ending the weekend checking out @PopstarMovie and it’s already ridicul… https://t.co/lHmpPJBIUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyPAnderson 3) Because it impairs our spiritual faculties, and because we are limited to begin with, we can't r… https://t.co/oXS4kFx8xV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__Faraz @musicnewsfact Because you can’t handle it all at once. You’ll need a breather.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcDenis_RDS @PierreHoudeRDS kinkaid bonne nuit va finir 7 a 1 Julien voulais la perdre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darla_Crane It would be hard to walk around the piles of poop in heels]]></document><document><![CDATA[These la girls all wear Gia the label  And dolls kill that they sharecrop on depop  They could never understand the drip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, I understand it’s a trope.  But guess what? Nobody is saying Jews (specifically) have some secret double loya… https://t.co/FxRjdXa098]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Grant603 @GageTenebris @CHSommers @USATODAY You may not live in a cave but she'll damn sure need a club. Bull… https://t.co/4nXRGPkkdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moverseesvivir @pedroferriz3 A sacar a los chavistas antes de que. Venezualicen México]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cal5k @MaryJanekeao @cowboytexas @MSNBC Yeah, we're kinda waiting for those, and it's been four @#$%ing years.]]></document></documents></author>