<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[When you updated your website at work and it goes down. Your backup files are at home.  #happytuesday https://t.co/hIUf10ogAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: Leaked Photos Show U.S. Border Facility Overwhelmed by Migrants https://t.co/Prvw7nYxHc via @BreitbartTexas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLMWHB @OfficialMHF How many babies are planning to run down w helicopter. You pretty darn awful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemodogsandCats @DawkinsDog @davidfrum Yup. And if the K1 says Moe Larry and Curly LLC, might want to do some investigating😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @verizon says “2 day shipping” you order on Sunday. They ship on Thursday. And you won’t get it until Monday.… https://t.co/hp9lZ9v5Uq]]></document><document><![CDATA[inhumane things done to them, not to mention the assault these things did to their very dignity as human beings...b… https://t.co/PJXhpW3FKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker Organic hot dog. Gluten free bun. Mustard, relish &amp; onions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@henyome I honestly like Japanese dubs for English shows/movies too lol. They are usually acted out well and even t… https://t.co/36jh2wXEi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can really tell a lot about a person from the friend activity section on spotify]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though me and Josh aren’t married yet, I’m still Tania’s auntie 🤣 and my niece looks just like her momma 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if I was his mama and saw this on tv I would’ve beat his ass 😂 “ice cream”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Based_Jedi A couple of those look like they could be from a Death Metal album 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a glimpse of VERY LONG DAY.... more to come. @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/h09pC22T3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to win #Whiskey43Special and don’t forget to RT to win!! #lovenascar #nascar500]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek fact check David Brennan’s McCabe book review released today. Jeff Sessions is a former Alabama Senator,… https://t.co/idpqppsRpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be totally honest.....I’m not sure Bernie Sanders should have thrown his hat in the pool of Dem candidates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cassandraEspir 3235217721 texteame primera consulta GRATIS   #florida #usa #estadosunidos #eeuu #penbrokepines… https://t.co/1nzJE0r6NX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PucciaPatrizia @mich_onelove @Jose93571656 @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @gabryluce @consuiglesias @GizellaGerics1… https://t.co/bhK2xLNCey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Readying for jewelry show #deliciouscolors #gorgeousgems #jewelrydesigner #handmade #purplesandgreens 💎💎💎 @ Brookly… https://t.co/cwRuMdyhnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dios es bueno nos sorprende cada  día, de la nada hace cosas maravillosas increíbles en nuestras vidas 😍 saludos bendiciones Buen día✨💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexMcDaniel Apparently this program/coach in Kansas are super abusive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ILAToday A teacher surveyed her students and the top 2 things that got them excited about reading was visits to th… https://t.co/0occRuMVaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kp_1318 @EliasToufexis @Charlyp12345 @str8toutoftampa @RobElgasABC7 @ABC7Chicago The fleshy part of the thigh.  Th… https://t.co/hQV3bUtugt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely just bought a salad and 2 packages of oreos. I feel like they'll eventually balance each other out 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dublin film festival: Matt Bomer loves the ‘Irish spirit’ https://t.co/hUoN3nmIOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend said “ i can’t believe i went to a public expensive school and had to wear a uniform . Made me feel poor”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UltaAndwea @jocelynszul1 Both taken at @LibertyU https://t.co/9nDWEIeBIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #ValentinesDay ❤️💋 We are open until 9pm. #selflove #treatyoself #valentines #vday #vdaygifts #valentinesgift… https://t.co/AAqWbNqcvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which design is preferred for making a couple pillows🤔 https://t.co/C3f9qQV9nP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t describe what it’s like to listen to Lincoln Ragsdale talk about his life in Phoenix during the Civil Right… https://t.co/KtFfXR5Ghg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/EXVo6i1BpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaxonThegn @GovMikeHuckabee @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse ❄️ poor, pitiful wittle Snowflake ❄️  read ‘n weepy some… https://t.co/kDp9SL2BS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA  Where was Lara Spencer at the Oscars today???? Another gma snub!!! @LaraSpencer]]></document><document><![CDATA[You all look amazing! Can’t wait to see who wins Summit &amp; a Globie! #TheBestComeFromSTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jenifer Lewis addresses Jussie Smollett at Essence's Black Women in Hollywood luncheon - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/hpnb8TJVlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias @JaimeConcha10 por entrevista en @BuenosDiasTVN y por tu permanente compromiso con las víctimas silenciosas… https://t.co/Bb9rOMHtfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse Moral of the story:  don’t run for President if you committed some serious crimes in your “past life”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You have no idea what you are talking about. Per usual.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously if u want to see what’s going on in my life then friend request me again.  I know u are on my page on the… https://t.co/TdPvhIMP0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to NY in a month around times square and Central Park, what are some (food especially) places I NEED to go?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grade 5 Intergenerational Program at Maple Grove!! Making Valentine’s with our friends!@PeelSchools @SpringbrookPS https://t.co/5Pbk6M19Ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday! Are you feeling irritaded, nostalgic, tired and or too conscientious of life? Blame it on the solar s… https://t.co/8vxXp9hNDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[rest in peace to the loves of my life, one album was not enough. you will be missed.  https://t.co/UwC44Sy0DH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngrierWHStaff Eat less meat. Is that what he is getting at ?  Would be funny if it wasn’t sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO, TELL THEM TO GO TO THE INN AT WISE TODAY. #lovelylucyspopup #pickyourpetals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jewelosco I am in the immediate care after an accident in your store.  They didn't give me an incident report.  I… https://t.co/nod4pnioI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[One World Trade Center - awe inspiring. @ One World Trade Center https://t.co/5h7AUGh4Nb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WesternMastery @Kajabi Its software.  Love it and been using it since 2012.   Are you looking to create your first online program?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Annual carve_4_cancer Winter Festival Weekend at @skibluemountain Raising funds to support Leukemia, Lymphoma and M… https://t.co/e7PO9cWGxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other reason I came to Louisiana (beignets). @ Ville Platte, Louisiana https://t.co/m7kZmdgkWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt Yup. We already forgot about this chick https://t.co/SBfOUly4rA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Deflection, your " Go-to" defense.' YOU' and you alone Stated Kim Jung UN knew nothin regarding th… https://t.co/SIUTNAtK6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garyvee Excellent!! In teaching a personal branding class to Realtors in Spain next month and this comes in handy!! 🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC I’m so sorry for your loss. Our mom’s are special and, no matter our age, the pain of losing her is like no… https://t.co/0AFpF0JbVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must learn not to worry concerning the cares of our lives for God cares us Pray and Believe and All Will B Well N Jesus Name Amen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenedictDonald_ @Perpetual_Now @Jim_Jordan Gym Jordan is a creepy lying non protector of anyone including kids exc… https://t.co/kmJwU0Ikyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Sprouts Farmers Market - @sproutsfm in Santee, CA https://t.co/Z6TRDBNt3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[B2: Wild pitch scores another run for the Toros, 11-1. #azpreps365 #azhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boycott anything made in the State of Wisconsin, We are done playing games , Stand United People, @WisDOJ ,… https://t.co/Pl3baN2Dok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missyrussell81 Their all stupid.. and whoever thought of it should be bitched slapped! We no longer have slaves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @zoiesmith_ . I hope you have a great day! https://t.co/ffU4Q3tcN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Custom fashion pieces = costly. One person is doing the job of an entire factory with specifications to your exact… https://t.co/hl7Ceu2bip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollierSZLive @zklemmeADI 1983 was my last district tourney and it was at West. We won. 🎉. Beat West in the first… https://t.co/UhNzCN2DRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Person in my right ear just said, "Woman, I get paid to torture you. " I'm in excruciating pain in my mouth. They'r… https://t.co/R2k5JEwMZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay, my movie OILDALE is coming out! Join us at the premiere in Bakersfield https://t.co/qOtZgvKYiZ #oildale… https://t.co/aqDQkw8ex8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TechyMargaret @InsightTimer I also have BREATHE app on my watch! Takes time to stop and chill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToastFundraiser I'll have to read more about the kind of automation you mean. I just have never seen any results f… https://t.co/BqFVMXcrQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micahuetricht @gmarlowe1917 @BernieSanders @OaklandEA Sure Micah, yuk it up? His is not a pro-working class record… https://t.co/V3wy2JSheK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 Rosanne is not mentally stable. When I saw the video of her current rant, she looked horrible. I serious… https://t.co/iLjzPEnHeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Officially took the plunge and signed up for some #improv classes! 🤩😬 #secondcity #hollywood #voiceover]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police don’t witness the overwhelming vast majority of incidents because people call the police during or after an… https://t.co/m6Tlo0FqLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM DYING OMG😂😂😂 The amount of times I wake up during the night and think I see Momo standing in the corner is sad😂😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathrynresister There are a great many of us who are #VeteransAgainstTrump who served this country. We love our co… https://t.co/z1omEGbzhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch this👇insightful video @PwC_Canada #CEO @nicolasmarcoux on #CEOSurvey focus on #client preferences and use of… https://t.co/POke3eQhwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinmwhitaker He’s so terrible that I adore him, even if he stole @fran_cervelli’s song.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New music 🎶 &amp; video 🎥 from @followBBB coming soon !  #brianbuckleyband]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUSPress Very good that POTUS is reining in the intolerance on campuses. Brenton was an example &amp; brought this to the forefront.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what I’m SO sick of ??? People using prayer as an excuse for things. Maybe stop saying “The Lord told me..… https://t.co/yNERJB3J3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Cuando no se tiene nada bueno que decir, lo mejor es no decit nada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's humor all around us. #comedy #tee-hee #smile #clever https://t.co/jjr2Xft33G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a fun workout for your Saturday! 🍑 ⁣ ⁣ Complete each exercise then move to the next, 4x or 5x, depending on… https://t.co/Yd9h399pvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched a guy ride a bull tonight, the kids name was Lane, he was a dang good hand, wore a black felt hat, red trim… https://t.co/5l1dG3IpNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faint show of northern lights in Graceville MN 2-28 @BobVanDillen @StormHour @FOX9 @weatherchannel @AMHQ… https://t.co/E8QNr1gZP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[KIPP Charter tells their story at @MOEducation  When does the Board get to hear great stories from the schools that… https://t.co/Qu5bjL9LZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took these while standing in a downpour and girls STILL think they can compete with me. Wow. https://t.co/q5k3LRkTDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[💁🏾‍♀️An absolute beauty! 👰🏾 Bridal makeup 💄 by me! 💙Send the brides my way! 💍 #memphishairstylist… https://t.co/DEXTFfbEx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DashawnJ_ Girl meets world was really good! What are you talking about ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else get annoyed how if you have your flashlight on and open Snapchat their flashlight turns off???🤬🤬🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsRamiMalek deserved it!!!! So let’s stomp stomp clap😉 for him!!! and I’m so proud of you happy for you and I lov… https://t.co/ufkPIPnAwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for sharing @AndyKalbaugh. “Really listening to what people have to say and and having an open mind about di… https://t.co/zOpKx3Bjq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom’s in town for my birthday and she requested I cook up one of her favorite dishes, pasta primavera. Someone’s be… https://t.co/zHnGNeYqjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DenaliWinter he literally stalks and preys on drunk women and people still defend him because he got in good with a few influential people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 You know people like Roseanne Barr are sad. She needs attention so bad, she does not care how she gets i… https://t.co/ndtknwblol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 May death come to all that threaten the U.S. with Socialism and Jihadism and denegrate the Jews. Mossad… https://t.co/0PJtBBjSHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babyabell @adrishellie @ericacaseyy @KatiVanOrder That was me this morning!! 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cenewman0 Don’t forget Cherokee Rock Village, little River Canyon, high falls, and all the other amazing state and national parks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FULL TRAILER IS HERE INJECT THIS ENTIRE SERIES INTO MY VEINS AND DO MICHAEL BENNETT NEXT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ah_ra_cho @AERADivJGradNet @ashegrads @firstgendocs Thank you for sharing this! It was a fantastic read and challe… https://t.co/VtU5KfjAPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at Arundel for the Wrestling county championships — semifinals and finals day.   Here are your team scores bef… https://t.co/9D5yP9GeSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMAxlaw I have chips and donuts around me and it’s so hard for me to not think about it]]></document></documents></author>