<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Trombone Choir preparing for the 11am service at St. John’s UMC in downtown @RockHillSCCity this morning. Catch it… https://t.co/8waFCUsxny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Johnathan_Wood1 Yeah that he has been free from off season surgeries is a sign of good things to come for a class act]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I said this last time but I’ll say it again: there is no way Trump is going to get played by Kim at this summit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorldOfStu should point out the vitriolic language of the press using the term #explosive - I feel #targeted]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my opinion as MUCH as I love 90’s anime. I swear almost every anime during like mid 2000’s was a different type… https://t.co/jO6i7iimi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bajablasted__ I stared at this for a long time trying to decide if you were standing in a bath tub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtygob @AdrianDeLaGarza @elnorte @multimediostv dos años y no pueden arreglar esto, cuanto tiempo mas? https://t.co/aArdiB1JfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slim_mirokujin @Surisskeptic @Lead1225 Not the same, you are not backing your assertion that what SJ did happens a… https://t.co/yDMCaOM80Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meesh_626 @v_cakes I don’t believe Wade. Not saying I don’t believe everyone. But I don’t believe Wade. He approac… https://t.co/92JIsiqCmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horrible goaltending call against @KarlTowns by @NBA officials. Ball never even went above the rim and was bouncing… https://t.co/ewx83VmfSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notvlove87 Jeff Fisher got my family season tickets in the South Endzone, best seats in the house]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAFrench Thanks for sharing. It's touching to see someone he never personally meet in his heart for so long.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @HawkofNewYork @prageru Where did u get that dummy at lol that was funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidENorman @jesush1979 @jcorippo @kat_goyette @RothmanCS @LisaTeachesTech @EdTechAntics @AndersonEdTech… https://t.co/fjzC8F6M08]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_theAMANDAshoo @sblpodcast on Twitter and Instagram  https://t.co/HTphxXakzP  Spotify -https://t.co/TkH7RuoFTC  iH… https://t.co/7GCrQ9T7XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebJKirch @NorseReport @atmcdonald34 Can cloning pass compliance? We have the technology, so like 2036 we could st… https://t.co/AMtN35SzkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHerd @ColinCowherd @JonGoulet @gregtoohey @JoyTaylorTalks @jasonrmcintyre  https://t.co/uVObHqmSmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom told me “ You’re working very hard”   I said “Thank you mom. This is only the beginning” 💯🔥  Much love to al… https://t.co/lhUGolW63h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wellnotreally2 @TheJuanWilliams @realDonaldTrump @thehill Diverse meaning who and what Muslims, Liars , criminals… https://t.co/4mFA5GURIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highs and lows, ups and downs, smiles and frowns, joy and pain. If you’re living a life that sounds that all simila… https://t.co/Mo8hF0tvzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is like buying a new car and then just absolutely crushing it into a 7/11 at 2 am cause you hit the wrong peta… https://t.co/1ibORmOQqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Racist politicians: racism is dead and not a current event issue.                                              Real… https://t.co/oNYx6EvDGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dQcQb @Whatevah_Amy 🤔now I have been called eccentric before it must be the adult term for “special “ as I was referred to as a youth 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safe_its I believe he was looking for messages. I told my wife he will be fine, he is just confused. He was probab… https://t.co/rwTZOZ7n7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisPower1 @AOC https://t.co/4gGuB9fZi5.Viewers.  Please leave them@be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexandria Ocasio Cortez read a prepared script given to her by the Democrats. Her questions were simply repetitive… https://t.co/0xaY184JYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews Shocking that he's sporting a red MAGA hat. #LeastShockingThingEver]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReadDavidCase @PrincessBravato From the Opening statement of Michael Cohen, "Donald Trump is a man who ran for off… https://t.co/4VlOyO646f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay , this makes more sense than just the flash headlines on this news item.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizbethCaro07 Americo Vespucci " el verdadero descubridor y navegante de #America .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oikonomos1983 @RedesAMLOMX @leozuckermann @Qlerator @Reforma @lopezobrador_ Y quien le paga al reforma????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creative director of @kitsune liked my pic! 🤩  ..I would like to thank God and the Academy for this great honor... https://t.co/Nv3mAXNgly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pulpjedi @Lons @MurrellDan I win!  lol gotta love the subjectivity of the subjective vs objective fiasco.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To act like this is a new issue with society is funny. People have been defending terrible people for decades.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentines is upon us...so I picked out some romantic to watch while she blows me...being evil is awesome :)… https://t.co/5HltrogKej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OD_Birnell Not criticizing the writer. Simply making a point on how quickly and drastically things change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just as Trump has fired n purged n smeared all who Comey snicthed as witnesses against him. Damn Shame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rubyredlexxi You available for a one hour session in Oak around 9PM. I have wanted to have my tongue in...well you… https://t.co/JyV1rkFJhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[No sleep til #Brooklyn. @BernieSanders returns to the borough where he was born to launch his #Election2020 campaig… https://t.co/RRfIhFZ25x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bohemianmoon @CariniGambarini @CNNPolitics Wouldn’t say FDR was too liberal. Though Teddy’s attack on big businesses was more in my liking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's a real smart ass @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/iSOStzfcL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandfather Isidore Zerlin — for whom I’m named and sadly never knew — seemed like quite the charmer. @ Santa Ca… https://t.co/WOz2Rw7D59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darylvazmp @DamionCrawford Lol no sah DC stay in the Senate is not everything is good for everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keshon00 @In2WeTrust They did but the model felt very strange....  always thought a class room  would be better]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is exciting to start the Lane County All-Star game. Game is at the Morse Event Center on the NCU campus this Wed… https://t.co/VZj8I10Xr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[A special thanks to @ErinKingSweeney for taking the time to meet and congratulate our @BellmoreJFK Regeneron Schola… https://t.co/XyfzJpRVOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ravens: what you got Denver  Broncos: we have two Gatorade tubs and an almost full yogurt stamp card for trade  Rav… https://t.co/fjLMQnxHmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[43 more sleeps until Stanley cup playoffs 😆🥅🏒🚨 #backtoback @ Capital One Arena https://t.co/tAC361yHHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TopeAjao WHE WHE WHE 2385.  .36 THE  THE  THE. 2085.  .33 Just Two Trucks passing each other on the HigHwAY THIRTY… https://t.co/0gTSbqhiY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProFacilit8or @DanCrenshawTX Of course. Same reason I own/carry. But I hope as fellow gun owners we can agree that… https://t.co/vEcomVKU0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanIdol @Scarypoolparty2 @LionelRichie @katyperry @LukeBryanOnline Totally amazing!! Wow!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wuzzardo It is amazing. Simon keeps mispronouncing crayon, so it confused us when he would ask to see the crown episode.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Straight Jacket (2019) by @revbrewchicago @ St. Andrew Episcopal Church — https://t.co/npYMFzvDjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally had the worst week of my life and if some pretentious aging millennial thinks he’s going to ruin my day… https://t.co/FHiBqRywbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking to my boy on the phone my sister gon say " he sounds fatter "   Me "what?" Lol   Her "i know what fat people sound like "]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning with coach @mark_munoz how to throw people 👊🏽🇧🇷🇺🇸🔥🥋 @ Huntington Beach, California https://t.co/nDaU7pwPei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TobyLee41723424 @kyrie11swirving @kashkeller44 You got me , I normally be rocking a bad ass chain , you just caught me slippin lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrishadfun Hi, If you have any plans to hire a resource from an agency to work on your project remotely, we would… https://t.co/yZ7T0LncP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsReneeLawless @TimTebow Thank you @MsReneeLawless I sure miss you and love you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 1995. I was so excited to have a team in NC and for a 9 year old kid it was the biggest thing ever for me!… https://t.co/8rr53jiNrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[What song have they made together that’s better than anything on Watch the Throne?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Facepalm followed by a Scary Smart Strategy by @peggynoonannyc.  Progressives put out the unwelcome mat, and city… https://t.co/s1bmBk489G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t make it to the #MondayNightPolitics candidate forum tonight?   Follow along here as we live tweet the event! #TogetherForDallas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kimpton @IHG @ihgrewardsclub The kale salad, fried chicken sandwich, the burrata, and anything that Sous Chef Eli… https://t.co/sPKBNds3iE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got new bedsheets from bed bath and beyond...being adult you get excited over dumb shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WMTWILL @sportingnews He can do whatever he wants, but suggesting he should "shut it down" is an irrational and illogical argument]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamanthaEileenT Maui is awesome I went a few months back even though the 8 hour flight was brutal both there and back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertevanbank That isn't a gag rule it is censorship of the English language in America.what ever happened to the… https://t.co/5IOZTYcNH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy who was going through dialysis kept calling the nurse a faggot and every thing but her name and she just g… https://t.co/SaHF2laZ9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[A friend recently argued Buttigieg is subtly pitching himself for veep based on contrast with Pence, a fellow Hoosi… https://t.co/PHXFRpQf3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I opened this and immediately felt every fiber of my being cringe in response]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time hanging out in #Nelson with @bhphotovideo and wppievents for #daytripper ! Great group of… https://t.co/GEPGA0sNqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[[Exhale] Daniel 3:14-27 | Antidote https://t.co/2U5dqF6oU6 via @PodcastAddict https://t.co/AmT8gMbqRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extreme precaucion al conducir, choque en Lincoln y Morelos, hay personas lesionadas. en Nuevo Laredo, Tamaulipas https://t.co/c9UrUFLHLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@threeagainst4 Something about having your attack run through a LB not named Roberto Carlos...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akalali @eclinical @chrissyfarr @RasuShrestha @janemetcalfe @RichieEtwaru @nickisnpdx @JohnNosta @ideapharma… https://t.co/17udhIkCKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hmgivingsoul @magee333 @Cbp8Cindy @confessions_cup @JackConnie @suziday123 @linds4fins @ja2cook @jflorez… https://t.co/AC3kR5CfXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your role is to govern to the highest standards for your constituents. To not raise the bar to to exceed it.  These… https://t.co/VwqvqTqE6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChipotleTweets I got an email from someone on your team. I emailed them twice, called once- still have heard nothi… https://t.co/KymihA0tql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frantic_Plague @LoriGreiner Word. If she were to give me $2 million, I'd still be a few hundred grand short of bei… https://t.co/TNInrBAw0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mannyritex @7KESoRockies @phil_petty @Nothing2no123 @SpeakerPelosi Then, once again, where's the source for this material? Gullible much?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tennessee Flight has 35 players who played in last weeks Division II state tournament and is playing in this weeks… https://t.co/HC0AxPPJUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annie_parker Conference and team make up for it. Just want to teleport home when I’m done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously that was every thought that went through my mind when this movie was playing #funniness #giggle #smirk… https://t.co/3vWdKGaSeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#photography #split #splitphoto #winter #cold #snow #snowy #frozenwaterfall #ice #nature #landscapephotography… https://t.co/WHJU0B6BbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker @hazardeden10 @ChelseaFC Reckon they have a favourable schedule yeah?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate According to Democratic Party rules, he must register before running under their ticket. Let's not f… https://t.co/2qhcyR8TYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Venezuela Bolivar = Bad Money, horrible store of value.  Good Money #DigitalCurrency Helpful Money #CryptoCurrency… https://t.co/1QxJBk4lwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Night Lights. #drone #aerial #ski #snow #nightskiing #mavicpro #led #ledlighting @ The Summit at Snoqualmie https://t.co/pnFihVLt8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[STEVIE D of BUCKCHERRY at Ace of Spades in Sacramento!  Interview posting soon to celebrate their new album, Warpai… https://t.co/FFvnqoqQ54]]></document><document><![CDATA[SuperStar @skyylastarr #Champion Here's A New Spokesmodel champion #ChampionAthleticApparel champion_losangeles… https://t.co/81d5SPuTMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@accidentalwinn @TheArtofAntony It is, but I don't have the time or the at home stability to commit all of my love… https://t.co/1xUUa7I4Pc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresh gel mani that I did MYSELF with @SensatioNail. 🙌🏻 I didn’t think it would turn out as good as the gel manis I… https://t.co/bW43F9CtdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @realDonaldTrump @POTUS How many family members have gifted a bible they signed to a loved one. Happens all the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current state of the Wild: #itsoverjohnny #hellodarknessmyoldfriend https://t.co/gCtFIdugYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adam_Puzio @stevenLholder @BarackObama Obama had almost 13 million more Americans on food stamps. He had the lowes… https://t.co/K1mQFg8Yhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow me to see my adventures cleaning and getting rid of crap in my garage. #snapchat👻 #snapchats #snapcodes… https://t.co/P4qqg1f4Bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarielosUca A ti,si supieras lo que siente mi corazón,al saber de ti ,paso de la alegría al regocijo,hasta la lluv… https://t.co/vRkUffJAEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to travel.  Get out of TX for a while.  Sightsee.  Meet new people.  Visit new places.  Eat great food.  Live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chileeee stay tuned! Shit is lit 🔥 x’s 10 from last season! Chasing Atlanta #ChasingAtlanta]]></document></documents></author>