<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Someone came up to me in the mall and asked if I was that girl I think her name is Aria Something from Game of thrones and I don’t see it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming from James Woods, is this supposed to be an insult or a pick-up line? Or both?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Drasky &amp; Gage Auto Paint &amp; Body Shop in Norwalk, CT https://t.co/4JpGFzxUBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did not thinking choosing a color for my car would be this difficult 😅😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching #BernieTownHall on CNN. The most sincere and authentic political leader. #bernie2020 🙋🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Mi flaco de flacos! 💓 Quien me conoce sabe que la música; en especial la salsa, es parte vital de mi vida y no hay… https://t.co/ijQ5wLcVDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSDOT_East any update on the pass opening? #snoqualmiepass #wsdottraffic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ninja I ninja I just wanted to tell you that I am a big fan of your vids.are great and this is not my face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers spill the tea in this Carpool Karaoke 👀 https://t.co/BMlsIromZW #HTownRush]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #NationalLoveYourPet day! @fox6wakeup @fox6now https://t.co/07p5zhuNDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[How my mood be when artists play songs I’ve always wanted to hear live, BUT NOT AT THE SHOWS I ATTEND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow They have held on to his false premise and will try &amp; keep afloat  b/c he’s black , gay and Deranged Trump Hater .]]></document><document><![CDATA[EMS Huskies becoming STEAMers today! #EMSHuskies https://t.co/9eqkSeV9xz]]></document><document><![CDATA[🕷White Spiders 🕷 is up as a #single on my #Soundcloud https://t.co/wToLeaOs11 https://t.co/aywMqXdnI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acho super válido ressaltar este assunto! Vamos cooperar com a natureza galera? #carnaval #meioambiente]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boomer6948 @trucknorris56 @imlosinit4u @Alyssa_Milano Here’s a fact - the investigation isn’t over yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs Political ideology - I don't think so.  The Dummycrats supported it before.  Now they want to resist… https://t.co/8on4ASBJjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrownWarrens @Mr_VBranch @LopezprinciPAL #abovetheinfluence #therealdeal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I just wanna put on my @wearfigs scrub bottoms instead of choosing real pants for social situations...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stupid healthy lifestyle. Good morning Twitter #SundayFunday https://t.co/QZuDaXmfbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[and their dead bodies will lie in the street of the great city that symbolically is called Sodom and Egypt, where t… https://t.co/H3cpZIcQRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[De verdad que las redes sociales me enferman. Ya he intentado cerrarlas pero me pone muy triste no ver la felicidad de mis amigos]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone who’s been hurt a lot is either very understanding or scared to take another chance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexzBrown @BollAndBranch BITCH report back on your experience immediately. I’m so jealous!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayawiley @KatyTurNBC Interestingly “the blacks” while less common phraseology in US, is something I have heard fr… https://t.co/bXPrZI5Wjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check em out at CF today @VerapyTherapy @NeuroRehabVR https://t.co/WPGiY6JZTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here she is and doing GREAT! I was the only one at this stop with a sign and the runners were so fun rooting for Ju… https://t.co/R8h0td4kUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm seeing MRG30 - Merge Records 30th Anniversary at Carolina Theatre , Durham, NC on Wednesday, July 24th.… https://t.co/2ovx27aMMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta stop crying over spilled milk and put myself back out there. Niggaz don’t see nothing wrong with their acti… https://t.co/HmoeoSN7Kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fernand80760480 @angsala67 @LilianaSnchez9 @mainzina @szalacain1 @jobragag @Cantero9Vega @JSaintPastour Gracias Fe… https://t.co/1dtveCsj8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank god for urasmellybitch1 right now because I’d probably be crying in my car at the park in front of little kids again]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Mastercard Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/puEZ5HTBYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know what I did to deserve Matt but I thank my lucky stars that he’s the most understanding, loving and gen… https://t.co/KahOauTMPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul O’Bama can’t hold a candle to Trump. I don’t know why you would bring him up. Same thing about the Wall.… https://t.co/L05WbLCIq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sopdet Considering they mean very opposite things in the sports world, the English language kinda really did us dirty there 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when I got my first cell phone, we would spend HOURS on the phone. And one time she joked that we didn’t… https://t.co/lzNz9ujqST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RDUAirport  WHAT IS HAPPENED to you nice smooth lines for security? Not these out the actual security area - secur… https://t.co/RDD0Zk5G1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Mullet @RyanPritt That count must have been last night. We’re way higher by now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visiting with my parents today and my dad is (of course) watching the #Daytona500, something very soothing about th… https://t.co/UmgScmhID0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best position is when they on their backs and you rub your head on the taint then slide in slow... do that and watch them melt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey  @Walmart the least you could do is take the feathers off your rotisserie #chicken!  This is why I usually buy… https://t.co/jIvQLfKqLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimMastie @DominoNazario @Raquel4Detroit @eventbrite @latinorebels @LULAC @BarCrawlLive @Latinos4MediaEq… https://t.co/9VeDtrhAMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WickedIzze For a bit you know u mean like half a day while I was over here with 0 sleep 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertBlumofe So wonderful that you keep your grandfather #JackBenny's legacy alive. I'm curious whether you knew… https://t.co/HgWsa55Vga]]></document><document><![CDATA[im in bio before my exam and the bitch next to me is BLASTING ‘only human’ by christina aguilera]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's early but super energetic...with #GetUpDC #CheerDC! Supporting important causes throughout the DMV!… https://t.co/rr1yjsSivx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ghostarmy131 @DemWrite @HillaryClinton The parents are responsible for ICE stealing their children??? You really h… https://t.co/BNFwyz0bnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NajeebaSyeed Please tell more! How do you mean "accompaniment" exactly?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pratoshnivedita @jill_magnussen @pkamla1 @spendharkar @gerrinnesmac @loveGoldenHeart @BabyGo2014 @DianneD03113533… https://t.co/WBNQUlQt5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElvisDuranShow @VISITFLORIDA Seriously, why do people who LIVE in Florida call to win the Florida trip and WIN it?… https://t.co/Ov8ntHJQTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone mind sending me some cute things or memes? I’m sick as hell and have to work tomorrow because no one will take my shifts 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[That will be awesome if we had some real weather u guys could work with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbykasch Welcome to @kelly_clarkson #TeamKelly!!  Much luck to you!!  ❤️  #VoiceBlinds]]></document><document><![CDATA[damn me &amp; @kawrtt scrap on the living room floor worse than y’all fight 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iveinzell_ @whalakid Wait what? https://t.co/cmxNaSRGzY https://t.co/hgdI2mngFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenraycosta 💯. At least a week! At some point every time I’ll think “why do I feel like such a zombie, maybe I’m… https://t.co/WcinDML6c9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPol I thought these were guinea pigs at first glance! I have GPs on my mind... my son’s has an enlarged heart, s… https://t.co/V15DquJ1Kt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaTruly Awe thank you so much I will also subscribe thanks for the support!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking Where did they get this guy &amp; Factory farms feed cows mainly corn 🌽]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need to find someone who loves me as much as @mulaney loves steely dan]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MattBomer I just watched @DoomPatrolDCU for the third time, and it’s all so awesome. I love what you’ve already b… https://t.co/GGhpahWnJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning girls and gays, after being a gold member for 6 years, I decided to just join the team so today I star… https://t.co/FbVcXjTmOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nolte: Networks Refuse to Cover Senate's 'No Russia Collusion' Report https://t.co/vlCHNI0IxX via @BreitbartNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@o0_tracy_0o @patnspankme Thats where you’re wrong-this absolutely IS high school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HeelPain and #PlantarFasciitis are common foot pathologies we see as #podiatrists. If you or someone you know is s… https://t.co/H675Dx8uMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheVegasTake @MikeGrimala @jondavid17 @CoachingChanges @Bischoff_Tyler @markanderson65 I remember when TKM came in… https://t.co/By5lEAjW7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are getting ready for Valentine's Day. Did you order your flowers yet?? #valentinesday2019 #roses… https://t.co/LzXOCcwPSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[hit my dm if u wanna see my passport pic i look like an actual crackhead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @KamalaHarris @JussieSmollett Oooooo.. Who is scared of @KamalaHarris  Donald is, obviously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to play catch up on bills is super stressful especially knowing I have a daughter on the way and I’ve only bought her a few outfits]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao am I the only one who cringes every time that postmates commercial with Iggy Azalea plays on YouTube 🥴🤐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tree Shaker Imperial Peach IPA by @OdellBrewing at @BeerNV — https://t.co/0I3O5opOEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey now! Empty seat between us. Too bad it’s a a short flight. ALB ✈️ BWI #adventuresofmegaphil #southwestairlines… https://t.co/HWl2gJ4Vwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the thug started shouting, I lost my shit tho 😂😂😂. Can’t believe they didn’t see me recording]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cr7P1HWJjC   Voici l'enregistrement de notre audience cour d'appel banc de 3 Magistrats Août 2018.Entr… https://t.co/cOEl0Dj6qT]]></document><document><![CDATA[For I am afraid that when I come I may not find you as I want you to be, and you may not find me as you want me to… https://t.co/whlABEl3p3]]></document><document><![CDATA[just watched then came you and it was so sweet and beautiful I might have bawled. @Maisie_Williams and @asabfb are so cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive been feeling very discouraged and sad with myself lately..... but whyyyy https://t.co/CN3GIgz5jo]]></document><document><![CDATA[HackerElvis is in the house!!! Memphis in Vegas! #2019MegaConf @EditorPublisher @localmediarocks @megaconference… https://t.co/T7BpTNf35B]]></document><document><![CDATA[i know i’m getting old when i fall asleep during movies and wake up confused]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach K is next level. Just tells his players to throw their faces into the other teams elbow. 2019 Final Four: ent… https://t.co/TWHSfIfo3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #RollingPrairie, IN? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Cashier… https://t.co/SxbIuLAgiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOY es el Gran Inicio de #MitadyMitad vía @multimediostv canal 6 https://t.co/jgSEJbFqVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's the spawn of djt. They are incapable of shame. Hollow, soulless fools.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated @Gigi2my3 Again, I ask...who thinks this nightmare is going to end peacefully?  When an elected co… https://t.co/HSbedc0xkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow this mans such a hard worker. the village can’t afford sprinklers so every day he goes out and makes himself in… https://t.co/FYUk1PCTPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[McDonald’s chicken nuggets are the best things ever when you’re hungry af, idc what you have to say]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @lukecombs, if you’re reading this...Please play Must’ve Never Met You at @RODEOHOUSTON tonight! 😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eats one bowl of ice cream 🍨 *Wishes I had 4 more bowls* ..... #thisispregnancy #33weeks]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I'm in the Facebook group for the Princess Half Marathon this weekend and the admin keeps warning people to not… https://t.co/IecXD0XEqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[new twitter game: badly summarize your skincare routine i’ll go first  1: splishy splash 2: acid bath 3: sap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chinga tu madre una y mil veces si haces con otra persona los planes que tenías conmigo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strawberry, Bananas, and Cafeteria Peaches DNA 🧬 extraction https://t.co/ePBAjLTaaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me begging @KelseaBallerini for m&amp;g’s for next Saturday’s show like: https://t.co/VrRLCPUQGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimPace05325262 you just want to fight and that’s ok . A wall won’t fix problem a better border security is needed .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @flnativ @JussieSmollett Maybe they should show a little humility, For showing how Big of Asses th… https://t.co/OPD14cDqxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[last night I said, “would you like that grande or venti size?” in my sleep. Starbucks has ruined me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@armarrero803 Shipping not shopping. I used to read the comments. And I shipped it a bit then but seeing the chemis… https://t.co/cPiXYmapWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lkoturner Self-care and brokenness are the top two cringy words for me 😩😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @realDonaldTrump These people are master manipulators for a Jesus they don't know.]]></document></documents></author>