<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@vrb1955 Thanks for Following! Like a good spy thriller novel or know someone who does? Please check my author's si… https://t.co/Wp1ilDiIS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajjaffe Fantastic! We were at Bernie’s rally in Brooklyn. Start taking videos and stream them out on Twitter. I’ll… https://t.co/na1rMTqrU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[While in line these dopes played with their iPhones, drank $7 artisan coffees, and were warmed by the latest winter… https://t.co/dqBBTfNkkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cat showed up in my life, and saved my life.  Powerful shit World.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are open all week with holiday hours! Be sure to check https://t.co/A66Rit4lTr for hours this week, tubing is op… https://t.co/OkxVJ5xq6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird A national emergency should require him to stay in DC!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@975Middays once at Wendy’s they were out of Chocolate Frosty.  Only had Vanilla.  Was pretty pretty good]]></document><document><![CDATA[These kids in class were talking about going to the club this weekend. They’re deadass making plans and I overheard… https://t.co/yl7MGowabw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok can someone explain to me why I can’t get  my grandsons building blocks back in the same container they came in?… https://t.co/3g07PEWS5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soulgoddess1111 @MsSassIn My emotional mirror was shattered years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One not-so-fun fact, "According to the 2010 census, Reading has the highest share of citizens living in poverty in… https://t.co/YySH9d0ghb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 Of course voting rights opponents @RepSteveChabot and @RepBradWenstrup voted against opening more vot… https://t.co/FuIMg4pC9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome General Wesley on Twitter @EricWesleyArmy! https://t.co/Hk5mya6k7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apologies, pastor friends, for the racy album cover. I can't control what Vargas did in 1979.   A glimpse into how… https://t.co/PijZ3nlPeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnwrittenRul3s I miss the real IT I honestly hope he gets back to form, but I wonder if Celtics completely broke him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the problem is like 3 different brunches of math rolled into one 😭.  The basic principles of Calculus, trigonom… https://t.co/iHh1I4P5S7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhinestonecowb Seriously! I'm looking into those injection therapies they have that stop your armpits from sweating 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vgescobar Please help me and my wife we have not had any help yet from anyone except for Beto ‘s group and I’ve be… https://t.co/gSRyZU4kbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the Archbishop Ryan Girls Swim Team for winning the Philadelphia Catholic League Championship 2019 https://t.co/xjZGjnHtIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also the next series I will be working on is house on haunted hill.   I put it off long enough and plus I thought t… https://t.co/XAydEVOYbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this album. Great soundscapes, great melodies.  #AnAlbumADayMonth https://t.co/Nce16kKDtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ritchey87 @cobber_bobber @BIGPartyOne Happy to discuss all oppression, but this topic is specifically about wealth… https://t.co/caL4meQ3sa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Airing Of Grievances (2013-2015) by @uneannee at @GHomebrew — https://t.co/3TSLphREmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg mark!!!! How are you you need to stop being fake, no I’m not gonna put you on with my friend she has a boyfriend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CreamyButters @OpieRadio Wow! Thank you! That’s a real story. These will be a little more vague but, melodic. That… https://t.co/FK2ZAJDXdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! So incredibly deserving. Congrats to the team behind @SpiderVerse! #Oscars2019 #Oscars #AcademyAwards]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope these guys get a chance to dance @marchmadness @RMUAthletics @NCAA Gotta #win the @NECsports tournament. Put… https://t.co/oUVJAPrcbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @TheLovettSchool athletics webpage unde Lovett Broadcast then connect now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CutterDriftwood Sounds much more interesting than physical therapy... sure, why not?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rumpfshaker Good choice. Seeing it screened @FloridaTheatre with @johncusack doing Q&amp;A afterward. Maybe that’ll be my question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel @mfuller297 And why is that question mark what the hell makes him so special? He was trying to start N… https://t.co/flLJqTYVDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plantbasedsav There’s so many useless inserts and the shakes looks like when you try to use image stabilizer on premiere 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I assure you it’s nothing personal between @mattvanda209 and I. We really are good friends 🤘🏻🤘🏻🤘🏻 right buddy?… https://t.co/gbh3kMyGHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏠 New listing in Nocatee!! 🏠  Here is another new listing in the active adult 55+ community of Del Webb.  This is a… https://t.co/ivJaq72Wyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The key to being a good manager is keeping the people who hate me away from the people who are undecided.” — Casey… https://t.co/EJfhwUEp9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m always happy to return to the magnificent Thurgood Marshall US Courthouse, home of the Second Circuit.… https://t.co/eDhJ5RhmbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smokey_77 @EditinKing @SantanaTeddy You weren’t involved in Vietnam. How are we the pussies? Exactly. Stfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexMBorland @CamdenProud @MattDiBenedetto @mattdracing Only Camden https://t.co/NwUUaYSoKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Brooklyn Lager by @brooklynbrewery at @irvingplaza — https://t.co/tjIfBleucQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOLY RAIN • MARCH 8  produced by @prodreid video by @jasxnmusic https://t.co/AeBloYted4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pros: draft order is known pre trade deadline, promoting movement. No incentive to tank down the stretch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final round of the Honda today: who thinks Vijay is going to win??? @ThinkFink_KW @drewmfarris @OUMensGolf careful… https://t.co/FfdzZHKRER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeltroTio @ChapoRomo @UGRSon @MesaCancun @mensajero34 @feroropeza20 @hilarioolea @rquirrin @Chaposoto… https://t.co/z2SUlnNy4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JERobledo #LaJEPdebeSerDerogada Es inaudito que multen  ciudadanos por comer un empanada en la calle, pero que res… https://t.co/l7CmT8NNV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Won’t the bone spurs cause issues for @realDonaldTrump in Vietnam? https://t.co/BOOYezwuYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[With IRAN launching a ballistic missile from a sub, was TRUMP correct in getting out of the BAD IRANIAN TREATY? #obamafailure]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of the Boy-King. He tried out for and got the part of Olaf in the school play. We are beyond proud and exc… https://t.co/kIw54ZF8S3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrunkBrianF I know you aren’t a fan of the trucks on the super speedway, but it was a heck of a lot more exiting t… https://t.co/22a2EIS12V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lifestyles of the rich and socialist: Bernie Sanders has 3 houses, makes millions https://t.co/SbrNovOqmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 24 hour leap year party at Disneyland was 7 years ago today  (saw billy hill and the hillbillies in the middle… https://t.co/Y9zyEHV3Zo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bensh__ @108_Victoria_St Could be politically related in a good way: PA says, “We’ll give you Atco if you give us CHOP” or whatever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't really know what to think about this one.. she sings with my little buddy Sarah Lee https://t.co/kn4vByP5HQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Corsair 100R Silent Build) •Ryzen 7 2700X RGB Cooler •Asus PRIME x470-Pro •Corsair Vengeance 2x8GB •RTX 2070OC Arr… https://t.co/mgwRUqMIXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jillymoe @PuestoLoco @SethAbramson @maddow @RepMaxineWaters @RepAdamSchiff @DevinNunes I think Bannon is singing l… https://t.co/GfTpCpfd9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deafboricua21 @Gealbhan1 @WestWingReport No. No. If I hit the Powerball and get rich then I’ll have to pay more ta… https://t.co/1MNw2m52Hp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been driving past this town since I was a kid visiting our farm, and it remains my favorite town name to this day - Nanty Glo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have received notification from the Texas Future Problem Solvers (FPS), that our CmPS Team, won 1st place in the… https://t.co/t0uj6oq6ZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debbiethetexan @HoustonTexans I think since joining the Texans, Kareem has had an unfair assessment of his abiliti… https://t.co/hkV8mUaPgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems it’s the end of an era: Saturdays are for projects... the #tikihouse trailer is sold!  So here’s the last tou… https://t.co/rJnQkIy4vV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Views from the 10th!! #sandiego weather feels like #charlestonsc @ Sheraton San Diego Hotel &amp; Marina https://t.co/vyD33GX1OS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hiveaclue @kneadinghands @Elinor27652146 @CONSMILITIA @Mel_the_geek @Trixie883low @sascat @YeshuaLover1970… https://t.co/cG947t1FRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Try To Keep Up - Episode 3 Adam And Eve, Its Complicated https://t.co/BLI3iyV0XA via @YouTube Finally, some clarity… https://t.co/Yljvv7GGUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here. We. Go. @Houston_Hoops has a 44-43 lead with a minute to play. @BC_Bearettes ball out of the break. Bearettes… https://t.co/gG5RWBQKIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump The bad news is you’re either really bad at sarcasm or don’t know basics about el… https://t.co/1vDqD7JHOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife @smmckinley said NO to the $47 Vineyard Vine cap and the giant Empire State Building statue, so I had to se… https://t.co/M6Tgu5x9BE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyKillinit Isn't that weird? Since I had 1st kid a year ago, I oft find my subconscious bringing me back to tho… https://t.co/skytfQTLI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Subrinas comments on my essay are sO FUNNY WHY AM I SUCH A BAD WRITER FJNDJDNDND]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start of Spring Training sure has me missing the days when we could see the O’s here in town at #MiamiStadium !… https://t.co/pOl7PVjyvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems like just a week ago that my friends and I were in *the room where it happened* when @brielarson was announce… https://t.co/PAGoCatUGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaaZerW @SpeakerNation9 @cynthia4943 @PettyAirJordan Nah next game Mrs Trip-Dub making a appearance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sin acuerdo término reunión entre #Trump y #KimJonUn y suspenden almuerzo programado, otro intento fallido de la “d… https://t.co/tITSainfWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams Lmao, will you agree to Retire! You’re an old and broken record! Nothing fresh new, retreaded BS is your Thang]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FatherTF @DCLatinMass You lost me at the very end. At least in these United States, Jansenist preparations for a s… https://t.co/9muMmMJ4dm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My feelings are finally being validated by another person and it’s the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look who I found while visiting my friend #CrazyRay in #NawLins #MAR9_2019 #MICK ! @ Aunt Tiki's Group https://t.co/g8e85BARX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lumbar artificial disk surgery preserves motion in the spine and is an alternative to fusion. @VSortho https://t.co/tyeEhSg95I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rdene915 @JaimeDonally @nearpod @magistrazee @mrnickcusumano @EdTechTinker @steve_bambury @hiimpactMrN… https://t.co/zarViWAKS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its cranking up here in Clinton at Ind wrestling Regionals. Straight up Dudes. 💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SJJ2270 @ASDS_THD3102 @EWootan28 @Patrick79717194 @JeffGroomsHD @angbest33 @HDMuzi When You  Lose The Bet, You Pay… https://t.co/AFWR58RDH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MONYRODRIGUEZOF Hola mi amor. Ya no veo Dia A Dia porque ya tu no estas. Como te va?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCorollary Not a historian, but I think the life of Rios Montt of Guatemala is a very interesting one in this context.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But 80s minimum-investment-in-car-storage-requirements – which mostly remain in effect today – made traditional Hou… https://t.co/UeQqRZR1jx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz Think of how much better America would be for women, if an arrogant coffee billionaire didn't run as… https://t.co/szWAqXjKrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toastfuker Don't call my bluff. Getting Pelosi attention. She is speaker because a lot of people want Trump out. I… https://t.co/YhySgIuk3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piw13 @edschultheis @TeachDMD @JohnFea1  Big Data #SpellingMattersInRoom3 https://t.co/snDtVMs5mI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @other98 with get_repost ・・・ This is what a real emergency looks like.  #borderwall #whiteterror #memes… https://t.co/PY6T2iKbVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the world Mr. Noah Malcolm Thompson...coming in at a whopping 9 lbs 4 ounces!!   Baby is good and gettin… https://t.co/H6sb7918k7]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Hero! HOOAH! @starsandstripes @USMARCENT @Martin_Dempsey @oirdcom @mccaffreyr3 @StanMcChrystal @parisislandpod]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a bad New Yorker dies, do they wake up in New Jersey? #AfterLife #death #spirituality #geography #faith]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is insane. A. That it happened. B. That no one was hurt. We're going live at 9:30 on @SpecNewsCLT with the lat… https://t.co/ziAii0xzsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[So hot. Enjoyin this day off @ Hialeah, Florida https://t.co/cghzC5F3WH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tercera vez que veo en el día que sale humo negro , ¿que tanto quemaran  como a altura del vado del río  ? https://t.co/zDz9aorwBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the nicest seats I've ever had AND I get to boo Jake Allen in TWO periods! My landlord has good season ti… https://t.co/yDcDlvoId3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@royceca54144730. YOU make my day be happy all the time just like me !! SHARING with people all the time ! Sincerely yours me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huskies Boys 🏀 Sectional pairings for the 3A Sectional  at New Castle.  Huskies (14-7) open up the sectional vs. Mu… https://t.co/L2deTAiO4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conservatives launch zillions investigations and that’s ok ... Dems hold one and the GOP loses their ever loving minds. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Please don’t use logic and common sense @realDonaldTrump ...  ...you’ll be unable to communicate to the Leftist Party]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macbrunson Brother Mac did you see Israel sent a probe to the Moon on a SpaceX Rocket...the probe Rover named Ba-r… https://t.co/Pz1ejIb2fO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You fucked them with tariffs and now you’re taking credit for helping them...that’s high class asshole move right there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Whamsey Knew from the beginning. Having the manager call the police over an hour after the incident and still, for… https://t.co/QZl7kMeOzZ]]></document></documents></author>