<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[One of the best parts of being an adult is that you don’t need your parents permission anymore when it comes to des… https://t.co/WFwElzkZ96]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating my Moms retirement 🎉 @ Anaheim Ducks https://t.co/U7sNdJugZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaysondbradley You know what I don’t like. When you publicly champion someone who took an unpopular position, give… https://t.co/eanuX9Nsvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MmeBlouwolff @GMancuso13 I use it in class with Ss at the beginning of the year and remind them in the middle agai… https://t.co/2SHkjh2syx]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #InternationalWomenDay, so thank the amazing women in your life (I love my ladies!), go see #CaptainMarvel, an… https://t.co/2jy6NU8lrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJusticeDept @GOPLeader @GOP @WhiteHouse Insane @SpeakerPelosi must be impeached for TREASON!… https://t.co/v2NqFULqOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 He keeps getting her bigger and bigger tits, she keeps letting him get her bigger and bigger tits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mccarthy_max @CharlieDaniels No ivied it Was a Cat 5 Don’t What Anyone Says !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Fresh To Death by Aurora Ale And Lager Co. at @awwander — https://t.co/7qmL6scnSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pinterest blocks all vaccine-related searches in effort to combat anti-vax content https://t.co/BTOtVXGsNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CillizzaCNN Here we go! The media starting to work on Trumps 2020 victory 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan The only weapons I want will be to protect me from cray-cray Republicans… …and they’re only gonna be lo… https://t.co/0xRapkoDOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Myranda_Klawuhn I’ll let you know as soon as I find anything so can give notice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching up with this lovely lady, Sam....in a English pub! 😜 @kentlawschool @ Duke of York https://t.co/oQzgldEVSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh bitchhhh if you haven’t seen how to get away with murder you are missing out]]></document><document><![CDATA[💩Fox News: Schiff: Dems 'absolutely' will take DOJ to court over Mueller report if  necessary. https://t.co/GRFGau7ch7  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RhoniDu This is unbelievable. He furthered the interests of every murderous Dictator he could get his hands on, bu… https://t.co/X60horAqFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I ever meet Jooheon   Jooheon: So you really like me that much? Me blushing: If you smile on front of me my answ… https://t.co/7Tvy9GwCYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I done made up my mind that when I find my husband he can’t have a Twitter . This place is awful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning everyone! Have a blessed Monday. Safe travels today. We had such a “major” snowstorm last night 🙄😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EcoSexuality @RepJerryNadler @SpeakerPelosi @IlhanMN MESSED UP GIRL!!! TRAITOR!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one: Me: I impulse cut my hair because I’m mentally and emotionally unstable lol 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[“No gifts, only beer pong, only success”  It’s getting competitive here lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EosRose Sort of. The genetic lineage of trauma tends to be in health conditions and predisposition for various men… https://t.co/RvBuvCcSNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CajunChick25 @JulieReichwein1 I live in Chicago, he's not only done a great disservice to Chicago, he hurt Black,… https://t.co/x0YSloXwRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I legit was just thinking to myself “if I wasn’t a Flyers fan I should go back to being a Pens fan because of how m… https://t.co/uwkgjU7h1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Embarrassing fact about me: Until I was 17 I thought I-Pass stood for Interstate Pass...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsJeffreyBrah I well  allwhys  bee your  namber1# fam ❤😌😙😘sweety hart ...a big kiss for You]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 @realDonaldTrump Is he the top or the bottom?  (I meant bunk of course)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedavemiska Lots of problems, lot’s of good... just like the rest of the human race. They are no different. No on… https://t.co/seSYNvqc8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I thought they had stop overbreeding and are having abortions so the evil swindlers can make money off of aborted babies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Isaac_J_Miller_ I love how the interview was done in the same room as y’alls serverely loud instrument.😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm looking forward to being there. See what can be accomplished when "No one ever slows her down"… https://t.co/yg6HjAHarU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Round 2 - let’s hope no rabbits decide to snack on my plants this time! https://t.co/XlMGwKpcA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our kids loved the Container Park and then checked out the Fremont area. Vegas with kids is doable, you just have t… https://t.co/PK4CffnTMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re single and you whine about it on social media, get a fucking life bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FanBoost @svandoorne #StoffelVandoorne @LiamPayne #LiamTheWorldLovesYou]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/7IWC4dFXIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re a writer who struggles w/ peer-envy or a professional who feels like there’s always someone beating you a… https://t.co/K83O9uOTVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[an older lady hit my new car .....confronted her and felt sorry for her so did nothing.  now without car for 3 days… https://t.co/ridF4rIOII]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m attempting to make pasta sauce with random crap I have in my fridge and various canned tomato products I keep a… https://t.co/24qXfJWXro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok @whitesox fans. The Cubs are letting us watch Eloy and the boys from Mesa!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardA_Esq My opinion, worth the price you paid for it, is that it is far better to be alone than to wish you wer… https://t.co/g9zZDq2Xel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealKAYEYE We need to catch some regional acation at the closest SEC school host!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entra aqui y vota por todos ellos https://t.co/CnyY9Vtx1Z https://t.co/Lrl049mhCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnv378 @HillaryClinton @BernieSanders Hellllllllnawwwwww!!! #NeverBernie ✊🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk how we got so lucky, but Kacie and I now have 3 fairly large TVs in our apartment and got all of them for free 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seadweller_ What brand did you get? I’ve had the ninja air fryer in my cart for a month now...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello old friend (@ Austin Bergstrom International Airport - @austinairport in Austin, TX) https://t.co/FwyPMjX7zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aiiii Deus que as coisas deem certo pra mim e que eu não fique mais preocupada pq não quero ter mais crises!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My period is making me so emo rn. I'm crying because I'm thinking about if/when I have kids. They are just so cute… https://t.co/j1u5VWRxIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. I love them already! 💜  TXT (투모로우바이투게더) '어느날 머리에서 뿔이 자랐다 (CROWN)' Official MV https://t.co/pqICmiAZPo via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aceboogie0515 I always laugh when I see her in some shit cuz I literally rode the same bus home with her 😂 I'm just like damn]]></document><document><![CDATA[i luv waking up to a full on anxiety attack and feeling like my heart is gonna beat out of my chest that’s what’s up]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think I’m stupid enough to blame my fucked up, moody ass attitude on this super moon, you’re abso-fucking- lutley right iam🍄🌚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VOLUNTEERS_TN @vol_bandit Burn the house down 😱 https://t.co/4yERXcCwoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cjuN4wStDh  Amazon phone number guarantees world-class solutions tech concerns 1-855-431-5111  #Amazonphonenumber]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pastry Experiment in Culinary II today. A basic pastry made with a variety of fats. So far shortening is their favo… https://t.co/h96tGJtz08]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muy buenos día!!! Dios me los bendiga a todos en Heroica Guaymas, Sonora, Mexico https://t.co/96SSQNcOkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[my true and unconditional love !!! @ FC Barcelona - Més Que Un Club https://t.co/Q901MWVp7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @Delta employees Pam Mathis and Joanne Williams and crew at gate c12 in #dtw. WAY more helpful and fri… https://t.co/b08Fkq5Nuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are full of love and hearts today!  Happy Valentines Day from @diamondsdetails! #valentinesday… https://t.co/5rpv5oTsSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sniper64286433 That’s all they have to babble about. I call it grasping for straws]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Wednesday, I’ll be kicking off my indiegogo campaign to fund my third album! The amount of encouragement and s… https://t.co/63XGxyR2vX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 6 countries have equal rights for men and women - eg Sweden, Denmark.  The United States scored only 83.75 of… https://t.co/jYPvwLkymz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to remember not  wear my good clothes when I do my DIYs I got paint on my new PINK sweater 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cellmavin @cedarflats @badhopper @HermannTLombard @wolv54b1 @excitedtofeast @NineGiant @bodyfit67 @afrobeerchick… https://t.co/upSBku7XGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanOlson906 @RepMarkMeadows Yes, classified. I guess after 2 years of Devin Nunes running the committee, that migh… https://t.co/OV2O2mwkza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please Frankfort, KY do more to protect our children and communities. Vote NO on permit- less carry bill today!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention @GOP, your leader believes Kim knew nothing about #OttoWarmbier. Go read the account of his family receiv… https://t.co/entwHX9S7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dancing and collaborating! Who can ask for anything more? Love ❤️ #coteaching @AndreaHonigsfel @bcsdschools… https://t.co/TLzK91RQYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @shoos4u For example his wife claim to have a skin care line that's BS just another company they could use… https://t.co/wszQSaZE3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAO BUT THE AMOUNT OF CONVERSATIONS IVE HAD EXACTY LIKE THIS...  smfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking juice is pretty much the same as drinking liquid sugar 🥤🍬 Check out my latest blog on Natutal News:… https://t.co/y7lAbOhu6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aroseblush Watch Out 4 Jeanette Johnson-Jing. Bernie Sanders Old Hatchiteer. An Ultra Conservative Green Party Mem… https://t.co/CaVhLdihTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, when I see someone spreading lies about israel https://t.co/NsYKjYKfx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[my splash sista making movesss!!🙌🏼💕 Congrats @eden_gainer so happy for you!!!😙]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we made it back in less than 11 hours, close but still less!!! What a trip 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Kat 🥳 I love you so much and I’m so glad you’re living your best life in Florida! Can’t wait to see… https://t.co/TDsr6YCWMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe one day thins week I’ll get up, not late, but on time, and get ready like a normal human. But today...today i… https://t.co/k5zxY3i0cR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittneyLLynn YOU ARE SO RIGHT.  But I *do* get a lot of steps in, going back and forth from my desk to the kitchen 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirkhawkins Awwww You're Awesome, Kirk!! Thank you so much for the shoutout!! You're the BEST!!! 🤗🤗 hugs😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[New: @TulsiPress is going to reintroduce the Ending Federal Marijuana Prohibition Act next week that proposes compl… https://t.co/XrLrBbuqb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their voices are absolutely beautiful together.... @pussnbootsmusic at @martyrslive 👏🏻 ✌🏻❤️🤘🏻 https://t.co/QC6voCcO0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@actorbat I thought i was the only one who love that teacher 🤗 he loved my report on a starving writer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah well that stand was against America, her people and our National security. He's ruined his career and made eve… https://t.co/eR9VMMrX18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love Unicorn Art Parties! ❤ Painting or slime, they are always so much fun!  https://t.co/GY1afAk024… https://t.co/60ubQldi6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time standing still @ChristianSlater Interview with the Vampire &amp; #thewife https://t.co/JA43fVq9lf]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you pay for a large and this is all they give you.... wow. @SteaknShake https://t.co/hiNb7w0mn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am warming up my arm to get ready to throw out the first pitch as we speak! This effort will, unfortunately, requ… https://t.co/g0hFhz5DqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[ando como pendeja caminado en el zen garden tomando fotos de plantas para mi proyecto de biología, y como dijo era… https://t.co/Xt1wO2YvYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitter @TwitterSupport why don’t y’all be suspending these Caucasian’s twitter account when they say “nigger” to… https://t.co/la5VZOwfG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[my idea of stretching at the gym is foam rolling and playing on my phone for 5 minutes then leaving]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miss_Phoebe_Lee You are very beautiful.  Your ears are outstanding.  They are jealous indeed.😻😻]]></document><document><![CDATA[ovaj američki sistem, sve veličine su manje, visoka sam 5 nešto, milja je tako varljiva, jer sam navikla na km, sve… https://t.co/GynLersREW]]></document><document><![CDATA[💋Check out When She Says Baby by Jason Aldean on Amazon Music💋💋💋 https://t.co/VLzGUQGII0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eight most popular #podcasts as of right now #dccommunicators https://t.co/4NqdzKcsRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The day @chaserc_ and @awonderland get married is the day I can die a happy woman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love that my oven isn't hot enough to cook my food yet somehow it's hot enough to give me a steam burn on my face💦💨😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s too many people around here that aren’t on the same page as me. It’s always boys and drama and the party yo… https://t.co/DFu4uPcD2F]]></document></documents></author>