<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Twitter fam! Help a girl out for a project. All you have to do is fill out your first name, your last name, your em… https://t.co/vdB1GyGSrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“you cheated on my ass wit a bitch that wouldn't last you ol foolish ass nigga “ -kenthaman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allthatsean @EquestriaGirl @Lyssipe @sir_squiggles_ @jamesxingleton Podophilia is another term for foot fetish bec… https://t.co/qxfdSFaWnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone heard if @NAWMBA still exists!?! No social posts, no conference? Did it just close up shop? #MBA #nawmba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sjones524 @brithume I guess we should all play golf cause that’s acceptable]]></document><document><![CDATA[either once upon a dream-sleeping beauty  or the entire hercules soundtrack]]></document><document><![CDATA[BFFs for 20 years and counting. Here’s to 20 more. #girlsnightout #Drag Race #selfie #manilawasrobbed #instagay… https://t.co/c25gqJK8if]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Onelife Fitness - Princess Anne https://t.co/BkYaQoy4OW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t miss out on #TEDxUofT 2019: Spectrum on March 23rd. Tickets are now available. Get yours here: https://t.co/6A3tBNXtGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArdisTheAnomaly Thank you! Hope you’re having a great weekend playing XO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nochill_jojo @ssoocchill Give me money to send you some flowers and I will 😊💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hicimos una parada técnica donde tía emilia_berg_mazara en Queens, New York https://t.co/xNnzD2Hnln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop asking , “How are you?” If you’re not going to wait for a response.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working a crazy story right now for my show thats filming this week, I’m laying in bed shook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy tendré la conversación más seria que he tenido con mis papás, no tengo nada planeado, van a llover pedazos de c… https://t.co/8HNLDakGhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karli_bonne @MazurikL Are you saying we should trade with governments thta are cruel to their people?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdultDiddy @carliejoprints You made my day :) these peepers are sparkling now cause of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_axelrod Going golfing under a national emergency declaration isn’t going to help his cause when this goes to court...#dumbass]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this rain has me wishing for a good sunny day at the beach like maybe this weekend #rain4days #la #sun… https://t.co/X1HL7qciyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks like a country music, windows down kind of day, but in reality it’s one of those rare moments Antarctica sees sunlight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At launch pad 39B looking over to launch pad 39A where the Spacex #Crewdragon  awaits launch early Saturday morning. https://t.co/QfTNGedoE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ELOgurl01 @AUniqueSongbird I had it at work for dip day and I was hooked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lovelydorrie @CurtRichyYT Step 1 guys: get demonetized 😂  Step 2: overcompensate with hair #fanservicevideo @GetInTheRobotTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlphillips71290 What do you expect when the pitcher hangs a breaker like that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[he's trying to save me from myself. he picked up the lollipop in his mouth before this and casually tried to walk o… https://t.co/kze0TR85vG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker I feel danger ahead with this man. Hope we are up to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cantswim_ thank you for last night y’all are awesome #filmborn #hihat #la #iPhone7Plus #iphonephotography https://t.co/hZqHzSz3aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love Polydrons and teamwork to start our day! @MabletonES @CobbMathDept #UltimateLearningExperience… https://t.co/plguxlu8b5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Graduation about to be hot as hell‼️ Have the ambulance on standby for my final PV Pass out 🚑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @realDonaldTrump Can you two just be nice.  Jacob your eyes must be covered up and do not pay any atten… https://t.co/01bSlftC1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[El arte no conoce de fronteras  #YalitzaAparicio @YalitzaAparicio   Te admiro carajo orgullo mexicano https://t.co/RlyRimqdhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkyCinemaUK @ReginaKing @ChrisEvans @ChrisEvans you took my breath away, a real hero helping @ReginaKing https://t.co/uMkID6FOMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StephonClark investigation went just like this. The system itself is working as it was designed, which is to break… https://t.co/xgx1X2Nasr]]></document><document><![CDATA[😰 #RIPJaniceFreeman #TheVoice @abronxchick @birdieglad @jihettly @pannlewis44 @graceslick77 @veterans_i @DLTrunnell… https://t.co/rPMzZ0GLOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This painting has been sitting in a corner for years stuck in “I don’t think I like you land” in my brain.  Well, t… https://t.co/x3hGqD5MA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[When are we going to stand up and take our responsibility as patriotic American citizens who have refused to addres… https://t.co/d2XiDxyEYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mildredsfierce @MissBrittHayes you’re ok!! thank you for the support and the RT 😊😊💖💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BulldogBen @ladalavara @lang51b @LawsResist @LeChatNoire4 @Liberty2Bfree @LilCox2627 @LipShtick @LisaTalmadge… https://t.co/wqjiHGe5oE]]></document><document><![CDATA[thinking of purchasing a military grade weapon for the living room coffee table]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do elite athletes keep their balance after executing breathtaking spins and flips? This Johns Hopkins Universit… https://t.co/PBTtNkaVNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FuctupMike Falsely using the police should have some consequences. Not like CPD is sitting around waiting for a co… https://t.co/egOntpfEWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am no expert, but I wanted to pass along this advice: Advice for residency personal statements in psychiatry: Avo… https://t.co/TlaOkoOI4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re off work and you just have to have a delicious breakfast from maplestreetfrisco ! Always a favorite pla… https://t.co/pzutfO8ZFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I am my muse, I am the subject I know best. The subject I want to know better.” —Frieda Kahlo @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/1ZUF4RgMRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t make her feel like she’s your everything, someone else will and that’s just how it is hun 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never saw myself going to a Disturbed concert, and I definitely never thought I’d cry at a Disturbed concert... B… https://t.co/mkGNe7t5zB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger I would love to see his 2016 return. I think they made a fortune running last time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's go #MUFC! I'm predicting a 3-0 win for the #RedDevils.  #MUNSOU https://t.co/dvSGki4qrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffDase You should have seen the whole dance! Heck the whole assembly! Come out Wednesday evening if you're free!… https://t.co/NpMBehHwYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to hearing more about you and your many contributions at the Worcester Women’s Leadership Conferenc… https://t.co/w9YDDMo4mu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump just remember that if you do the right thing, keeping in mind those you serve, and for the right reason we will win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“No one wants an angry colon” @news2alan @GodvikNewzGirl https://t.co/Ll3qzIivyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsButchGoneYet @RealGFeemster @wesrucker247 That has nothing to do with this situation at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might as well gon head and call the ambulance if I fuck around with this]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeTrumpEmergency  #FAKENationalEmergency  @realDonaldTrump  #TrumpIsAnEvilTraitor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being a process server and just ruining people’s lives everyday lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Feel Something by Adam Lambert  #FeelSomething https://t.co/eU060lImJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brothers &amp; Baseball at Sunset. ⚾️🌅💙 @ Guntersville, Alabama https://t.co/XzfUgq86a1]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are the only one in your friend group that doesn’t drink😂💀 https://t.co/4L5eWbBtz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to the nearly thirty year old women I follow on social media platforms, I had a Jonas Brother dream last nig… https://t.co/pjai4YQKkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was pleasantly surprised at his sincerity.   The old saying holds true,  never piss on a skunk.... he'll get you… https://t.co/EnGoctguNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only difference between the girls on the bachelor and girls my age is that one knows their man is hooking up other people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FluffysUniverse I know that too well also. Took 18 years to get over someone for me! I guess it just somehow happe… https://t.co/tCFYHLaUsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[No apology and her twisted followers are still dunking on John Batchelor. Hey NeverTrumpers you own this gal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me tomé una taza de café para poder estudiar y hacer una tarea y pues ya terminé y no tengo sueño, ahora como le hago para dormirme?🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion is $5 and has yet to even play in this rivalry  Tyler Hansbrough is undefeated at Cameron and is $4  And don’t… https://t.co/paTZJJOyt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you block or unfollow me nothing I tweet should be valid in your life .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people you know are hurting and lonely. Please reach out to them today! Thank you. Happy Saturday!!! @ Brighto… https://t.co/tKpHF3G55T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like now would be a bad time to note I’m 0-3 in Senators games I have attended this season. 🤣🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“One is loved because one is loved. No reason is needed for living.”  ~ Paulo Coelho ~ • Happy Valentine’s Day! •… https://t.co/s9262zcZsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[What to Say (and What Not to Say) to Someone Who’s Grieving https://t.co/BgrEtad0IZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[feeling feisty so I called the curtesy officer on duty on someone at my complex playing loooud base &amp; I think I feel better now 😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mizz_Keisha_ This tweet is a perfect combo with your profile picture. 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody who knows me knows this what I type every time I see a paragraph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice way to end an intense week. - Drinking a Magical &amp; Delicious by @fallbrewing @ City of Long Beach  — https://t.co/Ys4222WA2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @RodStryker Fraud. She should be expelled from Congress and maybe arrested!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cernovich If you have something plain to offset it and maybe some Converse or Van's, that would probably work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No where in that article was there mention of how that would affect Black Students currently attending and looking… https://t.co/UjhCwP6FaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming soon! “constant escape,” is an exhibition of works in sculpture, photography, installation, text, and video… https://t.co/tHQnuVnUXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard a strange, yet familiar sound this morning; a bird singing.   Spring is coming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[accidentally stress-ate an entire tin of peppermints just now how’s ur day goin]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you surround yourself with good people who believe in you, they’re going to help you carry that ball over the line.” ~ Melinda Gates]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Regal Essex 14 &amp; RPX in New York, NY https://t.co/Lz0khzs0Nx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cabellschools Your students are to talented, I’m glad I was able to preview their work yesterday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealDisco @AOC She is a far left radical communist who's socialist and Marxists ideology will not only bankrupt… https://t.co/04XdfkKiFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OL_America @Outlander_STARZ @_CineAddiction @TallShipProds @OutlanderWriter @SamHeughan @caitrionambalfe @mariadkennedy Congrats👏🏻🎉👏🏻🎉👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikemorua_ It’s not the place, never said it was, I said that i miss my mom and my family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fun weekend bowling the @NDOBOWLING Smooth Team Challenge! Team #1 shot +558 and Team #2 shot +477. I used m… https://t.co/T8lUczuXrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[she makes my heart go 💙💝💜❤️💜💓💙💓💚💘🧡🧡🧡🧡💓❤️🧡💝💛💝💛💚💞💙💞💞💞💕💚💞💓💝💝❤️💞💖❤️❤️💘💖💙💓💙💞💕❣️ https://t.co/bfxS2CELvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoadtripC @confessions_cup @hmgivingsoul @JustJane2019 @PoloOrtiz9 @TheAngelOrsini @suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy… https://t.co/wmqqSswOrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to see my parents in two weeks and I am so excited https://t.co/s4waRsRRnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Copy_Culture Aristotle's view is consistent with mediocre art, yes. I said most, not all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@osteoarch @george_capen Yup. He has had a hard on for Obama for a few years now. His sole existence depends on one… https://t.co/bweTNEWGvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to learn a fun fact about me? Go check out @MLSFemale's IG stories!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Look at us... always running around, always rushed... I guess that’s why they call it the human race”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alicekeeler @DellEMC I’m there in spirit #coffeeEDU keep me posted on the great conversations👀🥓💥 https://t.co/kGIxSo9ZlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SussexPrayerChain Continue to allow the DoS to walk in your name.  Allow her to continue to tune out the noise whi… https://t.co/shmex3FBt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[snicker for some stress relief. Funny Pictures With Captions (25 Photos) https://t.co/xjIuX2Jv3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2: when teachers model it and talk through it our Ss learn metacognition skills, that is how we think about how we… https://t.co/JMz7GKvijM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto @larrythkw So why isn't Bernie under investigation? He could be leaking sensitive information]]></document></documents></author>