<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@FullertonMBB @CSFCoachTaylor @sjonesy_02 @espn @SportsCenter @ESPNU That was a very classy thing that you did for… https://t.co/uVQfUOaUYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Saturday morning 🌞🌞🌝 #fourseasonshotel #advisor #meetings #ericdilauro #mentor #consultant #protrainer @… https://t.co/R6XmD9w56k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willmansel @3ssvd @damnumb Ole buddy saw like 30 percent of the steering column and almost Guessed the car 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really be having a  “my bf rich I don’t have to deal w this” mindset😭😭smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElinePowell I was the red box &amp; I was thinking of you https://t.co/uC3AxVsP51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always amusing to get to the gym and change out of my black “dress” converse and into my black “destroy at the gym” converse]]></document><document><![CDATA[Complaining about the snow yesterday so we had to go play in the snow on Mt Hood today. https://t.co/2x6n43ES6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of training session this afternoon.   The comeback rolls on.  #workout #sunday #training #noretreat… https://t.co/r9nS1ZG03m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to @rjochoa he speaks truth @JasonMinnix does the commanders offense make your peers stink the next day though?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eric_M_Guerra @tweet_maravich Ben, two senators each state, has to be that way ya dunce. Did you not take civics?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff @ILoveHillaryC When does the don tell the truth. Anyone ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamColton on @TyltEnt—Colton Underwood is my favorite bachelor https://t.co/kwX2EkaidL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordantylerc That’s beautiful. Bloodborne is my jam. I DEFINITELY prefer Bloodborne OVER Dark Souls. BUUUT, that’s… https://t.co/41KGiLj72E]]></document><document><![CDATA[To fire Kushner would only set him loose on the world to quid pro quo Intel. He must be indicted. If he’s giving in… https://t.co/uMFT2cigBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@porlagoma @jguaido Totalmente de acuerdo y por pura casualidad tenía el mismo argumento en una conversación hace p… https://t.co/Cw3nBvp7vN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking Customers First! “What Projects are working on? in the future? How’s your Windows? #Serviceconnect… https://t.co/eizno2hE8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DevinNunes @FoxNews Trump is the only POTUS that serves crap food at the White House https://t.co/Lc1iXxftPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsaCoachYVida @Mabe_Fer_ Yo no he ido nunca de caza, pero conozco muchos cazadores y éso no lo hace un cazador.....eso es un crimen😞😞😞😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The Russian interference investigation, (Robert Mueller's instructions never mention collusion at… https://t.co/K2RQxPVaeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikHansLarson @SmelOdiesOG You are bombarding me with tweets when I don’t want to engage with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Dont believe her apology,  she will continue with her antisemitism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FatherTim Like Baptism (and/or Confirmation... whatevs), this is less an age milestone than a commitment to a bett… https://t.co/dgVitsUVvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teresaguerrero_ @jvasqz23 @_Stud_Muffin__ yeah......chris loves me more https://t.co/v2SptlhejB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep he peed in their Cheerios, it’s pretty frickin sad!! Macarthyism has returned!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another lie... salary my ass...it was a political move to get the anti lynching bill passed for Harris and booker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraUnderwood Boomerang, Beautiful.  Wait.. did you say "sweet" or "wet"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo the same lil racist fucker that was bothering those Native Americans??? How the fuck?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STARCHILD0920 @AtomicPunk8 Never know STILL why he would voluntarily go from a top gun in DIO to playing rythym in… https://t.co/OCQvNa0NDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[TERRIFIED Of Bernie Sander is @MSNBC, Their Coverage Shows It https://t.co/axoI7izl5Y via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[They just offered a $850 travel voucher to a passenger that’d wait for the next flight. Sucks that ain’t my flight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeDiGiovanna This deal hurt Trout’s future earnings Harper was looking at a higher per year for less years and w… https://t.co/0KYQkWTUFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColtCabana @gradowrestling Colt! Be careful. He tried to hurt you and sell you his DVD in Chicago, remember?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jon Snow will be our 6th man because he's reliable and always there when you need him, plus he'll have a connection… https://t.co/2laYUxZnJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[40 mil miembros del ejército de #Cuba tienen intervenida, mejor dicho INVADIDA a #Venezuela y nadie dice nada @UN… https://t.co/7GJNCBy5Vp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMichaelWaltz @TwitterGov @facebook @instagram @YouTube So proud of you!  Love you like a brother, Mike!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve been busy at Old Buildings. New Mural in Dickson Street Creative Suites, Insomnia Cookies opened at The Dicks… https://t.co/xfcgE6f8zk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the last photograph of my favorite fruit stand man and his lovely wife. This man works so hard to contribut… https://t.co/C1dCawaXJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spcwrighter @BettyBowers Well, James Garfield had only 6 months to wreak havoc on the world.  And by many accounts… https://t.co/3nXdoihBO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are the fucking traitor and should be taken out....bang !!!!! #RogerStone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol omggg if I lived in a different city with different kind of journalism I would be sooooo like stalked. Maybe it… https://t.co/S3EPKdS6Hj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sprint it’s snowing really bad and my fiancée works at the kc legends area. Can you have your guys call them and h… https://t.co/CJ5flcNtnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Grandson Chase, dressed up as an Old Man, PaPa, LOL, for Spirit Week at school. Looking Good! @ Dunn, North Caro… https://t.co/X1Kj5VWpUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dating to marry so please don’t come my way if you’re looking to waste my time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Invest in the Business Leaders of Tomorrow https://t.co/gQF4gyUHzQ This #TigerGivingDay, we are seeking to raise $2… https://t.co/nhUdqJ6nal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous poops are commencing early this morning https://t.co/jI60wmYGGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejoesorg This is so sad (and crazy). I really wish we would all get on the same page here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CosCobKiller @OpTic_Scumper @ShawnAbner Not even close https://t.co/IGnFcYPnAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely charge, boat was innocently just standing there and dude smashed straight through him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT!!!  LET’S RAGE!!!! #darkwavedisco #darkwavedisconyc #markgertz #homesweethome #homesweethomenyc… https://t.co/IYTzkqzy0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/90boHNvb3h Nice to see @netflix continue their run of fine films with Paddleton. Enjoyed watching and… https://t.co/GP14dWr5wO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSnowMan72 @SonyaDevilleWWE @WWE_MandyRose She's about to snatch that SmackDown women's title]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EpiclyShort @DandRpodcast Lately it's been a matter of getting players. For my campaign and then second . Most dif… https://t.co/Mf0NNuXdUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But privately”   are you hiding in the closet or relying on your sources that were part of the Russia hoax ??… https://t.co/UKLLYAMApa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will forever love bombing, especially with a longboard, best feeling to be free]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNRGLDN @BrandyLJensen @stavvybaby The most beautiful. But not the most beautiful woman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceoofthenbm Wild right. Someone posted his defensive metrics and it did blow my mind but that was awhile ago. What happened to him!!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisBrownOnAir Wow, had to go there.....great question, unfortunately I’ll be pondering it the rest of the day. T… https://t.co/PNyM0kMizo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConradMcGorkin Concur.  I35 OK I29 BAD I635 Complete fucking disaster last night/this morning.  I really don't kno… https://t.co/7zoF1aEKQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahaha Hahahaha seriously, look at his face. This is the moment when he finally realized what a shitty movie he w… https://t.co/7s39Z1mMpV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realFFK God has been telling this man to leave this BIGOT. I don't know how someone with a SPIRITUAL understanding… https://t.co/Aax49fJejw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llegó Solo o con los cuernos Luis Miguel llegó a Lima y se hospedó en conocido hotel miraflorino | VIDEO… https://t.co/m7MOP4i89g]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your masseuse looks like the Rock and then gives you the lightest pressure massage you’ve ever had https://t.co/JKpHKY2M0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one better on the pre-show than @TheBethPhoenix! #WWEEliminationChamber is going to great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we get #GarrettSucks for @AstronomiconMI #Astro3 maybe a dunk tank? Lawn darts? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vodkaskank Why all the hostility towards Bradley? He's an actor, not a singer. He was acting. Not the worst thing… https://t.co/XRJGbUexub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chillee google could have award show and her ass would be there dressed to impress]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not moving from this spot all day ❤️🐾❤️🐾 #dogsofchicago #dogsofinstagram #furbaby #mydogismybestfriend… https://t.co/GBBwabzgNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast today competing with @AmberLeventry @hellobabydirect @dad2summit #changingdiapers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chasing rainbows: inside the battle between Radiohead and EMI's Guy Hands https://t.co/CGKLyVgyqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyMLBLineups When regurgitating news goes awry. Jim Salisbury is the reporter who first tweeted about Phillies… https://t.co/8DdIQufYZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two nights in a row once again christopher.k.carver comes thru from skinstoriestattoos and give me finally my… https://t.co/ILKLdTDC3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aveces uno no sabe lo que tiene hasta que lo pierde... https://t.co/MfsFrkYwDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattGlenesk @indystar He’s 80 perfect through the season- it’s clear he has no idea how to coach this team, to dev… https://t.co/HZUz9dJRo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having koolaid #margaritaville #nashville @ Margaritaville, Nashville https://t.co/2VEqmpBTfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adam_Jacobi The only question I have is why this tweet was scheduled at 6:36 AM. Why not something cleaner like 6:30 or 7?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobRathbunTV What was the 3rd? I know this and the Knicks. Was it the Cavs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my nurses ❤️even though they can be a pain in a *** sometimes for US RTs. Lol. #MedicalField #NightShift… https://t.co/yzxErLRpKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought Kanye was canceled??? We’re not supposed to like nothing he does anymore, right? The sarcasm is real.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @AOC Everyone knows she is an idiot. “Forgive her Lord, for she knows not what she does...”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que nervios en Abril nos encontraremos mis @NacimosBravos y yo en tierras yucatecas ⚾️👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeerLeagueHeroe @Josh_Waters97 @Lowetide @OilersNation I would prefer Brown and Johnsson myself.  Both will be che… https://t.co/1P9T9MyHqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValPac3 He was forced to either take a buyout or be fired. You think that’s a good deal or even a fair deal? The a… https://t.co/3Nc7WObAs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkyNarcotic @bratsabbath Psycho, Babadook, Candyman...There are literally hundreds of examples. This seems like… https://t.co/pSC2isL2zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. So I never had Pokémon cards. I never watched the show. I’ve never played any of the games. None of it ever rea… https://t.co/QNoxszRNqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cXvntD6Wvp Pelosi the door is CLOSING on the HOUSE you are going to lose CONTROL! These 4 MUSLIMS will… https://t.co/eXx1TpVVWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the memories! Now go get yours 🐐’s @AB84 @LeVeonBell https://t.co/CgZRco3FkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought me a shirt with pineapples, flamingos and palm trees on it today and I think it may be my new favorite shirt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course he’s 100% correct.  Consider Arrow’s Impossibility Theorem in the context of unassimilated multiculturali… https://t.co/HcvdTlFN6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Raleigh: scattered clouds, 25°F 92% humidity, wind 2mph, pressure 1028mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b_christ_ @13Duds @ajbjerkaas @KirkCousins8 @Vikings I love Keenum and what he accomplished, but no one wants him back 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only time I ever think to tweet anymore is when I realize I’m washed up/not cool anymore. Until further notice,… https://t.co/4bxjgGnxv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[A look at #LSU hoops rankings, stats, NCAA tourney projections &amp; more https://t.co/vcSOg1jFYX https://t.co/EVBjMEsT0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton Question becomes, why did our side sell us out? You've been out there, you know there are remedies to o… https://t.co/DiVCFFsmW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you gotta feed people BULLSHIT just to see who they run back and tell...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vocal Coaching will not only train you to use your voice properly but will help you develop into an awesome perform… https://t.co/TFvoU2K5XB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mornin y'all !!!! Waiting on my load to get ready . Should be done in an hour or two .  Headed back west to Odessa… https://t.co/ifVPA3mnV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaniceTXBlessed @ECHOtheCALL @realDonaldTrump  I am one of millions that voted for the president he needs to clean house]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seraphicpetal My goodness it looks like you are swallowing bullets! Will pray for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTyleneBuck Happy Birthday Tylene much love u rock girl!! You are the hottest and best!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valley aviation, 793 echo hotel coming up on final approach. #studentpilot #pilot #touchandgos @ Swoyersville, Penn… https://t.co/qtyWGVKeEw]]></document></documents></author>