<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LynleeGeorge @kingcanfilmfest It was great to see you, too! I loved Go Boy &amp; U-Turn...hope you enjoyed your movies as well 📽🎞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Potamie_ 😂😂😂 I learned just last week that this Pope was American! That's the most confusing thing 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaLang @NellOnWheels @_ajawilson22 I thought he was just unprofessional and had no journalistic training aor t… https://t.co/9waLAzzuGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[And that’s how I spent my Saturday! #glutenfree from scratch, chocolate cake, #bacon wrapped, spinach &amp; cheese… https://t.co/Hr9RI3a2i4]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I know is that I’m happier than I’ve ever been and he doesn’t comment on my insta pics and I couldn’t care less ❣️🤙🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[even when he stated that he loves women but hates bitches. He separated women based on their ideologies, or if he s… https://t.co/JLMLPTgmZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFMagus @uxprompts Not asking for coding help, but for designs.. of the design prompts, by designers, (if that makes sense?).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delaney’s first South Carolina visit as a declared presidential candidate was to Myrtle Beach for an… https://t.co/zUHbejHF5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamKeithFL Our candidate will emerge after a healthy respectful  exchange of ideas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllenPage Are just too blinded by your liberal bias that you can support a liar perpetratinga hoax that hurts inno… https://t.co/V052fDmUML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincipsofProsp Good question.  I think it starts with communication and intention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pantone165 @Twitter @johncusack @SenBooker @maddow @CoryBooker Watching. Stanford pals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally all @barbie_dancer22 and I complain about in Chemistry...while also complaining about Chemistry 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile back at @CA_PlanoTX, all the CAts are checking in for NCA practices today!👏🏼😻 The music will be loud,full… https://t.co/2tLRbFX9kK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZFed116 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣can not stop laughing! No drugs no evidence!!!!! 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣an act ofkindness=drug a… https://t.co/4AGFcsuNaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian You are sooo much better than the situation people try to put you in. Hold your head up high and k… https://t.co/5p5481XzlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is 6am spin! I love it!!!! Drenched in sweat and burn a lot of calories]]></document><document><![CDATA[And when they are exposed and their identities found out. Their wives mothers daughters will know the truth how they torture the community.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help Bring Back Face Off On SyFy - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/2AGrRRpvez via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[SkillsUSA District 11 champs! 1st, 2nd, and 3rd place teams. It was a sweep for Osbourn! #SkillsUSA #csi… https://t.co/mtbWjEZLAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StSenka I refuse to believe we are this dumb. However, it’s clear we are lazy af and can’t prioritize if our lives… https://t.co/ox7sEvCnnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Baggiepat @BarbaraHershey8 @ConchitaCampbel @RichardKahan @jenni_baird @JenniferSkyreal @sonya_cassidy… https://t.co/OE6GcWpAqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Each lap is a mile @ Reclaim Fitness Studio Co-Ed https://t.co/Xm2q1HlxFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstellaJeter Someone said that about me and well.. I got my karma 💁🏻💁🏻 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending @AARPVa All Volunteer College to learn about 2019 initiatives and how volunteers can make an impact in ou… https://t.co/XPLxF3yvhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all Khloe was a dumb bitch for not leaving him after the first time 🤷🏼‍♀️ once a cheater always a cheater… https://t.co/IlzdcfbF4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[SEE YOU AT SALT RIVER FIELDS TOMORROW #PUMPED  Side note: if you need tickets, the Center Field box office is open… https://t.co/I7fIGS2538]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Congresswoman shows her total disregard for grieving.    #AngelMom #AngelFamilies #BuildTheWall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope is a big room with lots of chairs because there is going to be a lot of us there... 😢 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s challenge our friendship! #BoardKings https://t.co/h1ztGzLjyN https://t.co/eHWKApt7uf https://t.co/h1ztGzLjyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m happy to announce I’ve finally recovered from my hangover from vodka when I was only 13 years old. Vodka crans are my shit again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone spent clearly over an hour writing this and failed to Google. I despair at online reporting. Rose is a not… https://t.co/PznESGKkRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone please carry my chipotle leftovers from my bed to my fridge so i can eat them tomorrow instead of shamefull… https://t.co/KkxWWamffi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wil__Hunter @OnSpartans MY GUY!  Also my take: This is the number one reason we’ve been successful this year - https://t.co/clA3nDDf5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OklaEd #OKSs #ThoughtfulThursday: In honor of #InternationalWomensDay⁠ ⁠tomorrow, teach students about the… https://t.co/qo45bZp4Sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile @SamsungMobileUS My husband and I in front of The Galt House Horse in Louisville, Kentucky! I'm trying to… https://t.co/ILdthraWn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asking him which nail color and the nigga reply with PINK powder my pussy has lifted]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could be the type of person who didn’t stress eat chicken nuggs and could stress eat carrots or kale 🤷‍♀️🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaKissi @TonyaGJPrince This simply must happen! Too many white children are learning intolerance and ignorance]]></document><document><![CDATA[My lady days give me insomnia and a roller coaster of emotions https://t.co/c5oZ4LxYfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, someone who knows: does Dante’s inferno have a level for people that use Jesus’s name as a tool to harm othe… https://t.co/MPkkvakZZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t heard from him in 2 days and I’m trying not to worry. We aren’t anything more than fuck buddies but can’t help but feel sad...]]></document><document><![CDATA[james cordon really got to sing let it be w paul mccartney... could u imagine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beanbrightly @AriMelber For reasons unrelated to @AriMelber’s show, I really needed that full excerpt of the lyric… https://t.co/kaXk4F5VdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[We stayed up late last night with friends who use words to mean power and who live exuberantly, powerfully, describ… https://t.co/Ff2iOliBhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimCantore I think mobile home parks owners should be responsible for putting a storm shelter in mobile home park… https://t.co/ksaq5I5Z65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDBerryMD @weightwatchers And they wouldn't have to make up "keto-crotch"!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya mate a uno y traje a otro de vuelta en Apex Legends, ya me siento pro. https://t.co/VfKoqN8HwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar Can I DM my resume to you anyway? I'm willing to relocate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The view as soon as you walk in the front door! Quite a site from house #1 #stgeorgeparadeofhomes #stgeorge #utah… https://t.co/Vf5KDv2oam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only do I love my pets.... They love each other, too!!!  - - #LoveYourPetDay #LauraSellsRE #Home #JustEngaged… https://t.co/u2jDrOra2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Migel2Uno That shouldn’t even be a question lol https://t.co/G9xwFnJhFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Skretta crossed 10K. Time 01:00:51, pace 09:38 min/mile, est. finish 12:18 pm https://t.co/TV0HjcIatV #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[So right and true under both GOP and Dem administrations @vanitaguptaCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Omarion "O" I swear if he perform this at the b2k concert, I'm gonna lose it 😂😭 @Omarion]]></document><document><![CDATA[28 days to opening day! Go Brewers! 👍🏻😁👏🏻🎉🙌🏻⚾️  "The game of life can be too short, so play with everything you've… https://t.co/7mZeDWbjE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow along here and on my Instagram @amcvetty today for a full day at Sea World's Seven Sea Food Festival! We hav… https://t.co/KGWUhb14jp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We know Kari Jobe more than the God that carried Job.” @JmontyStudios 💯🔥😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diallo Yaaaasss🎊🎉👏🏽👏🏽🙌🏽🙏🏽... congratulations to @essencesays ...well deserved ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[He has no friends, only children, creditors and debtors. #MichaelCohen #MichaelCohen #MichaelCohen #MichaelCohen An… https://t.co/DpD68ufTsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry about the rant.  I just needed to process and be honest. but know when I ask about how you are, I mean it. I'… https://t.co/0iWzJAZh88]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler_casper Black is the darkest color, the result of the absence or complete absorption of visible light. It is… https://t.co/5mkwsFHvEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social media guru 👇 #socialmediamarketing #socialmediamanagement #Realtor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillClinton @jguaido Just watched the movie "One Frame" and felt so proud of you, President Clinton. Was impressed… https://t.co/aPJc54qoym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yungnopal i support that plan !! &amp; platonic soulmates are real and yes we are!! hehe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christine Fallara started the Princess Half Marathon! https://t.co/DunbjTdoz7 #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s nothin quite as soothing as laying in a completely dark room, fan &amp; John Mayer on 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey! Look what we did! #newstudio #mywiferules sparkling_soul_wellness @ Woodland Hills, California https://t.co/qZsa6UP0Fh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guarantee she confronted him in front of the whole class to humiliate  him about it which further escalated. What… https://t.co/KsklGpjGVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @kkeen0 did you know today is #internationalinternetfriend day?! You're the best friend I've never met!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsJachymiak @MrsHankinsClass @StantonAlana @RaeHughart @ChristineBemis2 @hayes_melisa @jeffgargas @tamaraletter… https://t.co/krtSr2nLY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tenho cara de babaca pra deixar de me seguir por causa da namorada daí termina e me segue vai toma no cu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Freak, freak, freak nasty Ice on my neck, let it drip down my chest Look at this muthafucking money make me wet Ri… https://t.co/kyjejYF4kc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi vicio ☕️ al despertar y para todo el día y para ir a la cama ☕️👌🏼 nada como una tasa de café ☕️ 🥰😘 u mas si teng… https://t.co/ZLZQeli9BF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sensei_Indigo I just love him and his humor and his talents MAY GOD IN HEAVEN BLESS HIM IN THE NAME OF JESUS AMEN AND HALLELUJAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denisebella @LadyTLove123 @venicetheseries @crystalchappell @sanbar769 @popspeach @Malti_Sharma @jeanettedoswell R… https://t.co/mJNeirf1wV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Or, south of Columbus 4 miles to Shane Creek Road then 14 miles east.  Contact Information:  Mailing A… https://t.co/I3ZXTCnpKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EagleSoulMan @gottogetoutof @AlyseTobler @TSCLI @SaugasideTori @EndingSilence01 @DamosLawSP @mjnanna @livingwithabuse Ok sorry about that]]></document><document><![CDATA[We defeated a motion to dismiss #ATS claims brought by survivors of the Lutheran Church Massacre in the #Liberian C… https://t.co/CPfHj3CUpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankiLoveMusic The fact that my old ass got out of bed this morning! 🙏😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HemiWhisperer22 @ShSherrer @Kert200 @shotgunsmoke12 @rebrokerjoe @PigglyAGoGoMAGA @flowerpot197 @GraftedInByLove… https://t.co/xKZfabq0EA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to give Illinois beer some love tonight. - Drinking an Alto Porto  Porter by @AlterBeer at @burgerone2  — https://t.co/TA1qBhEbM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GLOSSPHOENIX Thank you Miss Jennifer God is good and thank you for confirmation God bless you and have a blessed day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Privileged to hear @AmyCEdmondson speak about Fearless Organizations: 1. Embrace enterprise mindset 2. Promote inte… https://t.co/5YtbW9Alyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catturd2 Hope they come up against this hero   https://t.co/JBAOvwucHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This didn't surprise me. #traitortrump has the reputation of not paying his peons, bankrupting them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNTata2000 @narendramodi Keep in mind that ancestor of Pakistanis is Mohammad Ghazni, their policy is same as Moha… https://t.co/P1YJbtcB1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGoonersPod @irelands4courts The ‘burbs are wild. https://t.co/pgyOMGkNfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My stye is much better, and I ate breakfast so far. Here’s to a brighter day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BusterSpiller @Jasonbeckman11 @RepMaxineWaters I’m guessing with your humor you reallly don’t work much.  Bless yo… https://t.co/Z1nfw2Ih2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[#recovery time with this sweet kiddo... I love that she drinks tea @ Salinas, California https://t.co/9OPd3GTEKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathySchwab77 @GeorgeTakei I agree, Bernie has good ideas but he would basically hand Trump another win.  T need t… https://t.co/1KZjgqErvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[who is this Julz person? i automatically thought Juelz Santana bc that’s all i know. 🌚]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying a nutritious meal while discussing the future or work at the first ever @elnonline’s #CivicDish event. Loo… https://t.co/0yNfZ7cKP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suziday123 @vinovolo @flyLAXairport @GrnLakeGirl @DemiCassiani @pietrosd @_drazzari @MyVirtualVaca @RoadtripC… https://t.co/QiJGVKNglz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsRobThomas @MatchboxTwenty So awesome! You deserve it...Congratulations!🎉🥂😊♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two styles of ice cream eating. I’m with the dog on the left. @ Strachan's Ice Cream &amp; Desserts, Dunedin https://t.co/8vZt1vN0sJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Frum on MSNBC tonight with Steve Kornacki used a word that encapsulates the Trumpian administration/travesty… https://t.co/DuRqJy8Kap]]></document><document><![CDATA[the security guard dressed as indiana jones on the door of the star wars-themed bar wished me a happy almost birthday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaked Documents Show the Government Tracking Journalists https://t.co/ky2VVLMkyA via @nbcsandiego]]></document></documents></author>