<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AdamSKutner I say we get Stone a PPG, sound good?!?! #AdamKutnerPowerPlay #VegasBorn #GoKnightsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me &amp; Elijah 🥰 @elijahcorral1 #friends #wegeteachother https://t.co/kxEcPJlt1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris The idea that you racially-divided this country in your defense of con artist now suspected felon… https://t.co/BbMXxLkCcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you  do pretty good,,, with good sponsor,,,,, https://t.co/y2Rj1eSX3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into Houston Punk Rock Royalty and longtime acquaintance Christian Kidd of The Hates at the Hard Luck Revival s… https://t.co/aLupfEjVXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Djmwhb3C @bigredwavenow @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @SecretService @NSAGov @FBI @DHSgov @Telford_Russian Anyone w… https://t.co/HtTHcfXbSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raisafuenmayor Muchas gracias Raisa y que así sea cuídate y feliz día ,!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCarlAdams94 @GameSpot You don’t need to comment to show you don’t care]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to hearing from addiction experts on how we can do better for the millions of people suffering.… https://t.co/rIGCHbFp5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s display @Target  Still waiting to get another wave of Star Wars Vintage figures from @Hasbro. This everlast… https://t.co/beEaY6ZbAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PharmacistReb @Chozraham @therealroytovar @HuntsmanAbby I'm wondering why any of this matters. You mean to tell me… https://t.co/abPr3JboFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charged Shot Gamescast Episode 105: YouTube Demonitizing Big Black Business  https://t.co/5hNJapIcTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MannyDouglas419 Or would you trade OBJ for our 24th, first rounder from the Bears next year and out 2nd rounder? S… https://t.co/lluHymd822]]></document><document><![CDATA[People be calling Chris Brown Crack Brown and it’s completely fine cause I been to rehab too so like oh well 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalShort @ckennison47 Increased her net worth off of the backs of her constituents who are among the most poor. #termlimits]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to get some @DBKelsoLongview ☕ before i head out!! Hope yall have a good one!!! @ Longview, Washington https://t.co/vtIHez1rZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RHR002 @andieart808 @clarencehilljr @NPR I'm saying fact check your source young fella.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PCobbs43 Good quote but I’m pretending someone else said it. Geaux Tigers and Go Mean Green! ;) #TexasTiger #MeanGreen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Did you give President Putin another handjob in his honor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all out here eating the booty like groceries but won’t eat the end of the bread. Smh. Can’t trust y’all in these streets!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it to @TTUSystem Day at the Capitol! #GunsUp #WreckEm #txlege https://t.co/gH1yF0aTRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly the heat sucks but way more things can get done and my knees won’t hurt by just going outside]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BGiesenschlag We haven’t peaked yet this season. We’re saving it for late March or April ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday my boyfriend and I spent quality time together by getting our cat to eat treats off my face. I love my relationship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[50 percent of people answered this correctly. Can you? https://t.co/pIVKqM2yw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge study confirms people who exercise feel better. Causality less clear- does exercise improve #MentalHealth or d… https://t.co/5LuugZI3GB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaPerino @JesseBWatters @EmilyCompagno @dbongino @PlanetTyrus // as an introvert I want to thank @greggutfeld fo… https://t.co/tEeUMa97VC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remind me: Why have we lumped Nixon, LBJ, Coolidge and Buchanan with Washington, Jefferson, Adams and Madison?… https://t.co/EVIjxt1UHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reason why people won’t become who they want, is because they are too attached to who they’ve been... ~B~]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisamatonm Que lastima, vistió a los papás de nosotros los cuarentones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuruLupus Just thought this to myself to the tune of the pizza bites song]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcushjohnson But that one time had such an effect on him! Just look at him now! He’s aged a million years!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mark_volkmann @sseraphini @dan_abramov @reactjs Or maybe the component (I don't know its structure I'm speculating… https://t.co/fS7PSkERCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keaton Vogel is this year’s recipient of the Jason Even Memorial $2,500 Scholarship for team spirit, enthusiasm for… https://t.co/SuZ8bzOJNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJr @GregMcElroy @BMSupdates @BMSupdates is a good start, or my home track @TooToughToTame Can’t go wrong with either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jiminssockpaws @junghjackson @JIMINSPROMlSE You have alot of nerve saying that as though theres no domestic violen… https://t.co/9h9QaaA8dv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg The NRA has never killed anyone. Planned parenthood on the other hand kills 4,000 human babies a d… https://t.co/ACcnwPSx7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at Monongalia County Ballpark for @WVUBaseball 2019 Home Opener! #HailWV https://t.co/18gyCmdOVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Melissaabecerra @seaiiruh @sorrkky @faby_h24 I do tf sjsk who said I didn’t I miss my friends too :( also i’ve nev… https://t.co/omPqpqd8LN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT Point taken, but do YOU think that's sufficient reason for not raising it now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a nice gesture to me, skeptical that it is the desired intention of supporters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge Thanks to Mark for his continuous Trust here with D’Arcy GMC!!! His 13th truck from the D’Arcy Group.  Enjoy y… https://t.co/oeWx2LNgX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/O to everyone commenting and showin lots of love for this week’s episode of @realdncpod! Your efforts to listen w… https://t.co/JrAJAmopYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a look at the wwe title  @JCLayfield is carrying here then look at that manstrosity @WWEDanielBryan is carrying around]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend at the @gateriverrunjax #usa15kchampionships was pretty brutal, it was a race where I pushed and pushe… https://t.co/eO0VPYTuiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kritical419 you still got your ps3? i have the original 3 digitally if you serious]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTH with this level of stupidity and craziness? 🚹 and 🚺 r different! There r 2 sexes: 🚹 and 🚺!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realshanerichie @BLuisaW @YeoAnnette Shane X"DDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chitoseofficial @NakiTenshi Trolls can be annoying but banning is usually enough.  If you think it’s the same pers… https://t.co/TJFwLyKD0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!!!! @peteslivingrns #organic butter lettuce on sale @BallardMarket for $2.98 https://t.co/GqmapJOodH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody wanted a reunion tour like the Xscape reunion. 🤷🏽‍♂️ Sorry B2K but y’all needed more time...]]></document><document><![CDATA[or whatever) in a settlement, well, that’s substantial for them in their lives. In the history of American jurispru… https://t.co/2ueMhF5wDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karl Anthony Towns officially has as many points as the @Pacers whole team. 🤦‍♂️  #Pacers]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the Middle of His Official Business, Trump Took the Time to Send Checks to Michael Cohen @peterbakernyt… https://t.co/gQE7GCmuMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to thank the local news for their attempt to throw Cincy in a panic over a dusting. It’s pathetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because the permissible injury rehab stint had ended, and they can’t send him back to LV or they’d risk losing him… https://t.co/zgxnfeEisb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The milkshake to Frappuccino rebrand was the most iconic thing to happen in my lifetime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living in my house is like being a member of the Avengers... I finally get through one crisis with the kids only to… https://t.co/4lueXXsqPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@not_isaiah03 2A school. 300 enrollment, tops.  That is the student section they brought.  I know you’re struggling… https://t.co/gHZye5FVuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachTrout10 Need post this on Facebook for all them to see. I should tag a few parents]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HHSEngineering1 students 3D printing our steering wheel for this year’s @Greenpower_USA competition! @HarlingenHS… https://t.co/qLHtGDtMdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of having politicians, why not elect people with good old fashion commen sense?? Oh, because they wouldn't… https://t.co/aWMa9uTJEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmbryEthan @DonaldJTrumpJr Which is exactly why it is a preferred sidearm by law enforcement]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilysoriginal I get that he wasn’t doing that well tonight, but I was shocked he wasn’t getting more minutes down… https://t.co/IekOd3nHE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephen Whistler crossed 20K. Time 02:06:29, pace 10:27 min/mile, est. finish 11:34 am https://t.co/nrGkibKKie #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Human rights mean nothing unless we defend real, threatened people | Kenan Malik https://t.co/DacBqMQHr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[to try and get tickets to see maggie rogers in oakland on april 19th ugh i wanna die]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing more popular each day. Democrats are being exposed as the Socialists they are and people learn of the faile… https://t.co/cBu9rv36d7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys The BEST Way to Help someone is to give them what they NEED!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danno2430 Now I need Elton John to break all sports news. Imagen him breaking into Philadelphia Freedom to announce Harper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@npierce84 @GTBaseball @ACCNetworkExtra Safe to say broadcast booths are built for softees]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess it’s “cold” for Oregon for this time of year but have y’all looked at those Midwest temps?!? This is the wa… https://t.co/A3F7ByLaXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DustyAnimemes sorry to bitch ik this probs Sucks to see bc. it all Sucks. &lt;3 &lt;3 tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJamesMattone Imagine being excited about the   N E W   Y O R K   M E T S  ...for any reason other than Tim Tebow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics The only people that are going to screw this up is a Democratic Socialist Party and the Socialist news fake news]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I’m picturing every single pitch will go in the rest of today’s game https://t.co/900XWtS7Yk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either Delphox or Arcanine I cannot decide between my babies https://t.co/6rwbiGFQSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peacemakerPete Wait.. is this tweet trying to gaslight me?? Haha I’m a BYU guy through and through and I never onc… https://t.co/7TpdDxTkJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We may be able to come together and uplift each other like no one else, but we can also tear each other down like n… https://t.co/cttfMSX22I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Lies...lies...lies #PresidentPinocchio https://t.co/cUiNICBp2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like, I cannot eat and you know it, but I have to be nice and if I am forced to eat, I better have something light, not spicy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did pretty good considering the weather conditions. 10mi race ended up 15 overall out of 126 and 2nd in Age group… https://t.co/gDcpUAIEyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find roommates who’ll support your crushes better than mine, I’ll wait https://t.co/X3ZK2iqCcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched @TheTreyRose’s audition. Super emotional.  Can’t wait to watch this guy jump up 10K followers in the next few weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHumble_21 @LeVeonBell @Earl_Thomas @Mathieu_Era @weddlesbeard Man aye I’ll personally buy you a pair of buffs if you come to the D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vancouver high school students disciplined over alleged #bullying list  CTV Vancouver   https://t.co/4qRZbYRxrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SpikeLeewhat a big baby and sore losers Lee is. In my neighborhood he would have to hide. Little punk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait for these days again ecoxcreative lansburial onyxdesigncollaborative #setstaging #luxuryhomes #interiors… https://t.co/WXpX8tbIGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kpoc Alma mater of many fine hockey players, and at least one member of Phish if I’m not mistaken]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goats out here missing the Playoffs in their prime huh https://t.co/fXSD7AP2XI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gabino_Iglesias Most writers I know (meaning ones who didn't have most all of their shit optioned to Hollywood), h… https://t.co/uELabk39bH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Donnie, there are 4 letters in Cook. Apple has 5 letters. So, it should be easier for you Big fella. Why lie about this too??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahForcier I’m sorry Hannah I hope you can take a nap or something so you don’t overdo things but you’re probab… https://t.co/tIfVcos6ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Code letters babe. Code for ily. Like my favorite. O’Brians brother, ily.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mechesimosa Hay tiempo para amar y tiempo para odiar. Pero nunca es tiempo de cesar la lucha para el rescate de la democracia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cletribegirl Depends on the beer. And as much as I like Skyline, this honestly sounds like a terrible idea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Manruss @ottovonshitpost @JacobAWohl I mean, "person" seems to be an extraordinarily generous term for folks like… https://t.co/1SSTpbAr6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rebeldill75 @dkhtx @DonaldJTrumpJr I don’t think they’ll be out of jail by then 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamzaKK @ManUtd @Ibra_official A free transfer set the club back??? Get a clue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sad day for a denomination I’d come to respect, and an enormous challenge for schools affiliated with them. This… https://t.co/ALVvktQPgs]]></document></documents></author>