<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This is the least excited I've been for #InternationalWomensDay since I understood that it existed. Every post I've… https://t.co/k7o43HBzzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[because our happiness does not depend on people’s recognition and praises.  We find an inner peace in us, living ou… https://t.co/wjjvSiBRxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to invest in cameras on my front lawn because these neighbors just let loose their dogs all over my grass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WithPod should we motivate #ClimateActionNow by fear of extreme future? I get fear’s appeal but it’s a bad idea. C… https://t.co/rNa4O0VXK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Avoided_Anomaly but then when that turns out to be a success, they'll claim they were against it too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manifestation is SO real, you guys. Speak the things you want into the universe and it will bless you with them when the time is right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fell asleep with my hand on my laptop, in the middle of importing pictures.  So that tells you how much work I actu… https://t.co/ovTSqxaSY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrouciDjamila @pamdon18 @morgenpost @faznet @DogsofYulin SHAME GERMANY SHAME JUDGE'S FROM YOUR COUNTRY JUDGING A D… https://t.co/cUV3ZM23pX]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏🏾😭🙏🏾👨🏾‍💼 Wow wow wow!!! Finally got to see #ChoirBoy yesterday. There are only a few more chances left to catch th… https://t.co/Iqm15wxlFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It must be nice being ugly and regular. Don’t nobody ever be bothering y’all huh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sensualhazel I’m down for lean and toned AF, that’s not too much is it? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always get a Venti for my shift and a tall for the ride to work which is like 10 min from the Starbucks.. send help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone reposted and broke my link. Ahem! The #SpaceXFleet is halfway home! No, I won't be predicting arrival just… https://t.co/BT2sVOsy8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timothée Chalamet’s voice isn’t what I expected it to be. He sounds like such a man 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeedNews @shanedawson ❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️ look at this!!!! it’s you!!! 🐷🐷🐽🌮🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KillaKam1947 Lmao actually I don’t haha I had used the free trial from when u first sign up and instead of cancell… https://t.co/j2WNUcum2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still a bitch. Still lying every so-called answer she gives. This is pointless as they always were. #pressbriefing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Thank God!  Don't debate.  All you do is show your ignorance by calling people names. No… https://t.co/2HIgPJx1cb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ricka168 @HowardSchultz Hahaha. Exactly what I said. And I really meant it, too😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[especially when these great trees are fully dressed in brilliant green leave. (I blame my Mom's love of Shepherd of… https://t.co/lwYsL2NF1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamRam2333 Happy Anniversary to both of you!🥂🎉🥂...More years to come.😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[.ugh what a rough night of sleep😣 not sure if I'll make it through the day 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilygasoi @GenePinkard @Ward1EdCouncil @BeckyCReina @dcpublicschools @AnacostiaHigh @DCSBOE On another note: do y… https://t.co/A0fPEEFkgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brein789698 Those rankings only change weekly and have no impact on bracketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her compassion and moral compass are one of the many reasons that I think Elizabeth Warren would make an great pres… https://t.co/W6SOwRNsLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pd4wson @MacKenziePMusic @EricMcCormack @JaredAbrahamson @PatrickGilmore @LeahCairns @NestaCooper I was trying to… https://t.co/UFIEdgXztt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bravo @GayleKing quietly, patiently in control while he just implodes and let’s everyone see the real @rkelly #Bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for honest and loyal sugar baby that I can get to share my check with.. Will be receiving a weekly all… https://t.co/rRlb5fVE1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not sure what you mean, like the Grade Point Average?  If you get straight A’s it’s 4.0 GPA, etc but not all co… https://t.co/mcsVqS8v2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to rock n roll. First show at Bigg Daddys Helen tonight until 11pm. Last show of the weekend. Nashville road… https://t.co/qEL6Xe6J1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tgifraidy @xoJustJessicaxo I guess it depends on what you like, or I can just give you a few of my favorites?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“At @leapinchicago, we don’t think the change happens at the school board or even the district level. It’s happens… https://t.co/AXvtFoHZUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanMillerbrad @tutty352 @LakesStiles @ceadela @thisismenic70 @teresa_knox @LansdellMum @laxidaisy @tessthebutler… https://t.co/nRlpL9ii1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Shut up....all of this crap has already been dealt with. Stirring up meaningless verbal vomit...be… https://t.co/MACrJZGNHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chanceseales I can see why! It makes me smile, not easy before my first cup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @BenSPLATT @beamiller @jonasbrothers and @Hozier on all the new music. Loving all of it- especially that Hozier album omf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGoodNewsom @YouTube @ashleyymarcum @yokesideup I wish I could go back and do it over bc we could be so much better now 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaJen6 Good! Was getting worried!!! That’s crazy that it went that high?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolineTXBQ @Capitals @NHL @CarlHagelin As a caps fan, I can say I don’t give a shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Debating if I should shoot my shot.... but then again I’m such a pussy lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thick Cut Veal Bacon as my appetizer 😋😍 I'm really having the BEST birthday ever! @butternyc @ Butter Restaurant https://t.co/isuLag6NRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so over sports. Every league is corrupt and riddled with awful people. I understand that it's just entertainmen… https://t.co/dyBTb9eJt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump California is part of the USA, you know this right? Right?  Then again, maybe you don't. It's like… https://t.co/XFUMyO1WCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude everyday is Russian roulette for immigrants in this country and all mfs wanna do is work &amp; provide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photo shoot with both my Turtwigs! #pokemongo #turtwig #smeargle https://t.co/UCEaOJkyu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[why couldn’t i hav e gotten a good memory who’s in charge here i just wanna talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a very upsetting dream that a stranger was wearing my coziness pair of socks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 Female Pirates You Should Know About                                                 https://t.co/jvOfvMaBOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Use money you got to build barriers in strategic spots and reevaluate. Stop your hysteria.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#repost workinprogress_advisory ・・・ ONE MORE DAY! It’s the final day to join us in artist @kmainenti #metooboutique… https://t.co/urO7DVQpLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Read about our latest job opening here: Associate Logistics - https://t.co/B61gftEmUD #logistics #Destin, FL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Looby007 @martine_piers @LZ181818 @PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump Reporting you Linda . Masked kkk troll . Follow p… https://t.co/6NEJD3OmzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching some @hallmarkchannel saw this #Toffifay with #Hazelnut mention ws all I needed to get out on a wet rainy… https://t.co/OEascMVA7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[CNN has effed up now! Losing huge amounts of their audience. Bad move CNN. Bad move.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who was the model for Calvin Klein @ShawnMendes or Benito? That’s what I’m wondering lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trumpovic02 @LeahR77 @skb_sara @KatTheHammer1 @jojoh888 @DaRealGrizzle @Barnett20Todd @SiddonsDan @StacyLStiles… https://t.co/w4jdfjRMeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re wondering about the “joys of parenting”, my daughter has figured out how to take off her diaper and this… https://t.co/whebOzn0EF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I didn’t have to be there cause my bestie was there and my bestie tells me everything” 🤞🏼😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir Rrknup is the locator. Beaumont Texas to Wichita Kansas with layover in Dallas February 23]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my @BdaleESports R6 Siege PS4 captain @Willsosa21_ and his @HSELesports Winter Open All Star team that… https://t.co/REt6f35tz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory Ladies &amp; Gentlemen: Here he is—our CARTOON president:🤣🤣🤡🍊🥜🥴🌊☮️❄️ https://t.co/APz6Aj3QvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost They can get away with anything and there are no consequences! True sign we are living in a dictatorial society. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a sugar substitute very deadly to dogs. It’s in gum and many “sugar free” items.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 Trump needs to be put in a straight jacket and locked away]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mañana tengo campaña de vacunación antes de las 8am hasta las 7pm y la niña está en terraza 🙄🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jazzayers My son has 2 brothers ... 1 younger and 1 older... different moms and right now he's not growing up with… https://t.co/6b94Jgisx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oooo insomnia mixed with random panic attacks, i missed you I’m so glad you decided insert yourself back into my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miltdawg The disparity needs to be addressed. It is also sometimes a challenge to find a rehab that accepts their… https://t.co/ajlqiLXpP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wanderlustin I know! I happened to see a tweet about it last weekend and was like hell yeah let's do it but people have been quiet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_arriaga94 Well gotta put them I. The same state first🤷🏽‍♂️ then we’ll see what your disappointment can do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vspattillo Please Do The More We Get Slapping His RW Ass Down The Better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que tipo de ritual satánico tengo que hacer para conseguir mil pacientes ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so sad to learn of Dr. Bill Reid’s passing. I remember his incredible kindness to his patients and colleagues.… https://t.co/iJm7724bun]]></document><document><![CDATA[POWER OUTAGE REPORTED: Several traffic lights are down along AIrport Blvd. near E. 46th Street, APD assisting w/ tr… https://t.co/nD1AHWjuwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christinaslux @AmeliesBakery @Adventuringgal @KaraDiDomizio @MattsRoadTrip @Sostraveluk @thethirstytales… https://t.co/WrAoIDHqwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being hurt by someone you love is one thing. Being hurt by someone you trust is literally something else… https://t.co/Bcw1vqqee2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having Hulu has really shown me how dependent I am on early 2000s @ABCNetwork sitcoms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreneBrown Faith and Courage.  Courage to have Faith and Faith to have Courage. https://t.co/e7znQz9FAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madShana Good morning,  Barbara! Happy Saturday to you, Sweetie! Has the wind calmed down in Vegas? How are you an… https://t.co/bsKOpPsuzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“To fall in love with yourself is the first secret to happiness.” -Robert Morley https://t.co/h3QtnIJCEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[ISO ADVICE: Currently the extent of my current social outings are pretty limited to pinball related events/activiti… https://t.co/sLw0lI3xdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalifaxEditor I find it funny that people think editors are obsessed with typos. We have bigger fish to fry, friends. #notaproofeader]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I really have to get up? It's 10am but It's 46 degrees in NE FLA. To a Floridan that's too cold for our warm wea… https://t.co/SMx1BmQg1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN You know what? I'm sick of this Michael Jackson bullshit. I don't believe it. He's not here to defend himself.… https://t.co/9tBlkhi1Le]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilovelivesafari I’m still new and never “met” Hosana — did he like to inspect the foam of those nests? I am so bum… https://t.co/aNuEjFQkz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MustangFishing Congrats Beltz/Bailey!!  👏 I saw somewhere that was out of 500+ teams 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoHWFanClub Good morning @BravoHWFanClub I loved the pictures of your birthday dinner 🤗🎂how's your Sunday going?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s noon on the east coast. @ Riviera Golf &amp; Tennis https://t.co/Q6IwcYW5jf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking about implementing new strategies in the classroom and teachers stepping out of their comfort zone… https://t.co/LpOuwtWt25]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m falling in love with places I’ve never been. I knew when walking NYC streets I’ve never seen felt familiar that… https://t.co/oA14sEkVup]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve taken up a new cause and it’s getting #Champions uncanceled this show is amazing?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone else was a victim of the @Jasper_Ghost_ or @KingOfTheblue accounts, DM please. We can talk. I will not pr… https://t.co/eu8Tvl7f6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MenaBuchner That's great Mena. I'm so happy for you. https://t.co/V7gIqGaKsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point I kinda give up on learning to speak it cuz I know that I will have an accent and my pronunciation wi… https://t.co/ZcsImk1GFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhSkeetKowala Idk what u talking bout this thing gonna gimme nightmares]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @libertythePD My Mom was a German war bride! She looked forward to coming to this country,  i'm sure… https://t.co/l9GRT8liSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmlTN @djrothkopf Don’t worry about weapons. The Trump business oriented folks, are always thinking profit when th… https://t.co/mY1b3jNBPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ed Hess crossed 5K. Time 00:33:32, pace 10:48 min/mile, est. finish 9:41 am https://t.co/QtKGguj6UP #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LunaBelle_Cat Beautiful year you had LunaBelle and congrats on your being there at your forever home 1 year ago to… https://t.co/Pd05cQAeb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only I would decide to rearrange my whole room after a 10 hour shift 🤧 finally done tho]]></document></documents></author>