<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2Britta Good morning Britta and happy Friday 🌫🌫🌧🌧. Can you follow me on twitter 👍👍☕️☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone running around doing a lot of nothing, no time for family, friends nor community. #IntentionalCommunity #Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don’t care about anything but that dude running into that little girl high chair. Hope that baby is okay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still think Clemson needs to win at least a game in the ACC tournament to feel safe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marisela 2019 Sábado 30 de Marzo para boletos llama: 800.668.8080 o visite:https://t.co/ySxwak4cCC @FoxSalinas… https://t.co/UQv7JCyuJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoGotIt Bro coke is HORRIBLE for you 😂 go in YouTube and look at what you can clean with it 😭 no reason for us to be investing that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emeraldbulldog @realDonaldTrump I never said i was a socialist.  classic fox news.  labeling people with no information.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Evans wanting today Matmardigan and Oscar wanting to be snake, why aren’t these in production yesterday?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlgap @lajornadaonline jajajajaaja qué pedo wei. Están actuando a favor de la sociedad sudcaliforniana y de todos… https://t.co/0s15q1lGPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SpringBreak @LucysKeyWest  $10 All You Can Drink Every Night #KeyWest is Cray Cray https://t.co/vMSuR8Dy4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nkwanyanad @HOKAONEONE I am leaning towards sticking with the Clifton line!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmbc Patrick, you should try our pizza place in Lee’s Summit, @pizzaandpours. It’s pretty awesome and On Deck Pizz… https://t.co/D8XpDvGfot]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t be up by 23 to duke with 9 minutes left and loose, get blown out by Syracuse, and be up on us and tank...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unfollowing everyone on ur Instagram to make ur page look cool is not part of marketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[To sign off Love Day, here's some light trail handiwork from a night in Joshua Tree with friends. I'll call this on… https://t.co/PH0brcpHv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DefiantlyFree @justanurse25 @NucMM1retired @PolitiBunny @OrdyPackard @TCC_Grouchy @RowdyRick73 @MartiniShark… https://t.co/i2VCFKyQuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wenlamei If you feel that it’s compromised your position there, talk to a lawyer. Then you know if there’s a case.… https://t.co/9VbF3UkMls]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a tribute to Greg’s YouTuber that he watches, I give you “Lumpy”. @ Shake Shack https://t.co/PPA0Kh9qzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@law_champagne South Florida is awesome. The rest of it is Georgia with more bugs/animals that can kill you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hcapriles @RCR750 Díganme como combatimos estos antisociales sin armamentos? Acaso debemos permitir que asesinen n… https://t.co/aT2L2NUwwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JessieJames100 lol I’m talking about his height and weight , he is short as hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burtsgaminghub Great question. Especially 2008 and 2009. They were always one piece away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaldingsWorld You might consider Dream Beans coffee in Hanoi, by the cathedral, when there. Young Vietnamese guy r… https://t.co/5icWq5CqPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump All your tweets won't keep people from watching @MichaelCohen212 testimony #DUMMY!  He's going to… https://t.co/USISDAb487]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thottyproctor tbh @KaceyMusgraves should have just performed instead of present 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCinciBiz @kevinflynncincy Their claim that FC Cincinnati isn’t negotiating in good faith... is really ... “th… https://t.co/7qmjXpACNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyDetoni The NY Post is owned by @FoxNews @RupertMurdoch And he says that is exactly what Trump Republicans pla… https://t.co/RlAKBioqRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you say, “The Lord is my refuge,”and you make the Most High your dwelling,no harm will overtake you, no disaster… https://t.co/qtpgztp6On]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I have found another good candidate to join our weather staff… https://t.co/kil7siY7mk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scttrmac No doubt. That’s a group of kids that has won at everything and easily should’ve been in Lincoln for football as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Professors are assigning so much work. Ughhh get a life!!!!!! Worry about yourself please. https://t.co/qrksRo1Va8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noam Chomsky  - History of US Rule in Latin America https://t.co/0ep6pKqwAJ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apologize to my mom so sorry bout the past. For every time I didn’t clean the house or cut the grass. Or the time I… https://t.co/Ir3xFvlcZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eclith That how I was this morning, I was thinking about calling in this morning but this month of February has le… https://t.co/clwbjkKG3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day to my beautiful fiancée! @KiaWhitney 😘😉 https://t.co/YJG7rzSqNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just hope that the people I care about care about me as much as I do then]]></document><document><![CDATA[The twincityzens and I made it on the @nbcsportssoccer broadcast today!#myplmorning #cmoncity  (Thanks Verizon). @… https://t.co/GwM2M4eMv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look who I found on the wall in the WMU lockeroom. Coach Haverdink!!! @PortageNorthern https://t.co/lF2gzyHzKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep a dead one on my keychain to remind me the impact one simple thing can have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeMurioChispita De Coahuila con ascendencia e Colima y Jalisco.   Tierra del verdadero cabrito asado,  la deuda im… https://t.co/gOFf27y2MF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s in the Virgin Islands? I’ll be there! Turn up. 🤪 https://t.co/IFWUGjbFCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encuentro con tonejo_rodriguez en las aguas de Miami a bordo del contrarianmiami Vienes con nosotros? #sail #boat… https://t.co/4Kvqn00CEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BirdmanMarco I think kingdom would end in 2040 .I’d probably be 65 years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go PATS!! @985TheSportsHub @BosHeraldSports @BostonSportsOn https://t.co/C8CdfPIldH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@porsha4real #porshawilliams @bingeworthyvid #realhousewivesofatlanta @bravotv #bravotv @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/rzi2mOcc9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xotonironixo Unless Ryan goes after Josslyn or Kristina or someone Jason cares about, he's got no business in this story]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin Thank you Michelle for your fiery speech at CPAC. Loved you are a true Patriot.#KAG 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @realDonaldTrump  You are so full shit... Nothing you say is even close to being true!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFricke @Bighugh53 I would love to see Bryce Harper come to the ATL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TobyAaron Demi is indeed a CRACKHEAD! Stop trying to give her ass a pass bc she’s a yt woman🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GIFSkull They can comfortably go an hour. Wrestlemania will be like 80 anyway]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tasty!! - Drinking a Lines by @anchoragebrew/@monkishbrewing @ Gerhart’s Garden  — https://t.co/nY2Wj3lu6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Tom Bradley International Terminal (TBIT) - @flylaxairport in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/vkQE1eiKkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a proposal. Let’s start referring to states as the head of that state. “Netanyahu”s Israel - just call it Ne… https://t.co/OmkCXWzfeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty fuckin great burfday 👌🏼😤🥳 thanks for all the well wishes https://t.co/CsV5DVHBKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sckit Ok then I need to re-listen to that cuz that makes it even funnier lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stood in the dog food aisle for way too long, agonizing over flavors and thinking things like “oh Wilderness Blend… https://t.co/r4YR5unoYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet a $100 on the warriors -6.5 either I’m paying for the Celtics to show me life or they are paying me https://t.co/IFRgHwu0cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Debbie_Teashon @HoarseWisperer It was a false video Debbie. The real version is out know. I just posted it from… https://t.co/mQp6Yh6zbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJJoyner @pptsapper But remaining “loyal” to a state that seceded BECAUSE of slavery (as most of the Confederate… https://t.co/AFZnNmPST7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly FTP has nothing to do with today's cops, I just thought it was ironic that that's what came on when we ackn… https://t.co/wqvztjOogS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched a documentary from @CNN on Netflix on the 2000’s they talked about the start of the internet age in one of… https://t.co/svPal0YkYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZephyrTeachout Publicly financed elections w/o instant runoff is anarchy not democracy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morganapple What about a shoe horn for them loafers? Rec. Omsorg from IKEA. Also an excellent backscratcher and laundry hooker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amnesty You're confusing tactics (short-term moves) with strategy (the over all goal) a peaceful incorporated DPRK… https://t.co/0xYIQvwm9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The VA lawmakers truly deserve praise and recognition for passing this bill. They willingly gave some of their powe… https://t.co/OO8s2sm6Ib]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got woken up by the dog two hours early and couldn't get back to sleep. Now I'm headed to work being screwed out of sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚠️ Winter Storm Warning for the D.C. metro area for late tonight through tomorrow evening. Snow (4-6”), then ice, t… https://t.co/Qo7FIKLiuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Valentine’s Day with this beautiful lady and we’re spending it 663 miles apart, but I couldn’t ask for a bett… https://t.co/KgkvFbaMTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @kingcountybar Young Lawyers Division is a great opportunity for service and networking.  I served as YLD Chair… https://t.co/DNoMpNz9b3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XabiAlxnso Dortmund throttled them 4-0 at home 🤷🏻‍♂️ im more confident than I probably should be against them lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a clever, entertaining way for @melindagates and @BillGates to introduce the annual @gatesfoundation impact re… https://t.co/917wB55J8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speakers will include @searchforbreezy @msmithadc  @ls_cc_askme will be joining, me @freedomforce990 Today's Media… https://t.co/S1QR0xODNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KNayyeh @DustinGiebel Had an account since 2012 but has no tweets. When will his vow of silence end?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait what?? It’s not the bench press? Or even better...225 rep test?? Or even better @jonhersel “dips and curls”...… https://t.co/LSgoInHbXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThreeOranges It’s one of the dumb reasons why I didn’t like Farrell for a while...then I saw in Bruges]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angieee64 @fireball_jordan Haha yes we can. I’m literally friends with hundred of seafood lovers. And there’s alwa… https://t.co/LvKhLebjzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s jordyn?? I wanna know what y’all yappin about I’m not about this life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @RichBTIG have you checked the price of $snap lately... only up about 100% in 2 mos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codybtapp @SpruceGoose_ He takes Bubba 100/100 times.  And we forever get to play the what if game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC long time viewer, first time Tweeter... I’d consider changing ‘This Is Who We Are.’ to ‘Is This At All Legal… https://t.co/HhH8kNMmCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamCoachBuzz Great Win!  Proud of Win - most of all a class program that reflects VT's values!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont deal with sell outs that lose there Word to white people all that leave Sanaa alone shit aint what to look at @FloydMayweather]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RoseCross (c also #RoseCroix and #RosyCross) is an #Icon associated with the semi-mythical Christian Rosenkreuz (R… https://t.co/UuSaoZgRyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jack It's amazing what a little dose of optimism can do for ones way of approaching issues and challenges. For me… https://t.co/LIYdvCSilA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner Congrats Andy, such an inspiration. You are a very brave man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattandkim what are y’all doing tonight after the show at the ga theatre?? any chance we can meet you? so excited for the show!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haram_Stan @SenWarren How about driving and/or job performance while under the influence? It doesn’t seem to be a… https://t.co/Kj7LvmRM3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NativexTruth When you’re attacking a general type of person who ENJOYS tomatoes, no, you can’t!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very interesting shit that’s going on right now https://t.co/YekuD2odyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avery Joe's Pilsner cans now available. https://t.co/vL4ofFxDBr @AveryBrewingCo #BeerMenus]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re making a movie 2/26 come be in it ——- @RayValdezPhoto 🎥 in 4K  @exoticshay_ on the 📸  —— Come check… https://t.co/DGfv0PtGA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllDukeGang Yeah long time commitment but coaches were not contacting him as much. More like a mutual parting lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇦🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss Renae! @renaeayris The White RACE Australian BLONDES👑Women Are The MOST B… https://t.co/Eq9bWchvOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danbroski @JLPtalk We all love America Jesse! The first generation of Black Americans born out of wedlock had whit… https://t.co/5bspRXBfqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hilarious portrait idea from photographer Jason's Lee. #comedy #laugh #smirk #comic https://t.co/sQ4vV3bgRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliviajesko Life goes on even when shit goes down🤩🤩🤩 https://t.co/Y1ywXF07lL]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had our first @ChicagoStMed (University of Chicago) run last night! What a great experience for these socially-m… https://t.co/qtBSUbl9EO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent so many nights as a family watching Jeopardy and Alex Trebek. Devastating news. He is great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealWolkie @TheAAF @aafAPOLLOS @aafhotshots @aafstallions @AAFFleet @aafiron @aafcommanders @aafexpress… https://t.co/kT2pIA42BP]]></document></documents></author>