<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Telling jokes again tomorrow at @dromedarybar in Bushwick at 8:30pm. It’ll be fun, you should come @ Brooklyn, New… https://t.co/0udtkn0BYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhirlpoolCorp when are you going to fix the remote start feature for your smart ovens?  I'm frustrated I just boug… https://t.co/LBVC1fk38n]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is amazing. Great meeting Alison and hearing about the work she’s doing as a journalist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love sitting all alone during breaks at work. It gives me time to plan and live out my fantasy life in my head for a little bit..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phunky_Brewster Here was the test for me: cover up the right side of the screen. Still impressive? Absolutely not...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@its_Fallsy @zacshipley In some cases, it sounds like it. In others, they just thought he'd fire them if they didn'… https://t.co/uFw92FQRkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commit your way to the Lord ; trust in him and he will do this: Psalm 37:5 NIV https://t.co/vZ0y25SHHF https://t.co/a5g8aSK7G5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sleep, so when Dad gets home I can play. #YankeeBrady https://t.co/QFKYqlEUpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve from @nynjpaweather and @wxconcierge has today’s weather video discussion with three live cams from… https://t.co/CphAFIbCdg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen ppl of status and power preach the importance of insurgent practice, of punching up and challenging the s… https://t.co/2STiAMuMWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cawayee You’re sooooo good enough and worth it!! You’re amazing. Hugs ❤️ I know we can get hurt sometimes by the p… https://t.co/K9YjjznoJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight we’re gonna do something different 😌 Tonight were gonna touch  a little different 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_becks22 @NYIslesNation @Barzal_97 Occam’s razor: the solution w the least assumptions is almost always the right… https://t.co/9HhC78gWy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn @KatrinaPierson knowing your history makes a difference when you're trying to make a point.… https://t.co/wjTmo6qMSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy hell. My 11 yr old almost peeing her pants Dad, Dad there’s @_IvyConrado and JLo. I’m not sure what will happe… https://t.co/2BTJ3tLnCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Prospects_Watch It's a New England town where hockey should have flourished instead they let the team move to Nort… https://t.co/093qr6iU2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei I had not known nor had I seen this picture until now. That is so gross that the elected officials wou… https://t.co/JI3QJcMQeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell yeah. Adam S. - Drinking a Mexican Brunch by @kanebrewing @ Cooper Beer Cellars  — https://t.co/SNjjBtAfwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the dilly: You play MJ on the shuttle bus and I’m moonwalking. Here’s a dollar, driver]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been stuck on this ship for a week I want my own bed so badly :( and cuddles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElizabethCano23 Defense attorneys always describe it as “what the gubment needs to take your kids!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at PITT (Parque de Innovación y Transferencia de Tecnología) in Chihuahua, Chih https://t.co/dpVyktQe19]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂 Muy cierto. A VER, le entendieron? @RafaeIRamosV @LeoPoeta_ESPN @RazaESPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FinnWrites Take control of that car and kick them out! https://t.co/jXDao6IQpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sketches @ Breakfast  #art #sketchbook #mechanicalpencil #superman https://t.co/MCOLhcRtnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BRussellSoFla @freddymo2 @BetAmerica @ChurchillDowns Freddy is a personal friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doh_MTL @guycrete @Jpbeauch @Franlaga @Val_Plante Pis ils parlent français]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whiney farmboy misses a BBQ and then leaves home with a crazy old man, two robots, a criminal and his giant dog. He… https://t.co/6NH8805vqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeLawrenceNJ USA Hockey is looking at it. No idea if it will pass or even be considered for a vote in June.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collin got his drivers license todayyyy so we went to Bob Evans duh👏🚗🍳❤️ love you brother!!! https://t.co/segvdUuCzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[DREAM HEAVER I believe you can get me through the niiiiiight.... 💫 @ Sullivans Island https://t.co/hLLjddyHuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished day 60 of my Bible Reading for this year. 2 Corinthians 12,13; Numbers 1; Psalms 51. We should real… https://t.co/DUoGyQSFjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoIthaca @THETHOUGHTJUNGL @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump No, I was making the same point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdoubikin42 @FlatgroundApp @TriCBaseball Ask the big guy behind you. He’s a HOF and 🐐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricHolder This is your legal opinion, until the right call is made by the US Supreme Court. Even the DoJ - you on… https://t.co/oi1H45Kze1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amtrak hey! Thanks for not letting WV have heir excursion train. That only provided a small town with a huge influ… https://t.co/rbQ5rq1eN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[“@MayorMikeDuggan pulls off with great regularity making chicken pie out of chicken feathers” - @CountyExecEvans]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never claim to be the fastest runner. Consistency is how I roll 🤣 This running journey is about growth and a… https://t.co/4vwwsKeqWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC The question is answered.  "Because they are slime!"  Anyone that believes what they say is ignorant.  #WalkAway]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite things to see at state basketball is Bud Legg hanging out courtside.  One of the legends of Iowa high school athletics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fimschweiler @BHGolfEquipment I'm in Atlanta. I don't have a set home course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nikosvazelas @SimonTSN690 We never get the right one at the right time though :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Money Room Attendant - Coors Field O/H" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about t… https://t.co/0ECcYXEg7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamie2181 @dinok1975 Everyone has preferences, because you prefer certain physical characteristics doesn't make yo… https://t.co/DNa1tB9KBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume Hopefully you’ll find a modicum of the courage she’s shown, Brit, but I highly doubt it. You’re too busy… https://t.co/ZZIL8p9XPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#foxandfriends  Goodmorning @JaniceDean.....  How can we tell DC is 'closed down' due to weather as opposed to ever… https://t.co/PeT6zSulDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JniorGaldino7 @hotmenBR @GarotoGay5 @BOYSHOTX @hot_connection @mundogaybr Nice tatoooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spencer_josh @PackMensBball Excellent memory. He outscored them 30-29 in the second half in Reynolds. But not the… https://t.co/SA6R4hvrBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I have new neighbors next door and I didn’t realize they had a little kid until I hear creepy crying through my wall at 2am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizlaineuk The Joint Chiefs of Staff declared Climate Change a national security threat years ago. U may find this… https://t.co/memVKMZr5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Feisty_FL Plenty of trees and they grow bigger each year. They are planted as are crops.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is really interesting, considering how much Vox Media has put into their creative studios]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judicial Council Ruling on Traditional Plan.  90032 - Constitutional 33 - Unconstitutional 34 - Uncon 35 - Uncon 36… https://t.co/syrZyJvFF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Oilers are going to waste Connor McDavids career. It’s a shame. #NHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyjayphil I literally can’t watch him play bro. Dude travels multiple times a game and doesn’t play defense...yet… https://t.co/p9bvuGwmec]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @AdamSchiff and the Democrat House pursue #RussiaGate investigations which 70% of voters say they DO NOT want, t… https://t.co/CYkaG8KFcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think about you day and night, it's only right To think about the girl you love and hold her tight So happy toget… https://t.co/M3fgesAX0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop by and see Hectic Wear today at Durham Art Market today. . . . #durham #duke #durhamnc #bullcity #huntstmarket… https://t.co/QCIhM1oKPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turns out the local paper in my hometown of North Andover, Massachusetts is bankrolled by [checks notes] Alabama’s… https://t.co/igyVEOCB3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well looks like @jlj17 @Shane_McLovin @CavanaughPet will be stranded on I-70 for 5 to 6 hours!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you put in the time?   Have you outworked your opponents?   Have you improved?    Your true competition is in… https://t.co/JS9tX1QqDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vschaumann1 @ohneh2o @RyanAFournier Sorry but he's morally bankrupt. This is not decent behavior. My parents had a… https://t.co/RR8k1zb7ro]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are committed to seeing you have an incredible experience here at L.E.A.N.!  Come try us for free for the next t… https://t.co/KBxmc2HTPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The school you grew up loving and that you attended for several semesters before you chose the service industry lif… https://t.co/RtdGYobdH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You trying to be discreet but the ones that know you personally can’t be out here calling you by your real name you… https://t.co/a8webFq6He]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi Why are we rewarding a country that has failed to be honest with us? We need to block to get answers… https://t.co/5q9PBjz6bw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I'm ready for the 2nd half, but I'm also ready for this pizza delivery guy to show up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyDiComo This is nonsense, does the organization understand how much money he brings in just in jersey sales… https://t.co/Dike39U8vQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @ArethaFranklin account just tweeted for the first time in 4 years (since she was alive). This is a problem bec… https://t.co/KFEFkf8bZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DolamiteD @WhiteKeithSweat @KSfireslayer @SM0KEDAWG_ @lv_teacher We’ve grown out our feral guinea pig business and… https://t.co/AGzWJ5IOY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolcarl Sorry for the late submission Carl but this is definitely worst way to get your beef. https://t.co/cgruwxXDi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time celebrating my @annam0403 bday with great friends. The Lemon Mascarpone cake was delicious… https://t.co/yYXQZGqwZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @AOC Thought you were going. Don't let the door hit you on the ass on your way out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adrianwalden47 @MKdonsladiesfc @FAWNL Minor Finals Day is Sunday 14 April. #FAWNLfamily #WeAreNational]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Baby it’s cold outside but we love our new favorite camper!” - Jeffrey and Karen #GANDERRV #Bullet #keystoneRV… https://t.co/wKWaWBsK0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krz_luksza @RuchNarodowy O nienawisc i brak akceptacji dla mafii, sluzb i loz oskarza YT Grzegorza Brauna i blokuj… https://t.co/LPMLsq8T7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmLowkeyLoki @BrattyCupcakes @YouNow Yassssss @BrattyCupcakes I can’t wait!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si deseas Donar tu aporte va hacer importante sea la cantidad que sea esta es la manera de hacerlo 👉🏽👉🏽👉🏽  por y pa… https://t.co/TB6ymmjRoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddishott I guess she didnt sleep as sound,  finding little pee spots all over]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oscars So if Rami (good performance, big fan) lip synced to an Oscar then how big of an award awaits Taron Edgerton??? #Rocketman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scotyvonnendave @CardConnector U block my with a knief should I be scared lol. Enjoy brother]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the topic of esports viewership, specifically the Overwatch League, it’s especially difficult to track viewershi… https://t.co/sEeHRGP2oS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NVBats Thank you. This was the last piece. I'm running this story tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteTailTakes Same. I always do, but i advise others dont to save them from heart break lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving thru a crazy hailstorm while along I-680 around Fremont, CA!  I don’t think I’ve ever seen such a downpour… https://t.co/RMBKuwGnOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MajinMG @DaBuggg5 @JCrossover @mg @M2Nation I’m on team J Cross! He’s gonna be snatching ankles when he’s 50]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ @mattgaetz Witness testing? Is this an alternate fact? Just another Republican lie Matty.  Go have a drink.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends It’s not fair for Americans to pay legal fees to fight these frivolous lawsuits! It’s time to make them pay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jay_kec @UmbrellaAcad @RobMSheehan Is he not the greatest character ever!?!? That series was great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no link between autism and measles, mumps and rubella vaccine, new study finds. #VaccinesWork… https://t.co/BKULOtAQxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouCanPlayTeam @DallasStars @NHL @NHLPA And, unlike #Preds, was there a Chici-Fil-A tie in as well?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Norzagaray @CPJannyBarrera @SantiagoLunaG @PROFEPA_Mx @AlfonsoDurazo @lopezobrador_ @LillyTellez @Elcesarfraijo… https://t.co/KJVGOh7kzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[this will make you tee-hee. #hilarity #snicker #smirk #funny https://t.co/es7PZpoe9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CallMeDrRage Hi hello how are you have you heard this? https://t.co/oNSVf3sMcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told you the United Conservative Party was an oxymoron. https://t.co/EJZuYgukLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saben algo,eso de que las personas eviten hacer cosas por alguien, solo por el hecho de no recibir lo mismo a cambi… https://t.co/ES9BwZvsxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another round of rain today in Mississippi….75 degrees in February is crazy enough, but now we have hail and wind warnings……]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quinn has pieces on Iggy and Cassius that went up this week that are both tremendous. If you haven’t read them yet,… https://t.co/eqFi5flP59]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DavidsonMBB picks up a solid win on the road at URI, 75-66. @Jaxelinn provides the headline by registering the fi… https://t.co/458gQU3Ipb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @saberbelt and @Herofied for making my #PinGame stronger! Their first pins are killer! #SandsofTime… https://t.co/2Y0DHCnKQ2]]></document></documents></author>