<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@withconfidence_ @joshwithcon @jaydenwithcon seeing y’all was cool and stuff! Love you guys! 💕 Stay warm as you hea… https://t.co/HUb9qq2KJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys my skin cleared up so nicely and shiny ~ my lil pimple is so HD now... ;_;]]></document><document><![CDATA[💫✨🎉 | tinky winkyyyy , hai lil girl ! I love your energy , lil happy ass 😂 . You are funny asl , and you don’t even… https://t.co/Fse9eOkVJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pontifex Amen and hopefully the talks included the horrific abortion crisis that has been plaguing us for decades! 🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seabreeezyy Honestly idk which is worse. One is disgusting and the other is infuriating]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized I want to watch my boyfriend put string cheese on pizza for the rest of my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the underrated aspects of Urusei Yatsura is how Ataru is so hated by all of the locals because he ends up at… https://t.co/nKuG4PvUfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tracy143DC @nbcdays Do you really think so little of Jack that you think that he would purposely put his son in da… https://t.co/zCBjbjZ58g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t realize I was about to start my period until I saw a picture of ice cream and started crying]]></document><document><![CDATA[People need to stop comparing After to 50 Shades, it’s a totally different concept. Sure Anna maybe drew some inspi… https://t.co/Q06Is5GXoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando tus pensamientos van de acuerdo a lo que deseas que suceda. Encontrarás la forma de que suceda. Piensa en ha… https://t.co/Wa4TJbPUWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Advocacy works. From @statesman - “I didn’t know that,” Nelson said of the teaching requirement. “They are teachers… https://t.co/xBUoU8GC5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I put up a wall in every relationship I’ve ever been in. Trust me, walls work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Choose The Best Pair of Leggings For Any Workout https://t.co/RGvRli3hkN #WholesaleLeggings #USA #Suppliers… https://t.co/l5VWTFcXz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad news from the #FashionWorld #KarlLagerfeld, one of the most prolific fashion figures of the modern age, has die… https://t.co/zjc7nE2Wmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me opening skyward all pumped to see how well I did on my psych test to find I got a 73% https://t.co/FtPuOK0ZT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[They cut the claws of a lioness to play with tourists, rescue her! https://t.co/sYdQplrso2 via @sosvox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuggalosAntiDV Absolutely Right.  Women that have been partners of abusers are NEVER SAFE!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAvaArmstrong Not a fan of him, singer, has sexual abuse charges and doesn't pay child support.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kitch3400 @marchmadness @NBA @NHL @TheAAF @NCAACWS @MLB @PGATOUR Well- bits of. I had the tv on while cleaning all day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the first time in my 5.5 years of being a mom, I am keeping both of my kids (5 and 2) home with me. I’ve always… https://t.co/9uiFfnHI5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to “This Is America” by Childish Gambino https://t.co/ahLePOQxAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/uh6ON2zodq            Find out which celtics player your most alike I’m most Like @gordonhayward which… https://t.co/QotmACygWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don't need the diva's who panicked. They aren't worthy to be on my team. Thank you to My 🏈 guys who stay are Tru… https://t.co/qhBwqJ0eQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Set It Off Midnight Tour 2019 • • • • • #torontophotography #torontophotographer #musicphotography… https://t.co/PrMS9DaLs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abadesi featured on @pocintech today!!! Woot. So proud of this amazing woman. https://t.co/08TFPb1MAF #pocit #WomeninTech #Leaders]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS. Be still my heart! The dreamer in me says imagine one in all @HenricoSchools ! @hcpslib #phaseIIBookNooks… https://t.co/zq0V3PnW6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CheesedChallenge #cheesed  Cheesing the pets is even better tho! https://t.co/DrB41ZGkz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: hi I’d like to go things my way :) Life: no Me: but please..? Life: well since you asked nicely, no!  Me: (: Life: (:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets see how many times we replay Zion’s knee injury... sorry Duke, shouldn’t put all your stock in winning on ONE… https://t.co/DESyoJmqUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lexa_Merica @RLTW797 @DavidNPhillips2 @MAGA4Life6 @samennen8 @mom2x @Alpyka62 @farmerd19 @timmeb454 @fixer_54… https://t.co/JP35SbGp1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mizbambixo @EllaDesmondxo @BrookeTyers @KDavisGayFriend @pink_crayola @ajaqueen @TheBiancaDelRio @nottodaysay10 Si… https://t.co/WXrCOAluiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful for @steve_garlick1 and @mgoblue52 for all the laughs and smiles every morning at drop off....If your S… https://t.co/1q9MJ7yHrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anthonyd_209 You’re not happy with your life and yard he’s not happy with her life because you guys are evil you g… https://t.co/zBzQ9lDHxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The GOP had 8 years to fix the problems of Obamacare. Insurance had an opportunity to help fix the system. Instead… https://t.co/L8k9YG6ncS]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏👏👏👏 @MDominguez_DSS very well deserved because you're simply amazing. #thethreemusketeers]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t get enough of @Pro_Duecer reading the comments in his “seductive” voice. Pure gold! @DrewMikePodcast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for giving her one more reason to be proud of me. Country Aircheck/CRS #1 Large Market On-Air Personality… https://t.co/vFAWeeIhl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I AM IN NEW FOUND GLORY’S HOMETOWN RIGHT NOW AND IVE BEEN LISTENING TO THEM FOR THE PAST 2 HOURS]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s got enough money that it will be gone tomorrow. Take a gd seat and let me girl live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what is happening on our college campuses. Parents make sure u know the philosophy’s where your children r… https://t.co/cAz3dJ3FhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Ronda can dish the jokes at others expense but can’t take it. And then acts out like a baby in response. Typical. https://t.co/anbbljr3YD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peachesnana @donnalihalfpint @dontgoawaymad2 @ZellnerLaw @TManitowoc @Rookie1082 @Lilmisty84 😂The struggle is real! 😅🤦🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Covington student sues @washingtonpost https://t.co/A1H28Z3eJn via @timbpearce @DailySignal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, I went outside today! Greetings from Downtown Brooklyn! @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/AHJFzYcD6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aramburo_isabel @beto_moraf @AlfredoJalifeR_ @JohnMAckerman @fernandeznorona @CarlosLoret Y admirado ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could not pay me to look at these ugly mugs or listen to their rot. Seeing them on twitter makes me nauseous. J… https://t.co/FXsEGxbm9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I somehow managed to break my phone, miss my flight, and have my luggage flown across the country... so all in all… https://t.co/AQKjT6wZOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat fights me to the death when it’s time to have his nails cut like dammnnnn 😂 why can’t he be like my other cat and be good]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fuck him with my red flag on and  when I cum, I say gang, on the gang]]></document><document><![CDATA[visitsuzhou talked about their beautiful area in China at @gbk_productions Oscar gift lounge   #travelwriter… https://t.co/R5vPhzfvFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay but i seriously cannot wait to meet my @thejmblya family! they are absolutely the best people EVER! may 3rd couldn’t come any faster!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@declanvarley Whoever they are I hope the stay anonymous...and enjoy there winnings.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to ALL the women in #CdnAg  Every. Single. One. #youmakeitwork #IWD2019 #iseeyou]]></document><document><![CDATA[It might've been a creative way to crack this Doctor's façade, since like most of them she tends to mask what she's… https://t.co/gXvkC1iUxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTVToronto Autism Protest against the changes made to the Ontario Autism Program  -Tuesday February 19th 9:30am at… https://t.co/UzfUQmCrPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASimmons32 @tristenmadison @BreeBoruff64  Good Luck in ft Collins  this W/E Thu vs @IdahoStateSB  Fri vs… https://t.co/1Un5QqeOrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE SWIRLING COLORS NEWSLETTER: March 2019 https://t.co/E7ONPEf1Zh https://t.co/nSnuaydzr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AristeguiOnline @lopezobrador_ Ya basta de simulacros, esas “encuestas” nos cuestan a los que pagamos impuestos, s… https://t.co/lhKWxMtwTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe this and always try to be that teacher whisperer of talent and worth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Lighthouse Baptist Church https://t.co/jbFGGfJWOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[On air until 9am to raise money for @WUWMradio. 414.227.3210, https://t.co/JuaPuCmjNF, or use the WUWM app. We have… https://t.co/B6NqTAMKQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[El Salvador!!! 🇸🇻 Pero que bonitooooo y que ganas de haber podido ir 😥😥😥😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[if the jonas brothers tour again i need some camp rock songs on that set list]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got to chat with our friend, Carli McFarland,  who celebrated her 11th birthday yesterday! Carli suffers from ce… https://t.co/sZzKn15uFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning🌅 Tap and share❤  #grateful #blessed #prosperous #abundant #growth @ Richmond, Virginia https://t.co/qyBfPViyIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nailed it! Women’s History Month is in full effect 🚺💅🏾 @dericacolewash | #nailinspo #manimonday https://t.co/j3NAUV6JUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thing they weren’t transporting oil. Could have been a disaster. #buildpipelines]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursdays 8am-1pm #fortmyersbeach #fmb #fortmyersbeachthingstodo #swflartsandcrafts #shoplocal #supportthearts… https://t.co/oFr49XZCnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found a second bird feeder in the garage. Just needs a little cleaning up, then it's good to go. #MondayMotivation #Garden]]></document><document><![CDATA[America put a man in the moon, but there’s an unending wave of people who keep saying we can’t accomplish anything… https://t.co/JRpr7WgFiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoLimit_TC I’m a Taurus but i don’t think i ever encountered a male Taurus, crazy. My top two are easily Leo &amp; libra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GSophia62 @Bravewriting @kater8868 Fucking magical?? What is it about white candidates that attracts cultists and worshippers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don’t know what a cult is, but I know I don’t have one” - R Kelly 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Qweeniey Disney and a lot other things have warped our view of what love is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When girls try to get their hair like mine ... oh no honey what is you doing ? 😂🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Gaithersburg, Md it's coming down fast and heavy now. Looks like it's going to be a white out here. #Fox5Snowday… https://t.co/3HUhyKee1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yasssssss!!! New client photo shoot on a cold Friday morning in #dallas. Thank goodness for #coffee #myotherlove… https://t.co/kSGqttZ5lC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Publia1920 @wvjoe911 As a former member of the LDS church, I sadly agree.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blahoaf I turn 25 this year and I already foresee my quarter life crisis lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[[redacted ex-client] had a youtube video embedded in their flyout menu i swear to god. #aeasea #aeasea2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @WhiteHouse @mickbk What? @WhiteHouse is promoting this travesty? You’re not supposed grope the flag… https://t.co/FimBThg657]]></document><document><![CDATA[If You Cheating And Your Girl Ain’t Catch You Yet It’s Cuz She Cheating Too😴❗️❗️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdfmc500 So exciting. I have some friends there. Have a great time!!#GoStros]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We’re doing amazing in Connecticut, thanks to our incredibly LOVED elected officials… https://t.co/hutWH8yEUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[i took a poster from the venue tonight for the state champs show only bc i thought it had grayscale on it and i jus… https://t.co/cxgcQATkpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please consider supporting SUA Athletics Track &amp; Field💙💛  Purchase your tickets here: https://t.co/fstOBD6Kbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worked on invites for 5 hours total... and we arent even done 😩😩 Carlos didnt think it was so much work!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg speak of the devil, pbs just ran this story we are on the same wavelength (gives uptick in donations of select… https://t.co/f6g4zCjsMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a beautiful mess. #tamales #bff #bloomington #mexicanfood #nevereatingagain @ Casa Brava https://t.co/JE8SxU8Sn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silky smooth hair has never been easier than with the Kerasilk Style range. Effortlessly achieve either straight, s… https://t.co/kupZs6HnZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mind is so weird.  I keep thinking of things to do since I’m stuck inside all day...one idea is clean, another i… https://t.co/vdpbBBAhct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump calls for Rep. Ilhan Omar’s resignation after anti-Semitic tweets https://t.co/TfaTCdYQ0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[She seemed OK and probably only had scratches and bruises but she got SUPER lucky because she was very close to hit… https://t.co/uzmGq1wyen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drvox “Just 13% of respondents said they approved of the federal government directly investing and maintaining own… https://t.co/KAG1OowQGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShimonPro @NatashaBertrand I'm waiting for a really smart person to interpret everything in this report for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ampincivero Ugh. I guess we do have to f***ing wait. God d*** it. @BachelorABC why do you do this to us?!?  Why do… https://t.co/f0ljyD7SKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big game day!  So proud of ALL these coaches and athletes.....do everything for the glory of the Lord… https://t.co/KMasx0cdKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4: Be on the lookout for those who go need hope givers. Sometimes those people aren’t in our everyday path.… https://t.co/FxTXVCpPS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ambrown @busproject I’m open to being convinced otherwise but what’s the actual barrier here? Voting requires some… https://t.co/1zS8Swh6fL]]></document></documents></author>