<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Was there ever a doubt? 5 fight deal - funds to be deposited as follows 46m after Canelo fight and 1m after 4 other… https://t.co/H56gHpqArN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elon Musk should be held in contempt for inaccurate tweet about Tesla, SEC says: Tesla Inc. Chief Executive Elon Mu… https://t.co/PCXc7E0HJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottforFlorida @blanken01 @BernieSanders We have an uneducated bunch of indoctrinated young people whose civics a… https://t.co/9n2W2DhvY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakersReporter @LWOSLALakers I Hate To Do it, But I think it's time #LakeShow 🎣 https://t.co/8eiTzv6PyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:08 2Q: @MentorAthletics 47 @ElyriaAthletics 18. Six players have hit 3s for Mentor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Along those lines, shout out to the kick-ass women I get to work with &amp; call friends with on a regular basis:… https://t.co/In38yvsNhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh buddy, this gem found by misssilvz the good ol days #carlsbad at the lew3rdp pad. Love these kids ✌️💲💲💲 @ Carlsb… https://t.co/YwT9Yxt7nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Concourse B - @atlanta_airport in Atlanta, GA https://t.co/EOf12hUL23]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sunsets are getting later and later, and it’s starting to freak me out. @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/e4BrhXiAnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristaBowman12 @Jim_Jordan It was Trump's own.mouth that said Ted Cruz's dad killed JFK. Info wars pushed pizza g… https://t.co/tSo41SF91o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrayThread @BekaCK @paulsperry_ @DonaldJTrumpJr Cops are not gullible. We've heard it all. We know a scammer when… https://t.co/PYBjoM64VP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrVChimhutu @LynNemudonhi @NzouJnr @D_Nyambiya @PacheduZW @mtakagogoe @nickmangwana @BitiTendai @revesaymutede… https://t.co/i3erGYwRk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[A cook asking to borrow my knives is like a dj asking to borrow my headphones.   Cálmate cabron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Harwood Myth by @urbanchestnut @ Paint Nite — https://t.co/6o2YZ1hxNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul  Please support President Trump on the emergency border issue.  He needs the support of all good Republic… https://t.co/HyuxR0md10]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke Ayling somehow conceded a penalty as the attacker is WALKING with the ball away from goal.... 🤷🏼‍♀️🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fredontwittur @RantyAmyCurtis I see no reason the senate shouldn’t be apportioned in similar fashion. Vastly diffe… https://t.co/WcEVyLEqrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though Rousey VS Lynch VS Flair is of extraordinary talent and high performers and just going to be amazing it… https://t.co/KwZ2AJAVss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cofrederic13 You learned well Luke Skywalker.  The Force is strong in you!  Field looks great!!!  I know there's n… https://t.co/qyafUWy6V2]]></document><document><![CDATA[D’Angelo Russell went from “yea but he doesn’t get to the line maybe they should trade him if they can get any valu… https://t.co/LkSMPBhRGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedoubleshot Congratulations Brian! Looking forward to seeing the new spot today. 🙌💪👊👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intro to AI Product Management   Online Twitter Class Reading #1 - prep for class   The jcurve #jCurve  Cc… https://t.co/NkgtbAsrns]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite opponents and favorite people to be around in and out of wrestling congratulations… https://t.co/CcwZYNeGiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenMab87 @thatpeterfox @MeghanMcCain So... That you "feel" this way makes tolerance and/or denialism of left-win… https://t.co/0fVNHTdMqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed west for a 2 day @TheAdaptiveFTO in-service for the Ogden (UT) PD @TheVirtusGroup (@ American Airlines in Ch… https://t.co/UHAOj8EvTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @myvoicevibes with get_repost ・・・ Which one is you? 😂 • • Like - Comment - Share ••• Follow @myvoicevibes •… https://t.co/yWtef4o3Bv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldeeenS0UL All the Cute Pictures of Pits &lt;This Video  #SorryNotSorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smell the dark chocolate goodness of Pale Chocolate malt, 2 Row, Munich light, Munich dark, Crystal, and Carafa III… https://t.co/gOb7Nv6pqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE PERFECT FAMILY HOME...GET READY COMING SOON! Parker Real Estate Residential presents....2307 LOCKERBY DRIVE - D… https://t.co/Lvns0AD0Ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@BryanM_KVUE will know exactly why I thought of @YvonneN_KVUE when I saw this on Facebook tonight.… https://t.co/9dJ9GldSzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayemesssam I don’t recognize that saddle cloth says something like Vanilla on it or something ?😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I was going to broadcast a first look at the new Dirt Rally 2 game today but 1st to my great surprise I’ll be… https://t.co/wttR3B9khJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigSJ I told a friend that this “the middle” song was the new September for white people. Now look where we are]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jali_Cat @ColoradoGirl2A @IlhanMN @Ilhan @SpeakerPelosi @DNC @HouseDemocrats She's from a very liberal district li… https://t.co/BUplr9AvFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorKeating @OpTic_Scumper I went 0-5 with highest kills each time. Does that mean anything ? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Grandchamps Kitchen &amp; Market in Brooklyn, NY https://t.co/yzYz6NrCX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@jgiannopoulou and Dean Vásquez-Poritz make opening remarks and kick off the 1st Biomedical #BigData symposium at… https://t.co/5JAja0nzua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedavidcrosby IMHO no matter who each of you bring in to sing with there really is no substitute for the harmonie… https://t.co/D2jHwVqK0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[The GOP Keeps Changing The Rules After It Loses Elections https://t.co/S24Bkvnb87]]></document><document><![CDATA[My basketball season isn't over just yet. Permian pulls out a thriller against Arlington Martin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxWeltman27 @JakeKrak Kobe has 2/5 Finals MVPs so idk what you’re argument would even be lmao Kobe wasn’t even th… https://t.co/lMjyf7ir6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah Valentine’s Day whatever but did you know the worlds first electronic computer was also born on 2/14?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latest #drawing. Amplifier-Bot! What's in the box? I think it's a kitten. ❤️ #dailydrawing #art #robot #robots… https://t.co/aF4ova9QiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are we not talking about uniting Spaceship Earth? What's more important? #DrBronners #magicsoap https://t.co/yZ0rIY4HEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EJXD2 @winx_horse Does the guy who beats Winx become the Steve Bartman of Ozzie history? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flying to @ORNL to attend @InnovCrossroads Cohort 3 Finals event today and tomorrow! @CRIstartup @energyEERE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Bibibop Asian Grill - @bibibopgrill in Columbus, OH https://t.co/NhdVoaM3vm]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the morning, sunshine and 12” of new snow! #morninglight #winter @ West Silent Lake https://t.co/VXDNWeK6f3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachkulprit @IolaFirebirds Cool, sounds like a game that we’ll see used more and more at the younger ages.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some ideas where to buy my baby earrings? (She likes rose gold) https://t.co/YFKuyOccO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies in my timeline; any who haven’t muted me by now. What do you think about this guy’s statement? https://t.co/N5sqTqDo38]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time at today’s @INBlackExpoInc Chapter Leadership Training. The Indy chapter are looking forward leading the… https://t.co/b91kWDFnxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@americansoulbet soul train was a huge part of my life growing up you felt prideful of black people showssing amazi… https://t.co/t6bhUfNCVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great team! Our @davidwcoulter is again joining this group. @CHMFoundation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeeperofthePop @DisLikedObject @FB_FilmAnalysis I think Knapp schematically was the right coach for him. But they… https://t.co/xyzr2Vzve9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraceBarnhouse @vocalpercman @IAmUltimatePred @justinbbradford https://t.co/S8seeho0u1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am glad someone on my feed retweeted Joel Osteen, gave me a chance to block his account from showing up again. #fraud #ScamArtist]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Boston like #NYC has major mobility challenges. Our commuting and trip demand patterns are 21st century. Our… https://t.co/21wA0bCSRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Done with work for s few days ny and  Coworker you so much fun she's a goofmd actor https://t.co/tDT6fOMghz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gutfeld's slide into insufferability the last few years is such a sad thing to watch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why so much need in a land of plenty? Your generosity skills are quite dumpy. But will you fall like an egg on a wa… https://t.co/pBskda1F7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch said ALL I asked for was a Pandora chain, earrings, and ring. I fucking cry when I just get flowers shit so u… https://t.co/9YXOvnIHhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super Snow Moon tonight taken with a 500mm with a 2x teleconverter. #SuperSnowMoon #supermoon https://t.co/fh3zGCchEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yungpresident_ Aw hell naw his ass gon be tired after the first quarter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joester91_ @BonjourFrankie @rooach @marcos_chi_ @fancypantsberni @Ruben_Ceniceros @23Erik_ @OscarAEJ @anava_416… https://t.co/2FdPcAOrFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't argue with this, nope not at all. 😁 @ Simi Valley, California https://t.co/0JhqGfFFtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @realDonaldTrump Pelosi wants illegals to vote. So what difference does it make what side of the Border th… https://t.co/9zQxnq52ax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samedi 23 février 2019 Vernissage à l'Atelier de l'Ile de Val-David.  Artiste Marie-Josée Lebel https://t.co/SL2125Ut6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm damned if I do and damned if I don't Holla fuck the world with my chest full of smoke I choke on my breakfast,… https://t.co/E4Nw0cb3Wq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although indirectly related to education, this is a powerful reminder of how dependent we have become... https://t.co/Ov0TZQrJv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard @NevadaJack2 Amazon needs to make a DEAL, get rid of Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez first.😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rehearsal   Again  - https://t.co/wERGFxbMgv of the @Rockies Ex 80126 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joesphVoid @NBCNews You're funny. Can I borrow some of that anger? I love you like broski.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmf1030 @jlong63 @CBiggerPic @KimStrassel @GOPLeader @RepAdamSchiff @DevinNunes What Bush tax cuts? The Democrats… https://t.co/5Occ4VGQko]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait till he sends out, “ I will be indicted by SDNYC tomorrow at 9:00am Enjoy” !!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @POTUS &lt;—- continues to prove himself to be in fit for President.  So very stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An honest question to ask yourself when you’re mad at someone or struggling with un-forgiveness. Do I wanna see tha… https://t.co/s5gmDzoLtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early (@ Toronto Pearson International Airport in Mississauga, ON) https://t.co/V23jAQbF3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liberals revere John McCain because he never really resisted liberals. Conservatives could never distinguish any di… https://t.co/I5mB59R4Xr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nofate1991 Oh gosh is it not good? I was looking forward to seeing it, even if just for the visuals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Community Walks Saturday morning And Sunday Morning... simple connection... https://t.co/obMGsCiLn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry, I told the tree to get  out of the picture, but she wouldn’t listen. #biltmore #biltmoreestate @ Biltmore Es… https://t.co/eSXo2m1nup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcNATSHACK 46?  I guess if it has a special meaning for you. It doesn't for me so that's why I would wait to see how he does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those paying attention: This powerful statement by @NIH made on Feb 28, the day @McLNeuro might loose her job f… https://t.co/bKormMSf2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArizonaRsol AZ can take a more considerable step by eliminating the annual driver license requirement for registered offenders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A mi no me gusta que me mantengan yo quiero trabajar yo y ganarme lo mío yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellr2010 Exactly Ron. Our judges must be set to a higher standard. Or impeached.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s very simple.  Debit - Credit (Long - Short) = cost.  Break even price = Strike Price + Cost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradleyMbastian @allthehoesjock Who the hell wants to play in shitcago]]></document><document><![CDATA[11 years old, playing TV themes on the piano, reading from the sheet music, including the M*A*S*H theme, Suicide is… https://t.co/iiNRAdQOd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArizonaCoyotes @Jake_Falk95 What a contrast between the Blues and the Leafs.... The Leafs may be even less comfort… https://t.co/15tPuxjXUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSUsuperfan5 @Hogtrough @W00PIGS000IE Look like homeboy got the raw end of the deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just did some reading &amp; I see that the wwe company reads the SuperStar's tweets that's why they never respond!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peteholmes @JuddApatow congrats and thanks for making @CrashingHBO  I will miss it greatly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I appreciate these thoughts from @RevOxley on #GC2019. I can't help noticing the parallels with the urban/rural div… https://t.co/Uu91xCwE7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MutchmorPS Mutchmor boys participating in the Junior Boys Region #3 Tripleball Tournament https://t.co/aST4PiW4uY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews But if she said anything about Native Americans, well then...never mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport - @atlairport in Atlanta, GA https://t.co/E3jJyMGkxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love to see the Eagles get Dexter Lawrence I’m the first round if he’s still there, if not try and get another DL.… https://t.co/A7e9Sl9iB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greetings from the Charlestown Five Cents Savings https://t.co/aaspM7uCbg]]></document></documents></author>