<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AlaraStarShine @DrPhil They’ll never recover from what that man did to them. Nor will his own parents. I didn’t kn… https://t.co/qdj8VngGk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dudamel não me desce pela güela, muito menos o El Sistema, mas é uma aparição com tanto significado que não tem com… https://t.co/vHL2sbW9Aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four trillion for free health care for all is okay, 5.7 billion for a wall to protect our country is too much, soun… https://t.co/MNdrIE5vUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWordOfErynn Poor pupper...Hope all goes well for you too, in my thoughts #pawprayers...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Athletics Alonzo Jones (2018, 25th round, Vanderbilt) https://t.co/vnXMUUrCNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessBravato Somebody jacked him up on adderal? Or what ever they do when you have lots of $💥 Trumpty shows the… https://t.co/NE6xRhGzXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindasmccartney Omg can’t wait to take u to Dennys to cure the impending frost bite ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beansieweensie @jacobinmag “Isn’t thaaaat nice?!” He should have said “Schuuuuultz?! Schuuuuultz?! Like Soulja! 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idgaf i haven’t stopped listening to Ariana’s whole entire album on repeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp. It finally happened. My @EpicGames account was hacked cuz I was a doofus and kept putting off enabling 2fa 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trust in the Lord with all your heart; do not depend on your own understanding. Seek His will in all you do... - Prov 3:5-6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of note, a check on Tug Hollywood shows a more recent ping at a speed of 7.5 kn continuing SW since GO Quest's olde… https://t.co/KlNCx9xi89]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning about Media Literacy and Fake News with Mary Robb of andoverps @primarysource @ Burlington High School (Ma… https://t.co/6qmPzKS32i]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a difference between sympathy and empathy, learn the difference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AddieMart2018 @OmarLopez0207 @LaJoyaISDEdTech @FelyTeachnology @CGarza0930 @mrstalktechie @SciTechieGuru ❤️🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelsearae813 Ugh yes. I’m definitely feeling the anger right now. Maybe I’ll want to try again eventually but right now is not that time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coolest hotel I’ve ever stayed at! ⁦@FoundRePhx⁩ https://t.co/tIFuJU1H7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BubbaJoeJimBob1 @StormyVNV @busbee_deborah @mvj737 @ChuckKeller14 @ashau68 @cspippin @Hell_HasCome @deepdvr1234… https://t.co/h6HqEPTbxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanhale115 it baffles me how people are so outraged about this tax but are still too lazy to buy reusable bags.… https://t.co/ITxN06noPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey peeps who use mascara and love to recycle and help wildlife, you can recycle the used wands!  Here's more info!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What #Saturdaymorning doesn’t start with #theboys singing @officialheart #CrazyonYou #mythemesong… https://t.co/x8IrvnPepZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am SO PUMPED to be performing with these hawt, empowering, kickass, hilarious women this Friday on the gay90s mai… https://t.co/M6tUykLyCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a dream @LukeBryanOnline was going to make a random appearance at my old highschool.. in the pool. And then I w… https://t.co/jzii9M19na]]></document><document><![CDATA[A benefit has been planned for the victims of a school van crash in Clearfield County Monday. https://t.co/TopRalzHp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[After three unsuccessful scans through my “Frequently Used” emojis page, I realized I couldn’t find the eye roll em… https://t.co/0UeUXfCOMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[For my birthday gift to myself, I bought a new nutrition/training  template (because fuck my previous attempts). An… https://t.co/vXqaQtd8bh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having hard battles? , so did David , here are some ways he got victory! https://t.co/5cnF6qXKV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[It annoys me when people ask me questions under a picture but don’t even bother to like it. Sooooo, I won’t bother to answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soft Bulk Microfiber Towels From Beach Towel Manufacturers in USA https://t.co/NERHhEVHmh #towelmanufacturers… https://t.co/9zFMbXMjEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 11th Anniversary ♥️🎉 to my wonderful husband who made this beautiful cappuccino ☕ for me this morning.  . .… https://t.co/tfBNWoFXbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will the American people realize the GOP is not your friend. They’re owned by insurance companies and big Phar… https://t.co/TQGn0RPRet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyNY4Ever @luluHru Congulations luluHru! On Reaching 85k!! Way To Go!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's the weekend! That means, staying in pajamas until I'm forced to leave the house and posting pics from the week… https://t.co/Yfnl6wMmaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAMALAMODE @weedlewobble Yeah, no one really knows. But W ignored the Al Quaeda intelligence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For some reason, I have never been able to dream about someone when I have a crush on them...this stinks when all I… https://t.co/HszezMnpZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhhMeee I feel you. As a Scorpio I think we just have lots of deep emotion but don’t want to admit it/express it i… https://t.co/rpv5nxMx1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a super hero because I am willing to (co)teach, model, coach, assist...whatever it takes to make a tech-infused… https://t.co/teTpHlQisG]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @realDonaldTrump supporters fall for the scam and report that the traitor has done everything he promised in his… https://t.co/M2rCwPsJY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work flow. (at @Walmart Supercenter in Ellicott City, MD) https://t.co/bKpQbHucd2 https://t.co/H9aNUkBNfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Autumn_Shafer @tonyhawk My youngest brother Josh Matthews. Two of his boards are the ones hanging in our office. https://t.co/tFtbNKCwN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate you white bitches who never move out of the fucking way, Jesus learn to be the tiniest bit considerate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein https://t.co/QtxbotmcEr of Billion dollar Condo. My Fear for you is so low.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seguimos tomando ordenes ! Feliz día de san Valentín ❤️🌹 @ Brenda’s Beauty Flowers https://t.co/C7bx8tz8IM]]></document><document><![CDATA[outstanding people have one thing in common: an absolute sense of mission]]></document><document><![CDATA[An angel SHE IS FREAKING ANGEL ON EARTH don’t @ me ✨✨✨ @taylorswift13 @taylornation13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff All locked up and in for the night in Saint Petersburg. #9PMRoutine]]></document><document><![CDATA[This looks hard right???!!!!   Actually, it gets easier as you do it. The imaginary hurdle was the hardest thing fo… https://t.co/RS6yOh9vMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainy day mood ☔️🖤 @nordstromsea  . . . . . . #seattle #seattlerain #mood #pnwgirls #cityscape #downtownseattle… https://t.co/ijsgITFcEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am listening to music on my phone @ Providence, Rhode Island https://t.co/xUDYToWKil]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello, just bc calum and ashton unfollowed people doesn’t mean you have to cancel them and be complete assholes!! thank you for your time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually stopped buying freezer items because I lose power so much.  I couldn’t keep up with throwing everything away]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahjaswim @PPeakers @MyPeakChallenge @SamHeughan @MPCFitlanders @Sheugs @barbaramills1 @LaurelSchuett @GHJNancy… https://t.co/Yfq3tLVVvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to read reaction papers my students are writing about the #violence against children surveys conducted i… https://t.co/vZlCv77Hso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Build The Wall: The Best Argument You Will Ever Hear! https://t.co/8g3fIMlPfQ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back home ... and at home. 🤣 #lobsterbennies #sundayspecial❤️ @ Black Duck Cafe https://t.co/U9d8YBRseh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long calls with my grandma always manage to recenter me in a way that I least expect it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hat_rad @magda_kosmider @PenelopaCwierci @Wojak_Szwejk https://t.co/9mmD2HcpU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPM If he loved his family he wouldn't have cheated on his wife in the first place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys!!! My 5 y/o lost his stuffed puppy somewhere in the house. Do you have any remotely deployable teams who s… https://t.co/sqP6lx9dO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Chris, you realize that everyone is laughing at you, don’t you? Why take the doctor’s report as *truth… https://t.co/bHPUfqvZBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[this makes me so mad. my illness isn’t a fashion statement okay? thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lights, camera, coffee. #Behindthescenes @myfox8 https://t.co/85TRtaZHEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[22 degrees out and I have the window open a crack and the heat in my apartment is on so high I end up soaked in swe… https://t.co/Y3OMevV93b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alimariemeadows Your way too beautiful girl That's why it'll never work You'll have me suicidal, suicidal  Is this… https://t.co/gnHUSUorcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what happens when your workout playlist has The Tommies, Olanda Draper and the Associates, MC Hammer, Chaka… https://t.co/2t1FHGysih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Excelsior @lopezobrador_ No creo que lleguemos a los 3 años , es demasiado esperar !]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s March 1st and it’s cheese”.  Next to Normal Quote https://t.co/kQMFyXrkEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up in the middle of the night with the worst calf pain and now I’m convinced I have a DVT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd = #BULLY. Democrats, Free Press are AMERICAN'S #BULLIES.  SAY most outrageous things, lie until it's bel… https://t.co/PxOUsGqkpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomColeOK04 @jaketapper @NPR @POTUS Did you finally plow through the wordy House resolution to be able to free you… https://t.co/8xeptcrEjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know its love when your SO takes you to a cajun restaurant when they dont like cajun food. My husband knows my… https://t.co/R8hKMJEW8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnbcrist chik fil a strips or raising canes strips? https://t.co/Jni2LrJgHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never assume Black people have an inferiority complex about their skin complexion. Yes, colorism is real but that d… https://t.co/DWq92IAey2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reepRN ~ wear your CPAP ~ Don’t think you’re all better and stop taking your meds ~ if at all possible, avoid opio… https://t.co/Kuyg2T3wJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittanyFurlan  I feel about kid rock and Sharyl crow. The same way you feel about Bradley cooper and Gaga! Watch… https://t.co/oRFTHKLG1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all must have never of raised teenage boys. Tangy, ripe, sharp, outdoors these are all ODORS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Troubled  that we see fetal tissue as essential to find medical treatments. What's to keep the research community f… https://t.co/CJEJUGF8r8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHoustonWade @tedlieu Trump is doing the same thing to SNL actors, but hey, you know, he's the president so he c… https://t.co/amONMZqgp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Coffee ☕️☕️☕️ (@ Home Kitchen in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/90EFubcSPr https://t.co/l93TnDiN1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why I just went on Facebook to watch the red table talk and ended up crying over a video of people saving a baby from choking at the mall]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm saying that taxing all religious organizations would hurt #synagogues, #mosques, and #temples far more than it… https://t.co/J8HEg0MEia]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the fruit of the Spirit is love, joy, peace, forbearance, kindness, goodness, faithfulness,…… https://t.co/GQLrcNKPzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stannis was wild. Came in villain, was kinda cool for most of season 5 then he pulled the most villainous thing out of everybody  Crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SNUmbb i love ya’ll ....but i also almost just had a heart attack. ❤️⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepRooney @FoxNews @LelandVittert You WILL NOT GET MY VOTE next time around.  We the people put @POTUS  in the whi… https://t.co/E5VAGk6Zd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conservationists plant a 'super grove' of redwood trees cloned from ancient stumps https://t.co/Ndwk2vSgMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sonofliberty89 remember when I got rejected from UF and you ridiculed me for FOUR CONSECUTIVE YEARS?!!!!!! LMAO https://t.co/Z1hOwXMSHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldsbie WHAT!  I WORKED THERE!  My FRIENDS work there!    Leave Cineplex Scotiabank ALONE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and shine gang! Bring the coffee and I got the breakfast goodies. See you in 30 min! #case3atl https://t.co/6Zr26jjeUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jump out of a relationship and start talking/fucking a new bitch. That's classy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever suck dick with your head leaning off the bed upside down and you can feel the dick go all the way by your left lung]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@chrislhayes Thank you for staying the obvious and keep stating it, please. My neighborhood in #Nogales is just th… https://t.co/yD1mshrv3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe.....a little LESS! #dirtyglove #weonabudget 🤦🏽‍♀️ @ Detroit, Michigan https://t.co/jKKlEjRkDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commen sense isn’t prevailing hence the new dress code. Professionalism is still tied  to this sport. Fashion can s… https://t.co/2YqYVETsj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just slathered myself in sunscreen, TIME FOR WORK!!!! https://t.co/11MYgOJRuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our family has truly been blessed! #WeAllBall #Family #SmallTownKids #Thoroughlybred🐎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett @AOC If I’m not mistaken, you just ushered in a whole new version of 🤡🌎. I’ve been a fan of yours s… https://t.co/hAzsWkusXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@absolute__unit @Hero_TweeTing @Oddjobs_Ginsan The last portion of Death Note was to showcase Light's overconfidenc… https://t.co/JxFGqdiDdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no emergency on our southern border, but there is one here at home. Philadelphia is a city of immigrants f… https://t.co/F6Knk9N6AK]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS IS NOT A DRILL PEOPLE. I REPEAT THIS IS NOT A DRILL. https://t.co/IhEH48gthc]]></document></documents></author>