<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[can someone explain what VIP means on edm remixes? #VIP 🤔 #helpagirlout]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar Please!  Workers who get a W-2 are footing the bill for the rest of the country.  Rates, loopholes, all stacked against us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@297c1441a2fe4ab @LionelMedia And which Middle Eastern country would you support?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portland Joins Coastal Communities in Opposing Offshore Drilling https://t.co/0Szc6h25nW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kendalllake @kelskeyz @Sarcasteph @Sarah_Elizabath @SamiCappola Brb sending a million letters from the corgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlquintanilla @KatyTurNBC So once again tax payers are footing the bill for trump’s tariffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big day in the governor’s office — @GovSisolak signed his first bill! SB1 funds the legislature for the 2019 sessio… https://t.co/CFtnlNoiRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that time you said this wasn’t a bob @elliegoulding? You were right. This is a beautiful f***ing ballad th… https://t.co/lmjzEFZkWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Coral Gables: mist, 71°F 94% humidity, wind 7mph, pressure 1017mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Creed49175759 I was completely💔2yrs after my mom died. Getting better then I get a call that my husband died from… https://t.co/qH4kP79Nse]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not enough to engage institutions... need to follow the community. @RushMedical did Westside listening tour. Our ac… https://t.co/tqhaFRvQ7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iTweet_HOTFIRE Cheapest on there is 500 .. I'm not about that life lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never realized how Fucking fine lil durk is until I seen him tonight 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[A truly important question - - Can you have integration with all four STEM areas equal or do you have to give up th… https://t.co/0KokQVb4q8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cupid coming in hot 🏹❤️Shooting arrows of love to all of you, Happy Valentine’s Day! 💕 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/jEoSltNoMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woow I wished that I still had mines to take!!! That is so sweet mom's son to have your blessed mom!!! I lost mines… https://t.co/DlDLaqrVTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StuartRBlythe @msuwrac @crmcardle @jrhodes That’s some good company! Can we get a trophy or maybe an office nap co… https://t.co/OwpzJ8ZlwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mother Nature needs to pick a season and stay with it bc I don’t have enough medication for these sinus-induced migraines every day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening Night with my agency brother! Thanks CTG! ❤️ #Repost @CTG  ・・・ Congratulations to CTG's @matos_tomas and… https://t.co/RNilXpYPqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree.  Saw Ms.  Savage exhibit in Jacksonville , Florida and thouroughly enjoyed it and was awed by her talent!]]></document><document><![CDATA[R6 Cynwyd Line best kept secret on @SEPTA. Small train, great walkable neighborhood, amazing walkable public school… https://t.co/zV0QVRFuxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteelCity_Burg @bulletgifts Lmao. My kitchen table serves that purpose. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s easy to get involved and support Loads of Love - any amount of 💵 will help! Check out the link 👇🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Introduction Shezad Nawab MBE BA (Hons) Owner Business Consulting Management  Birmingham, West Midlands… https://t.co/ygnKkEEl6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kreed: "this is too strong"  Other kreed: "the core?"  Kreed: "no, the woman"   CAPTAIN MARVEL WAS BADASS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Candy Shop [feat. Olivia] [Explicit] by 50 Cent feat. Olivia on Amazon Music Song gives a whole different… https://t.co/Nbr33POvQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[i fr do not have time anymore for these whack ass games dudes are playin. i’m bout to be mean to all these dudes all year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best headline of the day: “Home Depot ‘bomb threat’ was actually customer warning he’s about to poop” 💩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow @MalcolmNance But this is not really funny. I’ve seen this gentleman be an apologist for Trump and th… https://t.co/Rk0r1q04EB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OffMuteRKelly ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ More proof of how amazing you are.  Thank you for watching out for Survivors]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vincerandle @K8_mile @sarpalida @NykeeLove_ @KimberlyNFoster @khloekardashian @jordynwoods Nah, I’d only cheat on… https://t.co/Eg8Iyo4gK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BennieGThompson U EXPECT AMERICANS 2 KEEP PICKING UP TAB 4 ILLEGALS? THAT'S WHY THERE'S NO MONEY 2 HELP BLACK NEIGHBORHOODS😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to invest in a new rounded barrel straightener. Any suggestions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also send me a screenshot of your subscription and that you turned the notifications on, if we get to a 100 subscri… https://t.co/rluf1MycBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corinna_cohn @HRC @stonewalluk I hear you. But “we” also will make our own spaces and our own platforms (like your… https://t.co/8jtnoS2sEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[New England Patriots owner charged for soliciting sex at a massage parlor  https://t.co/h9iGZiEpUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[ME. We don’t gotta be with each other every single minute of every day lol. We can’t? Then cool.. No big deal😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have bought 3 festival tickets in a 5hr span. EDC, Get Lucky and a Circuit party for St. Pats Day in LA. 2019 is… https://t.co/e2DpJPcfCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[im putting it out into the universe that within the next three yrs i move into my own place in baltimore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everytime I go a Vietnamese restuarant they're all so surprised when I speak Viet to them lol like yes I'm one of you dont act so shocked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y fue un cumpleaños infinitamente FELIZ! Gracias a Dios por un año más de vida. Gracias a TODOS los que hicieron qu… https://t.co/jOkm0CtUtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌲Con Sue Photography and Design🌲  ♥️On-Location.... March 9-14, 2019♥️  🌲Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌲  ♥️This… https://t.co/NH6oTdQuGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@illitchico If you need a new movie rec, Life and Nothing More is playing at the Enzian Saturday. It's a super good… https://t.co/0jZum2fnnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants another ❄️ ⛄️ day? They’re calling for more🤷🏾‍♀️. 📸: @bagladies - . . . . . . #snowday #winterwonderland… https://t.co/WINRf8qsLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still play overwatch for some god awful reason when even in quick play it's all the same boring comps I'm sick of "goats"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iammikemitchell Lol..... I feel that way all the time! Damn spellcheck 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FebronioG @OvercomersBC @KABBFOX29 It’s actually dark blue, but thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[tis' so sweet....take Jesus hand and let Him lead and guide U....thru your promised land.... https://t.co/xedRW0zqgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This still makes me cry till this day by the way this video is from 2 years ago, May 9th, 2017 to be exact and just… https://t.co/fSDn4JX4vD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Olivia Smith (2019) unsigned workin’ tonight at Hoop City - reppin’ Bishop Gorman @BishopGormanHS 🏀✅]]></document><document><![CDATA[this will make you tee-hee. Wait, what, where??? Get away! Imposter!  #cute #funny #teddybear https://t.co/jV2U4VNxfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legitimately just sent my coworkers the Harry Potter house sorting quiz with a high level of importance. Priorities. 😂⚡️ #HarryPotter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenna_Marbles When are we gonna see you in the new Just For Men and Wah-men and Jenna commercials?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caitlinrraine @norvina1 @pxttygarcia @beautybykellyo @justmahia @TheNishaEvans @cutcreaser @peachcait_ thank u so… https://t.co/Mgl4qniNIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will someone please buy me to James Charles palette tomorrow, I will love you forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me tell y’all! After going through a lot of hurt and crying for a long time tonight just wanting to give up I s… https://t.co/zEdo8tMnUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShellyCov @PGutierrez630 @GOP @gatewaypundit Why would Dems vote for this? I thought they were against this. What misfits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[YSIV was.... decent. Not the best. I still have high hopes for his last album dropping this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robotic noodle maker at Dragon Pearl restaurant Toronto. #robots #Al #food #toronto @ Dragon Pearl Buffet https://t.co/ooS5g0kLZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing all of u a very Happy Valentine's Day! ❤❤❤😘😘😘 https://t.co/bubfvJkIFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosalindlex @mgerman01 @She_IsRose @BlackInkCrew Really? Let’s see in 1921 the first African American to fly the p… https://t.co/Q5NpJCBCM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dealing with a person who always feels fault in your relationship is just ANNOYING! 😫 #pieceofyourlovechallenge #BlackLove]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lydia Bolin crossed 5K. Time 00:35:42, pace 11:30 min/mile, est. finish 8:11 am https://t.co/HCjMYM5T68 #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SvenTrueNorth @cathmckenna @OmarAlghabra @gagansikand @RStaceyLaforme @S_A_Society @PortCreditYacht @CPIA_ACIP… https://t.co/9P94YxuZbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s sooo funny listening to ‘Girls need love’ clean version, i just heard myself yell out “dick”, shit caught me off guard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving it!! 👍❤️Moving in RIGHT direction for MARCH Madness!!💙💛Go HENS!🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep Eric Swalwell of California is yet another I wish would throw his name in the hat. I have seen him stop for man… https://t.co/vjbjFBeHbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here are some of the others! I’m getting there. 😁 https://t.co/6vpTIQEjNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 30th Anniversary to a hubby who is fun to smile with and be silly with! @ Sebago Brewing Company https://t.co/gh5dr7f725]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those saying Willy Wonka are 100% correct. It would also make an excellent escape room. 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump I’m one of them! I am so disappointed in the GOP for their support of this man that I… https://t.co/HcgnlY0UKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Dhg3xBX4Un I Love Aaron and Jennifer's podcast too. Can't wait to read their book. Here's a link to Ep… https://t.co/M08YNeS8Fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@direct_commerce Collar Show Display Space decoration and display rack making factory,if need the display props or… https://t.co/lSk7fkL4pQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting my Winter fix #xl8 #workingawayfromhome #tapetenwechsel @ Saint Paul, Minnesota https://t.co/eCYUNzaaNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anybody else lay in bed at night crying because one day your parents aren't going to be here anymore.... because same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher @Demonoid55 Some scary shit going down - he’ll start a war right here at home!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLELnetwork @ELnetworkSDCOE @DLeNM @OCDEProjectGLAD @SanDiegoCOE @DLE_SDSU @r_simaan @CABEBEBILINGUAL… https://t.co/FEhIcMx0Qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamscottevans @NBCWorldofDance I love you. You brighten my days. I'm a disabled vet with chronic pain and ptsd.  I… https://t.co/mY1Tx1X4Qr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews By the time we reached  the 2020 General Elections, you will be but a passing thought.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The “mercy” killing of seniors is not far behind. It will be considered a “kindness” to put old people out of their… https://t.co/w5uD9joZFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched Die Hard for the first time. Two thoughts.  1. It’s an AWESOME movie. 🙌🏼  2. It’s still not a Christmas movie. 🤷🏼‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s my Shawty! My childhood faves...Chun Li/Batman/ Dragon Ball Z all in one. Thank you @melvintodd_ls… https://t.co/xHjBUwpa6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[#foryarnssake was #rosecityyarncrawl2019 stop two after a huge delay with the buses. Enjoying taking my time. I hav… https://t.co/uohJwIcDhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dzsozi22 @DeannGoss @PinupStickers @LuisLuiskiss1 @VixenVegas @LuCkYDaDDa666 @Lefac01 @rosethatsme1 @icejedi1970… https://t.co/h9gmhSZlPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m now 31. I feel there are no birthdays to look forward to from this point 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inyourgoodbyes4 At first I was gonna say I also have a nice one outside mine but realized we have the same dunks]]></document><document><![CDATA[“instead of jesus you just believe in and worship muhammad”  NO.   we believe in jesus. we believe in his resurrect… https://t.co/zI8hD1MzTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlairBraverman sending you waves of support and best wishes from your fans in Key West, FL! 🐾 Warm woofs, Cara, St… https://t.co/QkehosxLds]]></document><document><![CDATA[me last week: gonna rewatch tvd for the 5th time! netflix today: i wish you would’ve said something sooner...we’re taking it off in 5 days..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol people treat you like shit if you’re  the nicest person in the world and they treat you like shit if you’re a b… https://t.co/sAl1NlIqOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flyaway_k You need a bowl, or edibles if your throat's sore.  Cures everything. 🤗🌊🌊🌊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @KylieJenner  I can be your new best friend, I won't do you wrong like Jordyn did😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissDebGee Packed for a six day trip to Seattle this past summer with just this bag! :D]]></document><document><![CDATA[03/05/2019: We had a very special day celebrating an amazing and loyal friend, LaTianna Will, who just turned 34. W… https://t.co/gsmINrgE8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall i can’t believe my presentation partner gave my the section about state penetration so now i have to stand if… https://t.co/BtHx9136CU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y is there drama on my tl i was watching New Girl and I come back to this https://t.co/IipnPaATNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I got asked during a massage if I would suck their nipples. I said no.   Filing that one under one of the wei… https://t.co/jAIJMgOSuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gstrick16 @avlschoolsports YES! Can’t wait to make to trip to Asheville.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melly and I are at Waffle House sitting at the high bar and I dropped my damn check into the sink. My waitress came… https://t.co/VYcd7ZClhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano In other news, I'm totally changing my name to Melissa Alano.]]></document></documents></author>