<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@dickfain Saturday cinches it with a W! You go undefeated at home for the season. And, 16-2 in ANY power 5 Conferen… https://t.co/nCdzfeHky5]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Colossus Festival Kickoff at Piano’s: Ecstatic Union #newcolossusfestival #newcolossusfestivalkickoff… https://t.co/JZXoBme8OA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaceySkrysak My mother in law is the sweetest person alive. If my wife turns out like her I’ll be a lucky guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Osea, no puedo creer la química que tengo en general con Diego, es de esas personas que adoras pero al mismo tiempo… https://t.co/55lu1vvq9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me 5 minutes late to work  "We were wondering where Grant was and we look out and he's just doing donuts in the parking lot."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP And not one of your Representatives could even come close to challenging his assertions. That’s fairly damning for the party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:32.4°F WchillLow:16.6°F Wind:13 mph Dir:W Baro:Rising Rain2day:0.24in Hum:63% UV:0.0 @ 20:00 02/24/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met again this morning with the pastor of the Iglesia Gracia Fundamental de la Gracia for strategy and prayer]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a tie game but consider it a victory for Dickinson Trinity. Holding the top-scoring team in the region to only… https://t.co/lHrzIKzApJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Oh golly gee.  The poor GOP.  Deutch is a turd; we flip him the bird and boycott MSNBC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us for spring classes. Bullyproof them for life. Fun, focus and fitness. Great for all ages 4 to 74. #karate… https://t.co/oVbiPDBmjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#motivationmonday Think no one can get sober during #MardiGras? Have a look. https://t.co/1n2rZe06h9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philipgawthorne 1. It’s a Wonderful Life 2. Annie Hall 3. Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind 4. Cinema Paradiso… https://t.co/aIw6OibGte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffreygoldbIum it's bn this many years since I've realize "Jolly Roger" was the msge in Indep Day '96 when you dr… https://t.co/S2iNoDI1ls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the Onion. This is #investing, without #ethics, morals or a social license. Just an extractive industry with sp… https://t.co/rRv8s2VBEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilshipley There’s a lot of stuff like this in dating apps. In Bumble, you’re either “new to the area” or “a local” 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiagosoczek @AlfredMyers @Bradesco @itau Hahahaha mesma situação aqui! Tô com uns pontos represados no cartão do B… https://t.co/VPttcPbRH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pulloutday21 Is there any other way for me to get a shirt if I can’t make it during the times you’re on campus?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Filming in Los Angeles documenting awesome orgs that fight food insecurity and promote urban harvesting!… https://t.co/tJtGoQliGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[These will all surely miss:  ⚽️Arsenal +.5 (-122) ⚽️Spurs/Arsenal OVER 3 (-102) ⚽️Both Score/Arsenal Win (+450)]]></document><document><![CDATA[You leave town for a couple of days and all hell breaks loose... what happened, @RaeOnTheNews ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FJN_Nathan I swear, I think Wynot held the ball for like 3 minutes against BDS yesterday. In the 4th. Up 3. Oi...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so dumbfounded that people still ask if Orlando should tank for the draft. It makes no sense where they are at… https://t.co/PtyGe44OFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbsgirlshoops Thank you!  You’re the man!  Wish we could have done your game.  Next year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dan_OMara This tweet speaks to me. I believe he used the Juan Gonzalez-Style stance, which was the coolest in the game]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect from the opening bells to the closing ascent from Sky Harbor. Of the five CDs that I scooped that day (Slea… https://t.co/wqQx9E7XXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennaJacobsen5 If that comment was directed to me, yes of course I read it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parkway Central 49, Kirkwood 41, final. Colts will play Marquette next wed. in sectional at Lindenwood. #stlpreps #WeAreSTLToday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylevc @DylanNowak @NHLSeattle_ Yeah totally get that. I was just trying to adapt what I already had. I think ther… https://t.co/vOwh3uXUQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only reason Luka wasn’t shut down 10 games ago with some random “injury” is bc Dallas still wants him to win RO… https://t.co/9uLH8vLB0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Habanero Mexican Cafe in Austin, TX https://t.co/OiFNnoX5MB https://t.co/ASsRtdPLtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Binz is absolutely already a favorite. And clearly this is meant to be played on vinyl. I can’t wait to hear those… https://t.co/K126jBGHZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuukka Rask on if the Bruins are turning into something special this season:  “Special group for sure. It’s in our… https://t.co/GZqEi6L8rE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t claim ur mature if u doing shit like this, you gotta be a petty as mf if your still blocking people. https://t.co/B9mJ1JmkiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudiMantere @hjkhelsinki They do have great festivals over there, I have seen a bunch of you tube , wish we could… https://t.co/2wBQv154EE]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must take sides. Neutrality helps the oppressor, never the victim. Silence encourages the tormentor, never the t… https://t.co/CXP6siOARi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanWHendry @matthewasears And I don't see how this relates to what @matthewasears tweeted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome! Happy Birthday @bmabercrombie30 &amp; Roll Tide!! Keep believing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheECRN @Raiders My Sons a Raider fan!, you losers!! Go Bears!! Trubiskis gonna dominate next year!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenn198523 Thank you for the follow back Jennifer.  I enjoy your tweets.   :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[When #CHRONICPAIN  takes control of your life you try to adjust I have for 22 years but now Pain drs are failing me… https://t.co/mwCcHs5e4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I needa learn how to make friends in class so we can exchange quiz answers :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UZlSWHORE @watsonmane Would you look at the time, it's a quarter past ruining your life. Lol https://t.co/Yv1IcaSNec]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kareem Jackson might as well come on back to Houston lmao play safety fam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertElPaso @LChavez_ES Congratulations!! Kylah works so hard, she really earned the Flo Hyman award.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EntrenamientoDeCiclismoDeSalón miércoles 8 am #OverTrainFitness #WeAreOverTrain #LaCasaDeLosCampeones… https://t.co/0rJvER5YRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dieterbeitwitte @BernieSanders Also, why would it be a danger if they preferred #GreenNewDeal  jobs advertising or… https://t.co/NIZq5pKk7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would have loved to see Michael Vick serve as the Legends' OC during a game. I imagine he would've been creative… https://t.co/L8sP0lPScj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jets, Michigan and NMU all win last night 👍 plus Detroit got a nice return for Jensen. Friday night hockey was solid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to make some $$ @GoPuff (@ Gopuff in Bethlehem, PA) https://t.co/l54VoKB6An]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlymouthDawg @Me_Miss_C I love the hell out of her, that’s the damn truth. I always think to myself I can be bette… https://t.co/NDoZXiuKnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZeranDrew @MapleLeafs Apparently there is a trade waiting for the cue to clear up]]></document><document><![CDATA[LADY PANK - LIVE IN TORONTO !!! JEDYNY KONCERT W KANADZIE !!! 31 Marca - Centrum Litewskie Missisauga ladypank_offi… https://t.co/X5DE2FdYWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw @HowellDori Is the president of Venezuela separating families and putting children in cages ??? If… https://t.co/rNtUYIBhfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahjeong Sounds like you are the one who doesn’t understand the Constitution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you on Instagram ??? - Please go follow Paulbrown_uk and BrownsWave  Later Today - I do an interview with Brad… https://t.co/rBsOa3hH0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[A pretty day in #vancouverwashington @ Vancouver, Washington https://t.co/Lgvfvv02jM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally a name to call a couple friends who have crappy camera quality!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HawleySports @FOX59 @BoilerBall @CoachPainter Excellent story Larry! Well done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you press twitter’s handy little translate button on this tweet, it comes it to “compliment me, right now”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@max_tesnow Yes--we sure look stupid to the world for putting him at the top--though he had some help getting there]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite zoo in Indiana just welcomed a little (6 ft tall!) baby girl giraffe to the world! Her name - Makena -… https://t.co/OglDJMinUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 @CRufsvold Lock that Trump loving low down no good Russian asset sorry piece of 💩 up]]></document><document><![CDATA[CARTOONY PORTRAIT, WORK IN PROGRESS: using a chisel edged marker to give it a chalky look. See… https://t.co/UlhGSRPGQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing MANA at work is literally a tease from me to me 😭😭😭😭 I wanna dance sooo bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@___Aaron___ Honestly, I think it's an issue that needs to be addressed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @DHSgov She can be put into the cage for a week, with pay of course, for four weeks or so before she's… https://t.co/tky8ENikOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[ACPA Latinx Network loteria photo frame at CelebrACPA #lafeminista #escholar #ACPA19 #ACPALN @ Hynes Convention Cen… https://t.co/J5E7EKjZ9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day Five: I’ve accepted the 7 Day Book Cover Challenge from @mmorrisBHS. I’ll post covers of 7 books I love—no expl… https://t.co/g7rSQVjjb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolyRhuagh @tklforgiven @Heliocoptero @PittsburghTodd @zapher134 @yourmumspants @zypisfy @Cern_lXXl… https://t.co/15vxPyCpha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawnbrolin @HSatterley @ParkhurstCPA @HeatherTowns @CalebLJenkins @SherrellTMartin @MMartinezEA @IntuitAccts… https://t.co/CSikLpbTqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fakecoatesy @Real_RobRossi Again, reading comprehension, yikes. Take another crack at it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My review of CROCODILE https://t.co/PAvOvbdXsq @CrisMovieCorner @AmberGanoe @RevEwwEr @AndieMerchak @AdrianaMerchak… https://t.co/408xhG5Wrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to our friend Dwayne Bowe @Moneybomusic for hosting our @ColliersIntl_WI crew at his FL crib. https://t.co/l2yDpDOPE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[You heard it here first. Media matters forced Tucker Carlson to call into an AM radio station talking about how muc… https://t.co/GYOaNE48MN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unfortunately a tragic ending. R.I.P. Riya. Wow! People called the police to complain about when the Amber Alert wa… https://t.co/fmN1lyrDBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸🏒🇨🇦✝️❤️Thank you to anissabay harmonybay isabellabay_ for allowing me to return to@coaching the game i move . Tha… https://t.co/fFzsbwr6Hn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren @SenBrianSchatz Just a random thought - Senator Warren, you are a badass!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mixed precipitation coming down in the UNCC area! 🌧 ❄️ @wxbrad @LyndsayWBTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Trump doesn't threaten. He makes promises, carries through with them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blue_Wail @Nap5151 One day when 👃🏻 rejoins group texts 🚶🏻 will be there 🤲🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenJonesIEQ @ihrice @CorsIAQ @IndoorChem I would expect the pan would get discarded due to coating damage before t… https://t.co/VXn5NOrVBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeWeathereye wow i thought my 3.6" was lame. hopefully we do better tmw night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimberlyBlumen1 @PaigeWickner @ICHEJournal Looking forward to seeing this paper @KimberlyBlumen1!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanMillerFox2 Hard to hear I know Dan but @davebirkett speaks the truth.  Winning free agency is good. Winning act… https://t.co/V3C21ZVjBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blackishabc @EvaLongoria @MilesBrown @IAMQUVENZHANE @marsaimartin This show needs to come on more than once a week… https://t.co/riAtvNhRJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally done with letting people let me down when I know from the jump how it’s gonna end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your 69 year old mom sends you a GIF of @djkhaled and your 100% certain she has no idea who that is, you live… https://t.co/QysbcWUmRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boston__Sucks @JoeGiglioSports @The_Jay_Bink @JackFritzWIP Your favorite Phillie this decade!]]></document><document><![CDATA[KION: ICE accused of using DMV data to target undocumented immigrants: Supervisor Luis Alejo taking action @KION546… https://t.co/lrPYTQcrfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEVinceRusso @steveaustinBSR @VinceMcMahon Another GREAT SHOW! So many behind the scenes stories!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Refs have more whistles tonight than combined points in this game - Jazz vs Thunder]]></document><document><![CDATA[This year isn’t easy, but I’m trying the best I can and I’m pretty happy about that]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl right here is my rock. She has always been there for me when I need her the most and I can’t thank her en… https://t.co/iwsETJQHiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CryptoEuclid Thank goodness i was in Florida last month and heading to Minneapolis next week. Phew https://t.co/NM7taZcUP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweatsntopknots Hall and oats wait for me November 1979 Denver fitzsimmons hospital my 1st wife and I lost a 3 month old hep b]]></document><document><![CDATA[* Are You Looking For A Tile Contractor In Your Area? * Fl, Ga &amp; Sc * I WANT TO SERVE YOU! * @ I-77 &amp; SC-34 https://t.co/e9slef0w3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elenahan1 Ah congratulations!! Looking forward to seeing your adventures ahead. And welcome to SF. And thank you f… https://t.co/7H3a1UaDjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had NO alarms set this morning at all. i woke 5 minutes before i had to leave the house. i hate life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coupgurl69 @NickMiroff @RodStryker I have seen other evidence of this posted several times in the past two years.… https://t.co/PRAGzcTUef]]></document></documents></author>