<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Confidence in the US PRESIDENT to do the right thing regarding world affairs...soooo countries are… https://t.co/xeTIGPZfUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grooovaliciousn Thank you. Our visits were good. She is strong and doing well. She appreciates all of the support… https://t.co/aBT6Z7oHhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristianoOrbeck @SpeaksKen I was just talking to @SpeaksKen about this 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Aboard the &lt;i&gt;Golden Girls&lt;/i&gt;-Themed Cruise, Destination Bone Zone https://t.co/EbqzOTKx02 via @jezebel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuffShedShay always has a smile on her face no matter where she is or who she greets. Mike will always teach you t… https://t.co/GarrtkWot9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BalleinTom Yes, daddy will sabe him.... I know he will... he is a good daddy...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelintheOC @sugarbeatbc @HMJonesWrites @annerallen @TheRuralVA @fahma311 @jonathabrooke @juliaparktracey… https://t.co/59zv71OaO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobChristie11 Rob, that poor dog was humiliated enough without you posting!   😂. LOL, I've owned some of those "do… https://t.co/L4xRxp5g4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kyle said we’re going to buy all the junk food I’ve been wanting and have a movie night when my teeth are healed #truelove]]></document><document><![CDATA[“life is a highway” by rascal flatts is like the original “lane changing” by SOBxRBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emanuelwildones No me mires a los ojos, porque no me quiero enamorar. Dicen que esas cosas duelen, pero por ti yo… https://t.co/wkYA3n0AEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shr2da1 @WinchesterBros @FangasmSPN @SuperWiki @jarpad Wow !!!!  Gorgeous 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little over two years ago, this little girl captured our hearts. She allowed us to love her and in return she has… https://t.co/OK6nLdPrzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexboulerice @LisaDjeva Merci les amies! C'est vraiment le meilleur cadeau!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final in Madison Dodgers Girls Baskets Courtney Bland lefty jump hook buzzer beater gives Dodgers the victory v… https://t.co/oTRKGnQINq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xo_keelyy if they follow you, but you dont follow them back &amp; their account is private, it’ll do that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RustyMay14 @TruthHurtz2019 @AndrewPollackFL @realDonaldTrump And recoups every quarter and every dime (in spades)… https://t.co/jPeFBvy4b1]]></document><document><![CDATA[They elected her. Don't feel bad for NY at all. Will never spend another dollar there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking back to my time in NYC... what a wild ride. This shoot for @aeropostale with @kckrows and these two babes… https://t.co/XRwQuKRZYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also my 7 yo put parmesan cheese on rice noodles that already had soy sauce on them. And is eating them. Kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As seen on the streets of Boston… . Brilliant day… —started with my first experience with novemberprojectbos,  —inc… https://t.co/ErLqqlSRiK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valley of Fire State. Park 2016 #throwback #HolidayPhotos #Vegas @ Valley of Fire State Park https://t.co/PYWyGLoQIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything you need to know can be seen in @kevinmarsh eyes.  I’m on to you bub.              #kc #kcfoodie @ 1900… https://t.co/4QHeVU4JNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to win $799 towards a new Mattress from @rcwilley https://t.co/gZRcdaiEcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KslippySlippy I know! Everytime I go through i feel like my tires are going to pop 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying a cold 🥶 day❣️💋🥰 @ Ice skating at Georgetown waterfront https://t.co/0LFMgKHX8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone meet Mavis and Matilda. I’ve been waiting 21 years and I’m finally a dog mom! The cold rain was well worth… https://t.co/O1RRMh57cK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please protection over and God’s work through the interns @MainstreamORL interns as they spend the next week in #NOLA🙏🏻❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland LaHood, a one-term district attorney who lost his political party’s nomination to one of the lawyers h… https://t.co/eGsVWDNeAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NilsHeadley @JaniceWyattRoss Excellent point ☝🏽. How can my young adult learn these essential life skills if HS is… https://t.co/AGvOfTKPo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marciarusso @jonfavs I assume you mean POTUS when you refer to winning 2020. The Dem candidates will be discussing… https://t.co/6pUprFLV4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day from this crazy bunch. 🙈💕 #lifewithWBA https://t.co/pV9TUc7glg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the @GettyMuseum @pawstv #CJruiningthegroupphoto #collsedu #collsLA19 https://t.co/MkZkSpv6lh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our Show Me District finalists!  Alaric Chen 5th US Extemp  Aiden Maschger 5th IX Extemp  Xavior… https://t.co/kCuzdSwFJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QmagaMike @wbshaw3 @Patriot925 @TigerLetsRoll @TVismeuc @sonk004 @RL9631 @doranna07 @laurieDuMi @sc08960854… https://t.co/Lw9AzGwtAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soft spoken with a broken jaw 🥀 @ Troy, New York https://t.co/VWDzfuFtsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 10th 2019- I attended the the #Unicorn phresh off the runway fashion show looking for some diverse content… https://t.co/pHMzYHMkZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 25th Birthday to my very best friend, I love you! Nick and I are so sad that we can't be there to celebrate w… https://t.co/KztEL596Zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s this dominos effect where everything you do impacts everyone impacted by you.  Make good choices... https://t.co/V68dF6iuEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panic! At the  Disco #HoustonRodeo #panicatthedisco https://t.co/pVlIvwybyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennbonafide @GeorgePapa19 He proved me wrong. He made a statement. https://t.co/AouANglQrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[African black leopard photographed for the first time in over 100 years, scientist says - CNN https://t.co/sOOxtfnCYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McKesson - Are all your driver's this rude and ignorant, or just those in the Twin Cities?? The police should have… https://t.co/8xLxXKwIaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[After spending 5 hours with her,brought her food,and got food from a church.Street To Homes finally came,no food Ti… https://t.co/fDCd9DNp4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway’s husband just accused Trump of a new impeachable offense - https://t.co/x2BcPCbVd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@67jewelCDH I’m hopeful this nightmare will soon be over so we can began to work towards healing from all the ugly… https://t.co/37haA2Hl6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ednaelm I'm watching as it as homework for the Oscars, but its eh to me. https://t.co/KuBJeSWpiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlowerMoundHS TAFE has another blue ribbon from the Teach Tomorrow Summit! This one for Teacher Created Materials!… https://t.co/RNI5KHBw7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so looking forward to X Ray Season 4. The soap opera bits are so damn funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Vietnamese has gotten so bad that I tried ordering at a Viet restaurant and the waitress had difficulty comprehending me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The things I cherish most in life: my dog and text conversation with @AllyRubens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebradfordfile @nancyleeca I live in the terrible state of Ct . Our new dem . Governor is about to tax EVERYTHING… https://t.co/wmQTRGl0V4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGchronicles @aminatou Disappointing to see another “not all men” argument here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going through my first breakup, and it's really tough on me. 💔 https://t.co/7mClbviGwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how much time has passed, the love I have for my LGSD peeps just keeps growing and growing... #grateful… https://t.co/T6F2fQXcyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[A family survives the wrath of a hurricane then gets scammed after moving into their new Atlanta home. Can… https://t.co/Fe0AxtezXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[RESTOCK ALERT!! We have been restocked with our favorite scrubbies!! Hurry in and grab some!! We are open today, 10… https://t.co/YqBWKP55Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved the final movie for How To Train Your Dragon, though. Great series overall and it’s definitely my favorite cg animated movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ERICB This new way to get PAID in FULL. Check it out! https://t.co/pjznR0BZ8M #gold #cryptocurrency #guaranteed #ROI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayleewardd Legit saw a convertible with the top down today!😂 it’s not THAT warm. But I feel his enthusiasm for warmer temps &amp; sun]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re interested in adopting this beautiful little boy you can snatch him up at https://t.co/u0a8EWXZvM @ Sprin… https://t.co/neGAG6zt1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just slept for 12 hours even though I’m not sick and it fucking ruled]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeuceMason @jasondumont @SacramentoKings No, I think my media credentials got lost in the mail. I get it. I’m just… https://t.co/gUCxZn4NQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThursdayThoughts when baking and testing recipes for the next book, one MUST wear a kitty apron! #CatsOfTwitter… https://t.co/sm2jkphmrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[We say “Friend” in many languages @mistral_cec! Annual Friendship Day Parade!  @ElenaBuley @HISDWestArea https://t.co/9fz8uZ0vAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sometimes I don’t even realize I am at work until I leave for the day.” #corporate @corporate https://t.co/JUaBCCs0ZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was young I saw them, 1963 In a black and white world, music coloured me. https://t.co/qAanC5G6tQ Today is t… https://t.co/XHpeYeowjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking this week to relax, spend time with family upstate, and getting after those 2019 intentions 👊🏻But first, ☕️… https://t.co/43XZUlccuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlyhosoi I did!! It's so bright and colourful, I'm really into their image]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerfumeFlogger AAAH! WHO CARES! SHE IS A NOBODY WANNA BE SOMEBODY IMPORTANT! DIDN'T FOLLOW HER ANYWAY! NEVER EVEN HEARD OF HER! LOL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our city council held a press event with special words from @LASDMurakami, Captain Lewis and @kathrynbarger to say… https://t.co/QdKwOzQ8qk]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Grade is making community maps for their robots! 🤖 https://t.co/BQWFhelX0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[On our way home!! Tabby’s first time at Buc ee’s🤣🤣 https://t.co/Bwupe3QiGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaqarVick i could lift every second of the rest of my life and still be furious at him 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds for Y word sort in 2nd grade.  #washpride https://t.co/sgAuleNFWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know what’s better than warm banana bread?  Frozen banana bread.  Trust me on this👍😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve literally had the Genovia national anthem from The Princess Diaries stuck in my head all day. I don’t think I’… https://t.co/M1xZiBLeSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you know sleeping that extra ten minutes will make you late for work but you do it anyway :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucasdirt Tough.. one looks like a baby Bloomer and the other a baby Jimmy.. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw I have always supported Israel but under Netanyahu I find my self wavering. He is hurting Israel. A fasci… https://t.co/s1BXxcZjsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all ever wondered how stupid I am I just went to work without even checking the schedule only to find out I do not work tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daddy is always my Valentine. He has never missed a year of making sure I feel loved and that makes me feel so h… https://t.co/6rpd5dMQEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my mf sister 💖 i love u stupid bitch ass hoe ♒️💘 https://t.co/2uwH2HHkex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cell Project with a touch of Spring! ☀️#wpmschat https://t.co/Mj7lc2GIEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2: I have accepted a challenge from @chadsmithelearn to post covers of books I❤️: no reviews - just the cover.… https://t.co/G3IaZXz7HZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emoore @freckles What if it were a penny shy of six oh oh would it be five nine nine nine nine?]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL people be mad late to work today using the excuse of day light savings. Y’all had a day to figure it out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell Congress: #PaidLeave is our Jam and it should be yours too. Support the #FAMILYAct now... https://t.co/C7T9b3QSmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrick_Clarkin Yeah, but it is SPRING. Only one season that’s better. https://t.co/z0M4pFNCSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday my friend told me to Forge his dad signature so he can play in the soccer game bc he was failing a class.… https://t.co/Esj5Jyu7Ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Giants will probably end up in last place this season but I will root for them every game Go Giants]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WNEMTV5news Of course!!  Superintendents of schools take responsibility of every student from the time they leave… https://t.co/sehbc7WdtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evening_brew Ohhhh but what a show!!  Totally 🔥🔥. NWA just wasn’t ready. Periodt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddybaker420 Drinking while with my white friends drugs when I’m with my black friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmaLaineAuthor Thank you for doing so much awesome Twitter work for all writers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpencerBoyd @DISupdates @jimbobsgrizzly @KCJO_LABMOM889 @lisa_nor @sherylkeller66 @DannyLeBlanc24 @CMANGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mexopolis I asked my mom to call me Pinocchio when I was 5 because I liked it better than "Tasha"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess which state I'm in based on the curtains and the blizzard: https://t.co/aPObBCSAZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YuH8TM3 @RobChristie11 Next time, a rope? It is ridiculous that teachers can share their beliefs with kids. Like a… https://t.co/PJDlDzt7mB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The man accused of burning down the old French Broad Elementary School will be back in court. We’re live from the B… https://t.co/Sd1nPerusT]]></document></documents></author>