<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Need a reminder about the importance of our work? Need #inspiration to get through a meeting or meet a deadline?… https://t.co/MPFPueHQAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mis angeles ... 👌🏻💯 😇 👼 😎 @ Boca Raton, Florida https://t.co/2ZqK6jLIX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Candy Conversation Hearts Won't Make it To Production This Valentine's Day  I'm devastated! I guess the gift card t… https://t.co/byUj8qBJYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MildsAndDatYak @Paulie_Bruz What site? Because they shut down the Asian spot downtown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THERE IS HOPE "".WE CAN OVERCOME ANY OBSTACLES IF WE PUT OUR MIND TO it and have FAITH as a MUSTARD SEED.GOD IS A… https://t.co/Zkl4vSObFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Seminoles @FSU_Softball @FSUHoops @FSU_WTennis @FSUBaseball Not a bad day at the office. https://t.co/4rJNzCHNjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going nuts 😂 I have work in a few more hours...... 💀 https://t.co/0jykJ7EEyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kamenta I'll give you my address if you give me yours.. we could watch #twd together sometime! lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cara Delevingne presentando la última colección de Karl Lagerfeld... wow. https://t.co/B90A2GpDEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good team win at White Cloud. All but one player scored tonight, including all 3 foreign exchange students: Alvaro,… https://t.co/vE4u7uJZ4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drkelp_0829 Well that’s good!! At least you guys get a good honeymoon that you deseve!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinHatten21 @LadyTiger4life @m_anselment @IHSA_IL @OneTigerNation1 @wmixsports @areasports @Rick_Sports10… https://t.co/zDKJZGoy8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas Baby #lasvegas @ Flamingo Las Vegas Hotel &amp; Casino https://t.co/hS49FU3yG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piercewashingtn 😂 did you hear her at the end “don’t hit the ceiling” 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entre al baño y salí botando porque creí que había una araña en el bote de la basura y pues no, eran las pestañas d… https://t.co/pssv6XxYR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Link in bio! #richardcalvin #2TheMoon #MusicVideo https://t.co/JZ3Wqx6Ws8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Braedon Norman hits a 3 from the left wing to give Butler an 11-0 lead over Sidney with 4:21 left in the first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m sorry but i rather hear the artist 😂 but i love this moments tho as an artist, must be such an amazing feeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elise_shield @KDrawbaugh Why am I not surprised at all. And congrats @KDrawbaugh!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuzyQ44ks @clips4sale I'm intrested in joining again,  but I'm not sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puff balls of snow held by dried Queen Anne’s Lace.  #snow #barn #winter #toocold #dof #flowers #shotoniphone… https://t.co/ebGvehQhcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I  went from not jaywalking in Illinois, to finding my very own private place to urinate on Sunset BLVD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bud_cann @borntoraisehogs James woods would sit down and shut up, he might not be an unemployed actor. He’s not un… https://t.co/pJHD0EEMDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #IF #IF #IF #IF #IF #IF #IF That’s all you ever say, which means you have no freaking clue. Stop t… https://t.co/v2fFhwZYrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@undisputedmeg @Marcel_B_WWE @FabianAichner Ummm..... https://t.co/INRFUeTgVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fajardonews That is true. My love for horses for becoming a true fan of the music Group Bronco from Monterrey Nuev… https://t.co/WCIU0Png0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is going to be a long post. For the short version, just watch the video with sound. We could not be more proud… https://t.co/XqejZi1gOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wastingtime222 Sorry that you suffer as such.  I was a worse case sufferer for 25 years, 4 xs in psych wards, and… https://t.co/vi4dR9t82g]]></document><document><![CDATA[The HIV breakthrough not trending, but  it’s not a surprise big pharmas tryna prevent all this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zqtk_94 @alexmathis I got offers bro in case that’s what your asking, 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve literally been talking about pizza numbers and colors all night like toddlers are so cute 😭 how do you know orange already 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[It makes zero marketing sense for NASCAR’s premier race to be the first of the season]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holotech Fuel Chips are second to none!!  Saving up to 65% on fuel while cleaning our environment ⚡💥⚛🌏🌌… https://t.co/UVk4D1uds0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jobs requiring a lot of training are growing and those requiring none at all doing likewise.  The good quality work… https://t.co/Z8oqZDSOtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This all started with the SECREAT meeting of FDR AND SAUDI'S TO FORM THE STATE OF ISRAEL EISNHOWSER WARNED you of t… https://t.co/1JJYy4WS2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don't understand why people are treating the #learntocode thing as an insult. If anything thinking that it… https://t.co/qfDbcqLejz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goodtweet_man Liberals only support democracy when they get the result they like, marriage amendments only failed… https://t.co/j8EKqgc1xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been awhile since I went to Laguna. For awhile I felt like I’d accumulated too many memories there. It was nic… https://t.co/53Y4hWThwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMR_NASCAR @derek9kraus @HailieDeegan @brittneyz52 https://t.co/OBUmTPxHUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjaimesb @LMOTTAD si todo el país se quedo sin luz dudo que lo puedan restablecer en 3 horas ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slacorp @CityofTacoma @sonimtechps @sonimtech @MotoSolutions No transparency for the public’s right to know ? @USATODAY @seattletimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[played wind waker all night instead of studying for tomorrow’s test, let’s see how it pans out]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thanks to YouTube's algorithm stuff, I fell down the rabbit hole of watching other great honorary Oscar moments… https://t.co/OdMB2U05hR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cstross Commodore Vic-20 was my first computer supporting colors. A Toshiba laptop was my first all in one unit wi… https://t.co/w0g7bVZM3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[This photo from this past summer in Boston totally captures the spirit of my partner in crime.   She makes me a bet… https://t.co/WobCzesNcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XXXChelseaMarie @EliteTSCams OBAMA CARE IS FREE AND MEDICARE IS GOING TO BE FREE TO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews So you're saying a fake interview. I'll pass...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paintwiththrea2 That is super disappointing to hear. I was hoping it would be good. 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Advil @kaynat_nasar The key thing is "per bathroom". How many bathrooms dies she have?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teamwork: Wardrobe malfunction. @DavidWMTW has two different suit pieces on. Black or Navy @CristinaWMTW ? https://t.co/XZxkXjNcUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@izzatshbeeb This was basically propaganda dude. That’s a real problem  The left has been constructing a dangerous… https://t.co/mZXoUjWnT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upcoming possible spoilers for Scythe: The Rise of Fenris. Don’t look at the photo I post next if you don’t want to… https://t.co/d2Njw2ySGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[lemme pack my bags and move to atlanta..cuz virginia boys are hideous as fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[let me gone file my taxes so i can be feeling like y'all 😭@_caramelcutiee_ 🕺🏾🕺🏾🤳🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely love the feeling of being in a room filled up with intelligent, creative, passionate, powerful, inters… https://t.co/e9bjtoahCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro you straight shouldered a guy in the temple. What did you think was gonnabappen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IowaGma1 @Mango_Stitches @updatewithinfo @RealSaavedra @benshapiro OK, stop right there. What  has Trump shown tha… https://t.co/7CyhxTFgPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gladove Gracias Gladys! Todavía no se en qué va a consistir mi participación pero igualmente estoy entusiasmado.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all just putting “unpopular opinion” in front of fucking everything now huh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing one of my sons a happy birthday @Daviddileo14 enjoy the day. #Feelin22]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was past 11pm and I went out for a late dinner pickup, threw on shuffle and glow came on. The night was/is grey,… https://t.co/LvEbzbDZU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Eugene: moderate rain, 34°F 74% humidity, wind 14mph, pressure 1015mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awsten Every time I look at your tweets my eyes hurt in the greatest way possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone tries to tell you they’re “watching they’re macros”, punch them squarely in the face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loveeeeee Valentine’s Day. Pink and red everything and people are happy and nice to each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeberk86 @JTansey90 @sportsdoctormd Well, maybe he changed his mind. It happens. And I think he got a really good player in the end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryDunleavy I shouldn't feel such contempt for other humans, but I kinda despise anyone who takes this demagogui… https://t.co/nQhrnElujf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanPBali @ShepMornings Wait, is this your show now? I assumed you were guest hosting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4JoshReed I am up with ya even changed the avatar ready to see you break the news]]></document><document><![CDATA[comedy right? The Mysterious Animal: | 26 Texts You Need To See Before You Die omg I dyed.... https://t.co/zOw1FkIVex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StatsGuyDaniel Pats Bout To Turn Him Into A Slot Receiver https://t.co/ME49EjnKKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckMcNeely1 Happy Birthday General Yeager. Would be Awesome to see You be here when You are 120 :) @GenChuckYeager]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewYangVFA will drop out within 2 months!  The dems already have too many radical candidates.  If @JoeBiden doe… https://t.co/rGFkcnxReC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sgt_Avila_USMC Damn I sure looked different back in the day 😂thank you Sergeant Avila]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @VP @WhiteHouse @TheJusticeDept @usedgov No need for conservatives to put up with this sh*t anywhe… https://t.co/TglrXDaME2]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you will never have any of this. You showed yourself for what you are,  disloyal, a cheater, a liar, a scammer… https://t.co/DO9mMZQ2PN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Principal Brown! It’s a great day for #MarlinNation and #HiramClarkeHigh! @SouthArea_HISD]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump should grant Political asylum to Venezuelans fleeing Maduro. Asylum is for Political not economic reasons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lego land was awesome!!!!!!!! @ Legoland Discovery Center https://t.co/uXI24BpjXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenSasse you were one of the Nays on S 47. Either in a nutshell or in long form, what about this bill made you vote against it? Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por eso valora cada instante de tu vida. Disfruta del éxito. Pero sobretodo. Aprende de tus errores. Feliz sábado.… https://t.co/mlSQsFOtEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@connectingSW Covering Georgia football and basketball games, practices and recruiting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acceptable use of Peeps: explode in microwave. Acceptable use of Peeps Cereal: pour milk on it, eat, like a real fo… https://t.co/E9SIAeEU5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never know what someone is going through. Life can hit you hard, always be cautious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yapimamba9 Molson &amp; Bergevin are buddies .. haven't you heard?.. lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch break (@ Calzone &amp; Macaroni Co. in Vernon Hills, IL) https://t.co/8wLgUIavtk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCKatie This is how clouded they are. To even think any of what was said today was viewed as credible is laughabl… https://t.co/7S9EOcdtqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prepping for #GivingHeartsDay2019 with some @HUMANITIESND #poetry by Billy Collins. With line reciters like me and… https://t.co/fF26GXt6Oi]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏆 District Champions! Congratulations @GHAthleticDept Bobcats on the huge come-from-behind win! What a finish!!!… https://t.co/AwZI0blPPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing makes me wanna go to work til 1am on a Sunday like gale force winds, grey skies, rain and a headache.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck Jerry Falwell Junior little bitch, shut your ass up you fucking moron!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daddy, it's not Saturday? 💯 baby girl 🐶🐾 @ Irvine, California https://t.co/NaKMYOcYxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acnewsitics @TucsonBlonde It looks like an armadillo: a hard, protective shell against marauding reality of truth and beauty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitchyTeam One might wonder why Jussie Smollett sought out a high priced defense attorney if he is a victim of an… https://t.co/0VvxqTy3v9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BShep712 @EdBouchette The #Dolphins didn't win the #SuperBowl with their version of the killers B's: Baumhower, Bu… https://t.co/chVbAeDVUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lowe’s 502 Jacksonville on Old St. Augustine road has beautiful color and is ready for spring.@Lowes https://t.co/EBlPWLBTha]]></document><document><![CDATA[That new 🔥🔥🔥 from @vapetasia  Killer Kustard Blueberry!!!  Coming soon to https://t.co/QXoqyB04sB  @vapetasiaejuice… https://t.co/cZFQ1sT5TI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottwblack @PelicansNBA @AntDavis23 @Lakers No, it’s because Gayle Benson wants to win now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherNation Yeah somebody should tell him the  team he plays for has the highest payroll in the National League.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dunkindonuts why do u guys always hire cubans or Hispanics to make coffee or even work for u. Cuz honestly they su… https://t.co/Mz0aws7I3B]]></document></documents></author>