<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@edgarramirez25 Do you think she’s able to verify something impartially?  For me  she’s just a dangerous clown for… https://t.co/DzG7gtTwCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@remickisboring Yeah @OfAllysonAndMen already got tickets.  Not sure where we're at but I'll ask]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliemason your roundtable is really good. If there were more of this on cable news, cable news wouldn't suck ass so bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a haircut this morning and they had Live w/ Kelly Ripa n Ryan Seacrest on the tv next to the chair I was in.  W… https://t.co/DijIoa8Wv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[trump's canceled Salt 2 SO PUTIN CAN AIM MISSILES AT EUROPE  NOW ATTEMPTS TO LET MADMAN KIM POINT MISSILES AT USA… https://t.co/SRSzjJ6VQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday funday when oh snap is on. #deanshtx #dreds07ish #Houston #rodeo @ Dean's Downtown https://t.co/ZY54pnF7Kr]]></document><document><![CDATA[y'all need to listen to @BettyWho's new album. my girl has outdone herself yet AGAIN and released her best album to… https://t.co/udiOPxGSJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dreadful_damsel I’ve been to Caribana  a couple of times and love whiling out, and have lots of fun.  I’ve got fri… https://t.co/2mIMPDdBhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@genesis_news @genesisfan @BritishProg @progarchives @ProgMagazineUK @SquonkplGenesis @WorldofGenesis https://t.co/hlGImiCaqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun Show! Great experience to work on Penn &amp; Teller. @ Penn &amp; Teller Theater https://t.co/Ft6JKJzs5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billpeduto Asking POTUS to allow 5k illegals to reside in Pittsburgh...you have an odd definition of what "funny"… https://t.co/hmiXFxze3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StockTwits ISRG is a red flag. Quality stock and industry but over-valued with 10-11% steady growth. Run up in 201… https://t.co/CXdfzDtpYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mario_Sanchez1 Así es el negro , no ser el de la presión y da más , es su mejor fútbol , que el no sea el que nos… https://t.co/83m5s2JnJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark your calendars as We continue to contend for revival in our region. We invite you and your family, ministries… https://t.co/yZIyMKsguJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronSuplizio Kanye first 3, First 3 TI , First 4 Rick Ross, The Hov 00’s catalog, first two Ghostface, Clipse, fi… https://t.co/qHkWv5tayk]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of sudden @GOP has a problem with executive orders and a national emergency declaration, bth common practices u… https://t.co/NeS9A2IypX]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you wonder why politicians are hated approval rating of 18%?" Children in cages, ripping them away from their p… https://t.co/fFtb6WihR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally agree. Your reputation is your most valuable asset. Kuch dinged his up for no good reason and this half-mea… https://t.co/1lXrTZMExg]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Keeping them honest”  Anderson Cooper &amp; CNN claims against Trump.  Just who, who is really dishonest?  CNN !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TennesseeDonkey Right! They wouldn't even notice it because of the hair. Especially here in S.A., a.k.a. Northern Mexico. 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[El retraso de aportaciones que el Gobierno del Estado @KIKOVEGA_ adeuda a la Universidad Autónoma de Baja Californi… https://t.co/gRb56TMTbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[26 Reps on 225 bench today 👀⚔️😤 #DontBlink I’m coming for everything #ah @DRRJuCo @GridironRR @Shastaknightsfb @DirtyShasta]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tell ya. TheseDreamers have the weirdest Dreams. Seems they always involve   ( you know AOC) like, Murder,Rape, V… https://t.co/ZGjVXqBaWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@englemanmike1 @Joanie513 No one does care excerpt for the one lowlife numnut that sought her out for an opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol Circling the cup blocked me. Guess they don't like being wrong. They are in the wrong profession. #SJSharks #CirclingTheCup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trump_jackass @realDonaldTrump Especially with a Diet Coke! It is what is for breakfast...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did your chowder get forgotten? God would have provided an extra bowl... #justsayin  #FVCLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshmorrocco Been saying this the whole season, def one of the worst players in college basketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[This information is not taught in our schools so children of color do not know these facts. Jax Book Fest… https://t.co/T1NkN8poxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all eyes on ”Hidden Scroll” @GulfstreamPark @TVG today, awaiting his next move with baited breath, I am declar… https://t.co/52wwozRmBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CristobalJAlex @JeronimoSaldana @laloalcaraz Mi amor @CheetahBronze, were going to take the N train one day... ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[The boys are back @ The Penguin Piano Bar And Nightclub https://t.co/kPe21neR79]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s a black persons favorite sport? 🤔 Basketball 🏀, because we can run🏃🏿, shoot, and steal. 😂 Happy Black History Month 🙏🏽😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Davidthagnome @TeaPainUSA You know why he signed the covers, don't you?  He wants people to exhibit them, but, if… https://t.co/ep5KCyKuMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vicky4Trump @Jali_Cat @SaraCarterDC @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity 😳/ unbelievable coming from somebody who wants t… https://t.co/oYganAFzvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so funny how judgmental people who have never worked in the service industry are of those who work in the industry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think you forgot about Harold  Washington in this article @CNN : No matter who wins the runoff election, Chicago… https://t.co/qgfACE03NY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @JMaccabbee Post Birth Abortion? That’s a kinder way of saying newborn baby murdered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Don_ONEz Also, are they smart? We should bring them to the next escape room]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW REMEMBER HALL COUNTY NEBRASKA CHATHLIC LEADERSHIP. YOU SHOULD UNDERSTAND. I DO LEGALLY OWN THIS LAND TRUTH AND… https://t.co/KZkZUYBJ3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan Peele’s ‘Candyman’ Finds Its Star (EXCLUSIVE) https://t.co/vcl19YfGF6 via @variety]]></document><document><![CDATA[Focused on first mile speed today. 8:05 on the first mile this morning, and then took it easier on the 2nd mile. Fe… https://t.co/250CQxqTKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[When no one in a store cares about service, use Twitter.   Find the Twitter address of the national headquarters.   It works.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatbitchroxxi @_fckinfearless Never too early for mimosas! If y’all like them with a little kick add a little bit… https://t.co/ZvcWIiZLtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking in al show @TheMindreader completamente en español en las Vegas]]></document><document><![CDATA[ Gold On the Ceiling  The Black Keys on Spotify Red Hot Chili Peppers Artist Radio at 4:30 am Tuesday February 26… https://t.co/E1bfYlTMzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pease54Austin @kaylastafford8 Why am I no where near someone in this pic 😂 when we were together 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am not surprised that they are economically struggling once again, but I didn't expect it to happen so soon, Ch… https://t.co/qAJgF1EBZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicahotter1 She is most definitely a very beautiful woman! I definitely love her assets! She is most definitely… https://t.co/0uRQe6fdA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will never take for granted the fact that I got Steph’s autograph right before this game, then he does this, defini… https://t.co/ETIdGqpUaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[He will give you His strength and courage so that nothing will put you down or keep you down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/uNSmQSCURf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_S_Alexander @UMich Great work, Amanda. If you've been involved in the discussions at all, has any one from… https://t.co/jLMMQD0Www]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why go to the concert when I can see it from every angle through all of your Snapchat stories?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNLosAngeles @VeniceMase @LAIreland @KamBrothers They are done. This team has no fire. They are horrible on defense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kow89 Say you’re welcome! Now the kids have a DB coach that can spell football!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lopezobrador_ ya se ve que no tienes ni idea de gobernar, no sé quién es más PENDEJO??? tú o todos los que NO ven… https://t.co/GtnDKVgD35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams Juan here’s an idea, let’s all give all our assets to the government. Then Alexandria can distribu… https://t.co/wzIcoBlI28]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinPrepAD @photog24 @melrosemomof3 @HumboldtBroncos @AustinPrep @AustinPrepGHoc @MassHSHockey @BostonHeraldHS… https://t.co/UrjG4CzAOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeSherman @IlhanMN If the dems are smart they would force them out as a 3rd party]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robenfarzad @eroston @BradWieners she sure schooled those children. shame on them! teach them to take her million… https://t.co/s8OL68JnpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3x_a_Charm_ yes , that day too , them hoes better give me that day off , i put my request in that same day you told me what day it is 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeonKrauze @SECTUR_mx De pésimo gusto utilizar imagen de Morena en este tipo de promocional. Solo que efectivament… https://t.co/cXrSOy2YiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turbocheetoh @NBCNews Maybe he doesn't think Steele's work should have been admissible, but he certainly can't cla… https://t.co/wE0gPXYB7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm really excited to say that since I'm done with WrestleMania 33 I can finally use KO's face of America gimmick! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexthechick @GregStohr @maggieNYT I would have thought the incorporation question would be non-controversial w.r.… https://t.co/qsVJtsus0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 AM in Hamtramck can only mean one thing... #PaczkiDay2019 🇵🇱🇵🇱🇵🇱 https://t.co/1vkMUK5T86]]></document><document><![CDATA[22 mountain lion attacks on people in CO since 1990. That number is much higher than I would’ve guessed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickFondacaro @CNN @brianstelter https://t.co/e8rjg9wOIs   Hi $NickF + $BrianS  Have a favor to ask.    -Steve… https://t.co/W0limf1TvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would not give up this barber, nezzzzty, for the world 🌏🌐🌎🎫🌍🎻 @ Bebo and Willy Barbershop https://t.co/zMY5Xlt2kS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shangmortal @NicolaSturgeon will you ask your government to correct this fallacy to ensure people aren’t encourage… https://t.co/ORkcNvTBOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBILasVegas @FBI @GOP @SenateGOP @thehill @RepAdamSchiff @FoxNews @CNN @MSNBC @washingtonpost @WSJ @AP… https://t.co/zAEivdM7AL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooooo #Omaha friends! Have you ever heard of a better combination of things😍  Join me and @karissajo85 for an even… https://t.co/vxLgEdeT33]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamKeneinan @Lead1225 I disagree. It's not the amount of education, a little or a lot  that brings on or turns off pride.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NOLAnews Yes. It’s a Hallmark holiday. I should love and show my spouse everyday that I love her. Florist jack up… https://t.co/X6SKRjwrBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TC_Woods @KimStrassel @GOPLeader @RepAdamSchiff https://t.co/sRmb1OJDel]]></document><document><![CDATA[AB is wack as fuck honestly,  like I can’t believe one of my favorite players is such a diva. Big Ben has more resp… https://t.co/rZCusJ3a2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aafstallions what’s a guy got to do for a jersey of his new favorite team?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamianCC94 Si se usó, pero como casco cefálico xd https://t.co/Rno9HSXGXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Etch_a_Fletch I wasn’t promoting violence homeboy. It’s the truth online these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellydrivesfast It was so odd. It was like two apartment units.  @hgtv @HouseHuntersUSA @CastleHouseJT… https://t.co/P5Y3WXbUgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay seriously?!?! Finn makes his first debut since winning the IC Title and this crowd seems so freaking dead! Thi… https://t.co/Bza6QyNUC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[C- people may dog on the government but they help people like me get by.  People may dog on being kind but I am mee… https://t.co/QrrnxhVB1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bucket of evidence that anti-women structures and norms are core features of the systems that organise global hea… https://t.co/rxlyY5bqtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Why was it even debated and then watered down and removing miss Minnesota from being mentioned by name?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DukeEdenfield @JoyceWhiteVance @realDonaldTrump Did you watch what I watched last evening?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arpellegrino @NoraCrowley Resigned to accept my third place trophy this week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 3 days, your favorite day time pool party returns! @EncoreBeachClub #EBC2019 ☀️ You don't want to miss out on th… https://t.co/ScthPbtEjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanBaker13 somebody shorted Tesla. The short investors had demonstrated an interest in making Elon Musk crazed or… https://t.co/UmpKrjL62i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brian_GSharbin I think we can all agree on that. Good contracts were offered and they were declined because of the… https://t.co/asUjowZt0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before going to sleep Saturday night - move the clocks ahead an hour. https://t.co/Kep5cMADde]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JHerd6 @wendyp4545 @bedevilme666 @Serremmy @barbmic @jonz970 @rdrhwke @CDOV123 @RodHillis1 @rratkinson @clovis1931… https://t.co/NE7ONdse4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Answer: Nope. Reason: Because he was Jonathan, son of King Saul of the Hebrews, best friend to King David. Dude was… https://t.co/gO1UiVhvWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump protect American from who other Americans?]]></document><document><![CDATA[this why this is my best friend.. you can’t surround yourself with mediocre and expect to get better💯 surround your… https://t.co/CEOaapxqCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ottawapoet #canadianpoet #misfitpoet #ottawaartist #canadianartist #mentalhealth #recovery #anthonygorman… https://t.co/EAueS6Psot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Week 3, 2015  https://t.co/SbAXtkAQ0D  #BroncosCountry #Broncos #broncosfanforlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loudmouthjulia You would love @yiciai podcast. It’s literally two dudes talking about movies, lots of bad movies..… https://t.co/2PThGo7TVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I made a huge fucking mistake and finally watched Mother! for the first time tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@divinity_god @Fuacata66 @williamlegate Nice sentiment but that video is just a bunch of random photos w/ crappy mu… https://t.co/E5g4xVKc0H]]></document></documents></author>