<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday! May today be as productive as your best day this week.  And don’t forget to do a little dance as you… https://t.co/3I1aeWGv63]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnieBowers47 @NicolesChoice1 @TMNTBox @DwilightF66 Thanks 🙏 @JohnBowers47 thanks for everything @NicolesChoice1… https://t.co/sZKKPjLfVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElGiganteDiablo @Scream_Factory Don't you have an Xbox one? It's a blue ray]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrookCarper get your ass to DFW so we can go get margs for national margarita day when I get off at 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cue19 we are 3d printing pancakes in my booth. Want to help me design what we are printing? Download the pancake p… https://t.co/qmd1ifc55f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanKinder I can’t wait to see you tomorrow night in Michigan! What’s a girl gotta to for a meet and greet?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlenRoberts3012 My dear friend and great example of Home Depot’s values.  Happy to have share part of the journey with you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I laughed way too hard at this y’all!!!😂😂😂 #MomoChallenge #eatasandwich #shouldnttalksmack https://t.co/uO11d9ZKNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[death. the word scares us even if we don’t acknowledge it. recently I’ve come to find that many people don’t know h… https://t.co/pHwqKD0txw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that SHO and YOH went to support Yano at his curry release party!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayXgomez @tacobell I have the same problem. Every single time and it always takes FOREVER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AylaBrown @JacksonAndAyla @Country1025WKLB I'm Going Try To See A Show Or Two This Summer...!!!! 🎶🎶😀🎶🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beth2_k3a @ShawnG927 You mean she didn’t use it to start that fast train?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karolyncorbeil @Roogoogle @mattnafe @BoyanVAntonov @Kitkait08 Definitely!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesfox718 @BillOReilly Where the patriots love President Trump and I do believe there is an emergency at the border]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooo I was so fat in 2015 lmaoooo who let me wear that crop top in public😂😂😭😭 vs now https://t.co/BBehQ5TeeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida es muy sabia y jamás se equivoca cuando te hiere y te obliga a ser fuerte...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Word. #DST #DaylightSavingsTime #JeffDaniels #Looper https://t.co/g0evXZlYTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IDontReallyKara You little muffins! Happy anniversary bb! You deserve such light and joy — so happy you have a man who brings you both ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kellie2727Paula @Nicki030618 @Tony85956346 @RonSmit43799983 @jhane415 @duckusa @ifccproject @KimYenNguyen68… https://t.co/1wPCm24AN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 5 Months old! Growing SO fast! #FamilyFirst #BabyClara #BlakeLadies #MyWhy @ Back Cove, Portland, Maine https://t.co/O1n9SsXEPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lolol yeah imma walk into an accredited grad school with my community college associates degree and see how far tha… https://t.co/xIbFszVX9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj It is foolish to choose a favorite...They all have almost 2 years to eliminate themselves with what they d… https://t.co/TjBjhoDO2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravelLeisure Tried to arrange a trip to coincide with this amazing event but just didn't happen. Going in May instead!]]></document><document><![CDATA[among the people. This opening toward gentiles appears very clearly in the final order given by Jesus to the discip… https://t.co/Ug4uWWJoqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherryontopp Nahi aayega sir, aapka time aa gaya , chup chaap nikal lo warna bohot joote padenge #SiddhuThrownOut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok why am I still hurt over a POS who showed zero effort. WHY DO I LIKE THE SHITTY GUYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[That says so much about her. She should regret this. Not sportsman like.#BigBrotherCelebrity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Pam for your friendship, continuous guidance and ever lasting support. #northwestmaesp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chortletown Please someone step up... he's grieving. He'll heal n make a fabulous family member. Just needs some h… https://t.co/2udKgMj7pL]]></document><document><![CDATA[So all of March I’m only drinking two times and I can’t have any cheat meals 🙂 let’s see how this goes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why are you so obsessed with Hillary?  Don’t you need to deal with all the accusations you face?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!  97% in favor of our duly elected @POTUS plan for the wall!  It looks like #Patriots have spoken!… https://t.co/irUxpjqLyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My junior year turned me into an indie dyke. Not a bad thing tho. I think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LIY1800MinuteChallenge @LivingInYellow @9round #9RoundFamily #StrongerIn30 https://t.co/gyR7rFQguQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i told my mom im going out of town next week and she’s like “who let you go” but when i asked to go to edc IN LAS V… https://t.co/vMawtZTw4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to restock your spring wardrobe? 10 cool #Dallas  boutique. #DallasShopping https://t.co/RczJuYk90I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX I have no clue! LOL! Robin Thicke said Jamie Foxx can change his voice - True. But I didn't know J… https://t.co/4pisynXkZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Illinois ranked among the worst states in the nation for babies according to a new report.  READ MORE --&gt;… https://t.co/YVgDHD6BMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just wanna know who hurt @conkeso_ she’s the biggest blessing y’all are missing out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leidacat @akaD3V It was probably because he went past 1:45, which is effex’ usual cutoff time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@durwoodg @ProudResister True. But we do I need #police officers but it's some not all of the police that are fire happy with their #weapon]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is still time to learn that #pączki is plural.  I don’t know about you but I can’t eat just ONE #pączek.… https://t.co/AZJoavPls0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t really know much how Pokémon but I could tell he was passionate about it. He later asked me what my name wa… https://t.co/LG29G3legr]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pictures never do the moon justice! It really is beautiful this morning 😍 Happy Tuesday @ Dayton, Ohio https://t.co/NhEDqDnZ3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessieJaneDuff They hate Trump so much that they celebrate him not getting a deal with a dictator who could nuke u… https://t.co/E0W8IvxuxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@streetvetuk Aren't they large! Beautiful dogs I am sure the owner care and love them immensely. Blessings]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been trying to fucking vote this woman out since I was 18. Why did Barbara retire and not her?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Magic of Math and Science! Using observations to dive deep into science concepts with Ray Lesniewski #T3IC https://t.co/8yi5lZQQz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s just another day in paradise for my horse and me, courtesy of partridgekenneth  #peaceofmind… https://t.co/UUSIhiYG8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to bring up old things.. then you will receive the reaction the old me would of have 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thanks to @DexterSchools, @TimmisChris, @sharrarm, @mrskernsclass @ryanbruderk2,  @CraigMcCalla24, and teac… https://t.co/kNzwfBqyUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello San Diego! Love all your amazing live music establishments!🎼💕 https://t.co/1fjdNySm5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessieWare you are adored. Take your time and we are here whenever you are ready! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Gov. Greg Abbott Clinches Second Term As GOP Wins Closest Statewide Races In 20 Years https://t.co/4eaDMJv8cp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying for God’s Love to ignite the hearts and minds of those debating and voting today. There is no more room for… https://t.co/XJY7wFMCEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyFriday vibes! Here’s to a great woman entrepreneur @karagoldin @hint #HappyInternationalWomensDay2019 https://t.co/gd6v1vVWO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Never. She is Banned. We cannot trust her intentions to return.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I missed the ending of @TheGoodWife_CBS  rerun cuz I'm just now finding out about it! To watch you on… https://t.co/BXbwNN1cB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just discovered @rockabyebaby and I can’t be thankful enough for them being in my life now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you consider things like the stars, our affairs don't seem to matter very much, do they? ~Virginia Woolf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry, @GMcKinney2 I have been a dismal failure on my book-a-day challenge..I think this is day 4: no explanations,… https://t.co/pMth86ERA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to be naive but it still shocks me when people are so apathetic and cruel towards others like .. you’re literal… https://t.co/vFmmGVkOoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[ISIS wife is not a citizen she is an enemy to the U.S. she aided in killing U.S. soldiers she called for U.S. citiz… https://t.co/mOf3QuPFQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome oven fried catfish and Brussels sprouts with my last @EagleParkBeer Big BOTM  #singlelife #beerthirty… https://t.co/MsIBoVn9Ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took pictures of the cutest little kiddo today! Can’t believe Jaxson is 9 months old now! #knphotography… https://t.co/GZeYdBGmBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you could only choose two from the Trump administration, mob, inner circle and or family to go to prison for the… https://t.co/PYr6MIihDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Follett Corporation team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/4Zt5XGBwh3 #CustomerService #Clarlon, PA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Trump’s EPA...” Perhaps someone should explain to @POTUS that he won’t get any ketchup on his omelette/hamburger i… https://t.co/twql8gDQzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My poor snowman got completely buried!! The snow is now as high as the mailbox! #02067 ❄️⛄️ https://t.co/1OVvKdAHvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trucker_squigz @nationwide88 @AxaltaRacing Glad you made it safely!! Hope you have a great weekend!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids made mini projects to share science content from our unit. There were comics, models, posters, a website, revi… https://t.co/CYSA2xMkOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a pleasure it was to meet Rep. Lucy McBath (GA-6)! Congresswoman, thank you for all that you’re doing to advan… https://t.co/AmkojqcbY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any reason #BenCarson can't leave now? HUD Secretary Ben Carson says he intends to leave his post at the end of Pre… https://t.co/WTClRyZH6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[**HAPPY #TBT** Check out party pics from 2011.  Club Bounce is open once a month, most of the time it is the first… https://t.co/iPbPQoYJNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet I would compliment those eyes and ask if he wanted gravy on his turkey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ferbeltran @NegroMalaSuerte Yo también quiero saber 👀 yo por eso ya no subo nada jajajajajajajajaja Ahora nos dices @NegroMalaSuerte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traciemac_Bmore The idea that it is ok for the leader of America to say things like this is wrong.  It is time to… https://t.co/2e7tmq74ZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@standfortruth10 @kritter1963 Heartless, when it comes to our babies in US, but bring in illegals!  Can yassyF’d up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working until 1900hrs. (@ BlueCross BlueShield of WNY - @bcbswny in Buffalo, NY) https://t.co/mSU9VB86KC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moes Cantina in Wrigley tonight.  Hmu for bottle service. V5 baby. https://t.co/OmvmHtdOsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[North End Rows by Thrive Home Builders in Stapleton https://t.co/EdRUmnc4DG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidanRGallagher He deserves so much better no hate ❤️ WE LOVE YOU AIDAN❤️ https://t.co/bGTv7QY4AN]]></document><document><![CDATA[General Strong🐱💪 #waitingfortreats #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy #gingercats #pumpkinspicekitty… https://t.co/ziwZC5dK3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TammyShoemake18 @Zach_McGowan @DisneyStudios @MarvelStudios @Marvel @WaltDisneyCo @MCU_Tweets @ShuDonner @Kevfeige… https://t.co/HKGGFrAbCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I gotta come home and fold clothes 😒 not my favorite part of the day. But I want the house to be clean when he… https://t.co/sgLaFaKTIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was in this patients room and she was like that’s my darling from 1952 and pointed to her husband &amp; now I’m crying that’s goals 😭♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is the one  I was born in a different world  My age is so much fun  I like to see how many of you are going… https://t.co/ERWoNMgNW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quigonsmith Their relationship is probably the most underrated part of TLJ. I love how they challenge each other.… https://t.co/XUufH16kVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yeah, part of why I’m poking is cuz I feel old AF compared to this random dude that’s AAAing like all the songs, on fuckin expert. ^^;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gnarfolk y’all shouldn’t need to lift the seat up anyway the hole is big enough 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up with “Dani California” by the Red Hot Chili Peppers stuck in my head. It must be a full moon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Professor Carole J. Petersen (U. Of Hawaii) calls for domestic discourse on reproductive rights to consider incorpo… https://t.co/tLxlWDX88q]]></document><document><![CDATA[53 Gorgeous Nature Photos to Inspire Happiness https://t.co/5mIcD1gBPB via @NatGeoTravel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overthinking kills good things, good plans, good selfestim, good opportunities, good relationships... you don’t wan… https://t.co/njUxsFzhwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYDailyNews Unfortunate for him that it was caught on a phone. He’s a turd 💩]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔹🔷 ANDREA DEL BOCA 🔷🔹 #Actriz Internacional, con 49 años de Trayectoria y Grandes Éxitos en España, Italia, USA, Am… https://t.co/BBj5CGq6tp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the anxiousness and bad luck of Susan Mayer and the outrage and impatience of Lynette Scavo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrP_Principal My (Educator) friend and I had basketball and football😜 Played them like champs!! Must be an Ed thin… https://t.co/CFClHckqSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nut_history @Trafficmanmatt @janeleavy1 @RichSandomir @SportsCollector @JasonRileyWDRB @thorn_john @MarcCarig… https://t.co/1mxW10G5uc]]></document></documents></author>