<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WGR550 I can’t get my app or https://t.co/zlUqjatLGu to play is it not working?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am teaming up with other professionals and peers to help families impacted by addiction get answers, solutions, h… https://t.co/slwkskMxxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GagnonFrancois Est ce qui manque de confiance ou il as voulue être un bon coéquipier as Drouin, sachant que Drouin… https://t.co/rY4QnBh8D8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@superyayadize You really don't have to know much to know you don't want to be anywhere near them. AOC calling my c… https://t.co/sirPclzS9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching McCabe interviewed by Savannah McGuthrie. McGuthrie says “do you actually believe Trump was a threat to Am… https://t.co/icaXR3LQ9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they continue.... @Bakerjr24 with another offer from @HuskerFBNation ... #TeamFSP #FSPFamily #Huskers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @Melissa82225794 Maybe Big Cal won't be consumed by the Big Earthquake now so long predicted... rat… https://t.co/mhYpx054rL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@organicfanatic5 Ro was on hartmann for the hour, excited to see Bernie tonite]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, so here’s my weekly update - — @BattleBeaverC is the best company for controllers in the world 🌎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@t_Ebert17 @MuskieBaseball_ Hard work pays off! Congratulations, you’ve earned it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdussault77 @MattKalman @MikeFromWoburn @AlexReimer1 More like 14 yos weighing 100 to upwards of 250.  And to just… https://t.co/LG1bfBbPY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andyescalona Andrea , te ves preciosa , espectacular y súper sexy cada día en Hoy te amo 😍😘😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arreola_jas @danyellllej @xojazminneee @dreeasilva So when we leaving ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CM_SolarEnergy Do you know how much this hurts the ecology of the barren land under the solar panels?  Solar panel… https://t.co/moP0oSxpyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/JXSLV1kbvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treyradel @wilson_butch @jaketapper But it was Barry who said the debt was UnAmerican.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2747 Kelton Ave 2747 Kelton Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90064 https://t.co/88ldllSNwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Community Harvest Church in Germantown, OH https://t.co/xRzTWoF3Ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportsanimal @SportsMorning Bad defense  and I think a little coaching]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy toco cubrir evento, en un antro lleno de mujeres guapas bailando Reggaeton y otros ritmos de lo que le llaman "… https://t.co/xAyZ20dNyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayorNHL Oh no! That means somebody GOOD will replace him in the lineup!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I take so much pride in being ScumdogSlave I don’t think I’m ever getting another @ ever again 🥺🥺🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold on: Sebulba sabotaged Anakins podracer and it almost worked which could have very well killed him. Anakin grew… https://t.co/qDEv70wDRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see the boys in action on 4/13 and in the first game against SC. Surprise season 🤫]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happens when it rains in Cali #rain #calirain #cali #rain #socalstorm #sandiego https://t.co/WE7N9MlbEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This portrait that my classmate made gives me Southwest Vibes- (AZ,TX,N) on a 🥵 hot, sticky summer day ☀️ https://t.co/qcDozm4iLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Something is wrong With this woman https://t.co/1jFdB8rdJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lowered cars are really dumb, there’s no point and they don’t even look good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drboss202 I’ve never been a fan. He’s one of the best dunkers in history. That’s it! He brings nothing else to the… https://t.co/Lihrx7BeaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you text her "WYD" late night, you better have some good plans. Late night, date night with this Beauty, seein… https://t.co/ZEAQMFtakl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charris75375185 @JimCarrey Lock up Trump and Pence while you're at it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[another thought: Mueller has been working hand in glove with SDNY USA (remember raid on Michael Cohen's office?). E… https://t.co/DrKIMYrDU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donttrythis I’m totally into what You bild and watch from Seattle all the time. But I’m in your city now! #FANBEAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyRedDeer @weega52 @FOXSportsFL @FlaPanthers @NHLBruins @weega52 has had a helluva great 1st period so far. Now time to score!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @RealMelina Don't act like you care. She should've been back during the most important moments in wwe women's… https://t.co/MvQsyMtB64]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@joannagweiss highlights how cities across the US rely on fine/fee revenue to pay for basic functions. Research sh… https://t.co/nTom6QiXXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 year olds hit you with the most random encouragement. "You're doing a good job with that sandwich, daddy" #dadlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[This @washingtonpost piece on indies is great and also has a shoutout to my former boss the great @OliverDepp &amp;… https://t.co/gzvJDgPdVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1057FMTheFan @Bill_Michaels Bucks, bucks and more bucks. After years and years of frustrations, we’re finally gett… https://t.co/at7dhSzBUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/ZKCYQRGjR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[WWE is a politically correct mess. They forgot how to excite the fans. The announced WrestleMania matches made me y… https://t.co/znvdOwfq6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Olinecoacher @peterdaou @NRA Funny how the thread turned into a book promotion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the 16 GHS students who have placed into the state competition for National History Day!!  Just… https://t.co/uABwCHNKY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apartmentsitting while watching #IronkeepChronicles with DM @sixhitpoints and @HavanaRama @MostlyShit… https://t.co/XocHWOMNJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[La CAQ n'a qu'à poursuivre le travail du gouvernement Couillard au ministère de l'immigration, c'est-à-dire NE RIEN… https://t.co/zZHDoAyvR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[STRESS? Try this!  #reducestress #stress  #relax @ Buckhead Atlanta https://t.co/2GcD2UQl5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatBoysGood @fuzzybritches Last year when I was cranking the Friday night until 6, Saturday until 6 and Sunday 11… https://t.co/ct6ggTtNHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TnrRienbolt @tristanlcopsy Words cannot describe how much I miss them. I'd be down to get the boys together someti… https://t.co/aife1xevHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn’t killing a live human against the Hippocratic oath? Show me the doctor who’s heart is so black he’s willing to… https://t.co/pLWyFzhOhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRFGrening The surface at Big A is not a Cali one hope he’s fit or will be sucking air at 1/8th pole🤷‍♂️🏇🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mzzfederico @kirkcheney @darwinwoodka @JimPethokoukis It affects a lot more than advertising, including, but not l… https://t.co/lPZxtIeCSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#muses2019 #mardigras2019💜💚💛 #carnival2019 @ St Charles Parade Route https://t.co/xnn985x145]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean really Facebook &amp; Instagram... 🤦‍♂️ • @christuckerreal https://t.co/0rP4YfLHyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Maybe so, but not one of them circumvented the US Congress in order to spend billions of dollars for… https://t.co/NsI6V1j8DQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsDirectTV @netflix Haven't seen it. Won't for sure now, unless I want a nap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And right now this is current BIGGEST problem with the #RWBY fandom/community  Me: WHY??? how is this a good reason… https://t.co/eXVOSBxVTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mason just sent me the most messed up but funniest video I’ve ever seen]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things are just merry. #funniness #lol #smirk #funny https://t.co/1XCdpKxWc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @CarverMSCougars cheerleaders doing a great job again tonight! https://t.co/3IHQVGyyQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got all these downloaded to my PC and in my Apple Music library on my phone already 🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@webdevgeek .@richardsloss , sign is coming at you in Fairway.  It's sign war time.  @imfunnierthanya , KCK is not immune.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The good:  Hanoi, Vietnam could be a dud. But it could also be a momentum builder to something historic. None of us… https://t.co/3fvNZf96th]]></document><document><![CDATA[The three teams with fewest blown 10-point leads in losses all added to that stat tonight. #Pacers (led +10) now 35… https://t.co/vvZSsd2iXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danusiafrancis (it'll probably leak. And, you'll be mad you didn't just reveal it.  But...) If you think you can k… https://t.co/Jmgc6P8BIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NXSinsider @JClements51 @Repairable1 @DISupdates @NASCAR_Xfinity @BurgeysTikiHut Us guys worked very hard on the o… https://t.co/PQwTpEJrIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KidsThatFish @BHOAdventures @WILLSDAD25 @Lizardkingfish @1MonsterMission @OnTargetFishing @shannonc30… https://t.co/iIOb36BGI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this @Behance project: "Super Sábado Barcelona" https://t.co/j97p6EMXwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s cool driving directly by ESPN WWOS knowing the team is over there, but I have no desire to lean on a fence all… https://t.co/MdDE9vajLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nada peor q rodearse de gente con vibra negativa. Gracias Dios mio q tengo una vida, personalidad propia y una alta… https://t.co/0FfMdoN0gI]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fantastic finish. I love watching this over and over and to see each of the celebrations of players, the ben… https://t.co/tA273geXg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shell1935 @topthetater The boycoTTT was hard on our household. 🙏 it’s over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Huskerhuntshawn @RobertsAmor @kathyu13 I'm ready for spring/summer https://t.co/oc9gdyQ5wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing a little light reading...for my @ibcshawnee Wednesday night class. https://t.co/ZBmktgHqdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sknhcuk @HCGreenslade @RwandaInUK @markbrantley3 @drkmisaac @pmharriskn @skngov You'd love my Caribbean-Bahamas spy series. @Robert4787]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuck Mangione is the king of the hill when it comes to the flugelhorn. #NowPlaying Feels So Good by Chuck Mangione… https://t.co/uowrOjwhU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Predictable letdown on road against a very good opponent by UCF after bid-clinching wins. Knights got next to nothi… https://t.co/oeYIqUfDKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the girls basketball teams from Elmwood and Eastwood on tying for the Northern Buckeye Conference champ… https://t.co/l85XuO6SY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I introduce you to a restaurant and we break up, you better NEVERRR go there again.🙄🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BTS on set with @ronaldepps_ wearing @CarlosCamposNYC for 5elevenmag #ss2019 Issue  Shot by: @nickblumenthal  Groo… https://t.co/oTWxICND9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @CBSLA @PeterDaut @suzmarques @DanielleGersh @_JenniferKim @KandissCroneTV @KaraFinnstrom @lesleymarin… https://t.co/Mu8CsTNP1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lile_sosanna @JimmyNorman @RidgeOnSunday @ReginaDo @simoncoveney @SophyRidgeSky Yes, what this discussion certainly needs is pedantry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet Carlos “Earthquake” Ascanio, the first &amp; only Venezuelan player to played sepia baseball. @nlbmprez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisiousity @steve_shives Being the abusive situation I was in with a family member who gas lit me often, I see m… https://t.co/qwYErpA6UH]]></document><document><![CDATA[made it like half the quarter totally fine without my meds and with 1 WEEK left i slipped... depression is a ugly motherfucker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Hartford, CT? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/5LkdKHGqFq #SkilledTrade]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Week10Assignment #TradeOffs #WeAreCapable #SomosCapaz @ Dania Beach, Florida https://t.co/mTXLrYLWmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGAgirly @L1120Harold @GeanineC @Danie1607 @DaveSchreiber3 @DallasBrownin16 @jsGMan @raducom @jonz970… https://t.co/IfR36bByoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumansOfLate I generally agree with this quote. However, I do not particularly like the word "inferiors". | @jk_rowling @ziyatong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurrenSy_Spitta Let's get on Street Fighter II 🤘🏾🤙🏾 ⬇️↘️➡️ +✊🏾 https://t.co/MqzwAM4Ssd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing patience, being pragmatically hopeful, maintaining positivity, giving clear feedback...are key conditions t… https://t.co/FhfH9dMPGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you see the little bonus scene at the end of “Volver”?? I’ve always loved BTS video and wanted to find a way to… https://t.co/OSb9cToedu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Z_davis03 So we shouldn't compare ourselves to the best? I guess we should compare ourselves to mediocre teams. Wh… https://t.co/SlDzyqI0Au]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GDeLaurentiis I think you're showing too much boobage on Winner Cake All. It's a cooking show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JengaMaster22 @Jeanie45813886 @FLOTUS @ericbolling https://t.co/2nus9wEJ3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only watched Part One of #FindingNeverland and the truth in inescapable. Michael Jackson molested children.  And it… https://t.co/GEr8Idd1Nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please support @Bradleysfight by purchasing a #ForBrad Sunderland shirt. They are just £10/$10 and all proceeds go… https://t.co/q5Pgl4OvBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Penn &amp; Teller Theater - @riovegas in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/wgLV333jZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[U15 Boy's Midgets - Championship Bracket (G3) - @sbabball def. @MississaugaBall 60-57 #EBAThunder @exposurebball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anthony01851718 Just being Hals puppet which means no spending money. The 2 idiots]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big reminder: If you are still a confederate, you lost &amp; are a traitor.]]></document></documents></author>