<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Spending taxpayer money unnecessarily to build a wall that won't work while also ignoring needed immigration reform… https://t.co/I7omORPY71]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really invested in the #themaskedsinger &amp; hoping the monster is @TPAIN because ...awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh man. We had it good when he couldn’t read. 😂😂😂 Now he hacks the Netflix account and changes the password on me.… https://t.co/vPRUI8FMqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[More than 900 dead in Madagascar measles epidemic https://t.co/nPZzmG5loO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameOfThrones I am freaking out (or should I say geeking out). I cannot wait until #GameofThrones returns but I kn… https://t.co/M5VXzFMJgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to #lasvegas #Repost @janetjackson ・・・ I am so grateful for all the excitement about my new residency! We… https://t.co/YHbJScMjnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Servicio: ocupas traer tu bata blanca  Yo: ... 🔥 https://t.co/qJFOz9P0j7]]></document><document><![CDATA[No worse feeling than coming home every night and forgetting your mom won’t be there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidSpade’s IG story commentary on the bachelor last night had me howling laughing at 6am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trevor Noah Mocks Ivanka Trump On His Show https://t.co/CKHemTQX9T via @RJ Newsflash  He's wrong. If it's being giv… https://t.co/jRvwQj0efo]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t wait until next tax season bc we won’t owe anyone SHIT and we’re gonna have a shit ton of money]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr We will see. Seems like no democrats ever get indicted, only conservatives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checked in to the 2019 @NABJ Millennial Media Summit.  📍@ColumbiaJourn   #NABJMillennials #MillennialMedia19 https://t.co/D3fvAkT6zx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt #knottsberryfarm #characterdrawing #1986 #throwback #throwbackthursday @ Knott's Berry Farm https://t.co/sU8EWZpDuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xcalebungax Chick fil a sauce is overrated. BBQ sauce and Honey Mustard are two v important entities that need to… https://t.co/FVCwwJ2OSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kanouse2 I am @PhiBetaKappa theater with a masters in performing arts.  I was the @ABAesq rep of Cathulaw.  I was… https://t.co/ckKyn26G5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeyredPR Quieren ser las más santas, pero el tipo con quien se acuesta ha tenido más de 20 mujeres trepá en su bicho! 🗣😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been begging ryan to download fortnite and play with me...lol shouldn’t it be the other way around 😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump will sign border deal; but will declare emergency: https://t.co/jX2lDbR2cy -- Details on what to ex… https://t.co/tLEvTnRtZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyt804 @rkahne Sorry but this exact thing happened to my best friend and they did it the natural way. This is j… https://t.co/8V5kZJUgoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see me, I am here until 10:00. #liquor #liquorstore @ Wiser Choice Liquor Inc Dayton https://t.co/QwTamIABd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I'm just in the stall of the restroom and now the motion sensor light just turned off and at first I was al… https://t.co/agwdjW19g0]]></document><document><![CDATA[thousands of ppl go to emo night in la to hear incubus including @jpage and i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like the streets in Kingman: Bull Mountain Rd Calle del Sol Cactus Wren Lm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday and Congrats gymfoodfitness30 ! @ Elephant Bar Restaurant https://t.co/xdbz7kq9Q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@els_stuart @Maddwhy You paid $40 to get ordained? Pay your phone bill so I can keep sending memes please]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@maxandharvey is awesome. @maxandharvey is a nominee in the #ShortyAwards. Vote for @maxandharvey. Be like… https://t.co/VeiL53aM27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz @SenateDems Evil from the pits of hell https://t.co/MnZLC8Zetd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooooo, okay cole “that’s when we gonna do it forreal forreal”.. DREAMVILLE FEST https://t.co/FzwSBaJfWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time crunch is right! Lots of trial and error taking place right now.  But hey... you didn’t really catch my best s… https://t.co/AoUu8SV0wH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's here! My list of favourite things, winter 2018-19 edition. With highlights from London, Paris, Ottawa, Quebec… https://t.co/Zhcawcjt8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on out to see the workshop of GOING SOUTH, katyastanmusicaltheatre’s new musical that sheds light on North Car… https://t.co/emhwTiel5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well it’s Monday night at 2 am and i met my cry quota for the entire week because my brother just forced me to watch a star is born]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bridget McIlwee @SPFnOMT speaking on "A Dermatology Resident's Perspective on ACGME Osteopathic Recognition" at… https://t.co/qAl1drdlGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam....no words needed!!! #SamHeughan  #VanityFairOscarParty https://t.co/q6wewz2t3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to investigate him, Maxine Waters, pelosi, Schumer, we need to investigate all the senators and congressmen… https://t.co/Eln9M2d5rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[so much hilarity so little time. Little Funny Kitten Call Me https://t.co/G6WEyvtM4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helloimthomasl @FIFAWWC Considering going to the games then got sidetracked. Still a possibility?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today at the gym some lady said “I’m here because I just went through a breakup and I’m trying to look good so he w… https://t.co/mJhFtTIgzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dope and thank you but whoever was eating needs to close their gotdamn mouth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comme l’an dernier, nous sommes partantEs pour de nouvelles corvées, et même ouvrir la saison à la… https://t.co/NERVEAG3XV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly don’t know how I ever parallel parked without a backup camera]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to see #gloriasteinem speak! @ Castro Theatre https://t.co/Q41fgr1Dnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being fashionable at the fashion show with my girls 💁🏻‍♀️👠 @ Indian Hills Country Club https://t.co/UoLGxzE1kZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @StacieHigginsNC to post covers of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews. I’ll chall… https://t.co/DUPJUNcHg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Spiderman die or whatever he did in Infinity Wars still makes me cry...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmsathleticpage @CMSGoBlue Congratulations Cory!!!  Confident that you will do an amazing job! P.S. We miss you guys!! @aprildow2017]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you even go to college if you don’t  -think about dropping out 5 times a day -cry at least once a week -are thou… https://t.co/ePAS3GCMOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Try this booty burning 🔥workout that’s gonna have you crawling out of the gym!!! For every exercise do 4 reps and e… https://t.co/mT5aPGmLju]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jay Z and Beyoncé accept BRIT Award in front of Meghan Markle portrait  https://t.co/EwgBzwQ4eI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is not cute .. but aight go off parents or whoever recording this 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Real_Sassenach Mom slipped me some of the filet. https://t.co/4nfjujGXI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissMcEleneyK @Miss__Callahan check out Kathleen’s suggestion. She is an awesome K teacher to connect with!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_theheavenly Congrats new mommy, May more blessings rain down on you &amp; your family. 💓🤞🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiselleUgarte Because when I was growing up having self confidence was often viewed as being conceited. Nobody wan… https://t.co/C4K8SjQl9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pauldriscoll33 @weoncologists @ASCO Tweet at @DrChoueiri or @FAndreMD ! We may have room]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @StratOnLabour look who I ran into at our #OECTAAGM2019 Nice to see our former president Kim Kent continue to w… https://t.co/NhVJFVNrYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump @PressSec Donald Trump Tweet......Practice what you preached...   "Repubs must not all… https://t.co/HHQUZoGKhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latelateshow Out now! @HomeFreeGuys bring us a moody video for a cover of a wistful country classic ...… https://t.co/oYKJeGp0DQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OnThisDayInCountryMusic loved hearing #mamadontletyourbabiesgrowuptobecowboys. I met @MusicLoveWar (who by the way… https://t.co/OslyIbkbOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cofe6370 @MeeMichie @Naahledge @ms_chi_town_eb @12Chains @divateach37 @Imdatchick1985 @BIGJAMES_2 Hey fam TGIF!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished my 4th complete watch through of #FantasyHigh on @dropout, this time with @The_Murfler and… https://t.co/yLs08682P5]]></document><document><![CDATA[[twenty] 7th heaven🎈 || #ChrisLane #FSE #LaneLife #Pensacola #Savannah @ Saddle Bags Savannah https://t.co/SCXjiWCfHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EISD_Terrazas Definitely keep it moving! Tight transitions from independent reading, mini-lesson, collaboration, a… https://t.co/eIGmaEDmPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheApostle1776 @realDonaldTrump That was no defense. Blumenthal lies. Just correcting Trump exaggeration. And I sl… https://t.co/m0VVk9CSvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#naturallyshedope #hair #updo #twostrandtwist #braids #cornrows #braider #updostyles #elegant #hair #weddinghair… https://t.co/QHRPY8BZJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[***Scroll for more pictures!!!*** Happy Valentine's Day Everyone!!! You know what the BEST Valentine's Day gifts ar… https://t.co/8TezCOtiwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ultimate Man Cave is calling, and it’s your time to answer! Enter for a chance to win now. #DEVOUR #Sweepstakes https://t.co/UvvN0tlmae]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom calls me Chicken Pie cuz that’s all she ate while pregnant with me. And my skin is the same color as a prope… https://t.co/fvrevcJXox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2d7ba3001f664c9 @Serremmy @jonz970 @tagruber @BundyGP @RodHillis1 @Patti_Sc60 @MAGAgirly @AliceForkey1… https://t.co/rH4f6jUdVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheyyybutter @deartaylorbeth @kyna_westbury sooooo yeah see y’all there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vans challenge 😂😭 @Lifeasweknoit23 I guess it doesn’t always work https://t.co/9I5RAH80FE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden @CynthiaNixon Wow! A political person humble enough to accept and correct a mistake. I worry about the wa… https://t.co/kZud3SHvfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was over here crying cause I thought he said he wasn’t attractive to me anymore but it was his autocorrect that c… https://t.co/XkmNeOFSwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The award for best adventure documentary series goes to Rookie. https://t.co/vsrRExc8H1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pissboymcgee You’re legally required to call it the shag wagon if you buy it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayasesh @tpatt220 @pattyskim what would we do without y’all — we are SO lucky to have you ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Or PayPal because I’m really iffy with PayPal but if y’all would rather https://t.co/2AWVHnQMdc )]]></document><document><![CDATA[@texas_teacher68 @DeepStateExpose @merecatholicism 2 Timothy 3:16-17 New International Version (NIV) 16 All Scriptu… https://t.co/CFpIF4lOoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker @NicolleDWallace Smart to get out of WH. Trump has turned it into a hell hole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made a long term slave suck my cock tonight and then pulled his bussy apart and had my way with it via as many fingers as I could fit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGAindex @RyanAFournier Maybe Chuckie boy and his side kick Nancy should take down their wall and get rid of thei… https://t.co/jbX2b6XB49]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of March 4th #dool #days  Mon Mar 4th  JJ warns Haley that ELI and Lani are at the hospital for her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Parker endlessly. just let kids be kids. he’s perfect just the way he is. don’t let anyone take away his spa… https://t.co/85pcASrhLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeseretNews @donnyosmond @MaskedSingerFOX I knew it was you.  I enjoyed your performance as the Peacock.  But my i… https://t.co/HO5nnfH2xl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philocIea I’ve seen all these selfies already but there’s still tears in my eyes i love u]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5: I usually like to find some hidden rooftop access points to see the city from above! It’s a great way to notice… https://t.co/0ClJklBzl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bee_Bailey OMG! Totally get this. All four times I was NOT that glowing preggers everyone talked about. 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joyeuse Saint Valentin à tous mais surtout au mien !! 💝💝 ****** 🇺🇸 Happy Valentine’s Day to all of you but mostly t… https://t.co/dyC6eNNKRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance Out of all the people who were qualified to be Secretary of Labor, why was Acosta chosen? Did he e… https://t.co/Wis2zJKwaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad to hear of his passing. Always remember my @PGHCityPaper assignment when I followed him around in December whil… https://t.co/uJMg1OFKQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExtremeArturo @AnnCoulter Ann Coulter is a garbage person. Thanks for the infor. I wish she would crawl back to her dark hole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIDS_United Just wait till we get Medicare for all and see what doesn't get paid for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Sara can't sleep she tries to figure out why people 1. Try to shirk responsibility from people blatantly break… https://t.co/4VUQF1uaHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not AOC??? Just Sandy from Westchester, not even Alexandria "from the block" *smh*]]></document><document><![CDATA[His made me literally lol. 😂 Happy Wednesday everyone! The sweater and vest sale continues till Friday!!  . . .  .… https://t.co/Ztg3slpszK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Homb. (@ carrie bear's castle in Colorado Springs, CO) https://t.co/xcACCGnpBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Forgetting Sarah Marshall is on tv I will always cancel all plans to watch it. It’s on now by the way]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarcroftEagles start registering for Spring 2019 Intersession today!!! Register each morning in the main lobby. Ch… https://t.co/80QawrMPNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahaaa @jeffkaufman  here you go. Sooo evil. Sooooo evil. https://t.co/waTKlQePsA]]></document></documents></author>