<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheEliza2 @by_aoc @gypsyglutton @bigolfoot @CynChamplin @MikeroHonky @HamLibertarian @Merica_Media @jswifty250 I w… https://t.co/kN01sj6qeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I’ve been editing an old radio adaptation of Thornton Wilder’s Pulitzer-winning play “Our Town”, with Orson W… https://t.co/CKJFPM95Ks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well #WhiteSox fans, looks like the Sox are going to have a new third baseman this year....just not the one you wer… https://t.co/72pN44gWbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leftcoastbabe Unable to land "VERY" presidential in the plane of consciousness. Something oozing from a colostomy… https://t.co/olCY7hPvyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BritVoxUS It won’t be a roast. It’s a light broil.   @TheCaseyMcLain - let’s add James to the topics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just started #UmbrellaAcademy and it is stunning. Gorgeous cinematography, instantly likeable cast, and pogo looks… https://t.co/ceOS9YJw73]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FREELIVING69 @RealWayneRoot @realDonaldTrump lol 99% of NFL owners are friends with trump, this has nothing to do… https://t.co/GvqGm6z4Nm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoofingPartner Let’s schedule a call! I’m driving back home to Arizona tomorrow morning but I’d love to talk, we d… https://t.co/LDtrUfmaMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The media has put some y’all back years to your childish sore loser days. I would say it’s funny, but at this point it’s sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidNSimone That’s right around the number of people I have constantly tweeting at me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericripert The best parts of Ramen: amazing broth and a custard-like egg-yoke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can go 4 days without texting me back. Go 4 more.. and then some.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hora de darle a la rutina de ejercicio en People's Gym  Suc. Anahuac https://t.co/wFZ29MntYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magnusson_kyle @Bud_Doggin @tedcruz State of emergency has been called by about every President. Obama had several… https://t.co/rbf0fqVEns]]></document><document><![CDATA[Based on the push by the islander it has to be rules a goal - Toronto ruled it via video - black and white rule]]></document><document><![CDATA[Power went out on just our block for twenty minutes and im pretty sure a heist just went down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big 12 refs should know after all these years Huggins wants a chaotic foul filled game. He’s playing them like a fi… https://t.co/2RGXaFE9az]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadlerVaden You too, man. Y’all were fantastic and I can’t wait to see a lot more Sadler Vaden shows. 🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Economists diverged on how to read yesterday’s US inflation print for January; @grobb2000 at @MarketWatch sums it a… https://t.co/0eQ2XxOwga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the cars, the drivers. The only thing worse than a BMW drip is a Tesla driver.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What can you say that is positive about the #Kitchener #Rangers in their 10-2 loss at #Niagara?  Their uniforms loo… https://t.co/PoEsrEiDuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanadianEH6 @HunterTootoo @Mikeggibbs @Puglaas @JustinTrudeau Strange since the Ontario conservatives voted in fav… https://t.co/OKuCZsRaeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see LVP is trying to set up a spin-off for Vanderpump Dogs the way she did for Vanderpump Rules.   The first time… https://t.co/nodmiReOxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I’m saying is, if your pussy is horchata it doesn’t mean it’s great. Have y’all not had all different kinds of horchata 🤦🏻‍♂️🤦🏻‍♂️🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLCABaseball @j_han06 @ColinBelvin @GavinFragale @704preps @LNCitizen @PrepBaseballNC Nice work boys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenhorRaposa we need him and merkley in the senate..but he and Kamala were who I really wanted]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread is a good read for anybody lashing out on Spielberg today. It might be a little deeper then a legend be… https://t.co/cu64ZP9E32]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is literally @Julissavegga_ @keilaarellano21  @Elliiee_44 &amp; me all the time 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow @KFerrugia Reaching like this is pitiful, embarrassing and a total lunatic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janinebeckie4 @ManCity Unfortunately, we couldn't watch the women on TV.  Hint.  Stream the women's games online.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnOwning @JoeyIckes @BobbyBeltTX @VoiceOfTheStar @KDDrummondNFL @HelmanDC @Marcus_Mosher how long is tank going to delay surgery?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I doubt it. Especially after McConnell tries to blame Dems for the vote tampering in NC by Republicans by calling i… https://t.co/xm3IIvtO0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CougPicOfTheDay  The maestro of #MidnightManeuvers, @tyson_d_brown...#GoCougs🐾🏈 #CountdownToSpringBall 3/21/19… https://t.co/fajPnoOXo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trukurt1965 It has long been a professional fantasy of mine to revisit the Wonderberry and apply modern genomics t… https://t.co/18QpAzSJH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeoGarcia123456 @SonsMary The fruit of government employ and lobbying payoffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost mood_to_travel • • • • • • How cute are these flamingos 😍 Double tap if you want to visit Aruba! 😋 ————————… https://t.co/gZghKxPYKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you vote Democrat, you are feeding the Lion trying to eat you and destroy your family from conception. Any money… https://t.co/uusn1GUzE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_HambyReport Refs swallowed their whistles at the end. It’s truly a shocker that(sarcasm)that UNC is the beneficiary. #UNCvsCLEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Eyes and Eggs” 1983  Acrylic, Oil Stick, and paper collage on cotton drop cloth with metal hinges. - Jean Michel B… https://t.co/Mrhk6OlDkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebbiYeoman @Tucson_Police My wife used to live in Tucson, she didn’t know either. All she talks about is the airplane graveyard  ✈️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The next year is going to go by whether you’re doing something about your life or not” -Dr. Phil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonnyBunch My favorite thing about this opinion piece is when the author talks about how diverse Orange County is… https://t.co/Jt8A3nUkWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 Historical People Who Were Real-Life Magicians  https://t.co/cLp75yzNRf via @io9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope Congress will still call WhiteAcre(of scalp) back to explain his difficulty with Truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree Remember Graves is the married one not Carmella so aim your venom at him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceAilion Modern Contemporary like the home I built and sold and now I miss 😔 https://t.co/5KYZfm1R8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s no way Brendan on Making a Murderer has the IQ required to stand trial, be interrogated...or wipe his own a… https://t.co/g6CxkFCiPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering when is a good time to follow back all those Jusie naysayers.  🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @irenerusso124 @marc_lotter Enough said! https://t.co/UkKeOz4SQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregPickel Will the Big Ten, get a little progressive and think about considering @SandyB_PSUAD for the position.… https://t.co/IaDdn3pFc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Mentor2 No one should be talking about either of these niggas going into the HOF. And anyone that does should be labeled a communist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me thinking choreo:Maybe I could do this oh yeah I'll go try it in the parking lot real quick to test it ....  Me d… https://t.co/DQwNGtlhpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wralpheubanks Thanks so much for sharing @Wralpheubanks ! I hope you are well and hope to see you again soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackmb I would say a master’s degree in theology or divinity counts as specialized training relative to the vast m… https://t.co/nd56v1gAGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loungo when he finds out he needs to start a game at #TDGarden #NHLBruins https://t.co/3oHyQzs6Ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[I respect Richard Petty, but let’s call his 200 what they are - NASCAR touring series wins. Not MENCS wins.… https://t.co/802hZK47Zu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedNationRising @trump2020_Maga Muslims terrorist they should not be allowed to even be in Congress they and tryin… https://t.co/hci0kF7YEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[For her your ant man theories and Captain Marvel theories, this man will defeat thanos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PARABELLEBAND it’s been awhile.. so far away.. it looks so good on paper.. https://t.co/new9INfyaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@persephanie24 @mjfree @DonaldJTrumpJr Yeah, Hilary’s lower, Pelosi? Yep, well you get the drift]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I had a dream that Hillary Clinton was my mom...but like, in my mom’s body.   We were standing in line a… https://t.co/Ylk1fqIRwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueWave2020NY @MrDane1982 @ladyvictoria8 @clemietine Umm that was supposed to be fess up, not feed]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chicago O'Hare International Airport in Chicago, IL https://t.co/6aqrz2iwGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly you’re welcome for the motivational lift changing content.  #YouSuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marist is on fire from beyond the arc, hitting 6-of-8 so far to take a 24-18 lead over Monmouth with 11:23 left in the first half]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m forreal, I want a mini me and a lil family and whoever my girl is .all pregnant and pretty n shit lol🤰 👶 👪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsNadia_Ew @ThatKidChrisV I hope you acheive everything you want in life and this is nothing but a stupid convers… https://t.co/dRYXI10X9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REDee911 You are not alone.  Every time I add subscribers in a day, they delete subscribers.  What’s up with that… https://t.co/4smpEHoDR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyhcmaven84 @PocketofChRyM Guys are rarely go to that levee. They have to be driven!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathyDe11564196 @DonaldJTrumpJr 'First Amendment ...or prohibiting the free exercise of thereof; ' ('religion'). I… https://t.co/C0MjcvtmIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very nice stroke @Bdud27 #17!  #WarningTrackPower #JUPhinsUp https://t.co/rqXF3bdzdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[LNT: I overreact because I can't stand not having control with outstanding variables that are too erratic... The ou… https://t.co/cwHQr1nyku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InstagramMusic   New Dirty Machine single “9:05” produced by Matty J (Travis Scott, T-Pain)… https://t.co/S0CXd8DWMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertbrender They don’t historically handle the “good problems to have” very well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Universal mardi gra date night :) @ Universal Orlando Resort https://t.co/oMV2uaEmFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[She told me put my heart in a bag and nobody gets hurt.... 🍋 Juice WRLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hawk Don’t forget NFL teams that “quit” (cut) their players under non- guaranteed contracts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VixenLamoore I sincerely doubt a woman like you would ever want a man like me! Prove me wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦈LINK IN BIO🦈 CHEMICAL COURAGE (A$H IN A CUP) Prod. sir.spook  shark_papi  VISUAL. OUT. NOW. 🦈🦈💜💜🦈🦈💜💜🦈🦈 #hiphop… https://t.co/JsCrspU1JC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @blairsocci, are you going to get ashes on your forehead tomorrow? Seem like something you’d do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shadipetosky you seen the adam west batman costumes at the Hollywood Musume?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first Student Government President I knew and admired. Thank you, Kambrell for being inspiration to me and so m… https://t.co/megiYKDwYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metspolice One of the Mets' 6 20-game winners. Face of the franchise while Gooden was out/ineffective and one of t… https://t.co/cqzROMQWIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@circlecityvbc @ArmyWP_VB This athlete will be setting a precedent as she sets her sights on the next chapter of he… https://t.co/PPPa7hyAH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sgtjanedoe @XOofXOs #FunFact: According to family lore, my Mom declined a promotion and retired mainly because she… https://t.co/2kKk0Mu13R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChecoPerezNews @SChecoPerez Nos podrían informar por que dio Checo tan pocas vueltas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GusGowland @TheTonyAwards “A Little Night Music” starring Alexis Smith.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Lady_Red @lizzieohreally @Nerktwin He didn't say it was plugged in--c'mon, that would be savage! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheZacharyLee A few things  -This is just based on what I saw on film in 2018 -Your #’s / pace is off  -I said he’… https://t.co/65OewQCn9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is this even supposed to mean? This man needs to be in a padded room, not the Oval Office with the nuclear cod… https://t.co/u4pAmVJ3ls]]></document><document><![CDATA[What kind of world do we live in where the Thunder can whoop the trailblazers ass 3 times this season be down by 3… https://t.co/kbmZQaLUnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbDunningKruger @llunarossa @RealMuckmaker Does he have his hands up the flag’s skirt?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are a pathetic piece of human garbage calling everyone names. And the worst part of all this is the fact that n… https://t.co/eFpk0eUi5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSPhilly @CSeidmanNBCS Why don't we offer Harper $500 million and get rid of all other players on the roster and… https://t.co/svZ3iveU8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalHoeliness did you see the under armor special women's day Steph Currie shoe? IT IS VERY VERY NICE AND SUPPORT… https://t.co/bYon9zdx7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@btbamofficial, @tesseractband, and @astronoid! #CargoReno (at @CargoReno for Between the Buried and Me, Tesseract… https://t.co/cZbjcdujKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Sr. Manager of Traditional Media - https://t.co/NbDSNTRwqE #Marketing #Katy, TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HauntsJohn @Bornabrit1 They are already dipping into that. They know no bounds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need some humor. #comedy #giggle #smirk #amusing https://t.co/NA9U6HtWNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stage 4 cancer patient says Bolivar cops searched his hospital room for marijuana https://t.co/kdrTP1LCRd ps the st… https://t.co/f1PEY5Oqqp]]></document></documents></author>