<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WillWestWNML Let me give you a thought, it's a long shot I know but hear me out. Arya Stark for the Iron Throne.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations on your new home! 🏡 It was a pleasure working with you and I can’t wait for what the future brings.… https://t.co/fVLcYRVnnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[NWS precipitation totals as of 7 a.m. 7 inches of snow so far on Palomar Mountain. #sandiegoweather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McCullochKolten You think this gun is also worth $300 million in the MLB?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really strong lineup for @lotame’s #rethinkingrevenue discussion! @alonif01 @andymonfried @davidzspiegel @Hearst… https://t.co/wdMnXTdxXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbusa617 And we give them food stamps housing and healthcare. This is insane. We need to take back our country fro… https://t.co/lLs5BpvChn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmfao_ayee @_Morvelous @_ValTown_ It’s so sad when I see black men head stuck so far in white ppl asses. You sound crazy as hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some motherfuckers really need to get their priorities in line because there’s no excuse to be such a gigantic piec… https://t.co/niPIkmgFEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad that it doesn’t even matter that tekashi is a rat. I’m at a concert and people and still going crazy over hi… https://t.co/qe4oANndXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCheefReport another unconstitutional law put in place to further erode our first amendment rights, PC by legisl… https://t.co/sxg2Yf5hK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WD9EWK I sent a screenshot of LOTW credits page showing EM grid with the call worked.  Did not need to sent separa… https://t.co/1V8IjFTk7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 22575 NAUGATUCK SQ #Ashburn #VA  #realestate https://t.co/u9Fvty5uHf  [For sale]]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaReef70 We don’t know yet these are all strong opinions with shady info on both parties my point remains that fo… https://t.co/hjw3Sk5cRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffLane22 @THEVinceRusso Got it downloaded and ready to listen!! SUPERBRO status!! https://t.co/STHL8naG43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk @PFT_Live I raise cattle and med. rare is the only way to go. If you want a well done piece of bee… https://t.co/DuOg2JJbiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[today my tio is 2 yrs sober and he came up to me and excitedly told me that not only is he going to be taking commu… https://t.co/iFXhZL8RGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highlights from this week’s top news stories on luxury and global real estate, art, collectibles, and home, featuri… https://t.co/O7sZALbUpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selfie time! Shredder aka heather has been underperforming today. The boys and I have had a blast @ Hidden Valley S… https://t.co/aoxYHX1uGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh that interview process was just so much fun. It ended so quickly. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pbracknyc @DeadlineWH @morgfair @FrankFigliuzzi1 @NicolleDWallace More like these guys. RUSSIANS! https://t.co/vhwfYcj4eg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your bathbombs by DREAM BOMBS 🛀🏽✨ All Natural Ingredients in many different varieties like Vegas Nights, Tie Dy… https://t.co/G6pemshfwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii I love it when they claim he is working for Putin. Trump launched cruse missles in Syria after Russia… https://t.co/BaQt3T6V4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PioneerSeeds @CortevaUS has an extensive library with hundreds of agronomy articles from Pioneer/University studie… https://t.co/OhtSdgDgdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[outside of drawing and animating, this is probably my biggest hobby. it's a shame that alabama has like no cabs. th… https://t.co/hqV5PQQb12]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t work at Walmart, but the grocery store that I work at isn’t allowed to either, so we can’t say anything to… https://t.co/OYHVd3Fln7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tapak_ryan @JMV1070 coach knight would of damn sure stopped it as soon as it began you better believe that say wat… https://t.co/Jmii3iU1Xc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The boys’ @shelbyswimdive team finished fifth (200 points) at the Lawrence North Sectional. Key Moments from today… https://t.co/zYB34aBzQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Ann counter is like a kid who takes antibiotics for one day then complains that she's still sick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the barber shop I get my hair cut at recently moved from street to avenue and now I’m scared to go.   I feel like m… https://t.co/7ZINZJYa6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love to hear that alt-right nerds have fallen in love with Alita: Battle Angel, a totally non-sjw film about *check… https://t.co/e94MjYh8I2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AWilliams_Vizor I saw these little ice makers and I’m completely on board.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobandtom if Bo Jackson isn’t in your Top 3 Bo’s then the list is no good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Real_TC @Amber_Marshall @RamTrucksCanada My sister lives in Colorado, and April is still a common snow month even in the valleys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badhopper That sounds good! I’ve cut down on red meat but not completely. You eat poultry?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#betterlatethannever but finally got the @miamiboatshow off #mybucketlist with a potential #giftforme… https://t.co/cVc64eOqFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carvereric @realDonaldTrump So glad you reminded me. That makes everything ok!  🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisSlezak @GeoffGrammer You forgot the part about me dropping out as a junior in high school. Also, don’t expect… https://t.co/vx3wDYku2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickard_denise @Kendred11 @EdKrassen First of all he’s not buying Russian steel he brought steel back to the Unite… https://t.co/zEEZlUwt7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bf just helped someone spell "canal" by saying "it's like anal but with a C".... #true]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preach, beef is a boy’s mentality where they think that makes them a man. Being a man is about providing and making… https://t.co/aLO7E8FRCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@8_christiansen @AlexiLalas No not Lloyd. Trying Mewis tonight. I like her some.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@namphirodriguez @CisneroTobias Que se pare el chimesito de patio este.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With bases loaded in second and no outs, Corbin Burnes strikes out Mitch Haniger. And that will be it for Burnes, w… https://t.co/l1vLKTODI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WGregoryRoseDDS @erinarvedlund @jennablan College educated Americans who finish school, ( not drop out) make the m… https://t.co/Jo6evAmiKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHANGING YOUR CABIN AIR FILTER IS A MUST!!  PULL UP!! #autoservice #autorepair #autoshop #asecertified #mechanic… https://t.co/QJEVgEIHTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snap.   https://t.co/5ELNoG0lJY Subscribe to my Patreon! https://t.co/aST2cIlCax Yes, I am accepting new commission… https://t.co/lVHuP8XsBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cruise passengers praise ship's crew, Coast Guard for rescuing plane-crash victims: 'Incredible work'  https://t.co/R08tjmxonT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was at the Framing and recall that it was clearly understood that no money could be spent by the Second Branch fo… https://t.co/eu8bY7t5v2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garypastor_99 @PedroRVD @ELTRIODELFUTBOL Eso lo sacaron de ESPN de México]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMDStudio_Ca @PaigeRing @mtnbvan @Takurua2 @juliamarblefaun @JustinTrudeau https://t.co/bkweyLmkbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jairox310 You wanna build a family with a chick in less then a year yeah you delirious fam]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched Tank Girl for the first time and I have to say, it holds up. And as far as empowering women is conce… https://t.co/U98pJ6tphF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my favorite @EDiSCompany projects include our #aviation portfolio. Precision and #safety are key. Grateful… https://t.co/PlqOlPn3If]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi! Have I backed your project, booked your band, donated to your non-profit, or done anything else to help you out… https://t.co/6XRDtvoos0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkSZaidEsq It’s the type of thing you can do for any reason whatsoever — except for a corrupt one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahahaa where was this when I was getting drinking tickets in high school]]></document><document><![CDATA[@als1gal @IngrahamAngle @AOC Ridiculous?? So ur admitting it's Conservative Media Propaganda that the nation is bro… https://t.co/v2HsgSOOdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StreatLaw @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/jTa7FG5BbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christine_sarr @CorpsAfrica @Paroleaujeunes @unicefsenegal OMG  I LOVE THIS PICTURE❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP Maybe we should imprison the families who intentionally distributed these drugs to create addicts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanuckBassin @LiquidMayhem_ @Simplefishingca @ChrisKOutdoors @BaldBandit43 @SteveSMiller1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyKremer H-ILL-A st louis Missouri ILL in Oi:S The Statue of Liberty on Boston Island Hudson Bay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteNBCBoston Currently in Nashua its 28 degrees with snow flurries and windy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkSmellyBell My wife thinks I’m nuts with the eye shade and Breathe Right strips. Haven’t tried the mouth taping… https://t.co/PI9cKrpx06]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited for baseball season. Can’t wait to sit at a ball park and watch a game!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amicah1 @Razorsmack1 @ctanner3 @CCM1956 @harjo111 @dizzymom64 @deedee881 @luluHru @Lexa_Merica @enjaylady… https://t.co/aSQKI5xgs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ETC_ShowChoirs I think it’s really important that everybody in etc remember this moment https://t.co/cWVeqKQ7zU]]></document><document><![CDATA[fellas: if your girls on birth control you BOW DOWN to that pussy. do you know what we go through??? Sometimes up t… https://t.co/Fu6xXBQCdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yet, the Congress refuses a request for $5.7 billion from our President.   Go figure....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZEYNAZERDA @WallaceGeorge7 @mirtaimperatori @Ciriademattos @PolishRoyalGoat @jaimemiserachi @Light4ASD… https://t.co/WBqN5whudR]]></document><document><![CDATA[RP 🔂 #love #defy #nyc #westchester #rp #hustlers #sunday #2019 https://t.co/RplHQsWJix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaganBattalion @benshapiro @BernieSanders This needs to be broadcasted across the middle of the country on all av… https://t.co/ITR0du0VS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Airborne Never Issued Us Virtue MUCH LESS Patience!!! @ The Crossings Condominiums https://t.co/fYQZAFKvnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Travis Scott cancelled the concert cause Kylie got mad at him. Hahahahahahahahahahahahhahahah @trvisXX #Soft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cclifto12 this is a great read. I am already excited https://t.co/uxSKBpD4AN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending all day at the airport isn’t exactly what I had planned today, but finally home!]]></document><document><![CDATA[😋 I love #fortycarrots @ Bloomingdale's NY 59th St https://t.co/fGHpVKjwjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheReckonerFF @BRI1053 Shawn this was from my friend Brian and it helped me with his info, you need to follow him… https://t.co/ZO5waFOzVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[12:43 am was craving this why not its been a good long week.. #2019 @ Applebee's Grill + Bar https://t.co/la8HeIitBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydayhockey Heck Brad. I often wondered where you ended up! All the best pal.. hope you are well 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[left my inhaler at my friends house and now I’m driving to pick it up at 2am wearing my moms sandals. Whose tryna donate me their lungs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews MEANWHILE, THE MSM AND DNC COMPLETELY IGNORES RAPIST AG OF VIRGINIA! https://t.co/FJpG7CDZS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot how badass 47 Ronin is my god what an outstanding action movie @KeanueR https://t.co/O6a1yWoFdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Projectionists always describe themselves.  I. e. “Obstructing...big, fat, desperate.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish the NBA would adopt the baseball rule for league entry requirements.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swimming - check. Daddy / Daughter breakfast - check. Moments you live for and time well worth millions. #burgerinn… https://t.co/WPidC2rRs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone totally failed to write the obvious “McArdle vs. the Monorail” headline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@93Leao @rafa_elder @Nhyugo @bioluciano E dai? Vc é policial pq recebe salário ou pq é bomsamaritano??? O q move o… https://t.co/V9d4aTGIyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, Keldon Johnson just tried to kill a guy. Dunk didn't go, but that was some audacious attempt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And that is going back to the US to pay for what?  National Parks?  Tax Cuts?  Programs you cancel… https://t.co/2wgRCUgJhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charles Barkley is making the best argument on @NBAonTNT . Almost all the greats played more than one year of colle… https://t.co/cSdnRcjihI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyDaughtersArmy This moron can't even look straight at the camera. His eyes are all rolled back in his head. His e… https://t.co/jbBFbB0SdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CosmicMacabre #CFBallou #fiction #nonfiction #writers #poets #teachers #poetry #poems #writing #books #college… https://t.co/kLsOc3MoHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/9EKfyEyRxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jejomath I think I'll still start 2D, end up in a 1D embedding, finally mapping to a 3D output. Hopefully, I'll ge… https://t.co/W9WWjqmCAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday from the #SpiritAwards. See all my interviews over at @variety’s Twitter starting at about 11:30am P… https://t.co/zxwpqMcfo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterbakernyt @maggieNYT He knows indictment is coming ! “ you can run but you can’t hide”. Shine]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted @raulpacheco’s challenge to post the cover of #7BooksILove (1 per day, 7 days), no reviews, no explanati… https://t.co/ZdFMjvSlGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogueNASA @realDonaldTrump Why didn't you give "even better" healthcare than Obama created. Why is the job market… https://t.co/vWU9hsJwVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[DJT just got the biggest boost to his re-election campaign that he could have ever received. Bernie Sanders has ann… https://t.co/MwayMJCky7]]></document></documents></author>