<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ABCWorldNews Posting this for the 3rd straight day still doesn't make it "World News."]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hard part about working for the government is IT TAKES FOR EFFING EVER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josh_Cunningham Hope you get what you need with the least amount of frustration, buddy. &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaYim You look like you can touch the ceiling tiles in that pic! haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_hauser9 @RonReganRanch @JoeBrunoWSOC9 @DallasWoodhouse Britt's testimony said there were at least 780 absentee b… https://t.co/PEWfbs9Ue4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClevelandBurchs Yeah I saw it.  I’m ready for this scumbag to be gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BorrisSpassky @DUALIPA And you wonder why I refuse to participate in the KAF community.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My week is #CountryAF  Thursday @BrynnCartelli @KelseaBallerini @kelly_clarkson in Detroit MI  Friday… https://t.co/5LCIUFCjAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amconmag Dreher drivel and his obsession with others sex lives, poor little Christians defined]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what separates the people who played Oregon Trail growing up with the people who didn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever wishing I could win something in life but I know it’ll never happen 🤗. Oh well, fuck my life and fuck my fe… https://t.co/CZVPgul5bX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanMayo Where do you think Julio Rodriguez starts the season? #Top30Prospects]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GCTigerTracker Just remember back in 2012 he WD from Doral then won the next tournament he played. #itsallgood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WildcatReport @sean_mac44 What’s our record vs Iowa the last 3 years ? 😜 https://t.co/GFOX4da0rk]]></document><document><![CDATA[what am I not saying that I need to say to get you people excited about this. what more information do you need that doesn't spoil the book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helenchristophi @EnvDefenseFund But he didn't disclose that at the time when the monograph was released.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOOK AT THAT FUCKING TAKE HOME !!! Four fucking digits bitch. omg I don’t even wanna look i gotta wipe my legs from… https://t.co/ZJMhgiy3ly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VSiNLive @capjack2000 @The_Junkyard @vegasmurray @MitchMossRadio @paulyhoward @SIRIUSXM @fuboTV Damn, useless ball boys missed THAT spot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew! Seek the truth, tell the truth. One ♥️! 😎👁️☮️ https://t.co/aJJtPXl09l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy said you’re wearing Chelsea boots what are you a worship leader I DIED LAUGHING]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just think! A million gods or so To guide each vital stream, With over all to boss the show A Deity supreme. Such m… https://t.co/IA51gJ0NHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FAMU_RYS19 #FAMU_RYS19 #FAMU_RYS19 #FAMU_RYS19 #FAMU_RYS19 #FAMU_RYS19 #FAMU_RYS19 #FAMU_RYS19 #FAMU_RYS19… https://t.co/Mhd5K4T9Kf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even the power poles are laid back at the beach here! Can you say jealous?! https://t.co/qkiXmKozXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The FAQ also says that PII will not be sent unless a Veteran replies to the SMS shortcode service with their ZIP co… https://t.co/uXiX4twS35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sebasrocha96 El punto rojo del TWITT es representativo del pie de cordillera Tumbes-Piura que hace frontera con ECUA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USMC Can I have ID. Hummer, Silencer, my gun licence, a notice to DA in Riverton Wyoming, and my crossbow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GretchenLynn48 I have been sucked way too many times and know nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TR401 Come on, man! I hung up the phone a few minutes ago really, really liking you, and then I open up Twitter an… https://t.co/kkMWmXcuTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreelyRangers girls up 44-20 after 3 quarters on Brunswick.  Athleticism on display from the Rangers.  Anna DeWolf… https://t.co/03bvsHzajD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I guess he didn’t accept your request for political asylum, so you’re coming home and America lose… https://t.co/KbWzZLRVWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notoriousCFP @melias819 @ZerlinaMaxwell @Danils0N Just cause you move to nyc, doesn’t make you a local. The deal w… https://t.co/M7h2hKR7Sl]]></document><document><![CDATA[NICK WHITE x SWAY @MichaelBuble  Available on YouTube/nickwhiteworld https://t.co/UPqEITNPLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the first time in my life that I’ve  been unsatisfied academically. Second semester is literally kicking my… https://t.co/8ijhgsm4Vl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your false narratives about the border is the Fake News we've been receiving #pleasestoplyingtousyouGiantAssHat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goku Amen keep moving in God's army no retreat no surrender no backing up forward March in the mighty name of Jesu… https://t.co/oOqsCJRI22]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes @KamalaHarris @JacobAWohl The last election I was in line voting. Got a call from my Doctor office an… https://t.co/wbKxRhQybf]]></document><document><![CDATA[After what felt like a night of getting nothing but second place, this happens. https://t.co/ra9pp9EB4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colezwicker Oh I think Ja is a better prospect. But I’m generally not a fan of intangibles being huge factors in d… https://t.co/o6zbJl41xh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I better make with the good tweets.  Down to 500 followers.  I have been grumpy tits with nasty shits.  Tonight I u… https://t.co/Q355TVEBj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My take from Cohen Testimony is that he is a Half Liar: when it comes to critiquing Trump he is telling the truth ,… https://t.co/6JVyvhctz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning walk at Notre Dame #bucketlist @ University of Notre Dame https://t.co/z8R0ioPb4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what prevents you from losing the Constitution? The Constitution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Now let’s see if @rkelly gets a different result than he got in his last trial.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GGolfpro @JamieSlonis @DrakeGolf @367_alex @dhorlander @CallawayGolf @odysseygolf @toulondesign @GolfHQ You have t… https://t.co/M7rDRPnCsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Phoenix👍👍 #Arizona👍👍 #theholybible #Amen🙏  Every way of a man is right in his own eyes: but the Lord pondereth the… https://t.co/KJ2NZlZIsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mid-morning sun and clouds after a rain shower in #SanDiego, California. #cawx @StormHour #StormHour Photo by… https://t.co/vq6BX8MJ9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dominos Awesome work by your pizza makers here in Fargo at the 32nd Ave store! Thank you for the great customer se… https://t.co/m70k4jKHXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s Go Lex Wrestling! Pins=Wins #AllAboutAdvancingThruTheRoundsToday #GoLex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que si Sergio Ramos, que nadie quiere a Bale, nada,  todo el derrumbe se debe a la ausencia de dos letras y un número.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreppyProf I’m waiting for your own Alex Jones esque radio show where you rant about how great local government is]]></document><document><![CDATA[AWE Total pay seems to be slowing hasn't risen at all last 3mths at 527 https://t.co/dF3Hm6HOcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @stefsstuff Trump is well past the 'threat' stage and has been in the 'attack' stage on American Democracy for years now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open house TODAY between 1-3pm. Stop by and see this well maintained #roundlake home with a finished basement and b… https://t.co/tBUdedvdfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to our @bvnw_wrestling guys at state wrestling this weekend! #SITP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pray that we all know the difference between acceptance and infatuation. Devotion and Complacency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooooo heard the new Mr Rogers movie out this Fall is a fucking knockout]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to come in and tip me 10k later I would really appreciate it, thanks :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iron_Spike getting quoted in this week's Castle Super Beast is both strange and rad as hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAJIN2UU Yeah but could you imagine my small ass seeing you come charging at me 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PanAfricanSoul @MZanona @mkraju @IlhanMN @OfficialCBC I agree. Y’all really need to stick together because well why not]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fringetracker US citizens and nationals. In the past, NASA has hired a few non-citizen but it's exceptionally rare.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cody Ford doesn’t look that great outside of pads but MAN his game tape. Man!  Jonah Williams is going to be a great guard not tackle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladyluck34 Yes :) bigger companies have set programs but my mentee begged me to mentor him when I was moving off t… https://t.co/dLG6ohSWaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolishBaseball @MLB @si_mlb @MLBPAA @MLB_PLAYERS @CBSSportsMLB @MLB_PR @MLBPA_News @MLBTV @Brewers @BrewersAssoc… https://t.co/5oEM95czVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicious155 @JeremyWGR @BJWilsonWGR @NateGearyWGR @john_wawrow @SneakyJoeWGR @DerekKramerWGR I’d argue Jon Jones is… https://t.co/XiHHaRuC1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is not correct. Two points: 1. We are a week into spring training and like 100 guys, including a superstar, re… https://t.co/8BHGiM9BWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redsfantexas @markfuller86 @Starrbryte67631 @aaronson828 @jlaws007 @1Cowboy4Ever @jafah2012 @juan361canes… https://t.co/1ZUOzmoM6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Alien series is coming to a close soon. Spoiler alert, only 2 more parts!   https://t.co/hPC12fE9Fk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jillibean557 Half Cheerios, half Protein Cereal, a table spoon of chopped Walnuts with Almond milk!  Delicious and good for you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[DUPONT HOSPITAL​🏨 Open House “A Day in the Life of a Healthcare Professional” Saturday, February 16th 10:00 a.m. – 12:00 p.m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @MKBHD @UniverseIce @UnboxTherapy do any if you know if I can use a liquid Glass Screen Protector on my new S10+ when it comes out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattVogel311 Indeed, European countries and funding agencies are leading the way to OA with Plan S. But I wonder i… https://t.co/IORJdCc3d4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SantinaLula Traveling with our minor league hockey team to SC for a story]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camminxxx  said she’s going to beat my ass if I jump off another building.... I guess I need to fuck my asshole somempre so I can relax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllisterDen That's not even remotely close to corn. Nice picture by the way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out what I'm selling on Mercari! Fenton Hobnail Perfu… https://t.co/qiJvOrxx6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barroso Trio Highlights ⚾️🚀 #Benchwarmers #Highlights https://t.co/53FShTwQ4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[DM me vulgar and rude insults to put in the annual HBD text I’m gonna send to Scott in 31 minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealStudyHall @trevorlv31 @sprxys_ @agilson78 @PFF Hey man,  facts hurt feelings don't you know...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joaquin Estrada’s main event at USA BMX Winter Nationals Prerace. Proud of his 4th place finish with zero practice… https://t.co/Ghzi81qGep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at The Creative Group? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and… https://t.co/W0hDyomTQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StacyS_KVUE No, because if Cooper would rather have Gaga than Irina, he's got issues that would knock him down a c… https://t.co/msxiZXzxDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t park under a tree full of chickens. #incaseyoudidntknow #yesjuliatheycanfly @ Mallory Square Key West https://t.co/akKmLCn09G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @MSNBC no matter what y'all do, Kamala Harris will never be president #AreYouFeelingItMrKrabs #Bernie2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielruizzx @Presence_EE @lujan_jacobb @xisabellexx Watchu got for me brother 😮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morgfair @kim Opposes wind energy because slowing the wind down will cause temperatures to increase.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Pro Day at GameStop which should I buy for my Switch? @QuanFlix_ RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My strength shall be restored within  24 hours. The boss always comes back for a part 2.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @SIRIUSXM @altnation for rockin’ the @Weezer live from DC! Now only if I could have been there. https://t.co/RH5IZRsia7]]></document><document><![CDATA[More #cactus taken w/ my #FujiX100F. I adore the JPEGs the Fuji produces—I don't even bother w/ RAW files anymore (… https://t.co/OKUoBpn1US]]></document><document><![CDATA[So a girl I went to high school with who has a newborn has been coming to me for custody advice over these past few… https://t.co/MomtZnhyL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The husband shouldn't go to the hospital when the wife is in labor. Find out what the baby looks like at home]]></document><document><![CDATA[I walked by my kids’ leftover pizza over and over tonight and avoided eating it, and it’s the biggest victory I’ve had in months.   Help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this demonstrates that the Democrats on that committee do not care if an innocent American gets killed by such a… https://t.co/cH4QtlKix6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RampCapitalLLC @michaelbatnick Just be ready to join Ramp on his long walk home from the casino after his 'card-co… https://t.co/wlTkKfuRt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Singer: 🎤🎼Deja Blue                             Video:  🔵 Color Me Blue Director: 🎬 @peterparkkerr Clothes: 👕👖🧥… https://t.co/tQtDNDcKLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadBoiiErick He goes up a lot. But it’s the center backs that worry me. And yeah they missed a lot lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like being in row 5, 40 feet from the action. Hec ed, key arena, or Everett arena are all better options.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HYDRO-QUÉBEC. Au Maine des écologistes s'opposent  à l'énergie propre et renouvelable des centrales hydroélectrique… https://t.co/lF7zD5qcuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hooked” on a feeling for you (I didn’t choose to match) 😜 @ Bay Lake Tower at Disney's Contemporary Resort https://t.co/IDSKOcsB89]]></document></documents></author>