<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@cpmotts @SarahSmegal Nope not that. When that goes off it’s like loud and alarming. This is a subtle beep like once every 20-30 min]]></document><document><![CDATA[buying Girl Scout cookies is the best because they taste awesome and then also I get to directly see a little girl… https://t.co/l38lvdHK47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLE_Online @RueNahcMohr @iMikla @devoopes It is extremely awesome. What are you using for a controller?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Celtics0215 @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump @TVAnews I live in N.Mississippi and we are on the TVA...Tennessee Valley A… https://t.co/JPQOwgeznu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course Clapper is a liar. Everyone in Obama admin lied, abused THEIR power. They knew @gop would never do anythi… https://t.co/cLTH46a4Pu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKHbooking You’re sweet. Thank you. I’m changing them again on Monday because they didnt turn out the way I wanted… https://t.co/rvdwGRfW3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothin' but Good Vibes baby 👄👄👄 and some tea 🍵😁 ° ° ° ° ° ° #StephA #GoodVibes #Visor #Rainbowshop #Hoodie… https://t.co/s8DClyalRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated @SueGlashauser Trump spent most of his time in litigation. Even when he lost he said he won. The m… https://t.co/yWtMFcJfxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I donot watch that farce of a show.  The hostesses get far too hysterical for me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bonfiredesigns @vrosalia2 Narcissist much? President Trump doesn't even know who he is. He acts like he's such a h… https://t.co/hpVvw07njO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Ahhhhhh still thinking ahhhhhh still thinking  ahhhhhh I got zero.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadbr  @Esther188rod  CHAD THANK YOU FOR READING MY TWEET I AM 80 FULL OF LIFE LOVE TO LIVE 🎗️ TRAVEL BUT 2 YRS B… https://t.co/y1z5tNS0Nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kali Denner joins us today to celebrate #DogBossFriday. She is a German Shorthaired Pointer and is 6 going on 7 yea… https://t.co/I7XyUvjON0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimothyPeters_ Wow.u think all u hard core racers who win events would put money into it &amp; own something to preserve?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmykimmel Jimmy kümmel you really are a one sided ass. Get your head out and see how America is thriving now and… https://t.co/MQ3SWJMDJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s March! That means I’ll be writing every day this month, taking part in Two Writing Teachers March Slice of Lif… https://t.co/BgLpFysHoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to to DC to lobby for #MoreTitleIV funding at @SHAPE_America #SPEAKOutDay. You can help out by sending a qui… https://t.co/7J0uPJyIgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited about the @NASWAORG #NASWASUMMIT2019 agenda, including hearing from @SecretaryAcosta speak on Tuesday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s just stupid how headlines on articles are worded. But that’s just me. 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawBeautyKristi You are so pretty!! Please read “ You Are A Bad Ass” by Jen Sincero- it’s a game changer !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Launching our new ELM unit in 2nd grade. Listening to Rosa Parks speak. #WeAreMcNeil #MyMiSD #misdhrs https://t.co/Tdrvd3otUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirecrackersThe @KentuckyMBB @UKAthletics @vaughtsviews This girls stole the show today at Rupp!! Wow! #rupparena]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Walter_Kelley I spy warmer temps in our future.....kind of giddy about that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes This is so funny but true. Me and my husband are about to buy a waterbed. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Be glad you had her . Both my parents were mean alcoholic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was working on all my essays last night didn’t even get a chance to watch any one day at a time episodes :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayAndDan @TSN_Sports My parents took me to see the @montrealexpos play when I was about 5. I dont remember much a… https://t.co/q5bng4tUSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to understand whylLare folks still showing up to class late as ever 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebJHull The statement made by the flag jumper, was stupid. Massive amounts of bc pills? Do you men realize the… https://t.co/OXL5JLHSdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[He judge tells the remaining people here they can leave they have selected their jury.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be strong and of good courage, do not fear.. for it is the Lord your God who goes with you. Deuteronomy 31:6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LGiles1017 Neither do i .... IF IT WORKS.... We went back to see an ENT today bc " they dont make hospital visits"… https://t.co/1UwJDu99Er]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun times today at @LakeLasVegas with @PinecrestHrzn @WendyShy5 @ralph_krauss and @ThePinecrestFDN #charter… https://t.co/x6QLx5m7eO]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's seriously such a perfect little human being. I thank God every day for allowing me to be her Mommy. 💕💕 https://t.co/MmzujXn9uj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oliver went out just far enough to pee and then backed himself into the house. #whereisspring https://t.co/ueyD0mvwXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fluffy Ready!!! @fluffyguy #Fluffy #Nashville #AnniversaryWeek #HappyFriday https://t.co/pEeIVwBnpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pulling the trigger tomorrow and buying flights to head down to mariners spring training as a Valentines present to… https://t.co/DRFxxlR2hE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nesha2325 As he wasn't married to Mia Farrow, Soon-yi Previn was never Woody Allen's adopted daughter, she was Mia… https://t.co/TSMPcgteJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hottest 50 y/o I’ve ever seen. Conspiracy theory: all the celeb Jennifer’s have found the fountain of youth.. J… https://t.co/1rOELxpRSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astrogrant @saoastro @CenterForAstro These are #Galactic* images Grant!  Thank you for sharing #Astrobuddy!… https://t.co/fA8OE9MWPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDebDingell   What's wrong with this women?  When she speaks she is always moving, shaking her hands, arms or he… https://t.co/dq4GLdKvgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍷Where are my wine lovers?   February 18th is National Drink Wine Day!  Here are today’s five thing to know about W… https://t.co/stLATQmrcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 Yes, she needs to buy a mirror. Then go back under the rock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The longer I watch this show, the sadder I am that I will never have adorable little blonde southern children]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BDicksonNV CONGRATULATIONS!!! So happy for and you’ll AWESOME!! https://t.co/mqoON4xsKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CourtneyKofeldt delivered a great session on embedding 21st century skills in daily instruction, thank you! #NearpodTransform]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ms_JoAnne @MelissAnderson I cried when Albert was detoxing from drugs. He should have won an Emmy for that]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels like a party at the @ymcaindy at the Athenaeum - some people are already pedaling for a purpose at the 3rd… https://t.co/z85WfXnD9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dontstressme You missed nothing, except Clint's wife looks like she has AIDS now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing evening last night at Heather and Kenneth’s home.  Great wine, wonderful pizza from the pizza oven… https://t.co/y1gdZ93BJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just spoke with a neighbor on Logan street. She says she heard the shots fired last night. She knows both the suspe… https://t.co/hycUoHLjhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very shaken up... having a dream about something and than it actually happening 😯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gaining more faith that loving people unapologetically is the way to go. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[looking for a boy that will send me money but i dont have to interact with him at all. lmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeRJohnson777 @maydaymindy9 Not in mine, but I’ve seen them in other areas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the security takes your paraphernalia, takes two hits, then gives it back 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResaCam @KWCosby This society and your ancestors tried to enslave the native people of this country but couldn’t a… https://t.co/J0b5MZqP6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donwinslow @azcentral Pre-ordered yesterday! Might take the day off to binge read it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KING5Seattle I H8 Daylight Saving Time. It costs EVERYBODY big money. Twice a year. https://t.co/wtiJNGY28n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateJaneway25 Because as far as I know it will be implied that Leia is still alive and she'll have a couple of sce… https://t.co/ilhsEyKf68]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Till this New Green Deal comes into play their then might not be any gas guzzlers. It’s an awareness that we n… https://t.co/mgNtnPdkQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet He quit - he announced it this week.  His job disappeared when Barr got confirmed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi friends! I will be teaching a FREE bootcamp Mon Feb 25th @ 9:30am. Open to all levels.  There will also be profe… https://t.co/vsSR4mQ4fy]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this baby thing breaks Hope and Liam up I’m done with @BandB_CBS #teamLope for life! @sarahoweddell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Its_NayNay_bro Hey hey hey! Me and lovebug both love my chicken teriyaki 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Petco @RCoughlinPetco Ironic this letter just came out.  As I found a dead animal in the bag of cat food I bought from you yesterday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because every family needs a beach shot in February #vacation #mobilemardigras @ Gulf Shores, Alabama https://t.co/8TFTfJTE2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2019, Disney Channel should be ashamed of these effects they used in this Kim Possible movie🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp This man doesn’t have any respect, nor does he care about the truth!!  He is such a pathological liar, ca… https://t.co/VXelkcGwp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tegan didn’t appreciate me singing my favorite song from grease to her I think I need a new dog]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hola amigos! Los invitamos a que nos acompañen a la #teleconferencia sobre "La Ley de la Trata de Personas" que org… https://t.co/slbCxaMDn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamKeithFL 699,202 abortions reported to the CDC in 2012 (regardless of when in the pregnancy these abortions occu… https://t.co/g3kbNbtYzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[so listen, i understand some of yall are sad youre single on valentines day but one thing that i can assure will he… https://t.co/3dQeVg2AbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you hear? @hudsonville_ic is making pints and giving away all 7 flavors in its new pint lineup every hour for 2… https://t.co/vjTyvb3uvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much @butterelixir for sending me over this beauty! Butter Elixir has been a staple in my kit for the… https://t.co/aS0UgkKaux]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaydarcc What’s really bizarre is that schools are having to teach kids how to hold pencils because they do everyt… https://t.co/F8FUVpyTyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio  triste realidad. El impostor prefiere desviar la atención  con absurdas acusaciones]]></document><document><![CDATA[That picture isn’t freaking proof! It’s a cropped screen shot! What the actual F!? #RHOBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[So that Meadows guy who kept yelling at Cohen and claiming he lied on his form was ... wrong? Am I getting that rig… https://t.co/6kFKfM6Zfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarrysOtherBro I know — and I’ve never talked about or googled swimsuits (till that tweet😂), and I hate unisleeved… https://t.co/G0wM5tbSgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend is always making me put food on my face. She has to know I don’t have avocado mask money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh it slipped and got a kid. #GreysAnatomy  Alex has zero time for guns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019: the year I repeatedly injure myself in ridiculous ways &amp; eat lots of chicken tenders to cope]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewJshow @charliekirk11 @AOC BUT SHES THE BOSS!!!  According to her and the MSM giving her air time. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrZpitapita gooooooollll!!!! Les llenamos el canasto!!!!!! https://t.co/3Tm06vRIl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I broke a heart the day before Valentines Day...again. I aint shit forreal lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can Amazon generate over $11 billion in profits and they pay ZERO in taxes?   Obscenely Wrong!!!  😡#Amazon… https://t.co/cUuZU0POrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdHarrisMusic @ccassiypaige @KorieAnne1 @franniesings2 @muz4now @Thornebow @MattBoydston @vivid_peace… https://t.co/VY83wMNqx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sei lá sabe amigos o jeito q vcs me deixam triste quando acabam o namoro de vocês me magoa de vdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thestruggleisreal ...GOP lawmakers wore pearls while gun violence victims testified. Activists were outraged.  https://t.co/yo8GVWZ6jN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrdardy @joelbezaire @JennSWhite I wake them if I need them to go somewhere or do something. Otherwise I’m good. Quiet time. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[These dreams ive been having lately I really hope some of them because deja vu 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wpbf_farron Well I look at it this way.If you have a significant other at home why are you there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man the things Ive taken for granted: •Driving a car •Lifting something over 2lbs •Not being scared to fall (cant c… https://t.co/bjJD02k2fe]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love that my college friends are family to me. appreciate all of them more than they know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski @solidforce @TomiLahren Jewish and Democrats worked together against trumps racist Muslim ban!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarieJo21209334 @JeffreyGuterman @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Don’t worry, go back to your cave and sleep. You are… https://t.co/TUG9urF77K]]></document><document><![CDATA[God says, “God is always in the hearts of those who genuinely believe in God and they always carry within them a Go… https://t.co/wTVtp9rKWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Music In Our Schools Month! Join me: https://t.co/mPKRgnfQq8  #AllMusicAllPeople #WeAreWatauga  #MIOSM… https://t.co/m99RQPFqfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We the ppl these cowardly republicans represent are watching you. We can start right after vote to… https://t.co/HJY0ckBpWc]]></document></documents></author>