<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Anyone who didn’t think that Feinstein video was funny as hell is a cop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottgking Yeah I definitely can fake it but it’s gotta be money on the floor if I’m gonna fake it]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people try to bring doubt and unbelief, tell them to keep it away from you #Faith101 #FredPriceJr @eifministries @MatrixOfTruth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go! Global All-Girl!  4- Cheers &amp; More 3- FCA 2- Flyers 1- LADYCATS 😻💙👊🏼  #ncachamps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockgirl8630 Which print did you purchase in the crops? I can’t wait to see a fab photo when you receive them!💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeSignorello3 @MayorsRvl @mayormahr @patrickfgiblin Didn’t even notice since@joesignorello3 did such a good job f… https://t.co/0vrq8aKuCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlyWhisk Listing offensive stereotypes to point out that they're offensive is racist?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katrina_wiser @crawfishaka @mitchellvii @DanOHerrin Yes! Before another Democrat wins the popular vote!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly hate my job.. I should have just taken the week off when they asked me]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rise in temperature of 2 degrees Celsius could drive up to 40 percent of Africa's wildlife to extinction. Save wi… https://t.co/2W4BZ7t4a7]]></document><document><![CDATA[American Airlines Flight Attendants Burlesque Video Prompts An Outcry  https://t.co/tBZgoXdNsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBeesFan @333llcoolj No he fell off the couch of all things!! But super glad we could avoid the walk to school as… https://t.co/JiXSWCnYW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @jackiefro !! have a great day 😁😁 https://t.co/pvizeF6YKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yTravelBlog @divergenttravel @LandLopers @timleffel @AllianzTravelUS Did you know you can go horseback riding 🐴 or… https://t.co/OtX50higYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEED continued: - Account for global playing field and viability of US based companies.  - Go beyond Apple, Faceboo… https://t.co/1RbgWa8ab5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nnevyar Yes, we can certainly help you in developing your dream mobile app. Please take a look at our PF:… https://t.co/lmT5IXgWLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@propervillainy There's a proper villains sticker in my new apt building n im always like, "damn he got everywhere" 👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[The US: - is the only highly-developed country without universal healthcare  - locks up more of its citizens (parti… https://t.co/8cezkBP4SU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for Day 2 at my studio on the Off The Beaten Path (free) tour! https://t.co/3ZjZcL3VOz. aceddeland… https://t.co/UW6c8whFrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GStephanopoulos @ThisWeekABC @GStephanopoulos are like a dog with a bone going after @realDonaldTrump for one thin… https://t.co/2HZyv89Qdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por qué el árbitro no marco la que le hicieron a Brian Fdz ,pero la que le marcan al América luego luego sacaron amarilla 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carlos_Moreno06 @BarackObama @MBK_Alliance @bigpiclearning Congratulations Carlos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soulful Sips Social Delivery tonight with @natashadiggs ✨ #soulfulsips  ・・・ Attention NYC! Get your disco naps in n… https://t.co/yBjEekARV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I think about how different my life could have been if I didn’t spend my whole childhood trying to secure… https://t.co/ZwPeNzdMre]]></document><document><![CDATA[We know the forecast it's going to be a little slushy today but at least this morning's sunrise gave us this great… https://t.co/KQpXFRLNv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been awhile since I've seen this human in person. He's had his ups and downs, but he's always been very suppor… https://t.co/GciHlD4ieJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does farm to school mean to you?  Bringing local food to school and food literacy for children #OntF2S @SustainOntario @NutritionRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetraychang LOL, stop. You know what I mean. Natural vs. artificial. Thanks I dont beed to try though. I like en… https://t.co/r27fXcMnMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united .... How you gonna dump us on Valentine’s Day?! At @fly2ohare delay, delay, delay, delay....cancelled. You… https://t.co/gW5KpdT8Yw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrizmillr @philiplord Such a fabulous film. Def was new and fresh, best animated film by far. Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it funny how people are still so concerned with what goes on in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy el @guardian lleva en portada cómo Amazon estaría financiando a través de su organización benéfica grupos ANTI… https://t.co/FcZGRQE7q0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelaOkla Now you know how most of us feel when the real Trump is on. Do like we do and change the channel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow if CA were loaded with illegal aliens not having to answer the citizenship question on the census… https://t.co/M3HxAIkwEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laceykinng @phillygirlkiana @Marvibun He called the two black women gorillas last year. If you like his art/work t… https://t.co/kY1bC33sxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCatOnFox I hear you job is still on the hot seat. There's a mystery team wanting in. #Cover your butt]]></document><document><![CDATA[AQUARIUS SZNNNN ♒️COMMENT DOWN BELOW IF YOU’RE AN AQUARIUS 💙 PRODUCTS USED: - @bhcosmetics Zodiac Aquarius Palette… https://t.co/kVlFIunNOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to finally be able to post this!  More to come💪🏼 * * * #beachbody #fitness #morningmeltdown100… https://t.co/UVBsjE5SMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vaniaavr @odesza you’re such a great older sister for her to look up to. it’s always so special to bond with family over music:,)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Italian4Life71 @KamalaHarris It’s this sort of compassion that creates the kind of world where kids are shooting k… https://t.co/PtNNgowoc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[sprained my wrist and i don’t know how to use my other hand so i hope they don’t mind paying me to stand around at work 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[goodnight lads and ladies, i'm bout to collapse into a little pile of sleepy kristie 😴❤️ luv u😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blindman_54 @dhartk @CapaTosta122 Honestly, in my wide circles, there was a LOT of support.  And I went to a rally… https://t.co/qTDRsR8Xco]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he said to him, ‘Son, you are always with me, and all that is mine is yours. https://t.co/nwzm0RkPXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Children in #Pakistan and #India are afraid to play outside. #Tatiana will act.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer NO EMERGENCY??? TRAITORS!! #AMERICAFIRST!!! https://t.co/PV4vlvDEWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGould_SA @RestlessNews @poppij @andrerucker51 @DudekLinda @Itridpm @delgeo1 @hey_butter @Msgargoyle13… https://t.co/IqqcL1KipD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody gives asf about you wack wannabe rappers. Y’all shit sucks. Y’all don’t have real friends because they would… https://t.co/KUtd64IkXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulsiGabbard I hope this gives u the stage to open the eyes of many Americans to our multiple illegitimate wars. A… https://t.co/NLBXYw9fjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Get between a man and his meat u might be the one to get ate and don’t mean that in a good way]]></document><document><![CDATA[karina just found out that the cute guy in our math class is boo’d up LOLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakerobison1 Yeah...I'm pretty sure that's what made him kill people in the first place hahaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t for life of me, verify this information you are amplifying. What do you teach media and comms students in… https://t.co/Ylx11xiERy]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these animals are attracted to my presence...might as well call me Snow White from here on out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Gulf Coast Town Center in Fort Myers, FL https://t.co/hbZcn8MvnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pcdreamchasers @CopelandJKyle @MilagrosMontout @CristySwink Greg is 🔥💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmaikumeh @kreedcity @inecnigeria @akaebube @YemieFASH BUHARI IS BRIBING VOTERS. THIS IS NOT HOW DEMOCRACY WORKS… https://t.co/OO7Pia7Izh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I workout to achieve a tight ass...still workin #morningroutine #fitness #corestrength #FitnessGoals #gymmotivation… https://t.co/h8R2EsUUcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHaydnJones Whistling #MAKINBACON in #LoveUndertheRainbow is amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NachoRgz @YouTube @NachoRgz admiro tu trabajo y el d los otros youtubers q han descubierto la desinformación d los… https://t.co/CH8rzmyHez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free desserts and ice cream on every 333 Restaurant buffet!  Try our Broccoli Cheese Casserole on Wed. buffet.   66… https://t.co/a215hAq57V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so who wants to go to the vagina monologues with me on Friday @ 7:30PM? 🥰 It’s on campus! It’s a great opportu… https://t.co/fNQlRm5cHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikandynothem @AOC @DineshDSouza @RealKyleMorris @ChooseToBFree @DonnaWR8 @DaRealGrizzle @codeofvets… https://t.co/AwU59CWDaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drew that Ghibli piece so many years ago and yet to this day it has been stolen so many times and with the waterm… https://t.co/QZfaBLThaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone happens to know a lot about foreign stamps I need help identifying some of these he clipped out but other… https://t.co/wmApvd2Ho2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarteSCENE 📽Poursuite de sang-froid🎥 👌Serait un très bon choix👍🙋‍♀️ByE ByE 👋]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to get my hair reconstructed 😩 it’s going to make a difference in everything 🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@divadoc9 @vinivinidogo @aisisklopez I personally don’t like when women aren’t honest about the how we really treat… https://t.co/Y0bBMH8LkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just signed a petition: Don’t let Mitch McConnell kill democracy reform. Sign here: https://t.co/Pb6uZJuT3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fooddrinkfinder Certainly is - and we made it back to The Northman on a few occasions, including the @cidercon Cid… https://t.co/vLOiAXx6uB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsDtweets13 Yeah, this S absolutely has my permission to STOP!! https://t.co/S7Mae93yBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[these pics I posted to insta are in almost the exact same location w/ the same pose. https://t.co/v1f4Ew2H1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep, banned forever from @IHop #IHop Menifee, CA.  Story tonight 7pm PST on The McFiles with @Chrismc44 #Ihop… https://t.co/yqg2hxZFLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling pretty sick today but my ass is still dragging myself to work 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hpzms48Ou1 It takes like 30 sec Fb Annette HallWe get points for signups, likes and comments. We get p… https://t.co/Zb3YBcoYOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care if this makes me a normie, but I love Luka Doncic because he looks like a walking smiley.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FelizDiaDeSanValentin #FelizDiaDeLosEnamorados #FelizDiaDelAmor ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ironhorse76 @_wbstewart @mcspocky Thanks . It seems Twitter is on a wholesale hunt for people who may have broken… https://t.co/vqKD7TcqB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loverboy12390 In his face. It was very aggressive and you know it. Shame on you and them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ShiftIntoTurbo ⚡️⚡️⚡️ • #IVCC #IVCC2019 #ImperialValleyComicCon • #PowerRangers #PowerRangersTurbo #YellowRanger… https://t.co/0anCQhTHoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheugs @Angela1303 @SamHeughan @MyPeakChallenge @MPCFitlanders @barbaramills1 @sarahjaswim @LaurelSchuett @pjl24… https://t.co/dZqjkLQWlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a treat to meet these unbelievably talented Olympians!  ⛸ Ice Skating Superstars!!! Thanks so much for coming… https://t.co/Al42sY43qv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lozanopuche @Perafunk @ReaganBattalion @BernieSanders Welcome to politics, kid. That, with the tape of him singing… https://t.co/enflclQXZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[spaceykacey theryman #rainbow @ Ryman Auditorium https://t.co/Q6WQBV93TQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost This 1942 elder #babyboomer is the canary in a coal mine. #ubi will not cover this #ai nor… https://t.co/MfOD80y2h1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Constance8News I would name this dog Snowball. Btw, a cat would never allow this to be done to them. Just sayin'.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyleevnn yea of course I told him what I heard from YOUR friends after you got him locked up 3 times now and stole his money 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dangchick1 @realDonaldTrump It will be so much better than the real thing. Thank you SNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Teen Wrote a Bill to End Period Poverty in Schools https://t.co/UOkH28fAxO #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pstaatsdc @maryesnapp I love being part of @maryesnapp team. It is so important to encourage females of all ages t… https://t.co/2MPDUTS2RQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopCraveNet @CalvinKlein @ShawnMendes @noahcent @asvpxrocky @KendallJenner Omg Kendall soooo boring]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jagmacmusic To everyone who picked ihop over Denny’s aint doing it right]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this is my happy face. Around this time last year I was at the @buildseriesnyc assisting the cast of Super Troop… https://t.co/nIy7Tnimfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another little doodle for Pig and Birb! I'm working on consistency of character. Still a ways to go if you look at… https://t.co/M0aZi29wfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[. . Keep your face always towards the sunshine, and shadows will fall behind you.. . . 📍 : Somewhere on route 66 at… https://t.co/iwWzUjjVMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lewis Capaldi - Someone You Loved https://t.co/Pn4QbrbXwg via @YouTube Love this video. Beautiful message. I’ve nev… https://t.co/lOo1MRBtMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngiePerywinkle We will never stop worrying about our kids no matter how old they are.  There is always that linge… https://t.co/XwG7NPgCLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @SenRonJohnson @chucktodd You are beyond ridiculous! https://t.co/FOJmP6F7OA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessMarieGarcia @TheJasonGenao @netflix @OnMyBlock @OMB_Writers No one can tell me Jasmin and Ruby aren't M2B.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I suppose it’s “wait, hold my ostrich jacket, OK? I’ll be back soon!” FFS! #ManafortSentencing]]></document></documents></author>