<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DoubleEph It's the smug patronizing tone (a British specialty) which offends more than the stories themselves. Nee… https://t.co/PZx66LPhsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Georgia🇬🇪, Batumi❣✔ out author's gallery👉 👉https://t.co/uwZ4JxFo9M - Batumi настоящ is a real gem of Blac… https://t.co/KASbiaH6AG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheStagmania @SpeakerPelosi What is the payoff for a failed impeachment? I don't see the value in putting the enti… https://t.co/TIEPy5pptU]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@IQ2US have you all done a #basicincome debate yet? I think that would be a great listen! 🙏 #UBI #debate]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RIP #KingKongBundy #WWE #OldSchoolRassling #WWE #😎 @ Southern Village, North Carolina https://t.co/5V417UrUvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughters photo of the moon she used a tripod https://t.co/BxxAlfWURT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The black experience in this country was and still is deeply complex and disheartening. Nothing but respect for my… https://t.co/Pz5suDMzGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at Simpson Academy for the Lamar girls basketball game against Simpson. Whoever wins will be the MAIS AAAA, Di… https://t.co/d3NodJOZsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jake Mangum said that’s a game Mississippi State probably would’ve lost last year. He thinks this team’s patience a… https://t.co/Bqs75kxFRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickelcitycon They need to stop making movies with 100 different characters in it. You get more out of a story wit… https://t.co/LGldTYVgmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piovoso_1025 I wish people would know this reference without being like wtf lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hair by #jonathanluke maisonluisant mlskinspa #classylady #valentinesday #vanity #blackbeauty #naturalhairstyles… https://t.co/toXJaUiFAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here I thought the Repugnacans were against drugs.  And now I realize it was just so they could keep the good o… https://t.co/vtQqkQ4RYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNews   #CNN #ABC #NYTimes #WashingtonPost #NBCNews #cbsnews #msnbc… https://t.co/XEEEOu0amB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KINGjay305 @Sabrina_Arsenal She tripping too, couldn’t tell bruh was gay from the jump]]></document><document><![CDATA[For #InternationalWomensDay --#MGTOW / #RedPill edition, I nominate and thank Ms. @DeAnnaTLorraine for her co-maste… https://t.co/8edN62UtzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrainLoading I mean they’re SLIGHTLY better than Flogging Molly at least? #silverlinings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Performance art? Mental illness to the 10 power? hate personified? Is this a virus infecting multitudes who run ram… https://t.co/f0zpppqToV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitMarieox hey yo I could be wrong but I heard you pooped the fuck outta your pants dude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year I got to meet @DebbieGibson in Las Vegas and now it will be @alydenisof and Alexis Denisof. https://t.co/LmNSjVLhzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@subes01 @SubstackInc @MikeIsaac @CaseyNewton I'm trying to imagine the three of us in a room.  Also, make the room… https://t.co/VacvLpFZcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My DINNER with BIGFOOT henrydanger 🤯🤯 Wow!!  6 #legends all in the same pic!!!   You’re not gonna believe how this… https://t.co/r4Qcfedy3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching people toss kraft singles on their cat's face shouldn't spark so much joy... but it does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealElvira Why did I never know there was an Elvira show pilot?!? Where can I see it?!??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Holmesy_83 Thank you! I was literally going put that in the tweet, but I forgot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichieSchueler @chanch_8 @smerrill05 @USUBasketball He’s been shooting like that since 2007!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day Donuts 🍩 (@ Evander Square - North Club House - @evandersquareap in Celebration, FL) https://t.co/MqKvXykONe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sari- I got what I dreamed you would do tonight.  My people are free.  I was hoping you would be half this kind by… https://t.co/VqkvVjuz0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmafootball81 @SportsCenter @CapitalOne You do see the DUKE shirt on me right? Or you using Braille for Twitter🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only picture from this weekend 😅 thank you everyone for the birthday wishes! 😘❤️ https://t.co/cBgfGzw7MI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMek Merkel should be publicity HUNG for TREASON against her on country:: Germany!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Understand completely.....lost my dad suddenly last week....the loss of a parent is definitely a huge… https://t.co/Rt6cVSLfVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mediaite Disgusting animals eat garbage. Show this loser how he looks maybe he’ll trade or sell his earring for a… https://t.co/kIA6MLs71s]]></document><document><![CDATA[The man with one of the best cannabis ball cap 🧢 collections in Canada @dycktionary of @Shopify https://t.co/yrrvRUOHxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan’s first time out riding her new quad. 🥰   #ridered #irodetoday @ Palmdale, California https://t.co/pFkUa2R5kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final: #LadyVols 73, Auburn 62. Zaay Green scored 19 second-half points to help Tennessee pull away. https://t.co/g0fBbvAqsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasmineStylesTV He walked in the room and cats are like... https://t.co/xNtUK9Akk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time with Deisy yesterday @knotts #Knotts #PassholderLife #PeanutsCelebration #KnottsBerryFarm https://t.co/PQPSSukMyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobPadilla_ Add in that the kid is a senior; last time on the court.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heath Clinton will be wrestling for 3rd place in state  later today!  Way to represent!  @RISDAthletics… https://t.co/950qp2y7oV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cast your vote in now for your motordrome subway meatball hoagie driver. The winner of the race will win everyone i… https://t.co/Xry9yctZCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kharyp @common I hope everyone will take the time to watch the full unedited version.    https://t.co/6NJSSyyAzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Robert F. Kennedy Bridge (Triborough Bridge) in Astoria, NY https://t.co/Jorc5xm2Ym]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh schnap! Assistant Editor! #eminencehill #western #featurefilm #uncorkdentertainment #postproduction #lawman… https://t.co/CNFohwfFa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are here early for our seniors! #GoCoogs @BreaonB @CoreyDavisJr_ @g_robinson1 @lando_1_ https://t.co/EXpAetNYzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VidaSoCali Oh it’s getting played. May not be our stations but it’s getting played.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexxxWilsonnn Couldnt agree more. If we can get Rosen for less than a 1 we should run it to the league office IMO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LawrenceOlsen1 @CBSDFW Well i could remove the “originally “, point was she was born in Milwaukee but grew up in Virginia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s safe to say life has hit me harder than ever. But best believe I’m comin back swingin no matter what ✊🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[psa: after binge eating buffalo wings, make sure to *thoroughly* wash one’s hands before then removing one’s contac… https://t.co/HUeabYsuOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[So while I’m excited that Venezuela has a chance at a new government that will better serve the people, I’m truly s… https://t.co/LhULq8GU9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apex Legends - 5 kills end game to clutch the W https://t.co/PC92pRBQrm via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me leaving the movie theatre after being forced to sit in the very front row https://t.co/hTcshNetmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two  ways to handle putin is to remove trump and pence from office  via impeachment  and vote the republican party… https://t.co/9Jku4fUywW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisDuerr @ScottDRiddle 3 MVPs. Shorter career due to 5 years of post high school and then injuries. At his peak,… https://t.co/ZtIxMQS1OP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hickory Ridge High School - @hickoryridgehs in Harrisburg, NC https://t.co/4qdjG6yI6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just dropped on https://t.co/fpVU5ZLPNm go shop now!!!!!! #RichOvernight @ Glendale, Arizona https://t.co/3BiRyLCwTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BesiktasEnglish dont think ive ever seen anything like it. To go up 3-0 after 1 half of futbol to not being able t… https://t.co/0plkUs5Blq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marissadraws @JonRivera NVM. I just started watching the 4 minute long trailer and had to stop it after 1:18. Hard pass. 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/P0i6T5G98I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoilerBall It will be like playing at home with all the Chicago Boilers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mehdirhasan This is like Pizzagate if it was real. But republicans will not say a word because they are hypocritic… https://t.co/WOGatPzxo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could redo most of my high school years but with a wax pen smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who don't serve need to stop speaking on behalf of those of us who do. Just because you're a country boy fro… https://t.co/OxdyV8RzsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this CHRONOGRAPH MEN'S 18KT WHITE GOLD CASE LEATHER STRAP DRESS WATCH. for $32,000.88 on OfferUp https://t.co/Yi7eY9fXyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should i even believe @AfroSenju anymore when he says hes gonna put pt 2 up of the #smash match? This is like waiting for #Detox 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetallicaPod After watching the video debut I was beside myself with Excitement looking forward to the album release.]]></document><document><![CDATA[US #Army pivots on program to “transform” ground-based combat vehicles into #Ai powered war #robots. (See what I di… https://t.co/xo2QenFdrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just glad I’m going back home tonight after a long week from my good boy🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNotoriousNIK So you say the Queen pic was a whitewash but then say false things about Mercury? He wasn't a gay… https://t.co/oQPq2GRe4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Everyone That's Asked If I Ever Miss My Long HAIR... https://t.co/gHdRReINmr via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinWBrantley Funny thing is... Hillcrest South is not in @thegrindsession . So how will you see them in the Gri… https://t.co/P4oOYZqvtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmclymer How about Jill Stein or Ralph Nadar?He might want some veteran experience from people who know how to get… https://t.co/eMPWyrvgje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grendelsmumm @imisspoundsigns My friend who does my hair had to move  my appointment that was supposed to be yeste… https://t.co/ZAAe7wBhlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussoHockey Coming to a stop and shoved Stalock's pad in. Weird. Still 3/4 pts in 24 hrs isn't bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hurricane by @TreeHouseBrewCo @ Wood Creek — https://t.co/v2b8vm28X9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luvloungeatl wit my homegirl trisha__nicole for birthday celebration! Best friends Sunday going down every week!… https://t.co/VNy3A2ccDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #ColossusJavelin is my @anthemgame exosuit of choice. Make your selection to unleash your power and watch your suit in action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelgraham @marcmorehouse Probably because I’m a fellow Panther Alumni. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep. Seems like some would rather have Trump than someone they disagree with on just one or two issues...Or maybe j… https://t.co/6b4Noaah8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oigan y mi carnalazo el @yorchmusic1 donde anda ya tengo rato de no verlo twittear...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Grant Williams for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/eoq19NaMJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chronotope Apparently "Ziggy Stardust" 👍, "Material Girl" 👎  https://t.co/4B5xP523AE https://t.co/j8AcBGCFv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffreyswisher @JenBrooks727 @amandadeibert @karaswisher @smithmegan Perfect response!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I have to agree Michael, it’s funny how some things move us. I hope you are doing well on this blessed and beau… https://t.co/IOqqCVLWIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baltraven52 That past is your past idiot.  And we have won numerous NFL Championships.  There is a reason the NFL… https://t.co/EFO2TRv2J8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StJohnsRedStorm we need some crazy socks fro@ @JohnsCrazySocks. #WeareStJohns , John has crazy socks, we are all f… https://t.co/F4nEonXyCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for my child Apricot to tell me about something they want and i respond  “Do you have a budget?” https://t.co/3OHMLkQgTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[4th Survivor is hard! Haha made it all the way close to the end only to get my head eaten 😂 #ResidentEvil2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikpatterson I just binged Russian Doll (which is also fantastic) and it’s themes on connection thru loneliness a… https://t.co/K0gsXyXipg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieBorowski “Can we interest you in the metallic pea, Miss?” https://t.co/89A6mRWyHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CallMeTrapHouse @CFBHome @DClark1987 @Clemson @LSU @georgia Notice Clemson is one of the easiest? Playing an aggy… https://t.co/y4qoTu4jl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I realize that defending former IS fighters isn’t popular but arbitrarily revoking citizenship is deeply alarming a… https://t.co/9VNmKZLmew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bron had Love dropping 20 and 10 a night and Kyrie good for 25 a night and niggas was still saying he ain’t had no help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr That’s a pic of you! Spawn of the #LiarInChief #PutinsBitch #DonTheCon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met the owner of @Jodi_CoLtd while roaming the streets a couple of weeks ago. Some images came out of this encounte… https://t.co/jR1uU75Sm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing show from @Shinedown @paparoach 😃🤘 Drove over 5 hours to see my two favourite bands from the pit To… https://t.co/CwO9UV25gZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minor note. Cam Talbot will keep his Oilers’ jersey number (33) with the #Flyers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you lay down loot or what? I do! #LasVegas #Mets https://t.co/0iEPLY0ctW]]></document><document><![CDATA[WELL THE FACTS RIGHT NOW Rd he was attacked WE KNOW you love too spread fabrication and TRUTH IS NOT IN YOUR VOCABU… https://t.co/VLg8u8ujeu]]></document></documents></author>