<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Unlike tDump Spike knows what he is doing. https://t.co/Fk12SDKlSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no words, just so many thoughts. I don’t know who’s worse, he, or his father. My jaw is (STILL) on the floor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the laughs, thanks for the music #PeterTork 🕊  The Monkees - Theme Song edited to Full Length (1966)… https://t.co/rgxLGysIQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump If he can’t grab them by the p.  y, he doesn’t care about them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my it’s @CelticThunder Ensemble Sunday☕️☘️Have a great day🎼 https://t.co/91O5yUKWKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrancenMarine @franceinnyc @uniFrance @Film_Movement @DreamsCelluloid @critiques4geeks More #MarchCulture ?? :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contact me for all your Real Estate Needs. Buy-Sell-Leasing-Contact Stephanie Passler 561-436-8296 Real Estate Brok… https://t.co/r6m2okFHCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cruise booked for March, Sisters baby shower in April, and then the Dominican in May 😬😍 #cantwait]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never go straight to a dog and start petty them or they will do this every time unless their owner is around!!… https://t.co/eDiKjmLep0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PettyLyte Thanks to chipotle and chick fil a I don’t have a choice in that matter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta @RepCummings Why do you think he should wait. The president doesn’t have respect for the office. It’s gonna… https://t.co/ogqufCyllO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blawson85 @AliJanea @nethertonj Sounds like @nethertonj might be jealous... https://t.co/upb54uYD7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 109 #classroombookaday The true story of the Mendez family’s successful fight against desegregated schools in C… https://t.co/q51Yu23yDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOXSports duuuuude - where is the @GopherHockey game on the FSN Plus channel in NYC? Instead it’s a preseason base… https://t.co/1aJt0E43ye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deanglazeruc @UCnursing @UCHealthNews @AACNPolicy @UUHEALTH Staying at Westin downtown]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arvndgpta Go Gauchos! The access to meaningful laboratory research and projects during my time there as an undergr… https://t.co/tErHA9zg5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[cisco: how do baby snails find their baby shells???  rhyan: they go to the baby snail store]]></document><document><![CDATA[Youth climate strikers: 'We are going to change the fate of humanity' https://t.co/cYNBzsfFa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babyjesus1992 Happy Birthday to my favorite son-in-law!! Have a phenomenal day!!❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HubertRonnaud You are a wonderful man who sees the beauty and love in all creatures. Here, in the twisted, broken… https://t.co/8FQbIwQyVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OffMuteRKelly @rkelly @MuteRKellyDet @MuteRKellyTampa @MuteRKellySTL @MuteRKellyChi I am sooo happy to hear this!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmazonHelp No it just said it’s delayed and sorry for the inconvenience]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pumpkin_206 @fockthatsheet @jadineleto TY! can't guess who AR is bcoz i was thinking of a girl's name that they wa… https://t.co/4HqEJtLDpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiverofJordann yeah but he’s been around here for years now... idk just seems like that would’ve been a very viable option at some point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElizabethPand11 @SonyaBaker2 @minotauresse @sharon_elle @KimmeIsaiah @beverlynichols @EkbMary @MerriweatherSun… https://t.co/cs6SU6KMko]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m supposed to be packing for a trip but instead I’m napping in sheets that look and feel like mint ice cream.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As well he SHOULD strip them! Killing a child at ANY stage of development in the womb is murder! Killing it OUTSIDE… https://t.co/ahkPSf2Qdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyFay32 @francescamnt Lol I only know cause my Dr back@in the day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derekmagill @thsc @TexasHomeEdu @DiscoverPraxis   Thought you’d like to meet this gem of a human who believes home… https://t.co/tTqoXgtgbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm on my way to win CBD prizes from BiowellnessX ! https://t.co/rALPQx2AQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irinabaeva1 @markatalent @kguedimin @Victorkhun https://t.co/lEVQwiq8lG]]></document><document><![CDATA[In any type of  business you need to #COLLABORATE ! IT'S NOT A COMPETITION! #GIVE IN ORDER TO RECEIVE. In the end y… https://t.co/6HBbweBTuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Philly and burbs are getting hit with a snowstorm, tomorrow temp will be 52 in Feb. This is an exa… https://t.co/osS51KePWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time on a road trip I dropped like $200 on architecture and photography books and we couldn’t fit them in the c… https://t.co/ICf6IigxKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rottzillasgirl @OriginalFunko @lexcr14 @DannyLeBlanc24 Thanks Rebekka!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SHERO @NewJerseyDOE @DrLRepollet @LtGovOliver @ARHasanEdS @GovMurphy https://t.co/HsfEG3SdzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a busy gaming night tonight! We started off with Glenmore II: Chronicles which is coming to Kickstarter Marc… https://t.co/fO3Nj8HdLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRott_LU @LibertyUSGA As a criminal justice major, dipping nuggets in chocolate is a felony punishable by life in prison]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yours, Mine &amp; Our Children | The Raising Supaman Project https://t.co/0GKmyg7L1x via @Supamans_Dad]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are really excited to announce that we received the trademark for ”black box with LGBTQ Rainbow”. Our packaging… https://t.co/HvkYowGXWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tatum0420 @InStyle @JenniferAnnistn @benhassettphoto at least there were great photos to look st dice article was #yawn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyWolfeMusic Remember who has money 2buy your music lol ya might wanna rethink calling anyone older than 27 gros… https://t.co/P6qGBTa1ot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Based on Donnie-Do-Little's daily schedule when the first person referred to him as a "sitting" President, the doof… https://t.co/d7BZtpDa6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paleselan I truly can’t wait to watch someone on campus step up and do it all again]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic   If anyone ever lets me cut my hair again, I’m fighting. https://t.co/ZrFp2QxA9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we cannot get more seats in the senate, we do not get our legislation!!!!!!!!!!!! We need to turn this country a… https://t.co/2qtR6LskUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinCarterTV All those stories of snakes found in homes got me all scared already]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran out of poker chips so used dry fruits for playing instead. People went nuts when they saw me raisin the stakes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_alesy @melvillmatic This asshole can relate. https://t.co/0GC7PSyubS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776Stonewall Well I'm thinking we need to rise up against the Democrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Office Space with my friends after I graduated uni, actually made me realize I was settling for any ole jo… https://t.co/2jDr5UY2OA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash Give AOC no benefits ivanka has work for her father started her own business AOC went the easy way wen… https://t.co/0zoyDd8nXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[...at which point, a dog walked by, right between them, and the bishop accidentally kissed the dog instead. I think… https://t.co/iWF3OMUliv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasbonilla_ i’m telling your brother and you guys can sing it together 😆😆😤😝😋😫😫😔🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OkCallMeAL I want you 2 understand just how important my stuff is, we can feel young so much later in life. I have… https://t.co/rNzOsfzY3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t get why my suite mate has to make so much noise with he ugly ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[This came out amazing !! Grey blue !! #bluehair #greybluehair @ Cutting Edge https://t.co/ZPfCx8dHAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariecountryman @Communista2 @ElmagnotheFinn @lilith2u @haloefekti @ICEKweenKamala @bunkybun @jvplive @USCPR_ @codepink @buell003 Hmmmm...]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU want to be in a relationship where you constantly GET HURT???? BOO BOO that’s YOUR CHOICE!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know how i missed this now living part time in SoHo but love this! “When Women Control the Money, Female Fo… https://t.co/RnbxmzpRD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t look behind you, only look ahead. It healthier and you have a better chance of success.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby you’re like lightning in a bottle  I cant let you go now that I got it  And all I need is to be struck  By your electric love⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont be in or on anything. Basically stop existing until the lightning is gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly, i’ve been thinking about my ex bf for days like wow do i want him back or what the fuck????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brook Waldrop met w Ivey + issued a call for bikers to accompany her stepdad, Marshall Lynn Grimes, from his funera… https://t.co/gy1jc4Bm2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 25th to @Failure  album Magnified!  Magnified by Failure https://t.co/6gU0d2fjbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of new restaurant options in the #BlackstoneValley for your next date night. https://t.co/xJuRVXNdTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RV27 OMG I know you didn’t ask but... 62 and 63 Disney Channel and Nickelodeon and sometimes 64, Cartoon Network 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelatok @AafLegends 😂😂😂😂😂 okay sis. Btw I go to working 6-2:30 Sunday-Friday starting March 11th]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foggy #southcountysunrise @ Metz Stage Stop Cemetery https://t.co/8YNlQ6QBoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews Wow, wow, wow, what a face...that is clearlly a Satanic posetion...when Lusifer takes over, at this point… https://t.co/JwvRLSHyK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thespinzone He should pay back the taxpayers of Chicago for every hour of wasted time the police spent on his wild… https://t.co/T3awwy6Rbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wip @amber_benson  Fingers-crossed I get this finished for @wizardworld Portland... stay tuned! #art #drawing… https://t.co/T0ne1nG3Ay]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m watching @DearWhitePeople people for the second time and it’s still amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so sad that my 2 sisters don’t want any part of me because I’m transgender. They don’t invite me to family fun… https://t.co/KQ5hxgGYo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all are funny as hell right now. Tweets got me dying 😂💀 #SouthernU_RYS19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether it’s one or thousands, @NationalAction will continue to advocate and take action on issues important to our… https://t.co/WN92Oi0Rkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[𝟘𝟛𝟘𝟠 ♡ 𝟚𝟙𝟛𝟛 ・ ・ ・ ・ ・ ・ ・ ・ #internationalwomensday #womensday #wonderwoman @ Golden Boy Pizza https://t.co/OAhXNGJ6wq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right. That's what I want. Something completely impersonal and will serve no purpose then die within a week. Just l… https://t.co/OND5BQ5XwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colerain adopts 24/7 addiction recovery service https://t.co/owN7FPX4s7]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have got to be kidding. Can’t believe he is going to ruin the Democratic Party again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pay attention to the ending of the video I just shared for #TBT (Message: BITCH YOU THOUGHT YOU WERE SLICK!) On ano… https://t.co/yokePVmZ8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @GOP facts don’t lie. Even when they are presented by someone who lied. Checks signed by the President don’t l… https://t.co/B9JQGUyQ7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's 36 degrees in Madison. You know what that means! -my neighbors https://t.co/TEWcdyAc3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amerrick @dougstafford We’re talking about Melania’s work visa, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shaunaxoxo6 Why the fuck did this make me laugh so hard lmaoaoaksjjsjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[shout out to the person who hit my car tonight and didn’t pull over. most importantly, no one was hurt. but I sure… https://t.co/lBcSLzcv8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar To live with messy drawers and closets that I have to clean out monthly. The chance of my clothes making it… https://t.co/wedwRh6KBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_celia_bedelia_ @ProgBlacksmith1 I mean of course she did! She doesn’t want harassed and threatened over asking a… https://t.co/ZUp4RmCxQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay @carliejoprints outfit today is the most fire!!!! Be there or idk be without yummy coffee and my hot bean. So be there or suck? 🥰👯]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm raising money for Costa Rica Volunteer Trip. Click to Donate:  https://t.co/76mQvi6Q2d via @gofundme]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iTunes Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% Free in the Link Below 👇  Cl… https://t.co/aeUcf0y0Qs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett - I suspect that you will never work again. That is quite a lot of 'damages' to sue for. Why have y… https://t.co/aCki2LpKlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catturd2 Worst than https://t.co/tRBe9203Fx’re a failure who couldn’t make it on an even playing field of your pee… https://t.co/UiW9a3p9jw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard to break the hosting habit! I hadn’t realized we were doing that, but you are right, we did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VocalPineapple @AskPlayStation I miss the days when you would buy a cartridge or CD of a game and play it without… https://t.co/v0VqVTSyof]]></document><document><![CDATA[burst out laughing for some stress relief. This is pretty much Murphy, Kimber &amp; Gracie!!! Someone say treat???… https://t.co/KRi7u4uNrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐝Mon -Fri Day:   I grind for my clients and City   🐝Mon- Fri Evening:  I grid for my education working to finish 2… https://t.co/sWQ3BXMoP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the people are pigs category: Someone let their dog shit RIGHT NEXT TO the dog poop bag dispenser in Belmont P… https://t.co/LfQOCZ5zTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#gratitude @CBCToronto @CBCNS @CBC #youSeeMe #itsTime #yourTurnCanada @ShellaMusicCa @ShellaMusicCan #wereReady… https://t.co/W3selCu5UH]]></document></documents></author>