<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@nypost That’s real BS! We need to mute this high rent for nothing shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[True Security Design is very happy to present to the NY School Superintendents. Threat Assessments, Go-Bags, Classr… https://t.co/U9wVe9UzaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames have some accountability. This IS on you. 4 seed pre-injury to worst in the West after. Weren’t committe… https://t.co/JTi5mZ2X7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wttsfm Pink Floyd without a doubt, living members. I’ve never seen them, won’t ever get to I fear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josiane33791795 @Era_Of_Bliss @AlexaBliss_WWE So Grogous and Breathtaking ❤❤💜💜😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kam_Bontrager This was legitimately thrilling. You should compile it and send it to one of those FB pages that shares stuff like this 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Cisco - Building 3 - @ciscosystems in San Jose, CA https://t.co/djkvUZOP6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our cook at Benihana just brought out a laser light &amp; led lights. https://t.co/iwJKvK9g84]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rob_sheridan @highlevelcomic Congrats man. Picking it up tomorrow @hidehocomics here in Santa Monica!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get frustrated with myself when I can’t come up with a full strategy for a client in the 1st hour after a kickoff… https://t.co/jAz1hN1m1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna be a ruff night. Not sleepy nor tired. 8:30 start time for work tomorrow. Plan is to wake up at 6:30, brutal https://t.co/uPR6SN2er3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also have become that person who carries around an external keyboard everywhere with their laptop. 🤣 #noshame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill I love you jemele but you ain’t the woman I’m going to for an unbiased opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of people look in front of them, and I look beyond. __ #shootingninja  #respectheshooter  #respectthegrind… https://t.co/7J6BWtPe5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Hawwaam (#Silvano) and jockey Gavin Lerena winner of the G1 South African Classic at Turffontein… https://t.co/zlOCnfLLLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConveryEA @UQ_News @UQHealth @Louise_Hickson A belated congratulations!🍾🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alone in my office with this video and, unfortunately, I think I wrenched  both knees. I’m taking Shaq’s advice and… https://t.co/Q0O0TxjSR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need the humanities more than ever, despite all the shouting. https://t.co/zL89dKS5nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[trophywater_guff worked hard on the sticks in blown out water to help me chase down some fish. Heres a few of them.… https://t.co/PceFKifH38]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomsegura I mean I know she ain’t a spring chicken but this kid is just disrespectin @ChristinaP https://t.co/ZfCshFCb6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZMRollins Overall, given my personal experience of the last 30 years of neither program talking "the next step," I… https://t.co/b8hoPKtlpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m eating this candy my roommate left out and watching umbrella academy until I die]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nespimo @maurocastillo @TinoasprillaH @PoliciaColombia @FiscaliaCol @IvanDuque Jajajajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaystew71 Thanks for coming out on Saturday! We need to do that again. ✊🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice! At #chirunconf there is an open issue proposing to wrap cool API in #rstats.  Cc @EmilyRiederer @sharlagelfand]]></document><document><![CDATA[Washington misses a 3-pointer to get it to 13. Then misses that jump hook in the paint to get it to 14. He has just… https://t.co/MxPpVci5Dl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's true, we've accomplished a lot with the support of the PMO, and they're staff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna thank 107.3 the beat IHeart radio and my new friend @RadioArielle for having me! Make sure y'all tune in tomo… https://t.co/Fxdrh0AQnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Para mí amada esposa @LETICIA777 en este día del amor y la amistad!!! https://t.co/2OXC3Jpkpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[$$$ This is great for          Cooking Family... #funniness #lol #smile #ludicrous https://t.co/JuBZMl8ZZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will have updates of TCPS VS WEST Union at Pontotoc https://t.co/P2MIReivIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maurpin @CityofTampa Abbonda abbonda specialmente vendita nei negozi di giornali]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to be mistaken with berner415#nowplaying Dangote by Burna Boy via the @audiomack app https://t.co/7hTJR3kauA. @burnaboy]]></document><document><![CDATA[LGA 🛫🛬 ATL 🛫🛬SAN 🌴 innout 🍔 @ LaGuardia Airport https://t.co/JGSq5jnnL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[**Gruden proceeds to run the ball 60% of the time to establish the run**]]></document><document><![CDATA[@professornaite deserves high praise for his commitment to educating young men of color. Over the summer, Dr. Alexa… https://t.co/Y8t0n8PPlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigEasyLofton @bullbody84 @chrishandles @AntAtkinson12 @mooseisloose45 @Datrotter4 Ant looks like he needs some food! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN VOTE E--------------ToV              FGHIJKLMNOPQRS A---------------PEA-----------K At REA------------L… https://t.co/djrZ6KCbC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felíz Cumpleaños a ti Erandi Lopez-Salas!! It’s rare you meet a best friend late in life. Love you so much can’t wa… https://t.co/2VyFWvgelw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShortyStacked Let me be the judge of that !!!! I believe that you could slide with the best of them . 🔥💞🔥 you have my VOTE 🗳]]></document><document><![CDATA[The WA Horseracing Commission explains that it opposes HB 1975, tribal #sportsbetting, because “it would be one mor… https://t.co/Hgs2vZcjzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewRelease 💥INFECTED DEAD BOOKS-INTL Links 🌎https://t.co/qRIA63fi5C… 🌎https://t.co/IC2Xc0yayU…  #99c 🌎… https://t.co/m5gvISHTWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today my dad called to let me know that people were saying in town that he was dead, but that he wasn't. So there's… https://t.co/0LJLT3iCve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BraxtonMiller5 been searching for an autographed 8×10 of you in your THE @OhioStateFB Jersey #1 can't seem to find one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DomTheGoat5 @TallWhiteMocha How I would’ve been https://t.co/LnuWNDXPxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m all for CJ Johnson’s official name on the Toronto roster being “Poop Johnson.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cruising old reliable today. #longroof #hoonigan #nova #1964 @ Hoonigan Donut Garage https://t.co/oTWYj7aFus]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can get what AB is tryna do rn but his lack of syntax is just getting everyone a lot more confused lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the craziest stories I have ever read. God Bless local news anchors!  They’re out here keeping it re… https://t.co/HEiMf9t23c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gilad_Halpern And, in part Sam Sokol's statement "we left good lives" only strengthens it. I never saw me leaving… https://t.co/5xcrLtxogw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcspocky SO the attempt at diminished capacity didn't fly with the judge...lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_blvckk Son stfu pussy. The question was “who’s down?” Either say “im down” or stfu and keep scrolling my guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanKoenigsberg @ZacStevensBSN 18.5 mill is a lot for a QB who's gonna be riding the pine behind a draft pick? Is… https://t.co/unghVsZIB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaunAlex87 @RealScrambledYE @garyvee That actually makes sense and something I did not think about before my hot take]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patriot Athletic Conference boys tournament   End third quarter   Terry Sanford 45, Overhills 37  Davis Molnar with… https://t.co/DgCGPUNbPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amid the Canadian scandals, there’s quite a harassment scandal brewing in the art world at the Remai Modern in Sask… https://t.co/G0JgpNxHyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Introduction to 80’s and 90’s movies and how to choose the correct movie quote for any situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Players that I would like to see get a ring before they retire: Paul George, Westbrook, Antetokounmpo, and Derrick Rose]]></document><document><![CDATA[@niclloyd70 @Loomin_Knotty @Diekman_12 @BarstoolMSU @_Dbush11 https://t.co/I73XDbtshc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we talk about why people think it’s ok to recline their seat on airplanes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quinton_clarke @ckparrot I could see that but I could also see Teddy being just good enough to make Miami 7-9 behi… https://t.co/W4vpNVamEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end it said the truth is still unknown but he was proven innocent twice...]]></document><document><![CDATA[there was not, and still isn’t a gay bar in my hometown  unless you count me going to the new local spot when I’m h… https://t.co/XRF3gKogK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GayPatriot I demand to know: What kind of leftist, socialist, democrat, fake news is this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[En menos de un día, mi aguacate tiene el mismo número de likes que el anuncio de @nadalpower sobre@du candidatura.… https://t.co/yNjLUPCfut]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m running again to continue to build on the successes of #CarlislePA. To learn more or to help support my campaig… https://t.co/6TP3dQHePe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good start to Alabama 3rd as @Drew_will10 takes one off the foot for leadoff hit by pitch.  @Kobe_morris12 🇨🇦 follo… https://t.co/DPzLzrL1jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re pro-life, don’t have an abortion. Respect her choice either way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Refinery29: Charlize Theron Got Seth Rogen Hooked On The Bachelor &amp; Colton’s Virginity Was A Total Surprise.… https://t.co/oLVcnYvoA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yokika @TxSU_TF @BrownKrishanda @ClydeEDuncanSr1 @LykeMykeee You’re welcome! &amp; Okay Thank you .! 🐅💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianDeLaGarza Ordenado y limpio, dese una vuelta por las calles aledañas al meson estrella ahi vera que el depar… https://t.co/bnfM4nsPOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[McGrath wants time after Charleston starts the game on an 8-0 run. 16:03 left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, this is very counter to my experience.  I can't do creative work, especially with words, while listening to mu… https://t.co/mEFQrObdom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question is WHY would you take the chance they do NOT pose a threat? You’re putting your legal citizens at risk, ty… https://t.co/eWiQrkl3QZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @WCI_YRDSB Girls are ready to tear up the course today. https://t.co/hy2AhOWhf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertbbrown007 @BernieSanders The military is required.  We are not spending enough on defense actually.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real men wear pink😝 Fresh fit🤙🏽bandarinconcitooficial @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/EwJzRLulUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random quote I heard from a homeless guy in Miami today; mistakes are just proof that your trying • idk what that means but sounds cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[He could've played out his prior contract and become a free agent. That's allowed. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[_nilmarie_ shot by @robertcgrima styled by anna_castan #ronniepetersonbeauty #makeup #hair @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/DRQA6giBZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[A year ago today. Eternally grateful for the opportunity to work with these two incredible women #SheInspiresMe https://t.co/c8Ckw9v8q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Beach Boys [Pet Sounds] -You Still Believe In Me (Stereo Remaster) https://t.co/AGMr0aj9Sb via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man what if Tyler really got DID and that explains the sudden change. #yonkers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scoring totals for tonight... TOLSIA — 16 17 16 19 = 68: Muncy 25, Mollette 17, Salmons 10, Cantrell 7, Ball 4, Lov… https://t.co/mHZzH7Asol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be pastors like Jesus!  “Shepherd the flock of God that is among you, exercising oversight, not under compulsion, b… https://t.co/WwKDO9cw6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. I completely forgot about this, and just seeing the first image hit me viscerally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are still alive. Act like it. Hearing those words gave me such a grateful mindset this morning. Today is a gi… https://t.co/2eTd6NZVY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need more @JenBrownBooks YA books in my life. Just saying!!! I am still thinking about HATE LIST. About to start listening to TORN AWAY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[STEM, STOP ISOLATING THINGS WITH TERMINOLOGY. MAKE IT ACCESSIBLE TO ALL. NO MORE INFORMATION DESERTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a listen to my friend Alex Winters.  I love her and you will to.  https://t.co/VlZiHerTi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyway if someone you love upsets you and your first reaction is to cut them off without ever bringing up the issue… https://t.co/ojWVgTQ9MH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandondarby @AnnCoulter Yes they came to the port of entry asking for asylum! How would a wall make any difference?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kreager Would like to see cross region play during substate round, a rotation set up before the season or classifi… https://t.co/8Qs3c85TrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not talked about enough: the Lakers don't develop players. They keep buying high (Nash, Dwight). Sorry but I attrib… https://t.co/obrVEOsnfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best scene from catsthemusical @ Hollywood Pantages Theatre https://t.co/m5VRboL6iS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is NOT an easy thing to do! It’s like putting water into the pancake mix...too much and homes and property are… https://t.co/Fdx6yzl24V]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can’t handle reality you should have stayed inside of mom 😂😂😂 - Louise Belcher]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think Robert Kraft should distance himself from the @Patriots right now? Kraft, 77, has been charged with so… https://t.co/vzcmgFLELV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll put a whole welfare check on a nigga head if that’s all I had and a nigga was talking shit across the country.… https://t.co/lPjIsKeppP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markcwebster @AdobeXD Yeah, love it! I use it for all of my projects. I’ll definitely post the prototype links. Ho… https://t.co/x77eZbpFRw]]></document></documents></author>