<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The #Titans have resigned safety Kenny Vaccaro 4-year deal worth $26M and $11.5M guaranteed. #TitanUp MH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richconte With my line of work I can realistically work remotely if a company is willing to accommodate. With tech… https://t.co/mCKsoTSPUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Orlando, FL? View our latest opening: https://t.co/x2bfMW7iix #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willykohan @BancoGalicia Willy amigo deje el chivo q es un hombre serio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I realize how much my friends care about me and it makes me wish I cried.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Americans have very short memories!  They are on the next news cycle! They are on there phones 24-7! They need to f… https://t.co/jHZjm1llIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to use your help site and picked to have someone call me. It ran through message 3 times and hung up on me.… https://t.co/g9MsgclONX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSThisMorning @sethdoane Nothing will change. Only the deck chairs will be rearranged.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FeargusOSull @CityLab Berlin is not re-nationalising anything yet (too bad, in my opinion). In fact, the mayor jus… https://t.co/AULjn8afHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shine. #nofilter #newshoes @ MGM Grand Las Vegas https://t.co/sS5otjJNH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Benow_ @VOLUNTEERS_TN @Orangeblooded17 @jax_persists You’re wasting your breath. He knows you’re right but he’s ne… https://t.co/3cWO7VTEng]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya estuvo con la nieve no? @ Overland Park, Kansas https://t.co/UdSiA0lN5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikThePhotog I feel that pull daily. These&lt;Those https://t.co/LNRkvVe1SI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anchored men's breakfast tomorrow at 8am  Great food, fellowship and a great message from Tuvai Faatai Senior pasto… https://t.co/NzXTj4zWEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeCramer86 @didlibertywin @LibertyMBB @Georgie_126 The still pics to accompany!  Cred: @Ty_J_Davis https://t.co/uM0TKzMGIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm very honored by all the notifications. I read them and all and liked them all. Over a hundred. I love you all a… https://t.co/wdKxmYLuf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/B85HmqLUcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[❄️#SierraNevadaSnowpack and snow water content via @CA_DWR❄️  • 146% of normal statewide for this date (19-Feb-2019… https://t.co/QWWJahQdgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_csweeney_ All in good time. This is still a very new phenomenon for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkTruth3 Not Truth. You’re off the Mark. 33 cars racing inches apart at over 200 miles an hour will not put you to sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Okie569 Yeah, I don't think the non-Q-Anon people are bothered by complicity in "hoax collusion conspiracies." But… https://t.co/vs5hAOqZkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump A perfect example of a Con man.   Distractions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know. The more analytics helps us understand the game, the more we find out we don’t know about hockey.   Hocke… https://t.co/R1YAAlBQIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wreck: traffic is crawling outbound in #NorthwestRaleigh on Glenwood Ave and Lynn Rd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom Why does any real media outlet  give this guy an audience?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump How about taking the kids out of cages before you start some other bullshit that won’t help anyone but you and your family]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAIT WAIT @SugarDunkerton IN @ThisIs_Progress??? LONG overdue! Well deserved! #Chapter84]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jakef311 @kharyp Yeah but other methods are a lot easier to deal with. Someone who has a firearm is far more likel… https://t.co/3lmi36zpad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sorry so many innocent people got followed on my profile - someone has growing up to do #denial #careless #emotionsofarock]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyHicksGOP Socialism: vote your way in, shoot your way out...#Venezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[✂️ #vintagemashups ♻️ #biotech innovations #madeinnyc #newwave #sustainability #bwoodknows @ New York, New York https://t.co/YzfRU13BBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you’re wondering. It’s an American product in Canada with Spanish bilingual writing. In Canada it should be English and French]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews #MarALardAss #traitor #dotard #rapist #usa #russia https://t.co/jWZ89423HW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MufasaEvey Yall need offensive and defense tackles. Take some pressure off of Baker and Miles. But after letting J… https://t.co/Swk0KXayaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HrishiHirway I hate ads, but I understand the need to monetize a podcast. If the ad is something I would be intere… https://t.co/RRs0mS230A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t had any time to go #icefishing this week. I hope I can make it out tomorrow.🎣🕳😁It would be a great way to… https://t.co/0AnkZtyrue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to my angel and Fellow @leadershiptb Class of 2014 graduate Jennifer Noel! I appreciate you and all of yo… https://t.co/mDEDdA519K]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would be dream scenario for the @Lions addressed all needs and get 2 immediate studs on the back half of your… https://t.co/tXPy6fnIMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[So cool to see @NHRA drivers  @MattHagan_FC and @LeahPritchettTF give the command to start engines @LVMotorSpeedway… https://t.co/zTGQKpO5wY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edmondguidry @WAFB I wonder how old that law is (read, I’m too lazy to look it up) and if it’s been used much befo… https://t.co/YcNgPXAJQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel @JamesPMorrison paging Robert Mueller, paging Robert Mueller... might want to look into this too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boyriah That’s right up my alley then. I love wines that put me to sleep for some reason lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh. Can’t help but feel like this is 2016 all over again... https://t.co/UK1XB2jMak]]></document><document><![CDATA[“...online #advertising spending in the U.S. will surpass traditional spending this year, by nearly $20 billion. Th… https://t.co/4SKQkX0DnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is going to hurt to listen to. @BarstoolBigCat @PFTCommenter @PardonMyTake @KVN_03 https://t.co/AHbhyV7AB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElBolitaUruguay tatuarse está bien pero esto es exagerado para mi y eso q yo tengo 10 tatuajes]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY DID I MATCH A TEAM OF 7 ON LEAGUE PLAY ON BLACK OPS 4 @Treyarch @ATVIAssist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnAsplund1 @ScottKuffel @UJHPrincipal @UnitedBand304 @AllensworthDoug @r_dub15 I’ve accepted the challenge from… https://t.co/HfNkbSwo4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RSG_the_Large_1 @TheRealMiggi @WHOISCONWAY @WESTSIDEGUNN @BennyBsf Or am I just old and senile and can't tell s***]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeauStack @GregPor17 Thanks!!! I definitely painted it in that picture! They seem to have it going back in the rig… https://t.co/w6mJ0Gx9oG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMLwhere @Sulliview Help for journalists (and news consumers) from @onthemedia. https://t.co/djGhKOj4eV]]></document><document><![CDATA[El PDI se queda sin candidato, porque Ramfis Trujillo no puede aspirar a ningún cargo https://t.co/Pw77ulUAPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jfh82 Lui, Castaner,  il va laisser une trace de brake  (freinage) dans ses petites culottes!!!😨😨😨😨😨#france 🇫🇷]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dessert make me a band person to eat ice cream? #JustaAverageJoe @ Milk and Wood https://t.co/gwhbrusWkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomoDangelo It's the whole Asian thing -south, East or anywhere Asia 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox news refuse to show this Nazi trailer  CNN, MSNBC to air ad on American Nazis film https://t.co/ZYI1M5q14k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if they ever think about me I wish I could talk to them and tell them I know they would be proud..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ByteMyBits For details on how to enable NVDEC on PLEX, in any docker : https://t.co/85cVe0vEkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ribeyeszn I can’t think of this without thinking of that Jessica Simpson version someone posted yesterday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeunguraKahungi @IsraelUSAforevr Call and response is a core component of virtue signaling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bow2kaos @RepublicanSwine @secupp @TuckerCarlson @lngrahamAngle That picture on the right of @TuckerCarlson is abo… https://t.co/YOp4cIpYY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you shut down for the day, take a moment to write down the first thing you want to accomplish tomorrow. This c… https://t.co/ukYnsUvilx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews No the left is obsessed with race and sex and gender is on the right could really give a shit about… https://t.co/NgH6sSW7Pi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously.  You don't go to Madison in February for the soup.  He's building his grassroots army in Wisconsin to in… https://t.co/txM1BQg8N5]]></document><document><![CDATA[These boys hit the ground running when they officially got on campus and I couldn’t be more proud of the work y’all… https://t.co/kjjfaj6kDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManonGuggenheim @Wanita1 It may. It is holding on right now. The admitting Dr was not treating my pain well so I a… https://t.co/QRY2H7C7eG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LolOverruled So we're led to believe Bernie definetly seems to get under the skin of many of the entrenched establishment Good for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson Well he will no longer have to wander the streets at 2 am in search of a golden throaty! One will be provided!]]></document><document><![CDATA[People don’t mean what they say. Like in my experience “Im sorry”, usually means “Im mad you found out and I want y… https://t.co/0Jv4ThekDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotWithAnybody @jonahloeb @JustaRussianbot @jdavidgoodman @onesarahjones Not 3b annually]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's definitely a show-off. @ Walla Walla, Washington https://t.co/3jutQin2Sw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NAPARacing @chaseelliott Had a sweet run there too.  Might of had a top 5.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your mom finally give you back your DSi after throwing it when you lost in Mario Kart https://t.co/DkOmVGNrnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JynxLucky @The_VaughnWolff @sophiehen1 @Dayton_Dallas @CupcakeSinclair @CaringErin @thick_simone @SubStasia95 Yes!! https://t.co/RHAoAYs78V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods The left doesn’t seem to notice that all the hate and evil that they so quickly accuse Trump suppor… https://t.co/lZ6gXBGocK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha. In this video this guy is bench pressing and a lady pulls her pants down and moons him, he turns his head lik… https://t.co/nAO4NJjnGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[peep all of us from @NECAinNorwalk in the 3rd pic at Camp Explore!!! ABSOLUTELY beaming with #PTECHPride right now!… https://t.co/62TQgksbOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonCZacher @tammy Check out Mother Jones article today about the owner of the massage parlor where Kraft got cau… https://t.co/euwPJZvba6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Revoyons le contenu... Mais tout comme le cours de sexualité, ce n’est pas parce qu’on en parle pas, que ça n’exist… https://t.co/f67eE95yRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You, your Vice President, your press secretary, and Russ are all a damn joke!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathygriffin @karaswisher I agree Jack should resign. I got my account frozen for using some nasty words against N… https://t.co/H2yuTzC4aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cindynorth1 @EvilCEOE I read through her Twitter. She sounds bipolar. When the history of Twitter is written it wi… https://t.co/Cql0UhgHYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just can’t to go crash out, because I wanna sleep and forgot what it was like to stay up hours boozing. I’m tired of all that👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MZHemingway @realDonaldTrump Maybe the realize the gig is up?  Donald’s crimes are catching up with him.  Good luck]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡ Viva, no importa él o ella, que se auto proclame cacique de su propia tribu !  Si las tribus de indígenas europeo… https://t.co/HVxQCCOV9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_MegMuckleBones @bodgei @tgshepherdvan @angelt18 @LetsTalkTigra Omg too many good choices]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hillsPHresh Lol it was creepy how clear it was. And I usually forget my dreams]]></document><document><![CDATA[While my fiancé and I were drinking, we had maybe 1-2 drinks an hour and stopped after 2-3 hrs. I felt as though we… https://t.co/dgCWnsMpQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to spend time with @_jross8 and the good folks at @ClemsonFB. Their defense of the NC officially begins this week. #ALLIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans @BillyTolley @travelchannel That closing sequence in the lock-in was just nuts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrat narrative is that is bots or Russians. Its democrats and social media's way of justifying shutting down co… https://t.co/CSzn6u0fhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AyannaPressley @OversightDems The road to Hell is paved with good intentions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buchausen @creaturelives33 You got to work for it. Or,talk about how horny you are all day. 2 million followers the next week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime @ChrisCuomo He has never appeared more impotent than he did in the Rose Garden today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is yet another place where the #indiegaming community is helping to keep #gaming alive, and why they deserve our support.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jthake @vibronet @matvelloso FindTime is THE single best thing. Ever. It is very sad that this hasn't been focused on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qué país, o países, debieran ser parte de esa intervención? Ud está dispuesto a estar en la 1ra línea de combate? T… https://t.co/IfUQNkAR3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha it’s absurd. They should test this athlete’s vertical, 20yd shuttle and 40yd dash, perform this movement for 1… https://t.co/Mkfrn8dATd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantasias when i see you just came on and literally only 2 people in here know the words smh y’all suck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamHayesMTG @shevanel_mtg Buzzfeed’s business model makes infinitely more sense to me these days, even if it’s infuriating]]></document></documents></author>