<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[had a random ass dream that i was back in HS and there was a whole ass line to be dress code approved in order to g… https://t.co/XuIHLGTWrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes when I wake up in the morning I just want to be a soft, cuddly, little kitty cat but then I remember all… https://t.co/pLX97MJNAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bethenny The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel on Amazon and A Million Little Things on ABC, so different but worth each and e… https://t.co/djzhqc6B1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a thing about cows lately!! Well I am from INDIANA!! https://t.co/V9PlfN3rB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team fun and still getting the job done 🎯 #G496 @Target #WorkSomewhereYouLove ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[women who love The Bachelor have no problem cheating/getting cheated on &amp; that’s facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kamaribis @PhilippeReines Heck yes. We will have to rent out an entire town🥃🍺🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen Whitehouse Floor Speech On The Green New Deal 02/14/19 https://t.co/RdcqVvnY8c via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoTV @Andy I think you need to have @DVF in every episode going forward]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pedicure, manicure and eye brow wax! #splurge #workingonmeboo #purpleismyfavaoritecolor https://t.co/eY3JR0KfWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cj_spinks @SharonCarbine @Bornabrit1 @jojake111 @WhiteHouse That was disgusting. Giving someone our nation's highe… https://t.co/PZ0MO4122F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok @JoeBiden now is the time! We need you!! Please run!! #NeverBernie #NeverTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisHarrisJr @TheMalikJackson Yes!!! That’s what I said too😉🐐🧡💙come on @johnelway @Broncos  let’s do this!! https://t.co/PMWQPZLlnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sillywithsad Mine are still at my parents, except my senior yearbook pic.  I shared it for one of those challenges… https://t.co/AXCV6O0wNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, ok, I did get a bit beside myself this past Monday with (@Drake 😅)...but uh the REALITY is that, thee ONLY ONE… https://t.co/k8YzIB2ECC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outside of the house after they passed universal background checks.  With Rep Luci McBath who son Jordan was murder… https://t.co/S4Cwl5yjlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not depressed or anything but everytime I look at how much weight I gained I get sad 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mncities will be on Capitol Hill on Wednesday meeting w/our delegation. So far meetings confirmed w/@SenTinaSmith,… https://t.co/9uxiCBhH2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to that with the @MBTA_CR fare hikes proposed for this summer - Zone 8 is $25 more a month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just felt the need to share a PSA with my world-traveling hubby to never do this. Anyone posts him in his boxers on… https://t.co/nNK1laqiVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Surfermom77 @MaryThibodeau9 Buy the book or get the https://t.co/jjyIx8sXir's all about the real Obama,a liar.Mill… https://t.co/p4I48bIok1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mchugh_dana @mysteriousdays Seriously! I’m going to Buffalo next weekend to see @Hozier with @brittanyelle2 and we… https://t.co/z70GRuvKgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tulsa also has several witchy magic shops that sell everything from crystals and candles to straight-up voodoo doll… https://t.co/EY9PDJ1WFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatBarrell #SolidarityInStaches #DontFWithMyF #FightForWynonna #WynonnaEarp 💪🏼✊🏼✊🏼💪🏼👨🏻❤️ https://t.co/IYTkGZArJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissGFY Some people are so dumb/immature and should not be allowed to breathe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rajendra_2908 @MissLacyLennon @ladylynnxxx @AlishaRydes @Scarlet645 @YouLoveHelenaP @MsBonniemodel… https://t.co/oLcM7voO17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todos somos #Venezolanos #VenezuelaQuierePaz #VenezuelaLibre #VeneuelaAidLive https://t.co/sKL73cFmrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 days!!! Can’t wait to sail the Caribbean and sink my toes in the sand! #flashbackfriday #cruise @ Indiana https://t.co/aUyiYxOrtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#aussieposse with @AngelaBishop #foxafterparty #oscars #winners #bohemianrhapsody #thefavourite @ The Hollywood Ath… https://t.co/ikdqqMMwsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my Mom @MlottLynne!  For those that don't know, my Mom is an AMAZING #Vocal #Coach! She's now the ISSA… https://t.co/mGH08l7QNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do we have the right to lament in a time of plenty? New post on the blog today! - The Art of Taleh https://t.co/t3wUiKGXJU via @dr_reyes2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this confirmed? Bc i need to know..... this is important lol. #callicecube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck Either that or he’ll be checking into rehab for fill in the blank __________ reason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[f@ck you, winter.  i win. @ Willow Glen, San Jose, California https://t.co/F1kHGzSO0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[no one wanted to go out to dinner but i  made everyone go w me to el cerro bc i had a gift card and forgot to pay w the gift card]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP Why are Republicans not in the least bit concerned about a president who secretly negotiated a deal with… https://t.co/y0UHiHOKfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadie had space &amp; astronomy club today (@ KTEC West in Kenosha, WI) https://t.co/YvbY7db8Es]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would be that one Mexican with a sore throat and no tequila to take a shot out of 🤦🏻‍♂️🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[100 more wins since freshman year??? dang this man is for real the goat!!! Congrats Coach Rob, you definitely mean… https://t.co/Mk5Q3f45LL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The nation will pay a price for the oppression of the Palestinians. https://t.co/kGYGFXRSN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ghostdu59 @megitsunejinja @sayvooplay @kitsune_pac @A_thrash3 @Xicho2 @MoonfireLark @TAIMETAL_de @krmanic… https://t.co/YKXNLsjXj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smickable Funny you liked this @GraemeManson1 because you picked me up at the airport multiple times and well, you… https://t.co/mMEzD4ZQ2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd ride out to Quakertown but it gets dark early and only like 5 black people live there]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Shenanigans #Shenanigans #Shenanigans #Shenanigans #Shenanigans #Shenanigans #Shenanigans #Shenanigans… https://t.co/BxAaOcYiKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidRockMe @EllaBella200 @AmyBonaduce @ceoaetnews @ginger71111 @GhislaineExell @TheIncredibleDC @MsTraci4… https://t.co/xvM9mCNjDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dnicoleee @BrandynJose I don’t work until Saturday but idk when I leave yet I’ll let you know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Just_Becca @ja_pollino Make sure you bring wegmans bags or something though!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikaylabreann27 For reals. I’ve been looking at lens and other cameras that are smaller to carry for every day stu… https://t.co/taXTqTYZtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta Pay my taxes, Tithe, pay off all my bills, take my family on a beautiful vacation, give generously to Some v… https://t.co/iU5nCKFgoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who said referees couldn’t be glamorous?! @nyxcosmetics #nyxcontourpalette @bhcosmetics #takemebacktobrazil #drag… https://t.co/aE81LU6FaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[would never wanna be with someone who has me around just bc they don’t like to be alone.........  you’re not comfor… https://t.co/ubzK0I96Ke]]></document><document><![CDATA[An extremely hard thing for most women to do - this is perhaps the greatest lesson I’m learning from the #water ind… https://t.co/pal2Koyekj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wolframbrandon @NazmiAlbadawi @rosiedoll54 He was so, so nice! Showed us a picture from his honeymoon at Harry Potter World.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So grateful to @Trust_Films for the filming and producing this DVD 👣💕👣 #reflexologylymphdrainage… https://t.co/jjKrTP1acf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wine0nymph i’m so sorry baby. wishing you quick recovery. are they giving you anything to assist the cyst?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great morning of service with First Step! @ First Step, Inc https://t.co/RUISmnSfpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Louder, please, for the people in the back!!!!! Safe storage is 100% on the gun owner! Lock. Up. Your. Guns. People… https://t.co/tQjnZaqPbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawnt @ClarenceHouse @fmwales Thank you.  I actually think I get it...sort of 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you go on a date w/ a guy and he really enjoys himself and laughs at all your jokes that is how you know he ha… https://t.co/8UqWmbuFkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please excuse my loud mouth! Yep that’s my girl!😍 #goowls #1ksu  #thatsmileispriceless #backandbetter… https://t.co/OwCYa0jSZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jim Jordan is a jerk. Talk about grandstanding!! Does he think he's auditioning for starring role in the Trump Story?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You’re not a snack, you’re a full course meal. I just want you to know that” 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE HAVE BEEN WORKING ON THIS VIDEO FOR THE BLUE WAVE TWITTER FOLLOWERS, ALL DAY, AND ALL NIGHT, WITH SHORT BREAKS,… https://t.co/DvHCcXNAZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iowa western was only fun freshman year 16-17 year.. that shit looks depressing now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShakaylaRisati @naisha_lal @BTS_twt You got me on the screenshot 💜💚💜 ☺️👏 congratulations 1B for Hobi 💜💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[No mms porque nunca me puedo dormir temprano como una persona normal?!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drdididiva @vgallassio @SIBOD31 @District31R @SGreeneD31 #truth #SIstrongertogether #InspireD31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@old_osc @SpeakerPelosi @SenFeinstein @KamalaHarris @tedlieu @SenSchumer @TheDemocrats @DNC @dccc Pelosi is a maste… https://t.co/pqaduU6fPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@intactive @VioletVampire2 @CarterSteinhoff @zaaitir @eunice_pickett @Kommonsense7 Our son was born with these grow… https://t.co/dkag81DwIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men gotta love who they are before they want to love a woman. They drown in their own problems. #ClearlyPersonal 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisamurkowski Illegal immigration IS A CRISIS and you should be voting with President Trump and NOT WITH THE DEMOC… https://t.co/OUXTq36VMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah Ima start getting my lashes done again. I just don’t wanna pay for that 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are quoting Rush Limbaugh, who has torn you up the last few months, lol, but nonetheless, you… https://t.co/XNs4jpxHZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are a citizen, why do you have to fight for your Civil Rights? -- James Baldwin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stinakayy You can sing really good the first time I heard you I said wow she really sings good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anslemasylum @ChaucerKate @GarcysFlereal Thank you.  You are such a beautiful and subtle writer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be really great and appreciated if internships would respond to my emails...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t mommy .... Says “ I’m too hungry to move 😝” #froggylegsdodo 👿🍤👶🏻🐸 #DoDo #dodothemaltese #spoileddodo… https://t.co/J65nzj0lLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up watching my news crew!!! Hate when I get up on weekends and they are not there.... Lol @FOXNashville… https://t.co/zclxa1D00S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yea- you should just hammer 🔨 the nail in the coffin of your league @MLL_Lacrosse! While @PremierLacrosse partners… https://t.co/Z3JOI3cco4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimySemsem @PucciaPatrizia @ElbaklySami @enriqueiglesias @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @zetakaty @janaplauen… https://t.co/UGxzU3WH45]]></document><document><![CDATA[and privately own and trade in means of production, a class of workers willing to sell their labour power for a liv… https://t.co/KnsJn5z5xG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cada día estoy más convencida que cuando alguien se va de tu vida(hablando de amistades y relaciones amorosas), sie… https://t.co/uAUs8VyAjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Run_Kiwi_Run @RunnerMarky @caitpilk @KellyKKRoberts @oiselle https://t.co/003aufjp1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when I thought I couldn’t love @NKOTB any harder..... #TheBoysInTheBand takes it to a whole new level #NKOTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else wonder when Beanie Babies are going to be worth something??]]></document><document><![CDATA[We made it!!  Officially on vacation baby!  #floridaorbust #beachbum #lovemysunshine #vacationmode @ Anastasia Stat… https://t.co/hFfjIbwqAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are really simple. Be asking the stupidest questions. You’ve seen me for YEARS without make up. Once-in-a-bl… https://t.co/9gLgSeC3lp]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's your favorite color?? Can you guess what mine is....? . 💜 ✨ 💜 ✨ "Be uniquely you. Stand out. Shine. Be color… https://t.co/PKQe55A74y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggicarter @marypgkeating @StanleyCohenLaw Truth encompasses all. Religion, spirit and science. Truth is that tha… https://t.co/d8a9Co4Lkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[God really looked out for me, I got the same parking spot I left at 11 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoodMorning (@ The Forbidden Forrest in Hogwarts, VA w/ @bryan_warren) https://t.co/DTE8l0q8Y8 https://t.co/8S38jVKevZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many disabled Walmart greeters are being replaced by what they now call 'customer hosts,' - This is just not right… https://t.co/islBETQ0PG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so gonna get in trouble lol I’m giving Blanca cookies rn because she keeps telling me “rosa, yo quiero atole” 😂… https://t.co/u9SF2mONol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Birthday #Tiramisu #TerraMooMoo @ Louisville, Kentucky https://t.co/XdHWkuAgeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeiaJones1 Dude I actually just laughed bc that sounds WACK “ yo I got my new pen let’s go try it out “]]></document><document><![CDATA[If things don't work out, we'll just get an annulment and on to the next. We can look at human sexual relationships… https://t.co/RVgFNurNO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Digital urban panels” — term for real time clocks. I think. #ltrainshutdown #ltrainslowdown @cbsix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yesmam47 @joncoopertweets @Ricka168 Must have been sold a lemon at one time, by one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fun lil tb I stumbled upon #BirdcageSM #sara_hindman https://t.co/Y7OnCX0Mmr https://t.co/HPPHBmiH0D]]></document></documents></author>