<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@sledskillz I don't even remember watching the 2nd GGG-Canelo fight. Sure I did, but couldn't guess as to when or w… https://t.co/jegIKveKJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lotsofuss @TheRickWilson Another Trump rep. Saying there’s no lie, when there is proof of one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paula_White @Paula_White Hey🙋...Good Morning and Happy Monday! Hope you and @TheJonathanCain had a nice weekend. P… https://t.co/NfM7CSVmgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just pulled a 60k MT shoe from a triple threat throw back pack ,😀 https://t.co/q2YUZUAQY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jbird4203 Whew! It kicked my butt too!  I slept through my alarms the next morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeFernandez @daddymention How'd you guess? But I promise I didn't have any of that fancy tequila, which I'm blanking on the name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dang90 @102minus2 @valorousman @b4tsandB4lls @Bored_Anterieur @steve_vladeck @AOC There is a difference between yo… https://t.co/v8ugASKXKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump For months Fake News was Russia Russia Russia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlie_adler @realDonaldTrump Damn Charlie!! I mean you nailed it perfectly but damn!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“‘I can start back from zero. I’m willing to rebuild my house, factory and cars,’” he told them, Eid recalled. “‘No… https://t.co/uGKC1NBEpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see Joe Andoe tonight and 20 years of his work @ Almine Rech Gallery - New York https://t.co/GVutHsTNH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chocolate Mudslide with a Pecan Pie Moonshine Floater #chocalatemudslidefloater  #awsomenessoverload💁 @ NRG Stadium https://t.co/6eqNAFBG04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino what are your thoughts on making police cruisers bulletproof? So if a suspect arrested for a crime people… https://t.co/Q9ZR7km2L9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sixers-#Warriors observations: Mistakes, poor execution down stretch doom #Philly again https://t.co/nCc1WLhjFC via @phillydotcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[In great company in this re-released article. Tips by @ExerciseXPERT, @FindYourVictory @jarilove @tamalyoga… https://t.co/tzO9nLFFUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlobalDisabilit @Forbes Check out my new article @Forbes https://t.co/ezkYHM1Xvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bocasgray in Vegas you could go to all the Residentsy shows at 17 and 18.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Theoretically there is a videotape of a 3-year-old Reuby on the back porch of our house in Silver Spring, Maryland… https://t.co/Hy9V8yqHEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teresagross625 @specialtechie This can be done through Google Sites for free...]]></document><document><![CDATA[And down goes another one!!! “Alternative Transcript” Love the audience reaction. #TrumpCrimeFamily #FactsMatter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any other time this would have been treason why are these people not being prosecuted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your reaction when you’re having a spirited conversation about sports and the other person pulls out “who has more… https://t.co/Inz9iybd6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Classic free market economics. Adapt to change quickly in order to survive and thrive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phil_osborne @davidsirota Voting record from left/helping the most americans, to right/helping corporations: berni… https://t.co/ueKfptoEGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My physical health cannot continue to go through this. I need to go home and be away from this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Littlestown senior Carl Harris brings home his first D-3 title with a 7-4 win at 170 pounds. @LtownAthletics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all been doing these teachers wrong for years and they finally sick of it huh? Serves you right. Maybe if you sup… https://t.co/oA8j6c4Q9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost there. IMPEACH RASHIDA TLAIB - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/aZGuxgL9zb via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexpiersonAMP Did you notice Goodale is introducing the pot amnesty legislation today? Gee they’re not trying to… https://t.co/bxPI6062Rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chubs_mckenzie I was just tired. Came home and crashed! lol Sort aisle was cool, bulk belt on the other hand had C… https://t.co/JKXvrg8Kfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samuel is just another confused Liberal who can't understand; Hillary was a Righteously Flawed Candidate !  #Hello]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yassminelopezz Mannn they be lying to us 🤧 shit gon change overnight 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you ever wish you could go back in time when everything was simple.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standards and open source: Why are patents treated differently? https://t.co/6U2MuMa2Gc via @opensourceway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MylesSuer #CIOChat A3: Have predefined tasks to be accomplished with a pool of iterns - need to have a sense of ac… https://t.co/sCnaW8zCi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4gb4 I am ok with Fitz.   My point is I want that type of quarterback. A veteran who will be OK with being the backup. Just like Matt was.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Providing an update is @ConsumersEnergy VP Guy Packard with @WOODTV @LeonHendrix @_HeatherWalker]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you pray for rain you must be able to play in the mud! https://t.co/x62f2j0ZMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nj1015 @JonBramnick He should stay away from The airport in San Francisco. Eggs and cheese sandwich was $14. I’ll pass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canalvivaco @voxfractal @FullKnifeCol @AJRua @TanaVallejo @ATAQUEDEPNICO3 @aterciopelados @estadoalterado… https://t.co/sApU8x0uV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sesnyderleb @letsgovcu1 @CoachRhoades @jd23byers Looking like @EricMaynor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMaZaKuR @GFuelEnergy @TheScoopie @Ziytex These are great! Let’s me get you squared away with a discount or some… https://t.co/6QZyQDRexc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcspocky @LunaLuvgood2020 @Rey_Sistance @lfkraus @TrinityResists @B52Malmet @TrisResists @DebbieDoesTwitt… https://t.co/4FwUB1Kzxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFANmornings @steelers @KyleKrajewski never thought I'd ever call a radio show...but felt I needed to make amends… https://t.co/XJ0dWyjVZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Banner_18_Soon @Crack3rJax19 @ZachNagel7 Grady is 305. Was 299 at the combine. Olive weighed in at 287.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BanjoPope I have my Earthquake Detector around the corner at the local bar. He has shown me how to stay calm cool… https://t.co/4SrygAj9Rc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite a slight slowdown, @LinkedInEcon considers @CityofPhoenixAZ an emerging market for #tech talent in… https://t.co/a2LDV8Haxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice @AuburnSuper on conducting The Liberty Bell March tonight at the All-City Band concert!! https://t.co/aDdhEN451E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate these times when inspiration is as distant as the moons of Jupiter...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaOtten @mrBobbyBones I for one have NEVER called it that and never will. Say the full name or don’t eat it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColemanESPN “See, The way I got my bank account set up, there’s a checking and a savings....” -AAF Leadership]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timkaine It's official.  "Bishops Rebuke Catholic Sen. Tim Kaine for Voting for Infanticide: "Appalling" Lack of "Basic Human Decency""]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swimdad61 We Tee off in Sarasota @ 10:30.  Come on up &amp; we’ll have several cold ones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StLouisTraffic @MoDOT_StLouis @MoDOT needs to address the Westbound merge onto I-64/40 at Hampton. People don’t kn… https://t.co/rBD1rrMApG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrileywx @PaigeDavide So glad we all made it out safely! So thankful to be a part of the WCBI Weather team today! 🌪]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is  how it feels when ur feeling those hurt feelings https://t.co/uoBK6v9caP]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's our MENTALITY? A "Connected Mentality" #TheWesleyanWay #TeamWesleyan #BishopPride #BishopNation #brotherhood… https://t.co/2X85jVOmPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The orange man with strange fake hair, who if given a chance would fellate himself, calls someone else a weirdo. Hmm. Ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Mr. @RobDorans, who has faithfully served on our Recreation and Parks Commission.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murphdogg29 @JLBarrow Wall papering music!! But you know you felt it when J. Lo said "R.U.L.E." 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidYankovich @Alyssa_Milano McConnell doesn't want an anti-bribery bill. Neither does the Groper in Chief. If th… https://t.co/mmBDWunSQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IslaDeViva @Gulyona А вот этот момент зависит уже только от тебя и делегировать его не получится 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Underrated player in Izzo’s first two seasons. @raywear5 shot .412 from deep from 1995-97 and defended well at the… https://t.co/d2LOCyyVu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch is coming to an end on this night of overtime... #MakingThatMoney 💵💵💵💰 #WorkTimeBullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaEnica @vanessaleinani @FOX10Phoenix The jaguar was just defending its home. Does the zoo have a stand your ground law for the animals?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhunted1957 @tonyposnanski @realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter Zero of those folks are under investigation by the feds an… https://t.co/9cMkGKKPXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Youngsters on the Air Bulgarian Camp  https://t.co/oSMt1AMPlp  #ham #hamr #amateurr #amateurradio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Andrade_ @coachfully22 @TheAcornSports @achs_scorpions @Scorp_Baseball @ScorpAthleticBC @svhspioneers… https://t.co/CQhY9g3Fym]]></document><document><![CDATA[36 Hours in #Goa https://t.co/w26azI7tAu #India #StudyAbroad #EducationAbroad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericgrant I’ve heard! I need to experience more Hulu originals! I tend to get stuck on Netflix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout-out and thanks again @ladyke1987 keshawn for supporting #FiyaFlava @ Starwood Court Park https://t.co/fI2S8aSHjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAndyKatz @CalMBBall @UW_MBB @pac12 @marchmadness Do you think Washington is still a lock to make the tournament?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBC @guardian @nytimes @postpolitics @maddow @vicenews @RepAdamSchiff @davidfrum @sltrib @SenSchumer @PBS @ABC… https://t.co/WVEesuByBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game of Thrones definitely one of the best shows on television. Can’t wait til April]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner Somebody impeach already and end the madness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLos @allhailmswantz I figured you should know your crush's real / fake name...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackhunter74 @RepThomasMassie Why did you vote against the anti-Islam and anti-antisemitism bill?]]></document><document><![CDATA[4th time seeing @Malaamusic and man you get better everytime look forward to see you again soon 🔥💥😈#MyConversationIsCashMoney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @MjrCitiesChiefs @MCSheriffs You don’t love anyone except yourself - well and maybe Ivanka!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Absolutely agree with you POTUS WINS FOR AMERICA NOT FOR POLITICAL REASONS!! However I will vote for TRUMP again in 2020.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE CROSS(n)Itself IS INTEL AS aBinary Code of(1s_+_"0s")..4(Masculine+Femi(nine),(X+Y)(A+Z)ions..2=A(ten)..4THE1"0… https://t.co/ycizRDj7m3]]></document><document><![CDATA[KHANS NEEDS TO EXPAND OUT OF THE VALLEY AND REPLACE GHENGIS GRILL NATION WIDE!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s called satire.  Comedians get together to spoof government stupidity.  Historically, both parties were subject… https://t.co/5PucqDhvgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to pull a fast one and convince all the EDM kids going upstairs to pay for our show downstairs instead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be playing a short session at Talking Stick in AZ today from 1:30pm - 4:30pm. Attending a bachelor party in Sc… https://t.co/xjBEnVFU2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clepublicpower maybe put the trouble dispatch number in your bio. Or is that also supposed to be a fun game for us… https://t.co/PGNgoL5LZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deposit is paid...I'm getting tattooed by Ganji at @threetides in a few weeks https://t.co/RPmXdrIfRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @LindaSuhler The #Democrat wet dream. #SocializedMedicine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or maybe there’s one on every D&amp;D world. Spurt of Krynn. Spurt of Faerûn. Spurt of Athas. #wotcstaff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reynamadelayne Muy buenos días Reyna y feliz jueves tengas tu también saludos cordiales y cuídate mucho,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch The real collusion was the dems and the Ukrainians.  For as much great work that JW has done you guy… https://t.co/iZYGVJgkXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This so crazy to me cuz I remember when ppl used to keep sex quiet, like what happened to being Lowkey??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kittenwithawhip So true. I’m always using the weird mirrors over the desk that’s close to a oversized chair. That… https://t.co/h4CqpVrwbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sequencer16 @misspunk63 @amory_miller @Ramtheramman @RN_JB7 @bethtcoast @Alan13778263 @BundyGP @Birdle_2963… https://t.co/KUXWM4MvjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themikemancini No Mike. I’m not. I should’ve said some people. You’re good with me. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dantej21 Whoa this is actually insane. I get that they’re not stopping because of how slick it is, but it looks li… https://t.co/c2let9f1pk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerwallach @jorgecmoran U both look awesome! Liking the speedos , Do I really have to say "Enjoy" ? Lol 😜🌴🐚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeutrinoAlismi2 @katemshepherd @tedwheeler “We’re against fascism so when riot and attack the local gov’t, you need to suck it up. Cuz fa.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems mullah Omar has a new endorsement David Duke She's well on her way to a presidential nomination 1 day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ask_Spectrum My Twitter handle is my name. I have been in your system since 2002. Not really feeling valued as a l… https://t.co/XEiyWMQBeo]]></document></documents></author>