<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KevinOGarrett ‘s #hoax album out  in 21 days. Let the countdown begin! 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in a ride share that is a minivan and we’re listening to CDs so that’s where my morning is at]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The Whos don’t have a special movie because they’re only defined by the tragedy of The Grinch.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone truly did a remarkable job helping my mom with her Bitmoji. I have a little cartoon mom now! https://t.co/02BHReodpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[To Kill A Mockingbird - all the feels, just as relevant today as ever. Thank you denisezeee for being the best thea… https://t.co/SNQGqyBQ0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heartrunnergirl I understand the frustration. I've had two cardiac ablations, on and off beta-blockers for years,… https://t.co/UQjvtBxAcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I have a procedure tomorrow to repair the damage to a blood vessel caused by the failed drain placement attempt.… https://t.co/FRt4LtZL7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone opened a cookie dough shop next to my house this is going to be a problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stayed within my calorie budget for most of February. Gained a pound. Clothes don’t fit any better. Not giving up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First FX routine of the night to Black Skinhead. The floor music that won’t die. #NCAAGym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TarynDeVere @beannfatale @Lady_FMP My understanding is it is a little more complicated. The words ‘Parental aliena… https://t.co/apUeCnG1w7]]></document><document><![CDATA[🧬🔥🧬 PART 2🔥🧬🔥  Had to SPIT a #PopShitChallenge in OT.  Salute to @1BounceCTB “A NIGGAZ LATE with the SHIT POP. Like… https://t.co/WbscVyyAt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mountain View Chamber of Commerce Celebration of Leaders event! (at @ComputerHistory Museum in Mountain View, CA) https://t.co/nDmMwFWmfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex_nman @AnankesReich I had heard of this book when I was young as I read the greats, "A Tale of Two Cities", Mo… https://t.co/Mf0eOq5Ach]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gas I used to drive to Plato’s Closet cost more than the $2.45 they gave me for a $70 top 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vol_Hoops I still love you! It was a bad night, bound to happen! Better now than in March! 🍊🏀🧡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited for Play on Words SJ today @sjmusart ! This was the very first live drawing I attempted two shows ago. Usin… https://t.co/DNcxvjAqjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justjus713 @wearefrenship @GLADESMUSIC Oohhh it’s at The Fine Line... I’m in!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah Kong crossed 15K. Time 01:47:10, pace 12:08 min/mile, est. finish 8:14 am https://t.co/ukzH8jQiWd #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my cousin be having the weirdest convos 😂😂 bitch asked me "how do you start off phone sex" 🤣🤣🤣🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to find the UN General Assembly Hall for the #CSW63  Opening Session? Follow the Beautifully dressed women.… https://t.co/KM9KcsU0WI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks God for sending his only son Jesus so we may have this precious gift! ✝️🙏🏼♥️ @ Oconto Falls, Wisconsin https://t.co/fckkHugXKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent 3 months in the Pediatric ICU Unit at @OHSUDoernbecher back in 2001. In other words, yes. This is a mandatory… https://t.co/82bvPpsIrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manager Lip Sync battle happening today... #sneakpeek #teamstorm✌🏽🎤🎬 @sm547kATT @aprilboiser @bigyak67… https://t.co/BXyaMjGipS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @startrekcbs and especially @msmiakirshner, I don’t think I can explain how exciting it is to see the characte… https://t.co/OyNzCLxH4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much for going to bed early 🤦🏼‍♀️ just getting to bed now lmao. Tonight was so fun tho!! Just played cards with… https://t.co/xjcZem89WX]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's going on in Olmsted Falls??? Is this like the 3rd homicide this year?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Hey Judes did it! We cycled, sweated and raised a bunch of $$ for @StJude!! #RideForAReason  #stjudeheroes… https://t.co/WbAnPGxKxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cryptidgirI The vvitch was one of the worst movies I’ve ever seen &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @AbbyWall29!!! Can’t wait to see you this summer! Make it a good day!!😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @wellsh40 @BreitbartNews Mad about being a loser that she was in 2016!  It’s the big thing now to say… https://t.co/l9OhhjS2fy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Josef let me down on @MLSFantasy this week. 😒 Any suggestions on a week 2 captain?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, time to find out where Jay’s jealousy burst came from. #ExOnTheBeach #EOTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelloPeterNYC #JetBlue also has a partnership... anytime we use Lyft we earn air miles😊 #JetBlue &amp; #Lyft rocks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Writing an APA, 6 page paper in 4 hours and getting a 100% on it is probably my biggest accomplishment]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re the person who filmed the girl attempting suicide on campus yesterday afternoon and then posted it online, eat shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am in desperate need of a bit of dental floss. But alas, I have none and am fated to fiddle this seed from my lef… https://t.co/4DaFs8UlnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobChristie11 That is such a rare animal. Beautiful but I wouldn’t want to get too close.  Wonder how many there are in the world,]]></document><document><![CDATA[This clip of the last minute of “Dyin’” from the Friday nite Opry has eased my Sunday spring Blues.  #Gravy got the… https://t.co/IdKlKsnkSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I want to see Melanie’s Papers too!!  How did she acquire the Visa she got? And while we’re at it let’s see Tr… https://t.co/WiJvbmbkzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightOwlStuff @h3h3productions But I’m also at 16 year old girl who doesn’t know shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neonbumble Wehhhhh what a good boiiiii. I feel this way about Quinn all the damn time. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think ordering me a new pair of earrings will help boost my mood a lil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@s402river @RealJamesWoods Amen to that.  If you give an idiot enough rope she will gang herself!   Praying that th… https://t.co/gRcHDXIefZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaciMichele23 so glad we got to see you guys 💗💗 can’t wait to see y’all this weekend!! 🧁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyIsAmazing @kayyharper8 @Bharper3407 @Phillies He got a record breaking deal from @Dodgers not Phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrRFernandez When it goes well, one of my favorite procedures. To quote Lion King, “Simple, yet satisfying.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RavennaBlog helicopter in the neighborhood right now...anyone know why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I freaked out about the hartz shampoo and quickly went to get my dog a new brand of shampoo and came back with a ne… https://t.co/XMcfwVkpdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[chloe grace moretz is the worst actress on planet earth holy shit i cannot cringe enough]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiromuWonBOSJ25 One can only hope. Naito looked defeated in that interview.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having postpartum/prenatal depression is hard on the kid but just gotta push through]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elfcosmetics @NyxCosmetics @bhcosmetics @MorpheBrushes @KATVONDbeauty @COVERGIRL @LOrealParisUSA  these all the ma… https://t.co/EZBx4WHGu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Zeus scratches on the door and begs to come sleep with me 😩 how can I say no]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday: frazzled. Tuesday: sick. Wednesday: third time’s a charm?? https://t.co/f4LxxCFd1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dead sound like me, remember when you said i sounded like this @BigPlayKae 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WhoWoreItBest? wearing Cal swag with the #clapbackqueen👑 @katskiles #ucberkeley #management #entrepreneurship… https://t.co/vR7P4fzzbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[So after listening to the asshats in the Republican seats make @MichaelCohen212 repeat over and over that he’s made… https://t.co/NHEQ6uPC75]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabsNGripes Oh man. I’m so sorry. Cancer is horrible and I wouldn’t wish it on anyone. Please take care of yourself. Also, #FuckCancer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleMsBiddi @politico @MalcolmNance What kind of massage parlors is he opening? Like the one Kraft was caught in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Nothing is inherently a “right”. We get to decide. So if we want healthcare to be a right it can be.… https://t.co/SvJbkl5VS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok but the wildest bit is that she recognized me! before she said hi and we confirmed! because, as everyone says, I… https://t.co/YcL1AN5UBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DDFGhostHunting @logicked @Isethoriginal @OJungell Every book is research]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of Drew. He made the Freshman baseball team! #OnceACard #2 #GritAndHardwork https://t.co/Vqp0SIf4Xz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfMJCleveland These Illinois bills HB2495 and HB2467 will make Illinois the SLAUGHTER CAPITAL of the U.S.  I am… https://t.co/pWTXNdOM2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wef @JuliaLuscombe Would like to work there if they dont have age/race/gender descrimination]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it possible I get 3 more quality followers today? I've never asked before. Feels weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[En fait hier je me suis dit ça va pousser comme des batards et en fait y avait tellement de gamins que c’était tota… https://t.co/NYeTWO2Fck]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so excited to bring jestin to electric forest this year and watch him vibe and make new friends.… https://t.co/peqLw97nMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The server I had last night so happens to be in my class this morning LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I really think Lindsey has a crush on Brent. I mean she just keeps giving him a pass even knowing he causes a lo… https://t.co/niKsFBhtek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinheadspawn @timmmeyer11 @JeremyXWagner @PatLacey @JonathanJanz @ramseycampbell1 @LairdBarron @flametreepress… https://t.co/d2eDGHG8zu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu He Never Should Have Been Hired In The First Place With An Unqualified #POTUS Making A Decision Of Who Is… https://t.co/7nIYO8IHr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[New AG Bill Barr to END Mueller Probe-Senate Intel Clears Trump of "Russ... https://t.co/THSlTJHkfT via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you gon have porn on the timeline at least make sure it’s lit .. y’all be rt the driest shit 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can y’all please stop saying “I got a new phone” and just say you deleted that persons number]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janashellbug @marinoisking13 @thehill Bernie is the most popular politician in DC. (#AOC is catching up though) Th… https://t.co/vjNTLIPcmj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManorBB @PflugervilleHS @CoachSwain05 @FanstandATX @hoopinsider @ManorSeniorHS @Manor_Sports Let’s ball out🏀… https://t.co/baP8FQ03hN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Esports set to hit the $1 billion mark in 2019 #sponsorship #media #Advertising #merchandise #publishing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daryl and Connie taking a page from the whisperer playbook. A power couple I can get behind. #TWD #TheWalkingDead]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you at the Lego Movie 2: The Second Part   Feb 20th  10:30am  Ramsey Theatre. 🎥🍿😋 https://t.co/XzVmVXGSuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhIoeK @KhIoeK , You knee what kind of man you where dealing with a liar a cheater. I truly understand that he’s y… https://t.co/0X11GdDXPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MauriceBenard You look so adorable! Happy Birthday to your beautiful mom 🎂🎁]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SaveGotham everyone when it returns tomorrow night! February 14th Valentine's day! ❤ Let's show the love… https://t.co/sXhkqKnWOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isaacmarnold I’ve been following her on Twitter for a while. Doesn’t that count as knowing someone in 2019? 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waterparks Andrea Gonzalez San Diego, CA  PLEASE IM A COLLEGE STUDENT AND WANNA HAVE A GOOD TIME BEFORE MY FINALS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sparcharge @Kristenkelso23 @MeganBurger4891 @thx4thesave @Karenimustbe @JT419 @charlib1983 @toolsforbalance Gm😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found in the Lexington area. Will not let this baby go to just anyone, so if you claim that it’s yours be prepared… https://t.co/YUTWnL5LSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The highlight of our weekend and for my girls...their best birthday present ever!! Three very happy CNCOwners here… https://t.co/JuW8SdNGQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FORSALE 2bd 4ba in a quiet interior location. Open floor plan with large, spacious living room w/ patio and downst… https://t.co/zewzI4Ql6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is desperate to find someone who he thinks will be grateful to him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating President's Day at 0748! @njr2408 @SheaKing75 @josh_smartt @w84noneldl https://t.co/Ya8M0ZZric]]></document><document><![CDATA[To @CBColdSpringES Ts &amp; Ss-have a great day filled with lots of hugs &amp; smiles! You Can. You Did. You Will...💝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris  Do you know that, the US military is using video games and rap music to recruit poor young black men… https://t.co/cmKTdTb3u0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samueltking That’s unfortunate esp since there was no room in the J&amp;C to write about this 2A Tourney..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OU_WBBall @FS1 Win Bedlam Beat OSU Cowgirls Stop Vivian Gary &amp; Braxton]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @BOTSunshine for inviting me to your wonderful Sunshine Festival during during Black History Month. https://t.co/gPJwcbQwSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyPow43511632 @GregFieldsWX @News8Daybreak @GeneralMills And Boo Berries at Halloween! #iamup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyAller @TallyMacShack @7Hills_Catering @FJNunez7 @alloutofforks @CarrieQ82 @ChantaCombs @wakullawriter… https://t.co/ckj0vabfbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtashaJordan @womeninmedchat I had only one child and continue to feel judged by other women for not having more.]]></document></documents></author>