<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I still can’t get past the flags side by side. Today’s distraction has to be that tie! Wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NP  Errol Dunkley - Darling Ooh + DJ Style (U Roy Junior)  https://t.co/MW0v6uAqKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty amazing how one person can completely change your outlook on life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope families don’t think I’m weird when I’m staring at them I’m just living vicariously through them and admiring what I don’t have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally woke up this morning. Listened to this song once.. then twice.. then three times.. I think I’ll just put… https://t.co/YPJ7YC0WXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to all my amazing ladies and gents too❤️🌹#ValentinesDay #ValentinesDay2019 #NewProfilePic… https://t.co/r1J1QZUThW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RybaMichele That's the way we are. Certain music for certain places. #RoadTripChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's plans are pretty chill. Just gotta fix this entire relationship that's broken across multiple scenes. o_o #amwriting]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re gonna die like this, you know.... #NowListening @TBSOfficial https://t.co/T6BUAAkPlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjamindcrosby I would live in Princeton, New Jersey, because that's where God wants me to be and where the peopl… https://t.co/mFHNHU0Raz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating my birthday, un-Valentines Day and Mushu’s birthday tonight.  Thank you to grantkimura for cooking dinn… https://t.co/cTKokBCFiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#porshe #porshecarrera #carrera #stevemcqueen #internationalautoshow #autoshow #metroconventioncentre… https://t.co/Spn0BKihF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little warmup before the "Fabulous Friday Tune!" Enjoy!!! @pinkfloyd  https://t.co/NayQdhPgX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillGates @melindagates WATCH DIVIDE &amp; CONQUER-ROGER AILES STORY. EXACTLY WHAT TRUMPS DOING. CREEPY !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Please go live in Venezuela for a month and you will see that our country IS NOT garbage! #WakeUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForceHood happy Valentine’s Day to my  friend Ashley &amp; Danny ❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/LQah665jyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glowingggggggg #glowing #glowup #glowupseason #queenin #queen #grownasswomen #alphawoman #lit @ Raeford, North Caro… https://t.co/tk5PFQ83Ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @ReadWithMe_MrsC to post covers of #7Books I love. No explanations or reviews, jus… https://t.co/x5QYwxJjWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night in the purple jerseys! Can we please keep them?!?!  @Timberwolves]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HanaGebka @lady_franssen @lauracasali3 @lindafromoz @VanessaGaglione @TJRs_fan @Beccatx8 @AshleyDavidson… https://t.co/yyYuvtoJhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan So, you’re either a victim of Russian kompromat, or you’re a loon. Either way, you need tonresign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer It's a shame that the Socialist Democrats won't let nothing go it's costing the Amer… https://t.co/aQOYInbtDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to perform and honor Jean Baptiste Point DuSable at the 13th annual DuSable Heritage Association Gala at Fa… https://t.co/MhYdY64JPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristendoute @stassi I've been in the same kind of relationship get out now It doesn't get any better]]></document><document><![CDATA[if anyone ever wants to know how I’m feeling, @LilSkies will cover it 😩😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being sick with a sinus infection on Valentine’s Day is no fun bc I can’t taste any of the chocolate I’m eating :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FernandoSimao14 @wpri12 @FOXProvidence Where I am in Providence County, snow was light and easy to move off my car… https://t.co/lxpcYjTXMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIME Esta es la hija del Diablo así la veo y así se pondrá por ser tan mala con los pueblos Robandose el Dinero de… https://t.co/bPeRIriFbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatPoliceAssoc They certainly deserve the medals for all they do to protect us.  Love seeing K-9 officers shown respect and honor as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mindfoam @IngrahamAngle Look at her timeline, she has an opinion for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZoeTillman @InvestigateRU I guess you can threaten a Federal Judge and all that happens is they tell you to be quiet. Good to know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up this morning with a swollen ass left eye because a mosquito decided to bless me 😒😒😒😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[No mention of conspiring w/Dowlless to steal the election?🤔 I wonder why?   Honestly, the only truly FAIR solution… https://t.co/QlhWjV0FQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to change my 2nd training day to Thursday’s....at 5am...permanently. Bye bye 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd annual ski annual ski trip! @ Beech Mountain Ski Resort https://t.co/wq6UopAdNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally caught the Muppets in Liberty Square. Love the show! So witty! https://t.co/ysESUn1dOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to know when we can be voted on independently and not lumped in with baseball. Building stadiums for both sp… https://t.co/djuWJtDLvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the ropes with @denisewoodallks for Justice Day at the Capitol: a day to promote criminal justice reform in Geor… https://t.co/oY6ddYPoS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rodneygroce_ @ChadSimmons_ @GeauxBeaux8 @DatDude70 @pghs_spartans @JohnGarcia_Jr @Rivals @DemetricDWarren… https://t.co/iEQCYUwJLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thor is one of the goodest boys. He is such a sweet puppy. #ThortheCorgi #dogs #dogsofinstagram #dogsoftheday… https://t.co/73RCxNnLPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricksuttles 🎉Happy THREE-O!!! Just remember, we’re like wine, we only get better with age (trust me)! Cheers!! 🍷🍷🍷… https://t.co/mR1YN5QiVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[those guy friends that save you in situations when a guy don’t leave you alone &gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warm your mascara correctly.  #bannisternaturals #youniqueepicmascara @ Daviess County, Kentucky https://t.co/wCoprboViW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooper and Emma are off to Arizona for March Break with their Dad to visit Grandma and Grandpa. I'm excited for the… https://t.co/l2h2fJWjiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meganfrancis So glad to have met you. Your presentation was first rate!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teslahedron Clovis has a deep rooted history of KKK members  AND IT SHOWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh watching this tyrant on here now..he makes me nauseated..he is poised to announce his natl emergency as he is s… https://t.co/Ml18OaodE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[They be playing around and still be creative. I’m over dancing like this song in one of my playlist 😂.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedcruz The thought that Jews today could be Republicans is beyond my imagination.  You enable the most ignorant,… https://t.co/ahEiM7qLuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day for some Carroll Baseball!!! #eaglenation #carrollpride @ Eagle Stadium Baseball Field https://t.co/MDiqDRsPme]]></document><document><![CDATA[also, forget lanterns, I’m my own light source. https://t.co/jUh1iVtkig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tech Tuesday... This haircut entails various techniques to create this shape. #swipeleft #techtuesday #thebreakdown… https://t.co/bNNoqSC9Xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[to the cute guy wearing the L2TP hoodie I saw as I walking to library, wanna just slide in my DMs that would be great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dpangyy @GoldenKnights Come to Dallas on the 15th! I need them to beat the Stars again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great weekend the 1st graders in @MissWhite2017 class had! @mpohlman88 can you tell them about your weekend?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude that’s what the first doc said when I fell at @16WAPTNews . I told her ... guess I’m limping for the rest of m… https://t.co/2wGL3LvM4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivaVinophile @confessions_cup @TheAngelOrsini @hmgivingsoul @simplysallyh @Cbp8Cindy @suziday123 @jflorez… https://t.co/cqPeMdai7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pioneering Toronto transgender singer Jackie Shane dead at 78 | The Star https://t.co/TnGFmsdwZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m trying to see if twitter will let me posts the gifs as one gif instead of the two sets; i’ve been making them a… https://t.co/Pz6yTG9Vwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Before The Flood. First time actually seeing DiCaprio since Blood Diamond.]]></document><document><![CDATA[back to back to back 🏆 #substatechamps #statebound @ Circle High https://t.co/kCpPWAicx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennnaayduran_ I honestly just looked at my nipples after reading this to see if they look different but nope lmao back to normal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beardedPT @noigroupuk @LePubUK @EventbriteUK @timbeames Are you going to come and learn about the pelvis while I’m there??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wooowza I thought @jimmyjohns was freaky fast but an hour has passed and still no sandwich 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightShiftMD Be careful about the Drop In Clinic. Still hearing horror stories of doctors firing their patients fo… https://t.co/Hm8EfNFE0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Jonathan - #women Appreciate our #male #allies. We are #StrongerTogether #HappyInternationalWomensDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[I referred to the author of a book as "OP" so if anyone wants to stop me at any time, that would be okay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CricFanUSA @cheracuse @DukeLathem I sang this to the tune of “Breakfast at Tiffany’s” and it made it kinda fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Not all America. Speak for yourself. I for one stand for impeachment &amp; indictments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @MarcoGutierrez Sad. And, the same inept politicians keep getting reelected]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdlteach We can’t wait to use these! We just got some for our Kindergarten students! Thanks for the video.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conferencia Nutrición Deportiva #jrzteam #soyjrzrunning #runningday2019 #sportnutrition en Centro Cultural Paso del… https://t.co/CpzpzDFHQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lalaaidan @ThatEricAlper Definitely. I liked all the George Orwell we read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @IlhanMN I find it impossible to take you seriously. Next time this says or does something racist or bigoted, I… https://t.co/tdZzOiKplu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoswellGBB with the win tonight in the sweet 16. Headed to the elite eight! 🖤💚💪🏼 https://t.co/lQYOeLh0bJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panthers OT @tmoton72 ranked No. 4 in NFC South at his position by PFF | Panthers Wire via @thepantherswire https://t.co/QGorDhs6f3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexymni @TwistedOne96 @arkiegal411 @msnicole1124 @karli_bonne @PublishedReport @kingconvictions @SolidRedPeon… https://t.co/fVqiPVR4Iz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't bring them to Ohio we dont want them...I think TX, Az and Ca getting the worst of this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atlanta United FC vs FC Cincinnati @ Mercedes-Benz Stadium https://t.co/VvGAapLwvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yandiraa_ Strong point @yandiraa_. Only logical solution is for me to document them daily in an album and force yo… https://t.co/ZZKAmouP8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmcdonaldglobal @OPP_HSD The things people try to get away with!! Congrats, Graham! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish there were friend want ads or ads to find people who could bring elder/auntie energy into your life (YES I A… https://t.co/8ZxtNMoamt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karl Lagerfeld's Beloved Cat Choupette Is an Heiress to His Massive Fortune https://t.co/rCEBpqCIzR via @Yahoo Nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro took a pic of the side of his head and said “let’s see who’s head is bigger” I’m actually cryingg😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MistressOrochi In other words, my mom frequently yells at me for the content of my Twitter 😹😹😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo que es tener dinero. I wish I had enough money to be waited hand and foot when I’m sick...lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomensDay #HappyWomensDay2019 #FridayFeeling Happy International Women’s 💕💞 #FridayMotivation… https://t.co/f9FAtYF9CD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiablosRojosMX @alfredoharphelu @LigaMexBeis @AcademiaAHH @FundacionAHHO @MiguelOjedaS @El_Pato_Perez @Othon_DiazV… https://t.co/thtjeJvIcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laugh. Love. Live.  • • • • • Also, it’s “Valentimes” Day. So I thought perfect time for a post, right? 🤷🏾‍♀️  Can’… https://t.co/DsvOMqzZOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 Thessalonians 5:11 KJV Wherefore comfort yourselves together, and edify one another, even as also ye do. https://t.co/hGZfBQBaKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mspandamo @amyallantdf Awwww....sweetie😣My thoughts and prayers are with you. I know you will make the right decis… https://t.co/sBZf99URbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuxxxNaomie Qnd c’est livré ca le dit je suppose?? Il laissent a la porte ou ils donnent un papier?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen up! @SpeakerPelosi @AOC @IlhanMN @RashidaTlaib @KamalaHarris @SenWarren @RepMaxineWaters @CoryBooker https://t.co/ZLuSYfJMBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot wait to read their opinion letters! They are working so hard! I am a very proud principal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 58..... Namaste @ Greensboro, North Carolina https://t.co/bO3Tb7FG5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hair and makeup magic ✨ #bridalmakeuptrial #bridalhairtrial #125days #roadtoruth @ Oceanside, California https://t.co/BWLtiPBDxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3/7 for the challenge here. Favorite books with no explanations, no reviews. I’ll choose someone new to join ea… https://t.co/wSek6qFGa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Earth systems are interconnected, air to land to sea. Bills to regulate teaching won’t grow our understanding o… https://t.co/8ZoC1Ssytq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buddha is due to see his vet, his eye doctor, needs his annual shots, is out of his eye drops and is running out of… https://t.co/SHcg13Xt7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notetomarais @corbynbesson @whydontwemusic this is so good wth @corbynbesson look at this]]></document></documents></author>