<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[An attendant told me that mark stone will be sitting by the flames bench in the crowd but cant find him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a hearty "yippee-dippy-do!" to @BrentDiskin on yet another successful lap around the sun.   I also like this… https://t.co/h6gFwH6Mb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo Gonzaga Bulldogs beat BYU after losing to them on senior night two years in a row.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sick I’m in class for 8 hours today for my cpl😂🙌🏻 been waiting for this day for to long]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews #TheWarlockInTheWestWing https://t.co/qnwJFZ2uVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edsbs Don’t care you you are, like special forces gonna stop me if I think you screwed me on a call from giving you an earful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for Spring at https://t.co/8PgyTcQHwQ. Kickoff event on May 4th to restore pollinator habitats in our… https://t.co/dVT9K5DB4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Wow, I thought “Presidential Harassment” was your CPAC “speech”!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still think an IQ test should be put on the home screen of all #Battlefield games. If you don't score above a cer… https://t.co/hrAzZafyov]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @hilarious_7  sold out tonight at @HootersCasinoLV ! We didn't lose our integrity, we just filled every damn se… https://t.co/FG1KsmjW1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Valle de Guadalupe. Ruta del Vino https://t.co/5q4TxBWYMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janerrigby Yes it is. Although I suppose it’s practical given that it’s about to get really, really windy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly what I needed on a cold day like today!! https://t.co/GN2muKzl8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[my laptop charger died ??? i guess but anyway luckily i have the geek squad plan so even tho I had to buy a new one… https://t.co/5XBIZafgO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keith Collins @ Caesars Atlantic City Hotel &amp; Casino https://t.co/BFMrcjzjgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duhh_its_abbs It took longer than I would like to admit😂😂. It thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little beauty is my valentine and she’s all mine.  Thank you for being lovely both near and far.  I miss you m… https://t.co/5HmzWNrRHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@johnpletz nothing wrong w/ starting as "mostly a sales outpost", that's how many coastal big tech firms start out… https://t.co/EiG30hWAqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if you play on your phone the whole time it’s on I’ll be triggered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todos deberían escuchar 'Your Type' de @carlyraejepsen y llorar juntos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Global Warming: Los Angeles Has Coldest February in 60 Years | Breitbart https://t.co/gWOz8SO52a via @BreitbartNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having support staff, including me, in the class supporting and modeling as well as having scheduled breaks with th… https://t.co/Nyj3AXOBrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryan_Bell98 @benshapiro And once again, you’ve shown why I follow you. Bravo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrinceEmjayE Right! My mind was determine to stick to what was needed instead my eyes thought differently]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I ain’t tryn talk bout police let’s talk bout bitches let’s talk bout business‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Max Penton - Tryout 2016-2017 not rostered, all hard work and good attitude forced his way into 2018-2019 team but… https://t.co/bic7QoastQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t defecate at a @Target without thinking of you @OlanRogers.  Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeniseDresserG @jenarovillamil Ahora está pasando un fenómeno que me da aun más miedo. Latinos que llegaron de man… https://t.co/JZQT8P6jEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardsNCowboyz Perhaps they were simply proving “their” point with the tweet?? 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rish_km @raywongy @futureshift An 80s scifi movie directed by Terry Gilliam, yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wendys  What are the chances of me getting baconators for life? Or just maybe 5 grand to get my business off the ground?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever wrote the episode Scott’s Tots is evil. I’m convinced its the only Office episode that nobody rewatches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FOHQT500  Sure Truex had the faster car at the end, in another lap he probably would've gotten Brad and i get him… https://t.co/yCh4KpEmwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wisdom #truth #spiritual #theuniverse #oprah #jeffreybyron   On the Money! 🙌 @ Century City, Los Angeles https://t.co/abpaYNNmgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[After quickly questioning her and the boys (she said he's asleep somewhere), I ran down stairs and yelled his name… https://t.co/HDHiZjl0pc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcHochman @AlexDonno Hell wrong with you donno? You already followed me lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm thinking of something that beats like a drum and lives deep down in your chest... it pushes blood with a push f… https://t.co/j0GKWRpMlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking a little #ominous this morning loading up some ponderosa pines to take to our commercial project! #nofilter… https://t.co/791XEHuBOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_Stieber @lapham_katie @UTLAnow 3-5 police officers a day and NO school or college counselors. That is a crime. T… https://t.co/b42bpFuyjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelicaaMairee @Dwash_swaggin I don’t really see many ppl going out ordering fish fr fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew! One ! https://t.co/y7l8Op8A1E One💚!☮️☯️👹 https://t.co/U7YeWgpU8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shawty said “Do the 69 w/ ya husband for Valentine’s Day”, let em lick that coochie and you lick that dick😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight on at 7:30 on WFXR and 11:00 on WWCW, it is Gobbler Gameday! Myself, @ddeguzmanTV @SWaddellTV &amp;… https://t.co/nWUX4Ut7g4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmenBoquin saludos. Desde Oregon. Ya listos para  clásico https://t.co/c33c2hKoOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RileyGreenMusic by the first few words of his new song “Bettin’ Man” you can tell its gonna be a good one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cauzin_trouble It’s all good, it’s an old mount prospect police car, they were practically giving them away. you s… https://t.co/KqWyfNgvWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My MacBook is slowly dying after 5 years. Went into Apple store to look for replacement and I hate them all. Keyboa… https://t.co/MRTEF6l2EY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy, Happy 14th Birthday to our twins, Eamon and Ronan !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  Fourteen years today, Heather gave birth… https://t.co/uXwq7XBxyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poptivist I regret that my facial hair is weak sauce, because this is as close to mirror universe evil I can get. https://t.co/YWsxDXQItP]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of good stuff in this article, but this in particular jumped out at me (similar to changes we advocated for i… https://t.co/c9sdz4n6aH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foul deck scenario:  Player is dealt Ace of spades, King, Queen, Ace of Spades in PLO. The pot is 3 handed to the r… https://t.co/qwEfXWEFz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spotrac @80suburbia Fuck Case..All them qb in the combine we watched..we cant groom not one of them..oh thats righ… https://t.co/lUelBNPhKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[All hard work brings a profit, but mere talk leads only to poverty. - Proverbs 14:23]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at McCarran International Airport - @lasairport in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/OYQpW0BzfD https://t.co/wtUy9RjWmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Later this year.. #GetIt #MondayMotivation #Actorslife https://t.co/YXLZyUjPpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[GM and happy Mardi Gras from the ATL🎭🎭 #NOLA @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/usRQexOcmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% that is what they’re attempting.    Ginning up fear of an already illegal act as a precursor for taking away a… https://t.co/Z7AJoyDQFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #complaint was sent to the #FTC in December and was made public this week.  https://t.co/qmg8KNFZ5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when you dm someone a funny tweet and they read it and don’t respond. Like oh “im sorry for going out of my… https://t.co/dK8AWFUB0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because Centro Med services are a joke...I'll drive to edge of San Antonio for quality service...been down most of… https://t.co/iAweidRRbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's in good hands  #atlutd championship Trophy! @ Georgia State Capitol https://t.co/xWQPFyasGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rest In Peace to #KingKongBundy Spent lots of Saturdays being entertainment by WWF in my college days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robyn_s_lee @EpiDemos82 10/10 would risk active shooter situation for Hamilton again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I hear ole slew foot in the WH talk about "lowest AA unemployment" in U.S. history, I get freshly incensed for 2 reasons:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do the right thing, even when no one is looking.  It's called integrity. @CoachTenney @dbongino @charliekirk11… https://t.co/Pgin5muaFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should gave asked if we could have a DSA table at the show. #RadicalizetheLambs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Much of my humor particularly for the last 10 years has centered on why we hate      -as a child-from other kids-my… https://t.co/HmCbWoUhlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcosCrespo85 @rubendiazjr @zellnor4ny @NYCHA The rent roll is weak. Withholding  or reducing rents will only add… https://t.co/xUmVVGA8IS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SiskoWorld I’ll hope for a result in another match if it benefits FCB 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dragon Fans, Doors open at 5:30.  Be sure to arrive early to get a good seat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabetheapache @marioq_11 @LexiLassiter Cause we ain’t gonna let you come at us like that on the Twitter 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point I’m definitely a perfect fit for my city’s team @nbagleague @NBA @okcthunder @okcblue‼️💯🤷🏾‍♂️💙🤞🏾🤐🙏🏾 M… https://t.co/nxy3t0FaFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a chance. It would reinforce the established truism that those with big money, big connections, or significant… https://t.co/WC3TfnY3wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pose (2018-) 8 episodes Pose is set in the world of 1987 and "looks at the juxtaposition of several segments of lif… https://t.co/Psnk5xteLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeff_Attinella1 @fox12oregon @ZarekValentin Can you give me a shoutout and mention the toy drive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrokerAceKid @Skittles @KyleBusch @JoeGibbsRacing @NASCAR @rottzillasgirl @eddiecolvin7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gpadova Well this speak volumes to your tenaciousness and the passion you put into so much of your life and work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurneyMorgan That’s why I stick with Twitter. Same group of lunatics that were here day one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Aeroporto Intercontinental George Bush - Houston (IAH) in Houston, TX https://t.co/aaF6JmZHGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody:  22 year old decker account: my parents are so strict I can never go out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finebaum Sawyer makes a compelling case to cease reproduction on Planet Earth....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urbanbarbarian @FrankTieri Disagreeing here. No matter the intent, "Say that to my face" is going to come off as a… https://t.co/rZJjCfZc08]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Because it won’t make a bit of difference ya hack !]]></document><document><![CDATA[A friend is someone who knows all about and still loves you. #koreanbell #friendship #lovequotes @ Korean Friendshi… https://t.co/Ep5YVuW58X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovRonDeSantis Thank you @GovRonDeSantis. Happy to share our success stories in Florida with #DirectPrimaryCare dr… https://t.co/QzZT6Rp3JH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNEWS @FOXNEWS our Debt Ceiling has increased horribl… https://t.co/FtS9FEroe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanOrleans Sometimes you don't want steak you really crave a McDonald's cheeseburger]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I think this story can't get more horrifying, it does. https://t.co/eKGmORSJZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems that law suites have taken the place of common sense.  I asked a hot girl out 45 years ago and she turned… https://t.co/l7jRtPeyvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[How the Trump tax cuts have helped ordinary Americans like me: 2017 tax return: $1,400 2018 tax return: $0.02]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @SteveScalise @GOPLeader Democrats are using taxpayers money to fund their oppo research.  Republi… https://t.co/vQwPGxMcdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow my business page @BrewingtonThe. . . Ask me about our consulting services. Sharing my business page and refe… https://t.co/UVLsK6sv29]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday guys! Hope you are doing well! I wanted to let you know that I’ll be doing my next Instagram and Faceb… https://t.co/1Usf0PkZWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Getty Villa Ranch House in Palisades, CA https://t.co/TTNEmyHH0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Views_86 Says the dude that doesn’t call on check on his so called kids. Kourtney miss you so much that she preten… https://t.co/pXM4py7Kbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingShaMugga_ Yo man I laugh that shit really classic yo. “Pernell showed me what’s up”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anamariecox I just finished the most recent episode of With Friends Like These. Thank you so much for the work you… https://t.co/PlLed25ZLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than a month now. Been nice knowing you guys. We had a good run.✌🏼 https://t.co/IFDcLphLCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump TRUMP JUST KEEPS DENYING IT STRATEGY https://t.co/q94MGyMh5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trae Young got ejected for a staredown....not touching, not spitting, not throwing a punch....A Staredown...😂😂😂🙄🙄… https://t.co/45soSG1eBE]]></document></documents></author>