<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@sunrisemvmt @The_UnSilent_ @SenFeinstein You've been doing this for 30 yrs? Madam Senator I am a Democrat. Unfortu… https://t.co/K88mfEYhnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man. Could you imagine doing what @AB84 is doing to his team, coworkers, friends?  What a horrible person. Blame everyone else society.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I cry out, He hears me. And comes through.  I hate crying, but it's therapeutic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is another sneak peak to yesterday’s Spiderverse shoot! Here is a side by side scene from the diner! They didn… https://t.co/478NlAkGjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattGeorgeKHTK Buddy should be on the Top 50 list!   So important to the Kings season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a lady rn on the side of the street trying to clean windows for money .   She had bags on her feet as socks .    My hearts shattered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Which is roughly 4000 times less than Donald lied to the American people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On your birthday, you drink at noon while watching the Mariachi Divas. https://t.co/etTXGM7kxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcrd1972 @yeiferreira Verga que ignorancia. Estudian "tranquilos" pregunto yo ¿Con el dinero de quièn estudian?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BostonLogan pathetic that this airport closes for a few inches of snow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden . You see why we know Biden is not running for President. Why Obama is pushing “Beto” from Texas to run?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jimbeam377Beam @JCaporoso Same. Thought he got a bad wrap, played arguably most difficult position on the field an… https://t.co/LrwFZLZtYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twitandrewking Seriously why can't they just design it like the rest of the building? Why does it have to look like a Toronto condo wart?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally something to fix our loophole of having insurance.   https://t.co/dBkFGSYpBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwestr @LivingnTX I accept Venmo or Quickpay, and as long as a 3rd party to this agreement is willing to sign off… https://t.co/6VlcoVrJj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_JeanPierre And how many Indigenous children are missing from ICE/CBP? You've heard of Sen. Tester's initiative o… https://t.co/GcgFZR2UAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[(2/5) Knock Knock by Smog (Bill Callahan). Semi lo-fi rock with weird textures &amp; off-kilter songwriting: https://t.co/H9tLExDilo]]></document><document><![CDATA[3Dans1Ben Music Charts Album Chart 2.24.19-3.2.19  @AvrilLavigne’s ‘Head Above Water’ spends a 2nd week at #1 while… https://t.co/gtESrgBT0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat is acting really adorable and sweet and I swear he’s smiling at me as he rolls around on my lap. I’m very suspicious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At what age do kids stop puking in their sleep thus not making it to a toilet? Nothing like waking up to vomit covering a bed. Argh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatPet1776 @TBruceTrp773 Of course we paid for their vacation trips and the democrats want to raise taxes to waste… https://t.co/UQQxbhLhZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black History Month is extended all the way to March 3rd since they gave us the shortest month ✊🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baldnerwin @adoublerjones @DrewCMarine @Bryce_Bozadjian @lissawithm @CarsonMlnarik You have great taste in your fi… https://t.co/Q9Wgv0L3FH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueGhost40_ Sounds better if you don't split the infinitive: How not to get a woman…]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting on this nigga @Heisehnberg who acting like it's not brick outside!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion is coming for blood the rest of the season and I can’t freaking wait! #GoDuke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coenesqued @70sFilm Maybe my favorite Altman movie, usually find his work to be an acquired taste, but his take on… https://t.co/0zuCg0vwna]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is election day #NYC ! Activists at #WFP4theMany are getting out the vote now for @JumaaneWilliams for… https://t.co/U48lBpmmi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think if I were Jewish and if I were a Democrat, I might begin to re-examine my politics and my political philoso… https://t.co/c2UJu40J7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFLMarquise @RJinVegas @Dave_Essler @BradPowers7 Mich is 12/1 at Venetian/CG Technology.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LinRoseResists @Evanjoseph66 @Sean74357583 @wjr_me @SuperEliteTexan @KendallMigues https://t.co/bDBJa49dAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Muppets: Delighting musical comedy brimming equally with nostalgia and forward-thinking humour. Most of the gags and songs are triumphs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday March 4 - The Guardian Today US:     Most US coal plants are contaminating groundwater with toxins, analysis… https://t.co/P55Lsfuh65]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t remember MJ ever saying he had nothing to prove. I believe every time you step on the court you have someth… https://t.co/NiTNu86LoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magnumCJ I hope there's a tie breaker in Nashvegas in the tourney. Whether KY is full strength or not, we showed w… https://t.co/vEzYSXVbH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andizeisler @MeghanMcCain Ay Meghan I heard you didn't like being accurately described as an opportunistic fame se… https://t.co/Ij10VvTeTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OffAirGaming1 @uasalmouse @BlytheGifford @davidhogg111 So run as a Republican?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaPurser I was held POW in Cleveland-I moved as soon as I could—everything froze-I use to think those people h… https://t.co/c5HGWPC28W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markryan243 bumble from first transformers movie .... what an awesome down to earth dude ... thank you… https://t.co/SSdh9zTFGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimBobb20808476 So would all of Congress. Dems &amp; GOP. Neither can read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scout_Finch Let them sit in a courthouse waiting for most of the day first.  Of course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laura Zapata @LAURAZAPATAM hace el ridículo de su vida, el día de hoy, uniendose a la marcha en contra del presiden… https://t.co/gCOgoXRIuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends: In 5 words or less (-ish), why do you pick up the controller/mouse?  eg. "The story" "The graphics" "Shirt… https://t.co/XaGgmnw8Je]]></document><document><![CDATA[me at Trader Joe’s knowing there’s no reason for me to buy a dozen eggs as a single man in NYC https://t.co/WnswtabUWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks again to 🎶BigTime Radio🎶 Vegas BTR International on Twitter for spinning my Spotify single “Yeah, But” writt… https://t.co/peC4RS05vA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLBNerdy @_kimhanley @NashCLC Walking Ziggy. We'll be at MK 630 or so..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @FareedZakaria Good points but Omar does not try to hide what she is and what she is about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prometheus' creation experiment #1: "The title in the article the teacher gave me today wasn't capitalized. Drove m… https://t.co/TjTyLv6zeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyDangeloXXX @SexyVanessa3 @erossandiego @eroslosangeles @erosguide @PStarPlatinum Will you be meeting your fans for private sessions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristinajolonch Ostres, com m'ha agradat l'entrevista! Moltes gràcies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i told y’all i like to put flaming hots on my pizza would you judge me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maperezpirela Les paso el Güevo por la cara a todos tus opresores. Cojan dato!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Won’t buy an individual player jersey until After a person Retires. There’s always room for a change in opinion o… https://t.co/frFWlsnsaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[A slight slip but these boys did not fall down. 8th place after 2 games. https://t.co/c1qXLefhDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That’s not a misinterpretation, we heard you loud and clear. You’re an insensitive idiot, and you… https://t.co/UzCpIoiFsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAuthorGuy @Popehat Is he hoping for that presidential pardon? Manafort fis, too, but...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joedieseldodge But the reason student loans are specifically important is because millennials are soon to be the l… https://t.co/QK1efXL47p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackJoseyNewman @RepSwalwell @SenatorBurr @MarkWarner Looking forward to seeing it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GotNoSperm @HalNiederman Mets have been FAILING you most of your life! Their successes have been few and far between.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessing your feed with the cutest post of 2019😍 @ Thomasville, North Carolina https://t.co/h6G9ohgXWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TattedOnTwitch Same here! Things I think are going great for everyone, it's nice for this kind of change!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexigronzalski I replied to myself at first that's embarrassing. But I'm so glad it's not just me]]></document><document><![CDATA[She probably doesn't really believe it she just knows that by saying it many will believe her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SigneWilk @PhilaFlowerShow @phillydotcom I love this piece Signe. I’ve been rediscovering my watercolor skills thr… https://t.co/v2M38GnqJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steve_kass @PanoGeorgoulis It’s only 11 mill for 1 year at least trade him and get draft picks if you weren’t gonna design him unbelievable]]></document><document><![CDATA[“POTHOLE CAPITOL OF THE U.S.” -  Emails show Mayor Sylvester Turner's pothole patrol is well behind its goal of fil… https://t.co/EXKXAOkLyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to Alou-Hicks in APES lowkey for constantly reminding us about the Mangrove Forest and the other biomes th… https://t.co/MhFSpBsbol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5pluseighteen Even if just shot 35% from 3 that would open the floor up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerperry @madea @MadeaFamFuneral Can't wait to see this, Madea has kept me sane for s long time because I laugh myself silly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidlagreca1 @BustedOpenRadio Maybe if they’re gonna recognize the people behind the scenes, just announce their… https://t.co/OOoHmi8XOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @danielledsouzag @foxandfriends Physical and mental bullying is the lefts main use of its ignorance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You give this kid Hart 3 goals I don’t see how we don’t get at least a point out of this game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@somevelvetblog @sxsw @BlackPumasMusic @Western_Youth @illuminatihotts @LizstokedStokes @combo_chimbita @jsondara… https://t.co/owvRUyAjKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a GoneAway by @halfacrebeer at @tjsbeer — https://t.co/bLBWOPXr1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ford says Senate Bill 12 is not a Hate Crimes bill and the rest of the country knows this.  We will not come off th… https://t.co/OS1qPmxlL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tiedes59 Please note there are mistakes to your listing.  They are the following:  No 00 Biron. No Horton. No kozl… https://t.co/yafj4XVtBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hagaman_kl @RFHurteau @PoetEli1 @LeeFGabel @TheSpinDoctor @WhoThat_One_Guy @JayJayjay2683 @leneeh4 @iamfierless… https://t.co/UXCiShiv8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro dont you just hate when you help someone and then when shit hits the fan they throw you're name under the bus l… https://t.co/xFaQZkUZT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Song Spotlight February 21, 2019  Featured Songs For February 21, 2019 Vibrasphere - San Pedro  https://t.co/LlJ5tPTajl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBigCat @PFTCommenter  THE BUFFALO MAFIA IS BACK. Bring out the jumpsuits boyz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The evolution of @Nationwide's talk show for employees is fascinating. The Nationwide airwaves. Involves so many mo… https://t.co/Mwe27529lW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to Steez w/ The Real Bros of Seguin Valley out here in Cali. #GameDay #KB4 #SuperSteezy #Farewelltour… https://t.co/WgWHAuF8ID]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chickenboo23 @ShelleyElwood We did that when we read little house in the big woods. And I’ve done it a few times f… https://t.co/ZLpRpfsTqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattowanHP Lol.....you are well aware it's a false equivalency.   Pirro should be fired but she works for STATE TV… https://t.co/oUxksRnwnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekSTerry Add this to the “What exactly was your plan here?!” List of videos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not preaching on #GC2019 this morning,  but delegates, know this: every church in the denomination will be praying for you this morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder I sure hope all those wonderful weapons sold to Saudi Arabia and others in the Middle East aren't used agai… https://t.co/ycarmKbaje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliaHodgson5 @JulieReichwein1 @kimbokintz PICK UP AN AMERICAN HISTORY BOOK. TURN TO PAGE 1 LYING ABOUT KINGS. 3/5… https://t.co/yI76ns9sku]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would put us at the status quo. That is not the worst news, but it is not good news. At best, it is okay news.… https://t.co/j5elNBXFxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not out hitting the bars and clubs of Seattle on Friday night or during the weekend (or on any night for that m… https://t.co/tYHRyTYwgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulTheDaly 💯 agree there needs to be a healthy connection. Social blurs this even further. I think those that are… https://t.co/WJDIUii5Gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetroCDMX @Alfamarino Es muchísimo el dinero que recaudan “Diariamente” como para que no puedan contratar el perso… https://t.co/oi9o92frxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get outside your comfort zone... always something to learn...  @biggroveben   🔥🔥🔥💯💯💯💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patrickjulian_ @CoachJamison @CoachTCalhoun @EDGYTIM @lemminginsider @CoachBigPete @CedrickWilson6 Thank you bro ‼️ God has a plan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thechuckgettemy @SheCanTech @justin_fenton @Twitter @TwitterSafety That horse face blocked me already 😂 which i co… https://t.co/AvgD0fHRmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[please like or retweet if jordyn, khloe and tristan tweet is still ongoing lol #RedTableTalk #teamjordyn… https://t.co/r5SrRW4Lzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realginnyrobins ...I don't NEED tobacco, I don't NEED alcohol, I don't NEED hallucinogens and I don't NEED a psych… https://t.co/EX9QkdABga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petrogustavo @victormo1623 @mluciaramirez Pero no se acuerda cuan pertenecía a la narco guerrillea del M -19 cuan… https://t.co/ax5vNdIwIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlabamAppeals @RMFifthCircuit I agree. This speaks volumes in terms of judges—and justice. This shows that the system largely works.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PARDON ME AGAIN. I MUST RECEIT ANOTHER REQUEST.  "Turn down the lights, turn down the bed, turn down these "VOICE… https://t.co/weCTcCnUh4]]></document></documents></author>