<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Ever since I watched twitches when their mom was running down that hallway holding her dress screaming “fanthos” I… https://t.co/euA3SydSAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@balcom_holly Are there? Wouldn't surprise me but I don't know much about that. Seems like if that was the deal she… https://t.co/l4wAeHYAgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lhbizness @alexxkittle @brohibited @citizendamepod Media is becoming encumbered by more and more trappings of corp… https://t.co/KZAvDcJouA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm bored! 😉💕💋#latenightsketches @RossLynch @thedriverera https://t.co/XHLzMtFRnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@directxman12, you weren’t meant to have a rainbow background 🌈 #KubeDay https://t.co/Tx2LDJZl2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5 of #bookchallenge. Of books I love. Just covers no reviews. #ReadersAreLeaders https://t.co/mbeRFPzGBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think #BlackPanther was super on point musically thanks to @ludwiggoransson took the storytelling and ran with it! Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once upon a time I was so good at Twitter. Now I forget about it for days 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bedabear while it is an amazing film, it is not a remake of the animated classic but rather a version of rodgers a… https://t.co/jRpHQYJlsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STLCardinalsNYG We all know your weird obsession with checking the bank account.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello 👋🏽 .......You better join our team before your down line does😳.  ➡️ It’s hard to pass up a Free Business Oppo… https://t.co/J986X8Zfpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of these boys! They smashed their own record in the 200 Free Relay (it was 1:35.62 and they got it down to… https://t.co/FGi11BoYnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[That looks sooooooo comfy, I can’t blame the first creature to get a flying leap into it!  Anyway, now you can snug… https://t.co/3Dk8oCgv87]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rant: I couldn’t even bring a guy to Trinidad until at least a year or more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LewisRobbie12 @_thedavina me with no boyfriend: https://t.co/EiP6Div73y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m hella intrigued by this trailer and the premise of this story. Plus, hell yeah Southeast Asian lead!… https://t.co/RfLGLsC4Uc]]></document><document><![CDATA[98% of the points i lose on Mastering Chemistry is because of wrong units.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@StarTribune - Washington Post: Sen. Rand Paul says government should not force people to receive vaccinations… https://t.co/uHW33SWRPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mellyindc @Chelsea_Fagan The ghirardelli triple chocolate box brownies are the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tenacious_O @ThatWokeAuntie @magi_jay @ShimonPro RunSwitch PR did crisis management Scott Jennings a Trump unoffic… https://t.co/0PGTZ4l8Wq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The two most important components of personal development are pain and time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i HATE it when people around me feel embarrassed for crying/being excited/being “overly emotional” in general— who… https://t.co/quDDa3Xr9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @AOC @girlscouts She should have exploded with the Challenger reenactment...such BS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gymnat545 @hardhouz13 Reread the thread, where in this are you a nice person? A nice person never has to say so. Y… https://t.co/EZzl5G6eeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandiKHOU I think they should be roving guest service ambassadors. Then they can greet but not be stuck at the do… https://t.co/gXkp470q8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am really so blessed when it comes to Alex and how good he is for me 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I Just Want A Fucking Hug, But I Don’t Need It ❤️✨.. #Knowthefuckingdifference]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggottesman @AOC @amazon Agree. And I have even less regard for the way @NYCMayor @GovCuomo conducted their side… https://t.co/oICijkfgWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now how do I tell them I have to skip out for the AHJ shows for two weeks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PARIS__FRANCIA @CarlosEVivasMay Era rubia hace como dos años, pero es muy difícil mantenerlo así que en un arranqu… https://t.co/6NafQTBzc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannnoni LMFAO yes bae yes!! We can have big ass houses next to each other and go to the Gucci store to shop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I naturally grow out my nails I get obsessive about cleaning under my nails like 8+ times a day is that normal or am I nuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima need campus safety to stop letting RANDOM ASS KIDS on this campus ion pay tuition for everybody to be just on MY CAMPUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and blames its patients: "Lifestyle diseases, the high cost of healthcare, delaying or non-compliance with medic… https://t.co/Ki184MhsTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always end the day with a positive thought and a grateful heart. Good evening / night to all. https://t.co/OXCpq0fzsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman VOTE to 9 months Abortion TRASH of MURDER BABIES !! STOP Planned Parenthood Murders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@verrawrrnica same! I tried the whole fair thing too and just like you said waaay too crowded and hot to even enjoy… https://t.co/zKKTwU9YS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m drawn to these shapes. You’ll see them over and over in different gems and juxtapositions in my gallery. Come p… https://t.co/rzvUKYZv3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s our update for #TOJ4C Week One update Feb. 15, 2019 https://t.co/WQdROqi5ow via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinBrannan Is this something we might think about here in #BayRidge for #participatorybudgeting this year?… https://t.co/ekJhjR32LD]]></document><document><![CDATA[i found out some kids were making fun of my 6 year old autistic brother and i’ve never felt this kind of rage before]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about incorporating a quick book recommendation into PD?  @pernilleripp #mra2019 Love this! @jlobrien25]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Steelers about to lose one of the best WR ever. Raiders, bless that future hall of famer 🤘🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldengateblond @JasonCrowCO6 @SenatorBennet @maddow @ValdezforCO @Alyssa_Milano @YadiraCaraveo @SenadoraJulie… https://t.co/nHkRGFgIxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3, no sugar for #lent. Guess what was in the newsroom today? 😕 https://t.co/PrjBbpcbZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dogs are so dramatic when it comes to food lol. Like chill, the food is right there. It’s yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Fearmongering About Pot Tells You About Mainstream Marijuana Coverage via @thenation https://t.co/QI4QfVNTig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christopherwink @seerichards @jeffbodle @Jah_Netti How do I get on the list?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won’t be able to wait to more days.  Just waiting until March 17 is too long.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megdogwuff @therealroseanne @JussieSmollett but the left is not racist if you believe that you need a brain scan]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you realize your foster dog has a coke nail... 🤨 #CueTheInterventionMusic 🎶… https://t.co/faLW2ZV4Lt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber @lyft Who will be the first to offer strictly electric car rides?  I would pay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[23 Amazing And Inspiring High School Yearbook Quotes #humor #laugh #smirk #amusing https://t.co/8yQtaxBAHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm the caregiver type, always trying to take care of my friends when they're sick. I get sick, no one cares. I fin… https://t.co/vFFQEb51ZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This father daughter dance on the @OneDayAtATime S3 finale - I just can’t 😭 please watch this show]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carnival is the weirdest time. You party nonstop for seven days and you’re hella confused when the rest of the worl… https://t.co/opfDubNBCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Tuesday!! There’s a lot going on over at the FB Page come check us out if you haven’t and don’t forget to sca… https://t.co/feJq9yofbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Janeunplain RIC has recently started making you take out ALL food items - even small snacks. I think they probably… https://t.co/eiHWy90etw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love sitting outside in the warm sunshine under a red umbrella at In-N-Out ☀️☀️, but even in this wintry weather,… https://t.co/HxEAIgHS3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL @bob_glatter Listen you Bob, how dare you speak to Mr Pollack this way.  Tú eres un idiota con el… https://t.co/Vv4YEyHSnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Career Day at RSD! @RanchoWallc @CajonValleyUSD https://t.co/azmZpHsqxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Limonggi Yo necesito uno. Pero empieza por algo más cómodo y más baja presupuesto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re typing and accidentally capitalize the “u” in osu . . . os- https://t.co/WfoFWd8ahz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CampbellGators give their ❤️ and soul to our scholars everyday! You all can never be thanked enough!… https://t.co/Z32tlAnKLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Insurance is refusing to pay for both of my daughters NICU stays because they “didn’t require mechanical ventilatio… https://t.co/ClSB7iYAmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Letting Nicholas Britell's score soothe me to sleep tonight. 😴 https://t.co/fRirPld545]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I hate the most is when people lie to me more specifically my own Dad]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a giant bruise on my butt bc last night Yoni said I would slide down the rain between the two escalators and… https://t.co/ngFWLuNU29]]></document><document><![CDATA[International Women's Day 2019 @ Cheryl Uttley - Fifth Avenue Collection https://t.co/sKnHsRySTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The older I get the more content I am with the idea of living alone forever and never socializing with anyone ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a fine line between too much water and not enough. Still haven’t found it 😂🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I picture Andrew Cuomo personally reading my statements like o wow ok u need this more than we do just take it really]]></document><document><![CDATA[thanks @mountainman for the perfect wake up song to loop as the sun peeks through just right:… https://t.co/kM3BkKL7IC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Declared a National Emergency, then hopped on a place to Florida to golf for the weekend. Trump is the National Eme… https://t.co/bav6yXeN0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[freshly shaved legs, cleans sheets, a big t shirt &amp; panties. sleeping on cloud nine tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Education Department Backtracks on Accreditation https://t.co/W7yoYQzPx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iCaptainMorgan Okay dnt get a shot of anything Mo got https://t.co/OhprgG1xRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tired. Stressed. Depression setting in. Ready to break down at any second.]]></document><document><![CDATA[what is the reason that i have weird dreams about english research papers.... last night was me stressing about fig… https://t.co/uguCrzULf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bibi_Trevi Muchas felicidades a tu Mamá Dios la bendiga https://t.co/0WneEIZlPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MickysWeHo #tishtish03 WATCH: https://t.co/zmR06G6iNs https://t.co/ttqCl8Hthy]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do I think that people who are left hand just do everything so naturally and don’t have to use effort bc I can’… https://t.co/gQZEkRzcGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m no expert in anything comic book related but I saw #CaptainMarvel last night and thought it was fun and ente… https://t.co/6HmBvbolkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Don't vote against the will of the people.... We voted you in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #bestfriend. #dogsthatsmile #girlsbestfriend #adoptdontshop #rescuedog #kensingtonpalace @ Kensington, Ohio https://t.co/Gb6V18aRrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I looked at a picture of 1 #police who stole our home . I thought " I Hate You " we wasn't allowed to say that word… https://t.co/K2azUjPJYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's 7am and I'm high as fuck  watching wish hauls on YouTube with my cat. Happy Saturday to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[feelin’ legal #18 🤪 @ Spartanburg, South Carolina https://t.co/oROSP0H5jL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Presunta asociación p delinquir busca impunidad p narcoterroristasFarc x delitos d lesa humanidad y condenar milita… https://t.co/2MbofaLyMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda want a beret.  Kinda only think people with bangs look good in berets.  Kinda want bangs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extremely important cheese taste test from @WisconsinCheese ahead of 😍Cheeslandia😍, which features more than 150 ch… https://t.co/fgJj3Po9xl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left my Casper pillow in a hotel in San Francisco one time and I think about it everyday. I hope you’re doing OK buddy 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisterTwyst @GovMikeHuckabee Please tell this low IQ person where I said anything about Islamic people that’s the… https://t.co/JYBsfKmjcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron_C5 @BenLewisAus @YorkshireSmash @Matthew669691 @CarsonGarrard_ @SamTanginoa Gentlemen I never told you about… https://t.co/XlaOiTOrD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#preschool #earlyartsnj #sonjaearlyarts #elmwoodparknj #february #2019 @ Early Arts - NJ State Certified Child Care… https://t.co/35P6EGNJMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to @Magda_Sepul “the impact of #SocialProtection should not be #gender neutral.” Dr Myamba urges us to “s… https://t.co/RiMaZmHHCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KWilliamsAuthor @Dillon2592 @JBOpi1 @untohernest @Scandianvia @shaunking @BernieSanders Abuses lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[They spent too much money on advertising when it could've been used to update older buildings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee &amp; chocolate chip cookies for breakfast. Yep, living the dream 😋 #SundayMorning #SundayFunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcma23 👏🏻🍷 exacto! Coincido en los 2 puntos, para secundaria Técnica NO ES EFICAZ, debe buscarse otra modalidad pa… https://t.co/MjXuU7lfKZ]]></document></documents></author>