<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[T-minus 1️⃣0️⃣ days  Until #spring #2019 🌷 #swipeleft ⬅️  #panorama 👀  #canon #t7i #lightroom #edit #clovis #sierra… https://t.co/SElpDAI78Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[He must wear a huge pair of depends if he actually does weigh 243...cause he sure as hell looks like he weighs 273]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough pill to shallow as a fan around trade deadline. You have a full roster and sit no one, for game day because n… https://t.co/cKWF5ud52J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also some interesting arguments to support self-represented litigants, replacing lawyers instead of judges. #SRLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAR AT HOME by @LifeNA360Degre1  Dedicated to the War at home Vets lose to daily, of the 20 service members who com… https://t.co/ceZJItIESl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opened my first Mythic!!  #lightseekers @LightseekersTCG https://t.co/FGeB9IYv3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Sham Characters: -Bookworm (Bookworm Adventures Deluxe) -Bandersnatch (Bandersnatch from Black Mirror) -Captai… https://t.co/6iiDyAnB3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellievan65 @Bornabrit1 @GOVTWINE @Sky_Lee_1 @Rey_Sistance @TheUSASingers @EarlOfEnough @Katpa73 @pebbles9010… https://t.co/pyZWnJAM1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Day of the Slugg Book Club with cure_the_streets_ ... I am so excited about the work we will do together.   W… https://t.co/glGoCt9VNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InspiringU2 Of course it is. That's why he wanted the job. And he did want it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiewright I bit into and immediately realized it was the last cookie from when I baked cookies for someone's bir… https://t.co/Gt2FRLdTeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barcalover9 Yupp pereira and mctominay did good especially since periera was struggling last games he played. We p… https://t.co/xrD3VHvHS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkySportsNews @ManCity @ChelseaFC Everyone is putting the blame on kepa when David luiz and Jorginho shanked their penalties]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dearborn (Mich.) 2020 DT Ali Saad was offered by Western Michigan, his first offer. https://t.co/6jiJsTWtQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[NIGHTS LIKE THIS out now  🌃  https://t.co/VIGcpKXn1r https://t.co/a08sowim7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[PRAY WITH JESUS .... awaken to this reality as I pray - Hebrews 7:25 @ Marietta, Georgia https://t.co/QikCrh1CEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful sunset over World Showcase at #Epcot wdwtoday #disneylife @ Epcot - Walt Disney World https://t.co/vD0LNjmQX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ❤️ the #Oscars, the #AcademyAwards #ViewingParty, presented by the #Queerbots lit up the @ClcktwrCabaret tonight!… https://t.co/Vfzd9x7b8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Link in the Bio:  #techfall👾  @glennericnelson #BlueFalcons @glennericnelson #ArnoldStatue @RedCon1Official… https://t.co/SKqOaqwY0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love it when a commentator as articulate as Jim Courier resorts to onomatopoeia. Ker-boom! Perfectly good way of de… https://t.co/eTxDZQamu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smonnat explains why the opioid epidemic is worse in some places but not others. Where we live/work/play matters! https://t.co/vEaLhPaELz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdeewayne Ray Liotta telling us he doesn’t even think about cigarettes, that is hilarious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @redpilledaus Get this terrorist out of there and take Rliah with her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pochodiaz @chempa @LORENT_SALEH @MariaFdaCabal @PoliciaColombia https://t.co/zEkyibTFjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SGUYBRAY She is already giving me some new ideas for understanding why I’m so turned off by so much of the titling… https://t.co/YD8gV4SQIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran the lake this morning last winter conditioning! Spring ball around the corner! #dawgspeed @ Saluki Stadium https://t.co/UQrQqsZSzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg the replies...I didn’t know 1D fans were still in full force lmaoo shouldn’t they be doing their college homewo… https://t.co/Vj9LZQeASU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's almost time for more #NewBedtimeStories at Cherry Tree Bar. This Saturday at 9pm we return with more excellent… https://t.co/8f4MsAWHJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been to Miami like 3 times a year last few years. Never made it to live. Never cared to either honestly. Eithe… https://t.co/b64hNCMPt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I’m glad your enjoying all of this. Cuz it’s killing me on the inside]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my wonderful and lovely Wife Eleisa! You are a true blessing from God!!! Time to pamper you some… https://t.co/a9RMnMF9cE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetylerhayes @ShaanVP @benthompson Better break into a good gmail account then]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCheckley Can’t wait to be on the beach! Make sure u bring the drinks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hagaman_kl @indie_man77 @quaintpeppers @infofromcloud @CorryRue @orchidslantern @gibbard_richard @TheCleftonTwain… https://t.co/o7Y0X4l33K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom “Tonight is What It Means to be Young”, the best Jim Steinman song that @RealMeatLoaf never sang!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Mighty Lion Boys Basketball team fell just short of an Area championship tonight.  What a spectacular season. I… https://t.co/yz5TI3ZGnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OU_JamesMyers Just saw your OU TV Spot on the OU Club Hockey Team! Good job! It was a disappointing though that yo… https://t.co/Xwu3U0eY3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re at @sxsw this weekend be sure to check out the homie @kjbagchi tomorrow. It’s a very serious topic with s… https://t.co/WlqUb5gMYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom I’d believe it, they would have shot or ran over him and killed him if they were real MAGA follower!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't get why we can't do a Berlin-type airlift for aid to Venezuela.  If Maduro shoots down a plane, it's his fu… https://t.co/9qSGvwJy1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Iowa TEs get a lot of publicity, so Irv Smith gets forgotten. I like Smith and would enjoy seeing another Badge… https://t.co/thETOoJUMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the mind of a socialist, yes the French poodle(aka John Kerry) is a conservative. I’m a little surprised you don… https://t.co/ZKcSE3CQAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Fusion Intelligence Analyst, Mid" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about these t… https://t.co/cE0jMzZQ0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horrific Hogwarts! From the House of Slytherin, Apprentice Wizard Andy Mccabe casting spells and lies at Trumphouse.  @ffweekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, @GovWhitmer's tax proposal will hit Michigan's poorest residents the hardest. But you know what also hits them… https://t.co/7O6vKoIWYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoldBlueWave @mcspocky Well how high of a wall are we talking about here?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AboveAllNorms @michellexdiaz And you’re fucking ugly 😂🤷🏽‍♂️. Anymore childish insults ? I can lose weight. You can’t fix that face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy how “family” is 15 minutes away from you and never makes an effort to be in your life🖕🏻🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkatz0630 @mdudas @JonathanErlichL Shuko and Noz for sure. But need to add Noda to the NYC list. About a year new.… https://t.co/bf8b1Tb1VR]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did they decide to make washing clothes two steps but washing dishes only one?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someday by The Strokes is one of the few songs I don't skip when it plays on my playlist]]></document><document><![CDATA['I Knew It Wouldn't Last Long.' What These Former Pro Athletes Can Teach Us About Preparing for Retirement https://t.co/pmTIulWKx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me waiting for all the chocolates and flowers from all the guys who slide into my DMs saying that they love me! 😂 https://t.co/MbU3sZUZjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@higginsgggg I think it will help you. With your gang stalkers. I could be wrong. Just whenever you can. Or not. I… https://t.co/ANDGG4ZGYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waltshaub With Trump's character and background... always overvaluing himself... he probably has experience in ext… https://t.co/rvb8DZLaUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadWendy @wvpublic I second that. Because nothing says “I love you” better than a day’s sponsorship on @wvpublic ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao okay so one time 2 years ago i was being really bold one night and thought i was gonna sit down and drink a pi… https://t.co/Z4vXujsadb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyCityParking I’ve tried speaking to three people and had zero luck. Adam, Amin and Alina.   Last response I recei… https://t.co/vPMQbnyWy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC WE HAVE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS CAPITALIST HYPOCRISY ,,ITS TIME TO GET WALL STREET PROFITS AND INSURANCE COMPANIE… https://t.co/Yt6097MXm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asuma ud el liderazgo ya que tiene tanto verbo y no coma una mierda en las castañuela ni se vaya a cojer perras a l… https://t.co/64MHIn8Kfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TransUnion I have yet to be able to reach your Canadian offices by phone, after 20 minutes, then another try curre… https://t.co/koncuuqNb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sick photoshoot today for no real reason.  📸: muikeee   #tragicherorecords  #sharptonerecords  #schecter… https://t.co/32qWbfoz5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3MW_CBB What madness is next, running their offense when they need a buzzer beater, instead of 4 players standing… https://t.co/1OLiAPyiUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife's a talent agent and she had a lot of parents not letting their kids read for this movie ... looks hilariou… https://t.co/x2cTlwAA2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow night is gonna be dope.  #Brooklyn99 at 9pm #CaptainMavel at 10pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaFC @ChelseaFCinUSA I know your international audience isn’t your biggest priority but how do you just chang… https://t.co/2S2S7cNYLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miguelsilvapix @mazzenilsson @vegans4bernie @wikileaks @marcorubio Believe it or not, if there’s one thing to atle… https://t.co/GXQVsdT85E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @roripierpont1 You should look at yourself in the mirror, if you can figure out how mirrors work with your 34 IQ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity We should be able to remove this Elizabeth Warren Kook from office with a doctor's note...]]></document><document><![CDATA[It'll interesting to see how this stands up:  “I told the president that if you colluded with the Russians, if your… https://t.co/ogCWjeszg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makkox @welikeduel Con la faccia de Salvini quanto sta?  Mail please =P]]></document><document><![CDATA[We loved Bella’s first trip to visit the snow, and so did Bella! Slide through to see baby Bella Moon making her fi… https://t.co/Xj2mduZAh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[El @Nacional paro en @CenturyLink_Fld y jugo contra @soundersfc_es hoy en Seattle, WA En Los Estados Unidos. Buena… https://t.co/vThwu5oWsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tessavirtue @RobertWeir1 Beautiful picture young lady all the best going forward]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Like Mueller had no clue Clapper lied? https://t.co/ZOrXsFIS7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yahoo question: I've developed an interest in anime and I don't like physical contact am I autistic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats guys on your opening first day in #lasvegas loved it! thenakedmagicians @chriswaynemagic miketylermagic… https://t.co/EFceE3e99G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesleyabravanel @thedailybeast Trump and Carlson belong together. They are both narcissistic, they both don't have… https://t.co/m7oPpnMHrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormyDaniels A lot of women will be jealous of you because your famous and they are not.  I wouldn't even stress… https://t.co/FfgftIpjh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala Harris calls for decriminalizing sex work, insists Trump is racist  https://t.co/IlZUrnHVmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker @AsteadWesley @jdawsey1 This new sign at the entrance to the White House is outstanding. https://t.co/WqJdTvkFjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CfieldsVFL @dchangas @sheapayne14 @CollegeGameDay It does in basketball. For technical reasons, they can’t broadca… https://t.co/dFTvi8plsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The crowd breaks out in DSP chants. #capsprom @smithpelly23 https://t.co/MTld6DkRTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spicygenuhveeve @callmeLucy_ We'll get that beer yall introduced to us]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_zavandija @MinjusDH_Peru ¿No reflejará la personalidad del Ministro responsable de ese sector? Digo yo🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. Putting it on the top of the head where no one can see is traditional.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Indonesia this year and probably japan again 🥵 or see the northern lights 🥺 idk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lucy_Osborne really enjoyed my chat with Rachel. Could I trouble you for a retweet please? Would be hugely appreci… https://t.co/shEOvTEQOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ral1 I hate his Yankee jersey, and this all of his ancestral beliefs, but he is a pure sports fan in an impure wor… https://t.co/l03cJvVo2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarianneZirkle @williamlegate “The Optional Emergency” by William B. Turner https://t.co/qgCwHzflJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump You can’t even behave like a statesman and/or diplomat in your own country.  Including… https://t.co/nADJJkqid2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does everyone at the club have to get 10 of there buddy’s involved and not fight 1v1. Tired of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Pliny the Younger (2019) by Russian River Brewing Company at @apexbar — https://t.co/0aJQtozFh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackj3nkins @RYDERBPATTERSON Yeah same with u of m. How many chances at a National championship have they had and… https://t.co/dSR9kQes7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be watching anything else because you are repulsive and disgusting. Enjoy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FilmTwitter  What the duck is this??!!!   #TheTrumpProphecy https://t.co/A2C18b6XYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shesmaad &amp; @mnek brought the color &amp; the vocals! 🌈🌈🌈 @ The Bowery Ballroom https://t.co/fkbCQacRro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaureenWilcox1 @realDonaldTrump Fanatical fascist statements by cult ridden and sick individuals should be banned from Twitter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally bit the bullet and got me an ESPN+ subscription. Ready for all kinds of MLS and Saint Louis FC goodness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moment when the guy next to you at the airport stands up and rips a massive fart. 😮🤔]]></document></documents></author>