<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Get Free $25 Roblox Gift Card Offer  Win $25 Roblox Gift Card Offer By A Complete Simple Sign Up,    Sign Here:… https://t.co/4HaCTkiIAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked exactly the same question!  In fact Jewish friends of mine stopped speaking to me when I asked them that qu… https://t.co/fE7hXm8H63]]></document><document><![CDATA[And thanks to the wonderful Megan who is covering my @chirpradio show today from 4-6pm CST, give her a listen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StantonTravis So easy to find something personal... https://t.co/RPyHcnUJYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbhermann @DesiLydic @TheDailyShow @zoisays Absolut richtig! Sehen leider die wenigsten so...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiseiLounge I might occasionally see a bottle of kombucha in my home, but I certainly don’t want to see that garbage at my bar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parrot want to touch a cat https://t.co/3knQHqes5F via @YouTube @catnip0715 and all cat n parrot lovers out there. This will make your day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hcapriles Qué cinico eres no te cansas de tratar de buscar como te puedes acomodar con el nuevo gobierno eres un descarado]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been blessed with a wonderful pregnancy and I can’t wait to meet my sweet boy but I just came across this pi… https://t.co/9a3R5yPUby]]></document><document><![CDATA[my name is not i was born in a new brand  my age is going on a day  i like to the point where we can do a lot more… https://t.co/6lrWwbPJaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDanielGih Most definitely! And flavor is a huge factor for many people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another reason this show was amazing. The relationship between Shawn and Angela was one for the books 🤗😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SancadillaNorte A mi no me tocó verlo jugar pero para lo que he escuchado de mi.papá te quedas hasta corto.. como… https://t.co/pLEFvZNPV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I selected #Integration as this week’s #AzureTrivia answer. Who else? https://t.co/eWP3weEnRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monaloca @ThomasJTobin1 I'm a woman There is a War on Women going on right now  You need to read more]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got: Darkwing Duck  You’re a natural performer, and while you may be too modest... #humor #laugh #smirk… https://t.co/FtAWD3Gjpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachKy_Louw Pretty cool! Congratulations, keep doing your thing, well deserved!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grannygrande I hope it somehow stops. When I saw the crazies at CPAC both the speakers and those in the audience,… https://t.co/E4OKGiWkLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question @JWJIEmory #jwjiblackmen : Fahamu's work can be seen on several MARTA spaces, including buses and stations… https://t.co/ZGIG4by9M6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Dolvett #quince #3121 #diet #thebiggestloser #biggestloser #diet #mental #spirituality #pyschology https://t.co/UEKvIJUE3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wffconf #wfflimitless CA Schools Represents 💪🏼💓💪🏼 #sodexo @ Dallas Convention Center https://t.co/G0h2UuRHT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyTaylorRock @DJPh03NiX @AliciaEDove You don’t get diabetes by eating! Sorry but as the mother of two type 1 di… https://t.co/zVCUo9JpR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So can we just plan a movie night for next weekend and niggas put up to cook? 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to get home from work today and get the depression nap I truly deserve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentines Exchange @longbranch1st @Longbranch_Elem https://t.co/ZH8DQCfQdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BellsInequality @DLoesch We are tired of it and Nancy too impeach Omar and Nancy and talib]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @FrewsCrews to post 7 covers of books I love - no explanations - no reviews - just t… https://t.co/36sxWeMqNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar Ask Him How He Feels 2 Be TOKEN CPAC BLACK MEMBER. Was The Closet Big Enough 2 Include Throngs Of OTHER BL… https://t.co/05wD6H2dkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dude thinks I’m playing hard to get but I’m not playing at all?? https://t.co/YAJwH7ZzQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper Beauty and the Beat was released the year I graduated High School.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Boys Basketball Team!! 🏀 Good Luck tomorrow! Let’s Go Eagles 🦅 #STATESBOUND]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Apodaca, Nuevo Leon https://t.co/8igsJ2BO9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Wow! Wow! If there was a theme for Sunday, it was #worship and #sing! From @aaronrburke message with… https://t.co/F7BWSmZCpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @MikeBloomberg Feckless? Google this old woman..if you know how to use google... "President Trump's… https://t.co/vgKGZD3awT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright, Kansans. Thank you for several of you reaching out already. There is not an online link and I am not sure… https://t.co/Yy6RTslnJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to head to bed with my sweet stuffed puppy friend of almost 16 years, hard for me to believe that I've had hi… https://t.co/XzEeh9fwyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s been a whole year today since I got my trees constellation tat. the song and this tattoo still mean so so much… https://t.co/gm3srxFWwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ladyminutemen fall short to Newark Collegiate Academy 65-54. Sam Keller has a career high 30 points in the loss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome time with Team @joe_farrell21 at @TUVirtualStudio  #LifeAtATT #rontourage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qanon76 @realDonaldTrump Projection is the narcissistic denial of unacceptable inner impulses as though they are outside of self. . . ,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foreverkneeld Welcome to the party! We have a lot more fun here on the women’s side!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AddisonDJenkins Pete just makes me sad.  Probably because I worked in celebrity treatment centers.  I’ve seen this before.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this bitch had the NERVE to take my assigned seat literally almost halfway through the semester]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickd9678 @kulpilis318 More like Preston. Piper’s jingle bells ruin her sneaking, Preston rips his collars off when in sneaky pursuit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GettFest Yeah they quickly just became my least favorite team in the league. Kepa - least fav player]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate an, “i work really hard for my money” guy at the strip club. what the fuck do you think i do? i deal with me… https://t.co/eAkmiqF2e0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lsdevargas @lharris63 It's just a little wobbly. I might add another cross bar on the wide side to add stability.… https://t.co/gHAIwkAneZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Please don't put that old partial-history trop up.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Bday to best guy a gal could ask for!!!! 🍰🍰🎂🎂 @ Every BODY's Fit https://t.co/puZ70dX8DF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream last night that for some reason I had all the boys numbers so I decided to call Connor and he didn’t… https://t.co/gO4tHfxcwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DarKnightYT @NBA2KLeague @chiquitae126 @WarriorsGaming She honestly only had her friends support and the negative… https://t.co/tDgptUxkcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the girl who reschedules brunch plans because her soccer team is playing a meaningless match that they won’t wi… https://t.co/DmiZx0FdGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAY 3: I have accepted a challenge from @WabashPrincipal to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no revi… https://t.co/mbs9bXZy9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kaitlin_Benz @Tinder @bumble @okcupid @hinge 41 states and DC have revenge porn laws. Remind them it’s a prosecuta… https://t.co/2iKi64zTnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @CNNOpinion that was the cyber attacker jared valdez is downloaded malware spyware rootkit trojan on their pcs… https://t.co/fcqER9kALT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I never knew Chuck E. Cheese recycled their pizza ew lemme go vomit now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m0onsucc look at you just going IN all the time ugh my artist , my friend my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have never been able to watch this episode without bawling. Today it is just for a different reason. RIP… https://t.co/YIy71pREpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luvlylayy @Cristy_jal @PostRoz @mffisher what does race have to do with it?  You dont even know my skin color!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrible 3s and now headed towards the fork you 4s.... man this kid sucks the life out of me with his multi persona… https://t.co/2t9r5pzXXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Jackets have had a great week of softball! Beat Dora 15-0 &amp; Sumiton Christian 13-3. They’re fun to watch 🖤💛 #jacketpride @jeharris2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddstarnes Someone said it was to stir up sentiment for the anti lynching bill (which passed) so they can’t be hu… https://t.co/7lN4yjtj08]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just remembered in middle school i had kurt cobain’s suicide note saved to my iphone notes???]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. CR Doritos 2. Regular Lays 3. BBQ Lays 4. Fritos 5. NC Doritos  6. Cheetos 🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men just can’t deal with the fact that I will always love the Bash Brothers more than them, childhood crushes never die 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyKrueck Wow, eavesdropping sounded like a phenomenal way to spend a lunch break.]]></document><document><![CDATA[who wants to be super crackheaded with me and get umbrella academy tattoos?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justabloodygame Holy shit, using this garbage madlibs joke format to actually tell a *different* joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassySwift1 @RawStory @Sherri317 Only if I can hold the door open for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i want to watch this movie like a millions times just so i can see all the small interesting details. This movie is… https://t.co/LjVWZseb3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[What president's real campaign footage appeared in Clint Eastwood's movie In The Line of Fire? #PoliticalScience]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we know .. 35 infants ripped from the savanna #ZimbabweElephants #VisitZimbabwe destined for brutal #China Zoos… https://t.co/zZO3W0IsJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaPutrelli @acidoviejo @adribilu De qué país está hablando que huyeron los que pudieron?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helped watch my coworkers account while he was on the presidents club trip and he got me a baseball from Jamaica it’s amazing 😭🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets I knew it!!!Graham has been in Trumps back pocket since 2016]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LexiDanger ❤️💕 #hoochthebasset #desert #houndog 🌵🐾 #bassethound https://t.co/OdjC9mpgBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that you give them choices! My girls always tell me how much they love your art class! Thank you for letting… https://t.co/NW7TB9Q7v9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueVavoom @__wonderfrankie Shit looks traumatizing and like a bitch gotta wear a faja https://t.co/eh4mZAh50f]]></document><document><![CDATA[More fun snap shots from this weekend ingoophealth. It was like Disney Land for adults. Thank you @gwynethpaltrow,… https://t.co/5CfAvxyBIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truck in the shop.... Who cares 😆 I love this bed already. The box has wheels #tuftandneedle #ls1 #lsx #c5… https://t.co/TR9d0URdSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Intellectual property fosters innovation and promotes economic growth while shaping an organizations brand identit… https://t.co/g6cfBGQAwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_TWC @DoogieTWC Looks like fun. I what to go.😊😊😊 Have a blessed weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took Jacob driving now that he has a permit and my mom told me to only take him to the high school but I took him… https://t.co/mLU4YEFmUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tatianashanks2 My dad now works with one family in particular. He built the website for Rachel Joy Scott a couple… https://t.co/C1OItXCiyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the kind of phony love and attention given a dictator that Trump craves.  He will not stop until he receive… https://t.co/9gjCbSSxf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[he literally just got in the shower (his showers are short) and I’m mad bc all I want to do is hang out w himmm 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please donate $5 &amp; help support Rowan’s Women’s soccer team!! https://t.co/b1qB64WEIG https://t.co/7HBzwY00Gk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes He won’t end up in jail... Trump will pardon him unless enough pressure on Trump makes him retire before]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatefulchance I am so excited for you!!  You will be great at anything you put your mind to!  Congratulations!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[But we see Him who for a little while was made lower than the angels, namely Jesus, crowned with glory and honor be… https://t.co/VGt0TkDTFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottHech Not real comfortable accepting your opinions either. So....let’s wait for the truth. I think we can agree on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else have so much hate towards someone that just seeing their name makes you wanna stab them? https://t.co/uZ1IwvkTZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry me wanting to kill my self because of what you did to me made you sad. you fuck face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking @Martamendoza718 @BernieSanders Iowa has given US Grassley &amp; King Does Anyone Care What Iowa thinks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know u been around your friends way to much when you start talking like them 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This transformation isn’t about weight loss or inches, it was about confidence and proving to myself that I could s… https://t.co/sbdlaDbvM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti I took me a sec, but I see what you did there. Good job!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reidenbach8 I might have to invest in that since it’s my only other option]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blackgirlinmain I only use towels once, but jeans, as many times as i can before washing. lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week I voted for the environment in the #Outremont federal byelection. If you haven't voted yet, today's your… https://t.co/LOJ0QO9icv]]></document></documents></author>