<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Remember DMs, gold doesn't always have to come in coins. And it doesn't always have to be a reward. Sometimes it ca… https://t.co/JIiMdXbpH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebruenig My granddaughter is Peanut, her aunt is Sweetpea, her mother &amp; grandma both Sweetie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevZCastle @BFKillah Some hills aren't worth being wounded on, never mind dying on.  SCSA is right.  I get there's… https://t.co/ZSCIv1wYT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OCNaNa2013 @mitchellvii You noticed this too! Seems the only party screening RACIST are leftists. I certainly do n… https://t.co/f8VHR6SRNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up hung over... got over it... drank some more and now hung over again 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Not so fast cupcake. Far from done]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anorthnorth Oh, y’all are going DOWN!!! Dunks fo days!! #TeamOtter https://t.co/d6RnUty8mz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frigginhiramguy @tuesdiwoodworth @SugarjetsStudio I’m already hooked on Population Tire.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlombardiNFL @evansilva A lot of players do not like playing for Gruden and many also don't respect him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mixitwithtom207 @revrrlewis @mmfa The guy Trump said was crazy hahahahhaahahahaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's sunset!!! Downtown sky's was on fire!! 🔥🔥🔥 📸 @canonusaimaging  📸 Lense: @tamronusa AF18‑270mm f/3.5‑6.3 Di‑… https://t.co/ueoYEpFSdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniPrickett @FishingStripes @eo_chic @litecamping @curlylox5 @kathym8896 @KathrynKHarvick @kyprobassangler… https://t.co/aSDtQkXTPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This needs to stop NOW !!! @Edwin_Boyette you are a good man, God Bless🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSavingDisco Do people actually say that shit to you???!? What the FUCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UHC when you want to take the survey and put you on hold because they know they f up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bribrilukes Lmfaooooo this just made me laugh mid bar you’re not wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "College Intern" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about these types of opportunities in #Denver, CO. #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanLRodrigue10 Hay que ser objetivo, aunque duela: la batalla de hoy se perdió!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheySleep_55 Is it only for today or can I vote daily? https://t.co/8bvdexeTJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Quinn, Branch and Parker alone free up just under $30M in cap space. Likely Amendola will be cut as well adding… https://t.co/Dkp6bhAgPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank @VetTix for a great Valentine’s Date with the @ArizonaCoyotes tonight. #VetTix https://t.co/yMrlUoJ0hQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanehardy58 @Sue85162237 @HillaryClinton Funny thing is Crooked has NO IDEA how irrelevant she is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY GIRL @_officialnova JUST RELEASED A BOP... GO LISTEN TO IT YALL https://t.co/ncyu2oKdTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucky4192 @BostonGlobe U didn't see on the news yesterday how USA BEGAN I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Ea… https://t.co/GvTl6Phk5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[The western swing comes to an end in Edmonton tonight. @HennyTweets has the preview for tonight's matchup against t… https://t.co/ScETEMIwlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klthoreson @bikebrampton Ya church / voden are pretty good, also going through the park on etobicoke creek trail t… https://t.co/IFoeocwneZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucker, Concha Blast CNN for Cheering on DNC’s Fox News Ban from Debates https://t.co/6CrTcnBXAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@11thHour @KenDilanianNBC Divide the millions from Party of the Regions by the number of years, less than 4, and yo… https://t.co/wFTK6QXiDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spicynormie @bbykaelin oh I know and I can see why too I just. You’re unreal kshfjdekdjdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like posting my dick that’s what I think of this momo devil cocksucker face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MercedesGlobal Keep up the great work you do.. #InternationalWomensDay #Respect]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsTylerKSR I could say something but I won’t. Coach Cal is as good as there is. And then some.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RochelleRitchie MAGA ppl are happy because a fraud who told a vicious lie about THEM has been exposed for the liar… https://t.co/jvRVk3j73a]]></document><document><![CDATA[9) Ruta 129 Ramal Santo Domingo, recorre San Nicolás - Monterrey  10) Ruta 310 Ramal Praderas - Estación Talleres,… https://t.co/j12nSu1YQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't know what's high 'Til you been down so low The future's bright Lit up with no where to go To and fro the pend… https://t.co/7mHZP604dK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another successful pumpituprp party. @ Pump it Up of Randolph, New Jersey https://t.co/jowZTZ952l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskJayne @UberShouts @Fusion @carpe_ow Lol take the day off or not you’re gonna get slapped by the fish!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@georgew73855762 @TrumpSugar @SpaceForceBravo @phil_mckraken @DWCDroneGuy @HouseOfJames2 @alterhan @alshadowdancer… https://t.co/yfytIX7PQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody:  Samsung Users: YOU KNOW MY GALAXY HAS A BIGGER BATTERY AND ITS CHEAPER!! I DON’T KNOW WHY YOU’D WANT A IPH… https://t.co/IM5zBWBsfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dropsofjmw awww my love 😍💙 these last three months with you have been nothing short of amazing, and i look forward… https://t.co/QGOg2VgG7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aquí voy a entrenar de nuevo, 4:30 am con un rico clima 10 grados y a darle. #liderazgolimpio #journeyto100 en Mexi… https://t.co/XObGVx0bra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always fun to hit my favorite book store in #pnw @powells to sign a few in-store copies #masteringfearbook… https://t.co/QHT70hJcta]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a washed up gokart driver, a NASTRUCK phenom, 4 proof of purchase box tops, and two podcasters share the same… https://t.co/OGLQDt8qkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimothyMWallace @annvandersteel https://t.co/rW3xHY4OTA Comments about the coup in the Vatican.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I’m reading now. #ReadingMatters #GoodLeadersRead #GreatReadersLearn #JWrightMinistries @ My New Normal https://t.co/w9J5m9rRHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh @KatyTurNBC. Loved the last words you had as handing over the show to @AliVelshi. You both... continue to garner… https://t.co/poDu41Ynj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think we can all relate !! #beerleague @ Greater Anaheim/Orange County https://t.co/0JER83dIeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wikileaks @maddow So did you search?  And if so were they telling the truth or lying?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fucking hate school bro like this shit is so tiring it makes me feel empty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Church Hill North, Richmond https://t.co/5nPbcvip0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudisExcitatio @HHardliner @WhiteIsTheFury If i supported censorship just because i disagree with someone, I would… https://t.co/W45kvV4agr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyOatley I need to meet your sister, we have so much to talk about]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want my main focus in life to be building a better relationship with Jesus. Be around people who love Jesus and w… https://t.co/ivvlWRfil3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwobitcoinEstaf @ealmal Si te calmas y vuelves a leer todo vas a darte cuenta de la falla en tu razonamiento No te apasiones. Control.]]></document><document><![CDATA[trump trolls don't care that he allocates money for the military just to cover the fact that he has never served]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitivamente agarraste al toro por los cuernos , gracias por aguantar mis locuras y darme dos personitas maravil… https://t.co/yXeZdJ4aTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[d*_*b Morning reality check. If anyone ever deserved the Nobel Peace Prize... It's that guy. #lespaul… https://t.co/yBgA58uez3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrazyAF_ButCute A lot of ladies are jelly of those big natural beauties up front. Jelly being short for jealous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karli_bonne @Hawk_Eye_79 @TAnon79512106 @KamalaHarris @JussieSmollett @realDonaldTrump 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaVosk this portrait hangs right next to the @broadwaycom studio door and every time I pass it I’m like 💚💚💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karaswisher @kevinroose @nytimes @Twitter @nest @mosseri @facebook You spend longer on your thermostat than I do on my phone. How?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruuuhhhh do not sit here in the Sauna and laugh at videos out loud like ur at a comedy club!! WHY BE THAT GUY!!!???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so dumb excited for Vive Latino and my trip to México City. Y'all have no clue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jknapp_ @wolfofmutburner @CameronDawgsFan @2KSupport @Ronnie2K Dude's a clown lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday neeyahbeetv @ Urban Banquet Hall https://t.co/3fYGz02rOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alisonlunch @BrittaRowings I’ve been nursing a family size bag of Target brand frozen chicken fingers since Monday… https://t.co/2wMjOhuuie]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can run outside in shorts when it's 20 but need 3 layers in the house when it's 68.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an absurd, illogical, ahistorical take on the work of an extraordinary historian who looked where others di… https://t.co/VuVV0VA9eb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bangladesh fire: 70 dead as blaze rips through Dhaka apartment buildings - CNN https://t.co/9q69UHZi6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rob_Stover @JaimePinkynm @stevekaplowitz Ok, like what? Winning? Being the best of a generation at your position?… https://t.co/AyHq9bLm8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiggsBarstool He just robbed us a Fowler vs Brooks playoff. Gonna take me a while to forgive Keith Mitchell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djsilverback13 @archiekinnane Losing after being 3-0 up is tragic but it happens. The lights going off  is complete bullshit though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fifi_Foxx That's an awful way to talk to a woman you don't need him. The only person worthless is him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KentBoeseDC This is a good time to take a hard look at parking in the area. With these spots gone, the long block… https://t.co/srRZOIAJ6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Electrospect People was saying Lebron hit that YesJulz chick. Then niggas found a verse where Pusha T was talking about it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickmon1112 @neontaster @SpeakerPelosi She...deleted it after it became apparent it was a hoax...this is the big “… https://t.co/MoC08UQ0nA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fermontyvila I wake up and I look up. I hope for darkness A storm for me I love storms. https://t.co/ueVVzZJHuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sokol914 @jessevasquezz Love how the Hawkeye fans and present and future wrestlers are recruiting at all times.  F… https://t.co/tnc7LVev8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[You right-handed people have no idea how difficult it is to fill out a card!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youlosenordys @HLAurora63 @SpeakerPelosi And the new funding bill just passed prevents the detention or charging o… https://t.co/f34baof6yN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pixelpreaching @oufenix Wonder which party Rat Winger John Wayne would join today? https://t.co/JqOZ8PT951]]></document><document><![CDATA[#washingtonmonument #McLean #DC #biztravel @ McLean, Virginia https://t.co/EFKiX8aPCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GandalftheMead @RabbitRidgeWine Was there any toast or char on the oak?  What kind of oak?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The giant gala at Union Station every year is arguably indiscreet for a secret star chamber.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph N. Barometer 30.135 in, Falling. Temperature 20.0 °F. Rain today 0.00in. Humidity 69%]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awsten I love how you think talking to his mom is going to stop him from sorting you into the hufflepuff house honey. #theshade #acceptit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Binging S2 of @SCDiet. It sure is strange seeing @AndyRichter playing such a jerk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlisfitDisaster I told you my life story. I guess all the tag games are gone now. Too late ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work goes by so much better and faster when u don’t have to work around dickheads and cry baby bitches]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are just ONE NIGHT away from the 2019 @hrc_nash Equality Dinner presented by @Bridgestone, an annual fundraising… https://t.co/KzdKUUVfeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frechinawesome2 @tripp1972 @SethOnHoops @GoBearcatsMBB I’m a huge Bearcats fan, and this is true.   UK is a legit Championship contender.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Juice by Lizzo. Fun song! https://t.co/TJf5U42uju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZurnElDos Don’t even start. See what you started @tmac0313. Ya try giving a kid a compliment and the people in the… https://t.co/zSGZ3S0eOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UnlikelyMondayAccomplishments: Gritty jumping in the ring at #RAWPhilly. (Would be great...) @WWERomanReigns fans,… https://t.co/jPWSUqnnD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who puts all their bags in the overhead bins leaving nothing at their feet while they are sitting in a row with extra leg room?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danny52570162 @MarkFishkin @SleterFC @MLS Why would the league fine one of their franchises, when the league agree… https://t.co/3wTSQ6ijsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebbieDoesTwitt @laureldavilacpa @NWPinPDX @B52Malmet @ProudResister @RoArquette @BetteMidler @OhNoSheTwitnt… https://t.co/sVF36x5lpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end of the day I have wonderful friends and family who are always here for me 💯💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMcElhinny Isn't it roughly what the coal severance tax would produce if it wasn't being eliminated?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last time w/ da #Illini in Champaign this season.   It’s also senior Aaron Jordan’s (@Pilot23_) last run at home as… https://t.co/JSUM6MommD]]></document></documents></author>