<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Former Oklahoma Senator Fred Harris is a nice man, I met him in 1976. But Senator Harris did to the Democrats in 19… https://t.co/jviAESw98h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharlesPreston 6. I'm pretty unusual in that I worked at one for nearly 9 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenCherryhomes @dirtberry It’s just reality as everybody knows that throwing overhand is an unnatural motion and e… https://t.co/UY4Kw8veEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuarioCandanga Nada, que tu nombre suena para ser presidente de gobierno de España.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep it real, there simple is none other. Today's #newrock #indierock #Music  #unsignedartist #indiemusic #Rock Say… https://t.co/kH1foqubMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't understand the GOP leadership right now. If they let Trump get away with a declaration of an imaginary nati… https://t.co/A5Krk3Delc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seen someone get shot at the k liquor store on painter when I was in high school]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of LN girls tonite. We played hard but came up short in the state championship. Congrats to HSE on winning th… https://t.co/byMPJ0ULAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited that the future @CMofEC site at the Block 7 Development will be the new location of a two-section ECASD Com… https://t.co/JtIdxFOjbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HBCUStrong @UNCF @Bakari_Sellers hosting the State of HBCU’s https://t.co/dPzTG3m0lA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little dry and woody, yet as splendid as ever. Needs a little more time to mellow. - Drinking  The Purple Kriek (… https://t.co/cbzSl9ufD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[i tried to let go my  lover  thought if I was alone than maybe I  could recover  to cry it way... to write away...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eyes2die455 @rt_feet @rt2promopig @rtfemdom1 @rtfindom @touchRTP @mike_mashall @rtsuck3r @RTAlex_1 @Rtpiggy30 I wa… https://t.co/94CvAfLfjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pdxalerts You know it’s bad when they’re just ‘souls’ and not ‘people.’ Hoping for a safe outcome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jameschough2017 @jacobinmag @SteveNickSmith I already loved her before, but I love her even more now. 👏👏🔥🔥 https://t.co/gwX2YBiEz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ERCboxoffice @Batmancanseeyou Disney can’t afford another loss like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottMColbert Collapse? They have a license to print money forever from their smartcar app and subscription platfo… https://t.co/QdFLLfXQJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikonasis1313 Bro I use to rock the no Limt chain in middle School lol and death row]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissy_lee24 I agree to a point, but Kyle had plenty of power until he screwed up on pit road. Maybe some self re… https://t.co/fs3gnYFyD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyCorne @beerbarbeyond @BeerCountrySA @RolyTheBeerGeek @metallanebeer @SABreweries #hazedandinfused https://t.co/o7tI7Fjb7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been up since 6:30 am #tcb. I worked on a few new tattoo designs. @JLClothing and I got some new fabric today for s… https://t.co/INBJFAGIDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PupptLeader #PresTrump has NO control of #HouseCommittees which are NOW going forward in REAL investigation of… https://t.co/41Dv3y5m0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill The real issue is why did the staff recommend against giving Kushner and Ivanka security clearance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorDScott @Americanpie48 Really? How come he got $4Millions yesterday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kings_coast Question, as I don't really know much about coffee, your blended coffee, for example the brown sugar f… https://t.co/NzqIwv9tc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FullFrontalSamB Why worry about fat people if your comrade says the world is coming to an end in 12 years. And BTW… https://t.co/66h3Q4UpaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachWatson11 Wish I could get my wife to listen. She won’t protest,not because she doesn’t believe it, she hates… https://t.co/SY2X3XTb5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@137pm I’m reading “A Random Walk Down Wallstreet” right now and it’s been great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those videos aren’t that long ago. Yikes. Killed my vibe. I’m going to bed. I’m a dweeb. 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyRod33 KC is red Denver is Blue Whoever starts Flacco No playoffs for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why I’m not with nobody, cuz I don’t  wanna hurt nobody ❣️ @ Downtown Baltimore https://t.co/eHqipls7QP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Albert Einstein said that the definition of insanity is is doing the same thing over ans over again and expecting different results.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was McNeil’s first hit of spring!? Sheesh. I’m rooting for this guy. Big time. But the game is littered with g… https://t.co/SeBK5kbfQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodmorning Family and Friends. Be Blessed! @ Browns Summit, North Carolina https://t.co/kAOo1uqgby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adriiyeet All of us have a little prejudice towards new people we meet of if there skin color it’s about seeing pa… https://t.co/6ynwGWelsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomstakes I clicked on your Twitter to see if you were and eagles fan or a rams fan lol then I see it all over you… https://t.co/auYdT7G9my]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robsonian Glad to hear! And yes to both! It’s amazing what a great sauce comes from such simple ingredients.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Believer’s Valley Experiences @NMazepin the LORD is with Angelica &amp; his goodness and mercy will follow her… https://t.co/V3hjareQBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wrath_of_Comm Thank you Amy for including me on your lists! I think the next collection of photos should be on the… https://t.co/5vn47XeAS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_UnaSonrisa_17 Muy buenos días para ti también Sonrisas y feliz viernes cuídate mucho saludos cordiales,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little something different, #flowerpower at #mondaymorningflowers #balloondecorations #balloondelivery @ Monday M… https://t.co/8TtrUOeuXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great reasons regardless of the position. I’ve always believed in personality traits over skills. You can teach ski… https://t.co/V3emJzQigZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kare11 Given the shoddy way a lot of Medical practices keep their electronic and paper files, I have not given my… https://t.co/ZkBS7nqUBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandyDarity @blackenterprise @MARCMORIAL @NatUrbanLeague No self respecting Black Wallstreeter is putting in all t… https://t.co/BGNhFmQ8Uw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can do breakfast (or #brunch) at anytime. Day or night. Especially at night. 😉 Having breakfast at night was one… https://t.co/1gJupnTqZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maximildublin Oh I know. She has also gotten in trouble for violating ethics rules for political activities since… https://t.co/FZU4LAlZgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN GOAT GRIZZLY BEAR ENCOUNTER IN CANADIAN ROCKIES https://t.co/jdjr8i1sgU via @YouTube    This bear had moun… https://t.co/YoWYHHx3hS]]></document><document><![CDATA[treyarch fucked up by changing the score from 75 to 100. i drop 40 with ease now]]></document><document><![CDATA[The google and apple ascension to the top of the rankings was wild to watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Schwarzaile What ryan did wont ever hurt a victim of a hate crime, ever. That's where it starts and end for me. Ju… https://t.co/9gPptLChpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am an #energiaphoenix  Few people see the work that’s done to build a brand.  I’ve been learning the hard way and… https://t.co/7BNkvYjhPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillybean9280 @tristondahlke @rcon530 @PatM0540 @tiffanyrazo @fernando262371 @thd0540 @mattspencer1983… https://t.co/L6JyiZ58Jw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DariusJButler Zero. Unless Jerry Jones asks Jon Gruden's advice on retaining an elite pass rusher.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandondarby While the department’s history has been plagued by corruption @SheriffGuerra should not be painted w.… https://t.co/UwSEi4fTJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw the greatest thing. Homeless (I assume) white guy holding a sign by the road that says "spread some cheese on this cracker" 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[bro what is wrong with people. i get he’s a miami fan. but come on man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No surgery needed on the knee! Small meniscal tear and cartilage damage. God is good! #blessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisEvans Too poofy for my tastes, but I’m not a stylist. So what do I know?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PCHdotcom_01 🤠🤠🤠Please Reply left message  Stopped other orders from going thru @pchdotcom  Get TV Series DVD Blu… https://t.co/Cep23BwDtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Download the @WTHR Weather App, monitor @KellyGreeneWTHR social media and tune in to #WTHR TV at 6pm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheaFontana Thank u for all u did. I'll tell u again, my 5 yr old daughter loves DC heroes because of your writing… https://t.co/B6r7xJzSdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobebill @charliekirk11 Fake Christian? You Know? Many in Bible had multiple failures but God still chose them.  F… https://t.co/e04p4tE7l9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@upine @VillanuevaEdgar @AnandWrites @VillanuevaEdgar I’m curious how you’d respond to @upine ‘s comment to me above.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CowboysNation!!! If we're not going to get Thomas or Collins..who would you like the Cowboys to get in free agency… https://t.co/Z6qTBHijay]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Record for 2020 LB @nickschwarz3441 up to 310! Nice work, Nick! #TheChase #WinInTheDark https://t.co/ugm9iJhQ4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best short from last year wasn’t even nominated: Tweet-Tweet, from Russia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have new secondary instagram account where I will only be posting my Lego and toy photos from now on. @ Galveston… https://t.co/Ez7TMHQA8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DodgersNation If there are 6 healthy pitchers worthy of being in a starting rotation, sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clever, but the Raiders did have Amari Cooper which literally made the WR/QB connection AC/DC, so I feel like this… https://t.co/FBGR9Fh8Aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 29th. Kappa Sigma. K Camp. 91’ Thompson. All proceeds benefit the troops. Good music, good times, good causes… https://t.co/7dcBP0TZpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[New slap for ya airpods! Available everywhere so go download that shit! Link in my bio! #russcoson #jzp #junglezone… https://t.co/w1fTpYYWtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timescolonist They gotta re route the Pat Bay through the water shed...its the only way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonJeffries Should you estimate without going into a complete technical analysis? Experimenting with trying to rel… https://t.co/N6cRhf2hIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elguapo Congratulations! Thank you for being a Brown! We will always support you ! O-H!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alienchemtrails @TalbertSwan You want me to show you where Trump openly admits he’s racist? That’s ridiculous! No… https://t.co/ALBps9C8Xp]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had eaten this during an undergrad hangover I would be invincible, like Mario with a star]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amfa_4 @AMFANational @SouthwestAir Thanks so much for acting like children and burning the passengers because you… https://t.co/gpQyL2OteX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that we're heading to @WrestleMania 35, the question is, will we see #TheUndertaker completing in an match at t… https://t.co/UBJifq8ExA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t like this mans character.  Not worth the risk of him screwing up the chemistry that @SpursOfficial have rig… https://t.co/cNxrJT5abj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanStebbins I’ll play whatever it takes to keep him. We’re not going to replace him if he goes. He’s one of the… https://t.co/oPB9DcXCLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will confidently say now the Big 12 race is over and the precious streak is over unless they pull a rabbit out of the hat tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cocinadeolivia Cosita bella, cosita bien hecha. Un urra !  para Dios por tan bella creación 😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Complex @Drake @creedmovie @HollyWoodHino Not if he keeps dropping that left]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring break is next week and you betcha ass that... I’ll be sittin at home all week with my friendless ass😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I want the Raptors to take control of the east but they’re gonna do so if Kawhi never plays 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like my trip to Chicago this weekend may not be happening. I’m so sick of winter. I need sunshine and warmth… https://t.co/ZonwtJlD3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rw_briggs It’s a pretty obvious choice as Reading is the poorest city in the state, with a dense population encirc… https://t.co/ZRIDLhmr4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll post the stream, might adjust the time depending on when the race ends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Colinmort Centrist sell out! I demand a candidate who climbs the Grid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See, evolution was a sage, and she knew that there is nomore convincing a lie, than the one we… https://t.co/lmv7bJQM83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LovinDisney08 @MKing7403 Nice. I lost a lot awhile ago but gained some back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is exactly what is happening in today’s world. It’s not just kids but adults also. Everyone wants the clout bu… https://t.co/xeZPbdQJ2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hellodivorce @expertsdotcomvp @ClausonJe You shouldn’t post funny stories then lol.  Did it clink on the side when… https://t.co/yJxKAcsp0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspan @RepDavidKustoff @RepEliotEngel But we will tolerate anti Islamist hysteria all day long.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseline: nervous OR very vocal soul woman on a funky beat. #alsomybestfriend #loveher]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EASTBAYDFRESH @weembust Well man, you make it hard by IMMEDIATELY calling me white devil 🤷🏻‍♂️ Jeez dude]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheilaFrench20 @drknstormynite @JacobAWohl @ali Jack and I are of the age where we made cave paintings for fun as kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qSuited You play your keyboard angled high like me right? I feel like a 60% would be pog af for that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Orange__White Nascar not happy with how the racing was. No shit the first race with the full package isn’t going to be what you expect]]></document><document><![CDATA[temperature down 55°F -&gt; 49°F humidity down 76% -&gt; 71% wind 7mph -&gt; 6mph]]></document></documents></author>