<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[RECOVERY. IS. NOT. LINEAR. not even a full year can change the way you feel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@8bitnitwit hello? is this my IPC study conductor? yes id just like to say: does your cruelty know no bounds? https://t.co/CnH4hKnGq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world's first beluga sanctuary will open soon. https://t.co/Um96pOsn0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericfisher terrible roads from Westboro to Auburn on the pike. Multiple accidents and people driving too fast. Too… https://t.co/oYvpBD3H3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t have a valentine this year... I had 20 instead lol the sweetest dang valentine’s ever might I add ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShelbyKStewart When last did Fox News hold Democratic Primary debates anyway? They are talking about Democratic Pr… https://t.co/xRWvo4DoJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[2018 me:  Why aren’t more NJ Breweries doing the #PinkBoots Brew Day?!?! 2019 me (with still no recipe planned and… https://t.co/cBCFmlsxrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bookshouse1 The encyclopedia. My brother threw it at me. I believe it was the F-G edition.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetns1579 @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump @harrisonjaime @scdp @WSPA7 @TheDemocrats @senatemajldr They both lo… https://t.co/v23UjZDvi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @iPicTheaters Scottsdale for Captain Marvel in Scottsdale, AZ w/ @stoodder https://t.co/S4QRDoUaXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took cute pics here but this is more important @control_nicole https://t.co/4pyqaUSOR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Hump Day Wednesday! Its a rainy day on this side of the map! But everyday is what you make it! It's a bless a… https://t.co/us3DkrhpoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewFeinberg @realDonaldTrump You are an idiot. Quit talking. YOU are the one with no clue. #cantfixdtupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews @Arriadna He’s right. It’s a problem but it seems our biggest National Emergency is the group of rich… https://t.co/oQNnQxu927]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is wrong with Venezuela that aid cannot come thru ? Starving your people is not a good thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took my first @solidcorestudio  class yesterday , followed by an @orangetheory class. I have muscles sore that I never knew existed ☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[My contribution tip #NationalMargaritaDay Jalapeno Guava Margarita https://t.co/GeScD1dDOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[My continuous #grannysquare #crochet #pyschadelic @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/uu9LXn2zD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein This is scary! Trump is not looking out for Americans. He is Putin's puppet and only looking out for… https://t.co/GBWOTMxnlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“you know how boys are supposed to smell good? well, he didn’t” -10 yr old sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rafaelrayb Ummmmm meeeeeeeeee I can send you one of my brand spanking new media kits if you need it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JEAlexander @MrWrightNowTV @OAP @Saeed_Kirki @tonetalks @tariqnasheed Where did I say that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If i ask you what’s wrong and you not gonna tell me, I’m not asking yo stupid ass again 😂😂 You Just gon be mad until you come tell me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimDTruax just got my card! Crying and making mom get a frame for the prints!! Thank you all so much💜💜💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathleenmadigan I tried to watch and stopped 1/4 way thru....#didntgetit]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Kristen Maynard  I was born in a good night and it worked  My age is not really good  I like to know how… https://t.co/vdPSUz8If6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R8ders_4life @OneBusyBeeEnt @werehungry2 Thanks, Nelly! Good fields running into old friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FourAces56 @MSNBC @SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer @JeffBezos @washingtonpost @amazon @JKhashoggi @CNN @AP_Politics @AP… https://t.co/JOVNbV8xAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[ROBERT MUELLER. WHY IS TRUMP ALLOWED TO GET AWAY WITH ALL THIS CORRUPTION? WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU?  Okay. Carry on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo muy buenos amigos la verdad, a cualquier lugar que vaya, para mi eso es tener mucha suerte.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Japan again, an entire CHORUS was assembled to record the grand finale numba for the Soundtrack to The… https://t.co/9TBjJslU01]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best wishes this weekend to one of the coolest people on earth @tylerreeve and his new wife @_AshAnderson . Much lo… https://t.co/PSXiPqjhwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[A7 Mission Impossible so you can pretend you're part of a secret elite team touching down in your upcoming destinat… https://t.co/VjPGmdwz5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kindnesshelps68 Enjoy your time off, Charity! We appreciate all your hard work with our little ones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sifill_LDF I can. As a teacher for nearly 30 years I can say, “I quit,” the day this happens in my state.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Belinda George, you are amazing. As a mom of 3, each w/ different, important needs afterschool, I would Facebo… https://t.co/gXwhou29BW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsungMobileUS how do I teach my predictive text to guess a new word? when I first got the phone I wrote "aaaaand… https://t.co/QHD6tMPArG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeMarcioSlaugh1 @DianaRoss @VWOfficial @LoveTinaTurner @DenverCenter It was a magical night indeed. @VanessaWill_… https://t.co/AeKio4uEYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only bad thing about moving out is, I never know what to fucking cook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #tapas place was recommended years ago. Finally here! (And the iberian pork sliders 🍔 disappeared pre-photo.😋… https://t.co/PeQnWT5Lul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolaC51255305 @SimonAcePursall @MattNelson02 @TaylorFan01313 @Lampi_NRW @HarcourtDoug @Wendyglitters @raehering… https://t.co/NFV4f2FW6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Astro_Nerd_ Facts. Last time I hit up the local aquarium, my bf sees the rays and says "if they find animals like… https://t.co/3H9jFtRX4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tgewin @FelipeCar That’s it - I’m not speaking another word aloud unless I absolutely have to before Sunday so I c… https://t.co/CoHHRpO4rt]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Verizon Sales Consultant - https://t.co/8Oc1WY6ZjE #Sales #SantaFe, NM]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Lewis Introducing Green Book at the Oscars Sparked Outrage on Twitter #Topbuzz https://t.co/4YhZULyhR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell @realDonaldTrump Why is he trying to get into a hearing to ask questions as part of a committee whic… https://t.co/AvTIZtr2OS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else just keep watching #Riverdale Season 1 and longing for the good show that made sense?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean...some friends are beyond the best. You know who you are. 💜💜💜🙏 @ Santa Clarita, California https://t.co/4Asg8a0GwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Car Selfie from Sunday Funday. It was a good one. Celebrating our Ang ❤ @ Minnesota https://t.co/m3MmnUSDVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@verity95 I say that shit on @instagram too! Just to be a smartass! https://t.co/Vr4tkPqn28]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve spent my morning studying for my Econ, Accounting, and Programming tests while listening to golden hour in bed while it’s raining😭👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gdinwiddie That's a great question and I truly do not know the answer but I am seeing the reaction of them just tr… https://t.co/BZhkE7Dhsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@datfoo_jaws @ScottxCreek I am ozuna, if he was fat so fuck you, fuck your party, fuck elijah https://t.co/hhhvlFHqeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a meeting with a board member of a major climate change activist group. We both agreed silent auctions are gr… https://t.co/GktHZ9qUaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama Dear Mr President, Would you consider running as VP with Joe Biden? Also, declare every action this Pr… https://t.co/bvPlueO7QW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Improving working relationships with @NationalAHEC can increase exposure of students to primary care opportunities  #ADFM19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick pit stop for lunch with her Titi oh #KHazzy @ Arrive South Loop https://t.co/mrSL3ZQxM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Colt_M_4 @jamiepalks83 @smalltownandrew Yes, you’re correct they are sociopaths.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing irks me more than when people say drug addicts and mentally ill need to be treated with kid gloves.  Fuck t… https://t.co/ajlNyGQdTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffSpeckAICP Curious - does the city do a good job of enforcing the lane restriction?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PilotFlyingJ your coffee is too hot for small cups that squish and spill over and then it  burns the skin #superhotcoffee☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ishkabibble - A bedtime rhyme about a monster afraid of what’s lurking in his closet. #pbpitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusanDelacourt @Puglaas @JustinTrudeau .A productive conversation for Canadians at this point is whether the role… https://t.co/LOME0kSpsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got a 6 paragraph text from my Dad saying I either need to “overcome or succumb” to my Lupus as if that’s the… https://t.co/xddgZNPveT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustenBundyDC So....actually, Quavo and Offset are cousins, with Takeoff being Quavo’s nephew. Now you can you judge ME for knowing that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all this man came into our office talking about his car got stolen when it was actually towed and I can't stop thinking about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndiansRadio MuniMom is in the house today!!!!  Wahooooo Go Tribe ❤️❤️❤️⚾️⚾️‼️ #EastCantonOhio #BrownsBunch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@belangelyn Acá por las uñas de las manos me cobraban $70 y me las hacían feísimas!! Me las dejé de hacer. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ballade sur le #fleuvestlaurent et dans le #vieuxboucherville❤ 😎😍☀️🌞❄⛄. #hiver2019 #boucherville… https://t.co/VlZ6qi85iN]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it's #greathornedowl breeding season when your education GHO lands on your head while you're changing his… https://t.co/vKCjpmxtQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulAllan5 not sure why this made me think of you but it did 😂 hope all’s well. https://t.co/4P7ezxh24r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nayibbukele We are at your services working with parents since 2015: for a new society https://t.co/flCVFDNqT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BGooddude Here is the latest video of my son fucking my tits, is it fair to trade this for anything? https://t.co/QnNJDFIg4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love beating those 🐂!! Defense of the @BaylorWBB was awesome tonight. #SicEm #SicUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terrycrews terry i usually love your tweets but this is misogynistic bro...]]></document><document><![CDATA[For #valentinesday we are rocking the pinup style Dragon dress from bettiesbombshells #pinup #bombshell #rockabilly… https://t.co/LfAe5lTdVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rarasu @Intuit @debashis_saha @IntuitVijay @MariannaTessel @rapparna @tracystone1030 @kimhoffman @lhasenhu I see m… https://t.co/VX2gO0PCEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[orange (bird) you glad i spent $15 on this cup? 🍊 @ Epcot International Flower and Garden Festival Fans https://t.co/ASAjHw6VsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GOPLeader: Oppose the Trump admin's proposed changes to Medicare Part D to protect people living with HIV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fantastic take in down in North Miami 💯🌻🎉⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ I would highly recommend it for anyone to go the art is incre… https://t.co/gw0mKnFuh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 8 #keto breakfast. Cottage cheese with blackberries and raspberries. @ Denver, Colorado https://t.co/nkTp9iHDZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to hear about the state of the industry at the Winston|Baker conference #effatla #quibi #legendary #netflix… https://t.co/FUvU3Ta8gD]]></document><document><![CDATA[4th grade plans to ROCK the STAR assessment today and tomorrow to show what we know in preparation for FSA!… https://t.co/p6QL8DxoeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wookiamantha @sabhatz @saraahschultz @samanthonggg @briannairvinn @lindsgayh Ugh what I would do for a big ole IAN hug right now!!! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaSGrey @CTG_CEOGEH Face it, with five what’s one more. I think though, twin girls would be amazing and Phoebe an… https://t.co/VPleDyYa6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a little over 200 days until this guy’s officially stuck with @asuriani120 and me FOR LIFE. [Also, highly reco… https://t.co/A83L0res1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisarinna You have been trash talking people you know and supposedly have relationships with so do please look in the mirror]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyonce   Die With You Official Audio lyrics https://t.co/YnfJSVGYW1 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emmy-nominated @TheDoctors host, 5-time author Dr. Travis Stork is in the house. @thepacker @ProduceCouncil… https://t.co/hweJOgWoS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we remember the lives lost a year ago in Parkland and continue to stand with the entire Parkland community #MSDStrong #ParklandStrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wolfblitzer JUST STOP IT!!!  Your questions regarding trump and Cohen.... Who the F(*^&amp;^k are you working for!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nativeesoul @ProudResister Are those cubs orphaned? Did something happen to their Mother, or is she hibernating? 9… https://t.co/8hOciSsVg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poniss_CHET i’m tryna look like someone’s next goth gf w the all black fit n black fur coat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdeTeal @EricIdle You do a great job. I hope you make good money at it. If not you should look into it. 😉👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgcondon @lrettig @_jillruth @delitzer Great to hear — how do we tap into the expertise of folks who have been… https://t.co/3R6zcEjaow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump EPA OKs 'Emergency' to Dump Bee-Killing Pesticide on 16 Million Acres.  https://t.co/iyROxVzTSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regresa @_PonchoDeNigris a #MitadyMitad y @mmistral como consejera de los protagonistas  ¡GRAN ESTRENO! Miércoles 2… https://t.co/U8rqeK9cKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Louie is giving me this look wondering why I'm not feeding him grilled chicken for dinner. @ Ocean County, New Jers… https://t.co/sdiuVdKcTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acissejkane I miss you so much! Wish we woke up laughing on the blow up mattress this morning lmao❤️ You’re the best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending #ValentinesDay with my mom @MomCBS  - you know I love you @marlahope #motherdaughter #selfie https://t.co/M5wwUMHFXK]]></document></documents></author>