<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@szilviade_ @LolyCruise @TomCruise @ZuzanaSuzy111 @Lovely49200223 @osawasakura @mametom1269 @anne221072 @lanaazzati… https://t.co/YwBpsrU65j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vampire Weekend always getting better. Modern Vampires of the City = incredible. Ezra Koenig produces Beyoncé songs… https://t.co/CwWVIjARmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are happy that the precipitation has turned to ice and snow. Can you believe it? But right now, it’s better for… https://t.co/WeZgAuQH3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[who needs love from someone else, when you can just love yourself a whole lot better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkepticalJAG DDPY bro help me brand DDPY 💥 @DDPYoga #PositivelyUnstoppable DDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CynthiaSchwind @LynneKelly @randomhousekids @Jarrett_Lerner @joshfunkbooks @ellyswartz @annbradenbooks This is on… https://t.co/t92wKDyY64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Here is a suggestion. Instead of making more of an ass of urself by insincerely attempting to clar… https://t.co/8VB745VNI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been keeping myself busy And I thought I was doing okay But then everything changed When our song came on today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarryS1409 @Harry_Styles #iHeartAwards #BestCoverSong #StillTheOne @Harry_Styles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanetMaslin Most foreign language films get limited releases — if any! — unless they break out. Sure, Roma could h… https://t.co/Vt56pfTsTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandystlpd But what will I miss in my 10-minute walk?!! I guess that gives me time to ponder who’s gonna play all these scrubs in the movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Synchronicity34 Wasn't talking about Canadian sources that have strict environmental regulation. Was referring to… https://t.co/ZnKeKekdqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theboosmom @JaniceWyattRoss I’m sorry he and you have had to suffer in that situation. As educators we must do better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your plans for downtown Orlando fall through, all that’s left to do is eat and let that food baby growwwww 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just living baby retweeted my mom and I’ve honestly never been happier! You go girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i really meant it when i said he yelled at me :/ https://t.co/M6CmOXDqNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart absolutely breaks for this family. Please donate to their gofundme if you can https://t.co/xzrZxfMCCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billboard @itsrllyinaluv I’m upset.  They have  c h e m i s t r y.  Bro.  He needs to um get with her lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twitt_witter @PoeEternal @GavinRossdale He most definitely is perfection indeed 💕💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve decided I need a portable margarita machine so I can just set up shop by the pool and take my summer pool days to a new level🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m not stuck up or boujie, i just grew up having too many nice things to buy low tier shit. i would if i had too tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daviladamian @CREchatLIVE @rgthornburgh @FlannCasey @SIORglobal Wasn’t it an awesome chat tonight?! #CREChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such out of control maniacs should not be wearing a badge or in possession of a gun! Shame on SHTPD and shame on SC… https://t.co/o2B1xxMR67]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart aches for Jassy and her family. PSA ladies: if you go somewhere together, leave together. This world is crazy. #RIPJassy 👼🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smorgasburg at #CabbagePatch  cabbage_key 🌴 @ Cabbage Key https://t.co/ubWDvHyV55]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonToerek’s fantastic podcast The Innovative Agency we talk confidence collaboration &amp; culture #agencylife  https://t.co/GghZkCy3cQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keith_kbddmi Sad. This happens all the time. I have seen no less then twenty stories exactly like this. They don't… https://t.co/1dXDZD1ef0]]></document><document><![CDATA[sunlight on your skin when I’m not around @ Daytona Beach, Florida https://t.co/I7osul0fsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning I've really been thinking about my life and the decisions I've made. Never in a million years would I… https://t.co/XhsV3iDTot]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know its sad that we could care less about some summit in Vietnam as opposed to the Cohen hearing. #45 is pissed attention not on him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como diplomática, te deber dar vergüenza de la manera tan vulgar que te comportas. En ves de mandarme fotos de comi… https://t.co/tr9pE9AJHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Captain Marvel for our 2 year Anniversary later!! Couldnt think of a better way to celebrate!]]></document><document><![CDATA[with teachers and learning. The education system across the United States is needed. Kids needs adults to help form… https://t.co/CxNzGtVZec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_StephenKLP I’m okay with some veggies in things, only a few though. Meat, dairy, grain is about all I eat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smittyg76 @Michuntapped @MIbeertaster @badhopper @SommBeer @MichiganBeerGuy @sommbeer_john @mibeerreview… https://t.co/YpwcRMADfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchellWinkelm @fromthe108 You can't take it back!  . I was kidding. I unfollowed a girl on Friday. She made a stink.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi please retire and make America Great Again, all  of Congress &amp; Senators over 65 needs to go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardmarx I wish I could turn on the TV and never see this orange corpulent prick again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Larryputt @CarlBotha2 @fagan_copper @RandallKraft @bbusa617 @Truthtease @OutOfTheBlue201 @t2gunner @J_Allen_CA… https://t.co/vTRcydhpY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to hear that @BostonRegionMPO is studying curbside management to repurpose how we use this valuable street… https://t.co/RDXkE7tzCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is conspiring with all of our enemies but please go on and trash the woman..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SciTeach7Davis I have a Class Insta - mostly followed by students, but it is a great connection. I love when forme… https://t.co/zwb5jI4SZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaPutrelli @acidoviejo @adribilu Así que es adivina ahora?? https://t.co/o9UvOiHZOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[alicia keys and john major together is so so magical wow wow didn't know i needed this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @60Minutes You are supporting the most mendacious, unfit, corrupt president ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excuse my tardiness! Teri, lead learner at @PESDragons in Floyd County. #TECHtalkGA https://t.co/vCLycAWEzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, ace of base has been playing every where. #isenoughenough #isawthesign]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even at the hearing, Tlaib made her remarks aimed at Congressman Meadows. Het words were directed right at him abd… https://t.co/xvPJwAp7o6]]></document><document><![CDATA[excuse me while i cry my eyes out today, i can’t believe my baby’s this big 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s the name for the psychological condition where you ALWAYS leave your to-go box at the restaurant????!!?!??!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rick_Dubagner @AndrewHiller @krassenstein @TeresaMac2009 The Antichrist comes first...lord comes later for the fin… https://t.co/Wqvh07Qo0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful , @jamiejvalvano .. and I too “patiently wait with eager anticipation”. 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomSteyer @Need2Impeach @realDonaldTrump @SpeakerPelosi We Need to save Our Country against the worst danger EVER… https://t.co/g4n97k3t5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jade_maria12 oof yeah a big ole five likes. better pin it to your profile 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Why would a world leader wreck his credibility for a moron? There is something about this “man” that I am not… https://t.co/XIyKekuEIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fidelgustavo Como asaaaaaaaaaa! Yo tomo pilsen, pero qué pasó hajahaahahaha estoy perdida mk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KHShan Donald duck would make a better president which takes nothing away from Mueller. A house near me has an out… https://t.co/7wdomKmFwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Srl82Shawn @10jmcda @Ben_Parsons__ I would question the "grass roots" part.   They are buying a line someone has f… https://t.co/7quwH4Q6Um]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pleasureisitsownreward  Taking action for my own pleasure is a novel concept for me. There are many things that gi… https://t.co/Bn8j2kEIwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KalTheSquirrel And I gotta it set to enter from the radio contest. I’m determined to see them https://t.co/J0YPqezyS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexHolleyFOX29 I’m a yoga teacher and runner and my 10 year old asked to come to the gym with me and I let her… https://t.co/MafPeL8rvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article about the STAAR Test measuring our S’s reading levels way above where they need to be and the psychol… https://t.co/NcyfB3kAzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolmswain Dr. Swain, would love to meet you. Education Panel, ReThink Forward, Trevecca Univ, Thursday Feb 21, 6pm. 🤞🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[me and my uber driver have been talking about drugs for literally 30 minutes omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel like I keep my emotions hidden too much. Sometimes I just feel like crying at the most random time… https://t.co/GP20FCKMTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLAZOOOO_anna @JeffreeStar @MorpheBrushes @evianwater @ultabeauty I’m dying just thinking about it 😂😂💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing edits of Sam heughan Credit to @Camilla68521063 #LoveForSam✨ #Samheughan @ Richland Center, Wisconsin https://t.co/7RVPDFkwL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A nice #POVshot of my #RiverdaleCW #vixens #harleyquinn from #comiccon2018 #DCUNIVERSE @DCComics @ArchieComics… https://t.co/gb2yDS5qAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love and prayer to you and your mom! Know that God is with her and with you! HE'S healing her and holding her in Hi… https://t.co/OOEsKYqw7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dia de San Valentín, no tengo quien me bese la boca, pero si quien me bese el alma... #HappyValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just pre-ordered my Samsung Galaxy S10.. can't wait... 🤗 @SamsungMobileUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharp_reagan @ayoolalaa_ I really didn’t mean for it to blow up like this now people all around the world are in their feelings 😂💀😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yalitza Aparicio Martinez is a teacher in Oaxaca.  Being nominated to the Oscars has given her an opportunity to be… https://t.co/s5YZzlkofi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ @SenFeinstein Yeah she should have been like all other politicians and pretend to give some self ent… https://t.co/BhK9icPDGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jade78052492 @KelliDa22369986 @BruinsSandi @gemcos12 @BodtonBears @djglidden @GillyWillyWoo25 @saraturner19… https://t.co/P4sEiLv703]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido si no haces algo drástico condenaste a ese país a vivir en oscuridad no más diplomacia se acabo evita las… https://t.co/STqK0CsZHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait sorry did @jordynwoods forget who fucking made her who she is ??????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[A son is trying to move out his mother’s most treasured possessions before Magnolia Assisted Living closes. He only… https://t.co/iG7pef9bqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So Unpresidential 😡 but then it's you quoting Rush Limbaugh lol lol so phucking pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pixietwit In Cait’s interview with the Irish magazine she said she is going to be a producer ( assume Sam is too)… https://t.co/7H29plKAA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[my cousin said “Jackie, College is taking a toll on you” oof do i look that bad? 💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[mayb it’s just me but I loose interest when you txt me every 3 hours L O L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone told me I wouldn't get a new chair, but here it is 🥰🤷😀 #workplace #spoiled https://t.co/Lbh3t6dH9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday, March 8th @ 7pm!  Don’t miss your Raaaiiideerrrsss!!!!!🏀💪🏽 https://t.co/tTEEXUJdRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted to get to work early...currently sitting in standstill traffic 10 min from home and have been in the same 1/… https://t.co/buiz1zVvUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw @apollo11movie yesterday and now I want to be an astronaut when I grow up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alcourington I mean I am wearing my fur coat... https://t.co/3DbpW5yEpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when I had a busted lip and my speech was off so then my tables couldn’t understand me... ALL BECAUSE I... https://t.co/OPITLnQy9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anyadesiree @maydaymindy9 @PersianKittenz Nope. She’s as useless as trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for 2 amazing artists to add to our salon family! Maren Karsen Aveda Salon is in search of passionate, crea… https://t.co/p92dk7prU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: don’t try to make friends in the TSA line if it’s anytime before 9 am. We are all makeup-less, not caffeinated… https://t.co/IrLADmTdFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3. When content teachers and ESL teachers collaborate together then language and content objectives can be better connected.  #ellchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s determined this wall will not be built just to make her idiot point that she won’t see another Trump campaign… https://t.co/sgogtqVXKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t really post my military life but my basic training graduation was one that I’ll never forget.. I can’t even… https://t.co/XyKD1VXP8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kev13F @EvaShadowgirl18 @Putneyman Thanks Kev! All good there in Gators Snout? We're having almost summer, well le… https://t.co/FDamcNBlnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok.  The Catholics ... need to get with the times.  Another reason to go atheist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tea #healing #cominghome #springiscoming @ Cabbagetown, Toronto https://t.co/giZlA5xjx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoshikiOfficial You have the kindest of hearts! I believe your kindness will be rewarded!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great internal clock clo always up at 5:56, such a needed skill to do this. No alarm. Wow amazed 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrancoNero12 Vorrei ricordare che se rimane fredda non si bagna... e soprattutto con il freddo le gambe stanno chiuse😜]]></document></documents></author>