<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m not like other guys. I’m not even a guy. I’m a pterodactyl. *screeeeeeeeech*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do smallcakes cupcakes have a gallon of icing on top? Like damn nigga, if I wanted a cup of icing I'd just buy icing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kattie_maize Там и до этого были, мы просто многодетные, а с 2018 новые ввели на первого]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ericblanc @Nash076 The faculty at our university went on strike.  It would have been awesome if the students and… https://t.co/i50KkIJCyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Gym gym gym hang up the towel already. We see you much like you saw that pedophile]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keay_43 @BallastPoint @HendersonBeerCo @LoudVoyce @hukari75 @DrunkPolkaroo @SudburyHomebrew @david_buist… https://t.co/4g7Vnb0Ubb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC it doesn't stop dems from trashing and threatening the President 's young son]]></document><document><![CDATA[y que es lo que dice el Kevin Hart dominicano? hahahahaha no pero que igualado]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been doing pipe fitting work for about 2-3 hours and there’s now a 12 pack of Michelob in my fridge and I’m wearing Oakley’s?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TriciaKiepprien I’m not trying to pick on you. It’s just one of my favorite oldies]]></document><document><![CDATA[#boboandjoko #sundog @ Washington Square West, Philadelphia https://t.co/UgNMj14wua]]></document><document><![CDATA[The overwhelming response from you guys has definitely reawakened a part of our past that has been dormant for many… https://t.co/jgcyPsN4BK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wisdom I’ve gained at the ripe old age of 38 (as of today) includes knowing I’m “in my mid-30s” until at least like 42]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Instacart @Publix I completely understand that what I do not understand is why they take the photo with their pers… https://t.co/tj3MzTaS0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If I wanna show my titties at a concert, IM GONNA SHOW MY TITTIES AT A CONCERT” this energy all 2019 😂🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your out driving, would you please kindly turn all your lights on, I realise mom always said leave them off but… https://t.co/YlXL5Byyau]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jay incitando al pueblo a que "chingue" lunes, pa’l miércoles estar quejándose de tapón.   Será pendejo...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leave them with the last impression they have of me....being escorted from my own house by LSPD with a “protection order” in hand]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sun is still shining on the drive home which means the sunroof is open and the music is cranked up]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact he’s a lying cheating AH that even his son had to turn in, nothing to do with it!  Fortunately the apple fell far from the tree!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s ‘Hire American’ Policy Delivers Record Wage Increases to ‘Job Switchers’ https://t.co/T12diePRz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicicleto04 @ElPincheJuan4 @davidant264 @manuel70m @maskarita4 @pelon_73 @unttalhanckoc @cero3801 @PAYAXO… https://t.co/GQ9NrsaqbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young up to 21 points, @ValleyGirlsBB leads City High 50-47 with 4:03 to play in the game https://t.co/5Fuo27KA5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the rest of my career adjuncting, I’m going to remind the department how I took over a class scheduled at 8:40… https://t.co/BseuGlvyY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not surprised.   Can't believe Chicago gave him that contract, then was able to unload him. Gotta love NHL hockey m… https://t.co/ylZs2aLGmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You either die a hero Or live long enough to see yourself become the villain]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really missed seeing the #GoodBrothers @KarlAndersonWWE and @LukeGallowsWWE  on tonight’s Fastlane ppv..  actually… https://t.co/WwiTDmTX9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kahil @williamlegate You really are clueless, you are the one that said CNN should countersue this family. I am me… https://t.co/X132X9j406]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been home since 9 am and I just got home. My parents didn’t even call or text me once. Should I be happy or concerned]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iniciativa #CeroAlcoholAlVolante se inauguró hoy @consulmexsjo, agradezco @CHP_  y @SanJosePD por apoyar esta inici… https://t.co/WAMgHYuIqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep your humanity said @Pontifex (Pope Francis) to @Microsoft pres @BradSmi on 2/13. I believe key to keeping on… https://t.co/xXdVv0ytv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely true. It’s not 🚀 science. #OhioEd #Edleadership @OHEdLeadership]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhakiBlueSocks Yeah, Matthews not being there yesterday on Cohen day was eyebrow raising. Have no idea…]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dizaniel25 Agreed, Gators should probably have a 20-4 advantage but let’s not split hairs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josey4u @MysteryTackleBx @ChrisKOutdoors Nice..cant wait to play with these.  Kayak season is almost here! Ive bee… https://t.co/dByIHYpAeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kind of bullying message is basically everywhere now. Ever since Bernie Sanders announced. I don't think this… https://t.co/qwKF1diOV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[DCSAA Wrestling Finals #Yafait#Miles#Charlie#Chris# Championship round#Go Dogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eustace_iii @BeaversColeman Wouldn’t that turn person into swivel bait 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justin and Anne look just alike. She is so cute, waking up all peaceful. @jillianharris https://t.co/FGStNi7NIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[must not have had my coffee yet but i agree with @AOC and yes i'm a #Conserative  There are two tax breaks for comp… https://t.co/eGHahD4BU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[BLOCK UBER/LYFT IPO #washingtondc #uber #lyft #america #usa #freedom #motorcity #nascar #christian #faith #muslim… https://t.co/35RaFqbq54]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paddybrendan daaaaaamn, Paddy. You famous! Unless that’s not the all-time leading scorer in state history in which… https://t.co/UAC4ISnbc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was the meanest game of Tetris 99 I ever played everybody started attacking me but I ended up ko all of them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gunnar just loving this weather. #nastyday #snowday #wildwind #gunnartheshepherd #iamgunnar @ Bethany, Ontario https://t.co/WJsehEDGNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pictures worth a 1000 frames!  1. Perfect photo selection  2. Motion Graphics  3. Smooth editing with just photos… https://t.co/WT7La1QIvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've finally got the Lightning now let's get a Volcano! Who what's to help me get a Party Boat up?? Full server All… https://t.co/SQ36QmUPsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KVOA @TucsonStar @whatsuptucson Weeks before November election I received notice that Ariz Attorney General settle… https://t.co/CSn8RQDoor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@36_bowser Just remember, training is a marathon not a sprint.  And never, ever, ever, ever, compare your training progress to anyone else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegionBobo @NewmannMichael @Eathbound420 @bfosterls7 @thesaucyliberal @BlkSantaX @MrsblksantaX @CIAnderson3… https://t.co/pSIRtJdZUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Available on ALL Digital Platforms!!!  #SpillSeason #4evaRocka #DenverTwitter https://t.co/wIe3vqqtOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you like our owl? "Is it artificial?" "Of course it is" 🦉🤖 @ Phoenix Zoo https://t.co/KAwrPXfoRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of posting books I love w/o review. @JeffreyASee  #EverestPride https://t.co/mzpsnpd0jB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edwiebe @glichfield @techreview That's a great project - didn't know about it- thanks for posting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkBarrington2 @DewayneDuncant2 @TPM except you're making a claim that i makes Larger states "underrepresented".… https://t.co/21d6B5d3NM]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you raise your kid to be racist and be so fine with it? Anyone who supports Trump is racist and simply stupi… https://t.co/olMZ5opqxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Nation Deserves Security how can the Stock Exchange No the Countries true Worth. Or what we have in the Bank if… https://t.co/Ta1r1Xky5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lamentable despertar con la noticia del accidente de #ET302. Descansen en paz tripulación y pasajeros. Es momento d… https://t.co/O7nF9UQfIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a video of this costume/persona that i'll post soon! https://t.co/IyYZioc07h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoveringDelta @NSKinsella @pierre_rochard Highly recommend @NSKinsella for a  podcast. His work influenced this Na… https://t.co/q26L08qTyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goknightsgo @ Las Vegas Golden Knights T-Mobile Arena https://t.co/OzPGNcddDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aroma is of earthy dank lupulin cones. This may be inoculated with campaign yeast, but tastes more like a west coas… https://t.co/hEKLg4g33Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope @pen15show goes all the way to their high school graduation 🤞🏻🤞🏻 @mayaerskine @annakonk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thjs mash up shows how believable and deep this CLOWN went to put hatetred towards The President and Conservatives… https://t.co/AYpYmQ9hdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ninety nine year old George still moves fast! 💪🏽 @ North Little Rock, Arkansas https://t.co/lsRBEHKH3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Under the stage selfie w this diva. I love watching you work @Lauren_Alaina What a great night of country music. @… https://t.co/KqNFoBLqWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ClydesRides @juniorsalutes @jswimberly @CaliRN619 @BarbieG1961  @ImabitcSumtimes @BerryTessie @briantopping66… https://t.co/JWRw5bRFCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drove into Terre Haute Indiana last night, and had flashbacks of the one time I shot a car here. I even drove by th… https://t.co/stzaBsFmho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, New York! :) #Sunrise 06:21, noon 12:07, sunset 17:54 EST (UTC-5), March 7. Day length: 11h 33m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How's that little pedephile case you're involved in going these days Jim?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahFOX6Now I see you every night in the cold and snow. Let know  when you are next time to take you and your cr… https://t.co/JYUtsRZSFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@60Minutes I crash for five hours and it's just more treason from #notmypresident. #MarALardass  #25thAmendment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_j_j_t_m @BjGotSoles @FOXSoccer @FCBarcelona Fair enough. If comparing the rivalry between these two fixtures El… https://t.co/HA1Cx6rFap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MORNAFAN93 He was in shock. He’d planned on putting on the glove, since it had brought OJ luck, but didn’t need to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lolo_Nicole I didn’t not pull over does that make my dedication more than theirs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AWxNYC Morning , Allan. Looking foreword to your latest take on the snow potential. I feel a general 4-8” is likel… https://t.co/PBK5yLwLlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Sunday with fam. #jupiterflorida #sundayfunday #baseballsunday #miamimarlins #blessed @ Roger Dean Chevrolet… https://t.co/muGk4yCvZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dealership changed my oil, washed my car, AND filled the gas tank. That’s like $100 i don’t have to spend 😂 look at God]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisdelia are they thooooooooooooo?! #ThreeLeggedDog https://t.co/vcUQgkyAbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidShuster @CarmenYulinCruz @i24NEWS_EN @BernieSanders Whoopie! I could put forth the proposal that I’d match wh… https://t.co/uevnQFRDpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is pretty much work today.  Lol. #ALLoftheLights #Work  https://t.co/LNBz15eFth]]></document><document><![CDATA[iALREADY LOST EVERYTHING BUT MY FAITH IN GOD‼️ . Now It's about  putting MYSELF in Positions to WIN💯 .… https://t.co/rg82O7ij19]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Give Apps Sensitive Personal Information. Then They Tell Facebook.. https://t.co/SZR944SLlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard We the people must be suspect of anything brought forth by the Dems. Their agenda is to redistribute we… https://t.co/GKmWSG6qQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kyle Lowry just ran out of the way of Winslow going up for a break away dunk so not to get a foul. Winslow misses t… https://t.co/4wseY7ewR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Improve Gym Sales Immediately! Try us FREE for 30 days. Includes our library of over 800 expert led training module… https://t.co/KHl1pQ969b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewOsier @Bharper3407 Welp.. the big NL teams didn’t do anything in the offseason. So I don’t see how we don’t ha… https://t.co/FuK0aetsQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not sure why you would use “deigning to respond”. I respectfully responded to your comment.  I am aware of rese… https://t.co/fY0A12L7Q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theheolikein One of the best Bristol night races since I’ve watched the sport (2004)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbisa92 @mugzreigne Both haha D17,18 kame sa Thursday. May LA show din btw May 26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDAcquaviva Sweet- I have those too! Too nice to actually put drinks on them 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @AprilDRyan But join her next week for another dose of the Judge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialNBARefs @SportsCenter @JalenRose @Espngreeny @GetUpESPN @YahooSports @SBNation @gkelser32 https://t.co/ZwTGSFXI9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buzzer sounds as Cornell takes down Towson 18-11 at @TheCrownLax. Up next we’ve got Jacksonville and Penn State. #NCAALax]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would have been such a good Martin/Lewis series. Missed opportunity....#SpaceApeCinema]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dawg showed me an app with free movies, shows, and cable.. I ain't tryna put a virus on my phone tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to rock it with @macpowell  and the Family Reunion! 1 Corinthians 10:31. #Grace #Family @ Greenville… https://t.co/9eqq6pQmYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fue el que le dijo a la DC que su mesa.directiva era una asociación ilícita para tapar la corrupción, y además repu… https://t.co/zoSYlgTj0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfranzese @SenBlumenthal @GOP @AOC And to be clear I’m just quoting Ann Coulter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delta amazing mess today.  Having to stop for fuel in Phoenix before going. To msp.  Gate folks and pilots had no clue what was happening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhyOhLordWhy @eclctc @charliekirk11 With what proof? Two years of investigations. Leaks all over the place. A medi… https://t.co/JeITTeh7Dz]]></document></documents></author>