<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I do not feel sorry for anyone even remotely involved with Trump.  They knew what they were getting i… https://t.co/MrZ96hOgBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[tried to raise crop prices by buying up and stockpiling production.2 That did not work, and after spending $500 mil… https://t.co/DD4wcHFWoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t heal what hurt you, you’ll bleed on people who didn’t cut you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSObservatory Thrilled to see @WillisCollege on CyberSecurity #Canada slide, thank you @CSObservatory for incision]]></document><document><![CDATA[@avrohomg @TriciaKicksSaaS @DrJDrooghaag @AmandaRay02 @NevilleGaunt @BentleyAudrey @Fabriziobustama @jdelacruz_IoT… https://t.co/0QMphT144S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited for the new location and the opportunity to sneak in a short family vacation after visiting with colleagues… https://t.co/623Two3Hoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[How San Diego handles the chilly (!) temps!! Thanks @livebeaming I love 💕 coffee ☕️ that doubles as lunch 😀… https://t.co/4GlLJoI09a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ant. 2 In the presence of the angels I will sing to you, my God.  Psalm 138 Thanksgiving The king of the earth will… https://t.co/BdvILMGYaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Knightd427 Be happy it’s not. It’s nothing short of an electrical storm down here. Kinda freaky]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cousin got me so high from these drinking oils, I was supposed to wake up at 11am... yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Ticketmaster for being so frustrating this morning trying to buy @CW_CrazyXGF tickets, only to be sold obstructed view 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uber driver: “what do y’all want to listen to?”  My dad: “Travis Scott”]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time last year I was going through it, and here I am again wondering why I’m still in this mess... https://t.co/1gA64tX8Lp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7Josh @julia_b_knight Josh! Congratulations!! She is so beautiful!! Lots of love to you and @julia_b_knight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deals &amp; Giveaways - Weekly Giveway - W7 2019 https://t.co/Iy5xAaLCM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dcevampiro A cuanto ,esta la temperatura ahora Vampy ,por Salta la linda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buuuuut I also rewound it and made my husband come in and watch just that scene so he could experience it too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learned a lot. Grew a lot. It’s all God’s plan. We’re not meant to know the full picture. Just trust Him with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We really thought we were gonna get attacked by a fox in the middle of the night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@varadmehta @HannahGraceLong Yep, that's a lot of catching up on with a show I'm only so-so on]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wienerdograces (at @Turf_Paradise in Phoenix, AZ w/ @rreedpc) https://t.co/AU2LYKXXgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to our MCHS cheerleaders as they compete at Cheer Derby this morning in Louisville, KY!… https://t.co/ZvPZlCB2S9]]></document><document><![CDATA[we have a king size bed &amp; my dog &amp; boyfriend still seem to push me off every night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @BillySterling are going to get it on in the mountains in Colorado! 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@choupete450 @AnnelaTannante On fera avec direction Terrebonne où tout est bon et délicieux 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍍Further proof that Hospitality is ALL about sharing what you have, and what you love, with others🍍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IdrisEl55376445 This is a FAKE ACCOUNT. The REAL @idriselba has a check mark certification on ALL SOCIAL MEDIA ACC… https://t.co/h95d1K5CpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAURENTZI @elcitizen Que mujer tan horrorosamente fea, parece sacada de una película de terror.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josmar_Trujillo 25k promised jobs over 10 yrs = 2,500 high paying jobs a year. Meanwhile 1k sm biz close every mon… https://t.co/meOYLwkzo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[For we are His workmanship, having been created in Christ Jesus for good works which God prepared beforehand that w… https://t.co/AcIzsCGOIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner I’m not a fan of Nikki Haley, but she should be totally insulted by this choice to replace her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Diablo Burger in Flagstaff, AZ https://t.co/pJbEXBlqbz https://t.co/T9G0222Rjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cahaba_1 Amen to that!!!! He’s done more for this country than anybody else!!!   Trying to undo all of Obama’s stuff!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found a rock this morning at the fire station after a call! It's a Turkey! I'll have to paint up some rocks with th… https://t.co/JruQyGlao1]]></document><document><![CDATA[High Horse is playing in Safeway right now!! 💃🐎@KaceyMusgraves is everywhere 👏🏼🎉💞 #seattle #KaceyMusgraves #highhorse]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jim a bitchass nigga for trying to forbid Stifler from coming to the wedding]]></document><document><![CDATA[[...] Il n’a jamais vécu ce qu’on a traversé. Jamais qu’il n’aurait la capacité de se mettre dans peaux. Dire des c… https://t.co/IwyNLjUj4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[yeah, @hulu, I’m really gonna need you to get on the “skip intro” level if we’re going to continue this relationship..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi sweetheart @RozzValo666 !!!  I’ve missed you.  What have you been doing?  How’ve you been?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louiseleto_615 @mysocalledMars True. There was nothing like the first year. So intimate, very special. I'll never forget it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RecomiendoLeer CAPRICORNIO Y ACUARIO (ZODIACO nº 1) de Isabel Mata Vicente @IsabelMataVicen… https://t.co/I5PWLPuGje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important lessons for white people to continue to learn. Stop using your perfect whiteness to deny racism exists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fondue goodness. #chocolateheaven #fonduesunday @ The Melting Pot https://t.co/RGs847AXqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been wild out at Windrock! I can’t wait to have another go and have a clean, fun run today!  PC: davetrumporep… https://t.co/l0kg7mAUj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FromMichelle @jessjohannes @librawhite @InXpressCali Um, thanks, but no. https://t.co/xLLfbf3ymE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@editorialunilit La Copa de Liberación: se basa en la siguiente promesa de Dios. «Voy a librarlos de su esclavitud»… https://t.co/ZZChugMuIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[*sigh* and #shutUP ALLready. https://t.co/3YDVS6ITZm #retention #TaraAnnMoons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyjrb90 Hi James. I am pretty new to WE and safariLIVE. You obviously have a tremendous amount of knowledge about… https://t.co/jPYaV1YObt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well this is mean. I’m sure they ain’t get pregnant on purpose. But damn, fuck them kids]]></document><document><![CDATA[@utahjazz If he leaves just take my heart with him too  cause I don't think I'll be able to live]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Jonas Brothers really drop a song/tour. I have no issues dropping like $$$$ to see Joe Jonas sing live again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another gorgeous Alabama sunset at Bayfront Park #alabamathebeautiful #sweethomealabama #daphnealabama #mobilebay… https://t.co/YtPbWdbsYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geoffdabelko Really wish I could but need to write this dissertation and apply for jobs and no power, no internet is not helping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xanboni @urisanz @mwolfers Navy Pier IS a PITA for most people black or white. Saying it’s bad for black neighborh… https://t.co/IfRXWWoDV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Thats bullshit Trump has threatened to withhold emergency funding because he's angry at California! FEMA k… https://t.co/j42fwONifR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just gotta say the Midnight Sky candle from @TheYankeeCandle  is divine !!! Thanks to @aly_rhein and @KarenRhein fo… https://t.co/d8sHnFZqka]]></document><document><![CDATA[#verycavalerri  When she was told about shippping problems She didn’t ask why she hadn’t been told I’ve been very u… https://t.co/GvaSVnXnOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PMorgwain @Kokomothegreat @rhiles2760 He looks like the homeless alcoholic I see every morning on my way to work panhandling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine me in my limited technical Spanish explaining what I do to my mom, who then translates my explanation in he… https://t.co/FDJDRRhswQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joslynn called me &amp; i woke up right away cause i thought her water broke lol ☠️ FALSE ALARM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alcohol affects you differently when you had top ramen a couple hour ago and had a meal that was a buffet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RheumaBlog_Wren @DeniseNolson @DrFrancesRyan @imajsaclaimant So sad 😭 this country doesn’t seem to care!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro this scene will neverrrrr get old 😂 that’s what I’m talking about yes!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz día internacional de la mujer. 👧👩👱‍♀️👩‍🦰👩‍🦱👩‍🦲👩‍🦳👵👳‍♀️🧕👮‍♀️👩‍🚒👷‍♀️👩‍🏭👩‍🔧👩‍🌾👩‍🍳👩‍🎤👩‍🎨👩‍🏫👩‍🎓👩‍💼👩‍💻👩‍🔬👩‍🚀👩‍⚕️… https://t.co/NhF03gvE9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @mrs_sbaker to post the covers of 7 books I ❤️. No explanation, no review, just the… https://t.co/ccqa7BIwLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Fiddlehead IPA by @fiddleheadbrew @ John Brewer's Tavern — https://t.co/EIcOas6ODx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got told I was dressed like a lesbo but I swear I had a man 🤷🏽‍♀️ https://t.co/xjOql1m57Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatsKitties @waitcho15 @ForgedInFur Maybe food allergies?  Be careful with too many steroids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad, going to work: “whoever leaves the house last, make sure the doors are locked”   We are 26, 25, and 18 😑 I’… https://t.co/LJgbjcSsYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows I just can't anymore with you two! You are beyond vile. Oh, did a great job defending t… https://t.co/ClFUU4G43I]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog gets reall fucking jealous If I dont show her attention like I dont get it lol like I let you outside 5+time… https://t.co/Tg5VKTGws0]]></document><document><![CDATA[geologists                       witches                            🤝                         Rocks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden YOU are embarrassing. Don’t you realize they all know you are an Obama suck up!! We remember those horrib… https://t.co/oT69SBpD7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catfish_AJ But wait...... you didn’t say the Yankees?? 🧐🧐 lmao jk i love you so much 💕🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendenfingers Oh, also, I too am entitled to my opinion so back to what I was saying before, you probably should… https://t.co/Uq4r0f4PCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice day for a drive to Dodge City to cheer on the Lebo Wolves!  #LeboWolves #leboproud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA oh you like your policies  thats ashame i knew you would turn on us in the resistance like the others]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, mommas! How do you keep on top of your health and fitness goals? Exhaustion, motivation and time are three of… https://t.co/JUn2rPlUAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marxist_neo @RodStryker @chowdallas I won’t disagree, when my children where small we were awfully tight and budge… https://t.co/Af1g3UtGpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[WSJ Tax Guide 2019: What Investors Need to Know https://t.co/zF3Zxbaq1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy this beautiful week.  Work hard, play hard.  Back to it.  Have an awesome Monday!  ❤️❤️ . . “He that dwelleth… https://t.co/wBypmdbvuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[STRONG STORM ALERT for Sumter County until 5:15 p.m. Monday. 40 mph winds, cloud-to-ground lightning and heavy rain… https://t.co/bKP7J7u32K]]></document><document><![CDATA[You the real MVP if you hold up your friends hair while she’s throwing up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also boo pilots for just saying a few minutes. 30 minutes is way more than a few minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinnyGinny_1 @realDonaldTrump @KamalaHarris @SenSchumer @SpeakerPelosi I cannot fathom murdering these innocent precious babies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dynamic_Signal @robynhannah @SASsoftware Thank you @robynhannah &amp; our @Dynamic_Signal friends for another great event! #RaganDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Signals Threat Perfectly In Line With Q Drops! "[bye] Crooked Hill... https://t.co/cLwiKVoNUW via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[The “talking” stage is an important part of a relationship because you learn about that person and find out if they… https://t.co/p94cByZ9up]]></document><document><![CDATA[My subject...my interpretation #freehandmachineembroidery #blackthread #starlings #threaddrawing #drawingwiththread… https://t.co/f8KCNk5tX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Fritz96 @iswiftitoff_ @taylorswift13 @taylornation13 @treepaine Thank you so much for retweeting this… https://t.co/uGytVb37MV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stoolpresidente called your downfall,@MichaelRapaport 😂😂😂 NOW MEEKS MEN COMING FOR YOU FROM PHILLY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brash_1 There were alot of Robberies here.  police told me that every house in that sub div without a dog, was rob… https://t.co/77yCMtuCT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well look at that 👀 I got a follow from THE Presley Cash 🙌🏻 And she won’t share her skin care secrets (see DOB incl… https://t.co/83vl0dAlpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I put this on and thought... #DontMessWithTexas! @visitplano #MiaInPlano #VisitPlano https://t.co/HLn6LfisuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the wrinkle/zit/peeling nose because of a cold &amp; allergies combo cream is in which aisle?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Island 🏝️  #ladytron #thefondatheatre #amazing #💙 #92819 @ Fonda Theatre https://t.co/sKjoKtBTTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TxStormChasers About 10-15 minutes ago Grapevine had about 1-2 minutes of small pea size hail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i went to sleep at 5. it’s now 9 and my fricken mom is making me wash the clothes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let us make three tents: one for you, one for Moses, and one for Elijah.”  He hardly knew what to say, they were so… https://t.co/kr3JtlVdQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hear the WhatsApp messages that keep refugee families together https://t.co/DHZR0vdqMz]]></document></documents></author>