<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Definitely did not just drive to Taco Bell at 9:30 on a Sunday to get a rattlesnake burrito]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramirezmaria844 😉duerme linda Maria y lindo comienzo de semana ✨🌙✨👼👼👼✨💓🎉✨🌬🌨🍀🌸🍀🌸🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer Few things in life are as satisfying as a squirming lawyer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BestBoyFam @scurkay @KEEMSTAR OPEN A FUCKING HISTORY BOOK I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Ea… https://t.co/EZSoTo5vVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess me yelling “TAKE ME BACK TO THE 90’s AND LET ME PLEASE START OVER” to Doc Brown, scared him away!! 🤷🏽‍♂️😃 @BacktotheFuture]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbh39 They control their own destiny.  Win 3 more and they are in.  Simple as that.  Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This look Arya has when she sees Drogon flying overhead for the first time at Winterfell . That is the look you wan… https://t.co/6jNbhQDfSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmeriWify @55true4u @MailOnline Trump was good friends with Epstein. Do a little research.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reportándome desde Texas @dani3palaciosdj si la tierra es plana como me explica esto?  #AlexEnElCartel… https://t.co/IZ3oT1MOpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw on @CNN that @HBO is doing a two day doc on @michaeljackson accusers called #LeavingNeverland ...this se… https://t.co/hwneSuJ7Pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Sales Floor Dept Supervisor" at Lowe's, then look for people you might… https://t.co/9RQfskJdnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Who shall separate us from the love of Christ? shall tribulation, or distress, or persecution, or famine, or naked… https://t.co/ljCzYnULZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithDeHaas She was invited by the Dean for Students office and they were very embarrassed. Thats like inviting Je… https://t.co/gdrVyiqzXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDept The 1980’s called, it wants its Central American foreign policy back. https://t.co/xpxApWqbbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DysonLogos @katewelchhhh Is that an update of the Sinister Secret of Saltmarsh? I loved playing that module back in the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I misspelled Skechers. Also this ad and its placement tells me Skechers has no idea who they are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_longton Good luck with that. I’m just getting to work and feel like smashing my hand lol jk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was awesome meeting the amazing Christina Ricci at Monstermania @ Crowne Plaza Philadelphia-Cherry Hill https://t.co/lDqA82MrEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new story by my talented wife: #writing #writerscommunity #flashfiction]]></document><document><![CDATA[My oh my, what has happened to the democrat party? https://t.co/VamN7Ydw1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaimeDonally @curiscope @ERHHistory @CatchyWordsApp @3DBearOfficial @mvs_org @cospaces_edu @orbapp @MergeVR… https://t.co/eNENDDMRGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0ut0fControl Friday - Dallas - @MtzEntertaiment   Saturday - Chicago - @AAWPro   Sunday - Denver Colorado]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you therevdvoss masters_justin tamiatkins agillispie75 and the entire https://t.co/Bn7hDayrrG team for leadin… https://t.co/6PnbABPaW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 Very important message today! 🚨 @ Ocean Resort Casino https://t.co/z8F6vm9aPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confidence is a Must.   Why?  It’s a showing of belief in your SKILLS.   If you’re a physician, you should be confi… https://t.co/6EdDzdM8c6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussiaInsider I don't care that's so neat looking do ya have any other neat pictures like this y'all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fcastillob no puedo creer que pasó esto en la liga Inglesa! 😖 https://t.co/OI6tjVvd2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from 1uniqueleo890  -   https://t.co/bZLJSaYc2T - #MylesSpeaks   - #regrann @ Detroit, Michigan https://t.co/1oDv0YOx4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday kenzie!!!🎊💛🌟🎉i’m gonna miss cheering w/ you next year!! 🧡🧡🧡🧡 (enjoy the last picture) https://t.co/qadSk95ULL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peter_king Peter, that email link to your email did not work for questions during the SunKing sit down in Indianapolis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateShu I’m going to change my last name to Miller. My adoptive father was a sleaze ball. I’m considering Ero… https://t.co/eFRCX4ikkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God for guys like David Corn for coming out on tv and having the stones to say there was "Collusion" between… https://t.co/5ZULUea88Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSoulbrother @ACatNamedMo Blood Orange Hazy IPA?!? That place is practically in my neighborhood! Now I have to g… https://t.co/drlINLgqYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vichernandezm buen dia....Tu sabes porque no pasaron el juego de tigres por tv en USA?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@business Nice guy but needs a lesson in economics. Starting to think Bloomberg is so biased it needs one as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @CPAC @ChrisCuomo @realDonaldTrump Because CPAC is about tribalism and almost nothing to do with conservative policy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@killingclipart @SenTedCruz @realDonaldTrump @HoustonChron https://t.co/oFBMQPn3jx watch it]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PatriotsUnite #PatriotsAwakened #WWG1WGA #GreatAwakening #MAGA #Q #QANON #WEARETHENEWS #FAKENationalEmergency… https://t.co/mYlvqWnVIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaseHorn We have always focused on staying off the ground at Bob Jones.  It’s full speed but not full contact.  P… https://t.co/NXdrG3NrJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miserable weather day. Might as well eat a crueler the size of my noggin. (at @CrankyAls in Wauwatosa, WI w/… https://t.co/KBdZp1R4J8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to be a board member/contributor. If you’re truly interested in genuine racial conciliation, journey with u… https://t.co/hXgPu6BRaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[In fact, Americans are paying a premium of 26% above world prices for aluminum—due in large part to US tariffs… https://t.co/ji2jpOBfLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritYah 3) And again, back to your weird obsession will MSM and NOT with biased sources across the board. That's… https://t.co/PTlCdVClYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KipHenley I can’t believe we’re still talking about backstopping. Such a non-issue to anyone that’s played competitive golf.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taco Tuesday!!!!!🌯🌮😊😍 (at @FuzzysTacoShop in FL) https://t.co/3VmgOR4sgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#columbusbluejackets @ #ottawasenators #gogsensgo @ Canadian Tire Centre https://t.co/421G029l6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[this group is a vibe 🤘🏽  - moves by anthonyvibal  - #dance #urbanchoreography #urbandance #himezdancelog #community… https://t.co/xMWfvmZoSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelovebabyE @the_zalfa What?? Going back at least 5 generations my family is Buddhist😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HappyHarlekin @WarriorPresent I just realized that in America, when people sneeze, we tell them "Protection Up" in German.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night downtown #lansing #michigan walkabout #michiganstatecapitol #bars #sculpture #cold 🥶☺️ @ Lansing Downtown https://t.co/Sz7FjZ4V29]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the sunshine in the backyard and a spotted falcon is circling around overhead. Sometimes there are little… https://t.co/4xSUM52oMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deboleena_ @xAwakxnx @alstarz60 @Tyosoul3 @balleralert You must not know about the fun world of black hair. Chris… https://t.co/qP2inSsjIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This book is a Western lover’s dream read. Eric Red is a welcome addition to the Western genre.” – Historical Nove… https://t.co/plD1oKs36J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Waynelambert123 @BookofJonah @realDonaldTrump I can prove u wrong all day. Like amazingly fast actually. To b a ri… https://t.co/FAiCR2AfG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ejmountainman @TheMichelleJean I've been voting for this cutie everyday we need her to win b/c we need more of her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time at the SA Sports Hall of Fame Banquet! https://t.co/NCBoBnz5Nj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrubek Yes! This was the youngest photo I could find on my Facebook account, me age 4: https://t.co/QFO1IbpteX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our 9th ranked @UHCougarMBK were victorious yet again. Not only did they get their 26th win of the season, they rec… https://t.co/cGCrCkFU5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spacerog @backblaze Also consider @Tarsnap. I support it because I know @cperciva knows a thing or two about secur… https://t.co/sLFvevNOfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y🚷UR ALL A BUNCH 🚷F DISH😩N🚷RABLE BETRAYERS. ℹ️KN😐W  Y💀UR DEEDS Y😩UR NEITHER  H🚱T N😩R C🚱LD! ℹ️WISH Y🚷U WERE 1 😩R THE… https://t.co/a5zJj2dHOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fangr @AhimsaEd @johnpilger @wikileaks But my point is that I refuse to believe he didn’t have dirt on Trump and d… https://t.co/ME5P0MStCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sick young women feeling their Oats thinking they are in charge Americans will show who is in charge hopefully gett… https://t.co/fnw8wqfA2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Head coach of one of Canada’s top female university programs passes away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many more years until we can jam Beastie Boys with the windows down and it be cool?? 🤷🏽‍♂️🤷🏽‍♂️ I’m doing it anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAMTOMMACDONALD, @NovaRockafeller and @iambrandonhart should go check out the official HOG group on Facebook. A ad… https://t.co/LkZn0JZq8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dabbin' on the Job @ LA County Public Administrator Warehouse https://t.co/qS31Ro8HFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everytime someone came up to me and said i should vote i told them lol i aint gone be here to see the changes lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it today! 17 miles in the book. The last few miles were a struggle but we got it done. #longrun #teamshire… https://t.co/2QysfVViqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithEdge21 these kids live only like an hour from me lmao 😂 they’re in a new band that tours and whenever I see t… https://t.co/d8einTWZpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EcoSenseNow @amf207 Exactly. Nuclear power needs to be utilized much more than it already. The GND clearly has no… https://t.co/WnlHj7bebz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Spin. Lies. More Spinning. More Lies.  See the pattern? https://t.co/SKLUlpPE54]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that I’m a believer #DukeVsLouisville @ZionW32 is the truth. @camreddish is a marksmen. The whole ben… https://t.co/6Ks5IIpV5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is saying to you today @ Chozen Martial Arts Academy https://t.co/Eh6riX9A8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is away to disconnect from the digital world, no phone, no computers and no#work! #FlyAlaska + #AlaskaHappyHour.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling you get after doing home renovations to accommodate a crowd which has now come to your party. https://t.co/8G9xoVy2jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez was “furious” that an Amendment was added to a gun control bill, that ICE would be notifie… https://t.co/QNlPLgIqCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Given up 3 goals, one being a 20 yarder while getting dominated in possession... I’d say any D would get a little “… https://t.co/O8HHd63Gib]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NintendU @PSNation @SteelSeries @IKEA That looks pretty good, my idea of cable management is hid cables behind big… https://t.co/o9kIU37bbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ilhan Omar and Rashida Tlaib show Muslim women don't need saving https://t.co/ST4NLFCYM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dayana gets today's #goodnewscalloftheday for giving great effort  and being super focused in class. Way to roar!… https://t.co/zZ2Lv0WSoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only Hispanic that ain’t scared to say how dey feel?????? I’m sick of this stuff that people are scared to… https://t.co/IAjAGA7z6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta Republican Special PERSECUTOR Ken Starr sought to bring down President Clinton over a consensual affair with… https://t.co/FGB9WtcExM]]></document><document><![CDATA[exo gonna pull a jussie smollett if they dont get a proper comeback this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @BreitbartNews @JxhnBinder Welcome to the real world, Van. Can’t hide behind CNN in public.]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi its rick from planet rick. we were eating captain crunch looking at the USA.  wow lets see you have dictator Don… https://t.co/cCFmjv9e7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwestr Under current management practices and executives behavior I believe Tesla will go Q if this does not stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chriscapxxx @Brandossius Meanwhile in the real world, not lying Breitbart world, hate crimes are up almost 20% whi… https://t.co/6pPBfiNkK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been spending the afternoon getting to know the new LP from Stella Donnelly. I think it’s just great and I c… https://t.co/yxbcETWy1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the only reason you say that is because it’s you that being investigated. You whine like a spoiled little girl.… https://t.co/Cx7ADpET9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsSHANGELA Bish, you better werq! Yaaassss hunty!  #killingit #Oscars #ERedCarpet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight @JackBlankenswag was named @NMGameDay player of the week  @KOB4 @ManzanoMonarchs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 @Voodooqueen6 Un will meet Trump every year until he gets Trump to feed his people, remove all milit… https://t.co/BjSMAdHYhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[MEANWHILE!...   •  #DjRodNYC #SoFlo #Florida #Work #Music #Art #FullMoon #Full #Moon #Life #entrepreneur #AlaTraka… https://t.co/iQYT9RZ1y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LLRugby I heard 1500 &amp; 1600 so far. We raised some awareness tonight. The @USARugby truck got hit by #Snowmaggdeon apparently.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer #MadeleineAlbright makes very belated but now politically expedient apology. Gotta fit the narrative huh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanPhillippe Trying to get in contact with you about Brody. Not a problem though..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZionistJew12 @Goodtweet_man After the Mexican-American war, the borders of Mexico shrunk. I assume you are awaitin… https://t.co/Io5obBmu7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly you have never yelled “necesito mas tequila” in panama and thrown up in your shoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this is what makes me so mad and here I am with about 5 other people that didn’t get a ticket @NianticHelp… https://t.co/otgJPBGuOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had to play a man down in the first round of a 3v3 GB tourney and we won 6-4 with them shooting our bodies 😂😂😂 i… https://t.co/WeLVOKNrxs]]></document></documents></author>