<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Q5: What do you feel about the role of data analysts? An essential part of marketing teams or only for certain indu… https://t.co/ilIY3KS5wL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@concerned_chi @fastboyent @HolleyGiirl @saharafox @PhilJennerjahn @Kamprov @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/rqII2TZGiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Teacher Week Ecard: If you're going to be a teacher, you'll need to consider developing... https://t.co/2YAja2Tlth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never underestimate the power and purpose of our students! So proud @MaddieFine6!! #TomorrowsLeaders #GirlsWhoLead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t realize I took spring break off.. oh wait I didn’t cause I need the money yet somehow I’m only working 5 hours this week 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone give me tips on how to get rid of a pimple please. It’s a damn mountain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You have no idea what you are talking about. I work in the mental health community and the homeless population… https://t.co/glPvDPsojk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CRStromante Mandatory evacuations in that area. The water is rising and will not crest until tomorrow night.  It's… https://t.co/zO9uXs2QCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowing people that belong in clear skin Twitter irl is so irritating... this girl really told me today that i’m “b… https://t.co/HYd0N9cdAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharmCityPanda @PandaChronicle @TheLittleLuns @DodgerAmes @DCZooWalks @kariek Glad that you enjoyed your visit but… https://t.co/c4nk8YQWf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rpondiscio @jaypgreene @rickhess99 @WSJopinion Not really mine either-- but this phenomenon is quite literally kee… https://t.co/5gXVpvTLVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gostaria imensamente que entidades esportivas, COI e principalmente a CBV @volei no Brasil, me provassem que um ano… https://t.co/y8vrKvfQzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning my boyfriend calls me over to him, grabs my hand and says “hey you look like a girl I could spend the… https://t.co/mG99dHkyiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMBollin Honestly Lovejoy wasn’t horrible this season but I’ll take a young guy and a 3rd over him any day of the week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keanubalani @jamescharles @MorpheBrushes @norvina1 @ABHcosmetics @ColourPopCo @SBounsom Awe, saw you retweeting th… https://t.co/P71wiqOrg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A dos meses de estar viendo a Phoenix en vivo y a todo color 😍  (SIN HABER COMPRADO AVIÓN Y RECOGIDO MIS BOLETOS, AIURA)]]></document><document><![CDATA[death cab for cutie and odesza are doing a benefit concert for wwu in bellingham 2 days before me and gabe’s 1 year anniversary fjwjjfkwkdjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best friends are the people you can do anything &amp; nothing with and still have the best time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited for my partner in crime @snmartin05 and her opportunity to represent @PLTWorg @DarnabyElem and… https://t.co/m5jYkAe11C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beanson40358184 Actually it was not a socialist group. It was simply a group of students showing their support for… https://t.co/unoyTl0yLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Port of Long Beach, CA: Customs and Border Protection Seized Record-Setting 1.7 Tons of Meth Worth $1.29 Billion - https://t.co/JjmYMcf29V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renee_being @abbyhonold @JacobAWohl She posted a stupid response to a stupid feckless twat, @JacobAWohl.  And with… https://t.co/qh1vVS5dpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nysteve27 That’s why @Wayfair is a Billion dollar company - you order the same thing at half the price without the hassle]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact of not being not being able to cremate you own grandchildren and being told so because they were submerged… https://t.co/an1jwueSr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii I’m thankful swamp-master-scout Rosenstein is leaving. He and McCabe can duke it out on the fresh-air,… https://t.co/xYW27XxKmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The best administrators act like a windshield.” We make sure our teachers put their attention and focus on what re… https://t.co/Givs3c41EZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @girlscouts @GSCNC I went from a coed junior high school to an all girls high school. Girl participation soared.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to be able to watch the game on tv!  I hate living in a blackout zone. #CBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#qualtricsdreamteam helping me cope with the temporary separation from my #Peloton with #Qualtrics branded cycling… https://t.co/cORgwix5xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @marcorubio thanks for the case study in how uninformed way too many of our elected officials are. So how about… https://t.co/9GlG6ekfz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[A roaring evening back to the 20s!  #wwvpythons #funnelball @ 28 Event Space https://t.co/Aih6USJ6Zu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MPsy1010 because he thought he knew how the trick worked but was shocked when there was “one doll”]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why I have no debt and perfect credit. Miss me with any of that shit I’ll suffer and struggle before I take… https://t.co/gmyJxMgMz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AylaForTrump why? Because she will be running for POTUS 2020....bank on it. Global Inc feel that they have the new… https://t.co/XHiBiUSceg]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few pics from the ice with @_briannamarie 🏰 I would honestly live in a glowing ice castle, but I couldn’t feel my… https://t.co/ZRTNS3lC46]]></document><document><![CDATA[T-13 hours Abbey just hit a rabbit on the highway We feel really bad Moment of silence  RIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory @RickSantorum -  chill out! #Trump will be back soon to offer you  some frothy #Santorum]]></document><document><![CDATA[“without any sort of insight into how you plan to discuss efficiency” Issue with the way you keep your data]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's quite funny that I'm a makeup artist and I still get my makeup done by my team love them soo much https://t.co/GGw8tNMYm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaynorJohnScott @SinTheFields One of my favorite raynor and Sheila moments is when they slept on an air mattress a… https://t.co/OrCpd1aBr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Cards and candy and Valentines, oh my!”  4/5th graders celebrating the day of love!  #igniteCCS #igniteSHS https://t.co/SZvIVc7wXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett “Racist and dangerous comments “ really? @POTUS ? You have absolutely NO moral aut… https://t.co/ILZA6Ay5jN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tnkithcart @frecklesgms @MingGao26 RICO- Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act. What they give after… https://t.co/m3Yva9TaiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because I can! #peeps #easter #yumm @ House Full of Crazies https://t.co/hB9HPnSejb]]></document><document><![CDATA[i try really hard to love my body but it really just don’t be there sometimes LOL, like i really can’t, which is wh… https://t.co/a2cmTs3TQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 2.0 mph SW. Barometer 30.301 in, Steady. Temperature 9.0 °F. Rain today 0.00 in. Humidity 65%]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingofQueens13 @agathabagshot @DeadEndDemon @Carla69Senora @lamarjackson2 @Dementia_Grimm @LunaKayne… https://t.co/lQFLrSQjDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[ahhh...Minnesnowta! It just looks cold!!😂 @ Delta Terminal - Minneapolis-Saint Paul International Airport https://t.co/kh2pPKuW1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow Welp, me thinks there are things okd creepy criminal men don't want out there, right, Dersh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mitch_Tischler Your Birthday party will be like no other https://t.co/vylmMe38Q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh also she’s blunt and anti-establishment lol. Now I kinda wanna watch the show even tho it got canceled 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/DnxNdZCy3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing better than being engaged to another Longhorn! @LeeTai46 I love you! 💍 ❤️ #EngagedToALonghorn… https://t.co/iZ2k06sqYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kikiismygod @kirakosarin @eatpraychloe @giuliasntana @Chris36577059 @Daisyig18 I’m listening to this song nonstop https://t.co/kb64isl463]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day Two of @onaconf Women’s Leadership Accelerator kick-off week in LA. kimbui - Director of Audience Engagement… https://t.co/GzRP5lPiuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Those who turn the conversation from prevention to promotion are 14x likely to get VC funding.” - @altheawishloff… https://t.co/HEG2z3vOlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I think I need a nap now, gn and fuck the notebook wtf y is it so fucking sad like wtf I h8 it sm I cried so hard bro WTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why after I eat a healthy meal, I crave chocolate chip cookies. Literally, it happens very time. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[wait wait wait wait. our sins are resolved???? first of all, what does that mean]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vet4Stros I was out at customer’s office near Park Row/Top Golf Katy. Saw more near my office by Bunker Hill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYYprincess33 If you need good vibes, I don’t need a reason why, you got ‘em. Hell even if you didn’t need em, you still got them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful sunset   #wilmingtonnc #sunset #nature #naturegram #ilm #naturephotography #naturelovers #naturelover… https://t.co/ehOywZ4E3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best feeling is fitting into a pair of jeans that were hella tight just a few weeks ago lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enews Obviously family comes first, but I hope some understanding for Jordyn can happen because when @KylieJenner… https://t.co/bAcbfiURNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCVB Myra Kraft stood or equality and for women to be and feel safe from domestic violence. He is being so disresp… https://t.co/QzycXFPFND]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone says you can't do it, do it twice and take pictures. - Unknown #motivation #inspiration… https://t.co/K9amJp5DHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marnes @rumpfshaker Your problem is you think a person can be a Trump supporter/excuser/enabler/loyalist w/o becom… https://t.co/JhAXf7ZcXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The March issue of https://t.co/YHNlqEXe6V comes out on Friday. . . . Look what hopped inside the new issue! This m… https://t.co/IRqV9RhT5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAFS_Original I feel for Kate. I do hope that she comes to terms w/her own happiness. I hope she can see that this… https://t.co/FIF3yjLa5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss you so much sometimes it physically pains me. I wish I could talk to you one more time. To show you I made i… https://t.co/LBLRYbiuzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a dreary day, raining and flooding every where, but was a good day to go exploring my #hometown.… https://t.co/b9Tk3bF7Xi]]></document><document><![CDATA[yall i wanna see how i look w short hair. someone photoshop me or send me some wig links😭😂 osrs tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially when you have an 8 am work meeting on that morning 🙄 https://t.co/rP7mNmTao5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoodMorning (@ The Forbidden Forrest in Hogwarts, VA w/ @bryan_warren) https://t.co/qepQItr58Y https://t.co/Ezyxeuq94c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don’t need my ex who is expecting a baby to be sending me heart eyes on Valentine’s Day. CANCELEDDD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE MET T’CHALLA AND HE SAID CONGRATS ON GETTING ENGAGED the most important blessing 👏🏼💖 https://t.co/nOLcrlWs72]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BldgingMovement “Many women of color described working harder to overcome these barriers; not only is this an unfa… https://t.co/cU2d4Hx94S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ouatcsship11 It is, but it would be nice symmetry to end the season with an ep for each of OTA. (What about Emerald Arrow?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[As if the outside world is not cruel enough already...people disgust me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XUCryptKeeper opened early for the @Everton v. @LFC match today. With the impending white death and potential snow… https://t.co/1kMM4Jy26E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonaldKurz2 VAWA protects all victims of physical and sexual abuse with no regard for gender, race, age or sexual… https://t.co/FTTWRo8OyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited to start this new activiy in @Flipgrid #Gridpals #SpainAmericaConnection🇪🇸🇺🇸@LODLeadAcademy… https://t.co/V06NZr2vHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Blackhawks Gustafsson 2 delay of game at 4:46 of the 3rd. #RedWings PP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diet talk is a barrier to intimacy. It prevents us from learning from one another and from inspiring one another. D… https://t.co/6F3BLGvpPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[i like having my curtains open at night so i can see the lights of the buildings outside, it triggers that special… https://t.co/priwgXpEGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahhahahhahhahahhahahahhahahahha just had the most intense panic attack]]></document><document><![CDATA[although few soldiers have accepted that promise.  U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said on Friday that he belie… https://t.co/zr3i4PpdSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[9am and I’m finally showered and undercover IN THE SHEETS *TRAVIS VOICE*   gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Venti_Poet @joncoopertweets Good news! Let’s go Joe! He has integrity and experience. He understands the law and h… https://t.co/owKSx02yTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord, thank you for the encouragement that although even the great apostle Peter failed and messed up, you forgave… https://t.co/KeaeosJmoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's latest attack on 'SNL' could be 'a threat to my safety' Alec Baldwin suggests - CNN https://t.co/0vwbqOWzHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Active tuberculosis cases confirmed in 2 Floyd County elementary schools https://t.co/s75Ptt85yI https://t.co/v1Babn3MQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought it was Wednesday and then I looked at my phone saying it was Thursday which means bts tickets go on sale… https://t.co/jDlwkbqNhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EbswiththeCurls Shit don’t put their name on the project then 😂 fuck em]]></document><document><![CDATA[First trip without my partner in crime @jeff_lemieux is going to be a different take! #NERevs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clear2Insanity @ParisValeska @LeahRemini @MikeRinder @BryanSeymour1 @ChildrenOfScn @WomansWeeklyMag Christi, you c… https://t.co/3T9HnC1Xq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jheil @NYCMayor It’s delicious! I always thought it was a western Pa thing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if... we ended every conversation  with a student over their behavior ... with these 3 questions.  ⬇️  A remin… https://t.co/2wsuTJpgn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[governors in the State Dining Room of the White House in Washington DC on Feb. 25, 2019. ... President Donald Trump… https://t.co/J0u33feYOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steps to a @Senators rebuild                    1- @MelnykEugene sells team to competent owner… https://t.co/Z1pLc9QaBV]]></document></documents></author>