<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SDePace dude im not a dem, you also cherry picked what i wrote for your own context]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanLeeTx Hahaha I hate to admit I am a mean person when hungry, tired or both. https://t.co/t8TxMLXflo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast When I mean they I was meaning the troll that mentioned you and your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basically the one reason why I occasionally miss my ex girlfriend is because it was nice knowing that I had sometim… https://t.co/BTrnnCCqut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonkaSly I am happy to see him having gotten up and able to go to the room]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was at that game in November. He deserved this win tonight. #SlamDunkContest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David56798816 @slicksteele @nat_barnard @RepDanCrenshaw Nice argument using a cartoon character, disenfranchisemen… https://t.co/N4OUEBSw6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miss_LexieMarie @realerinburton @sacampb Lets never let her live this down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MC_TurntTigers @suggswriter @MorehouseMBB @PaineCollege @NCAADII We’re just doing our best to get you focused on C… https://t.co/UW27IH4NDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's my reasoning why #captainmarvel is gonna be a "meh" kinda movie. We are way past the point of origin stories… https://t.co/OMJyuwqklT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo how many receptions will @AB84 have in the layoffs this season? @52Mack_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smartereveryday @thephysicsgirl You guys are an inspiration.  Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impossible to say just 1, Dynamite Kid v Tiger Mask (Sayama) series, Flair v Steamboat series Cm Punk v Samoa Joe s… https://t.co/9tYT2yNDVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our students did an amazing job today participating in the statewide tornado drill. Take a few moments this week to… https://t.co/mL7ImzHqVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadCop_NoDonuts @IlhanMN The deplorables yearn for a country this country to be white and Christian. Ain’t gonna happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 I'm not agree whit you. People from PR are more conservative than more of state I ever live. In here… https://t.co/hu8vPw2LtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you subscribed to my YouTube channel yet? Tons of free videos #takelearningwithyou https://t.co/WHmjoKBz4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing up in Austin I had the exposure to this music, and loved it!  I’ve heard @TexasFloodTX is like revisiting t… https://t.co/ikwJOmgZSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samuel Teah aka tsunami_sam1 waits for the bell. #PhotoByDC #Boxing #Philly #Fighter #Athlete #Boxeo @ The Met Phil… https://t.co/3qMMXhR0fI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time to consider only having 4 people on the court instead of playing Domenic Olejniczak @OleMissMBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[They would NOT let me drive it.  #HendricksMuseum https://t.co/2XO8EH5CyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The abuse of holocaust survivors is another example https://t.co/JPpOh8JfEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jay Lilly and MAF Teeski&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; Rylo Rodriguez @AintUMadison]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Now did she mean people who “hate” white men or did she mean white men who “hate” others? I’m confu… https://t.co/YJMyaqS99Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Science #sciencetwitter #westwoodhighschoolscience https://t.co/RuqKSWQxlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KiltedMath_T @MiliLaff Huzzah! Here is your gold star and your No Homework Hall of Fame Plaque. https://t.co/9Sx0o6TKdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Teejay5 This sounds like the Pulitzer project I did a while back... but in unity...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think there’s anyone in the world I’d rather be than Bryce Harper right now. Best flow/beard combo in the s… https://t.co/TPEVZrHKHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally Got Off Before the Sun Is Down.... Now all I need to know is what I’m eating]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs to realize that we need to do our tweets and responses differently  Important to read:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sufferingjuke @chillwig Loose Lucy gotta be the loudest and most amped crowed reaction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you think about the push to raise the smoking age in New York? https://t.co/Q8N3EeR0TC]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you base real actual good or bad feelings towards someone based off their zodiac sign you’re a nut lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DZMMTeleRadyo @alvinelchico @DorisBigornia Hi Po sir Alvin, AL MORANAS is in da house thank you po sir.👋👋👋👋👋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trafficjamjen Why don’t they change the election to warmer months you would have a big turn out . I’m not a Chicago voter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mav4fun @kylegriffin1 @EdRedstateblues @AnnCoulter https://t.co/0p6nlEga6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bigdoggpinc  Just sayin Bigdoggpinc on Pinterest to see more... @ San Ramon, California https://t.co/tOeYGcbX0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNAiAnalyst That is why I’m dumbfounded with the valuation vis-à-vis other bispecifics in the space whether T or NK approach (WTF?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Le_Pofin @go_jos_go @Dandelorme @50F10ULE pourquoi garder ça privé ?🤔😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[26/02/19 . . . #streetart #graffiti #words #neworleans @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/giWaiDekFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weathernetwork Niagara-on-the-Lake on February 24, 2019 https://t.co/iHRvSpLdv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Fellow Patriots and Happy Sunday to you All.  GOD BLESS AMERICA BLESS OUR MILITARY BLESS OUR LAW ENFOR… https://t.co/ZfG7AegUdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itschappy Financial goals and objectives with the credit card interchange fees they’re receiving. They could raise… https://t.co/ZOZ3wS0Rcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good point.  The GOP is calling Cohen a liar, but doesn’t question the substance of what he says about Trump.  https://t.co/mr3pbvhQpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMRutledge @MFSAVoices Pensions don’t represent people - they represent the work of people, and we are not our work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m about to start writing. Putting all my thoughts on paper. 📝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimelordGenius @Tyjos84 @StaticWarpBubbl @Tyranicus I went to both Day Of The Doctor Events. I drove to Atlanta fo… https://t.co/zH1JH6tjF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isaiahthomas Jaylon McDonald All Americans All McDonald's SLAM NIKE 5STAR🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀4 news sports ,jaylon 23pt11rd 4dunk… https://t.co/P1og1vM5Th]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs to watch Fox n Friends if they wanna hear the truth and not Fake News I’m sick of CNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your soul breathes into my body like a cloud of smoke... I should have known that you’d stay in my system even when you’re gone.. 🎙😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Barry Sanders/Megatron highlight should only serve as a reminder of how the Lions mediocrity ran two of the s… https://t.co/sRoJco3ARO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another “Christian MAGA” person calling me names while spewing misinformation. WWJD, amirite?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF #ChangeMakers @DKsUniverse @claynutting @barrybroome @KAIPartners @code4sac @lightedstar @vizthinker… https://t.co/AQY6ytnwru]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandparents could receive a loan on a hand shake What does that tell you about where America is going]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wooooow my new clothes won’t be here until Monday and I leave at 6 am 😐😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great teams don't lose to terrible teams like Georgia last week but neither here nor there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate Before or after the primary, you won’t be able to pry a negative word about any of the Dems out of me with a crowbar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time tonight at the Speed Work Clinic and When Can (should) I Run talk with @mikeyw14 .  #runclinic… https://t.co/G7PJ5MybTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waynesadin @CPetersen_CS @mthiele10 @techtalksio The cost cutting is easy. Left a job a few years ago because that… https://t.co/rDKz0GLVzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr Saru basically turns into a BernieBro in the latest episode of Star Trek Discovery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rothgar Also check out viper, from the author of hugo @spf13. It is great stuff: https://t.co/DtyB2PjncK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This probably needs to be validated... #foodie #whatdiet #travelingsalesman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lcalesolomon @dcexaminer @redsteeze @RashidaTlaib She represents Dearborn not Michigan, she is a disgrace!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those Nickens genes are strong. Catching up with the little sister finally! ❤️❤️❤️ @ Long Beach, California https://t.co/4wzZEtBFAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WORLDSTAR @souljaboy Nigga who is your girl fr ?!!! 😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/lWSLOo7fHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Secretly_Saucy #CatsOfTwitter fo sho, wait..... https://t.co/S8NXkQAh8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_Litch88 @Buckeyecardnut Match maker! .... hopefully you guys can come to terms unlike Bryce Harper lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desde que la moda se metio en mi ADN y mi vida vibraba cada vez que veía  grandes  producciones  inspiradoras que s… https://t.co/yZlTwonr42]]></document><document><![CDATA[We @Populous feel honored to have played a part in this endeavor.  Thank you to all who made it possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_nikkiLL Dude I hit a massive puddle today.. I couldn’t see after I hit it for a couple seconds 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonbelial @Mel_the_geek @Observer2541 @deelane @synredae @PATRICIAMEEHA17 @Elinor27652146 @Trixie883low @Hiveaclue… https://t.co/cniVqU8kEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[FIREWORKS: Graham Vows Rosenstein Investigation Over ‘Bureaucratic Coup’ to Remove Trump https://t.co/pnGQetygEE via @ILMForg]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOARING INTO THE SUNRISE! What a view for the passengers in this plane as it landed in Phoenix this morning. ANOTHE… https://t.co/7gGnbTEsSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MistyMacAll Looking Sexy Misty! I wish we could hang out in similar panties and chat with each other about the Hot Guys we love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeedQuiz real recognizes motherfucking real😤🥰😁 https://t.co/zvuBwsn3OC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Hokies coach Buzz Williams on importance of staying out of foul trouble, avoiding any more injuries: "We need a lot of things to go right."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not hiding Obstruction anymore now it’s business as usual for the Democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotJackKemp there are few things as weird as getting this notification https://t.co/Dskou0w72G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s test our friendship! #BoardKings https://t.co/2YbYDSgEde https://t.co/uGC28IkLFa https://t.co/2YbYDSgEde]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillJillmjordan @codeofvets @gepehill1 @amvetsupport @veterans_i @KarenLL11 @POTUS Read the Constitution please than come talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatxer01 @RealSaavedra @BuckSexton Fox had 2.205 million viewers on average in January.  MSNBC had 1.977 and CNN 1… https://t.co/OOtXSGBPZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DUPONTBLUES Thanks Ryan. Tell Monica I’m thinking about her and please feel better soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MentalSarahi I pronounce vow like cow. I’m still trying to figure out how you pronounce it that it has an “a” sound]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView Meghan McCain you retarded b**** if you want to see that climate change really does exist look around you… https://t.co/2zyB4f9drT]]></document><document><![CDATA[They don't dare do The Man Show with Jimmy Kimmel. Kimmel hates Trump, and like Frost's Road Least Traveled...that… https://t.co/N11gLlgCws]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been lazy and without anything interesting nor challenging for a while, now.  The nights and weekends of layin… https://t.co/zaEngSrZbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myDeathTherapy @JoshKincheloe @SilentGarrett Absolutely loved the first LP, I’m so stoked to see what you did on LP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayorNHL No, no, no keep losing!!! It WILL benefit you in the long run!!! Hughes or Kakko much better than pick nu… https://t.co/S7VJw2ITZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaddCompani @TheOriginalNai badd: i have a really bad feeling about a tweet trump did.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there a setting in Spotify where I can have it never play me remixes? this is getting absurd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Eagles fam! 13-3 or 12-4 this season? What you guys think? https://t.co/UJcSuiVczd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice day to enjoy a glass of wine and a mini cigar. #redwine🍷 #cigarillo #niceday☀️ #asticrewrepresent #texas🇨🇱… https://t.co/j6HlMMO3J5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FRONZ1LLA @ATTILAga I was hoping for a song like Bulletproof where you sing... glad ya made it 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathanfielder you’re a hero of mine. I’d like to be one of your unpaid interns. https://t.co/yQZUAs77Jm]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:06 to go in the first and Edison leads University 4-0 in boys lacrosse action at Edison. @EdisonLAX @EdisonSportsNet @ocvarsity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neontaster Eco-Queer lumbersexuality from the feminist lense of sexual dissidence with attention to latter-day man… https://t.co/5gO69VEwEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clayton Dwyer with the CG 3-1 win (9 IP 10K 8H) as Barry and Perry bombs provide the offense. GM 2 of @SalisburyBB… https://t.co/rQcLuAJppj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Njdevils44 @LeoScaglioneJr Goaltending looks to be figured out by being the tallest dwarf in the current 6 game losing streak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllenTStClair @ChaseConnor7 Kent and Ggreg Deborah Taylor, Disneyland, 1997. https://t.co/35e6oaixVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@senfeinstein  - I want you to demand Bill Barr commit, under oath, to recuse himself from Mueller’s investigation… https://t.co/Vd3ILPQpyw]]></document></documents></author>