<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[idk where this came from but this is a game changer https://t.co/Mdp1DJMgu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Complete team performance by #OaklandMSOC last night w/5-0 shutout over one of top university teams in Canada🇨🇦… https://t.co/zlvDR9npkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 @SariTreks If a Republican did any one of several things she has done, that person would be before the e… https://t.co/vq18ziGbFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meal preparation last night paid off tonight.  #Mealpreparation #Healthy #healthyfood #healthylifestyle… https://t.co/RAhZJysEwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[All caught up with new #RHONY. Who is producing it this season? It looks low res and cheap confessionals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job by you and your teams today @ChadChronister - keep up the great work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicherAmanda @MayorJenny I’ve already moved out.  When I say homeless. I literally mean homeless. The city is goin… https://t.co/iL5ML7pDgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This filth should be immediately executed we must not stand for this kind of Godless trash in our politics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Malia Obama drinking wine at age 20? So people are pissed? Are people going to realize that they are only attacking… https://t.co/sornJDMm26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dpineda9 ¡Gracias Diego!  Sigue trabajando porque se les escapó un resultado favorable. Algo anda mal ahí.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GET OUT of here. You can’t tell me #DarkPhoenix doesn’t look good. Especially being a Jean Grey fan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar @PeteHegseth @AOC If Communism means being able to work at a skilled job and being able to pay rent with y… https://t.co/2zgOrHTgk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING: One person severely injured after home burst into flames in Deerfield Beach overnight. @browardsheriff F… https://t.co/byoUjczwdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude wearing the NeXT letter jacket wins so far this morning. #AppleShareholderMeeting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to live in an actual building downtown, sick and tired of all my hipster dwellings over the years, shit is not fun anymore. Soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjayyjjayyjj @RudeCrudeTruth @Troy4LSU @LeslieRaeMag @marcushjohnson I'm not the one struggling with that idea. Go talk to your buddies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityMinneapolis @MinneapolisPD Isn't there a parking restriction in place.  Only parking on the odd side of the st… https://t.co/solTQl2nxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp Think about what it would have cost at just half price. That would have been an $4.5k savings for them if… https://t.co/54X8QpjgVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life is beautiful because of you  my lady love @JudyAnn_67 You showed me the meaning of love.  Your everything t… https://t.co/UwhZ4Ta6nj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Disney accepts $3.5B offer for #YESNetwork #Yankees  https://t.co/s3jhHC7bvj via @nypost]]></document><document><![CDATA[However did you know that @StephMcMahon and @VinceMcMahon are the only two people on this countdown who's achieved… https://t.co/4Z7PmTURKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ole Boone #7 was built in 1937 and still going today #Andersonferry #Ferry #FerryBoaterForLife #Ferryboat     -… https://t.co/sqb71g2MQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[SDSU starting to find their way buckle up Aztec fans this team will be a TOUGH OUT moving forward 🤙🏽.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMisterMarcus @MeninistTweet Because why not🤷  stronger men would have just laughed or ignored the comments]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Words "Dirk Nowitzki and Dwyane Wade make for a memorable final appearance as NBA All-Stars"  https://t.co/CsAfMI0fOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SNYtv @JeffMcNeil805 Stick to bowling. You won’t have a wack GM with conflicts of interest coming out the butt to… https://t.co/tpOopMSV2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accepted the 7 book covers in 7 days challenge from @armstrongta  Let’s see what @ChasStoltenow and @TFlakoll have… https://t.co/b31ax1hZl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox’s will continued to be the best news media the others can’t get out of their own way]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for Lego Movie 2 and I’m very jealous of the dad in front of my with the giant hot dog and 32 oz beer. https://t.co/FDkBNYrmXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSidesSF what’s an alt-cyber security event without a little @NSAGov recruiting :-) #BSidesSF2019 https://t.co/Imc6WIHuHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Ditto. But it's a long primary season and I am only supporting REAL Democrats. Bernie did enough damage last time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badhopper Yes!!  Been a while since I had Jury Duty.  Was called 3 yrs ago for Federal Jury duty, ended up never going to courthouse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now available and #InMyShop! #Vintage #Rena Signed #Agate Pattern #Retro Bowl!  Want it? Then head on over to The 8… https://t.co/fVDnCsYZ0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing funnier than foggy Republicans thinking #Trump is vulnerable in a primary.  Bring it on, #BillWeld  https://t.co/3ZFUgdu2sv]]></document><document><![CDATA[That time you were a sleeper cell agent and @mattgaetz drunk tweeted and blew your cover...]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never know what dispatch said. This man could’ve had a warrant out for his arrest 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best I have watched   #WithAuthority  #adamjcook #iPhoneRenegade   🔆🔆🔆🔆 @ChampionsTour  @fredcouplesgolf… https://t.co/fi5A9Soivj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LanceUlanoff Who's Cuban?  #sxsw  I guess he's ok  🏀🏴‍☠️  for an old guy  3-point is weak  @mcuban   but he'll do… https://t.co/Mc5FwKUUSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[An @ECUBaseball tradition like no other... @CoachPalumbo22 and @coachBGolden playing with their kids postgame. https://t.co/ptK5zM3FUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GunnarJL Good thing there was a nurse there to deal with your sudden lack of arms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just passed a stretch limo packed to the rafters with Buddhist monks. A bit unexpected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSarcasmShow Mar-a-lago is a front for money both legal &amp; illegal, as is everything trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bantercleveland in the new location in @vanakendistrict and gorged ourselves on poutine. Naptime!!!! #poutine… https://t.co/5AAYs8Sy1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go not a great slate but love these-  Cincinnati -8 Michigan -5.5 Lakers +3]]></document><document><![CDATA[He signs with that patriots it’d pissed so many people lol would be very interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelipeWWoHP @JeremyMcNaughty There definitely is tall glass walls but you know people are dumb and would act a fool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starbucks do you have any Keyo friendly coffee recommendations on this wondrous wednesday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @RedSox have added two more runs in the sixth as this game has come to a near standstill. Sox still batting, up… https://t.co/SRDq8yBHM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @drawandstrike Agreed but I'm not buying he did it for a raise or to promote his career.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Car shopping finished! 5 hours later and I’ve signed on the dotted line. New owner of a 2016 Jeep Patriot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KazamakisBob @ReaganRational @RNCastaldo @RyanAFournier Then don’t label yourself a socialist. You literally have… https://t.co/er9s1FMp0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to these chefs who traveled to #yuma from across the country to help with the #2019HarvestDinner https://t.co/cJ3vsrsa1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicwillow @mattgaetz @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @JudgeJeanine collusion IS NOT a crime, so what, it would have… https://t.co/4WFQw5CLkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[im not a reg mom. im a free range mom and i’ll come home when I WANT. https://t.co/ygjhSsqaKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squidbilly929 And u never explained why ur always angry and hate life... but everyone gave up trying to find out and help ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@UWL_Basketball is in! Congrats Eagles! What a season and what a job by @dernbach4, staff, and players. Incredible… https://t.co/1TXhe92vgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judyohtweets @RichP222 @KristinaNadia @MrsTyler78 @Dapple_TXUSA @LifesStyleBlog @riapanacea https://t.co/PyIFIkmkhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t remember an avalanche closing I-70 in that area before off the top of my head. Incredible the force of natu… https://t.co/b3aMzptjYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess this means I’m partying by myself tonight? Cheers 🍷 https://t.co/E495AF7LYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eva_marog Muy buenos días Eva y feliz viernes y día de la mujer saludos cordiales y cuídate mucho,!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a pretty good night but I just want to unload a bunch of bummer ass shit on Twitter because....... I'm a bumm… https://t.co/ZJZDzcwhbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might be trying to build a dream... #cargobikesolutions #yearofthecargobike @ New York, New York https://t.co/xZ6OBMp3qA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ruinofbritain Ask @ehutchinson1513 about a layman’s ability to “read” the “patristics”]]></document><document><![CDATA[W/ MR HEAVEN OR HELL #heavenorhell #heavenorhellclothing #heavenorhellwear 🔥🔥🔥 @ Vibz Uptown https://t.co/mNLXA88XhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nunyabiznasbro @RepDanCrenshaw You showed the same false facts as Trump . That is actually not an infringement. Th… https://t.co/7KZNNJUVCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bglB2Avj9U FACEBOOK MARKETPLACE TOLL-FREE NUMBER IS 1-855-479-3999 #facebookmarketplace… https://t.co/GQ1S0eusJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfWudan Agree and people suffer in many ways. Some physically thru illness, stress and violent surroundings. Other… https://t.co/Qa8kSEfNDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many years go by. I am aware @311. But I’m not a fan yet. It is now 2001. I have learned what marijuana is. I smoke… https://t.co/jT4lGi5u9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So someone that has said 10,000 lies, in two years, to the entire world, is calling someone a liar… https://t.co/XUg0Su8n1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Just Saved Taxpayers $150 BILLION With Brand New Welfare Rule https://t.co/xGiOPhtada via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello @SenatorSinema and @SenMcSallyAZ ?? No statements? #LackOfLeadership]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crepeau Any word on whether or not his child support issues will be addressed before he can be bonded out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pickensprogress I passed that wreck returning home to Bent Tree. I was impressed that local citizens - two men - h… https://t.co/RjLrxPJC3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Armando0827 @angelbc @Sifuentes @hconsombrero No, bueno, pero PARA NADA mejor. Para mi hasta The Fly la supera.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy V-Day!!! That’s V for Vacation for The Elke and Me!! Be back soon, happy Valentine’s Day Everyone!!!! @ Jacks… https://t.co/OSPpeSAIwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The premiere to Conga Inferno and Freak on Fleek happening now! Listen on youtube ...  Designs: thegoodyeareffect… https://t.co/lMulm4EqQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotLasers The character does briefly mention having considered gender reassignment surgery, but it’s not discussed… https://t.co/vRXjgTk3rK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metsrulein2k @MetsMerized @martinonyc @JonHeyman He'd rather play for a real team like the Phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrMatthewLC Above all else, the logic here reveals its fallacy:  That denying children a place is a sanction direc… https://t.co/5ecLGlCWkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b_piepenbrok @ISMRaceway @AshleyCote74 Lol he wasnt skipped over on purpose]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the privilege to be one of the “cyber experts” meeting with students at the #RSAC Security Scholar lunch — in… https://t.co/LPwMr423K3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DelaSt4You I haven’t peeped but gunna’s is better then offsets forsure lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport Can’t wait til he’s re-elected just to put all you crybaby , sore losing liberals in your place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice event, great people. gcu HOF induction #homecoming @ Grand Canyon University Student Union https://t.co/UW41nbk0Aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chewy. Thanks for sharing @JakeBonura - Drinking a Layers of Influence (2019) by @BottleLogicBrew/@JWakefieldBeer @… https://t.co/olNV1Cboii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrookByDaBook4 @j62966ay @PatMcAfeeShow @steelers You lost me sorry I’m not sure what you mean, I won’t lie I’m hu… https://t.co/LlsIMk7o2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthaig1 There's still a few months before the next election. Maybe Trudeau will decide to keep his promise. https://t.co/NfYunbWdbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Husker_Nick @ESPNHOOKSY @willyjwilson I think the Ok St game was the game everyone walked out on. It was rough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cougfanblue @itschappy @vakaviti @nihilists4jesus @boneyfuller Yeah, I saw that. I didn’t know the source. I thoug… https://t.co/0gdtG1clV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[&lt;iframe src="https://t.co/QOxcEE1wxV" frameborder="0" width="120" height="340" scrolling="YES" allowHALFscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 min hablando con chivo y le conté hasta que cague aguado, parezco vieja por que literal le pase todo el chisme😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeboone @SarahKSilverman @zoebritton I guess you have no interest in listening to someone pointing out how fundam… https://t.co/nGt8kh5n82]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got told at the last minute that we having a 4 day weekend... ima be a savage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[5th grade me: “Mom can I go outside, I finished my homework.”  Mom: https://t.co/iifFCc5iIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was four years ago. Same place, same result ! https://t.co/6kvuKSXSUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Not as much as it was when crazy uncle joe was Vice President. #recordssealedobama]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clutchcitycam @LandOfSteve @The_Raheel K. But that’s not what you said.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajapackertalk Totally agree! Antonio Brown should be a Packer. I don't care about $$. Aaron has probably 3 years left. Win now]]></document><document><![CDATA[If these are false accusations. Then fox is showing video from some other Countries border. I have say fox. The oth… https://t.co/EVqptZQDOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[OVC final: Murray St. 77, Belmont 65. The Racers are going to the NCAA Tournament for the second straight year.]]></document></documents></author>