<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jordanwolfe330 @AnnieLinskey @CWG_Workers @SherrodBrown Sherrod Brown would be SO good for this country. He is eve… https://t.co/Q0Zo6IuVcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HILLYWOODSQUAD @HillyHindi I loved the UK version! I tried the US version but couldn’t get into it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here in municipal court again. My wawa is getting absolutely savaged for misrepresenting prices on shelves and displays. I’m shook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop worrying about what "they" think! @ Carson City, Nevada https://t.co/ihxKkrTt63]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Fat Tuesday the best way we know how... with some paczkis coverage!! Have you ever had one of these tas… https://t.co/OfE39bhUC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Cher Show.. I got you Babe! lisa_arls @ Neil Simon Theatre https://t.co/xXUNdn5Tzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john35592542 @DiamondandSilk @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Again from Australia]]></document><document><![CDATA[NETA BAÑENSE. PEINENSE USEN DESODORANTE! NO MAMEN SON VARONEEEES! ENCERIO SI DA CORAJE QUE UNA SE ESMERA EN SU ARRE… https://t.co/BXlxrYfAH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does @corywellsmusic keep getting better with each new song release? We just don't know but he does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wierdest_lyz @Derrickblogs @Mariabo69 @AOC @AP Trump had experience. Five children with three women. Six bankruptc… https://t.co/Iy9ziA57UY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Maybe if they got off their asses and phones they could make some 💰.]]></document><document><![CDATA[alexa play moment 4 life by nicki minaj (ft. drake) @ Disney's Port Orleans Resort - French Quarter https://t.co/OqZ3wlflw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegan vanilla orange rice crispy treats. #veganforlife #veganforlove #vegan #happyheart #gratefulin2019… https://t.co/EnsM2PJBE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[why is life complicated/hard!? because it gives us a challenge, so that we can learn and grow to be able to move forward in our lives!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvePetThatDog OMG! Looks like my bloodhound/lab mix! Here’s Mischief. https://t.co/Th7r7EQXeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to visit @BadlandsNPS during this summer’s #GreatAmericanRoadTrip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to reading it so I can share with others who think I am beyond nerdy because I am in a doctoral pro… https://t.co/CrFzTbaFVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Engaging dialogue today in the first session of our campus book study. #growthmindsetywla]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team SAS having a great time at our Teach Significantly PD! #TeachSignificantly @MSMU @DBallWriter @Principal567… https://t.co/1cYkfxpEo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julieg000 @BryanStephensHR @barrettstork1 @Chamber757 @CareerPeninsula @DonStyer @vaemploy @Gucci_Hawkeye… https://t.co/7JPASc3hZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennybo0mx Lmao just @ @amaandduhh  next time...geeessshhhh #nobangs2019 🙅🏼‍♀️😂😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Does Planned Parenthood Do With Babies That Survive Abortions? https://t.co/w4r4XmWG11 via @Revelation1217]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StennettRennie @LowellCohn From what I hear, there will be DH in 2 years.  Players want it, union wants it, 30 new… https://t.co/ZrsHKhxMWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great teacher quote. Now I want a poster of a pebble  making ripples in a pond!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart is shouting for @al and @mainedcm  Forever #ADNForDaddysGurlWithALDEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This applies to our students and our student athletes. So proud of all of our students whether winning on/in the ma… https://t.co/PlBDDgV2Zq]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 new paintings for sale and I am pumped to start a new one because I just got an idea. Elton John. Its gonna be great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind-the-scenes with the team that gets us to the starting line.🌁✔️💯🏁 #Skyway10k @HillsboroughSch https://t.co/b1dsB1C9FZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @JackConnie @Jesus_Luvs_Us @debratankersle1 @Jimmysimmonds1 @MelindaYoe @Iluvinspireu @roads2… https://t.co/Q9lzLABNCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello everyone I’ve been mia for a minute now,, sorry about that. life is crazy and I miss tour, I miss following b… https://t.co/Swww0yhT4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scrappy_momma Is that a song?  I thought it was - walk with an E Rection.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally put ash twerking while standing in beer can boxes on my story.. she’s most definitely gonna kill me but...… https://t.co/sOag95p9YV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at ✨The Diva's Room of Solitude✨🌟💫 in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/JF5AdMFNcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman @rachelpchapa Me either and people are becoming spineless 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherylunderwood Why the silence now that he has been arrested. You girls were so sure he was innocent. This Countr… https://t.co/m3al9rz5Ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwainEvent I have a ticket for sale $100 section 329 row 14. #volsonly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeremiah 24:6 KJV For I will set mine eyes upon them for good, and I will bring them again to this land: and I will… https://t.co/X7Sce3jjy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jj051301 @aryservant @janet_bodell @ITGeekCT @d_ast777 @DavidHarris707 @JudyMcAferty @Reynolds2G @eunicelozano07… https://t.co/R2bjv1SGeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrinimeanie I dated a man that would taste my food every time but also never wanted to share. He brainwashed me. 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[생일 축하합니다 Happy Birthday SUGA!!! Enjoy! Cheers! 🥰🥳🎂🍪🥂🎈🎉🎁💜 #HappySUGADay #OurFirstLoveMinYoongi https://t.co/81H4LIXZDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @TPUSA I would have pulled my gun and busted a cap in his ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this item in my Etsy shop https://t.co/9stO6k87o5 #chef #red #etsy #shophandmade #forthecookinyourlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar’s giveaways are so insane and generous, I would die if I ever won something like that. Imagine being r… https://t.co/6KffCT8Uyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought ppl hired lawyers so that they would be less stressed —my lawyer really stresses me out. Like, really. I… https://t.co/rvxa3cGFBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottPresler Did that woman just laughed at her? What makes me so mad about these lawmakers that they're ignoring… https://t.co/GZy4JsR8mN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hallmarkmovie @Ali_Sweeney The Will  #ChronicleMysteries #VinesThatBind]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I cannot believe people haven’t jumped on this crazy coincidence 👺]]></document><document><![CDATA[I put on Instagram for people not to send me messages about weight loss products and I’m still getting messages wha… https://t.co/dvPGnJ8Cso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stellarbeing011 That’s super awesome! As long as they can hear you sometimes that’s all that matters. :) would love to see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1800GETUGLY sorry this purchase was late. &lt;3 https://t.co/MU5RKMSLon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I celebrated my dad’s birthday. Today my dad and I dug a hole for the impending death of the family cat J… https://t.co/LmWpecbgj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida es como un columpio en el que necesitas tu propio impulso y tus fuerzas para poder llegar más y más alto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow...yeah...great possibility...politics...all about $$$ controlling their own agenda’s outcome...legal or not...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iAmMasonLevi Pick up line day 43: We're not socks. But I think we'd make a great pair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you could not call the news station and yell at me https://t.co/jbYKNxY5hs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyVAGirl I just got the big body pillow from Target for $10 and works JUST the same as a maternity pillow 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Good 4 them. Now, rhey need to surrender their souls to Jesus Christ so they can go to heaven when they die.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you ever see a dumb ass tweet and check to see who liked this shit to have come up on your twitter https://t.co/iWhFgJeSW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[the kiwi bot that followed me home tonight is the only thing that has ever brought me joy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sethzaremba Well that’s sad but considering the small number of female agency owners then maybe it’s like looking… https://t.co/LV2wRoLYUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[i JUST had a conversation like this with my friend and used the term treadmill also 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[ABGs of parenting: Always Be Grossing (the kids out) ♡ Kissing this longest shortest month good-bye! We got engaged… https://t.co/6cDiJARjY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IGPrestige You really have to pay attention or you’ll lose track of what’s happening!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @MaiWorld51 If they can get his, anyone can get ours we loose that freedom, we start loosing them all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's funny. Hilarious quote of the day! For more hilarious quotes and short jokes visit www.bestfunnyjoke... https://t.co/xk2EG1UFJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courage can be difficult when what is important goes against the mainstream. Be brave - share your knowledge and yo… https://t.co/5TqYtmtaQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLM FUCKING #MURDERING #EVIL BASTARDS #KILLING A BABY FOAL AFTER #TERRORIZING IT AND SEPERATING IT FROM THE MOTHER… https://t.co/4hPjuNAV8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help make it happen for When Opportunity Knocks https://t.co/kxVwGJUeMS #indiegogo via @indiegogo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marmaduke765 Thank you! Early start for you in the UK, you out training?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little Princess has gotten up twice tonight so far. Took her out first time to party. Take her out second time and… https://t.co/GwEbnxRyni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sixphon6s She’s so boring honestly she had to do some shit like this for attention]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all this is legit me ! People be saying I’m unapproachable bc of my face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AALIVESMATTER Listen to QANON Tribute from TOOTS SWEET #PSBArmy #WWG1WGA @heytootssweet https://t.co/cCjvNbg8gL]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL! Donald talks to his "third" like a baby. ... "Melania, Comey is a bad, bad guy "]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viking Closet Prom Dress Event- happening now!!! SBHS Auxiliary Gym 9-12! https://t.co/NE4nG7NvOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@supergirlstorm They don’t actually think ur a cop, they just want you to try to prove to them that you’re not. If… https://t.co/3heb7RN9uV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottieUpshall @CarloColaiacovo hey good to see you writing and hopefully doing very well!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnMcCook44 R I P Luke Perry l loved pretty much everything he did. God bless his family in their time of grief.]]></document><document><![CDATA[CBS 13, FOX 23 to have live coverage of service for Captain Joel Barnes.  Town officials have released a map of the… https://t.co/6XWxyWjbwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/umykxTALCH 💪🏻2019💪🏻I’m so proud to work for a company that is taking risks to dominate the market! Mak… https://t.co/KANFbfvABN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna take a quick trip to China before I pop baby #2 out, @jonjeden? This would bring me joy-misery loves company.… https://t.co/iw16zNcthr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gutfeld on Lara Logan's blunt truth on media bias  https://t.co/yZZJy4RKSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anewsbreaker @Individual1Pod @Zigmanfreud Doubtful, but glad it was his money not tax dollars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who repeatedly cheat on their wife shouldn't be forced to pay the family child support and spouse alimony ,… https://t.co/WD6XFiSU0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hellyeah #powermoves #womenempowerment #notgoingdownwithoutafight @ Rushton Farms https://t.co/XevIU1gIJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@x_curly @brendonurie @PanicAtTheDisco So excited to see the final product!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamcbest @realDonaldTrump He is!!! That’s the funny part. He is kicking the ass of the left. Over 50% approval. T… https://t.co/OwH0v16hK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLUS i could get bdevs season tickets if i went there but my life is already a mess and i genuinely stress myself o… https://t.co/cijC2HfFjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever aspiring to be the woman in this airport at 4am wearing a hat that says “dog people” like who are you and w… https://t.co/kJtNfoC9yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[All. The. Chills. Everyone at @Bounce_Hub is so excited to be a part of the new #Akron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[soñé que tocaba guitarra bien chido y cuando me desperté recordé que no tengo talento jajaja lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruckKingGrito Honestly it’s so hard and makes me so anxious lol video games aren’t for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kittenwithawhip Ssssssh, I'm trying to purge some of the old man's!! He owned enough for an entire army when he mo… https://t.co/Prd04mTbqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@postcereals I have a question to ask. Would I be able to DM you? Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[2. Behind the new network idea: How we got here https://t.co/FAd56MibeF #axiossneakpeek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod I love the way you dismiss our comments about Bernie as "bitterness"... just like you dismiss anythin… https://t.co/jtFCQZyIJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you get a chance, GO SEE P!NK in concert! She's an incredibly talented, inclusive, strong, amazing, funny as hel… https://t.co/P8HWVxHEeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the bar has Harry Potter themed beer and pins so you have to get them. ⚡️ #polyjuicepotion #harrypotter #HP… https://t.co/OFyIg3qJ0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wandaoaj @NRO @KatTimpf Can't take the heat, stay out of the kitchen.  OAC will never learn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[looking at decor and this shit already stressing me out. 😭 lemme just go back to sleep]]></document></documents></author>