<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@EileenForBlue @Dax_x98 @DjMusgr I am.  #shameonme 😢 https://t.co/L5N9K4kYHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcardib and @BrunoMars together 😩😍 #PleaseMe was amazin’ as I thought it was gonna be. They’re so fucking cute and vibe so well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheerleaders always in sync 🙌🏼 Wonder if they planned this 🤔 #intensityelitecheer #iec4l #iecfamily… https://t.co/2g5h5eFNFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker bought me a sign that says “Caution: I do not have time for stupid people” and a dictionary of words th… https://t.co/s5fNttXstV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmorton73 @tonyposnanski @realDonaldTrump Thats not the accordion that is the Lame Stream Media that he is playing… https://t.co/753yPFk7Z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[my body is done. I legit spent 15 of the last 48 hours in 4 inch heels and booties.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the #Oscars2019 and saw @TheRealStanLee in the Memoriam. I’m NOT OVER IT. 😭😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best Wishes tonight for all the films in #BestPicture #Oscars #Oscars2019 And love these #OllyGibbs drawings https://t.co/jSZsyvumnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My moms friend is the reason warren Jeffs Is  in prison that was her case she had to oppose him for 8 hrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[MORE OF THIS PLEASE. Gymnastics is a real sport and should have gymnasts with real emotions just like the big boys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekPa56710094 @Alexa17101614 @dahut07 @MatthewStimso16 @Cathhewat123 @maype7 @LOYALFAN1 @ollivier_yves… https://t.co/YqJSrIxG2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BRC_Central Thanks y'all if you know any cis male couples who want to help improve relationship education programs https://t.co/MIRnfxV92r]]></document><document><![CDATA[#anabelgonzalezfigueroa #eldesorden #defiesta #partying @ La Terraza Tiki Bar https://t.co/V62VNVCjQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking bets on how many you think I can eat!!! @ Fort Meade, Florida https://t.co/VuaBuyqez5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld Get Audible.....read War and Peace...you will be out for the count in ten. No drugs...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that I’ve had the opportunity to drink at least 20 really good wines in the last 2 months]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not really sure what a sponge bath is exactly but I think I’m giving myself one rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah. Nadler said they have evidence. They have to investigate and certify proof. Words and full sentences  defeat a… https://t.co/3PabXLksXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patcollins4 Hi Pat. I had a question about the Freeway Phantom murders and Jim Trainum told me to contact you. Can… https://t.co/a3cU6hg8jM]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's blackmailing them I can't think of any other reason he's still in office,if it's about smut,that's old news,tr… https://t.co/1sTeEpLsoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does this rag smell like chloroform to you? Here let me hold it over your nose,,,... https://t.co/1JuPBazI2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump What a mean statement..about the best President ever..Trump 2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Logen9fingerz Yep. I love It, but decided this one meant more to both of us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Смотрели вчера Оскар? Что думаете о победителях? У нас вообще была настоящая вечеринка в смокингах и платьях и даже… https://t.co/X2qaETC7CL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad likes to comment on my appearance whilst being a half ass parent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right now, care plan documents can’t be updated in real time and parents often lack access. @SickKidsNews and… https://t.co/Lmt1hkBSM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djpublius @OhioIndy1 @markknoller @margbrennan @senatemajldr @POTUS No, really they don’t!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ftdflowers wow after spending over an hour between myself and my boyfriend on the phone with your company yesterda… https://t.co/jXQCBwAWqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunnysideupcake @wvjoe911 Her and DeVos—neither are worthy to smell the fart vapor of a good teacher—teacher’s are… https://t.co/FCOTU32pJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, I’m just having some trouble saying what I want to say for this first solo episode. Anyone got any good… https://t.co/oTKRIBbISI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @TheDemocrats 2. They already have precedent. They pulled King from all his committees. Double stan… https://t.co/D6eXkdhdHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found the end of the world @ Fort DeSoto North Beach, St Petersburg, FL https://t.co/xsdLxCMIri]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5 I hope that these skills we teach aren’t different. Both are intended to prepare for career readiness. Students… https://t.co/eYHziBOEY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson Just came aboard and enjoying the journey! You are a fine young man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creative Ways To Take Picture With Your Family | Just Imagine – Daily Dose of Creativity... https://t.co/lnqv2pV1YC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoctorJAuthor @AndreaPatten @ellenzelwell @DMatthewBarnes @dbmoone @OleanderPlume @KingofQueens13 @mischa_eliot… https://t.co/8iuSnnrjOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ongoing rescue dog plotline on Real Housewives of Beverly Hills this season is getting kinda old... #RHOBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GilGnoble @GOP @RepMichaelGuest Mexico has not bullied anyone to use drugs. They send them over because US citizen… https://t.co/aMKCkSIFU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is always a great way to start the day when you visit the book fair and get to catch up with a great friend!… https://t.co/jqd31QFSRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mama shark? I’d like to think of myself more as a killer whale maybe a dolphin 🐬 😂 https://t.co/WOUA1mgi82]]></document><document><![CDATA[True, but we’re in a global economy now. US companies get sold to foreigners too. What matters is standing up for w… https://t.co/BZc3fN0EEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZamirGotta Oh, Zamir! A trip I would love to make — now for a financial windfall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday zobird!!! i love you so much and i hope you have the greatest day ❤️🤩🎉  @zoehorton_ https://t.co/jtYWp72VrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turbotax That's crap..Did mine last year then when I went to send my taxes in they hit me with a bill..Wanted me t… https://t.co/BPK3i9PC1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interview tomorrow 🤪 thank da lort I’ve missed our on buku money this week lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennydorko @atrupar Don't tell the Republicans, Denny. We're holding out on them so we can ambush them in 2020 alo… https://t.co/uL5X492m0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you break up with someone for hitting the “skip intro” button on Netflix? Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[kyle guys girlfriend in a video: people throw a lot of shade at duke kyle guy: cause they’re good man  thank you sir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scrappy_Pro @realDonaldTrump Do you think @FLOTUS has talks at night with him about much of his bad behavior all day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AutismScienceFd @mmillerucd I mean in the USA who doesn’t take prenatal vitamins  ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strangely these people say what they mean, and politicians and media pretend THEY don’t understand it. Then the edu… https://t.co/2IisiBCr4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stassi Love looks good on you! Watching you on #WWHL and you are glowing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My furniture isn’t being delivered for days but I made sure the WiFi was set up immediately! #newpad #5g… https://t.co/ajEsE257AU]]></document><document><![CDATA[90s night #hitopsla with OMARA Let’s do THIS #HiTopsLA #omardijou https://t.co/IDT6JcXNrk https://t.co/bLYxU8EtgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremymbarr @StandingLeaf Unbelievable.  But (unfortunately), considering where it was supposed to air, not really… https://t.co/ebu7kvb3Ly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 6: I have accepted a challenge from @SchifferB  to post #7BooksILove-no explanation, no reviews-just cover(s).… https://t.co/754pHiOcEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reality Called, So I Hung Up☎️ @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/sgry8LlxhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are y’all hearing this thing? So good! S-Watt by Tx-Watt. ❤️ Warning! 🚨 I’m noodling quite a bit so beware. Lol 😂… https://t.co/AYnJkgofjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know that while #CaptainMarvel is not the be-all and the end-all of diversity and representation of women in the… https://t.co/IMQVlfoif7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KKatMiss @Snack8671 @CharismaMolotov @Always04177875 @Anti_Liberal73 @MarylFaunda @fightinirish109 @Kegan545… https://t.co/MM0g1bZP3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT! #EVITAparty welcomes #manilaluzon to the main stage! DJ set by #djderekmonteiro Stage Shows Starring… https://t.co/VWqlDCrBgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sometimes I don’t even want to be on my phone so I won’t look at it and I’ll try to form an original thought and i… https://t.co/PGpfwiYz6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfaooo I’m creeping on your twitter straight dying laughing i need to go to bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewamiller I don’t think so either, but it will be such fun watching them all squirm like the worms they are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makykae Thanks love..   Oh ya know, just shattering glass ceilings over here 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *Reads and watches negative news to stay informed every day*  Me this morning when the news hinted at a dangero… https://t.co/Vl1vJHOa0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ej__mac True. Also Jho kaya nga sobrang highlight nung friendship nila ni Bea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That #moonrise doe. #moon er1251 pelon2327 #moon🌙 #moonlight #moonmagic  juvena11 influenceartists @tamuseum interc… https://t.co/zJPG9X564K]]></document><document><![CDATA[It had cost India over `700 crore to clothe and feed them, while foreign aid was only `30 crore. During a UN debate… https://t.co/S5fijnMLMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4oceanBracelets Environmental friendly substitutes have to be found by the powers-that-be!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow is this a strange brag... @allysonfelix turned pro out of high school and @adidas paid her tuition as part of h… https://t.co/lcCBRek2gs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTtoronto care to have @Songbird_7_ back to spread the news about this incredible important cause? @rogerfpetersen… https://t.co/HIQDNjdmN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sokane1 Naw, Mr. Cook is from my dad's home town.  Trust me, he is used to being around folks that are not the sharpest tool in the shed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let your smile change the world but don’t let the world change your smile #Outlander #LoveForSam Credit to… https://t.co/FY707wB8np]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5SOS @QueenWillRock I think there’s room for a 5th member. what do yuh day? 😉 (volume warning) rip headphone users https://t.co/IGcMI9Zk2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dunkindonuts I sent an order to the wrong store yesterday and they wouldn't refund me. Am I now out $9???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarliSchmidt took one of my dads t shirts over the summer and wears it all the time and he still doesn’t know that… https://t.co/EGDeksroXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting with the world’s funniest three people is setting us all up for disappointment #Amy #Tina #Maya #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbya_music @JimmieAllen This sounds AMAZING! I am so excited to hear it. Great job @abbya_music and @JimmieAllen… https://t.co/VADdmUEru3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brasil247 Ja is tupiniquins di BREEZYL preferem morrer CHUPANDO as BOLAS murchas e VERMELHAS de Trump. E a mamadei… https://t.co/I6ZRKdfGiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Can I choose none of the above ? The Dems need to do better than this to get the evil out of the White House]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hospitals...where you eat tuna salad sammies and drink milk at 10am.  #breakfastisover @ Massachusetts General Hosp… https://t.co/FwRyEmhxL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump No one is saying women are committing infanticide, just like no one blames women for bei… https://t.co/bbfVaUJsM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Trump receive a heads-up about WikiLeaks? - The Washington Post.     Of course he receives heads up! https://t.co/DEdmTrHrE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very proud to see the partnership between @BrassforAfrica and @Root_Foundation is off to a strong start! Inspiring… https://t.co/ImJgDktyT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Medical Mystery: Something Happened to U.S. Health Spending After 1980 https://t.co/oeILp8Kker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NISDOLC Well it really came down to mining strategies as far as enviro impact. Some students tried to conserve the… https://t.co/EBFhxgf8n0]]></document><document><![CDATA[with spring break being here, everyone please remember to respect our beaches and planet!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[refusing to go to sleep because i know when i wake up, i have to go to work 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCPS_NC TLC cognitive coach training...seek coaching moments; not minutes of time to coach! Thx @bosstetter_edu #JoCoTLCs #makemagicjoco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abc13houston But, I am truly happy for her and proud of her for overcoming her hardships‼️💙💚💖❤️💜💗💓😇😃👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha!  Or if the rt was blocked from registering with the message “Account Suspended”!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You could win the 2020 election if u would help the 30 million patients in America suffering from… https://t.co/hch9ScYog8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldbach_jackie @nomad_soc_eng @beileyarthur @AOC I would say what Republicans say if you don’t like the pay get a… https://t.co/IKQYpXciTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible moment as Veterans in the crowd recite the Oath of Office with @GinaOrtizJones. We have not forgotten. W… https://t.co/NanhqZ24du]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi Keep fighting this is a huge mess.  I truly appreciate everything you do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[computer repair shop cat does not know i don’t like her... https://t.co/4l4dgeUg8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaSoprano An awful essay by a white cis-woman on trans issues. Contained errors, omissions, misstatements, rep… https://t.co/qwKLJMUpj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @AnytimeFitness in Madison, WI https://t.co/33mjChBte5 https://t.co/zjMId7xrP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I have to say ladies is look at your boos father cause that’s what he’s gonna be when he grows up. And gentleme… https://t.co/6WxHmsirMq]]></document></documents></author>