<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m having a really hard time right now...my first Sim just passed away. 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beulah members at the Prayer Dedication Service of the 2019 Pan African Devotional Guide, "Lament and Hope." Thanks… https://t.co/Fke6bYrgFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are going purple for #IWD2019! Join @CREchatLIVE March 7th, 7:30 CST as we recognize @womensday. @BarbiReuter wi… https://t.co/AfD8mHkjU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mississippi educators practicing new strategies to strengthen Math classrooms @CurriculumAssoc #IreadyMS https://t.co/estIzSBaFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it’s heads up- it means you’ll get some money from a known source. If it’s tails up, the money will be from an u… https://t.co/fKaJFiajto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrunkNewg GWEN. Can we merge our experiences and our lives so I can be in NYC but also here. (Also I miss you.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Medical PACS direct $ to pro-gun candidates?! How can physicians and surgeons better put our money where our mouth… https://t.co/Z8RXpjZD3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday National Zoo! Love having you in my backyard, and as part of my daily commute and many long runs! 🐘🐆… https://t.co/aPrKrM5ptL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was going to make a roast but got lazy instead. Homemade beef stew. 🥩🥔🥕 #homecooking #comfortfood https://t.co/J4118S6dra]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like grabbing my blanket laying on the roof and watching the Stars ✨   You see I would do that but it’s legi… https://t.co/ikPIsAyuCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My work has a rewards app. Periodically it sends you a survey.  For some reason I get those notifications from when… https://t.co/WHVBgu3u1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact: Taylor Ortega and Todd Stashwick, who play Shego and Drakken in the new KP movie, learned more about thei… https://t.co/3pzQ42QS9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay but what if RKelly pulled a Gucci Mane and released music from jail? Like a new Trapped in the Cell series.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bruce1911 @yut45 Great, now I’m going to have to block my own kids just so you don’t see my tweets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck I love my music choices  So soothing 😌 🎶  Música para el alma Un sonido que me calma  Palabras que a mis herid… https://t.co/gtZZpu7KCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TeamSISD 6th grade math intersession! Making our STAAR Review Jounals #GeneralsConquer https://t.co/n2xOxwOOL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/XaOJzJnaGd #hotelbaker#buzzybooth#stc#winterwonderland#whatmonthisit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElaineW12284375 @Danabrown4Dana Raj looks like he’s saying,Mom,for reals?! My feet they’s cold!! 😹😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things to know about me... I'm not competing though. @ Rave Motion Pictures Polaris https://t.co/qAdwbyqEBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lenamroberson Maybe rehearse a new  mental narrative. Think of being offered help, not that you are a weak gender.… https://t.co/1FUS06wzzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some things are easier than others to discipline yourself in. True freedom means learning discipline. In our though… https://t.co/98KfV9OVmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always wanted to be a private detective and figure out unsolved murders .]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so conflicted: i want to go to the gym but i also want to cook some french toast for breakfast 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to do @TheLauraSteward radio show #allaboutthequestions on @iHeartRadio 11am - my topic “Thriving and… https://t.co/Bw64uAbMaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[can I stop seeing the same 5 tweets from 2016...Twitter getting mad repetitive damn]]></document><document><![CDATA[LTER Road Trip: Restoring Seagrass in Virginia’s Estuaries https://t.co/1Ja5VgnI3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snagged these bad boys last minute, it’s gonna be a good day. You can just call me the fast pass queen. 🙋🏻‍♀️💁🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/deFbAsRzeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The time to save big on solar is now. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarEnergy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awww look at how cute he is! He looks like a adorable little gummy bear😍🤗😊 https://t.co/uaVIXaNs48]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daddy never forgets his girls on Valentines Day #loveisintheair @ Bridgewater, Kissimmee, Florida https://t.co/29LsxKPkoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bf just facetime me in the middle of the night so I can see him throwing cheese to his nephew’s face and his dog. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this is anyone in my life, please know that I am always here for you. I know it feels lonely but just please kno… https://t.co/nnYNvJ6axR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need you all to know I broke my toe and the only shoes I can comfortably wear are these Nike’s. So please enjoy a… https://t.co/UtBjHEQYzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barefoot beach bouldering date with this little adventurer. Practicing our alliteration and #badass19 skills. (I ta… https://t.co/rNa60eGzo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trish_regan You are absolutely right. If this keeps up Trump will win by 63million votes more than in 2016.]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF THESE JUICE WRLD N SKI MASK PRE SALE TICKETS SELL OUT BEFORE I CAN GET THEM I WILL DIEEEEEEEEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mueller is the CRIMINAL here, he belongs in jail with Clinton and the rest of the CRIMINALS he is defending.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coup321 @zedunow @WINFOCUS @globalsono @Wil_MaChan @jsrempell @aliteplo Absolutely.  But even without the outliers… https://t.co/LJbFvtqhFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my gosh the crush I had on these boys! #realmenwearpink  so many childhood memories!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryWal22 @paige_katt Also...if you need a pick me up.  This is a great song!  https://t.co/Jog5yw2UbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarzRoberts @astateherald @Astate_CLAC Congrats, @ScottRuple13, @StephPenn717, and Jacob! Proud of you! #Imagine ❤️🐺🆙]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been hurt way to much for being to forgiving. You fuck up, and Things will never be the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1:34 da manhã e eu aqui olhando página de exército p ver os boy fardado]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Your lying, I can see it in your eyes. You don’t want no wall, your just letting the idiot bury hi… https://t.co/8mPrfYVMCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[En el derecho Romano, el Ius civile, era el conjunto de reglas que regulaban las relaciones entre todos los ciudada… https://t.co/KDufvNIk2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wrote an essay about how catholism is a tool of oppression used against women and how women must reject religi… https://t.co/bsqJo9QkWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck closure, some endings don’t need it. As long as you are able to be in peace with yourself that’s all that matters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are only spring or because it was AOC's plan and she is the little darling of the libs right now. They need he… https://t.co/NIvNmb92Ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@know_the_answer My best friends, my 2 bitches that always have my back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flying home today 6.5 hours from Tampa to Seattle but @AlaskaAir upgraded me to 1st class, thank you to the best airline in the business]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonbellion I am utterly in love with this album. Love the last one but this one just crossed over into another rea… https://t.co/2TPmNQ2yAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[What about doing more reporting on the Marines &amp; their families poisoned by the toxic water at Camp Lejeune North Carolina?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone know a good lash extension lady in Tempe!! Preferably close to ASU campus ‼️‼️‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic GRIT Lady Hens!! GREAT 4th quarter with a PUNCTUATION point!!❤️👍🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT AINT WORTH IT TO KEEP YOUR “family together” let the man just be a dad and let go bitch damn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I WILL BE BACK ON MY BULLSHIT IF THIS ISNT BULLSHIT @nickjonas @nickjonas  #jonasbrothersreunion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews I doubt he even knew who she was until he saw her name on Twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[really tired of only being good enough when it’s convenient to everyone else, smfh..]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Roma wins best picture tonight, theater owners should protest!#Netflixisntamoviehouse]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can handle myself, so living with three guys isn’t a problem. Even the madhouse disguised as a low income neighbo… https://t.co/6De0CKbMS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s Black Excellence in Public Service Forum was phenomenal. Thanks to our fantastic panelists and brilliant Ja… https://t.co/Zy8xWJONsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked my best friend to marry me this weekend, surrounded by our closest friends and family, and guess what? He s… https://t.co/tN1mgJevHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliaLClose @UFMedicine @UFHealthNews So grateful for all you’ve done for me. It is no surprise that I continue to… https://t.co/0XclqznYeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud Mom-in-law moment! @mrstovar is Teacher of the Year for @ELPASO_ISD Charles MS! 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briannaaboom Yeah. I am pretty sure I have Peacock, Rabbit and Bee figures out but those two are stumping me somewhat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo. So many of my friends fuck me over when I would drop everything in heart beat for them. This is why I stay having no friends 👏🏻😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The names of the complainers should be published.... SHAME THEM!!! APPAULLING😠😠😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[House Dems will take floor action to confront Omar’s latest Israel comments https://t.co/pukA1laGaK via @politico]]></document><document><![CDATA[At SWA I never said anything because I was scared of being fired so I just worked with my mouth shut. I know my lim… https://t.co/Bitoi3BInG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still time to snag the others. Payment Plan Options Available. #authentic #louisvuitton @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/pLcU65JWea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sundays are for getting out of bed slowly and ordering in Mexican for breakfast 💓 after debating if I should really… https://t.co/fGcXhmovyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ImChefCole I’ll be lucky to have a dog that last longer than 7 years 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gnewfry That's one idea I had, yes. I have some doll house- sized things, too...and there's always a goodly supply… https://t.co/S6q9wCO6c8]]></document><document><![CDATA[See that man coming through the doors? That’s Mr. Ricky, a custodian at Tamarack Elementary school. Today students… https://t.co/3n18EHpA1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have arrived #Beantown! Consider yourself warned. 💙😊 https://t.co/20pBTA1oGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/5vXHDSQLVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday!! @miinutemaidd have a great day and enjoy my fav video of you (-: https://t.co/ZZsxrIV4Bn]]></document><document><![CDATA[that girl is lucky I have a DZ sticker on my car and I made myself behave. don’t be honking because YOU are running late and are impatient.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like Gudo I wonder does my ex hate my guts and hopes I burn or thinks about me and is alright wit me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KDbyProxy @PhD_femme @FiveThirtyEight @maggiekb1 Those are examples of toxic masculinity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Chiquitae. She’s the 1st to do it! Breaking down Barriers with the Warriors. this is… https://t.co/FIxEWg62H3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @dizzynicky for thinking of me and @Kalli_Martinez !  Awesome mugs that will be greatly appreciated each mor… https://t.co/bcFw6XTe7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlthed @realDonaldTrump @IRetweetTrump Please don’t call him sir. Even sarcastically, he won’t see the difference]]></document><document><![CDATA[2day on my mom's FB Memories 3yrs ago @DiceGirlsBball let's play in our style- as a #team let's give all we got tod… https://t.co/nFJkOuSwuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoydKRutherford @mica @SmithsonianNMAI @MayorPugh50 @JohnnyOJr @GovLarryHogan @baltimoresun @DanRodricks Thanks fo… https://t.co/iWyuwwLzAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aetiology @danengber @NathanGrubaugh @Slate [...] so, Dan, instead of spending time attempting to defend your posi… https://t.co/mLWR32soo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nihikineko2 @AndrewPollackFL What has Trump done to help prevent school shootings???]]></document><document><![CDATA[OPEN HOUSE SUNDAY! 2-4 6000 Richpress Drive in Wexford Hills, Williamsburg Virginia #openhousesunday… https://t.co/Ie0STseFf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I need your help. Section 8 where I live is not doing their job even though I am following the rul… https://t.co/SNfjsRtkdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/x9Ci4e5pwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poll: Do You Love KISS? #KISS #ILOVEKISS #Kissarmy @KISSOnline @genesimmons @KISSopolis @KISSAnthemPrjct… https://t.co/vOMS7XK5Ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[How come I can ONLY clean my room at 3 a.m??? Like during the day I have hours to clean it and it just never happen… https://t.co/Q7ZklgnC9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iRTMteam just thought about a technique for seeing better at The Ring at night. Using the Flashing headlight before the turn in point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are in the 3rd month of the year and I’ve already got 3 possibly 4 shows lined up to go to with friends! And wor… https://t.co/RvVIyg9aFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@efrain_s It’s not hard. I’m having trouble contorting myself under the sink to disconnect the faucet. 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know this isn't book related, but book people like tea, so I thought I would share.  ..... I have just discovered… https://t.co/c7k8YBwxN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lt_gray Oh! I have to keep what I catch if it's a type fish I like! All this rain we have been getting I could fish in my back yard!!🐟🐟😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feminine lesbians ALSO like feminine lesbians. It’s like looking for a needle in a haystack but we exist even if we… https://t.co/BupmpD1O5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissAshes92 I’ve gone to high schools and middle schools to speak about EMA and what we do. Integration and coordi… https://t.co/1LC40XjoUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@22_leggett well, we know not to have but so much mouth before the game starts unlike you duke fans. 🙂]]></document></documents></author>