<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RichRodDoesPCP I’m sorry your life is so sad that you spend it trolling me. Might l suggest putting your time to b… https://t.co/54UEOJ6Pq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bus came earlier than expected, it was a Rapid, and my driver has a “move it or lose it” attitude. Bless this mess. #munimiracles]]></document><document><![CDATA[More pics from our trip... #triplethetroubletriplethefun #stitch #thebig3 #disneydream2019🛳 @ Disney's Castaway Cay https://t.co/0uQYu75BcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angtruo Oh yes sweetie next event we’ll be doing the grocery shopping. Water and ice only]]></document><document><![CDATA[2018 I dealt with so much anxiety. Every since I prayed in December for God to take that away from me, I have not d… https://t.co/8ZcRs88CmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I lost another dab pen last night somewhere in California probably at that taco bell I peed behind so can everyone… https://t.co/ZkLwvbChjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My emotions are up &amp; down this morning, y’all pray for me  Looking at my account because it’s payday 🤑😃  Then realizing rent due 😭😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahlynntyler @RRuby44 Thank you for standing up for women! #StopTheBans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khanhakim_k @akomama_tm @SUPERGOCHOo @DerekPa56710094 @PatGrant7777 @Lee888123 @stradagangelica @meerbakker… https://t.co/tKExPVTFzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[21 years ago today I gave birth to a little baby boy ❤️ #birthday #myson #motherson #prideandjoy #realtor… https://t.co/iFJN63idc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[when they care about working out lower body just as much as upper body &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ordered these for me and my niece so we will be matching and I’m literally .. excited https://t.co/l9fjviRneY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hazy LA IPA by @goldenroadbrew at @bubbleosqueak — https://t.co/jF5NbFVQUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C3Eagles @averagegumdrop @CNN I don’t EVEN Visit Colorado Springs ... That’s where the Crazies Live ... Ft Collins… https://t.co/eiRkop22rN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JigsyMD Forgot about this study but had a case recently where I didn't give abx. Love your impatient teaching pearls!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeenCryo @SandiaWisdom I follow Q and see a correlation between WWG1WGA, awakening and the P’nti they all want us… https://t.co/HcG6D1K2Ax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @ccatmpt @SLBriscoe @thatsVeryKari @Cbp8Cindy @joneill55 @suziday123 @cowineco @AkronWineGuru… https://t.co/VxUD02n9OX]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great night of family math for our ESL students and families! Thank you to a great team of teachers for planning… https://t.co/3syaDL4IMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I just want my legacy to be one that encourages other people to live their best life. And yes, I’m gonna h… https://t.co/f4J90FJ1VD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just an update: I leave my crutches in my car. Because I know I can’t go long distant without them. But I can go to… https://t.co/9cb4hKxKly]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 4th ‼️ it’s a conversation that’s sensitive but needs to be had 💯 https://t.co/FhGwJewlOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey! What’s up!  Since I moved, I haven’t seen any of my spider friends around.  I know you like to avoid people an… https://t.co/fobUyU7BzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMO otro nivel como me llevo con mi jefe 🤩🤪💅🏼💃🏻 #dreamsdocometrue 🌈 https://t.co/PYZGYXo82q]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s my mom’s birthday today, and I can only pray and hope I look that bomb at 47. CAUSE BABYYYYY, she is poppin lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Living Spaces Distribution Center in Fremont, CA https://t.co/C5wVJPUeg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaPustorino @gmasara @FRGRQueensgirl1 @MysticAngel1985 @Jennife01055359 @JuliK317 @Robin08139490 @fulvia14130533… https://t.co/fE6Atmcyy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a rhetorical question. Those boxes can be a problem. . . . . . . . . #highvibetribe #happyblackwoman… https://t.co/eABcgG1JIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiggyTheKing @BiggyTheKing I hope you’re not yawning all over campus! #wakeup #youretooyoungforthis]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got asked out for the day before and the day after Valentine’s Day. MFs really ain’t shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be completely vulgar in a DM. #EffectiveWaysToAnnoyMe https://t.co/fj40kxbwwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuel pump replacement 2009 Dodge Ram 5.7L #hemi #TIPM #garbage #engineeringFailure #shameonyou chrysler dodge daiml… https://t.co/13ksUMzVgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me why I thought I heard the boulder from work....... damn.🥴🤷🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/Yp5zuFAhHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @ColinJCarlson Pretty sure that kind of shenanigans gets you banned from eBay...]]></document><document><![CDATA[After these last few weeks, I seem to be nothing but a walking Petri dish 😷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nanamarciaa @Jim_Peoples_ @FabKalEl @Max_Patriote @Melski1 @Civildefense5 @batchief @ronthepatriot @richardgoad56… https://t.co/zOstyGDDpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new study puts #Minnesota among the leaders nationally in addressing concerns about bee 🐝 and butterfly 🦋 populat… https://t.co/BwmR87gmJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AvilerED @existentialfish I believe that is Article 1 of what the Stupids call "Shania Law" https://t.co/hivStfpMGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Popeyes chicken, Bang energy, and a foundation soda  is all needed to work 3rd shift. The struggle is real y’all! T… https://t.co/nX7m9U5cmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[não acredito que segunda já to indo embora, vou sentir mt sdd de cada detalhe daqui (exceto das comidas horríveis e apimentadas)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ginamarie313 @RecordingAcad @brandicarlile That note she hits near the end of "The Story" gives me chills. So glad… https://t.co/j3PdP3CbFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning LORD JESUS I HALLELUYAH!!! Your HOLY NAME, JESUS It Is Higher Than The Heavens Stronger Than Any Mount… https://t.co/eC8CP2PW6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loeybug Hey Loey, I’ve got an assignment for school where we have to do a presentation about someone who inspires… https://t.co/XDplaK3Anm]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re comfy in bed and then realize you haven’t taken your contacts out ☹️ i hate being blind smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InVisionApp Marketing Team thank you for my #getwell flowers. I'm following Dr's orders so I can be back soon.… https://t.co/axew76hRgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂 seriously sad about life when that happens - https://t.co/gyJ0EqDo8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honor the LORD with your wealth, with the firstfruits of all your crops; https://t.co/3srV8VMaNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BasuGranthakeet @ipshita_ahsan @HumairaTM1 @MoumitaTripathi @patralihiland @Sriparna_RC @anupa30 @sabrinshahrin90… https://t.co/FvvkQdnlT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[“One time [@ShannonSzabados] punched me in the face ... it was awesome!”  Not true, but probably true!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LCNM99 The baby talks to the parents right after being born, and is then killed? Why is he not is a mental facility?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like I woke up for work the same time @trainFanForLife went to bed after work and it’s a time that neither activities should happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[The owner at Remedy asked me if I wanted a drink right before we closed and for some reason the responsible me said no lolol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harveyjkaye Sorry I missed this and thanks for all the thought provoking tweets!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had so much fun with these two today with some impromptu ice skating fun—thanks to the sweet girl for sharing her m… https://t.co/DSqt69oUNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sewimperfect I really like Klobuchar, policy wise, but I'm troubled by the interpersonal stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody needs to explain to him what civil rights in this country mean that we don't judge people by the color of… https://t.co/FOfglCx1nm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bolivar PD, they took down their FB page, they KNEW they were wrong, @DanLairdMD  check out this illegal search IN A HOSPITAL ROOM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy TGIFriday!!! CHELLE B in this thang invading your airwaves doing it like #ItChelleBDone 7p-Midnt on the BIG S… https://t.co/MGm6mW8zmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maine is happy so nakakatulog ako ng mahimbing specially on this snowy night Maine supporter forever  @mainedcm  /… https://t.co/G4pAmIz8zL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WESH Slow news cycle? Nothing like promoting this nearly two-decades-old online urban legend as a real story. 🙄 I’… https://t.co/JbIW01HIyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hyatt House Raleigh North Hills - @hyattconcierge in Raleigh, NC https://t.co/m3cBExJzin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenny_deam @jenny_deam for reference could you please post the patient’s plan benefit document outlining the lawfu… https://t.co/wyOwFD0VTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I turn around I see somebody from Marvel! @ The Hollywood Roosevelt https://t.co/SShrdM6QfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake up! It’s Monday! A new week, new goals and new beginnings!   Today’s fitness called for LIIFT4 Week 5 Day 1 Ch… https://t.co/FGh28BsBwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm praying the Jojen Paste theory isn't right because I will never, ever, ever be able to forget that. There's alr… https://t.co/PGQbDToLrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ten month old was sleeping on the sofa when bullets rang out in the apartment and shots were fired. @KXAN_News @Austin_Police]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just tested out a new product for my collection I’m pleased with my work- nick and I both tested it tomorrow I’m a… https://t.co/BS9SGlQ0pK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nodens_Jr @theSirToasty @ZeldaUniverse Perfect for building up a hunger for octorocs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephwhite324 @SmallcageGG @EstellaRomanFan @WWERomanReigns @fabiola_pizana @Fileana2 @Sardarhamza124 @kaikaisonic… https://t.co/NlzccEj3If]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @maddow and @MotherJones @MiamiHerald about the stories about Cindy Yang. #CindyYang]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ 6335 Club Restaurant &amp; Lounge https://t.co/zUaFWwb8kF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robcesternino @TysonApostol @dannybryson Since I have a ton of Taco Bell sauce packets, as well as Del Taco, Jack… https://t.co/veoEvnnbBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Donald, we know that Cohen was scheduled to appear before the committee before your failed summit… https://t.co/9ELd8TGGAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Winter is almost over ( thank the Gods ).  But I’ve never been more excited for this one 😆 #gameof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cupcakes &amp; Cookies🧁   #neverdessertyou #namecookies #cupcakecookies #nameplaquecookies #atlantabakery… https://t.co/AHE5SOIT6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at MOY writing data to develop grade-level, class and individual focus areas, goals and next steps.… https://t.co/LVWaFxiHcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the basic ass Los Banos pictures, enjoy 😊🌸🐶 https://t.co/Gygu9ZXdbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking @sunnyonthescene needs to take this show on the road and americanair can make it happen at the right level… https://t.co/hOVIsyxoMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraHacker18 Aw thank you dear I was very thin from anxiety and stress didn’t know what to expect when hub got h… https://t.co/l7QJDU0aVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a good cry before getting out of bed in a Friday morning.  @MSUAlaina]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I tweeted yesterday. Democrats stop the #mobrule and #vigilantetweets against fellow Dems. Grow the he… https://t.co/NA4QnHdtiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any donation helps big or small and if you can’t donate I understand. Life is hard. But the least you can do is PLEASE SHARE IT HELPS!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es cierto Carlos, ninguna de las personas que las han secundado han el criterio suficiente para continuar ese legad… https://t.co/dPr9M5kN64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck @michelleinbklyn The point is that 45 lied about Senator Reid being thrown out when he retired and w… https://t.co/1LmvHS3zFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek If it was his child that was murdered he most definitely wouldn't be taking that psycho at his word! Psyc… https://t.co/BnScBhKmtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really convinced now that #alcohol lowers your vibration overall 🙌🏽 just not worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amelia_Rowe_ #A SF/fantasy mashup about a terminally ill magic wielder on a revenge streak who must decide to forgive in order to live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[VOTE today for our own Emily Babson in the West Michigan Woman Brilliance "Peoples Choice" awards. Proud of our Mar… https://t.co/kpnSgbCgJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously I cried some more and then thought about it and I just ugh I don’t know what I did right to deserve him b… https://t.co/EhIfiZImCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next week can we just arrest them all as they come into our country...NO LAND LIST... https://t.co/ocHCV1aAt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Weinsteinlaw Why is a tax exempt entity giving money to @SenCoryGardner  and @RepKenBuck? If they are going to be… https://t.co/p5PlzcCEvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the largest painting I’ve done, and it greets you as you come into my studio. If ever in the area stop on b… https://t.co/3YdwRteZ6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine Donation for @LALGBTCenter 💘😊🦄🌈 #LoveIsLove https://t.co/wfxMR4xRR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha Hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha hah… https://t.co/dRdDSnDa8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TouringTastebud @MadHattersNYC @MyVirtualVaca @MattsRoadTrip @hooter_pettus @thelinetrek @RoarLoudTravel… https://t.co/qHR3ESbcqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardcobbett Only if one of my attacks is to just yell “BOY!” and overwhelm him with doubt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @FLOTUS You need to go away and take the ORANGE CLOWN with you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterYoachim I just saw one too! It was crossing the street but was slow and then got hit by a car. And then could… https://t.co/15Refe2hTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro it’s not exhausting seeing the phrase  “the first black person to win....” in 2019? Black people BEEEEEEN doing… https://t.co/bO2OSawLET]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mmm the vegan ramen with new kale noodles at jinyabuzz was sooo good. Nom nom nom 🍜🍲 @ JINYA Ramen Bar https://t.co/jiyRhUImZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@landogonzo5 @JeIIyAngeI i think they meant more explaining things unnecessarily that we already understand ;)]]></document></documents></author>