<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Day 3 medical aesthetic training. Topic: dermal fillers 👩🏻‍⚕️💉 https://t.co/7ywxK0h5JK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the dems could use the National Emergency later for their pet projects why would they be suing him to not be abl… https://t.co/UF98kcy9iW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squintyt4e Or referring to the "Whole Foods music" spot on the wheel to local Co-ops. He is after all a NH boy. Wh… https://t.co/rTMzimOzjA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan You are just a radical!!! You will lose next re-election!!! You bring evil to AMERICA!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nessgirl1 @IndeCardio Of course they are getting romanced from planned parenthood, these evildoers are getting ric… https://t.co/Ema3qQmRL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay but i saw @daytoncarrie wear leopard print pants and now i need them and can’t find them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh Jesus Christ why can’t trump admit he f$cked up and just quit the lies already. I’m so freaking tired of all his… https://t.co/bcIEyrCkeP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump The Devil has his Soul ~ Respect for Evil? I don't think so~ 😂😂 MAGA 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefsFocus It’s none of my business what he does for fun. So, no, he shouldn’t have to sell his football team. We… https://t.co/rshRu6gFQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello i hope my man comes down in the summer bc it would make me so happy 😔😔😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RedWings-#Flyers tied 1-1 with 5:36 left in the 1st. Shots 9-8 Detroit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh I really wanna go see @TylerRichMusic  tonight but I still feel like crap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast at olibea_oldcity before University of Tennessee Tour #benedict #knoxville #breakfast @ OliBea https://t.co/mwtUnVAggQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Follow4Follow Thursday &amp; Friday on #twitter and #Instagram (@1025Marissa) - you down?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpcarbs I don’t want to be a bad neighbor, I just want to let them know that THEY are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got called a crystalline alien faerie lady tonight and i'm actually super ok w that ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you tell people to go jump in a lake, you don’t really expect them to do it. But this month 1800 people did wi… https://t.co/dbqqvSZdqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎂🎉HappyBirthday Jade🎉🎂 @ Seven Hills, Henderson https://t.co/POyowJhMce]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet my bestfriend to buy me dinner and my uncle to buy me lunch... WOW I AM A WINNER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HallOfFamer0 @zFemaleGawdd @Britt_SYCU @WNBA @realDonaldTrump Woman" smn good night old man it's been real https://t.co/BaqXvOoCNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys the ☄️☄️☄️ hot Cheetos are backkk and your girl needs to know where exactly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BazzyBaz @nix973 Bingo, Kyrie was scorching everything in sight in 3 out of the last 4 games and all you hear about is "the block"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video shows cops use stun gun on unarmed man mulitple times https://t.co/1L0a7QcQbn via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alive_she_cried @benissa_byrd @DearAuntCrabby trump’s a good age for it also!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I stole this from a retweet. No I don’t regret it. 🤘🏼🤧 💤  goodnight y’all https://t.co/FT7dQf36SD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juste un rappel concernant notre recours collectif d'un milliard contre le gouvernement du Québec. Le combat contin… https://t.co/VJYPHqF3Xj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get an instant home valuation  https://t.co/1iyBoe1TlH #JustListedInBoise #WhatsYourBoiseHomeWorth… https://t.co/c78gEaVPsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anna_elmer4 Hi me 🙋🏻‍♀️🙋🏻‍♀️🙋🏻‍♀️ I’m applying, please consider, serious offer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I have only one word....MORON! How the hell did you get in to BU and actually graduate?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always watched on TV, but now I go to my first Caps game in 13 days, I'm v happy😍😄 #RockTheRed #AllCaps🏒🔴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a healthy breakfast but of course I treated myself with a cupcake 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $10 Roblox Gift Card Offer    Win $10 Roblox Gift Card Offer By A Complete Simple Sign Up,    Sign Here:… https://t.co/jU8IOHNOrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ola Amores! Depois de muitas tentativas sem nenhum sucesso de recuperar minha conta @NanaGouvea , decidi abrir uma… https://t.co/qETYW5KBaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewYorkStateAG @972_834 There is only one I would like to see the pee pee tape]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cynthia_kirk03 @WhiteHouse I'd still shove it up his ass! There are plenty of those flags around to replace it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redbullracing I’ll be watching the #AusGP from the Sunborn Gibraltar where I’ll be on vacation.  #sipfromyourseat https://t.co/XVG0Dim7SX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The old reliable. - Drinking a Guinness Draught by @GuinnessIreland at @brasstapallen  — https://t.co/2wKm23Eqr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨ follow the wise words of @arianagrande and GET AFTER them things you want, m’kay? 💍💍💍💍💍💍💍 @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/obFwynu3Gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday early afternoon FREE DDD class 😊.  Deeva~Nation  Deeva~Spirit https://t.co/jmq1eZWEVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intimacy and sex.   Mutually inclusive or exclusive?  Is there even a difference??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me desperate, crybaby, stupid, dumb or whatever but I’m a human being with feelings &amp; I’m not afraid to show my emotions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a blast painting live at the Azure Valentine's Party last night 💕 Such a stunning building filled with wonder… https://t.co/jxUFpMOx4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[snicker and move on. Art Impressions Ai Hampton Art clear stamp sets available at Michael's. Beach Babes set. Handm… https://t.co/pnIzcesE5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetbrk @oMAGEEo @rascality @blairmacgregor @petabites @lahkotashadow @8_6lightyears @MichelesWeb Thank you Nick!… https://t.co/KCeU57JIsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amysmcd If you just tweet @ them “I’m reading your book and it’s awesome” all intrusion will be converted to always appreciated ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megynkelly Remember your insensitivity on marginalized people got you run off NBC https://t.co/NNyZ3ZeTSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guns don’t kill people - people kill people. Limiting the rights of law abiding citizens will not change the intent… https://t.co/5DAAtW2v8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate true love♥️For those of us that are single you are so loved #john316 @ Huntington Beach, California https://t.co/32aAX07JqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Profgampo So many thoughts and own theories about it. Twitter can't hang yo !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made it to my eyebrow lady w/ 2 mins to spare... it helps to call in advance lbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have loved her podcasts and now lucky to read her restaurant reviews in my hometown #woke #vietnameserepresent… https://t.co/kEtXcUV0qs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ex-coach compares Freddie Kitchens to Johnny Unitas #Browns https://t.co/NqdgnNWHal]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you’re taking the 11 year old to FL in a week and he’s all actually, i have like 2 t-shirts that fit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamchrisoddo @BuzzFeedNews It's stupid &amp; racist. Well, that's being redundant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful, cold day on the Ben Franklin Parkway #Philadelphia https://t.co/EytgRN4Zpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a lovely shower. I have never attended one like this. Wow #shower #party#theme#design #designer #party… https://t.co/CvCvI87oKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overheard in the office: Person 1 I CANT BELIEVE THIS WEATHER. Person 2 .....That’s February. #truth #itswinter Mov… https://t.co/9L2zH3L3FA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@8extremes @RobertKennedyJr I agree; let's get Glyphosate, GMOs &amp; fillers out of foods and vaccines!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlitteredGoth He doesn't feel bad about making fun of other people's looks. As a genuine fat person, I have no obj… https://t.co/iJR558NaOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[In particular, #crdh2019 participants and twitterstream followers may be interested in the NEH-Mellon Fellowships f… https://t.co/CYyR84MvPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can Robert Muller has such extreme power to be able to arrest Cohen from his office and arrested Roger Stone fr… https://t.co/zdHoISDI0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#uglydogs fun to watch Nic put booties on his dogs as he prepares to leave Kaltag. Live feed now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have so many more but I didn’t write them down and I’m not currently playing. Will add more when I remember. Obvi… https://t.co/mGsB8gqEr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshBloomACSH Heck, I don't get enough to handle the regular daily pain let alone after surgery. When they mess wi… https://t.co/NPWcxtATF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't think that I'll ever go back to Britain . Sad. Remember Tommy Robinson .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Overseas wasting time, sucking up to a mass murderer, shaming our country AGAIN, while true patrio… https://t.co/WctmrLTw3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much to everyone who has worked so hard on this critical issue! Special thanks to the bills' authors,… https://t.co/UtlwRfYT2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[How tf do you signal someone behind you when they have brights on? I’m ready to get out and throw hands at the next red light 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just absolutely love this color @SamsungMobileUS. 💙 #GalaxyS10 https://t.co/aqjD2EX4rF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it taking so long to cancel these feelings..... damn a bitch is ready to move on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For people who points Roe V Wade,  written in 1971 when Infant Viability at 22 weeks not likely. The best path is t… https://t.co/MqzCbQ5JMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinrkosar @CaseyBurgat I think there are men in very prominent positions who have the same insider reputation an… https://t.co/YsFtZYWvFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly, the #Flyers strategy of taking out Letang and Dumoulin has paid off for them tonight. This mess of a game… https://t.co/m2Ny4mDUhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[theres nothing I hate more than what I can’t have you are so gorgeous it makes me so mad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZG_State @RealJamesWoods Don’t be Single Issue Voter. That’s what they’re trying to do. Trigger people to vote abo… https://t.co/6o01xxRkYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caleb done scored over 1,000 career points in college he might be the most slept on hooper from the city]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music on, boards games out, tissues close by, and some much-needed mending of Graham's sweat pants. Thankfully, thi… https://t.co/SIKBRTlLMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bit of funniness for you. First child eats dirt parent calls doctor. Second child eats dirt parent cleans out mou… https://t.co/Rfq61HEbyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#youngatheart #whatasurprise #hesanawesomeguy #happyvalentinesday #itsnevertoolate #mademeblush 💝 5hannonjackson @… https://t.co/yoBVskzIsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[John McCain was a Trader and he was no Hero they had to pardon McCain because he talked too much in Vietnam so ever… https://t.co/4jX18vluyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[WeHo GayBook: Tuesday, March 5 – Mardi Gras Edition #ThisIsWeHo https://t.co/qOREwqTrpR https://t.co/H2J2aXYKWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powerball jackpot inches closer to half a billion with no winner in $414 million drawing - ABC News -  via @ABC https://t.co/dqfAPb9qUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google Arts et culture a retrouvé mon autoportrait c’est dingue ❤️ https://t.co/Dbzv9mwKKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimannjosouth @NBCWorldofDance Agree, dance does NOT have to show a linear narrative. In a minute 30, tricky to te… https://t.co/8wu98eqc7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[That being said, the music/cinematography/actors/dragons were all phenomenal. https://t.co/ls6zc5FFWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to take off from SFO and some rando on my plane just tried to airdrop this to me? Just...what? https://t.co/Vtt18vLWf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entenmann’s® Little Bites® is having a Birthday Bash Enter to win #LoveLittleBites #HBDLittleBites #giveaway https://t.co/Xkcr60Apum]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s crazy is I saw this 2 days ago and I was gonna tweet it smh i could’ve had my shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[The flamingo was a big hit on our first family tubing adventure! #theisenfamilyadventures #elisevictoria… https://t.co/4BM9R9kf2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are witnessing history unfolding right before our eyes. Proud to have a tiny part of it. ⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sergioo_boii9 @tolinho__ @SenorFredrick @ochoaa123 @josefuuentes_ @OmarGuzman_7 @HalaJosue_10 @19Nestorg Wow so im number 1?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dogs got out and I just woke up the entire neighborhood screaming for them bc the lack of street lights made it… https://t.co/Hqp4rqH6HH]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter the storyline, long after I forget who was on this years Duke team I’ll remember we swept them. That’s al… https://t.co/gqPMmLyGRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamieeleecurtis @___shavon___ Ask them what name they prefer, like if they go by a nickname or something, usually… https://t.co/0OiMSXDeaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must listen 👂 radio: @bethfertig’s deep dive into another dimension of border policy.  Families torn apart - facing… https://t.co/6anFrKtxYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Belletire16u kicks of the MAHA State Tournament against HoneyBaked 7pm @taylorsportsplex. Let’s go get em’ BT!!… https://t.co/qmvFR0CZqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading about memory and having a hard time memorizing the material is quite the paradox lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvanDuque Gracias sr presidente vamos muy bien Dios lo colme de muchas bendiciones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdenovan @LyleGreg @ChantalHbert @TorontoStar &amp; don't forget fluently bilingual]]></document><document><![CDATA[@albertarabbit @christoaivalis @janfromthebruce @trapdinawrpool I am a feminist. If we want more women to participa… https://t.co/jaNzk9K1Jo]]></document></documents></author>