<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m washed as hell... tried to stay up after watching OKC/Utah go to 2OT and knocked the hell out...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaMooreTV @JessicaMooreTV Good Evening Jessica Moore! How is everything and how is Your son Nico Doing and Ha… https://t.co/o5tSbdLdyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPaigeWWE loved it! Money well spent. #FightingWithMyFamily https://t.co/m47yAJpNCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[too many girls know what they deserve and are just scared to walk away from what they know]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Message from a School Counselor. Together we are making a difference! https://t.co/yPJILVgNJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@totalcurtis @BeesonOnBeer I don’t have to explain to you that anatomy has been part of art since the beginning of… https://t.co/23tfPkjR5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dejan_Kovacevic Spent an awful lot of time in their own end in the first period though.  Got better after that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im recognizing 2 set pieces that look like they’re straight out of X Men: The Last Stand, which begs the question..… https://t.co/9dtRFBzr0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterAlonso20 don't do it. Just ask @TypicalHB Richie Allen, just stick with original choice! 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is no one discussing @TheDemocrats use of the Cloward–Piven strategy in their quest for socialism? Come on @GOP ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump Time to make Trey Gowdy the head of the justice department and clean house!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tacitassassin13 @JMicCheck @TheOpenBarFP Not even Mel Gibson can save you this time #TrefoilRebellion https://t.co/fALghTbDmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theartofed I love it when my students realize their potential and dive into it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolsports I guess he got caught.... Oops.... NE patriots.... Spy gate...deflate gate.. Now we got...well you know..tug and rub..wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexRedmond20 @NuanceBro @VanJones68 @Project_Veritas @JamesOKeefeIII If you need a citation for that I don’t know… https://t.co/erRLavr9QS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ViceSocialT @RobinsonVzla @Sociabolivarian @psuvaristobulo Y las turbinas pa' cuando https://t.co/LdIrYI9VLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Corey Riffin from Original to New! 👨‍🎤👩‍🎤🎸🎹🥁🎤🎻🎺🎷🎼🎶🎵🎙️🎚️🎛️ #Grojband #Teletoon @TELETOON @cartoonnetwork… https://t.co/EzolnHlvrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonLammardo @realDonaldTrump Tell me Ron, do you get headaches when you think, does it hurt?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I hear any more comments bad mouthing Anthem or Crackdown...I am serving these ice cubes to you. 😵 https://t.co/A9kQfuwKF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don't deserve R-Truth as the United States Champion. https://t.co/XxpPjyrEOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Jules-Lee Bruce Lee! #taekwondogirl #brucelee @ Park Slope https://t.co/90G6jRk7ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary  Huh...cool https://t.co/2J3xSJfzsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every sixth grader should watch Pen15 in preparation for middle school. Hell, adults too 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[HATERS WILL SAY IT'S FAKE 🎙☘🔥 #EMINEM - NOT ALIKE @ 8 Mile Road https://t.co/N1gUdIrc3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact: this is actually used to wean the calf off from milk. It’s so it doesn’t harm the mother and so that it c… https://t.co/G6tbpZhKZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[8/ When Elliott Abrams rears his head and everyone needs reminding of who he is and what he was doing in the 1980s,… https://t.co/CHXEYDtLrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obxleatherman @MLBRandomStats That's exactly how that went down. I was goofing off, highlighting that my account w… https://t.co/SdpPr2wvzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree, I just ask the Moron: How can you sleep while you are such a moron!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @JacobEngels Christians kidnaped and enslaved millions of Africans for a few hundred years. No religi… https://t.co/7rkwuysem8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Metropolitan Museum of Art - @metmuseum in New York, NY https://t.co/JRVCjcY5w1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poeticmagique @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/HkZfPf65r8]]></document><document><![CDATA[SARAH SANDERS SHOULD BE CHARGED WITH PERJURY FOR LYING TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE, SHE WORKS FOR THE PEOPLE OF THE UNIT… https://t.co/4KP9BLPSKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AniMeGalarza Gracias Anita estaremos pendientes. Suerte en sus actividades. La lucha continua.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdhardeman @JobSnijders I could not agree more, but that does sound fixable to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s taken me 3 years but I think I’ve formed the perfect balanced Unsweetened Iced Tea .... im calling it #DassIT… https://t.co/wOd3tilFdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein God also wants adulterers stoned. Who wants to help me introduce @POTUS to the real old time religion… https://t.co/OE2Jqm5ICY]]></document><document><![CDATA[How bout the Blues.... I got them at 80-1 to win the cup, still a far stretch but it’s looking like a better bet now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIVE GOONEY DIE #SAINT  @__ShaMuLa “ the bottom “  #plotsnplans #bwoodknows #newwave #brooklyn #BWOOD x #DOUBLEGANG… https://t.co/skd9Lc0GwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKostos Deflated, yes, but need to regroup at some point with all that talent. Carolina deserves some credit. Th… https://t.co/wZfPAT1KVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it to Russian River Brewery for one of the last glasses of Piney the Younger. https://t.co/oySFTgtQzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@transbay @FitzTheReporter @burritojustice @sfmsr @ChrisArvinSF Can always watch Star Trek!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@50cent Bro been tryna give u one of these hott hooks .. I sing my ass off I’m from Philly known for dope ass hooks ... 🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieRheaume1 @Dandelorme @50F10ULE a ce que je peut voir l'exorcisme a pas fonctionné]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think she was wrong, but her saying “it’s bigger than Michael Jackson” was a preface for negating that this… https://t.co/LHWWWplvMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[BRB gonna go watch All the Star Wars movies tonight...   @ZAKtalksTECH you’ll really enjoy this  https://t.co/J3vPfQE0RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1CrazyNoonga @chrisnkelli When Trump supporters have finally had enough of the "resistance" Movement]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm a walking billboard! Not pictured, BASF polo and jacket. https://t.co/zzD4XHmtWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe if there was more diversity this wouldn't have gone so bad.  #bottomfeeders]]></document><document><![CDATA[Odyessy Inside Out: This 1982 classic  was emulative of Slaves classic Watching  You  aping the bass line albeit at… https://t.co/ncqk4xI0rk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emailed my professor twice and no response. Well there goes my chance at passing his test tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the fuck facebook, i dont smoke crack okay. Also why the fuck are they making cute crack pipes now? https://t.co/9kNWMxwpm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early evening Dorian jams inspired by @AndreMadMusic 🤙. Shout-out to my pals at joynerinstruments for the killer ne… https://t.co/HykI98WJib]]></document><document><![CDATA[World News:     Theresa May expected in Strasbourg in late bid for Brexit breakthrough;     Malaysia court frees wo… https://t.co/POUTjFcEDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are a district focused on our community - Dollars for College to academic distinctions to leveraging legislation… https://t.co/7Iybw5iULi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first time having Turkish 🇹🇷 food and I’m COMPLETELY sold. Thanks @BosTurkishKitch for the great experience!… https://t.co/K8OMozTPxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealTimBlack @MeghanMcCain @TulsiGabbard @TheView I'll take Veterans For Peace over civilians for war any day.  [D… https://t.co/l4dVcgfDdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[A girl at work today had no clue that wrestlers had their own entrance songs and I was so disappointed in her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes indeed! We watched! #faith #miracles #souls @RealRodParsley @davidcrank @NicoleCrank @AshtonParsley]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT WOULD KEEP A FIRE FLAME BURNING ****** BY CASTING YOUR VOTE FOR BERNIE https://t.co/XvTslR9YkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[United or Chelsea at home would be a lot more manageable than at a neutral site. Since this is the last chance for… https://t.co/qtiHHcx9H0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This month come check out the art at @restlessmoons! @flobro7 and my lovely girlfriend, @jjojetplane, have lots of… https://t.co/NkCV7Czd52]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosemaryOrchard @csdesign72 Thanks for helping my friend Clint find it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSportsGuru5 @the_moviebob True. Dorian was my favorite character in DA: I. He was my characters best friend. Good times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pau Gasol gifted Bryn Forbes with a few books, including one by Kobe Bryant that the third-year guard hasn't been a… https://t.co/7lJHwpmZtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TODAYshow @KatyTurNBC I'd like to see a national gun registry and harsher punishments for crimes committed while armed with a gun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ordered the new @adidasrunning ultra boost 19 and I can’t wait to go running already!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated It looks like the sine wave of the fury progressives feel about this miscreant sinning scoundrel in the Oval Office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Han muerto muchos venezolanos en los hospitales durante este apagón, pero también han habido suicidios.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see a lot of MLB teams using devices in their practices/BP/bullpens they can’t use in games.  Imo if you want to… https://t.co/CTtXCG48BB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt_lansford If u don't grind they lose a lot ! But pretty cheap gain .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IIllIIlllIllIl @dbongino Your point is valid. I view it as an incremental slide towards a Socialist end state. The… https://t.co/KEVT81D3vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PGATOUR @NateLashley @PuertoRicoOpen Couldn’t be more proud of you Nate go get them tomorrow love you young man an… https://t.co/aVqK15EyB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never watched him or paid much attention to him until yesterday so I guess I’ve always been onboard? #BoycottTuckerCarlson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because I like to Photoshop things. @audiselect @Audi #ElizabethHolmes #theranos #power @Jalopnik @Adobe… https://t.co/Pq16oPFQft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can one overdose on Melatonin?  Asking for a *friend* who wants to sleep all day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t see the big deal give him his opt out. You get him for 3. If you’re winning he stays. Simple. If you’re not w… https://t.co/eAP392yx4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[One man activism in Portland, OR! @ Portland, Oregon https://t.co/yo4z9RQhFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[SCORCHING👏🏻HOT👏🏻TAKE👏🏻 (The same goes for Flyers, Bruins, and Penguins in my estimation.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And when the dollar goes up and the income that they’re receiving is in local currency, you have an asset-liability mismatch.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_GreeneyedSoul_ @Rrichardsii8295 @rexkwondox “yOu dOnT pAy aTTeNTION” 😂😂😂🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/tZcCtrsvBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdanClay @Twitter @StormyDaniels Oh man I hear you....  Porn sells and with your followers no wonder they did that… https://t.co/e5aEYvHB2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielTurnerPTF ‘It’s uh, well uh, you know uh, duh’... https://t.co/MkvlcZm0ax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thewitchdocktor @FitchLiza @DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump When I was there in the 70’s I felt completely safe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rio Hondo Bobcats (6-4) finished the La Joya Tournament with a 2-2 record. The Cats will open up district play this… https://t.co/FQMh6tp1nD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbara66066169 Neither has she She’s battling overweight problem we are working on it Just watching birdies outside]]></document><document><![CDATA[Momma was my Woman of the Year and I give a shout out on #internationalwomensday #irenesantana #rockstar @ Los Ange… https://t.co/XUcpjGAt9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damonfick People can debate the case of Israel on its merits.  It’s supporters shouldn’t face accusations that the… https://t.co/cCCz7MMCWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[What did she think would happen? Was officer Dave showing up to give my mans dog 1-2 years with the option of a red… https://t.co/vzw4ePq4LT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrAlexCollins @shwinnypooh @TheAthletic I didn’t sign because the incompetence of Isola. I dont kmow If Becks ther… https://t.co/WdyKuhnCTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rileyworld_ Reedy can you bring me by my dick? I asked Teedy can she bring me by my dick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this picture..milakunis__ x.milakunis.x @ Massachusetts https://t.co/1IJDAHoqFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight's I'm covering the regional semi-final game between Lakeview and Utica. @ Dakota High School Boosters https://t.co/1RmgIQk4nW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta love the pointy finger octopus dance that white girls do when they rap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was literally at this game, and it’s just my luck to miss out on one of my all time favorite cowboys :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seabass #amazing #htown #houston #soigne #seafood #chefDon #chefslife #nofilter #masraffs @ Masraff's https://t.co/GDa2U9rStH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The pace machine, @bradsmith_94, with a few thoughts after practice today.  Have a listen.   PS. Not on camera, Bra… https://t.co/MYHHm4XPv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NumiGG Have you been checked out for being BiPolar. It's a possibility !! Hope you start feeling better. Keep up the good fight !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #BusinessMgmt job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Senior Project M… https://t.co/TdgCBEEGgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m Obsessed With &lt;em&gt;Anthem&lt;/em&gt;’s Mech-Entering Sequence https://t.co/8203b9UvFA via @kotaku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck he wrong for?! My kids gonna know guns ain't toys, but better beleieve they gonna b able to empty a clip]]></document></documents></author>