<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[How did they pull this off? Seeing anything a bit ironic here? @mytrestle https://t.co/t8vsJmyNsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TH3R34LTRUTH @fellspeaks @basedinfidel8 @AlexWY18 @JayCory7 @Chriskl70208387 @SmackYeti @Americanthatguy @johnw299… https://t.co/T4tuwyIkLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPDONeill @NYPDnews @NYPD66Pct When did people become so mean and disturbed? 😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only does @TheRealDeadKids put on a freaking awesome show, but they’re also super nice! Thanks for a fun night 🖤 https://t.co/YcIcLlvduH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JammiRacca1 @MadiBall17 idk if I’m mentally prepared for how drunk everyone will be😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlotte NC Thu Feb 28th AM Forecast: TODAY Chance Of Showers Hi 61 TONIGHT Showers Lo 49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbrewster55 @garyaltaperalta @USouthFlorida @floridacollege We have a lot of energy at most of our home games I think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to thank all who came to my stream. @WengerJeffrey @spicercrowd9 @TheWraithofShadow @RobertDCollins8… https://t.co/UoEHccfOCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social Media Design: 11 Principles to Improve Your Social Media Images [Infographic] https://t.co/cy1lkootn7 via socialmedia2day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sharongoodgreaf @petsit16 @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump Yes, he can but you CANNOT😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just want to wish my big brother @2chubby_collins a happy birthday i love yu bro enjoy your day and go get that win… https://t.co/p2F25NJwmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that i asked @ColbyBrock to choke me he’s gonna know me as the girl he choked at playlist 2019 aksks]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the clock strikes 5, we'll be making our way to The Alex Speakeasy at @GrahamHotel_DC for wine and charred oct… https://t.co/eO4kT0A6dn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is CRAP, The USA have money for wars for PROFIT in the Trillion, Tax Cuts for the Filthy Greedy Rich in the Tr… https://t.co/oO9JBNATeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica Oh my That's serious #Karma But she put out ugly shit You're gonna get it back 10x harder This is s… https://t.co/igrj80YAH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyMcCarthy @JennyMcCarthy the fact that my family (2 boys age 11 and 7 AND the hubs) have the first show ever w… https://t.co/AhpQ1fMAqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Subtronics Thank you so much for tonight. Y’all killed it and the energy can’t be matched, keep growing together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duh.  Bawahahaha.  They’ve hooked up, uh, had a relationship before.  Trump regularly donated to her campaign a few… https://t.co/gnqYA1IRQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas Day in #canKinder was so much fun @canSTEM we did the boot scootin’ boogie, sang Deep in the ❤️ of TX, caught… https://t.co/kk3WyCXtk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dragon_Age_Fans @EAHelp They aren’t being forthcoming at all and I don’t buy that they can’t tell someone has the… https://t.co/QukPwXVgkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am one fall away from having to count a 9.325 on bars while I have 4 scores over 9.7 sitting on my bench. 😑 #fantasygym]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me first semester freshman year: Yeah I’m on the dean’s list 🤪. It’s really no big deal. 🤪. Hard work pays off 🤪.… https://t.co/eHxNgJ57xZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar I think we would all wait for you queen good luck everyone https://t.co/u1V3aDUTRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoHoesShxdy U think ion have hands? Well you’re absolutely right.😂 but that’s what the strap for https://t.co/uS2dFw4qWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My long phone charger aka my bed charger has been broken for a week and let me tell you it’s been harrowing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeLoveLane @DanielGoddard @ChristelAdnana Happy Valentine's Day @ChristelAdnana @DanielGoddard #Lane fans! ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[the By The Numbers in this article about valentine’s day and doggos might be the best thing ever..  A sample:  “25… https://t.co/tRnvhv33zW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some photos of the #FrederickDouglassSculptureVolunteer get together at the #MagRochester to see #IsaacJulienne's 1… https://t.co/bIdcWI36QB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think they actually made the maddox perfect where it isn’t a do it all gun anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[found out I’m gonna be an aunt last night and im sobbing nonstop!!!! how many more blessings in 2019!? 😭👶🏽💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kpteach5 @readwithdavies @auntierez @Beth_Parmer @erinvarley @MsAPlusTeacher @mrs_cmt1489 @KReilley5… https://t.co/yR5IXexN6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bthouston11 I’ll go see it with you. I would see it again in a heartbeat. I thought it was beautiful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel Love his long pause, waiting for the applause that doesn't come.]]></document><document><![CDATA[French toast in sourdough bread with Italian sausage and orange segments... @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/dBYn5QHnca]]></document><document><![CDATA[its so weird thinking back on when you first met someone and that moment you had no idea they would have such a big impact on you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gave thee a king in mine anger, and took him away in my wrath. https://t.co/LkFmk2R70d]]></document><document><![CDATA[// T h E n E x T G e N e R a T i O n //  *  These SPARKS IN THE DARK!!  *  LOVED being with these precious students… https://t.co/6iuGgcVYPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lovely_lauren17 @COIN Hello still in the car because the line is long and it is cold]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one makes money as a politician. Most politicians did something else before going into politics. You know what I… https://t.co/4Vsn50Nzkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carole_awebb Goodnight, Carole! God bless you.❤️ What a beautiful picture!❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cashityyy See I feel like she did exactly the same thing though like he definitely took it too far but she came at… https://t.co/hWONCqDXYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Allah SWT said:  وَالسَّارِقُ وَالسَّارِقَةُ فَاقكَسَبَا نَكٰلًا مِّنَ اللَّهعَزِيزٌ حَكِيمٌ "[As for] the thief, t… https://t.co/smi4P2qEvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful start to Desmond’s pre-birthday adventure in Kansas City.  This 8 year old requested: accommodations… https://t.co/IdCIGJK1eU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are running the #JerusalemMarathon on behalf of ACN for Christians in Syria. Please consider giving!❤️ https://t.co/m5gBURQprq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goldengal301 For you,  how difficult will it be to accept these two wonder actors after the perfect casting of sea… https://t.co/Bg3BOTHSEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Regions Bank - @askregions in Pelham, AL https://t.co/OLYc6sHTfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faith on her birthday in Harrisburg, PA.............almost forgot about this...these kids remember all the words 🤔… https://t.co/n3bUguVNzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walkin into a week off school like🤩 What do y’all want to see first: a End of Winter/Early Spring Haul orrrr 2019 T… https://t.co/3MQkIPiTsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 They are also the people who contributed to Roy Moore's GoFundMe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're there only local daughter and your dad has a minor medical emergency and your day goes to shit.  And yo… https://t.co/tlwEwUzCsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cut off the most toxic person in life and my life went from 0-100, you either fuck with me or not cause I don’t got the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weirdotoon @quartz__Angel @missmulatto247 She’s 20. She turned 20 in December.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt CUPCAKE rescued by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from the Mini #DogMeat #Farm #SouthKorea  CUPCAKE is fostered in Vancouve… https://t.co/WjTmCMUyx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know a tsunami is impossible in Lake Erie but living next to the lake with this wind has me in my scares]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL, HA, LOL, HA, LOL, HA, LOL, HA, LOL, HA, LOL, HA, LOL, HA, LOL, HA!  ALL THE WAY TO THE POTTY!!!            💙😄💙… https://t.co/jh8jeqG2ZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoungCorey I thought it was my neighbors next door being hella loud! But then i felt my bed jolt too so i was like 😳🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a hard way of showing my emotions sometimes but I love Kyle with every ounce of my body.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You might got other things to worry about, if it's true.  Deblasio running for President when ther… https://t.co/RQrOGuvgQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I am sharing facts about the SEA Turtle! My little brother also tried to join in on the fun with his super fa… https://t.co/NwrQ23BtEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the infamous barbie queen (@NICKIMINAJ ) said on her radio show “you mad at a woman for what a man is doing”… https://t.co/6tMkwNwYkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#80YearsOfBatmanTaughtMe that every villain also has a story... https://t.co/pLWJnySCqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenZelt @brianros1 @MikeSielski I love Target brand anything. I refuse to buy non Up and Up paper towels, toile… https://t.co/gYddWi7Acp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Disney @coronadosprings worst visit ever. Had 5 bad cust. service exp. (2 at front desk!) it’s plummeted since las… https://t.co/xeL21IVg34]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimmyifuplease @fenrir_71 @nypost Why we don't need a wall that would be useless we need border guards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebriankrause @H_Combs @drewfuller  @WizardWorld such a fun night! Thank you all! https://t.co/6D7Um8rxKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day, everyone. #valentinesday #happyvalentinesday #Valentine #love #monthoflove #animals #mammals… https://t.co/VFi9AyNhSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaShanneStokes This should be on the front page of every newspaper and the top store on every news program!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katy_fit So sorry for your loss and thank you to your Granddather and God Bless him]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/OkbmR0QVwi Taking the plunge for Special Olympics again this year with my Maine East crew!! Help suppo… https://t.co/YaPBLRZXye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @MSNBC They are always lying. God bless you President Trump! Have a wonderful Friday!.]]></document><document><![CDATA[CBD Facial Mask... Take advantage of the Anti-inflammatory Benefits of My NEW CBD INFUSED Facial Masks. CBD is Exce… https://t.co/Em7uf1PwtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This tweet was meant to be sent from @48hrstravel acct but is applicable to ur feed so I’ll leave it be]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ravenmackenzie Please remind me to do this in a few weeks because I will forget haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Savor the flavor! Salt and pepper shakers are kitchen essentials. My mini salt and pepper shakers are perfect for a… https://t.co/4sbRKdlEwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[TFW when it's too early to get up but too impossible to go back to sleep https://t.co/ltGUPvV4Oh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepTedDeutch Thank you for your powerful words! I am sadly discovering that there are few people willing to stand… https://t.co/T0BYQKtmKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, the name suggests it, but this is really a star-packed group of @AACPSAthletics athletes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaMijos @SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump Can't wait to hear Barrys reply to this!  He's just miss informed ab… https://t.co/LLzXQBT6Ra]]></document><document><![CDATA[pro tip - make a small circle on the dance floor to allow for some stretching]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m going to do all my hw tonight so I can watch “the punisher” all day tomorrow 😎 #luvdayzoff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surefire way to make Valentine’s Day great? Spend it by the ocean. https://t.co/l3ayFshQBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a fun trip to see water with @katiebug41 #az #sedona #nationalforests #coconinonationalforest #creeks #local… https://t.co/S0IbXhVZPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me skipping through Walmart because Gudbranson is gone https://t.co/yiPIzgBevt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ricky “wanna see a nasty toe” Me “no I don’t” Ricky *proceeds to put his phone in my face to show me the toe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewRelease Evermore: A Salvation Series Novella by Corinne Michaels Amazon US https://t.co/lzod2tohMO Amazon UK https://t.co/zo7XQQs2PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @AOC OMG, I wish I could debate this @AOC NOVICE, ahe woukd never consent though, she’s a coward.  S… https://t.co/KDx2jJTxME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdeleBonaccolta @SamHeughan @StevenLippman @Sheugs @GHJNancy @barbaramills1 @ClanHeughan @sarahjaswim He went jogg… https://t.co/HxI6subKrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stretch Therapy Thursday!! Do you sit a lot at work? Do you run? Cycle? Walk? Do you experience low back pain? If y… https://t.co/zRnShbWQuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fahrenthold @realDonaldTrump Psst, spread the word, that Trump fella is bad for business. Except, you know, the bu… https://t.co/s6maYmCKNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg I’ve been simultaneously #sucker and #boysintheband obsessed this weekend. It has equated to little… https://t.co/16p5aPvNzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plazathemes @plazathemes hi, I bought something from pozite a couple of days ago, I’m waiting on shipment confirm.… https://t.co/5Y3DT07ijG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birdcage opens tonight at 10pm #BirdcageSM https://t.co/hHI63T42JY https://t.co/HEiyeJinZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey everybody who sent me a link last night we are about to go live on my Instagram Live in a few minutes and play… https://t.co/8qigfuNS0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dandersod @cheesemonkeysf @druinok @averypickford @ablinstein @martinsean @hpicciotto Yeah man this really shows a… https://t.co/14CMgCD2UE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It's time to act on this travesty and release #RealityWinner https://t.co/XVm6WKKqEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[A whole ass pineapple and Malibu just got dumped all over me how annoying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodieorcutt Fun fact: it was our first Valentine's way back in 2014. I took amtrack and the weather was so bad I was nearly 8 hours late.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've made a lot of mistakes in my life, but if every single one had to happen to make sure I was right here, right… https://t.co/4NRKpkPBZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregTtheFratBoy Hey T! Did u know that Chris Sullivan from This is Us is the voice of the geico camel! Thought I’d… https://t.co/C5atvPZutc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuJu_S_Smith @StromfieldAdvs Haha! I have been able to effectively carry on now for 10+ years, even for a 2 week trip 😮😮]]></document></documents></author>