<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Spend responsibly and save religiously. Encourage teachers to save for retirement too. Low savings is a national cr… https://t.co/LbUNGkXJ2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @realDonaldTrump @TheJusticeDept I disagree! It wasn't the Russians that played the FBI, It was the D… https://t.co/2jUyXaOcaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[New England Patriots owner charged for soliciting sex at a massage parlor  https://t.co/nb25Cau50N NE PAT OWNER BUYING SEX?]]></document><document><![CDATA[20-12 Chandler Prep leads Phoenix Christian at the half led by 6-7 Soph Darian Masi w 4 pts 9 rebs. @ArizonaVarsity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talked about behind my back as if I wasn't worthy Lord knows that I ain't perfect but I sure deserve it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Bastrop, TX #WebDesign job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: Web and Multimedia S… https://t.co/dEGnk8MdN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattowanHP If he did The Green Deal I wouldn't oppose!  There is nothing  to approve or oppose.  Its meaningless d… https://t.co/4HwUkfvGjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikemayerMMO @BigAppleNYM I appreciate his effort but that drop yesterday was alarming....just hope it was nerves… https://t.co/COnrwRgMUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've shared ideas about using #maps in planning that leads to filling high #poverty areas with needed youth #tutor… https://t.co/jLFcUQNaAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went Thursday morning to deadlift. Got through all of my warmups and felt like death so I shut it down and rested.… https://t.co/rnyx4KXcBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well worth watching!  The Identity two parter shows the power of #TheOrville]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barry Bonds looks like a saint in his time in Pgh compared to this clown Antonio Brown]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I sabotage myself from going after what I want because I’m scared that It won’t help me feel better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson Trying to use an emergency declaration to bypass Congress because you think your ti… https://t.co/Jx9MsvKfgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drillingninja @HoustonDynamo @BBVACompassStdm Employees looking at fully stocked shelves. https://t.co/WNmCDnDLkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeDeVitoComedy is to cool for TV @FoxNews @GregGutfeldShow https://t.co/nvaYiYmXaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone did a "tbt" on one of the baddest DJ's in #Hamptonroads.  The late "Daddy" Jack Holmes. #WRAP AM 1270. His… https://t.co/qWdFO5ZoTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next COSPAIN comic is up! Visit https://t.co/ekWh0wrL4m for more!   #comic # #webcomic #humor #comedy #cosplay… https://t.co/KR4s837Tgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMossEsq Roger Stone Used "Corruption Central" Crosshairs Logo From Pro-Russian Site Which Also Threatened Hill… https://t.co/JCCuhAZlZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy Saturday  we SALUTE  #AlfredHitchCock master of #SCIFI  .@sagaftra  .@Variety  .@Talk2Sheryl .… https://t.co/b1Wz50sWND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dejaur15 I’ve been listening to Dave East, Cole, JID, Mark Battles, Future new album, and Kendrick a lot lately]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Yes, government tax incentives are bad. Should we stop incentivizing and subsidizing most stuff? Oil, ethanol,… https://t.co/Hkx67XFvPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericgeller @ChuckWendig @rez512 King Arthur congratulates me for destroying Dr. Robotnik's evil army of Robot Soci… https://t.co/YlImtrrEkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iheart30stm Good to hear...I've been working 24 hr days the last 3 days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracksuperfan @usatf You need to find @jmcin9 down there. A couple of Falcons running the same event in the Florida! Nice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXTREMELY torn between which @theofficenbc episode is the best: Cafe Disco or Dinner Party??!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady said they’ve already replaced the battery 3x, it’s time to let it go...NO BITCH! Bring it back to life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Blackhawks fourth line gets in on the fun with Chris Kunitz scoring his third of the season to give Chicago a 4-1… https://t.co/d8p7id7Mx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlrd Just wondering when the ordinary citizen going to thumb their nose at obeying the law en masse - seems like t… https://t.co/62N3vOMwWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJ_434 @PhoenixJustice @RingFalcon @smarktodeath @OldSkewlPantz @JustJeremyHeyYo @ImmortalOne76 @RudeTexasKitty… https://t.co/tJbDu7pKOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[💪🏼💪🏽💪 @RWDSU @MaketheRoadNY @caaav @JFREJNYC @nychange @AQE_NY @CUNYRising &amp; many many more ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamoneHardy No my argument is I watched the games I can tell when one player is better Stafford has had the longer… https://t.co/sdbqCBlXTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phunky____ Research Directory: [ https://t.co/oBlviLa18k ] --- open to find the truth.  SiteAdvisor Cleared Safe To Browse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Turki_AlOwerde @CNN @TABHQ_EN Agree!. What really happened to America in the years before Trump?  👎We sunk in ever… https://t.co/lNZJ2bop9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜African American History💜  Eddie G. Robinson Sr. (Feb. 13, 1919-Apr. 3, 2007) was an  American football coach. For… https://t.co/pcuMoJiHLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Communities #Partnerships #Employers #Sponsors #K12 #TechnicalTrainers #Apprentices #Journepersons  @VICA_BC… https://t.co/xjzyGY6kZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNHMHOCKEY 's Brett Pesce scored a goal &amp; Trevor van Riemsdyk added an assist for Carolina #HockeyEast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddyrose_xo Do you take the odds you live more than 7 years or are you betting she does something really stupid a… https://t.co/SmR7uH71A1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TxRadioGeek @KI7UNJ @KE4ALabama @ad0dx @w5pfg @dtabor @K7TABravo @WD9EWK @KM4Ruth @kc5qih @KI5BEX @WY7AA… https://t.co/87JhMkB9bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[We held our first County Affairs meeting of the 86th Legislative Session yesterday to hear from a panel of experts… https://t.co/wtokMQmPkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments @Forbes zuck, like him or hate him. actually - made himself. from nothing. kylie was born into a ba… https://t.co/A7bEajXAP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WISH_TV @randyollis comes to Shelby County to discuss weather at the SWCD Annual Meeting.  Thank you Randy! https://t.co/anVEUMhkFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Edward, if there is clear evidence why haven’t the Dems started impeachment hearings?  Think!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannaeAlonso @anetamariaa I made the background :) Happy bdayy Aneta ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you seen it in person? Looks overrated on TV but is stunning in person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time stopped and I just walked around for a few years unable to pick up anything of value.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m running out of creative ways to say “it’s raining” https://t.co/kWf2tjnIXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If people ask you for feedback you’re going to feel obligated to give it to them.  Take a beat.  If your answer boi… https://t.co/ugEBF6OMQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronfitt Always great chatting with you! Hoping for a warmer day tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldenKnight89 @GGFracing @3coltshandicap @annacotsteel @mikebench1991 @sportsandhorse Good luck! We both made it through the first leg!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanted to take a moment to remember the great Harambe meme of 2016. RIP Harambe, your death was not in vein. https://t.co/S7GHDUNCrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA on having LaMarcus Jr. share the weekend with him: “That was awesome. That was the highlight of the weekend for… https://t.co/Q46mwjF2M6]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Player attacked by fan during grudge match scores the winning goal”  https://t.co/ZdVqsle71y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanchris I wouldn't know what to do with them.  Also, I suspect they'd attract mold in the winter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jayton was 6 of 19 in the first half; Slidell was 10 of 25.  SHS won the glass 18-13......Jayton with seven turnove… https://t.co/iQYE0uPYs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy growth going on over here right now . Can't even see TJ anymore .]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OPSEU -#Hidaya Dancers now Performing Afro-Caribbean Dance! They are from Windsor Detroit! @OPSEU @SEFPO… https://t.co/NkeLOYIwqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deppelman @_pastelpixie_ My sub feed was so scary until I looked into it just now lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of @HobanGirlsHoops!!! Amazing accomplishment! Let’s keep our eyes on the prize #ChampionshipMindset]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickcollinsma @realroborthman @lilybeth1234 @jonchesto You probably know that Boston’s cap on liquor licenses was… https://t.co/Shgq081gVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bchanthavisouk @ahall1962 @USNavyMomPA Technically, SM make minimum wage. Take into account getting up earlier for… https://t.co/rehlrV0GHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo i am HERE for this Dark Phoenix movie. ABSOLUTELY. Phoenix has always been one of my favorite X-Men stories. I h… https://t.co/I3yJQUcpdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evanfernandez8 Yeah that’s my bad, I didn’t realize that  he was still out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #Collette the movie with kiera Knightly. I never knew that Parisians in the 1890's had the exact same acce… https://t.co/OOs2C3gduQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cormorants No. 1, Sonoma Coast, 2015. #art #fineart #fineartphotography #blackandwhite #blackandwhitephotography… https://t.co/VMBQD0HSW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBADialogue @BenStinar Stockton only averaged 5.5 assists his rookie season. Only point @BenStinar is tying to make .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill Stick to Blackish or The Game. That’s more your speed, race-baiter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Terry, Pat and George (@ Green Onion in San Pedro, CA) https://t.co/rYq5aKzbXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fellow #JNPRAmbassador @chsjuniper pens an article about implementing EVPN-VXLAN on @JuniperNetworks (v)QFX Series… https://t.co/tKqGTGLzLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @theresa_may @atiku @USEmbassyAbuja @10DowningStreet @UN @UN_HRC @HRC @USArmy @BritishArmy… https://t.co/h2r9JMVoqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReinaldoTorral2 Tienes razón hubo una epoca donde esa tienda de zapatos estaba al menos en cada pueblo de la isla.… https://t.co/Q6FQby3jiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Jr, Kushner and Manafort Met with and agreed to accept information of value from a foreign national: t… https://t.co/Ec6pOIe0ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[#arborframe #arbortech #arbortechtools @ArbortechTools @arborframe @ Meadowlands Exposition Center https://t.co/vnRopdMQb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AFish0 Bittersweet. Seriously, some of the best stays in the playoffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Given all their graft I kind of think Hamburglar is a Republican h/f @MollyJongFast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Released 2 new songs from upcoming album today! ‘Starlight’ and ‘Imagining Raindrops.’ Check them out here: https://t.co/etMAeLnZM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[invierte! Little Venezuelan Mondongo for the cold weather! Yum! https://t.co/nK9WWmRDD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RHS76 I agree completely.  And hats off to those who pour themselves into their education and make it - in any edu… https://t.co/4yetu2JF98]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Senior Day for @IlliniWBB, #Illini trail Penn State 39-32 at the half.   Both of Illinois’ active seniors, Alex… https://t.co/JR3LbSc8zC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwing a tantrum and declaring my intense hatred for the Reese’s Peanut Butter Cups my mom got me when she got gr… https://t.co/3TWenEO8yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided to teach myself Ruby on Rails for a side project and I have to say I'm really impressed by how easy it was to deploy to @heroku]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had two children by your age so you are not so special. Get of your high horse and keep your head and Mouth down… https://t.co/1Bm506f99H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't listen to just any Bluegrass Music. I love the good "driving fast through the mountains" type stuff. No lyr… https://t.co/lEfZ8ViO3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicobsessed Right. But PA is far and away the most important stats next year,]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't heal your wounds, you're going to bleed on people who didn't cut you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austin_delillo Get a goat skull with a bullet hole one the forehead. Like a Demon Hunter album cover]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessica_salfia @washingtonpost It was a great article! Thanks Jessica!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey everyone! I’m going to be playing Chip Tolentino (B Cast) at Showtime Performing Arts! More details will be out… https://t.co/3dKuch5ExG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinkyMinky43 @DeniseLMarineVa @MadeIn_TheBronx @StateDept @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo Ok then! I can see you have good negotiating skills.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump What? There is a crisis in the government. #RussianAssets are lurking in the hall… https://t.co/kClp9w4Nt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lying as usual 🤨🖕🏾  New York Magazine: #Trump Denies Calling Tim Cook ‘Tim Apple.’ It Happened on TV..… https://t.co/6pOrFlk40I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor VGK... HAPPY DURNK THOUGH! These guys are truly world class on and off the ice! Thanks @bellsy78 for making my… https://t.co/Jk1rbUgRCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brash_1 Please don’t EVER say “good grief” again without a Charlie Brown gif. Thank you. https://t.co/4iTZ5iN3Pq]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone is wondering where I am, I’m in bed crying to the new @AvrilLavigne  record for the next forever.… https://t.co/OsOa3Xe0B0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebBurdett18 Philly almost made the playoffs this season, and they added Harper/Realmuto to think they won’t be contenders is stupid lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobProvince Dude is stalking my airport in hopes get @AOC horseface attention. Pathetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rocktape is my kind of art! #rocktape #kinesiotape #chiropractic #movement @ Dynamic Family Chiropractic https://t.co/M4k3E7oPQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My trailer is unloaded so grabbing my empty (@ Target Distribution Center in Stuarts Draft, VA) https://t.co/TPIvxjPCnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reshare ♻️ from @OurLifestylePod 🔥 Stoked for the new @OurLifestylePod booth! Our homie Dan Sawyer hooked us up! Ap… https://t.co/KmjR1ONqQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Use my link to get $5 to invest on @Stash! They even have learning guides on investing if you don’t know where to s… https://t.co/PSpj8gkcXT]]></document></documents></author>