<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Wondering around #katsucon it would be real hard to miss @Cowbuttcrunchie blowing it out of the water again. This t… https://t.co/Yvd8U3Z2so]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scribsnotes @MusicCityMensch @MeredthSalenger @Twitter Np. Basically those of us who leave it on are the polite on… https://t.co/jl0zIi59Px]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanDreyerNBC thanks for asking a great question “what is the goal of the Cohen hearing”? No one had an answer I… https://t.co/VgvahqStVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't get me talking about guitars if you don't know about guitars because I'll lose you in about .5 seconds flat a… https://t.co/2CnFi5vTCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is excellent. Thank you to @SherylCole1 for honoring this American hero. #ATX #txlege #Austin]]></document><document><![CDATA[This last semester really got me questioning if these 4 years here are worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vols would have won by 30 today if it wasn’t for the refs! #Revenge #GBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation Words... Think About It 🤔🙏🏿🇺🇸🇮🇱🙏🏿 @ Tampa https://t.co/aKs37x73Wd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mads_calvink16 I’m so sorry. I feel like this is a problem everywhere but it’s especially a problem in Utah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You need to take your evening medications on schedule. Please check with medical staff on duty and… https://t.co/pRoImIieTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So - again, your tone changes when you’re faced down by another leader. You issue this statement a… https://t.co/fEXipc8k3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC “Conference call”. I’m sure the people on the other side were thrilled]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoniqueRosales @mskristinawong @FLOTUS @Nicklaus4Kids @jacknicklaus Fraud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 Those days are over.  It’s not okay to try to minimize this adult woman in this way.  Your days are over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This 💩is know as a #TrumpsUltimareDefender. Shouldn’t a member of Congress be know as a #DefenderOfTheConstitution?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antena3int  desde México  viendo #VenezuelaAidLive https://t.co/DT9i4nMESk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Thank You (Live) by @chriscornell on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/CHQKLRwY6z https://t.co/zhXVmNW0jF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Installed. Another happy customer. https://t.co/oxvHbAcbxs #murphybeds #wallbeds @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/jFBpseRPNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning World I didn’t check but it might be National Smile a Bunch Day. Let’s go ahead and smile today just in case. 😁😃😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calphonso Such a complex issue. Many will point to the removal of sick day banking but that wasn’t prevalent acros… https://t.co/NAH3rSyRSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/MpIZSzNR6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Super70sSports Why are we also not discussing Slimfast Marie Osmond. She’s dropping dimes now all day. 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Joseph Miller 🎖🇺🇲 #airforcepilot #usairforce #tattoo #inked #inkedgirls #jamaicatatts #realismtattoo… https://t.co/nWuu4Y2tc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn, @TomScibelli @RiggsBarstool I won a car in the Chicago River Duck Derby but I had to pay $13,000 in taxes bef… https://t.co/NEPrZ43A9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[do it for the culture, pat.rice_ ♻️ | #BHM @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/oEQwm07iuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley By not calling out #KimJongUn directly for the murder of #OttoWarmbier you have already forgotten him a… https://t.co/OPBkGbL1x7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kentucky has not attempted a free throw and leads by 13. Shooting 67% to Auburn's 35% and eight made 3-pointers to… https://t.co/R1WeDIXFZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sam_vinograd @BrettaApplebaum @realDonaldTrump “‘Conservatives’ Have Zero Standards” by William B. Turner https://t.co/ELqXWCyGWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not everyone is meant to remain in your life. You will not always retain every person who walks into your life. The… https://t.co/NaibXgiT7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love me some @JohnBarchard voice overs for gentleman’s clubs. Sadly I gave up strippers for #HarperLent  Here’s hop… https://t.co/ZBXYtYZkUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngieMentink Please make sure to include Clint Richardson -1975 O’Dea on the list of players that did not win a ch… https://t.co/Hk8lP7cF66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayoffKap @jbazoo @_2human @urkle9 @ChefBetter So much talent. I can’t believe Stevens is unscathed! Part of coaching is culture]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two Birds on Bat Cardinals Opening Day Ticket Giveaway! Follow us on all of our Social Media pages to enter and win… https://t.co/iKvlJDTYs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franciscopont No te olvides de los chinos y lo rusia. No creas que apoyan a Maduro porque les cae bien.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikenedie @fair_more @Duke1CA @paulmpet1 @AprilLigeia @CingetoOfBelgae @MariahShe @zypisfy @PCribbett @zapher134… https://t.co/6oiZpB6JJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewParent1 This is coming from a person from northeastern, which has been called northwestern for decades by p… https://t.co/3XiQgpCDhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will C. Wood hosts meeting to discuss future of former soccer coach Jorge Ruiz-Chavez https://t.co/sloatMNvqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinhanson No, the second-order effect will be disengagement from platforms/media outlets known to have a lot of bot-generated text.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely nothing worse than the person that tries to cut everyone getting off a plane. Be miserable like the rest… https://t.co/lBBbFibez3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever Continue To Love, Heal and Educate the Children. The Future Shines on Them. ~ ❤Michael… https://t.co/k2TFDNznQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @BikeNewton tomorrow &amp; help transform Washington St. into a livable street. https://t.co/5DRuH6Kzun]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haitian police arrest five Americans who claimed they were on a ‘government mission’ https://t.co/Qggf5MsRYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job Coach Chamblin, his staff &amp; these young men!!! #DemonDynasty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaMedcalf @EricBrotherton_ @T_Travis34 I expressed my gratitude 3 years ago, when we were the 1st female athle… https://t.co/x6dDc7Bhhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to be that bitch, but I can’t do social media because  people have war in their countries, famine, and other fu… https://t.co/dGQUajWSGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolyn__ann @SHO_Shameless I 2 love Shameless♥️but I feel its starting 2 get VERY depressing-Lastnights ending ma… https://t.co/NQ0lQ5Kgwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZehDuck These idiots hell Biden could win the election but nope theses idiots will pick some person President Trump will dunk all over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PunisherCoachOL Lack of parents, single parents, overindulging parents are all a problem.  I'm not disparaging sin… https://t.co/z3T962sOAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brendan_Tobin In a 7 Games series the Heat would Gentlemen Sweep the Warriors. On the other had in a 7 game series… https://t.co/YJngBJkp8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DZRishmawy Well his first big hit was a song about Allen Iverson so there's that...]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re like me and have never had sexual frustration, you better simulate sum #cs183afc. #ch7 https://t.co/Ca8asoNvmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aydens_mom @firstsgtang @SteveBenjaminSC I agree... then they should take responsibility for their “mistakes”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldenKnights tie it up with a goal from Reilly Smith 1-1 now. #VegasBorn #KSHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReduxitSpem Was bound to be with all the investment money fleeing Canada Anybody surprised except for the fake concern by the PTB!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BirchYoung @thehill Pesky Russians how dare they lmao everything is their fault. https://t.co/OnlnQvdCQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#valentine #fam #happyvalentinesday #lafamilia #familyfirst #familygoals #yachtlife #family #fun #yachtclub… https://t.co/1pjCz4HYkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Naw that man was an All-Pro cornerback. Put respect on that man's name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarlandWilliams @HamillHimself Thanks for the invite! I must have skimmed it👍😂😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VietBreadAndTea is Open! https://t.co/MaLjo3l8GS #Knoxville #DowntownKnoxville]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why I'm single but y'all not biting fuck it I'mma keep 💰💰💰💰💰💰💰💰💰💰💰💵💸🤑🤑🤑🤑🤑🏃🏃🏃🏃🏃🏃🏃still with u or without]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think if you file a false police report your punishment should be equal to all of the people you've accused maxim… https://t.co/6w2gIedufF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing people's Instagram stories/posts and realizing I dont really care what anyone's up to 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougWead Good Morning! Nice seeing you on @foxandfriends w/ @kilmeade @ainsleyearhardt and @SteveDoocy Great job o… https://t.co/ZvHtGJniwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@everybodyzzmama @saharris1210 ‘INDIVIDUAL 1’ is really sexy name for a building.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Why don't you talk to some of your own party they screw the illegal people buy making them work for low wages… https://t.co/gMfr44xoXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MenominiWanlip @JeffreyGuterman I can relate because we have a similar situation with the Premier of Ontario.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signs of spring begin to take root throughout Fairmount Park via @JustinUdo https://t.co/yaIMl1O8It]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it is any STEELERS FANS who is tired of hearing that the STEELERS can only get a 2nd or 3rd rounder because of t… https://t.co/OdJYhqdofH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bon voyage to @ConsulMexFresno David Preciado (right) who is finishing his posting as Consul of Mexico in Fresno. H… https://t.co/ks92ND8PHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw someone post a Valentine’s Day gift on social media and it literally looks like they got a peeled avocado as… https://t.co/dWMP4oABDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rossbigballer At least an e-cig has more of a function than a rock? That's about the only defense I can think of here haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[From My Book Heavenly Bodies and Human Souls “ The right of the sacred bees from the power of the fallen angel Luci… https://t.co/3o8cTsFfbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT SEEMS THAT THE REPUBLICANS HAVE LOST THEIR CONTROL OVER ANYTHING AND INSTEAD OF BEING PATRIOTIC AND DEVOTED TO T… https://t.co/QPKXkmHG7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lb7090169 @johncanzanobft We got amnesia now like okc didn't just get spanked by utah in 6 and could of easily bee… https://t.co/78hVymGpuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LexxDX @Athletics Lexx! My man thank you for the kind words! You already know baseball in her genes lol thank you !!! 🙂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeCHunter1 @TomiLahren lol its that dam twitter algorithm it seeks bots and flags accounts. you are also shado… https://t.co/d42taEn374]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your youngest son has a school assignment to write to "a friend" and decides to write to you.… https://t.co/uettDHXlOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnSmistWECT @OwenHassellSN is already recruiting me to take photos next week. https://t.co/Au319JbqXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Schatz @techemout Emma has wonderful insight and penned an overwhelmingly positive approach. An addendum at th… https://t.co/uu1nxlSKGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith @Lakers @JHarden13 Now u have to eat your words, the Lakers did come back and win so sometimes just shut up Mr. Smith!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zNPhVA5CidfQPo7 @smartdoll Poor Chitose looks worried with all the new girls arriving. ^_^ Congrats on your new ladies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nfldraftscout @TwoDEEPBrewing Wait a minute, I have to sign up? Come on, I know I got backstage passes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swole____patrol Good morning sunshine  My goal is not get fired I think that happened to me once. But when you get… https://t.co/1x0ZjqEpqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeilDiamond My condolences to you and you family. May her memory be for a blessing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We @CentralSquareSD are operating on a 2 hour delay. Our crews and highway/towns crews have a significant amount of… https://t.co/NVPzZFUe0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish I could apologize to all the girls that I never give a real chance to... Not even trying to sound like that either. It’s me, not you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealTebow3 @StoolGreenie Says the guy who has "Nick Foles ended the Patriots dynasty" in his bio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicki's a global superstar, 10y in the game, this is her 4th WORLD tour, what female rapper can relate? Fuck u doin… https://t.co/WFzUtP8ZQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4: I have a5cepted a challenge from @CoachDegarmo to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews… https://t.co/FxOPWMxX0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Utbighair @WilliamTheodor3 @dukematties Joel has always been a head scratching jockey,who occasionally gives brilliant rides]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronGoodwin Hey, IDKYU always let Zak throw you 2 the wolves Bro. https://t.co/8VzbngzmL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Beach. CBS. Loveline. *Radio only. The appreciation of which may be lost in time. :O. Now do they know which th… https://t.co/PItGo3wHOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome morning out at Mavs &amp; Mochas with @MaverickPCA https://t.co/xTTC6sDJcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaineCollegeLIB @MThomasWFXG @JAndersonWFXG @PaineCollege @CityofAugusta I live in Ridge spring South Carolina and… https://t.co/83jMWrTEjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of Neil and the crew at Griffen Fab Works.  They knocked out another awesome crew cab pre-runner.  I think th… https://t.co/dJ7IaB0DTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Adrian Dantley, Notre Dame; 2X All American, Oscar Robertson Trophy 76, 6X All Star, Rookie Of Year… https://t.co/XOJ1wcBSKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like NHL, like AHL. @monstershockey win 4-0 over Belleville. Like the Blue Jackets, the Monsters now sit two points… https://t.co/5LH6gV1zKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RomyGiacomi @feministabulous It’s because, like all good con men, he is saying what they want to hear]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jess291129 @K_Aus23 @YaBoySavage_ I like @YaBoySavage_  I’d like to watch them play. And better? On what day? I me… https://t.co/0q6PXzvBas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days I have a glowing neon heart. Other days, it’s dark and cold. It’s called balance. 😂🧡🖤]]></document></documents></author>