<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Morrison @DaveOshry The way Twitter grouped these I thought Dave was the best sandwich and Ryan was jealous of him… https://t.co/O1Yhn1aQHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoGonzalesTV Definite maybe. Basically it’s unclear how that will play out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eledawva I have nothing clear. Medical privacy laws make it near impossible for anyone but the person being treated to describe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASavageNation Money... liberal democrats won't do anything unless they get paid...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayorGinther why is the power out AGAIN! And why isn’t it showing an outage on the website. Get it back on!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hardest week of my life! Hardest day of my life.. laying my mom down to rest for the finally time. “They say there… https://t.co/e6U1n9Xe9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_REX1991 Of course Baylor could blow that whole scenario by losing to the Cowboys tomorrow night...😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HCS Don’t agree with this at all. Maybe just MAYBE ball getting reduced. Change it up and potentially add in Heretic Ball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmbJohnBolton @hfc7507 A couple of F-16s and one C-150 could end this quick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[...It is time to stop running and to continue to move forward, but hopefully sharing my most sequestered, innermost… https://t.co/N2qDm0Yqr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#travelphotography #photooftheday #bridge #manhattanbridge #nyc  #newyork #travel #newyorkcity… https://t.co/KrX2nNT14a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to NPR and getting a Triple Venti Nonfat Mocha at Starbucks. I'm a basic white girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just waiting for this season to end. After LeBrons injury the entire season went south. Who knows how things wo… https://t.co/XptiEJ57eK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza Wouldn't it be possible for voters that have their vote infringed upon to take the state they reside… https://t.co/gmY85xMYvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cmon man you can’t sign the ball in the middle like that. He’s not a HOF’er]]></document><document><![CDATA[@balompiedom En lo personal no me gustó el logo ya que no es original, me gustaría algo que hable de nuestras raíces]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your faith is not an equation. Stop trying to solve for “x” when “y” has always been God. - KJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday morning compared to after school! Illinois weather at its finest! It felt so good to get outside!… https://t.co/efzTmxLgJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure @RepMarkMeadows views Kushner’s failure to fill out his security form SEVERAL TIMES to be just as serious… https://t.co/IUYTyRQflx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DouthatNYT Ross.  You believe in angels. I always remember that when I read anything you publish.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: listen up ladies!! #grindsmygears #erksmynerves #DONTfriendzonemen #thisiswhatyouget #NOGames #RNS @ North Car… https://t.co/2nQillWOk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are currently living through the dumbest dystopia as a direct result of Mr. Weiner’s case.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShellyCov Why not have Voter ID. You need Id for just about anything else you do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen Pilcher-Cook says SB 16 addresses what the Kansas Supreme Court wants the state to do in reaching at risk stude… https://t.co/00epY0z0r4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Angenette5 @Local12 I think we all know what's about to happen, here...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreakonaleashC @drj21h @DanteAtkins Politically, that's nuts. Also Warren has done far more to actually rein those people in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our 1st point in the MLS. On the road. Against the defending champs! Lots to build on. #FCCincy see you at Newport next week 🍀⚽️🔶🔷]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOOOOHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO THERE IS YOUR DAGGER!!!!!!!!!! #GoAvsGo!!!!! @Avalanche]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever the budget for Book Club was, they could have spared just a little bit more to hire someone who knew how t… https://t.co/t4Bu3rQQ50]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbaradye921 Contact the @ACLU. If this is a public school, this could be a Constitutional violation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigRedRuckus @BBHistoryDaily @nut_history @OTBaseballPhoto @metsrewind @MetsDaddy2013 @DickYoungsGhost… https://t.co/RZlLrx7Bo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsGucciBro5 Bro I hate getting the #1 pick after Bron leaves , we lead the league in first picks lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ckates7 @PGAPappas @adidasGolf Enhancements. This year’s tongue area is wat better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Foko007 Jajaja tengo 1 juego en los últimos 7 meses compadre y fue hace 2 semanas con el friazo jajajajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gingerreckoning @meglish It’s not too hard! I can teach!  (I’m realizing I have no clue when I’d see either one of… https://t.co/qBldILnQPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Virginia Beach led a similar effort a few years ago. https://t.co/BU9V8Nh2cf @byjanehammond @nnschools @VAeducatorRJW #NNPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellyhastings1 @GastonCounty @VisitBelmontNC @cityofbelmont Thanks for joining the Chamber meeting this morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Osprey’s Fresh Catch (Season Six) by Horus Fresh Ales @ Greater Woodlawn — https://t.co/663zXTVyZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ben_Alpers Yes, Wallace was a key figure for the mid-1970s "New Right" that was seeking to mobilize the culture wa… https://t.co/O007W5zTXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drivers of overspending remain: (1) the rate making formula, (2) undifferentiated ROE, (3) fixed customer charges s… https://t.co/HpLw8Ttkvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed the Wildcat Warmup feature on my friend Rodney Woods @coachrwoods https://t.co/15SFaFyqWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPBF_Vanessa Morning. I enjoy when you feel in to do the weather. Btw, please down down the hot weather 🤪 enjoy the rest of your Sunday. 👍😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShelbyKStewart No one gives a Rat’s Ass! Most of us expect 45 to be wearing an orange jumpsuit before then and answering to 74821!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walked home after work Sunday. . . . . #snow #walk #winded #exercise #almosthome #tired #sundayshift… https://t.co/6pNPJMndG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is 6:19 AM on the East Coast. I am starting my morning with roasted pork, Brussels sprouts, potato salad,… https://t.co/nS5jsp4XS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@godux1987 @oregonfootball @uoregon @coach_cristobal @OregonPitCrew @OregonWBB @kayvonT8 Love this 💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaruchelNDG thank you for an amazing story through these 3 films. #Berk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Naughty Girl by Beyoncé is better than anything The Beatles ever produced]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow that was fun to go out haha, but in going to regret it in the morning. I'm too old for this ish 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimYoull @_fruchtose @jump_rides @FordGoBike (My 2¢: to help mitigate this problem, JUMP should provide discounted… https://t.co/uikCEXC0cG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Complaint regarding 2/28/19 program.  On the final exam.  Gutfeld is so much shorter than Jesse, therefore, makes h… https://t.co/lsVua3V0pF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Habs are sleeping.  Not boding well.  Playing listless and dumb...bad combo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebooksyearn Jon - sorry to hear this. Reading this thread from the Holy Cross Hospital where Mom is dealing with a… https://t.co/LLaTjuH04S]]></document><document><![CDATA[En el Bronx lleno de odio en Alta con el Boss @jrpetare 🔥🎬🎥 . . #newyork #newyorkcity #usa #music #film #filmmaking… https://t.co/wwPoKSiAK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the follow! I will follow back as soon as Twitter allows !  @minicrafter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the ProLogistix team! See our latest #SupplyChain job openings, including "Lumper", via the link in our bio. #Apex, NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFLALeigh Oh brother!  At least it didn’t get stuck open like happened to me once.  You have a fun day ahead of you 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump MAGA!! 6 more years. Before anyone can bring USA 🇺🇸 backwards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nfrostie @moonrakerkih @margarethodge @JoRichardsKent @thetimes Its not about the customers, its about the British… https://t.co/O64rXweePt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las mejores ! (at @InNOutBurger in Costa Mesa, CA) https://t.co/ISwAUtGdTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@What2have4lunch @thehill Isn’t being rounded up by Marshall’s part of the due process for contempt of Congress?]]></document><document><![CDATA[&lt;Full photo downloads&gt;  Are found on my Facebook Fanpage • (LIKE) (@ByrdsPhotos) • #scottsdalesaturdaynight… https://t.co/XpsPNr32Hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. It must be for truly accelerated closure, with emissions benefits that net out positively against what a market… https://t.co/hrfJdITknD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomwarren @JezCorden I just want Microsoft’s version. The Surface Courier. https://t.co/7tlpwJmZmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:38.1°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esté será un nuevo pokémon? Que opinan chicos? @NigeruWilliam @PokeRaptorr  @KarimeroWings  @zenpokefan  @FolagoR https://t.co/UnGyJCyAbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoptartLudwig @DavidHarrisAD I didn’t love the support poles that were going to be at near the end of the end zone… https://t.co/XuxwytOOid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WMJR17 No problem at all! Thanks for reaching out, glad you enjoyed it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come hang out every Thursday night at theavenuedc with me and all the wonderful people who’ve been coming out and m… https://t.co/NTL8tjYjAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump This is the face you make when you’re caught with EGG on your face - or “ummmm” let… https://t.co/kyN0VEc39N]]></document><document><![CDATA[WED. WFR PICKS R1-2 3 5 R2-3 5 6 R3-6 4 3 R4-3 1 2 R5-2 3 6 R6-5 2 1 4 3 R7-5 3 2 R8-3 2 7 R9-4 5 2 R10-2 6 7 R11-8… https://t.co/iS6lQcvC3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is https://t.co/MU3gq12S1x workout rant , its all about being #BuiltReady for life, #Success is not about mate… https://t.co/QYGRuG52Fv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guy @mattalexand talking about systematizing ur #startup brand. At Gig Wage we believe there are 3prongs to buil… https://t.co/7hkwA890oe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSaryuszWolski @StKarczewski @pisorgpl Zdradza sie tylko raz...historia moze wybaczy...U mnie masz prze..bane "na… https://t.co/mod8YBqQnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FierceTweetsNow No one said you weren’t entitled to your opinion. That’s theirs and this is mine. No matter what y… https://t.co/i7rMR4UmSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmittyLu Nigga wanted some free buns. Thought he was taking some drunk passed out buns. 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caltrain Palo Alto at 5:40pm Tuesday Feb 26th. https://t.co/DobpWs4jOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no words! I am buying this issue and putting it out for all to see and for my kids to learn from! “Who runs… https://t.co/1hCPNqr3ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerReddick @KellyCrandall yeah...uh...i'm fully blind, and i could probably make it down pit road without fuckin… https://t.co/MwKNzIr6vN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving #pokemongo and #gosnapshot !!! #pokemon #shinypokemon #meltan #pichu #chikorita https://t.co/Rl9Qm6xqAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disappointed to hear @JayInslee on @FaceTheNation say he’ll only sue Trumps #NationalEmergency declaration when the… https://t.co/6uoJnOBedV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thru 2: Alexandria, Piedmont scoreless in #CalhounBaseball19 semifinal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinsjuts We lost several at the beginning of last season due to rain. Ended up playing more games in Council Bluffs than Lincoln.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DuqHockey will finish no lower than the third seed as long as neither Pitt nor Slippery Rock get three points thi… https://t.co/F8ZvKiuT0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff LORD IM SO RELIEVED AND HAPPY THAT YOU ARE THE CHAIRMAN NOW INSTEAD OF CROOKED ASS NUNES!!  I KNOW Y… https://t.co/D08PO8tNaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#music #Spotify #imaginedragons #kendricklamar @ University Student Union at Fresno State https://t.co/XJI1M0kIdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @KalPenn and his story of how he got to work at the @ObamaWhiteHouse inspires us not to accept other’s… https://t.co/oKEoGR6G7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #VoteSpiderVerse on @TyltEnt—It should win #Oscars Best Animated Feature Film https://t.co/0UN4QiCkWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[its @thexboxdrive timeeeeeeeeeee Good Morning!!! https://t.co/uKNe7lEARq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me gusta estar rodeado de gente que quiere ser mejor. Me nutre, me inspira, me exige. En esa pantalla hay personas… https://t.co/aLr045nWRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have 3 times the amount of athletes as the rest of the schools in your conference, shouldn’t really come a… https://t.co/YwXmuER31o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheManAdamVan Her “Sonya Blade” look from Mortal Kombat. Like it better than the other look where she’s constantly adjusting her outfit]]></document><document><![CDATA[He referenced reading Star Wars books during the downtime between racing and Darth Vader, all in the space of about ten minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is wild. I’m holding a print edition of @BuzzFeed https://t.co/Z3CePclWH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakersGold @THEREAL_DV I read the story. They were looking for one if I remember right and cash. Just because, for… https://t.co/WYGCDpsJY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnderKnifeMovie @THEPHONEDEAD1 @yubarifanta I look forward to seeing Under the Knife, enjoy my latest horror film… https://t.co/68ab4wZCKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ptpwilliamson Miss Kacey herself sang the final phrase that way at the first NYC show last month]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDCUniverse, my birthday is Monday and all I want from you is the Xbox and PS4 DC Universe apps.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When cannabis is legalized in #California and particularly in #Hollywood people start to get creative...… https://t.co/F1EwPNmnX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBellRacing I saw your #WindingUpInElongationAcelleration2 ole twisted up in torque across chassis twist flatten o… https://t.co/x229hiMdWW]]></document></documents></author>