<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @BrittanyFurlan and @MrTommyLand who are now husband and wife!! 💖💞 https://t.co/C0GWVn3mxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_aneshana @SamHeughan @thinking_woman1 @Outlander_STARZ You are adding words to his tweet. He said he felt there w… https://t.co/KIX22HOhUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Savanna_house1 Yep. They were in the quality foods parking lot with all the equipment this morning when I was headed to work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @sxdoc Thank u president Trump god bless u each and every day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Hey toad junior...please stop the stupid. Could you for once behave befitting the… https://t.co/ekfjVaopN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking this morning about what it means to children to be able to rely and depend on the fact that they will have… https://t.co/xvHDf2NU79]]></document><document><![CDATA[Classic Books Becoming Movies In 2019. #PageTurners #Page2Screen  https://t.co/JtPhGBtPtI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing the incomparable Sutton Foster with the St. Louis Symphony was definitely a bucket list item come true. ❤️Br… https://t.co/RSafOXiPnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happier by Bastille/Marshmellow : -happy title -upbeat  -REALLY SAD IF YOU LISTEN CLOSELY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @FelixVMatosRod1 - hard to imagine a more authentic and inspiring leader to drive CUNY forward as C… https://t.co/nTjZYNvbU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone please take me out on a date and call me pretty:( I promise not to ask for a few months I swear]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3) (pt 2) however worded, center around the good of the school community and constant improvement  #ETCoaches]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KieseLaymon That’s what I was thinking. I’ve actually written about it, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankMarro @JimmyVanBramer @AOC Jimmy Van Job Killer makes over 149k for a part time job plus pension. he is fine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton @EWErickson Notice, the same media who made sure to emphasize the supposed “MAGA” affiliation, are tryi… https://t.co/Qm8AfbdVyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleLiTV You should scroll thru the different book series he mentions. I think that you'll find one particular… https://t.co/1N9v3A17Eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccislamabad  #DEVELOP_E12_ISB ASAP @ImranKhanPTI @mohrpakistan @ePakistanToday @PAKSupremeCourt  @mophrd… https://t.co/kXzUpToK6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[My tia really replied to me 5 days later with an “ok” , she’s worse than my mom lol https://t.co/XYen3kUIAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so entirely grateful for my boyfriend. He’s so amazing and sweet. Honestly this kid has so much patience and is… https://t.co/ATopelMihl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magnumCJ I think its dumb as hell, too. I'm way too clumsy when I drink to new trusted with an ax.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not that we are competent in ourselves to claim anything for ourselves, but our competence comes from God. https://t.co/oo8A9f4kEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OwenConnelly4 Matt Connelly #9, Kevin Polak #25, and Matt Jones #27 had our three goals tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Ahora El gobierno de Estados Unidos anunció este viernes cargos criminales contra el vicepresidente de Economía de… https://t.co/YQ2cIvTGwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrupoDeLima , @pontifex @Almagro_OEA2015 @realDonaldTrump si no vienen con militares, entonces manden civiles con… https://t.co/WzkPIzjoSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, please! We need more @7eleven stores with @LaredoTaco in them in (North) Dallas. After my friends and family,… https://t.co/NStTmtVrgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frank3700 @sheri_lynn95252 @Bozesgirl66 @CheekyAussieGuy @sweet___ash @ValentinoAndy77 @doitright651 @Sugarshack60… https://t.co/OgBACdNP27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Public_Citizen @ProudResister @MoveOn @AyannaPressley @IndivisibleTeam @Alyssa_Milano @RAICESTEXAS @WinWithoutWar… https://t.co/arW88cHPo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/1/19. Not feeling well. Bad. This is when being completely alone is an issue. And not having proper Insurance. Vo… https://t.co/B4PSgcgcxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah KIRKWOOD!!!!! @KCC_Athletics  @KwoodWBB  @anashahurst  Check us out  @ 3 p.m.  https://t.co/uU4fmBSPF2 https://t.co/wzXGjqoDbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[19 miles down and 1 to go! 🏊 So proud of all the young men swimming their hearts out this weekend at Swim to a Wish… https://t.co/DmyW7SdjtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re always waiting for the next stage of life to happen. I’ll be happy when....blablabla. Be happy now tho bc u w… https://t.co/T0JzjwTXo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Long_DohertyWB They just wow me with their enthusiasm and ideas! Thanks for popping by!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UPDATE: @CommishFish says he‘ll vote against leaving JTTF, but he wants to amend the agreement to require the FBI… https://t.co/FCbXpDxQHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @CoachAB34 and the entire @ClemsonWBB program- we 👀 you and know your 🧡!  Nehemiah and I are always proud… https://t.co/2rHeFdGald]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st Winter Wonderland mixed media collages. @Hillcrest_BCPS @visualartsbcps @HillcrestPTA https://t.co/tmcFR4y1OM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I talked about short stories yesterday. Today I thought I'd talk mention my novellas. It's fun to try to tell a sat… https://t.co/PsgdyFMXb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Octavio Garza Tanguma!! Feliz Dia de San Valentin Que la pases de lo lindo!! 😊este dia !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChipSkylvrk @Bouj_etto We’re probably the same people in one way or another. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start of the third with continued penalties and 2 #meninthebox for a few seconds! #LGR #BeatUnion #seniornight… https://t.co/nE6kHds8lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left #CaptainMarvel feeling powerful and inspired. I stopped to chat with strangers. A dude said; “Iron Man is mo… https://t.co/M0oknvxCQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RxchHeuman @britneyspears I found out through a tweet literally JUST NOW 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesleyabravanel @realDonaldTrump I could tell by looking at this clown he is a fake. Why so many were fooled by hi… https://t.co/LHHHd8Ke0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t know that I would ever relate to @JackJ  so much until he posted some of his recent tweets. Please, go che… https://t.co/rvqVKY2CQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I know is people needs to keep Dionna Christine Johnson name out their mouth , I don’t mess with nobody on this… https://t.co/ttpSryUNF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[We agree. Tree Chic started to raise awareness of more sustainable, ethical fashion options. There is a clear link… https://t.co/2YW9IOU6Mc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heaven on earth. @ Maple Street Biscuit Company https://t.co/OQ1prqPdzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@putemupcdukes @oconeebrewingco So excited @oconeefoodwine will feature @oconeebrewingco and Hey Man Ale at the Fes… https://t.co/LNOofhXofq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien @RepDanCrenshaw The only illegal voting that has been done has been by the @gop in NC’s 9th.  Don’t… https://t.co/ZiPHGTzNms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations, @c3hoosier! So deserving. We will miss you. Thank you for everything and being such an inspiring s… https://t.co/BN3Q4IpniS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FooteKnox Hai Sammie Sue and Dynamite and Seska!! (Mommy like Huskies) (PS: her usta be doggy person... den a ging… https://t.co/MOX3AXfGst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some personal news. My last day with the Community Press will be March 13. I will be using my journalism skills to… https://t.co/ycFnrVNQ01]]></document><document><![CDATA[@papivitela Ily bitch 😭💓 you know whats up with me , ima do wtf i gotta do regardlesssssss lol 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hand Painted Trible Owl On A Section Of A Deer Antler Accented With Buffalo Bone Beads On A Genuine Leather Cord.… https://t.co/rEc8iOGEdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not currently drinking but Cheers all from me and this guy :] #fridaymood https://t.co/OL4bXoi4Xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EpeeBill Hanging in there. Had a severe upper respiratory infection I couldn’t shake. Hope to be back next week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikesullivan08 @GamecockWBB @dawnstaley The Beach 4 plus 1 will be for OUR Gamecocks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really have a cold now ..... I just got over a stomach virus .... and I have a giant pimple that feels like hell… https://t.co/fEC5w5RuJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you want to go to bed but @JKCorden has too good of a lineup tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian Very nice. I wonder how many kids could have eaten for what that cost? How many veterans could eat o… https://t.co/qM01BireC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk What has this man been smoking? Or drinking? Does he know what year this is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realEricShaffer @Kimberly_Corban @loco_pod That’s what she wants u to think]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is everyone safe during this dire national emergency? #FakeTrumpEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felix Sater, a key figure in Trump Tower Moscow project, to testify in open session before the House Intelligence C… https://t.co/jHWUElOAMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three crashes, 30 some odd cars wrecked... only one survived. @dennyhamlin wins #DAYTONA500 https://t.co/S3LphDaYyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aisling_bn @IrishIceSP @cmdibley @SenWhitehouse @joncoopertweets LOL https://t.co/6ZQI2ia69c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is now an appropriate time to confess that I broke my glasses yesterday by dancing to hard to Burnin’ Up by the Jonas Brothers ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simplysallyh @FionaMorgan79 @Starofthesea007 @joneill55 @AkronWineGuru @CaththeWineLady @Julianna_glass @ccatmpt… https://t.co/2EHuhMRLRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another sign, Jeanie?  I say yes.. yes it is. @ The Smokehouse Market and Annie Gunn's https://t.co/yIBXpolY6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the great memories about my mom was her lipstick. #canttakeitwithyou #lipstick #missmymom @ North Fort Myers… https://t.co/IEjhgUhzgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again, the whole point that I *literally* lead with a nonjudging function was such a “well DUH” moment for me. I ju… https://t.co/5mUPBoAPo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shannonwas2 @DuvalNajera @Boomhauer17 @seanhannity Polling information? Yes...that’s information that’s readily av… https://t.co/F0QbONMDSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toniibatista sempre quis saber se vc gosta do Whindersson e sempre esqueço de perguntar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei I know something that they can do with those pearls and it’s not “clutch” them. Just saying. What a bu… https://t.co/ccHZNm1ImV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmoothBrothaB Wow you on the TL asking for macaroons like I don’t exist. https://t.co/3tWfHJS4L6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaranaBurke @RoArquette @GayleKing Every time I see his face on TV I wanna throw up. He's so disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B60Ballerz @MilagrosMontout @CopelandJKyle @Kristin59156744 @CristySwink @HitsonKevin Happy Birthday Jim!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[serious question - can anyone at @busboysandpoets hit me with the tomato bisque recipe, i promise i’ll keep it a secret]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to all who participated in the FFA Assembly today! 💙💛 https://t.co/lJTn5gLAPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[As questions loom about Jared Kushner's security clearance, House committee says White House not cooperating in pro… https://t.co/6POJh2ksee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got an email asking if I had a list of WOCs in tech in Toronto. I mean, I just know some. Can’t decide if I should… https://t.co/8v9Q6l4qQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamsethlevine @cornellgov @AliCirone @sabrinamkarim @sekreps @MonaKrewel @SuzanneMettler1 @povertyscholar… https://t.co/YxBevqA9ZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuildUpRDNs @CuseSportsRD @AmericanDairyNE Great discussion! We also have NY apples, eggs, potatoes, pears, herbs… https://t.co/QxsEc4gMI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wttw Rising from the Rails was an amazing watch today! I learned so much. Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[its been 2 years, 5 months, &amp; 14 days since my uncle died &amp; im still not at peace with it . soo many what ifs everyday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@startupbardi Thank you! He’s in the playoffs next week and I’m losing it. So proud and excited.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaSchwartzzz Did someone else say quicksand? I thought that shit was real and existed under the monkey bars at m… https://t.co/EUTF4O6spX]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/24/19. Trapped here. No way to escape. Nowhere to go anyway. Thought I'd die near the ocean. Reality is it'll be… https://t.co/qc4gij6CJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t know @RickyWilliams83 before this but I just love him!!! He seems like a great guy and I have MS and I would… https://t.co/JgTwX0N1wW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMartinSJ Generally speaking, celebrities sign what ever is given them to sign]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 available $5  #karissparkleroom  #karis5sparkle  #5dollarsparkle  #5dollarbling #paparazziaccessories @ Tulare, C… https://t.co/99zF9M3Wbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been to Ulta 3x in a 7 day span... someone come get me or take my wallet or something. This is a cry for help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DopeyRunr You are correct sir. Now they’re playing some song that sounds like A Dream is a Wish Your Heart Makes but isn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Communication is to relationship what breathing is to maintaining life.” - Virginia Satir #HappyValentinesDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Debra88352357 Debra, I believe it’s too late to answer. I had ideas to help her, but I’m afraid I came along too l… https://t.co/ycqIWbC9WV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I felt sick so I kept pretending I wasn’t. It came back with a vengeance and I’m real sick now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ppl used to call me lame and weird all throughout high school but idk ig I’m cool now lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was once with my dad in a packed elevator when, right before we reached our floor he broke the silence with, “Now,… https://t.co/K4PFk1f6zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning @MissMarisRacal @InigoDPascual! 😘  @mor101 #DyisIsltManila Tayo Na Di Tayo by Maris Racal and Inigo Pascual https://t.co/8DfcwPJDRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The American Craft Show is filled with creative vision! . Celebrating it's 30th Anniversary this year in Atlanta on… https://t.co/yxy8kN8qQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddieSkipsey @WomenEd @ThomsonPat @WomenedEM If only they paid as much attention to the content 😁]]></document></documents></author>