<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth @realDonaldTrump Donald you do realize this guy is a comedian right? IDIOT~!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you didn’t get chased by your siblings with a knife and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[One candidate accused the NCIP of being a “de facto arm of the Republicans.” NCIP Chair Susan Angelo Eberwein said… https://t.co/M6OvDRd5Fc]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people die they will blam the person that approved bill! So @officialOKGOP and of coarse @GovStitt! Weapons wi… https://t.co/C3moexDUVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg is dis a result of years of being top of the class during lower education https://t.co/DisRwRNKIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would give an arm and a leg to be at home this spring break working with the show string with weather like this rat… https://t.co/I95TKW5Qyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew_WSAW @WSAW I’m so proud of you Matthew for taking this amazing step in your career. I’m truly going to miss you so much 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuneMo41 Thank you!!! 😍😍😍  Have an amazing day! https://t.co/VRHxqgDMlp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SterlingKBrown Happy Hearts Day to you and your wife! ❤️ I told an acquaintance today that he should add some glas… https://t.co/y4KMzbSb3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mushmabubba @mamacubs1 @ItaliaSteve @60Minutes Heard this. 45 is eminently undeserving, as would be any Putin-installed POTUS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turns out I correctly remembered what it's like to be here. https://t.co/BncN3wmlV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[In our reflections of ourselves, there maybe brokenness along the way but that does not diminish the fact that you… https://t.co/9vDzp77k8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I JUST FOUND OUT THAT QUEEN BRITNEY HAS BEEN BACK IN THE STUDIO AND NOW IM TOO EXCITED TO SLEEP #ITSBRITNEYBITCH @britneyspears]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 The GOP always acts as if our social security belongs to them. Enough is enough. They never paid back i… https://t.co/M9vmZxuUXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bestfriend would be turning 33 tomorrow 😪 this will make 11 birthdays without him 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay new @TOMS! Things I ❤️: social impact, shoes, &amp; mail! S/O to @BlakeMycoskie and his team for the… https://t.co/pIyGlssTKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in the Supreme Court cafeteria and thought you all might want to know that the justices love mochi https://t.co/eIJLFQEQDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonasbrothers new song!!!!! #JonasBrothers  Jonas Brothers - Sucker https://t.co/89VaDAV6Eg via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarah_riley8 enjoying a gyro at Jahn’s. #ilovemyniece #goodkid @ Jahn's Since 1897 https://t.co/9tScoy02y1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @ClarkCountyNV Government Center looking pretty in the snow! #SnowingInVegas #vegassnow #clarkcounty #vegas https://t.co/2L7I42s8qR]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAY 2:  I have accepted a challenge from @libbeydetcher and @MsmithGHS to post covers of 7 books I love: no explana… https://t.co/ayilBDMU85]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton in Selma: ‘We are living through a full-fledged crisis in our democracy’ https://t.co/U2nbJGQ42h]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ain’t treating me how my dad treats me... ion want ya😂❗️sorry boo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zistar01 @thomaskaine5 Hi LT..love your posts usually, however the state I am from has 2 senators like every other… https://t.co/Ngo6YfZHso]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a movie where @LanaDelRey plays Julia Roberts, I will PAY FOR THIS MOVIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @MrsMcCourtReads to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations—just the covers.… https://t.co/Q9ag3wGIrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought my coworkers doughnuts because they've all been working their butts off at this sometimes thankless job. 😊❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @alyssasinesy 🤩 I hope your day is as sweet as you 💜 live it up girl 🎉 https://t.co/v7vymPeoco]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was a real unnecessary 11 hour shift for 1/2 it I literally did nothing.. 😴😴😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Singing Disney classics and coloring - someone tell 7 year old me adulthood is lit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to trade in my basic mom car for... yep you guessed it, the ultimate mom car. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBReich They haven’t displayed any honor this far. #LeopardCantChangeHisSpots]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I am alone, God is my comforter. When I am nothing, God is my everything. When I am sad and lonely, God is my… https://t.co/kluHfeDxp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then perhaps you shouldn’t speaking in public. This seems to keep happening to you.   Interesting thing...we all he… https://t.co/k0mXk0uiVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warm sun, feed me up 🌞 https://t.co/Ir8DCtKgtF #ethereal_moods #fromwhereistand #goddessgang @ San Pedro, California https://t.co/g4YuCRzYW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, good afternoon and happy Wednesday to all #Castle and #TheRookie fans https://t.co/Bu9Br9w8iN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bertrand_boily @OkanaganCider @bodyfit67 @timsmithrx @cellmavin @wolv54b1 @whatthejeez @bow_en_arrow @beerguypdx… https://t.co/UqnFd2KTvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadalynSklar A5. I’ve LOVED building such a loyal and insightful community via #smechat every week! Such a great w… https://t.co/IHjpc6h57B]]></document><document><![CDATA[2)I share this information not to brag, but because I'm sick of hearing wealthy people shame the poor or middle cla… https://t.co/Oy8fQZgcvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalFamily @ClarenceHouse Congratulations to HRH the Prince of Wales!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I try my hardest to be positive, but this world will test you lemme tell ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved it, too!  Why do you think it did so poorly (in spite of numerous nominations) this awards season?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the new president Donald Trump Jr. Will be taking the oath of office!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 Thompson High School Outdoor Track &amp; Field https://t.co/mNspaqrz8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Love bears all things, believes all things, hopes all things, endures all things.” https://t.co/lM6KpMakpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remembered I saw a dude using two lime scooters, he had one in each foot?? Wild]]></document><document><![CDATA[i keep crying and my kitty keeps licking my tears and it’s making me cry harder happy saturday]]></document><document><![CDATA[God ain’t have to do me like that for me to stay home and not go out this weekend. I can’t remember ever being this… https://t.co/SgieCcpCYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anthony Morrison has some amazing skills to share. They are for those who are interested in internet marketing.  Jo… https://t.co/OsNZItYd9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inicia tu semana con una sonrisa en #VivalaviEnEl6 junto a @adrianariv @angelcastrotv @florivonVeliz… https://t.co/gmhfbopKpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMehlich @dunkindonuts I know I couldn’t say no! Get those boys a donut!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s ready to move out?!?? This lady!!! Eight more weeks. I can hang in there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rooting for @stanwawrinka but cramping @NickKyrgios takes out Stan in 3 sets. Well done. #acapulcoopen #MexicoOpen #ATPTour]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not gonna sit here and lie like I don’t like Valentine’s Day, I’m still gonna celebrate w a bottle of red wine, allll to myself ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolewagner667 Leí que se la llevaron los federales, creo que por caimanes 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡A celebrar! (@ Guiuseppis in Tijuana, BC) https://t.co/XhzPssk8kI https://t.co/z4quRm6jXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just woke up to a text from Zachary saying “wtf Katy Perry and Orlando have only been dating 2 months and their eng… https://t.co/SDBRT8WR6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OklaEd Prepare for #summer ahead of time to make sure your students keep #reading and #learning over the break! Ki… https://t.co/fMOzhrr5Nm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHEVYWOODS Wait till ya get to London, we got mad love for you out here♥️ I’ll be the only girl who actually knows the words 😂🤟🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrwebber35 @PrincessBravato Yes, getting rid of the diseased organ then treating the other areas may give him a fi… https://t.co/vP2USIMxb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tatclouthier @sickjos @FerPla_ @HernanGomezB @lopezobrador_ No puedo creer que sugiera esto señora. La realidad es… https://t.co/fwTVLBR6Bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PFBC is back for the final day of the Muskie Max PLUS sport show @ Southpointe Arena in Canonsburg, PA.  Stop by o… https://t.co/g7l3Ettemo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ro_leovegildo @Jouberth19 Não tenho, mas lembro de ter visto já faz um tempo quando uma amiga colombiana me mostrou.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She needs to spend a few months in the “non-cage.”  Maybe then she’ll understand what a cage is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephGrisham45 @FLOTUS @POTUS @TheView You Got this WRONG !! That Would be Hillary Cinton]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pipersrush #sppkanesrushband @ Spokane, Washington https://t.co/iimGsuYtyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews One more shout out to ya Doc, Eugene Gu,  I like your style!    👍  👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Belong Somewhere You Feel Free​ https://t.co/BNWF5ipo2K https://t.co/nQ5tXDhv0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkClarkster @DeathByLipstik @DetroitBlonde @deedee_regan @MandyAntoniacci @Jay_Rombach @Resist37 @edgyerin… https://t.co/KrbUo0s5Kl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinbiba @cbquist @darth @Awl @ThomasHynes Oh thank god I was on the verge of putting myself in a Twitter timeout bc of that pun]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even #TwitterlessTim who is even keel and not shaken is anxious while watching this. HOW could someone do this?! #FreeSolo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fififevandbyron @gandusio @SamHeughan @fifi_box Absolutely the best birthday wishes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[you think I give a fuck about a fuckboy feelings. Negative, I’ll send him crying to his mom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanLin1230 I realize it was different time but their stupidity was on another level. https://t.co/FOcpj35uee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impacttravelall @WTTC @adventuretweets You honestly have made my week. Thank you! Hope to see you there too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should’ve went to bed like 3-4 hours ago but I stayed up watching A Sitch a Time instead 😂  Hey it’s a good movie though]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh what a sad, pathetic, fuck... Take something I and most forgot about and scream it out to the world... https://t.co/DcUDQu44jI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was about to do a junk food clean out and then I realized I bought Girl Scout cookies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I learn somwthing new everyday! Axolotl = "asholuck" https://t.co/oCahfha9Af]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber Mr. Melber I love Dick Cavett!! Where in the round world has he been? GREAT TO SEE YOU , Mr. Cavett!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I am depressed for long periods of time, I end up in a mood where all I think about doing is going to expensiv… https://t.co/qOfTytWBVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pbnsg @fatmanrants_com I have been WFPB for 8 months.  It has changed my life.  I feel better than I have in years… https://t.co/nGGrhDdRDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaye_gallops We should have zero tolerance for human cruelty.  That man should never work or be allowed to handle… https://t.co/oOI7G84EWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you feel moved to fast for lent this year, don't ask your closest friends for suggestions. They DO know you best… https://t.co/C7Lusp4zf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[next month makes one year since i lost my dog so if you see my crying on march 23rd mind ur business]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I’ve seen Bryce Harper’s parents at no shower happy hour in Avalon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch this ain’t Toyota, this European  Bitch she ain’t no hoe, she my girlfriend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get the WWJD phrase. I try and live by that too. I also know addiction is a serious problem. However, when a pers… https://t.co/ftKwjxX1UF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 5th Anniversary to the best car a girl could ask for! 🚗💨  Here’s to so many more memories, so much more love,… https://t.co/12W2zAfwkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stevie is such a rockstar. A night I’ll never forget. 🌻 @ Legacy Arena https://t.co/Z0dqyZR57h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally out of the cold (@ Phoenix Sky Harbor International Airport - @phxskyharbor in Phoenix, AZ) https://t.co/0A1QNGithc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHarris707 @d_ast777 @ArleneKowalczyk @JudyMcAferty @TheBread_OfLife @DavidAJMHoward @ITGeekCT @AnneKabes… https://t.co/Kf5SsdIVRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What’s happening in this Country  is the crazy orange man is running it into the ground !!!!!!  👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t listen to @daxshepard podcast, the ‘Armchair Expert’ you need too. Every single one is such an eye ope… https://t.co/oEcvtTtPeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw the moon last night and it reminded me how blessed these eyes are to still be here to welcome its glow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottRRocco A3 And this example hits home even more with my middle schoolers who dream of being a successful athle… https://t.co/E2AFs5Ak3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALLELUYAH!!! With A SHOUT! HALLELUYAH!!! The Highest Praise!!! Early Will I Rise And WORSHIP YOU For YOU LORD JESU… https://t.co/LnzZ3rGVTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatDamnMills_ Girl I’m knowing lol mills just let the bitch know you back again 😂🤣🤟🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIAMS NATURAL HAIR IS CURLY OOOIHHHHH MY GOOOOOODDD!!!!! HE WAS A CUTLY BABY TOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got a new tv and it has Netflix installed and I’ve never been so happy because now I can see greys anatomy without being disturbed lol]]></document></documents></author>