<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TKendziora37 @testudotimes The problem's not with your input, Tom ... it's with Maryland's output. That's what's f… https://t.co/GomkuK6FoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch the magic of #spraychrome But man I’m so much to get done before I fly out to #SF tomorrow!! wish me luck on… https://t.co/3A8sEGnJzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[So who ya got winning the #Daytona500 today at @DISupdates?! @NightwatchTitus who ya got?! https://t.co/Lh2NvvId2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[A la derecha asi viven la mayoría de los neoliberales. A la izquierda la mayoría de los mexicanos no mas prian. https://t.co/YMTSxhVFeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tony12fan @LVMotorSpeedway @NASCAR That’s a good thing it was over built, less people at the track = better at tra… https://t.co/jpV2wS9ZKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @ken_gymnast - not sure if you’ve seen this or not. Cool! #WPS 🐗 @RazorbackGym https://t.co/4CJtC1LmnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the studio that brought you the check writing thriller ‘Catch Me if You Can’ comes the sequel...  ‘Catch me Ca… https://t.co/TM3De3a9Kh]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's funny to think that the next time I'll see "Lunch" I'll be 33 years old. I'm excited to see how much my Japane… https://t.co/LnC1BINpFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys Our CHILDREN Need the BASICS! They are Creativities Building Blocks! Teachers give them those!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy made his very 1st trip to @WDWToday 17 years ago today! My how the hub has changed! Just so happens....we’… https://t.co/KBa28r5rf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well it looks like it’s just me, Twitter, Jack &amp; Coke, and this flat Earth documentary on Netflix. What could go wrong?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UpUpDwnDwn @Wizards_DnD @XavierWoodsPhD ok,  have to know: what level is he? that, and please tell me he has leather armor...]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your 5 is the best passer on the court — but then he also gotta teach y’all bout the UNFRIENDLY ROLL.… https://t.co/iq95BhxSUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNRIVALED_PSU_ @rudybux @wrestlingbucks Buckeyes won the regular season Big Ten, won in indoor track.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:26.5°F WchillLow:16.3°F Wind:0 mph Dir:--- Baro:Rising slowly Rain2day:0.00in Hum:72% UV:0.0 @ 23:30 03/08/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtyler1120 Jeff, sorry for the long delay in getting back with you. No, the regular season refs were not too bad a… https://t.co/N9dIAUQpE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about these freakin starters from @carminesnyc ??? Are you going for the Fried Calamari or Fried Zucchini? . .… https://t.co/5sBW6PcMp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 Resons that @SpeakerPelosi @chuckschumer @SenSchumer #openborder #policy is #AntiAmerican by allowing… https://t.co/WxadQXXcNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlkocher2 @MLB @MLB seems to market to stuffy old white people. It’s a bad move.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewHVoss I’m realizing just how many clothes I have. I do *not* need this many clothes 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgiaLogCabin Judicial system, don’t let this bigot slide. Prosecute to the full extent of the law!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshCox @kellyn_taylor @Steph_Rothstein @NAZ_Elite @HOKAONEONE @Roots_Running #likeaboss]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guy on the radio wants the Rooneys the #saletheteam so things are going well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandmother’s grandfather was a slave as well.  I well remember stories about him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry/ thank u to all my friends that deal w me having my favorite song on replay for like a week straight]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the mind of the Azeris/Turkomans. They are literally so brainwashed they think this is what “Azerbaijan” sh… https://t.co/4LBKQPo8R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another capture of Ms. Lisa on her 1st dog park visit. 🐕🐾 @NikonUSA #D810 70-200 f/2.8 #lightroom #photoshop… https://t.co/0fxKlcCcls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mccullylab @WUSTLmed Thanks Michelle - seems you'll be at BPS as well, see you there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisBHaynes @Raptors season ticket holders should get “load management” rebates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson Good for you! Coming clean. Or getting clean. Or whatever. Good for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are a moron.  If you had served you would understand how important this is.  You make us weak… https://t.co/BrgQb5gUW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Philly parks and rec. I wonder how much was raised to fight cancer since he started?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@COSADEL @YaBoiExclusive @Kafern @DEADSTOCK_T @TrapAndFamous @TheFemaleCope @NotChinks @Suzuki_Bj For a long time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrlsCntrrz @OriginalFunko Special Mickey 90th from Hong Kong I believe]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I h8 that I lost someone super close to me all because she’d rather be with someone who’s hella toxic and strai… https://t.co/BNlLAR6b1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all want this man to represent AZ. as a senator https://t.co/Pq6TwazJEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@41Strange @emm_ell_dee That dude definitely knew how to count by the time his puppeteer career came to an end]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_A10_USA @jcoralpark You know the CIA and FBI have the resources to eradicate this man. Why has he not been i… https://t.co/3PaHRmfoOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the weakest tweets ever. Do y’all(women) want to build an empire or nah? There were 300 million phot… https://t.co/YwhDOfbPcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[They gotta quit spraying these guys heads with that stuff it looks ridiculous. Unless that's the point.🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally finished Darksiders! Excellent blend of Zelda and God of War type gameplay. Definitely a sleeper hit I miss… https://t.co/7nwc8aQZZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes I was the girl in the salon downing a McDouble while getting my color applied https://t.co/W9coxmcocm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex_Ladd_ The custom pre settings for lighting inside the Sony A9 or the Sony A7III are really cool. You can manu… https://t.co/kaT8FyZPSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtgriffin74 @Alyssa_Milano Voting for a criminal, multiple adulterer, compulsive liar ... Yeah you sure have the high ground.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hit Tucson for the second time and left 72° for 15° back home // San Xavier Mission // @ Tucson, Arizona https://t.co/H0RWrXlrgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@txsweettar225 @im2b @GeraldoRivera @trumps_feed @realDonaldTrump @POTUS True that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Digging it, sounds remarkably vintage, like it was dug up from an artist who toured with The Dismemberment Plan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This "giddiness " was created by the mob not #MAGA people who want to be able to express their opinions without vio… https://t.co/f4AP5dmlAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Round of Districts tomorrow at Edsel Ford. Tipoff is at 6:45, come out and support your Tractors as we take on Cass Tech. 🏆 🚜🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK. Who: 1. will understand this? 2. will bother to read this? 3. and yet, actually needs this explanation? https://t.co/NOZ5PWYugv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump Your an uneducated man you must be speaking about Charlottesville his remarks tha… https://t.co/aqV8HkKkuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Peach Me How To Rhubarb by @oddsideales at @a2ashleys — https://t.co/1AtAOh8vqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toni Preckwinkle, Lori Lightfoot advance to Chicago mayoral runoff.  https://t.co/fskdvGftIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recommended Wesing to you @adam_white81  lets play s3 tablet in chapters directions aphrodites lomilomi party enter… https://t.co/issN9ideLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTTalkingPoints @ProviderOfTruth @britbritmarieee @BernieSanders Write your research paper and prove Stanford wrong :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[best place on planet earth #PurpleWall @ Disney's Magic Kingdom https://t.co/ZET9zK5Ovz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My buddy wants to make Albania great "again"... and he wants to use my #tesla to power the whole country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checked in and all ready for Miss SC work weekend! Can’t wait for a full day tomorrow with my Miss SC sisters! 💖… https://t.co/vw34qoXOqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@virginiagrind @espn @SportsCenter Definitely a different culture, and in my opinion a double standard. Can you ima… https://t.co/GzWZgcNQCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a playlist of songs that have been inspiring me lately  https://t.co/UkK6THGakz]]></document><document><![CDATA[)        )   )    (        )       )   )  _(___(____)____(__(_ \     Your viewers     / _  \     are people     /… https://t.co/ZSyZV3WbUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DocTsuga We’ve seen them @IrvineNature and a friend saw one near Park Heights and Valley Road.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at SR 436 &amp; Hunt Club Blvd in Apopka, FL https://t.co/byYur1RDai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awlatlanta @ashleynhinsley @gex_daniel @GodFirstGina @CensoredC1 @thor1usa @TrumperSeaney @_IamAnita_D… https://t.co/rtAKyKIUeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the total and exact polar opposite of everything HUHS stands for. And it shows.. If you do porn only for th… https://t.co/a1iEVw9RWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump It’s***President Trump . Learn how to respect your president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDrGina All thy American votes than are paid off if money has to be raised y Gina does money have to be thy mai… https://t.co/IoNKUce2do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell yeah I got 2 jobs now dawg. When I get my first check I'mma taking it home and masturbate to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to a blessing from God. Love you Kate. Have the best day baby.💜 @khelson123 https://t.co/t4C83dEARh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knocked out the #SOMN #PolarPlunge yesterday with a great set of friends! @sominnesota @ Thomas Beach (Lake Calhoun) https://t.co/MmJUp45ML3]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all the people who are shitting all over the Captain Marvel movie. You're hateful, sexist, pieces of shit. Hatin… https://t.co/dMT2yKsmpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pdacosta @joncoopertweets Thank you needed that with my Maker’s and coke]]></document><document><![CDATA[Irony: Donald Trump, the #Russian agent calls #Democrats haters of the US at #CPAC! Of course, the sycophantic #GOP… https://t.co/ig3CwtG4sp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know if you tag the NHLs pr twitter account they’ll actually do something about your request]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewYangVFA Firearms ownership/possession isn't a privilege.  It is a RIGHT as specified in our Constitution.  Y… https://t.co/uyg4DJhkWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanFromCambMA What makes Medford more supportive of inclusionary zoning compared to similar MA cities? @jessekb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestlingGifFri Vote goes to Sherri. Excellent manager, tough wrestler who made me believe she could more than hol… https://t.co/rsYQfkwRJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 Allen JV Tournament:  Flower Mound JV - 19 Frisco Independence JV - 1  FM Marcus JV - 9 Plano West JV - 2  Cop… https://t.co/LfGyi1SLAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes No man ever lied more than @realDonaldTrump. As someone wiser than me said, Trump is a man of no straigh… https://t.co/xuRn9aFV1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevantaeAubrey Hi, I have weekend 1 ticket that I’m looking to switch for a weekend 2 ticket, if you’re still interested DM me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenanthompson thank you so much for your wonderful words expressing what so many of us feel about @MsGladysKnight… https://t.co/L2hsWLTm2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when I get a slight cold and my nose get stuffy  https://t.co/wMKQObfsIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Universe map unearths 300,000 more galaxies https://t.co/u9OgbCeN3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[You must live in the backwoods. My African American friends are like family; they know respect isn’t a entitlement;… https://t.co/PPtwmAiJXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might be a good reason to allow priests to get married. To women. “Overseers should be of one wife...”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett @5000RoleModels Role Model...  "I will destroy the wisdom of the wise, and bring to nought the prud… https://t.co/ehZEZ2MXe1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFarm_87 Particularly because it’s the “patriots” which is what he really is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was asked “Why when men go through something, they rather neglect the one they with than actually talk?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarySharp1620 Too close. Coming back to Omaha or staying in Sioux Falls tomorrow since they won’t play til Monday night?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@booksNrulers THEY  demanded  more of me  than  just  info.  off  google,bing, yahoo..etc.   they  wanted  paper...… https://t.co/pvWYLPGjiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long overdue shot of @fiercestories and my matching @BearSkn underwear from Christmas #bearsofinstagram… https://t.co/GUoE4CDoaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamielinwilson @SloPro65 @RadioTexasLive @ParkerMcCollum George Strait?  Even he is well aware it’s a Rodney Crowell tune.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeaTurnerTV I'm up withya, watching - take a nap later so you can enjoy the 60s later today #warmways]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrekfanRick @LLAPawsper @BodyByStarfleet @MissAmyNelson @Tyranicus @ListeningToFilm @TrekFanLV @DrJenRows… https://t.co/4L4THavAN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[What got you started in the gym and what is keeping you going? - If you're starting to lift and starting your healt… https://t.co/OJGeEr919a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judaism’s view of good and evil manifests in yetzer hatov—“the good inclination”—and yetzer hara—“the evil inclinat… https://t.co/teBPcKvGle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@umbernhard @mcranechilders @philipbstark @vaELECT @BathCountyVA Hmmm...that UI looks very familiar...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@knarkill Likewise my friend. I forgot to mention I’m jealous of your fresh kicks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PMTS puts the FUN in FUNraising! 🎉💜 In 15 years, we’ve raised over $20 million for amazing charities. Let’s keep i… https://t.co/Zm0lrS8XkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellabyte Whatever you choose, you’ll probably need to change it in the future.  To answer this question properly,… https://t.co/ten8agmbJk]]></document></documents></author>