<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Thomas_Duncan @BernieSanders @realDonaldTrump He is running as a democrat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlusanSusan I like on one of the blooper reels Afghan Cas says something to Sam abt crossing the road and Sam says… https://t.co/NnkhufukRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maleritustin talk about your problems while buying more wild outfits ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to all @NTHS_Titans 2nd Quarter Scholars and Parents on a job well done. We look forward to celebra… https://t.co/XcPjmTAJSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[not enough esoteric wisdom here on twitter so here’s one for you: strength had her fingers removed in the maw of th… https://t.co/j6r9UGcT3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UBmenshoops congratulations on your 25th straight home victory and 18th straight home conference win! Most genuine… https://t.co/WMjsAWJlgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your brand is only as good as your reputation. It’s CRUCIAL you work tirelessly to protect it. #qualtricsX4 @richardbranson]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been waiting at the doctor 1 hour for my appointment -- but thanks to this mobile mini computer in my hand cal… https://t.co/r6KyiRk6UZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadLutzke @SadieHartmann I’m so glad! You’re welcome, Chad. And I really loved it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[T-minus 15 minutes till I ♥️ Pop Culture at the Port Orange Library!!!! #thewriteengle #popculture #ilovemyjob… https://t.co/ZAQIXKekzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTN24ve @luisgonzaloprz Gallardía es la lección que le dió este reportero al imbécil chavista madurista.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulNIKLAS3 Thank you for following me Paul. I appreciate it. Is that your Grandson? He's a real Cutie!! I hope yo… https://t.co/uHZM9bb8pK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ando_421 @cameronjhamill @khjelmgaard It’s not a rant, it’s an analysis. I see you have your own cogent legal argument prepared. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Balance is one of my favorite blends!! It’s actually the first @doterra blend that I tried and the reason I fell in… https://t.co/s9d6dZS4Qe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B1Gwbball @umdwbb @IowaWBB @RutgersWBB @umichwbball Go, LadyTerps!👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻🐢🏀🐢🏀🐢🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertKazinsky I can blame Bugs Bunny for that.... Gives me a good excuse to watch old cartoons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashaFarber I saw you last year to and showed you a video I took and you tweeted the exact same thing, love it 😂 https://t.co/cWIlFklld5]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s negativity in this world but at least we have the Jonas Brothers]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a loser teacher. I lose sleep every night thinking of how to do better for my students. I spend every minute a… https://t.co/ZhylZ0nWt0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder He’s decompensating in front of the whole world &amp; he’ll take anyone else down with him. a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carlito84428815 @DavidNakamura @benshapiro Not calling him out will NEVER yield to a deal either!  You are talking… https://t.co/uQcWt9g0Rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful in its loftiness, the joy of the whole earth, like the heights of Zaphon is Mount Zion, the city of the G… https://t.co/0eiieX0Emk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan and Caroline (available for adoption!) always manage to have tons of fun during their training sessions! 😍 M… https://t.co/TtYZCLD4Cc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonaldKlain @NicolleDWallace Donnie.  You have no morals and no ethics. That is why you find yourself unable to ta… https://t.co/g9wDYpjVY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimibobimi If it is your Lilith than youre extremely unconfrontational and passive when drunk. Also you may try to… https://t.co/cdjcGR6wyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miss_Peltier @littleBits @codeorg @60Minutes I’ve been doing this for years- https://t.co/82fARM6X9V &amp; little Bits. I feel VALIDATED!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaredMinary1 @rhisistance @WhiteHouse Do you wear your sheets to work. https://t.co/7DQHiyRCHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[KEEP YOUR COLON AND GI TRACT CLEAN EVERYDAY . AVOID THE EMBARRASSING BURPING , BACKUP , NAUSEA. GET IRON GUT TODAY… https://t.co/VYyx0Xnyuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I know what love is, it is because of you guys 😘😍🎈💕everyday I fall more in love with you guys 🤗❤️#lovelife… https://t.co/OYO0UVC9Ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@viewsfromdan @JeffreyGuterman @paulsperry_ @realDonaldTrump Wishing that a person would be hurt is the exact type… https://t.co/D3apRJPDV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traitor Trump, do the country and the world a favor and resign!  That will do our country so much good!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petitjean5567 @SethAbramson The IRS already has them, and probably can be made to turn them over...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously make my weekly pay at my job almost everyday on my phone... idk why I even work 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when the gym is so damn packed to where i can’t even find somewhere to do my thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen said he doubted that trumps taxes were under audit, as he had asked for a letter stating this and never received it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really planned this whole ass SoCal trip by myself including making sure I go to banda fest, norteñisimo, and la… https://t.co/9RIhPzqNNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericswalwell @44vreiki No she has NOT created more jobs‼️ That might ring true in Russia though‼️‼️😡📣🙄🤬😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need somebody who cares the way I do lol once I get this bag tho. I’ll know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine Do not trust this women, she is out to destroy our nation and our Christian faith! Anyone who goes ag… https://t.co/W9Ka6HcvuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@normangoldman @LindseyGrahamSC It certainly makes one think if all of them are compromised.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@COMANDER1 Se te salió el maracucho rajao! (Y se te cayó la cèdula tambiên) jeje]]></document><document><![CDATA[So very honored and surprised to receive this award. I’m spending the day with some amazing women who are making a… https://t.co/csLqcQdiEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DIRECTVNowHelp is there a reason why I cannot log into my app? I’ve tried 3-4 times and yes my login info is correct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I be obsessed with @shaymitch in @YouNetflix  I feel like there’s some weird irony there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Quin_288 If you think a man wearing a skirt is a loss of masculinity then you were never a man to begin with. Masc… https://t.co/UMC1pre4vF]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can also still purchase your #teamtommie t-shirts here:  Benefits will go to the Tommie Fund provided by… https://t.co/0tXZzVrd8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your friends and family haven't told you about my YouTube channel......they obviously don't love you.… https://t.co/6kBagLHwV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Rewind #Backstage #COCCosi @CanadianOpera #DressingRoom https://t.co/VNpvk4SuD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tool27lateralus @C3Nunez @richiesgenial Jajajaja wey, bájale a tu pedo TU. es twitter... la neta, el béisbol no es… https://t.co/jmLJhkpti4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiriaForsythe I did this for my entire life. It took two therapists to help me see this and one of them talked me… https://t.co/maG3HlwMmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhistleblowerNY @NVICLoeDown Vaccines are not 100% safe. But not vaccinating is extremely dangerous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EashJennifer @Pamelibrariland I came here to say this too! Women’s professions especially suffer from this trap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve got the same wide eyes — now they tell some stories • • • 📷: the brilliant @jennyanina (unedited) @ New York,… https://t.co/xaxRkxMGUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching last night’s #thewalkingdead Tonight on “How to Skin a Zombie”....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was the 3Ms: March, Massage, and manchimeansgood .  I was starving and wanted some warm food after my mas… https://t.co/JtUodMGl0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me word this differently...if there’s no food involved, I’m not coming!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[REPORT: Ocasio-Cortez Retweets Post from Supporter of Palestinian ‘Liberation’ Group | Sean Hannity https://t.co/Tqc9rDGRYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liz_berry22 I did that at sonic once when they reached for my money 🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t like those things at all.  I’ve used the microwaved inserts for warmth. I’m glad it happened before she had… https://t.co/4rheQBmKLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody say yeah! Intermission time. WOW! Fabulous production, and thos Lola is killing it! @KinkyBootsBway @jackiepklein #Kinkyboots]]></document><document><![CDATA[daaamnnnn, and he still won’t win a ‘ship. that’s how you know he really hated broadcasting. 🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJr  Thought you might like this one Bristol 2000 you almost wrecked him he hollered at Richard on the radio to… https://t.co/bd6a8NCMlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cephira @KaitlinBain @MayVOrtega @MayraC27 @ef_hou @PaulaCassidy14 @brookelewisa @RinconBianchi @goni_lessan… https://t.co/vrgCPEzdwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Transgression Culture: Wetter Gravity by Foreign Objects at @maxstaphouse — https://t.co/1p0HFiKAzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dictator Trump keeps trying to erode the conference that the US people have in the CIA, FBI, Justice Dept, any… https://t.co/uhsQkeeDrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our first #SundayBunday Double Shot comes courtesy of the handsome and charming @alex_mecum. Gorgeous 💜💜 https://t.co/fqIgdCCNhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hohumtweets @ssb1559 @TheTweetOfGod @mgmoody42 @POTUS He did, but God didn’t require it.   God will ask for proof… https://t.co/tegpS9MGma]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s an accomplishment to the@ but in today world taking on a trade is worth more then a degree unless your a nurse… https://t.co/YN66hyVp1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[She didn't want him to get up and leave her...#puppylove #dog #ILoveSoMd #somdrealestate #mysomdrealtor #somd… https://t.co/R4kR3hIlmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Whose fault is that? You ppl are disgusting blaming everyone but the person who is the cause.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerKaminski4 @UberEats @DoorDash I bet you your Uber driver did it to eat your food lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bd just keep asking if I have a bf bc he having dreams I got one. I keep having dreams I have one too, just waiting on the universe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LittleBlackDressParty was amazing with new co-workers!  Cheers to a new job and a bright future! @ JW Marriott Gra… https://t.co/uNM0kNRNVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tetris for the switch is MADDENING!!! It's organized chaos with a good amount of yelling at the screen thrown in fo… https://t.co/ClER0taGj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsJRReiter Oh goodness!  That’s the best gift a teacher could ever get!  😊 https://t.co/Idg35I13E8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoodsRoods OMG A little ray of sunshine on a miserable day! Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s been a knock at the door the jury uses, and a clerk went behind the door. Could be anything. My guess is a… https://t.co/ngpIGrBbgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're here! Country Buffet &amp; spotted The Pentagon on the bus ride to Arlington. #DevilsRunDC 🇺🇸 😈 https://t.co/cLIaEL2lBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KdeVosAuthor @KatRushall @AndreaBrownLit This gif is just a picture from our most recent agency meeting! ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need to see Ella Mai in concert someone hook it up w/tickets 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always said that these 3 were used as « scapegoat » to protect Ty Thompson and Runcie.  They though we would go a… https://t.co/OILmR0UdIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[A robot just delivered me a spa treat @MO_BOSTON... and I’m living in the future https://t.co/8yDWB1HFGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miaajudy @mini_raposa Dsclp me meter mas vi na TL, isso parece eczema. Principalmente por aparecer junto com nervo… https://t.co/VdiUJENdnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drion97 @mmurraypolitics @maggieNYT Those are not on the level of the policies being promoted today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winetraveleats @Dracaenawines @MadHattersNYC @Fiery01Red @suziday123 @WeLikeDrinking1 @HHLifestyleTrav… https://t.co/WRgAJTEIP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freefromfarm @JusticeforStan1 @iris19jones @thewoodieslive @amymaytrust @GemmaEvans @foodallergyuk We need to keep… https://t.co/5Zhb0Fk9dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AwardsDaily ...so, they are deniers, but they watched the doc. #BelievetheVictims]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Washington Post: A Houston socialite berated a mixed-race couple at their baby’s party. Then the video got out.… https://t.co/hCjwaoC0aT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Macabre Japanese creations &amp; erotic #art fill the space at @darkartemporium! Have a peek in my new blog post:… https://t.co/Kva6XAMDJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Omar has a child fathered by her brother wouldn’t the child be more retarded than her,.you know inbreeding.?????🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dfalls1552 @man007_b @TankIncU @bedevilme666 @63Rockman @robjh1 @RodHillis1 @codeofvets @Lathenerd @TheSteveKon… https://t.co/b07YkwGd08]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1: I have accepted a challenge from @EMillerFCPSAA to post #7booksIlove - no explanations, no reviews, just cov… https://t.co/cB3MGnzBVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yankeecannuck @PinkSparkleYums @steve45220 @dennisdiclaudio @MugabeJonathan @nypost We were talking about reducing… https://t.co/ZcmSn4MLWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Middleboro, Massachusetts https://t.co/KVaeRpibrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, husbands car was totaled and they came and  took it away. Luckily it will get paid off my insurance. So, now… https://t.co/n9DXN3LK9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rbud76 @emrazz Signing Bibles is a thing if it's a gift. My father gave me a copy of The Living Bible when I was a… https://t.co/YdvhextGjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know so many people my age making big moves towards they’re life dreams and getting closer and closer and that is so damn inspiring]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCoker13 @ivyjofreeman @hardhouz13 @LA_Karma1 @L_a_w_a_n_n_a @BlkSantaX @MrsblksantaX @suzystays @tlccourville… https://t.co/KwLYpYNGQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear lord i don’t know where this is going what the hell did Miller and Laurel’s brother do?  #HTGAWM https://t.co/4pnXcbzAkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beer and basketball (@ McShane's in Ypsilanti charter township, MI) https://t.co/wTJiYeStcx]]></document></documents></author>