<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Yes it looks absurd... but most #ewaste ends up just like this. Piling up in waste bins, and landfills across North… https://t.co/m3PziJLLyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicagotribune Few will recall Mr. Sarbanes’ previous legislation which has dramatically hurt business with onerous rules and regulations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump Hot, but I can also do iced coffee, coffee ice cream, Frappuccino, and on and on...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have an amazing day today my friends love all of you so much 💖 https://t.co/UBSfs8zlBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuqHonors I was drawn to both for implicit and explicit spiritual Allusions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__SpudMullen @Mitch_montana77 It is Lebron fault doe. On paper it look like he hooping but if u watch the games he… https://t.co/TpF22TSl3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyguy0012 @KeeganYoung1 Trust me, it was a master level negotiation that this kid pulled off https://t.co/tCAuJH0UPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmyfallon the never ending Kardashian story #ImproveAMovieWithOneWord]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta go home and open up a credit card for all the @theacesofficial merch @nadine_p64 told me about tonight 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is twitter enabling my depression or am I just elitist in my idea of humor and lonely: the ultimate question]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing how many of the “memorable” scenes are in the first half of this movie. Because I can’t remember a dam… https://t.co/OHCvNTtDUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[New rules: pin - in or out? #golf #golfing #golfer #golfaddict #golfobsessed #instagolf #golfstagram #twitter… https://t.co/wYPMuMVUr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THDDonovanD21 @LarissaGreenTHD @JabarrBean @WesternTHD @PS_RSM @superdave427 @JW_Floor Love it. Very creative!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, introducing an inheritance tax like the rest of the G7 would add an estimated $20 billion over ten years, acc… https://t.co/iquB8q0s7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCCURadio is in your community. Please support our programming. Call with your gift 888-454-7800 or give online… https://t.co/lLTT6YG6My]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wendy_love daaaaamn! Usually coffee knocks me out, but you definitely need to sleep lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been super busy these last months with other builds and projects helping friends and networking that I’ve totally n… https://t.co/OLiA6DhgFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skeels pokes in a line drive that died in front of Ward in CF. C. Carolina take the lead, 3-2, on the singl as the… https://t.co/yioyJ4CuZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[i dont want to leave home for college bc i can’t leave my dog uh..i mean my parents]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun day for the Riegelhaupt boys. @NYRangers vs @Capitals #lgr !! https://t.co/RQE5DRb8aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyLondonnn Since u not marrying me u better settle down w a man thats wholesome, loving and caring af or imma really be tight]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started therapy in January and ive never been soooo I love with myself yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of this is because I care a lot about those issues.   But it’s also a way to tell if candidates recognize big… https://t.co/AHppb3UvFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevKeithBritt If someone is unfit the 25th amendment should be used, Ovomit could have been an example]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillyFPC @JuniorClubSA @BarranquillaFC @JoseChunga12 @FabioPovedaRuiz @Data1924 @carlos7bacca @SOLO_JUNIOR… https://t.co/abl3SJsYjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the world go by... #EmpireStateBuilding #NYC #NewYork Now we are back at the hotel, on advice from the loc… https://t.co/zEU7np1BZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow more and more big thick’s are coming into my mentions and I ain’t mad lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing pic that can mean many things. Life is going to stretch you and throw a curveball your way at times. Keep t… https://t.co/5oNWOSvaiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlyfrenette Just like I consider do you want to get breakfast? as a sext.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“R” you ready people?!?!?!?  Let’s go! https://t.co/149De8d3Ns via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating the most amazing woman I know today, my Mom!!! 💜😍🍾💐 #HappyBirthdayDonna #ILoveYouMom #MyMomIsTheBEST… https://t.co/WOcggj3CVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Match Marketing is looking for teammates like you. See our latest #fieldmarketing job openings, including "Part-Tim… https://t.co/kiB5SIJOHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bayleeworth 😂 there are constantly an infinite number of reasons to tweet this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started remolding my truck &amp; drinking beer at 9 this morning. Probably gonna be an early day for me🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @jonathanvswan @foxandfriends Good to know that you're doing America's business this morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichanConnor @colindickey @citizenforwell And you may be saying that’s great but look at it from my perspective, a… https://t.co/rbb0exCIyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judging by the responses this tweet generated, Twitter is chock full of Parent of the Year candidates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nearly 34 percent will leave. We should have a citizen legislature. Forcing us to have a legislature that doesn’t o… https://t.co/puDc2x9Ehq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OregonJOBS2 It depends how she refers to herself. More than 12 hours and 1 minute a day, she is Stormy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChunSwae__ @IamKickz Yea!! Plus when you think you can walk out especially you very known they be watching.. I kno… https://t.co/jxMicWLBLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JParnell1 hi Justin, is your personal 540 Powered Cube list available anywhere?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @DanielYoung__  and family!!  I have a feeling  this is the first of many offers!!  #Blessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sun setting at Jimmy’s Crows Nest... @ Jimmy's Crows Nest https://t.co/tEEb3nJ2DW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you purchase clothing over 500 it’s for ig stunting not for you to wear]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hear a low groaning noise from outside and think "that's just a cow on the farm down the road." then I remember I… https://t.co/49S0u4mE5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les cuento que ace frío 🥶 aquí en #NY y eso que estoy afrentó de mi casa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ciaomiabella17 @mommamia1217 @Bornabrit1 If the GOP has their way it will be soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonErik7171 Na I don’t think they’ll actually boo him I think they knew he wasn’t coming back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let the games begin (@ Louis Armstrong New Orleans International Airport - @no_airport in Kenner, LA) https://t.co/3BCxRTfLDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is your #weather today?? #marcoislandwinter #marcoisland #florida #saltlife #vacationtime #Beachfront #condos… https://t.co/4NN0vtcSqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Undefeated champs #instramglesspat @ EC Lawrence Soccer fields https://t.co/y3h4KyNktG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that is one way to protect your head only just riding a bike motor on it. 🤔🚴‍♂️ @ Southpark Meadows https://t.co/31OGh17SZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Although circumstances may change in the blink of an eye, people change at a slower pace. Even motivated… https://t.co/Ki0Vq1i6nC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#48 #SendDonuts 🍩🍩🍩  @rodeodonut cupcakeroyale @ Cupcake Royale https://t.co/dxASdW28VT]]></document><document><![CDATA[In news that maybe only @PatClarke27 cares about:  PRESS RELEASE Beginning with the Spring season, my hairball hock… https://t.co/magBgaMRkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamKanyeDaily Hey my wife how is my ass pussy and tits my dick miss and it bigger then. Kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sellitti_MR @anthony77631293 @lagatta4739 @BrindusaB1 @BPerrionni @karmendida @Hakflak @AntonellaLaTor6… https://t.co/poVQld9FPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joanieliza @byDavidGardner That's just crazy lol! Hahaha!! "Silver linings playbook" was great for one? If you did… https://t.co/DDtIUcV13Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is amazing. For all that life has thrown at this guy, to be there in that moment must have felt unbelievable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to Judge Collins @Domjd04 and Sgt Williams @RoyWmsJr for taking the time to visit with our students… https://t.co/mEQxuIwDLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Lawrence do you think #KimJongUn was watching you’re show last night?? See NO eyeglasses on Kim Ju Unnon him toda… https://t.co/FJ9kAkEkJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@52Rural @MikeDoak4 Yes it did. Oh, and he signed the legislation making MLK a national holiday so that]]></document><document><![CDATA[i found a youtube video of a guy getting mad at how easy life is for minecraft players nowadays, he’s like a minecraft baby boomer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No matter how much you lie, fabricate, or misdirect there is more evidence than ever you were a tr… https://t.co/GxArxVkwKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting on some bloodwork, “I’ll be there for you” came on the muzak. At some point songs like that cease to be son… https://t.co/Q06tn35K0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bpz00 I've been watching Temptation Island and I have no idea why lmfao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to have lunch before I see movie. (@ Golden China in Stephenville, TX) https://t.co/fhDSUtmzTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Public_Citizen @RepSarbanes @RBReich @AyannaPressley @MsPackyetti @LOLGOP @IlhanMN @Alyssa_Milano @IndivisibleTeam… https://t.co/QNHfPMr8TC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Statistical Programmer II - https://t.co/jNAiX1wg5i #Actuarial #Buffalo, NY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyway, I loved literally all my teachers except that one individual. I hope and pray they have to deal with really… https://t.co/94t3eNbvl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hawaii it is (@ John F. Kennedy International Airport - @jfkairport in Queens, NY) https://t.co/MmH4oP7cLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BUKnights @BaseballKnights Phillips was outstanding today on the mound as the starter. Congrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec @realDonaldTrump And thanks to quality people like #SarahSanders helping him,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hockeybtch No fret, I was just worried, it looks just  check, how far can get, take your account and just get your… https://t.co/7jrxrzh8F0]]></document><document><![CDATA[To boldly go where no Pilsner has gone before... @lefthandbrewing Polestar Pilsner on tap @ the Fish House in Peori… https://t.co/KARUHt111J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Locadoes @BeijingPalmer @tianchao731 Sure, Vietnamese Latin writing system was a big boost for literacy efforts. T… https://t.co/QgI1j9zH8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Rose &amp; Crown Pub &amp; Dining Room - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/nAlpIkJQX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillyrexYT se filtró el pase de batalla en Xbox https://t.co/gRtWq5Nw2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[tom riddle before opening the chamber of secrets https://t.co/6NDlC0hOJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BishopJakes @FirstLadyJakes What a distasteful statement for a preacher to say]]></document><document><![CDATA[Size 12 ds 160 shipped.... @ New York, New York https://t.co/d99DDJzU5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching moment.. Feliz is playing great again tonight. https://t.co/RpPFLW0jVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chief Morales meet Chief Rojas.. From today at stmaryskidsny #superheroes day. #NYPDConnecting #CopsNKids Photo b… https://t.co/diwcF0Drmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I continue to fear for my safety &amp; my employer appears to fail to understand this. This is VERY concerning]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my opinion, a small potatoes portfolio compared to institutions, this is the essence of #TrendFollowing &amp;… https://t.co/t3ib15OVIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[AB’s MADDEN CURSE WAS THE BUFFALO BILLS. I’m dead😂😂 https://t.co/aDaobrDnmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure wish this one would make it back in the song list... #TwoForTuesday #2of2 #RnR  Dokken - Heaven Sent (Official… https://t.co/5kyKxL664p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone can build. Some are born to build.  - Create to be great. - I will never stop creating, building and growing… https://t.co/YfWNQIVzE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol I have no clue, but it makes facing Monday a little more palatable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 45 degrees out and I’m wearing shorts because I’m an Ohioan!  But I also have the seat warmer on in my car bec… https://t.co/f8oXBpjMmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need my self a boo I can send her funny videos and she sending them to me too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlaiddWolfe I mean the disposable face masks, not the hazmat respirator I have in my icon photo lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[BRO: I’ll have an Angry Orchard.  @jorgeparody: Woodchuck’s the only cider I’ve got.  BRO: Do you have Redd’s Apple… https://t.co/oSocM4pXjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexHinesBitch @tuckbill34 @brennenjjohn @Carlos_Film Alright just watched it. Very good, got chills many times. https://t.co/uhRZ2nLCp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itspoots @marchmadness @tableau @Stephanie_Roxy @tableaupublic Nicely done, Jason! I like the almost "chalkboard" aesthetic to this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowledge about God will get you nothing. Divine oneness/friendship with God will get you everything your soul longs for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanMann777 @CurlingCanada @TSNCurling Don’t you have a Mai Tai or surf lessons to attend to?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickyxcamargojr Bingo. Great opponent for his style in the perfect moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dang. Wish I was back on a #MardiGras float right now ...✨ 🦹🏼‍♂️✨ #KreweOfKingArthur https://t.co/VZHdoHIRuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maldito el Soldado que levanta las armas contra su pueblo...Será que no tienen familia y tienen luz, agua, y medici… https://t.co/CDsGC7ZKa2]]></document></documents></author>