<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Can I please be a student teacher already I’m tired of working at the habit?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another kiddo hidden in the background. #hornshiddenintheshadow @ Firth, Nebraska https://t.co/frHspKyACW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of focusing on and eliminating the cause doesn't make sense. Putting a bandage on the body that has a severed head won't work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joicehasselmann @erwalio @jairbolsonaro nossa mudou a vida das mulheres.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Building a binaural head! Taking name and accessory suggestions 😹  #researchproject #binauralaudio… https://t.co/PI6PH7LyRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoloresOfCourse So dusty, but not here in NYC 2 blocks from the city bus garage!its so dusty over in this area you can’t have rugs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshpincus She asked a question yesterday “How often do you wash your hands after using bathroom in your own house… https://t.co/xFWXXpCVq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoniBolin *like if your patients pee in the corner of the room because they’re drunk assholes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I got new running shoes and went running and made lunches for the rest of the week and thought I had my life… https://t.co/qzMA1pmI6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every state....this should be a minimum. Expecting the leader of the USA not just to release his or her taxes but a… https://t.co/KCuB64VIgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW bloomingdales #AQUA spring summer advertising #photographer @hansneumann #artdirector lauren_bockow #stylist… https://t.co/jH3VEHkDsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to Thursday for @WomenVenture #emPOWERSocialHour with @heatherbrown21 from @WCCO! It's been fun pla… https://t.co/WvZubavVQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only appropriate right? @apinv pgatour #homework #bayhillclubandlodge @ Payson, Arizona https://t.co/q4XInm5rG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericagreenway @BlaineStewart @JessicaNLarche @MHendersonWTKR https://t.co/AU0dqHkY8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beautiful thing about humanity is that we are all different. What may be best for you can be completely differe… https://t.co/TxMHDV8S5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[bro two weeks from rn i’ll be in NYC fuqqin it up w my friends can u believe]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to choose which IT conferences to attend https://t.co/Qav3vKCfrh via @CIOonline]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again, while there is still a long way to go in terms of represention of women, especially women of color, trans wo… https://t.co/NmYcgWUPnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Immoral? What do you call it then if they made the choice to join terrorists that are a threat to Canada? And who’s… https://t.co/fkqCmleIai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Knowita47918362 @DawsonSField @jray_redfever @geoffb5 @52VikingConv @oldmanluvsmineo @deplorablejam @LanaAshford1… https://t.co/5es7TeMHgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get almost to Barbourville going to work..the sky dead ass started dropping snow outta nowhere?]]></document><document><![CDATA[More like me checking where my mans atcause he’s not answering his phone]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my aunt says I have to go to the doctor and get this finger checked out... I’m just doing myself a favor and cut… https://t.co/tkpbKAu4QB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @realDonaldTrump If you could only see what is going through his head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happened to stop, drop &amp; roll? What a dummy? Don't play with fire!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickiknowsnada Is it because he just heard his 1st charge for lying will be 15-28 yrs on Charge one.And the Judge… https://t.co/JMWlwOiwPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad told me “no more fuck boys” and I was like “yah we kno but where the fuck did you even learn that term?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm ready this morning at @SavannahToyota1 .  Buy a new vehicle and win a prize. https://t.co/nCkPGwRwFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[a (f)ie(r)cely (a)n(t)icipated thread will be arri(v)ing somet(i)me this week. y’all are (n)ot r(e)ady for thi(s)   👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got told “your kids are going to be so beautiful and it’s because you are a beautiful women inside and out” UGH 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RHOCC1 I don't think Dimitri is a pervert. He may like to get it on, he does have 3 kids u kno. I think he's a ric… https://t.co/6171hQNdCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1N4PROJECT I’m looking for exhibitors for the first ever Student-Athletes Expo in Chicago. Do you services athlete… https://t.co/w3xcWHOtVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @AliVelshi The PA security reported promoted by Hickton is very concerning. It buried its criticism of… https://t.co/9qwTcEfP5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 Our planet is going through an Energy Shift,  or....   TRUMP HAS THE NUCLEAR CODE AND @jaredkushner TRI… https://t.co/LJ3UCX22gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[If somebody wanna charge whatever they wanna charge then that’s their prerogative.. idk why anybody gives a damn. A… https://t.co/jGWspHBomW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlakandBlack @Watershedd @adamknott777 Agreed. I know Fosters would not be my choice...😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaivanShroff I say EVERY candidate, regardless of political party, MUST release their tax returns.  PERIOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nprpolitics @NPR What ABOUT YOU? You got caught in a lie recently. How will you explain your complicity in daddy’s… https://t.co/zeasSsrVc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very exciting times!! Tickets sales are open for tonight’s game, snatch em up friends!! https://t.co/UulYGdYuYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that the @jonasbrothers are back let’s hope they go on tour and come back to my old high school, because you gu… https://t.co/7SOcji75Hj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently I’m in a shit ton of open relationships or I’m a cheater 🤔🤔reagardless...I love my guys. 🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[miles_of_styles_  gave me an amazing hair cut. I love it! Thank you Kaley! #haircut  #studio7 #greathairdontcare @… https://t.co/1tTDULfSH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one else I’d rather walk 18,000 steps with 💗🏰 https://t.co/xnersDOE6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wmanovsubstnc @ewarren Another of the 'gifts'.@theDemocrats have given women is making their own infants disposabl… https://t.co/gt2xahLdPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This follows the Catholic Church’s pregnancy prevention program their leaders have endorsed for decades: Sodomize s… https://t.co/uNCoxoJlu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m seriously fed up of people coming up with these expectations of me?! And then getting mad at me when I turn out… https://t.co/f1R1gJtLEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stlpcs @MelanieMetz6 @Dvscott81Scott @bbusa617 @robyn_lance @RodHillis1 @GeanineC @BundyGP @krunalley… https://t.co/1bkQjwjUdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrRCorcoran @EducEndowFoundn Where can I see you speak on this, or read what you’ve written?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobsonwong @cheesemonkeysf @averypickford @MrKitMath @Depicmath @mrdardy @jreulbach @DrKChilds @parkermathed Stude… https://t.co/3l325Ufqvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M2Madness @NormieWokeAF Was Kim just asking for some popcorn????????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj Drugs Flowing Across The Border?  Most the Fentanyl is hidden in Big Rig Shipments at Ports Of Entry...The… https://t.co/gxX8YQwvTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDawg_97 @JNastyyy_13 Sooooooo what if I just blow you upside your head]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNNews1 show the band please Texas Tech vs ISU #cycleONEnation #bandmom #please]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s just something about the voyeurism of your every day joe just doing normal and cute shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CickNollis can’t wait to kiss you so soon babe but until then enjoy peach hoops 4 me pls]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even remember how long we lasted but it was such a good time. I remember Valentine’s Day, he was the first… https://t.co/5mpNK3Egai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to #IDCDirections next week in Boston! Hope it gets s little warmer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kill 58,000 and you are revered as POTUS, PORTRAIT hung in the white house and capital..kill 1 person and you die b… https://t.co/ayq4gJ2QCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mathteacherleader brittanymcantrell is leading powerful conversations in Math PLCs today at Prospect Elementary! @… https://t.co/ZR2WktkYMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billboardcharts @billboard @Madonna @MariahCarey @JanetJackson @rihanna @olivianj @ArethaFranklin @katyperry… https://t.co/91mcAYnZ0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steeleio_ @NapsOnTopOfNaps RIGHT ?!?!?!? Like I’m shook AS FUCK!!!!!! I thought the cut off wasn’t until the 22nd-23rd smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stefsanjati No question just positive vibes. Wishing you a blessed day gf ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Branded #postbrand #curate38 #formasraras @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/xpl23ySN6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[“as a server you knew how you would be paid going into the job! it’s not my obligation to tip you” just say that yo… https://t.co/xsO2rgQQju]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen says he is in fear for his family. Talking about threats against his father in law also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pro choice, pro life issue doesn’t affect how people vote. I made sure it is not an issue at the ballot box.]]></document><document><![CDATA[More than 200 cases of water are headed to Alabama in the morning from Mississippi @WJTV https://t.co/VG6BjuR9tP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angry Utie stickers. @ Asheboro, North Carolina https://t.co/sAXLorWr3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like a Prayer: la provocación religiosa de Madonna que se convirtió en un hit global https://t.co/CpMoVoEZ9P via… https://t.co/PZLr2ciLEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not only that they won, but how thoroughly and completely they did it. #Raptors]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Global Issues Club kicked off Pink Shirt Day 👚 celebrations this week by selling cupcakes in support of… https://t.co/xMEiw7mwdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christenczech @LeonardPittsJr1 Agree. That wasn’t my point. While you may be insulted others wouldn’t be. It’s not that deep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My rule is that I only have one drink if I want to maintain my dignity and I’ve had two double gin and tonics so to… https://t.co/ErZQxT6QCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @Bakari_Sellers Congress did no oversight !! FIRE THEM ALL !! Costs US the taxpayers. Its their damn fault!! T… https://t.co/nSQw3MeOAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[If they are this fascinated by Gaga &amp; Bradley, imagine how absorbed they’d have been in Us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a good note, our past two interviews have been perfect! Building a wonderful Lifespan team 🤗 #abasolutions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates @dog_rates Jackson and Daisy, afternoon snoozles 😍🐶🐶😴 https://t.co/SwuGWqmONT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mind has been aching from replaying moments of the last time we made love. I miss you so fucking much. Please co… https://t.co/aTVgqLQQqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[💚 Spring Vibes 💚 Published in beaunumagazine with  Photographer: @psychobabblers  2nd shooter johannsma  Wardrobe S… https://t.co/N6THrdda1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 ball down.. my liver is not prepared for next weekend #rallywithKen https://t.co/GiFD67LIHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you put a face to tragedy it becomes more personal. RIP to all who lost their lives. @ Gainesville, Florida https://t.co/rpckegTia3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mistydemeo Some of you have never gone wrong about it and you don't want to go back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes to all of this.  TY to #franceshseih #drpratimagupta and @JaniceForBART for reminding us that sustaining our mo… https://t.co/jJiru8aGgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden #PeeNce is not a good man, not a nice man : #PeeNce is exactly every #evil #RePUbFUglyGreedyOldPervert]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT SCHOOL BOARD MEETING TO ATTEND ON MARCH 5th at 11:15AM at 600 SE 3rd Ave, Ft Laud  School Board members w… https://t.co/Xw81jHBvNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I’ve learned today so far today: -derivatives of trig functions.             -and Twitter rabbit holes are a… https://t.co/WwSvtEtEHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was very wrong about that and being here, with family very close to me, I don't know what I would do without them… https://t.co/g4xnjVJpHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took them some trial and error to find the right spot to record their bounces. #designthinking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prosecuted for treason.  Their actions are harming our Country and your Presidency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HBODocs @HBO 1.2 million watched only? LOL! And the Real Housewives of Atlanta beat your ratings? LOL! The Walking… https://t.co/098Q3KlH1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Derail (Abandoned Station Conversation), 16 × 22" #oilpainting on linen. Though I painted it, I'm not sure what… https://t.co/h6itltpjEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ring Ding or a Ho Ho? That is the question? Bahaaaaa LOL! #NBAAllStar #drunkedy #dingdong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anchorbound @nancylevine @femininecollect The casting agent for sleeper cell thought we did date.  I think blake r… https://t.co/2yUt345EMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[McTeacher’s Night was a huge success! We raised $758 for our 5th grade activities. BizTown and Aquatica, here we co… https://t.co/cWvhQGmHC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[its cool having spring break early until you have to go back to class and everyone else is on break]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmeLentino @paynepepperjam @Jaykle @JEdnaMae @jonmagnussonof @_chris_leon @composing4you @sydbergevin… https://t.co/A5T1m3xXVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[laugh and move on. A real man knows how to pet a cat. | 28 Ways To Spot A Real... #laughter #chuckle #smirk… https://t.co/J9sqy849xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Tyler_Grant This was me two nights ago. Kept repeating Phil. 4:6 to myself over and over. I frequently just ha… https://t.co/m71Wzmds2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else get annoyed by the major focus on the “magic” of sample size calculations? Other than alerting peo… https://t.co/nPz5nU5eAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very happy birthday to Mr. M - another great #mitzmoment faena @ Faena Miami Beach https://t.co/ueTMWqCT2r]]></document></documents></author>