<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[She tripping and it's only Valentine's, could you imagine her birthday 🤦🏼‍♀️  First of all, what did she get him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Pizza (216) - @216pizza in Cleveland, OH https://t.co/3iWXI1rrpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Embassy Staffers Say Jared Kushner Shut Them Out of Saudi Meetings https://t.co/cP7VyZ3zBj via @thedailybeast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol. I want this to be the least amicable, most public &amp; fame whorish  break  ever.., where she spills ALL his ☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAG4All @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @POTUS Praise God from all whose blessings flow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OSCARS 2019: Spike Lee, Marvel, Gaga notch first Oscars at Academy Awards #Fox35 https://t.co/XYh4RxK2Dk]]></document><document><![CDATA[if u dont play an instrument i don’t think i can ever fall in love with u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out the new Brown Room with a Gin Fashion. Liking the new digs and the new bar! Good job colleenbashaw  an… https://t.co/bZowVxkSFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets I will be SHOCKED to see Trump and his Crime Family brought to justice...it is all very disheartening...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright everyone, now that I've studied the heck out of jazz, if I identify that a song has a 12-bar blues or Rhyth… https://t.co/CzfPL1J5q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t get my tv to connect to wifi why isn’t my boyfriend awake to help me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course I’m sure that’s not what they were aiming for...I think mostly they wanted more war....]]></document><document><![CDATA[laying down the truth tomorrow since people want to believe peoples lies, i’m done staying quiet. have your popcorn ready😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[Among Democrats/Independents Who For President - https://t.co/UXOyuU77k8 https://t.co/JLxhU65MbN | Please vote and share!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to the gym 💪🏾 it’s nice #SpringComing @ South Bronx https://t.co/ra3rCADIzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer I’m sick that they have him on without asking about pending legal struggles that have splattered on him. He’s irrelevant]]></document><document><![CDATA[I rather be alone tonight, you can say i love you through the phone tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @SenMcSallyAZ Help people like  Christine Blasey Ford, you mean?  You frakking #hypocrite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it April yet!? Lol I just wanna go to Vegas already and see Aerosmith 😁😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jayyyne i don’t know how to attach a video because i’m a dumb idiot but this one:  https://t.co/jZo7Q0rKL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Curio by @fernsonbrewing at @gratabar — https://t.co/DfqQMfAs8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snowflake33470 @Barbaradye921 Do they ever send private messages? Asking too much, or maybe just creeps?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have so much shut due from the one day i was gone friday and it was all due tuesday and i’ve done none of it bc i… https://t.co/tQWV9HUKNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but if you have a brand new phone and your fingernails done you should not be receiving WIC checks 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very powerful to see all of the #DayofEmpathy events across America. We will be in #AZ @reinventreentry @Televerde… https://t.co/nuLygKhBEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 am and wondering if it’s Satan trying to knock down my bedroom door, or my spazz ass cats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear to god @TheBiancaDelRio is the woman I aspire to be. https://t.co/TpUCYEZxu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tippsysake I`m Professional crystal cup manufacturer、if you need pls contact me .all of my products are handmade a… https://t.co/L6BX79oNj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Self-growth should be a focus for everyone. Once you see that growth is there... you’ll never stop! #RISEUp… https://t.co/66gyMOVDli]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extremely annoyed that i don’t have wireless headphones at this current point in time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your in the neighborhood come see me and my amazing class perform tonight @ucbtla on Sunset. Tickets are only $5… https://t.co/Fsosnv40m1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told my mom about the rumors of the Jonas Brothers reunion and she says, “well they better! They’re brothers!” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want some bomb ass food but don’t even feel like chewing I’m so tired]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's think about Clinton and the one lie that started the impeachment, now think about the actions of Trump over t… https://t.co/P1Q0OjcKa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haleymillah walked in while I was showering to country music and goes “it sounds like a hoedown in here! Yeehaw!” 🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you could not get enough of Thor earlier, here are ten more pictures to scroll through. #ThortheCorgi #dogs… https://t.co/xTh62T06xf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@restingbface_ ❤️❤️❤️ It doesn’t even feel real lol some days I’m like fuck this I’m out then I remember it’s literally only 60 more days 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kdyrt49 So far it’s been for the worse, for the indigenous people but it’s better for the black Americans. We do n… https://t.co/fHAwl24A6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_Legend1976 Done!!! Al Green is doing his thing here, song it Al!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I talked to a good friend on the phone for 2 hours. I may never hear from her again. We wept. Tomorrow, I’m… https://t.co/WOAwdgwJQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angela Bassett has darker skin than Tina Turner. Should she not have played her then? I’m curious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTraceyJr @shayne571 @wlawren90 @DonCheadle She has a 90% lifetime rating from the League of Conservation Voters… https://t.co/EAa7sGLV5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityofGreenbelt held a fantastic Black History Program last Sunday! So glad that @GreenbeltMS 🐻 was involved!  It’… https://t.co/BeEh0MguiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a Marvelous Monday.. To all in #LE STAY SAFE https://t.co/q1zLfDQrCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating one of the most important influences in my life - her work started shaping my world at 18 months and st… https://t.co/8OFLFfefMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenberlincoop @JCoopJR27 Happy, Happy @JCoopJR27 ... man it seems like yesterday. 🎂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wear nates clothes more then I wear my own, they’re so much more comfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[genital based feminism isolates and enforces the idea that having a vagina is enssential to womanhood and is trans… https://t.co/kMowDbEu55]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hellboy (2019 Movie) New Trailer “Red Band” – David Harbour, Milla Jovov... https://t.co/lhzI5heD9d (OMG)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 18th Birthday to my best friend and my sister💕 so glad you have stuck by my side and thankful for all the mem… https://t.co/JzVr5fnAI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@softly_sighing2 And your eyelashes are 🔥!  You go girl! Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣😂                                                   then realization how / why did we get here...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Except for the killed babies who you torture to death and either throw in garbage or sell for parts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AMLObipolar siempre transgresor y anárquico #PobreMexico https://t.co/kWg6MD1cWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StreetSmarts001 Only a fuckstick that worships reality tv fucktards will insult peolle who argue facts and logic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickyDavila Me I'm sure there are many sweating in the sheets tonight! https://t.co/QCVNcorR3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump they are the party of hate and abuse they abuse their power and it is time for investigations… https://t.co/JZPtdSFvrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you ever notice on @TheGoodWife_CBS Josh Charles aka Will Gardner &amp; Alicia Florrick aka Juliana Margulies are both lefties? Cool....]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Z100NewYork has your tickets to a private @jonasbrothers show tonight in NYC! https://t.co/ND4heAXkCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ILoveFrogs2011 @RagingGayCons Your right only 100% true American Patriots should be able to hold a seat in office.… https://t.co/M24p82W2PL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebraPlumlee1 I hope your dream comes true https://t.co/JjVOQ9gWdk #writerslife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariofigueroa_ I love you so much brother happy 21st fucking birthday!!! https://t.co/cMqaFgZyG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time is so mucked up in my head right now. Being home constantly and not being able to do anything really does thing to a person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kids talk about Mr. G all the time. The other morning they were so excited to see what color he’d dye his hair i… https://t.co/nCUPTubyXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adrianeisoverit This got me good. 😂 Love that he’s so honest with you. You’re clearly doing something right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing better than some delicious fresh veggies! Thank you to my friend and colleague @juliedabrusin for inviting… https://t.co/f6RIB6Vt8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smigsie @BillyIdol I hope you get to see Billy in the UK...I got to meet him when he performed @FMKirbyCenter here...great guy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Something's Happening In This Place by James Grear on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/CHzV8oPMm7 https://t.co/Jm5rhlbJ5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy once you get into a relationship your “friends” disappear. And it really sucks. Especially when you real… https://t.co/HZcviXPhYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[And not put in the hands of jurors that look racist or have committed racial acts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Championship Saturday @PalAthletics Finals start at 2PM come see the top gymnasts in our State #ihsa https://t.co/SawXjbxLd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AztecaNoticiaGT @MPguatemala Corruptos y miedosos porque saben que ella gana la presidencia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[she’s got a pocket full of nothin, nobody tells her no. https://t.co/VfXnSHxBrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matinee_ca That’s a good point! I’ve seen it three times in theatre too, which ties my top flicks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, that's enough of that. I just had to get up to eat a tortilla with peanut butter. It's 6 A.M on a Sunday and I'm going back to bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing the final prep for a talk tomorrow on #PlasticPollution... to a group of chefs for a #seafood symposium! 🦐🦀🐟🐙… https://t.co/nbjGJvZloy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddedillard I had to run down the hall and be out before the toilet finished flushing. I don’t know what I was af… https://t.co/8lwauf56GZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebbieGibson Uh oh he’s ready to go! Has the Energizer Bunny beat! PS I’m loving the sofa lounge behind him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had such fun with this kitchen design! Simplicity with saturated colors really brings this space to life.  The k… https://t.co/CUeMoQZoxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You’ve got a friend in me”🧒🏼🧒🏽🧒🏻 @ Temecula, California https://t.co/oqc8OVK1wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to meet PRESIDENT TRUMP.  It would be a dream .I have never been to the White House because I never wa… https://t.co/Wo9T3EAFqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behold, upon the mountains, the feet of him who brings good news, who publishes peace! Keep your feasts, O Judah; f… https://t.co/xTtGcxEmX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fr has the heater on today.  I’m sweating like crazy! @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/sO4d1hKDLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[ESKINFORADRINK was not ESKIN  to be euthanized. SA officials need to halt racing there n move venue to another Cali… https://t.co/MnFT159Fv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Take this as a prequel to what a presidential term under Bernie Sanders would consist of.  He will liv… https://t.co/9oCvxSPuA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see @kanebrown love tonight 😍 with my fiancé @masonry41983856]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul Vile, his teachers must have thought he was as good a student as his moronic father.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally just watched all Jurassic parks and worlds tonight 😂💀 it’s 3am it’s time to sleep man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NostromoSerg And...like, 1.2 million dollars annually is more than enough to taper down your lifestyle over a few… https://t.co/lJ5Nh6aBPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kara King misfires with a mid-range jumper. Waynesville rebound and timeout. Spartans ball with a 35-33 lead and 52… https://t.co/Ivk0Cq5MJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys the name Miranda has NO good nicknames. My family calls me Randi but my friends don’t soooo any other ideas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimsDnc @jimintical OMG! WHAT IS HE DOING? FORGWT THE TICKETS! IM GONNA FAINT UP FRONT NOOOO..💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marieee1993 On the real. I had no idea you watched the bachelor.  I’m gonna blow up your phone each week now🤗🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAOOOOOOO sis really blocked me &amp; try to say my ass wasn’t cute. PLEASE have a fantastic day in la la land.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatsVeryKari @ccatmpt @FionaMorgan79 @suziday123 @AkronWineGuru @Dracaenawines @joneill55 @Julianna_glass… https://t.co/nSgokXwYHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Echo &amp; The Bunnymen to the Rock Hall....Original photo by Anton Corbijn; Design  Keith Humphrey… https://t.co/MeIws87BJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another super duper fun class with you all tonight! I hope you liked the playlist and let me know if there’s anythi… https://t.co/CnRT9ffvwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I receive this. Where God’s taking me, I have no room in my life for the wrong people. It’s nothing person, just bu… https://t.co/TsRFVlGtCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tailopez Omg!!! I can’t even answer the question. I just fainted. Imagine the rental properties you could’ve bough… https://t.co/cbYj75lXO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instagram vs Reality ➡️ Just kidding. It’s all reality. 😉 Sometimes I work outside with salad, other times I work i… https://t.co/z3PrF92vmc]]></document></documents></author>