<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I hope @KSIOlajidebt whoops @thatsdax but come on hoe you going to call out a person if you don’t know how to box]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMO, an excellent post-storm “plan of the day” statement prepared by WFO Birmingham.  It’s been quite a day for thi… https://t.co/N5oBAkPYhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@degiap01 @BillClinton I have 8 myself and plan on getting a few more. Guns don’t kill, people kill people. Maybe t… https://t.co/UT0l3quzV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you guys focus on some of the 'real' crimes of the Trump admin, every once in a while, instead of just regaling… https://t.co/f6SIF3OdBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trey54002737 @AriFleischer @Liz_Wheeler Spoken from a place of ignorance. Maybe actually talk to a climate scienti… https://t.co/pnIYxXK4NM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan So how is that sexual abuse case coming along at Ohio State?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricBoehlert In reality  If the Fairness Doctrine hadn't been repealed by the Republicans. FOX wouldn't have a FCC… https://t.co/z0GsJ7y6Ni]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I was expecting vs the actual look smh I’m so fucking disappointed https://t.co/xZ94emnSck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for those who have sent me cards and best wishes for today 😘 Special mention to @slowreadersclub for yours a… https://t.co/lZ2plHwU80]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb @maggieNYT @koblin Does this include those new fangled youngins like this 44 year old who watches their Y… https://t.co/7qPvROmIPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musicloverchick @phishedu : too late for my overview on the eras of Phish?]]></document><document><![CDATA[They came prepared, implemented feedback, and did the work. It paid off. Meet and welcome this awesome team of BODY… https://t.co/CnpAD9zSkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahashemi_3 @MajBinDE @HotlineJosh @jaketapper There you go, you are enlightened now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meliss2007 Sucks to be single today, but dogs make it so much better. 😅 https://t.co/QKkJ26RR7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @SebGorka We’re all calling him “coonman” down here in Virginia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepGosar this guy is a joke!! Great statements!! Cohen is a liar!! No credibility!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't get enough of my little girl. It's hard to believe she is already 2 years old! ❤💜💚💛 #TowardFamilyMemories @… https://t.co/hIDTcsILYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[📺 Now Watching 🍿 #AmericanWedding, this is still one of the funniest movies of all time. #NetflixAndNoChill 🤦🏼‍♂️🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelOsteen Amen. II Corinthians 1:18,19 says God’s answers are not yea and nay, but with Jesus Christ are Yea! So… https://t.co/joKj8hHLCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[These were the vibes on this lovely Sunday afternoon https://t.co/o77up39FCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duke had a great chance to win it all this year but that’s over.  You won’t see Zion again this year.  Not bcuz he… https://t.co/FmHwX51ZfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prom Invitation Committee📩 If you can help with invitations during your study hall or PAWS, see Mrs. Smith for a pass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for supercross @SupercrossLIVE  #DropTheGate https://t.co/hUJHCd3cJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dolly Parton knows heartache. #mirth #snicker #grin #ludicrous https://t.co/HImPoo3Fe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not well I think.  #Hearties #WCTH #HeavenWouldBeSeasonSeven @hallmarkchannel @SCHeartHome]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get it this is pre-season it means nothing and we are playing guys who more than likely won’t make the starting 1… https://t.co/BPm7xIUl86]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing stopping Kravtsov from coming over is a Byzantine set of rules that literally no one; team, fans, or… https://t.co/wSKQxGBEHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Experimenting” with dudes busting it every day trying to get back to affiliated ball. Doesn’t seem right]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the bucks don’t make it to the finals @Webdawg11 and I will streak down water street.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite pass rusher growing up. You know you are beast if your nickname is the “minister of defense”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC YOU HAVE TO BE DUMB AS A BOX OF ROCKS OR LIVING UNDER ONE NOT TO KNOW THE REAL REASON BUSH AND WOLFAWITZ INV… https://t.co/I4LQWdGI2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 2 #UVA gets its stars plenty of rest, going up big on Pittsburgh and cruising to a 73-49 ACC win. The Cavaliers… https://t.co/SYHvNsV7AJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fitch33Tim #Disagree There will be NO more snowstorms this year, Fitch.  :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[From maid to making it — single mom lands on #NYTBestsellers list with raw memoir.  https://t.co/ST3diyDR8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trumpifiedterry @Richard4m @MikeDomansky @jay_bird747 @newyorkval132 @lotettabhrb @MAJMO50 @BrandonN1271… https://t.co/AX294jm85U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hockeyteeth @chuckwoolery What's it like? I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day1USA HISTORY 3/5/1770… https://t.co/xEIevqGlW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hated to miss @gruverhoundball Bi-District victory, but I’ve got a training in Round Rock tomorrow morning.  Nevert… https://t.co/bUN3Ml6UFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your car detailed today! https://t.co/YzD8CM8PgL Dm for pricing and availability today! #Wash #Wax #Sealant… https://t.co/bUwylCta1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[She needs glasses. She yet again shows she will side with dictators and terrorists like Hamas and Maduro but go aga… https://t.co/1xyJ0XVZRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mad people already left for spring break I’m ready to hop on my trip already 😂🤙🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again, the fact that the MSM is the enemy of the people is proven by their own actions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Im_Pubs @TigersJUK Tigers are gonna win the central, watch that shit happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eo_chic @panekbill @pensfannc5 @JenniPrickett @pcdebol @oreomina1 @wgriffin28 @ElleRguez 😂🤣😂🤣 https://t.co/Bm830GwvEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomabbott1 @Dbacks @Indians Make sure to go early to our complex at 3pm for BP. Look for Dad too]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just fixed kaydens toy for him and he said “thank U momma” 😭😭 what did I do to deserve to be a mother to the most precious boy on earth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBurnaBTNH @ion_chiefs @jcharles25 If we could have 09 Charles on this team.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 SALES ENDING SOON! 🚨 RARE COLLECTIBLES! #EBAY STORE LINK IN BIO   #TwinLakesSilverFrontier #silver #gold #coins… https://t.co/fPulSSn64L]]></document><document><![CDATA[so wild to hear @DaBabyDaBaby on the radioooooo been following your music for a min now 🥰🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse WHAT? WHERE? WHAT HEALTHCARE? All we have is the tattered remains of Obamacare. Is going to take credit for that too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw @marcorubio I’m kinda disappointed he doesn’t wear a monocle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention Milton! Providence Road is under several inches of water in places and tree down.. @baileysouthside rock1… https://t.co/TuqPaI7Yvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little action from #TeamSTL last hockey game!   Blues are 🔥 Hot 🔥and so was the #TeamSTL   Thank you Robert Georg… https://t.co/7eyOV9DbJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can not wait to be on the golf course when this weather changes and snow melts. ⛳️🏌🏻‍♂️. @CodeBreaker_25 @MJH_straight_up]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's failing miserably - At the very minimum.  #UnfitForOffice Time for Trump to obtain a basic understanding of re… https://t.co/8Tzd2zBPzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday March 1 - MSNBC Daily:     Lanny  Davis: 'Everybody knew' Trump's Russian business claim was a lie;       Be… https://t.co/3Dc2psGMH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tinkerb80096912 @TomHall @doktordemirhan @AintitMarvelous @LudMarx1 @TheGood90551276 @FntsyWlkr @lester_lipton… https://t.co/o6Qa3ueA6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK I love my new job  Can’t wait to get signed off and MAKE THAT MONEY BINCHES]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only person who deserves an Oscar is the new guy running the @barstoolsports account send tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics He isn’t decent. He lies as much as Trump, and worse, is seen as sincere in his beliefs.  He will… https://t.co/p4148xIpID]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieClemmer @grumpywireless @HeyEddie Those are outside the sterile area so you would have to go back through T… https://t.co/WA1IlTaKlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieThunder44 @DonaldJTrumpJr Classic deflection. 'Silver spoon boy' is every bit as deranged as any of the people he raves on about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This had to be a blast (pardon the pun) to film. Where do you sign up for this job? #careerchange]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feud with: @WorldOfPW  Tag with: @realDonaldTrump  Manager: @ErinEK13  Trainer: @solomonster  I put over:… https://t.co/uRt5PBIvX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Musical instrument making shop in #Hindman #KY #Appalachia #photos #music #history #woodworking @ Hindman, Kentucky https://t.co/T5XewwvmiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chillin in dat San Diego sun 😎🔥😎 @ San Diego, California https://t.co/9cn8bLirGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s all fun and games until you’re in the ER for touching a scorching hot pot with you bare hand]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DYSONlife4real What ever floats your boat. A sixer, and a frozen pizza are gonna do some unspeakable things together with me tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ 1st United Methodist of Callahan https://t.co/NirynKZPcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today on International Women's Day I am thinking of all of the women addicted to drugs that governments don't let g… https://t.co/jIj8xWyJ3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read a Washington Post Business News article on Warren Buffet. The Oracle of Omaha with Berkshire shares earned 2… https://t.co/9N5UjppfTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @keselowski - Helluva job fighting the flu at a tough track and finding a way to bring home the W 🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:25.9°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando se tiene total dominio de las cosas, ahí es cuando hay que tener cuidado con la confianza. Esto aplica para todo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LATEST #PODCAST: ● My bucket list needs work. ● Jussie Smollett is an idiot and I give crime advice. ⚖ ● #Ravens ar… https://t.co/yz6wIMPRMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re officially LIVE! At GaryConXI! With Dragon Talk! #blackmagic #dnd #dungeonsanddragons #videoproduction… https://t.co/KjjDFfn52k]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RomanCatholic vs #NeumannGoretti is RIDICULOUS. https://t.co/kRLE1ykSDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForeignMulatto feel like this is always the first thing I here when I join the party chat 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kaycolts @FanSided For the third time, this has nothing to do with the Colts. It's a philosophy piece on what was… https://t.co/rPBPUkqnmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKinkhabwala Let’s look at it from the standpoint of asset vs. liability •6th round draft pick •10k+ yards •75TD’s… https://t.co/AQaCZEzza1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYDailyNews That's his style...but Attorney client confidentiality still exists]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeshinoda YAAASSSS I can’t wait to download them!! Love you so much Mike!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/64c8sl8qWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPECNewsAlbany check out foulton couty out , report that , meat,land , is on fire right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that Jon tried to PUNCH a White Walker will always be awesome to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prep softball: Experienced @EsteroHS gunning for state title in 2019. https://t.co/BJ9rgeUU7w @NDN_PrepZone @nphssports]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the house relaxing about to go to work soon wish I had a good person to talk to n spend time with someone close… https://t.co/IAOuZiGiJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usminority @KristySwansonXO You fascinate me! Your words are very powerful. Those who don’t agree and want to sile… https://t.co/qUlLZDashZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s now 4:24am and @JaxIcemen are back at the hotel asleep but the work isn’t over yet. Now the equipment manager… https://t.co/XrfgtmGWvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[No better feeling this late in the season then seeing the toothless grin of @RADUL22 and a smile so big under… https://t.co/gEGyZv4DBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao #du23 wilding out all in my tl 😂 the tea is will y’all even be cleared to get the keys to y’all dorm room ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorgiKohmander @luckynala323 That sucks I’m sorry lol. I’m about to clock in :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a special place in Hell reserved for the non-real estate, non-knowing anything about the business of real… https://t.co/3puNoDUnsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just did a wonderful jazz fest in Mitchell, SD.  Turned 40 tonight while hanging at the bar with some really cool m… https://t.co/lNiXwZXmR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fashion legend is gone. RIP. Karl Lagerfeld Dead at 85: Kim Kardashian, Lily Rose Depp Honor Designer – WWD https://t.co/LqPyFzXogb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffbauerjr @TheRealChris_A_ And I was a grad student there when this happened... Or, as it turns out, didn't happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[these are the times i wish i had a girl so i could roll over and rearrange her organs before work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FantasyFBStoner @ATLMike2007 @DanSiegelUnCut @TheFFRealist took a page out if ATL’s book]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TedFarrish @jgeltzer @justinhendrix @CNNOpinion Perp walks are appropriate for seditionists, not for people upholding the constitution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidcicilline He is hoping Cohen has no records of their conversation. Here hoping we can kill two birds with one stone. Let's go Cohen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyFanJoe I just finished a new Becky tribute video   https://t.co/YsgH3zi1pr]]></document></documents></author>