<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m hungry, I’m tired, I have to pee, my nose is stuffy, and everything is hilarious.  @petebourassa is a saint for… https://t.co/IpU6nV0PXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok but this bitch if forever talking shit .... like get your life together first 🙄. Pinche pendeja 🙄 one day ima just punch her dumbass .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need everyone to take this and send me your answers. It really determines where we are in life. https://t.co/iwPqs5IivE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Her STUPIDITY is irreparable...STUPID cannot be fixed!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lostal21 @TroubleDVJ @Bigb7893 @wweshirtguy @NikkiPav @BrianVistaAZ Morning all... Happy Thursday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NDN_Nikki_Luv @vladtv @SnowThaProduct And what are you doing to be a better example than @SnowThaProduct?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @united, I have two adults and two kids seated all over the plane. Both my kids have severe anxiety. Can you please help?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are overjoyed to be included in another baby shower!! Give us a call or email to see how we can help with your n… https://t.co/ZoZJD6aTfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/IGCejCUB7m Free to do some damage.. Keep speaking lovely strong 💪 woman! #rhymesayers @sarocthemc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markjacksonacts @ScottGrimes @TheOrville It’s from pissing in the corner!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This right here! @nike_sibande getting to 1,000 points in his SECOND year with @MiamiOH_BBall ! Hard worker on the… https://t.co/txgY8FtyLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldenduck @SallyGold @NYCMayor 🤣😂🤣😂 these replies are really making my morning start off with a laugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani @realDonaldTrump This was an expensive useless summit where nothing happened]]></document><document><![CDATA[My LEO daughter in Opelika, AL has experienced devastation on her road, it’s gone. She had minor damages, but her r… https://t.co/ILwkLSQnYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sad but this is how 90% of girls are, they get mad at the girl more than their boyfriend]]></document><document><![CDATA[The day is now also known as festa del papà and the religious origins are slowly becoming replaced by a general celebration of fatherhood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already got a call back for a new job , politely declined because they didn’t offer me enough. Patiently waiting for the next blessing 😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[#friezela tripping the light fantastic #sunsetlight #local600 photo by @dianneburnett @ Paramount Studios https://t.co/s06OZRKuYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess what? This gorgeous photo of the beautiful (heart and soul) @adamramzi_xo just became the newest inductee in… https://t.co/LyhM8vVVr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHarrisAJC @AJCGlobal they are killing them in large numbers too. They have been fighting over land they both feel they are entitled to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordynwoods Im ready gor "The Jordy Woods Show!⭐" On E!  @billie_kihega]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soul_of_Nowhere Was hoping MY boyfriend would be at Medieval Times yesterday.  He wasn’t... 😥    HAPPY BIRTHDAY!  🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow  Rachel l don't believe it. Judge Ellis should be thrown out. This is absolutely horrid. What kind of justi… https://t.co/L6A9zl4RIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Lord Farquaad I was born in the middle of the night  My age is really bad  I like to go eat lunch tomorr… https://t.co/VzpSNX0kxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s some of the details we have:  -Man killed by gunfire -officers looking for suspect  -police called to scene… https://t.co/D976Z1wCZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarenMorris @Spotify Ellie wanted to get in on it too but the filter wouldn’t give her a crown 👸🏼🐶💚 #MarenMorris… https://t.co/f5PANbo5vF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaron_mencher @MichaelRS_Music a fucking great time if I do say so myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karyns4 @NBCNews Why is Hate the theme of everything the Democrat Socialist does? They Hate anybody that has a dif… https://t.co/3tJmFZQCDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissK_USofA @celticman4567 @Alyssa_Milano You’re incorrect. Families were never separated. They were deported altogether.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cole slaw should only be eaten ON a Memphis pulled pork BBQ sandwich. Never on the side, never by itself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that Gucci really black face tho? I get it but it seems like a stretch to me 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JonasBrothersareback AAAAA AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA #suckervideo https://t.co/Mz8sW0ij4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pxcaballero About black people? What are you talking about? Im talking about Obama starting seven wars, and Trump… https://t.co/StGxanDOlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate when people snap/ text me like “where’s my invite??” If you were invited, you’d know 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump All I can say is... You are crazy delusional. There are just no other words... except liar, traito… https://t.co/ncQ4mYBbeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually, more of us (3 mil more) voted for Hillary &amp; have NEVER liked you.  We DO want you out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reviewwales I look forward to you tweets so much. You know the most interesting things!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my forever pet. Happy #NationalLoveYourPetDay miss you https://t.co/Zy9dpR3ibh]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is good, he will take care of all your needs, all you have to do is put it in his hands. Prayers for a speedy r… https://t.co/CHkCJLDd2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because I can’t think of spending a Sunday better than with a few episode of GOT. #ForTheThrone #JonSnow https://t.co/GeAXUlIRRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spot the white girl (it's like where's Waldo but way less fun bc it's so easy) https://t.co/n331plunWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m making friends at school!! But secretly I want to be friends with my profs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol got into one of those "clean everything right now" moods and now my house smells like The Y 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So basically the lesson we should all learn from this is that if you are already running a business or in political… https://t.co/odVMmdcOGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's love day baby💚  #year3 @ East Carolina University https://t.co/onc1hrF8yD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelGibsonFilms I'd take you anyway I could get you, Mel! That's been my saying since I saw the movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karen Wiltraut @possibilATies challenged me to post the covers of 7 books I love. No explanations. No reviews. Each… https://t.co/kLEqSyogEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UberEats why am I always paying a delivery fee when it says no delivery fee? https://t.co/57pbtpvmdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[We still on this? baby girl Allen is not cheating with me. I’ll be a damn fool to continue to fuck w/a nigga that w… https://t.co/C93HQwxnR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omfg this is 10-hrs that can be summarized with “Get your poor ass to church.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because someone’s in your life doesn’t mean they want the best for your life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Respect Ya LIFE!!! #ThankYou #Grateful #AppreciateIT @ Northern Virginia https://t.co/jQRes6Fk4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you all for a wonderful February! I appreciate each and every single one of you! If there's something you'd l… https://t.co/JpM11kPImN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hebahersi @IlhanMN @Amy_Siskind @mehdirhasan She may not be, but she is still an anti-Semite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaLuizito @rosecooleredboy @MariaEd07812623 @GuilhermeBoulos Vc soube que Dilma saiu do governo em Dez/2015?A part… https://t.co/aCoZYxa32E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consistent hard work and focus really does put you so far ahead. It’s hard but the discipline is soooo worth it yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me to Esai: “What are you giving up for lent?” Him: “You”  LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are also presumed to have rec'd 15% tip on every order and are taxed on 15% of sales, whether customers tip th… https://t.co/BxqMpkqKE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @margarachel, I’m addition to your big opening day, it’s apparently #NationalMargaritaDay, so today is definite… https://t.co/jqfqWfJwGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The campus shuttles are all messed up so someone asked the bus driver “is this king Henry?” to which someone on the… https://t.co/AQtflWUeQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Famous Americans are in the house today! #Irvinincredibles #MISDproud https://t.co/Jgx9UyjKCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA Friends TONIGHT do yourself a favor and go to see this little beautiful gem betterdaysthemovie at REGAL CINEMAS… https://t.co/8Tk2nEloZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viv takes the Quarter (don't worry, it was early and there was barely anyone there...or awake. Lol) #nola @ Royal S… https://t.co/bkR5U1mISQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joepinion @beardedrogue True. Though even the best designer can’t necessarily parse a problem from a solution, esp… https://t.co/jbi2Texu3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to be dramatic but if vine were still around, i’d probably be significantly less sad lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jellymarielly29 They’re not announcing it until wed! But it sounds like him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good article Mark. UNLV might be saying they are getting 8,500 a game. I hear they are actually getting around 2,50… https://t.co/wZuvVEFpL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please read, sign and share if you support quality public education in Ontario.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me going off on Snapchat didn’t work smh men can’t take no for an answer lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever worry about if you being too polite can be mistaken for being rude?? Like seeing two people you know in… https://t.co/L8NIz0w0b0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got the setup I wanted. Just need to do some cable management and it's complete 😍❤ #tekvirtuoso… https://t.co/FJ07OsWYBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillehennes @rextyler2 Pfiizer gets ingredients 4 meds from China, that was my reading. No laws 2 protect em. Ther… https://t.co/pjbxKQzA8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reached a new level in #Millennial status, yesterday. I ordered avocado toast and referred to it as "Avo-Toast" AND… https://t.co/YAdVw8ZpGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity That's rich coming from the man who idolized Roy Cohen, You think McCarthyism is fine… https://t.co/nNBLb7On1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Theres a guitar on my husband stone &amp; it reads our song,this is it! https://t.co/QmytOmZmr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m blocked can someone pls tell me what it says   https://t.co/ZxSYCUpAlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregNorberg @SpeakerPelosi Whoever is paying them is pulling the strings.  Or whoever is threatening them or black… https://t.co/61xTJf7TF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook keeps logging me out and telling me I’m trying to like things too much even though I’ve barely been on it… https://t.co/4aHe97vAPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHardwickWx @CBS4Indy @theWXauthority Let’s talk about SUNDAY!!  hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Doth protest too much!!! 1. He was your consigliere. 2. He lied on your behalf 3. He paid off your… https://t.co/qlxUqUtsgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_iam_awkward @evinawestbrook @hoopinmj @Kasiuniquee @ceemaries @Legend_Hooper @_kodakmoment_ @jazmine_mass @MC__23… https://t.co/F5NcPv8gIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well done Mr. Secretary of State &amp; @realDonaldTrump Well done indeed. 👏   https://t.co/0SHD8CHOQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad used to have a dog this breed and I miss him so much. Rest in doggy paradise Brutus☹️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whymustyoujudge @PressSec @GOP @SecNielsen Dems are the ones in favor of killing innocent children from the womb..… https://t.co/dMmRPJQ08j]]></document><document><![CDATA[sent this to my valentine when i woke up and she didn’t block my # 💖💜💚💛💓🧡💙💕💘 https://t.co/luctPKUdby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@photohappy07 Report the teacher to the school, local elections board, state AG as well local/state news outlets​ (… https://t.co/XpX12y1I06]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @MsAvaArmstrong @HawkofNewYork @prageru Is he really that delusional?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twilliams_007 Whateva Sgt Williams 😂🤣     Drop and give me 20!           lol. Kristina says heyyyyyy!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will add: in case of this year. Oprah voted for Black Panther, Tom for Roma, Tatiana voted for Green Book.   Movi… https://t.co/7Rg1vCNJ4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StellarisGame I already own the pc version but i want to buy the console version.  The info on Xbox is unclear and… https://t.co/acQIp3vjez]]></document><document><![CDATA[✅Durarara!! (S1+2), Hunter x Hunter(sub), The Seven Deadly Sins (S1+2), B The Beginning ▶️SAO: Alicization, Run Wit… https://t.co/sO9jq8obE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GForrester406 @MGigger Huh ... we have deer legs around the house all the time. I honestly just assumed our dog le… https://t.co/EQNsAuKHWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why in goodness name didn't they do it? "Andrew McCabe says the Justice Department discussed removing Trump from of… https://t.co/hj0s420P5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me in the kitchen at work vs me 2 mins later asking the table how their food is]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MeetAWriter D26: I’m completely happy with my name. Elaine has been passed down (as a middle name till me) for the… https://t.co/u9jVox5RnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ozcarmona @Fire_danny ¿Ya no necesitas que yo los saque de trabajar? 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@G23Donna Oh, nice! Well...Thank you! #Cheers! #TwitterFriend! https://t.co/cna7F3pHjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs this is such heartbreak the shedding of innocent Blood is something God hates, and it is evil how co… https://t.co/SogKQMb8Mq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This educator's philosophy is anything but textbook https://t.co/zaTsQu5j0N via @WGNNews 🎉🎓👍🏽🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicken enchiladas. Goat cheese and tomato ravioli. Cheese crisps. Pico.]]></document></documents></author>