<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Some of my work is available on https://t.co/bo67fHYDel   #thedailysketch #drawing #sketch #painting #art #draw365… https://t.co/8dUsEB9Idw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickWisdom5 Have a great season... still a fan even though your on the Rangers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracegerrett @BobMacKenzieTSN Also now I see that is an official Bob Makenzie 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will donate no more money to establishment Democrats in primaries. Rather, I will fight to primary them from the… https://t.co/VzWCzYd4X5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Customer talking to her son who she repeatedly told to stop touching thing   Mother- Chris u can either choose a sp… https://t.co/pV1ReJpmPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoDuTw @davidbix That’s kind of a nasty smear, rovert, calling me a drunk with no evidence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillWalton your commentary sux but love your passion and mentions for our military their post struggles for survival 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too cold and rainy in LA, this is were I want to be! James Bond Islands, Thailand. #maudadams sir_rogergeorgemoore… https://t.co/kpaUSdBL4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[gotta love the entertainment This mix of a Siberian husky and a poodle and you'll wonder why anybody pays for...… https://t.co/ZCxmdZu4dQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acquiring a new customer costs 5–25 times more than keeping an existing customer. Therefore, increasing customer re… https://t.co/oTD2PYtvxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[B's seem to be unbeatable since the break! Keep it going boys! #StanleyCup]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not even sure that my family can talk to each other for more than 5 min without quoting Napoleon Dynamite and The Office 😏😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marinavibu609g @elisabeth_petit @PatGrant7777 @grants4usa @fahadma45457790 @akomama_tm @EliLeonarda… https://t.co/g4GwtasKQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nadie nos dice que es fácil  Volvamos a comenzar 😍 en Nava, Mexico https://t.co/WWxavwUoCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the highlights of my day is my when JenksAnn poops quickly. Man, I am old @ Fair Oaks, Georgia https://t.co/dhJleLc2Uf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseball Final: Diamond Bar 4 Chaffey 0. Sean Martin pitches a four-hit complete game to earn the victory. @SGVNSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like the "man in the high castle"... #NYC #NewYork #modern #manhattan #architecture #landscape #city #love… https://t.co/ABVZ9jN0v1]]></document><document><![CDATA[IBM #think2019 forgot to think when planing the event at Pier 39. No tents, in an outdoor event in a city that rain… https://t.co/PEBcjS6Llr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently, 610 Sports has blocked me, because I can’t read this tweet. What the hell?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[$25 hats now available at King’s Steakhouse of Oxford !! https://t.co/uuKP8XJ40o]]></document><document><![CDATA[i agree if u not gonna pay college players at least let them sell their autograph n things like that so they can ma… https://t.co/r6EtFd1sA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it with thatnerdsoul checking out a #CaptainMarvel screening. Stay tuned for @OneYoungsta and I’s review la… https://t.co/oy82m2xfjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well Metal Health wasn’t  and that was their second biggest and it was HUGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wolfganghawkeye Can we just play 1 game without making a complete ass out of @uiowa ?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A6:  I set my own path towards my horizon.  I learn from others, but I believe we have to seek our own unique horiz… https://t.co/08APiyx3gF]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHE IS A FK'G TRAITOR! AMERICA IS FOR AMERICANS! NOT ILLEGALS! SAY NO TO ILLEGAL VOTES!   AND THE DEMS HAVE THE NER… https://t.co/9wr8QbOB6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richiecosme_ @MarianaMontoya_ El Padre del Año. https://t.co/aRWOq7CcFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @Pacific_Hoops goes ice cold late in first half as SC goes on 19-2 run for 36-25 halftime lead https://t.co/xJhrHGMsng]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random Caylena Fact: this is Cleopatra, Lena hits her on the head rather than pets her. This is the first time she… https://t.co/mvfhCo3JYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMRealLifestyl1 @justuseapen @mand0xxx @charliekirk11 The other big factor, they always try to tax income instead… https://t.co/3tEgQX0jfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GridironRR @BIGFACESPORTS06 @DogWiredDudes @SafetyPride @CoachCarthel @derekcarrqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wra12Cjwr1 The dnc as decided by a US court can elect anyone they want as their Candidate for potus without voter… https://t.co/Mr1HJHHKSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wcco #ready4summer Looking forward to roaring fires at one of the beautiful MN State Campgrounds. https://t.co/cnAlq1m1XN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRFLivingston @ClockersCorner She loves that tip jar! If you still there tell her hi for me🖐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@6RingsOrGtfo @Jared_Carrabis @barstoolWSD Did he wear that batting glove to try and help catch all the rockets he gave up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Charlotte Douglas International Airport - @cltairport in Charlotte, NC https://t.co/3CKPz2Rkud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueRobotDesign @TeamTrump @realDonaldTrump @CPAC Not one single thing u said there I agree with.  He doesn’t even… https://t.co/NzOfyK3xau]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey everyone me and the boys at zeta phi epsilon are doing the 5th annual Fortnite-athon and need donations for mon… https://t.co/WrnGURVANj]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of fun on the ice this morning. I’m really grateful for the camaraderie among this group of guys I play morni… https://t.co/lb9rNcscpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🚨$1 everything at the Bulldog after 9 tonight!!!! 🚨 🚨 https://t.co/UpfdSSS7G8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laci_Kay_Somers @FbsOriginal Ohhhhhhhhhhhjh shiiiiiiiiiiiit, that's a nice fucking ass!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[pos no  parece k el mundo se va acabar @ Paramount, California https://t.co/8tfUOsQdQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Kevin Roche, Pritzker Prize winner and architect of Chicago’s Leo Burnett Building, dies at 96: https://t.co/mSK8a7VFy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can tell somebody is on the ropes and trying not to act bothered when “LMFAOOOO” starts being used]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanMc23 @JakeAndersonFF @JesseReevesFF @tacitassassin13 @JMicCheck @ClutchFantasy @klabreck @amicsta @PeoplezPen… https://t.co/8kGupKvMkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[William is a fresh bread of air from Cori... 10/10 loves to grill https://t.co/cbcsjlsgKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its official! This place makes one of the best old fashioneds I have ever had. #actorslife #workflow💰… https://t.co/iOAeWppbZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EAHelp Yo on Xbox one the @anthemgame Legion of Dawn rewards disappeared from my equipment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[View from ... the Upper Deck is up on @DKPghSports and is brought to you, as always, by my friends at @MoonGolfClub… https://t.co/kFoAYQCl60]]></document><document><![CDATA[••• To slow the waves a bit  Take another hit Calmer, the waves begin to get   Onward we sail, My freighter  My ship]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a new era over here at frozenbroadway and I’m very proud to be a part of this new company 🦌 #Sven #Frozen2.0 @… https://t.co/9bA49oyqft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laughs From Santa Monica : Jonathan David #laughsfromsantamonica #lfsm #spectaclepic #standupcomedy #studio… https://t.co/CTtFJJW8PZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Noble Star Collection: Solar Evolution by @schellsbrewery @ The Starkeller — https://t.co/YJqbKIN3Ck]]></document><document><![CDATA[How’s everyone else feeling today? @ Perry, Michigan https://t.co/EPsbvdaTTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowglobe in March?? Oregon throws tf down. 100p, no🧢Thanks for having us boys!! #gleee @ Eugene, Oregon https://t.co/6jqMinLX2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does the media keep calling the fruit loop little guy that staged some kind of idiotic crime on HIS SELF some k… https://t.co/CaIS9uKYZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TimedHittingPerception Training, Special Invite to #CoastalFloridaSportsPark Cocoa Fl with HS prospect 2021… https://t.co/LQsYkZf9yL]]></document><document><![CDATA[How are 20 million illegals here if not an emergency since DC did nothing for 50 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Good fucking send bro” - friend of kid who did 2 weighted dips with a plate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune in for the @NHIAA_LOA D-III Girls Basketball Championship between  from @snhupenmen on the @NFHSNetwork  by @GraniteStateSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antoin @AlistairMcCay My understanding was that @eirgrid operates the entire island as a single system, so I presu… https://t.co/60BnC9vqrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @drmanejwala @AmyDresner Can we learn anything about recovery from #MardiGras? Yes we can. Mardi Gras Special:… https://t.co/nq7Mt85SYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @IAmSteveHarvey, let’s fight about it.... @ Oakland, California https://t.co/qetyjQ6hvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half ass investigation is how you run everything in your life. You are afraid and should be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite thing to do in my spare time is finding the weirdest most crappy looking movies on Netflix and watching them 🤔😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highs in the upper 30s and continued wet weather with some snow and rain mix coming with some wind through the day… https://t.co/J0OlXhyaMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyGirlboss So true. I wrote a newspaper column when my daughter turned 16 entitled A Bittersweet Sixteen. I baw… https://t.co/DnrQPDJwYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebaileylynn You can tell because they’re just now tweeting vids about it. That shit was a must.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preparing for our matches this weekend against SJSU and USF. Lets go! @CSUMBMSoccer https://t.co/4xdplNMQ7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[My biggest fear is having a child and I gotta watch their cartoons. Imma have to buy all the morning junts I use to… https://t.co/kHRKZHpHGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[summoning circle, hope this works                          🕯               🕯              🕯         🕯… https://t.co/Yu1WKDhyQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine not eating pizza for 3 months, then deciding to get some on your birthday, and they deliver the wrong pizza… https://t.co/cGml457jJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a mission.  The @scc_titans will travel to Boone to take on @MadridTigers in the Class 2A-District 12 championsh… https://t.co/KEurwaitkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My conclusion about the drivers in Southwest Florida is the following: They are either terrified of the accelerator… https://t.co/Y7RqGakyP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it's so groovy now that people are finally getting together...Oh wait, Wrong Again! Nancy Pelosi continues… https://t.co/SMSRgLb8lm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OriginalBayArea More like Team Gianni's shoeing why you don't want Russ running a team]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UncleRafy @davidtabrown So is Jose for that matter he was better than a lot of the people in his day!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump Lmao who is having a tantrum know like you said we can’t always get our way]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir Ok I have boarding passes in hand for 5:30 flight.  What can you offer me for compensation or upgrades… https://t.co/6b1fvc5yF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boltonjer The clock in our Toyota did not advance. Perhaps I am missing a TZ setting]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF 9th Annual Echo Awards Spotlight February 12, 2019 TMP's Top 100 Albums of 2018 71. Emily A… https://t.co/ghKxxSEDch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKia @tytornatore @RepLeeZeldin Except many Manhattan people like myself were not born here unlike upstate,  so w… https://t.co/nbWJqIjCGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Highlight Reel- Woodlawn @ WOODEN SHOES (SENIOR NIGHT) @shoeshoops @Smith10Dawson @unit50sports https://t.co/VbMdmxwo8f via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world would be a lot better off without KIDS!!           Burton Timmer #rad]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart rate is Finally back to normal after last nights episode 😂  @TemptationTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaarreaza Asi será tu final, y todo los tuyos 😭😭😭criminales. https://t.co/LLV832ZLUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyWest I have been partial to cocktails at the Carthay Circle, but sometimes there is a line and the wine bar gets you a glass faster]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited to announce my single 'In My Blood' has just been selected as the current Semi Finalist in the Interna… https://t.co/SRR3z40l9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebHowe @LordActonAFool In the context of gender equality and transgender issues, people make one or the other o… https://t.co/XYEJtTBY3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[they say money don’t buy happiness, but i sure am happy when i can buy whatever i want]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The longer it goes on, the more likely (the China trade battle) becomes more permanent,” said Todd Stucke, SVP at… https://t.co/66ZRcaHTM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arkansas forgets how to get a stop, and all of a sudden there’s only 1:40 left and the Hogs trail by 11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nlvalenzuela @El_Universal_Mx Esto se parece más a las acciones europeas para regular las casas calificadoras.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natsteinbrink Big noses Unite!  Just don't stand too close, I don't want to poke out your eye. https://t.co/Z8NLmBVItR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsingler88 @CoachHopperton @HarrisonFootba1 @wildcatsofhhs @GameWinnerKick Thank you Uncle Jeff!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaBartiromo @FoxBusiness @MorningsMaria @dagenmcdowell @Mitch_Roschelle @MBlockTSA @TomBevanRCP @DeepakChopra… https://t.co/w4LEOboeHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlogChurchWork just a “Stranger in a increasingly strange land” thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acaseofthegolf1  Glad to be on the bag for #mondayq and this week's @WebDotComTour event for @GOgolf711… https://t.co/XHl9M1anz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is @United_Way_WC's #UnitedWayChat Twitter Moment.  #VITA #MyFreeTaxes  https://t.co/T2jw87EH49]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mar doesn’t know why she picked that and she’s about to be HELLA SHOCKED]]></document></documents></author>