<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Where are the Republicans in Congress? Why aren’t they pushing back?? Especially when mueller didn’t find anything!… https://t.co/8la4ChbAcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The friends I dont know. #waysuspect #keywestcelebration @ Key West, Florida https://t.co/oIpUEqY7HR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Russia's parliament has put forward strict new internet laws allowing the authorities to jail or fine those who 'di… https://t.co/qsedtG2nrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lion King Graduation Cap -  "Simba, Everything the light touches is our kingdom."... #hilarity #snicker #smirk… https://t.co/VZ7Vyh63c7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianakochetkova I saw the weather and literally wanted to cry. I just need the sun in my life 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[You missed one..... they are white MEN! We don't fit in on any level. .....good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had to tell my momma and daddy forgive me if I end up fightin a bitch cause they playing with me bad lately😂🧘‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Milford #CT  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/MZrKm69ipJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ❤ laundry! BE the laundry! @ Suffolk, Virginia https://t.co/68o7BEXwwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you no one for telling me that they put more episodes of jeopardy on netflix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Emily Prasko who broke a 26 year old school record for steals in a career. The old record was he… https://t.co/EOJWZBRptK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPostPol @VP @SecPompeo @CNN @ABC @MSNBC @realDonaldTrump @CBSNews  @NBCNews @AmbJohnBolton  These Unethical Se… https://t.co/mk77XBTGoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[As an emergency manager, it always makes me nervous when @JimCantore is less than 30 miles away from me... #WinterStormPetra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few things coming up on the calendar!  #GetInvolved ⌚️🗓✔️ https://t.co/deiWTFiYFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone wanna go to prom with me? It don’t matter who as long as you’re not my ex and not a party pooper. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan So this Fake news lady is saying because drugs came through a legal point of entry we dont need a wall? Smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Seriously?  Manafort caught lying to protect you for giving the Russian Intelligence everything th… https://t.co/0W5P9dW7cL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sore many will be appalled, but hey... when I’m traveling for business or in a meeting, I find a way to keep my… https://t.co/k4SnwR6eij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lakers @PatrickMahomes Who is more handsome? Patrick Mahomes II, hands down! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don’t want to be with someone, stop! wasting! their! time! and keeping them from finding someone that does w… https://t.co/w3ccc35dgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @SherrodBrown He’s stupid and dumb walls work go to his house and see if you can just walk up to his door!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nadiazerka @Sephora If there is one thing I need consistent in my life it’s Sephora sales.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently they gave a Medicaid code to relizorb but  the insurance company @UHC denied my son so now please tell m… https://t.co/T9JG3LBxdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fedupcitizen16 @Lastonein66 I wouldn’t even look twice at a man wearing a dress.   I’ve got plenty of girlfriends Thank You.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yayyy BIG MONEY 💰 💴💰 In the BANK ‼️..  Thank you Micheal #KitchenDesigner On landing A $29k sale 💥 ! In Cabinet Ref… https://t.co/XAU2cfVY6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[ELVIS PRESLEY THE PEDOPHILE, DONALD TRUMP IS PRESIDENT, JUDGE KAVANAUGH SENT TO THE SUPREME COURT, HARVEY WEINSTEIN… https://t.co/DEpyov0m7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[These guys. brianbbrooks and jomissa digging work by #jessieharrod curated by the_magicians_assistant… https://t.co/8fBoxKYdtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[its not that i move on too fast, im just too mature to sit and cry over baby shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our first exceptional customer service achievement at 770 goes to Greg in our hardware department!!! What huge win… https://t.co/Vack9I932z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crickets in the @GOP on ethics of Trump WILL BE THEIR DOWNFALL in 2020 thank god!! 🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊😡😡😡😡🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊🌊⚖️… https://t.co/lUjeWRqfil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beaglefacts @Piper_beagle I tell her that Mommy has to go make the bone money! 🦴 💴🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/LV8JbQUXQa  #classics #ClassicRock #80smusic  #RUSHFAMILY   "Limelight" @rushtheband   @dawizzurd… https://t.co/l9cAZYZztM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Surabees @DonaldJTrumpJr Things like that happen all the time! It's a pathetic statement about the president becau… https://t.co/NjuEJ4d1kT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bessbell Really? I am quite open about my reservation about @SenSanders (deliberately using name to check your fea… https://t.co/2vGqUtw2JC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MeatlessMonday dinner:  miso soup with mushrooms and tofu. Recipe from @weightwatchers Cooking Up Comfort cookbook… https://t.co/S4Rgcgzt9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao some of y’all rly try so hard to defend being friends w someone U KNOW is a rapist.. just say u don’t care abt the victims and go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guerillagirly1 Thank you Donna.  The vet said we did the right thing and that is something .  But hoping the heart… https://t.co/UfRUOLn3Xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday! Happy thoughts! Happy happenings! https://t.co/UBuyXAQTpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshTBilly I was planning on buying a car this year (mine has 176K miles) but was thinking a Camry but this snow h… https://t.co/FRatOOsw8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TakeATuneToBreakfast every pancake has its maple syrup https://t.co/yiYff6seW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EWDolan @USATODAY If he talks like a racist, and acts like a racist, good chance he is a racist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaabricastro1 @ricardosaantoos @castelanomika Não gostou me processa 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarlaGamez Güey es que vi esa foto y como que algo quiere cambiar en mi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriceRoyTJ FAKE NEWS-BONBONS/TRUDEAU À INDIGESTION .... (suite) On arrêtera de vous APPELER FAKE NEWS quand vous… https://t.co/RHYq7CuEZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AC360 Harvard study said 90% of CNN’s and NBC Trump coverage is negative. This is not fair journalism. They are propaganda for democrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[(yes, a Mean Girls joke is one of the few things that I will permit to interrupt my @SchittsCreek GIFs)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Persiste falla eléctrica este sábado en 14 estados del país  https://t.co/SFG4M6ubVC vía @elnacionalweb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_Reece @TexasBaseball @YETICoolers @TexasLonghorns Yeah! Only if I get the drink 😉 #HookEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MtHopeNanjemoy How do you have your banner hung and is that vinyl material?  #Iwantone4myschool :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm scared to drive to work , park , and walk across that wide open parking lot in 65 mph wind gusts.  Please pray… https://t.co/Y7lIHXbS3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WitchyWife1964 @scribblymoth @mwagner8 I drink a shit ton of water, take an Excedrin migraine and a hot shower. I… https://t.co/wQgWperK09]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE ARE NXT! @WWENXT @KingRicochet @VelveteenWWE @WWEAleister #NXTPittsburgh https://t.co/1owieZXCzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrushTheCFR @BrianQuinn36 @ItsJustJill No - they are public companies - traded on the NYSE -]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiddenCash Could make a car payment for my parents. That would be really great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend I get to bring my "mini me" to her first concert ever!! @coleswindell @JoelHutsell @chris_marquart can… https://t.co/C4DuZxwRs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @mommytalks2much They were kneeling because unfortunately there are pro-confederate pieces of shits hol… https://t.co/q8fxNi8HzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duke vs Carolina Game! #bucketlist @ Cameron Indoor Stadium https://t.co/vbWHP8e7lr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @FLOTUS Be best should begin at home flotus. https://t.co/lBiMyzMbXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValeBellerose I had one last year. She was amazing and helped me learn about my body type and what will and will n… https://t.co/GRbjGyOmZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump They were his to do what he wanted with.  He’s still accomplished a lot in life, have U?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 I was so happy when our store recieved it! It looks beautiful! Of course, our team knows better to NOT to… https://t.co/MNWJlkhyVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new favourite item in the shop!  #coveralls @3x1 #denim #onlineshopping #ottawaboutiques #exclusive #ottawa # @… https://t.co/DgeF0SneXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care what side of the aisle, having worked on a #woundedwarrior Comission and grant and meeting Senator Bob… https://t.co/1QJ2w2hSns]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the phone with mom today: "I got you a card, but forgot to mail it. So I'll send it next year."    Me: https://t.co/zTybYstVBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rom 12:1 NIV—Therefore, I urge you, brothers and sisters, in view of God’s mercy, to offer your…  https://t.co/ws6RLpvDFJ via @biblegateway]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week has been rough...two exams, two presentations, report, and a proposal all due]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna go to a drag brunch for my birthday for a show n cocktails, is that even a thing in Chicago??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy AZ weather Day 2...snow in my mom’s backyard... #arizonasnow @ Marana, Arizona https://t.co/spuwVEclbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandolphTrent @HHMU_Banksia @WoodwarddianneJ @mikecoulson48 @BitarDeen Propaganda is a powerful mask]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would really like to live long enough to see more wonders of the world in a preserved and thriving state. maybe t… https://t.co/bKwXa7rM4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Error 2: (Willfully) conflating Trump’s subservient eagerness-to-receive things from foreign government with Clinto… https://t.co/l1fOcyeUoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @TheView Bravo! “ The View” still has my vote! Watch it every day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I have stated before I have a degree in Social Work and have spent years studying. It comes second nature after… https://t.co/ntYCAh3Bqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[due to personal reasons I quit my job. currently seeking a new job, will work for food.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@altonbrown @gzchef ISO best omelette recipe. Friends coming, breakfast for dinner, I'm desperate. Don't make me text @thepioneerwoman 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCoker13 @sianoresist Also, I'm always looking out for a wife for my son. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 20th Year with the company, you two are certainly examples of true leadership, I love and miss you both… https://t.co/LPmhFgfaMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What was with the weird shout out to Sean hannity? Is he actually there? #TrumpKimSummit]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a still picture of the plane I just tweeted. The name of this plane is Stealth Boomer I say it looks like "… https://t.co/4zGhqUpScl]]></document><document><![CDATA[is it just me or have the last like 3-4 weeks lasted like 3 minutes??? I swear it was January last week]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi beb. i miss u. i miss hearing u talk about everything and anything and i mis hearing u laugh until u snort. pls hang soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradlander @AndreaSCousins yet no democratic process when @NYCComptroller and ethnically challenged nccall fastrac… https://t.co/9BEOA9hiPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Achieve3000 A teacher’s work is never done...  sending out a massive parent email at 6am on a Saturday because I c… https://t.co/QbojniTmcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Badoo (I'd never heard of it, it was suggested by Google) https://t.co/O303dHpmxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do 90%, if not more, of your movies start AFTER 1pm?! It makes it impossible for all stay-at-home moms to come… https://t.co/zNFtcqB1bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[But what if the primaries were blind auditions like that thing where you play the oboe behind a screen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate that I still get a little influence by people’s opinion about what I do]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @SPJMadison70 to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews- just th… https://t.co/XVQXSf4p0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriotJenn @superyayadize #BuildTheDamnWall I am tired of these fools putting illegals first! Them protecting Ill… https://t.co/nItF56zLVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[IPhone case I just got   Jake Borelli &amp; Alex Landi https://t.co/2bsAwFzWsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I lay here hungover and hungry I am angry at the world, not for its fucked up ways but because there’s no Uber eats in Seymour.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Vampire Weekend and now THIS?!?! 2019 is THE year for music https://t.co/ki7Rvwmcwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rpskataria @IamSunitha777 @u_mirella @AnupmaMichael @fghdil @GsjpJyoti @greatairi @SsanjayTaannk @yogeychauhan… https://t.co/OBSUtQM6U2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who has spent enough time in and out of the hospital as me will completely understand the feeling of complet… https://t.co/IClVGQioGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oops typo City News,I must of been upset when I was writing this,and by the wayStephen,like I said before safe inje… https://t.co/0LDzB4CZuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[jaime just sweeped up a pair of fake lashes on the floor &amp; goes “u want them leslie?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#noncomplianttattoo #umc #allmeansall #welcome #reconcilingministries @ Baraboo, Wisconsin https://t.co/ornjErrYaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh Mr.Trump, aren’t you supposed to be running the government! Why are you down in El Paso  stirring up trouble, an… https://t.co/pQMTr3ygBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to flip @chrisstolle ‘s seat and the work starts, NOW!  Unless, of course, he and @DelRRobinson want to extend… https://t.co/bmXZenHqXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t appreciate mental illnesses being romanticized EVER, but I really, really hope that there’s someone out the… https://t.co/qSghrxLQkC]]></document></documents></author>