<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 and it wasn't even direct criticism.  he was just stating facts that trump doesn't agree with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why hockey is the best sport.  My son's favorite player is @89SGagner. He has cheered for him faithfully fo… https://t.co/DqniO7J93d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me da tanto miedo  cuando Emmanuel respira tan como si no lo hiciera al dormir. 😣 me saca cada susto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right after visiting the nutrition and dietetics program classroom, I ran into two of our students promoting heathy… https://t.co/Oa6pFDdFPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bailey__anns I’m counting down the days until I get back to menom to order one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waterfall Wednesday! The end of spring 2018, before Going-to-the-Sun Rd in Glacier National Park was open to cars.… https://t.co/EWb0NNjqTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarstensLavern @PaoloViscardi @iheartmindy @AOC That is literally what it means. How would the meaning you're insi… https://t.co/CYblRmQhZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Filled in on the AM shift. Thought I’d be super productive around the house the rest of the day. WELL the power wen… https://t.co/tqLb0pB63C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta wanna bee Negin se copia de TODO que fatal de originalidad https://t.co/gxp1XiSlgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hitting Day 2 of #ExpoWest! What an amazing gathering of companies who are literally changing the industry from the… https://t.co/tKdO47M4vv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvsherman @StormHour @ThePhotoHour Amazing, made of stardust and Walking on Stars!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to see this talented guy kill it on stage, like he always does!🎙🎶 This time wearing a luchador mask!😂🙌🏽… https://t.co/M8ztzhAKb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricRajala Haha yassss! Also the real #MarchMadness is pretty clutch! #OneShiningMoment]]></document><document><![CDATA[What part of the Democrats does Gropy Joe Biden represent?  Women hysterical over #MeToo aren’t going to vote for h… https://t.co/w3QhbDyG25]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUESS WHO BECAME A DOCTOR TODAY?!!???!!!!!! Meeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee #ImmaDoctuh https://t.co/fxTfaDp33s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahluwal What % were in the hands of human traffickers who were pretending to be their parents?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh If Dev’s full name was Devyn I don’t think I would be with him rn 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can’t forget our one and only girl on this special day. 💕 Happy Valentine’s Day Isabelle! We love you! 💘… https://t.co/B56pW5e71V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyWTSP @10NewsWTSP @BrightsideOn10 @PestWorld Ewwww https://t.co/DT1l9lAkJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Shabbos !שבת שלום - אַ גוט שבת - Wishing you that yours be Pe☮ceful! NYC Shabbos times: ⁦… https://t.co/i26lgUcjPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do guys continuously hit you up when you don’t answer them?? Fucking weirdos stop doing that shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gimpmaker @Friendofbenelli @JesseASweeney @Mikefiggs @MattyC801 @Alyssa_Milano Yeah.  I’m a super fan. Although if… https://t.co/yZjibUuMf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you all for praying for Chloe!She is doing much better!She is still in ICU but doing better!Praise be to God!… https://t.co/vaB5cvtiXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevKevDeYoung Oh my! His little heart is in the right place...but this one is worth saving #SeniorLove]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez, Castro plan to introduce a bill to block  the so-called national "emergency" https://t.co/bIPO71fmFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am still unsure if I am tweeting right. I am not sure  my tweets don’t get any answers   I must be very boring or inept lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dumbass!! He mentions nothing about you. But Klansman fits your bill? Well I would then say. IF TH… https://t.co/XuRBs3XTTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[a year ago I wouldn’t have been caught dead in a dress like this. last night I was glowing in confidence. ✨ https://t.co/xii82iduke]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight Oreo, Sylvester..💤😼 @ South Valley, New Mexico https://t.co/X7ViaIXW0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mme_Brown @yesmagazine Thank you for sharing this! I love that one of her points surrounds a series of texts one b… https://t.co/yU4FBAT0Wt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HolmesGWCSTEAM @SheriHundley2 @CarverES_RH Way to go Team Carver! Great job coaches!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @NBCNightlyNews The nations with @Flotus💌@Potus enjoy Joanna Hope #MAGA2020 is  global movement. Lady… https://t.co/S3RJy0dLWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a very long phone call with my man today! Can’t wait to talk to him in person! 87 more days ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Figured out why you’re supposed to take #probiotics on an empty stomach 🧐 https://t.co/7QmrbEVXUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sorry this just ruined my entire day, white people like this suck dude]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InScreamingBlue @yikespablo @daveyamador I’ll be your bestie it’s okay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanHollandBai6 She’s lucky she didn't get punched in the face.  Remember when people use to mind their business??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VersaceHorcrux can we go back to  when we would drive around at 2 am listening to The Life of Pablo.. 😭 I miss you… https://t.co/oJZOjN9T2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Taralson @Citizensowls @SalleeClark @historyfrog @jlo731 @design2research @AdamShortShorts @Melinda_Isham @jessxbo… https://t.co/5g4u1dVliR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up at 5am, and have been laying in bed, underneath the blankets when I should be leaving in 3 minutes to hit… https://t.co/NoOskwpMyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see you everywhere though you remain unseen. Today I cried in the closet because I can't unsee you and me...… https://t.co/kaH0Xg5jeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get excited every time I get this email only to open it and be disappointed it's never Brandy, Jennifer, Courtney… https://t.co/pOtrVWFzlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo EX Will have a whole new relationship and still be mad at you for doing you and be keeping tabs on you! Lmfao! W… https://t.co/r8BtLcSvr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a toasty 36 degrees and I can finally get out of my car and walk around at work 🙏🏻 blessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I can't respect them. They are hypocrits, same as congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBootsBrewing Yes mostly in the trap or next to it.  They don’t run and die in your walls.  They die in seconds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gunnadoit2 @ScottMorrisonMP 😂😂😂 oh little man, I’m a critical care nurse, today I saved someone’s life.  What have… https://t.co/fOo9AIDUKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Downtown Scottsdale during spring training was one of the wildest things I’ve seen in a while]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twittysuch So it turns out that person I know, actually walked along the bus route, not drove.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much fun! Thanks for kicking it off @LSE_Elliott Mr. Elliot #readacrossamerica2019 #theplacetobe @LoneStarElem… https://t.co/f6bK1S8lhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burt_Carter @CaffeinatedMike @KentMB1 @Scott_P_L @RealJamesWoods Try us]]></document><document><![CDATA[So in my Valentine’s Day presents from my boyfriend he got me bathbombs Bc I refuse to take baths 😂 #bathsaregross and I’m stubborn 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[A majority of the chamber now opposes President Trump’s national emergency declaration https://t.co/Vfg05A7Ou7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The theme of the week for me is definitely Be Bold.  Most importantly it is the story of intersectionality.  I am n… https://t.co/kvdSYLrKnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Business trip to the East Coast ✈️  You can catch me + @JamieHudsonNBCS on the road for POR @ BKN, PHI, and CLE… https://t.co/4ftCz6uYDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanbus @POTUS @CPAC @cspan @ACUConservative Thanks Best President ever ! TRUMP 2020🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of love and peace to my fellow parentified children. May we all take better care of our inner children than our parents could. 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kitty #5 joins my clan this week. But I think joes cat moving in is the sign he finally accepted he lives with me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my 23 years of living I didn’t think I would like avocado but here we are 🥑]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg imagine thinking anyone but the girls deserved that award couldn’t be me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chynnafuller27 Not a meme but here is a video of Baxter freaking out and attacking me because Ben was making weird… https://t.co/3rq4OCAppw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Hollywood knows what’s good for it, they’d get Ben Affleck to play Scott Peterson in a movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbagump324 You are so lucky helping him to grow! Can’t wait to see other pictures!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parking for tryouts: Is in the parking garage on the right building on NW 6 ST parking is in on all 4 floors. Gym is in 7th floor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blogdiva @tressiemcphd I don’t think I was treating her as a consumable. I saw her as an advocate for ppl like me,… https://t.co/GwLcqqpcZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sadiejezierski @tinyJeffrey My number now more accurately describes my apparent new found affection toward the lonestar state]]></document><document><![CDATA[They said that you #visit to #nyc is not complete without seeing a broadway show! We were eyeing for #Aladdin but w… https://t.co/es1CpdzbhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@br_kelley1 @AverageJakeFF @CPyles8 @craigsesker @InterMat Same! Young adults here who’d rather spend our money on… https://t.co/yHeceHoArh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Paulie says “earn your stripes” one my time.... Like it’s your 2nd season, bro. Stfu https://t.co/Mjb0Ci1DO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THOMASGOMEZ007 @guatemayabyesi @CatholicTroy @kansasauthor @sistervpaul_ @ChariiDavid @DavidT66 @vinodkambli349… https://t.co/SpRmBl7S0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone asked this very question last year maybe... and it didn’t go to well. Thank God you don’t have a cult follo… https://t.co/5iBFyWVhuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoudiniDancing You’ve started a new trend Houdini!  You can call it #SlowLickSunday! Have a great one!😸🐾💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉🎊🎉Dusty celebrating 2 years with Home Depot! Here's to many more!!!🎉🎊🎉 https://t.co/LGltgzsx3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraLaQuaglia @BrownleeAmanda @birneyartrocks @principalhoward Thank you for coming!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The highest rates of food insecurity in seniors are found in: *Blacks/Hispanics  *The divorced/separated  *Renters… https://t.co/0hThYPZzQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s @NikitaDragun doctor, I need like 20 apptmnt I’m tryna be SNATCHED after birth]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm seeing this and can't believe the difference...😬 I have no words... I know I still have some ways to go but 54… https://t.co/ovhcTqNgsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Whatever Wednesday is in the books! @EHGreeneSchool teachers have the OPTION to see @techyaveottaway or mys… https://t.co/mGeu8DepYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a beautiful day in the Lowcountry! @Bwelch15 and I are enjoying the view in Mt. Pleasant! https://t.co/spgHatylFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Admissions committees would be well served by spending more time articulating the qualities they are looking for an… https://t.co/hzKFdGpn7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s our Head Coach!!!!  Wow!  She has been our consistent, faithful and expectant leader all year!  So awesome s… https://t.co/i4eRO8GHul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @brielarson , @SamuelLJackson , and everyone else that was part of making this great @MarvelStudios fil… https://t.co/o41YtJViGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flavors from Ethiopia #ethiopianfood #chicago #foodie #foodporn @ Demera Ethiopian Restaurant https://t.co/jLlxR08bUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this #vintage #wedding #ring in my Etsy shop #etsyaaa #antique #wedding #band https://t.co/KI5gDBnxtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[: JUST TO CLEAR THE AIR... I don’t give a FUCK about no hoe.. I’m not jealous of no hoe.. I’m not in competition wi… https://t.co/iF4lCFDfI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when ppl write me nice notes or send me nice texts. I save/hang them bc it makes me so happy to reread them,… https://t.co/j53D5cm79d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Las Vegas.  Temp is 16, feels like 15. #Harrahs #LasVegas #Nevada #USA @ Harrah's Las Vegas https://t.co/eVZkMvXlb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have an interview for an internship today and I’m officially in panic mode !!! 😰😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had an escort to the door today. @ Keystone Pointe Health and Rehabilitation https://t.co/V3E8NJ7hos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanetBarstow Thank you sweetie and same here dear friend. Have a lovely wonderful Sunday. Stay warm and safe sweet… https://t.co/30MRvga1Bf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rainesghost @DaveVescio https://t.co/QcCmMANLRL                https://t.co/j7qmXy8HNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[psyched for @SpaceJesusBASS tonight 🤘🏼🤘🏼🤘🏼🤘🏼 make sure you get here early to see @sleepydragondub in Studio B 8-9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago Here comes the TransGirls Again!!!! Get Ready @ Innexile https://t.co/ZYbVfStme2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun with dabbers today! #typesofsentences #grabanddab #secondgrade❤️ https://t.co/uxVzvVIp2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitchhhhh I went to the bathroom to look out the window and I hadn’t closed my car door 🤦🏻‍♀️ when I got home I was… https://t.co/n7tCY3Haq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathyBarrow @EmilyRNunn I support this. I don’t know you but  Frederick is lovely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we try this &amp; get stupid drunk soon like asap lmao @briiiwith3eyes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cryptoecongames @trentmc0 Yes!! I wrote about this in our investment thesis!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neeratanden @SarahKSilverman It does not surprise me. When the president fails to follow the rules without consequ… https://t.co/LG9lvGxGxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rollcall The choice signals the DNC wants to move to the center to win the Electoral College]]></document></documents></author>