<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#FarewellProwler a steady, dependable and highly #adaptable flight platform and that has served many for generation… https://t.co/XrBnVV2DgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyWGR what if Rachel Bush thing is true.   What if not about play but how he felt about going to a Poyer frien… https://t.co/Jga9Z4m0IQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[DR: We need to remember and retrieve human values.   We have intrinsic dignity.   A soul.   And you can find that i… https://t.co/JKVvvfAVtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I'm not worried about a Disney movie not making money, because it will of course make money. I'm worried about… https://t.co/kevv8zvF86]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Padres there is is!! Pads up 4-3!! Just... Like... THAT! @FOXSportsSD #PadresST]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing Bohemian Rhapsody and The LEGO Movie 2 in one weekend means I have so many song in my head today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your body and mind will come back, will resynchronize with your world. It takes patience, humility, and rest. The b… https://t.co/jcyoPoYjiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like at any given moment I can look at my immediate feed and see 10 people who don't know how to use your/you're or there/their]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just in... You’re not allowed to “Stan” a band unless you know how and why that term originated. Except for ou… https://t.co/ZzRW3WEKrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ringer is there any #finaltable content? Would love to get @davidchang ‘s thoughts. Perhaps with @HousefromDC or… https://t.co/j1QQgpMpNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Poornavy1962 @DavePinFL @PCGuru0 @LouiseMensch @EWErickson https://t.co/ScToEXlVp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a great lil feature that's likely coming out in @NorthSouthNZ next month. Look out for it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBReich @AARP what are you waiting on to scream about this assault on senior citizens? stop playing both sides of… https://t.co/0Wylc86DnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[With _basic_ moderation (i.e. someone keeping an ordered queue of who speaks, and limits speaking time), at the ver… https://t.co/uWzC84jSLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimnTolomeo2 Como adquirio su Rancho Herencia..?o cargo de  Conciencia...?]]></document><document><![CDATA[...I'm doing what I received prior permission of to do. People attack/abuse me just for being who I am, having a bi… https://t.co/HbeKmf3Rjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always puts a smile on my face to see Neymar knocked out of competitions. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hissgldnmssr some fresh John Williams content you might find interesting. https://t.co/AqOF6lKZod]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unexpected Graduations, Unhappy Marriages, And Deep Regrets: The Usual Fates Of Those Who Grow Up Too Fast… https://t.co/HnbMfDQ4Ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 2 year old expects music from Google and jokes from Siri   #voicespecialisation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some parents don’t even support their kids... but once they start getting money it’s “give me this give me that buy… https://t.co/rrrivWP8JR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTN24ve EL  GRUPO DE LIMA DEBIO HABERSE REUNIDO  EN LA FRONTERA, LA CUAL ES TESTIGO DE LOS CRIMENES COMETIDOS POR… https://t.co/R3bCoSxsbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s the plug on young kids shoes my nephew been saving up and wants some retro Jordan’s !!! Tag anyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtgrizmimi @RoxFan17 It's like the old country song, "Mamas, don't let your babies grow up thinking Trump's not a criminal."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@porkforest @Ilhan @USAPowerlifting It’s really scary what some of these people believe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always Love talking with #bradenholtby from @capitals about #mindfulness #lgbt youcanplayteam @HRC #gorddownie… https://t.co/KRB7nZvLyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonysizzle @lil_bit_special @Schultz88 @GrittyNHL Nyiles was gritty before gritty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CunningSq16 @Suzyqfit4u @Steelerschic85 @CitizenWonk @EmmettMiche11em @caligalmags @calimom209 @LYNNIFY… https://t.co/1LALrYfONv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Denmark: One in five migrants say rape is woman's fault - Voice of Europe https://t.co/V2xR9ANyzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too bad that on some cars changing out a bulb is not a 5 min deal. Get it done anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eyelashes are supposed to keep things out of our eyes, yet 99.9998% of the time something is in my eye ITS AN EYELASH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping @Carvana comes through with this job emailed the recruiter and they are still interviewing she said I will f… https://t.co/VA62qoDQuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Carrots &amp; Sticks (2018) by @jackieosbrewery @ Grandview Theater &amp; Drafthouse — https://t.co/W0SakIDGyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe my ex had the audacity to cheat on me with someone who has a 200credit score.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get this draft wrapped up, but he is being too cute and distracting!  👶📝💻 https://t.co/KebgPzgdeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want all my players to win in life. To my guys past and present, I’m here to support you for a lifetime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancycol7762 @MichaelRapaport Fuck bein humble. U dont know shit about hiphop. Suck it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourFutureEdge what didn’t you wanna know about my experience with your great Bank? Why I left? Because you called… https://t.co/SJfgsWkIcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t help but notice the girls thst always complain about being broke are the ones that always leave early or gi… https://t.co/CDCOoydC66]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is big dick energy. Don't DM me if you ain't on this type of energy. https://t.co/IN2HiwLW8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now I’m guessing @BeckyLynchWWE is going to be added to the match tomorrow night because @MsCharlotteWWE and… https://t.co/0LxmgYCugY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@historylvrsclub The Salvation Army is one of the few honorable organizations that I know of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I know you think that everyone works for you, but the intelligence agency works for the country. Y… https://t.co/5yoUNlJCVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@henrykleeKTVU @AlamedaCountyDA @UCBerkeley @UCPD_Cal Is he even a student there? If he is, he must be in the exten… https://t.co/2c15F3dxpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StartupNation @gosharedotco @navSMB This is so ridiculous and he obviously doesn’t know how you treat your costume… https://t.co/pgGbsubljx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKGenest @AndyRC3001 It may be annoying but i don't think it is meant to be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @ASlavitt for your light humor today (and being able to brief Pres Obama in under 8 minutes!)...but also… https://t.co/JG8lfEkdAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not bad for an IPA. I'll drink it. - Drinking a Punk IPA by @BrewDog @ BrewDog Franklinton  — https://t.co/HwfrYGpz5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never give up. People will always discount you, and you'll always get rejected. But set your sights high. Be boldly… https://t.co/QR5YFtOn0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch with my bro!! Nice to spend time outside the cage and gym! @spartanlife32 @ Flagler Tavern https://t.co/HO8hXth445]]></document><document><![CDATA[Layover in Chicago. Should’ve worn pants. #WhatILearnedToday https://t.co/wbH0OVnA5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how Ben and Betty are distracting Devon’s dad so he can easily be sneaky and disobey him 😂😂😂 Was that staged… https://t.co/482OvrQAcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrettymanAlicia @ShaneDaleABC15 I've lived in Tucson 43 years. Tucson has never tried to wear big city pants. You're just wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews You’re an unfit coward One who takes credit for everything someone else does, but if some… https://t.co/hspYw6hRmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the future roommate @A_Jones311! Here’s to you finally turning 21🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers are lucky The Haycraft Brothers never made a band...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does your marketing plan have your business in full swing? Jim Strawn &amp; Company can help. #Marketing4You #SMM… https://t.co/zDcHVt3zfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[IVE BEEN IN A RELATIONSHIP FOR THE PAST 3 VALENTINES! IM SO HAPPY TO FINALLY BE BACK ON THE SINGLE LIFE ON A DAY LIKE TODAY🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dangchick1 @realDonaldTrump @GOP Damn Debbie that's about the strongest language I have seen from u. I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uepcsonora @Chaposoto @michelleriveraa @rquirrin @TribunaSonora @marcelobeyliss @megavisionmx @hilarioolea… https://t.co/2ABEA73feL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Assessing each team's chances of landing Antonio Brown https://t.co/1YO0KH38yv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Because. . .the Demo-CRAPs ARE hitlerian, by nature!!! Standing by for infanticide, corrupting our y… https://t.co/8NZ5y2WAEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[They just removed the derailed portion of that train here in Westbury. We’re live on the scene.… https://t.co/DXsfb59Q1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyCousinMoochie @Zigmanfreud Yet another blind Zig groupie suffering from TDS himself.  Seek help before it's too late.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at JW Marriott Austin - @jwmarriottatx in Austin, TX https://t.co/pS7sRvt5l1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarlisKezbers @netw3rk Oh Lord. I hope he didn’t see those God foresaken weird thumbs 🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-KY) says that President Trump has prepared to sign the bipartisan Borde… https://t.co/aIg1spwf48]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we don't change, we don't grow. If we don't grow, we are not really living. Growth demands a temporary surrender of security.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BirdieBaker2 @TellMyOwnTruth @MarfromSinCity @SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump One thing that tells it all is his appro… https://t.co/wsX3lb18mI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marchmadness @Hoophall @ZagMBB @LSUBasketball @MarquetteMBB @MSU_Basketball @RacersHoops This is horse shit. Where’s @JordanBone23]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Colorado Mardi Gras Type Party.  Maybe Clash of the Cocktails is ready for this place!!   Lets go!! 🍸🍸🍸… https://t.co/e6TmVob5Qc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrTroub1eMak3r @VexingVixxen Why a blizzard ? That's cold on the tongue which is not what it usually is . Peanut butter might work better .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sixers @BobanMarjanovic My hands are pretty big and I once shook Dr. J's hand and it went almost up to my elbow. P… https://t.co/4L5QWuJAnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darren Smith is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $2,867.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a $… https://t.co/MH6lcs9Wgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenMoore035 how on earth did you make it through the spider infested control center in #MetroExodus? Proud of you for facing your fears!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Hard Rock Hotel &amp; Casino Atlantic City https://t.co/wnYJD3q0oH]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re a piece of shit if you ever throw your friends under the bus to their parents]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussellFalcon Uh my day has been so busy whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa?.???????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomthunkitsMind Colin Kaepernick name will be etched in history alongside with many well-known civil right Icons.… https://t.co/8GJOoeA7pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freebasedtacos I just installed that shit. The nostalgia factor is high af]]></document><document><![CDATA[@booncotter Traveling abroad and experiencing other cultures foods and places are a cure for racism. Way more Americans need to do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch out for Kyle Young this year. He was limited by elbow issues last year, but could come back in a big way. He… https://t.co/u65oVaoEd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMVPCamps @diondre_glover @Mansell247 @CoachSkelton06 Balled..💯 the further is bright.. But he wasn't the only 1… https://t.co/v8X9sHIdGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The super soft Bonnie light wash short. Now available   #clothing #fashion #style #womendress #lookoftheday #ootd… https://t.co/wtd00dmJDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The pizzastone #Hearthstone card back is pretty epic, and is my current favorite. #cardgame #ccg #cards #games… https://t.co/YaIO6Egfjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm extremely proud of our team. Losing a game at the buzzer is always tough, but despite the hurt our kids stuck t… https://t.co/vI9lUuItoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cityzenpodcast Ok, ya thought i saw that. I think sane needs to be humbled. He could learn a lot through Sterling… https://t.co/LdRk5K3iSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madalynamoore Here’s a pic of my leg breaking 🤗 https://t.co/xppPLnzpyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@existentialfish @JudgeJeanine ...And your red dress makes me think you are a whore. Do you see the stupidity in yo… https://t.co/L5Xpo72NvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonPunchMan @GeoffHeartman @ImpishMATT I like FE. I just never got into any of them other than Awakening. I’d give… https://t.co/3FD51UrFnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember in courtyard Bubba used to blast Stunna 4 Vegas way before he was with da baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Well be prepared for our next democratic president to take executive action on it as if it were.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sweet and compelling night of intimate storytelling. https://t.co/5AYXZI6J3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcardib GORGEOUS goddess BEAUTIFUL queen I'm a big gay fan p.rican from the Bronx you are one of a kind never du… https://t.co/Z8bKeBMZYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianSandalow Hahahahahahaha 😢😭 only thing they’re going to do is watch SD do what they could and should have done, sign both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Father of 4 intro is absolutely wild lol, bananas! Got really bored listening to the rest tho till the features… https://t.co/JBbNBzsf3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayogastro No es mas fácil decir quien en vez de estar haciendo encuestas de cosas que ya sabe la respuesta?]]></document><document><![CDATA[time to smile a bit. "Thanks for Raisin' Me" Mother's Day Card for kids to make! #Cheesy gift idea |… https://t.co/0Dbiyh6LSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Capital getting into foul trouble in 4Q. 5 team fouls with 4:56 left. Same score #mtscores]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s unbelievable how Trump surrounds himself with the most nefarious characters possible, yet his Religious Right… https://t.co/KwosicJV94]]></document></documents></author>