<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Some of this week's sales circular from Nichols. https://t.co/MGjotAZcPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[He saw the best in me when everyone else around me could only see the worst in me he’s mine I am hears it doesn’t m… https://t.co/LW5CPxLuie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HanfordTrack. Remember, on Friday’s practice will be at normal time due to the PLC. We will be in the falcon gym a… https://t.co/dBLJ598uKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[A weekend of journalism history continues with @NetworkBway. https://t.co/vs0ZOUX7c6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph ESE. Barometer 29.851 in, Rising Rapidly. Temperature 49.3 °F. Rain today 0.06 in. Humidity 95%]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump It would be a celebration, and a bigger audience if President Obama was there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a fan of drag race and tennis means confusing @BelindaBencic and @bendelacreme at least 4 times a day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceNugent68 @robertbenzie @OntarioPCParty @LisaThompsonMPP I’m talking about sex education for elementary school… https://t.co/h4HWEzJdon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickLesogor @PeteBlackburn Someone payed for that. Nothing comes free my friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤙🏾 @samjaycomic @nbcsnl  . Book button in bio☝🏾 for salon appointment 📅 . Text button in bio ☝🏾for house call, offi… https://t.co/gIL0a4NS8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Younger people may not realize what a big deal this was. Here’s a good introduction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel was such a good movie #Disney / #Marvel did a great job showing love to #Stanlee and it's kinda sad… https://t.co/l2wLamh6fc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude hasn’t been on the field a lot these past few years cause of injury. Injury cost him a lot of prime years. He’… https://t.co/hzQezTcVJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get myself so mad just thinking about certain things lol I’m not well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifenews_ru Дозвониться  Путину? А зачем, он же награждён из ваших уст, нелестными эпитетами, и Вы ещё хотите с ни… https://t.co/jAFgxCDops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @Lake4963 A great example of AO-C's Socialism gone crazy, watch a Netflix film called "What Happened… https://t.co/gbitHV5Xgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have to meet all of their deadlines without question, but they can take their sweet ass with everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris7959 You said you were gonna call me so we can book our flight... it’s 24 hrs later.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msnicolemaria @morganbsachs y’all just can’t catch a break with all the weird hair going on. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @CantonRepdotcom The former Geisen Haus restaurant at 6955 Promway Ave. NW, has been purchased by Jackson Advanta… https://t.co/8EafGAF6pg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The final game of the Pac-12 regular season was a perfect reflection of the season as a whole. Awful, awful basketball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey all my Illinois friends, help us spread the word that Debbies moms house is now up for sale in Peoria.  Blessin… https://t.co/IVeQiYLVez]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was tryin to hit the hay early for once. Then @solangeknowles had to drop late night fire...fine! I’m up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse MrTrump, You have a long history of accusing others of your own faults- lying Ted, cro… https://t.co/1GzO9lROBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brihaus 0 for 5 last night...going 4 big bets tonight. i guessed on hockey and unlv/Nevada, used brain for UC and UL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpinky87 Spicy and sugary w/ alcohol... its sooo good https://t.co/Zx1tb7ncfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yaBoyCatah People who have this mentality are so corny. To be fair, you can learn a lot and develop from leaving T… https://t.co/Cldguehl0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to an unfortunate set of circumstances I have 2 tickets to the Isles-Leafs game on 2/28!!   Sec 213, row 8 seat… https://t.co/zFxk2TwFpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yah that’s why one is playing for a 2 a title tomorrow and likely two more are headed down there next week. Funny,… https://t.co/KewrQf0WNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎬🎞🎥 @ Scripps Howard School of Journalism and Communications at Hampton U. https://t.co/tORQi7KmsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ElCaminoDeLaJEPEs Pregunta: usted entregaría 500 mil dólares sin estar seguro de que se van a usar efectivamente e… https://t.co/YEl01Cpcam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @KimStrassel @WSJ I worry Barr is just another part of the deep state muck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aniela_88 Muy buenas noches 🌙💤😴😘 ANIELA y que descanses cuídate mucho y hasta mañana,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiet on the Coast (@ City of Half Moon Bay in CA) https://t.co/sB2xqPaypg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe it did because they normalized his behavior and didn't publicize information in the public domain about h… https://t.co/ySmAHnLvDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DocHoli44853949 @DoingRight1 Oddly enough, they would be insisting on others with guns who support the 2A to come… https://t.co/WECxpYYvdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s workout @journeyman_gym and post workout homemade chicken pot pie with rice &amp; no dough.… https://t.co/sQGy9S4CIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[99% of the time I’m clicking through your Snapchat video and not listening, every time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am with Jimmy Carter, voted for him twice. Never voted for Trump and I'm against Citizens United]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to Give Me a Clean Heart by Larry A.Hall Jr. #np on #SoundCloud https://t.co/0feNmkurPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prince_ital @USATODAY @hizousenextdoor @HwoodStreetKing @JudgeJoeBrownTV @Traffikmovie @DeidraLucas1 @bananavet501 Wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luckystreak12 @seanhannity @IngrahamAngle @GovBillWeld Just give them the same opportunity as everyone else. Too much to ask for fairness?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmi welcome to #Austin. As a local artist, I’m pleased to have your local presence. https://t.co/ymxyM51Z7Y.… https://t.co/nmZNrDqn0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colin_dunlap If Oakland gives up the 1 they got for Amari Cooper, it basically means they traded Amari Cooper for… https://t.co/1u0IgQ9rUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delegate @BurtonEstep: "Would you provide the definition of insanity please?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Selke37 @Ivan_Basic @_TyAnderson @MurphysLaw74 https://t.co/k4OmKxs16n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrNivAd @Innovationsjour @ISMICS The namesake says it all. The journal (and @ISMICS) is dedicated to “innovation”… https://t.co/iqxwuA53vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t need the alarm or the back-up alarm this morning. That booming thunder did the trick — perhaps too good. I’m… https://t.co/2hpbVxvdJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldMovieAds @RonFunches @JuddApatow I’m gonna assume they took both knees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't forget to add us and tag us in your pics on SnapChat rehabdance   💋 🎉 We look forward to seeing the fun you h… https://t.co/tJw7fXoNBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same, I think, goes for the Bernie Bro narrative. Yeah, plenty of Sanders supporters are nasty online. But their pe… https://t.co/7PrlbPGnSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Biggluvsbrkdown @mossow @NikkF07 @heelEvan @KwnStorm @christoplack Look at Johnny Gargano eyeing Ciampa's NXT Titl… https://t.co/YC0PhdCRKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Republican Party  Completely and Utterly Disgraced at the Michael Cohen  hearings https://t.co/2ewE2TWodK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ihatethedevil #sosad #helpuslord #yhwh #blessedarethosewhomourn #spiritualwarfare #comfortuslord #restinheaven… https://t.co/YNa3Ps4ptR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cesarbuenrostro @ArgoffTV @yohanandiaz @El_InternautaMX @MCOVIAN @EOtroShow @ufoofinterest Lo importante es verlos… https://t.co/q7QUJf3jG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would anyone attempt this on dry grass? And why not stomp on the fire to deprive it of Oxygen? Just a thought]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lags_TheCapper Bowling Green has blown 2 big parlays for me this season. They are dead to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a crock! A known liar to testify only on the left I Pray! My life is much roo precious to waste it listening t… https://t.co/oSgIxTvDn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going to be their superfan, hopefully they will recognize my  unique talent and pay me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almuerzo 😋 (@ Salito's Crab House &amp; Prime Rib - @salitocrabhouse in Sausalito, CA) https://t.co/uRQyTkdvXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG he did it again. Sean straight going to another level https://t.co/n3yuRyTX4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[T's and P's to all those adolescents in Lawrence who don't understand what they're feeling atm]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally none of my fellow photographers who i follow do this lmao i’m blessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotHereForThat @thesillybuddha Imma lace my butt plug with your ashes so you can destroy my guts one last time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All them old ass people hollerin build the wall need to be more worried bout who gon build they casket]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flashback when I was on the leaner side. #Me 👉🏽😂✌🏽🐦 @Sixp8ck - 📷📹 #ShreddedBeyondABSolute #PeopleWhoLifts… https://t.co/lMyrcgg213]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julianaazapata @halizzle My mom would hella make us these after swimming 💀 @hernanVVX @DopeFreshG21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ibrahimkase @xkeyscorobot @Ziya_Meral Well, let me start you.. I never knowed what the heck was really going on...… https://t.co/p1CSmdh1tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews I believe her..... why would she lie about this ???? My question is : When does she finally come to… https://t.co/rqrMqSpSkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[yeah sex is cool but have you ever cooked a steak without setting off your apartments smoke detector]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AzraVox @ComoNTvoyAKerer Zascoooonnnnn...en los hocicoooossssssss...😝😝😝😝😝😝😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are #sexy #bowls from #atlanticwatergardens . Get your #fountains #dialed by #thewaterboss #wichita… https://t.co/pfvv95owlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🚨 H O T  E V E N T  A L E R T 🚨🔥 2019 CI Weekend in Charlotte NC @djself  Tix on sale Now! Friday March 1st!  Link… https://t.co/PnyPaonh6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandow_john @scamarsn Valeu amigo, enquanto você tenta procurar os acertos dos últimos 16 anos eu vou jantar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terminando sesiones del Consejo Estatal de @AccionNacional #Coahuila donde nombramos vacantes de Consejeros, así co… https://t.co/e3DjmWFsw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Follow Friday! Check out these folks: @ZoserOfficial #FF @angryseattle @JuliaUgarte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MN_Wild_Fans Thanks for having some sense.  I like keeping the young D core together.  Would have been ok w adding… https://t.co/UZnPbmyxn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeDelMoro @JoeNBC @Morning_Joe Not sure but how does #Menendez get re-elected in #NewJersey ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve finally got everything merged and a few follow up releases out. If you use  a JVM language and need a super s… https://t.co/satNI73M2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianschatz Yes, on the floor! Mitch McConnell must not be allowed to hide this fight from the American people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #OrangeCounty on I 85 SB before Hwy 70 - Exit 170 #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The problem with the Esquire cover is that even the author is like...umm..that's not what I mean...to get at.. I've… https://t.co/Opf336AUW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports @ron_fournier Regarding the #wall expenditure, #California spent $5.4B on a "train to nowhere" and… https://t.co/WnAr9g1HHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for some mama slappin @ Collierville, Tennessee https://t.co/ujJEiQUDbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottchiusano @NYDNSports Their loss will be someone else’s gain. Good luck Scott you deserve only the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more grateful you are the more bullshit is thrown at you, but you gotta be resilient, stay grateful 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DZRishmawy Yes. Jeremiah also...but these were not developed concepts but rather prophetic hints at what was to co… https://t.co/RojoNK1q6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight's Homework:   Reading-Read for 20 minutes, log Spelling-3 times each, study for your test Math-Complete Mixed Numbers WS]]></document><document><![CDATA[022519 Craig's Weekly Penny Stock Picks for Monday, February 25th, 2019. Posted at 9:05 AM EST. @ Columbus, Ohio https://t.co/majkUHp3p9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This along with people fleeing because of taxes... Good luck with tax revenues!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that i might have to go back to work is really rubbing me the wrong fucking way right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebeccacoutcher @BettyWho Why it didn’t buy in the first place haha. Waiting for that Fri show!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh @TrueFactsStated Dershowitz continues to be an idiot ever since he started to realize his liability in t… https://t.co/aQllwdUCmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas saying Lamar Odom did crack cuz of that bitch is crazy... nigga was on crack b4 her ass. Pussy don’t make a nigga mad enough 4 crack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sorry. Im not gonna take limbaugh’s perspective as the definitive on this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @seanmdav Alexandria Cortez is the gold miner and has struck it rich.  10 mill for a video, money sec… https://t.co/OhVyMQkB6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Threatening U.S., Putin Promises Russians Both Missiles and Butter https://t.co/ff7v5TMJ8H  Doubling down with his… https://t.co/e3I3FW4GdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerbusJames @GodKingNobody @cxpage @BostonsBuddha @wiguy45 @LaurynHasIt @JBadass408 @forthemasses @NotATro04866731… https://t.co/gAmLBHVCiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowy hike in PHOENIX!! #onceinalifetime #desertpolarbear #itsadryheat #n2adventuring @ Camp Creek, Arizona https://t.co/0p8Qm0ELJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeltzerSaidWhat Apparently Ace Darling did a lot of the training... https://t.co/nL1LGbPwWg]]></document></documents></author>