<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@HughesSarge The reports I’ve read regarding the volume of business for those type of employees working under those… https://t.co/IcmFSWzAWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo mejor de ser soltero es que cuando terminas de comer 🍿 cheedar , no tienes que ocultar tus dedos manchadas de queso 🧀 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FactsMatter Cohen admits he has no evidence Trump colluded with Russians, 'but I have my suspicions https://t.co/6kYvffv4YE via @washtimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Delaware County, Pennsylvania https://t.co/N2eNALv7NO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery I’m trying to understand why @AOC gets off on telling people what they should and shouldn’t do or believe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Refs: We're going to make this game close Siakam: Imma ram it down your throat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hirnbrot @electronjs Just ia32, I'll make this more clear in the announcement. Thanks for asking!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late night return to the rink to wait for the boys coming back from Top Prospects, I brought my sidekick with me to… https://t.co/fL9zj1boix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE: GOLD-DRIVEN.  Are @NiaJaxWWE &amp;amp; @TaminaSnuka poised to capture the @WWE Women's #TagTeamTitles?… https://t.co/hph3kKgDm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the hell is the easiest way to have a polite non-conversational trip with your rideshare driver.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foldable phones have plastic screens? That seems like a bad compromise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@honestlyboxey @AFCWimbledon @DetroitCityFC This is one of your best ever ideas!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The marina walkway at Disney’s Grand Floridian Resort and Spa. #travel #waltdisneyworld #disneyworld #luxurydisney… https://t.co/Qf44JnE4rB]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those of you who know me, know how I am about planes. Soo let everyone pray that I don’t have an anxiety attack k? Thanks ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gym..yime.... Thank you jesus  DONT WORRY BOUT DAILY NEEDS PUT GOD FIRST AND EVERYTHING ELSE WILL FOLLOW.. @ Bedfor… https://t.co/6pfSNc32m7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepPressley @AOC The JFK marilyn monroe Mortensen Robert John jr2 Chris Lawrence Kennedy murders are solved by John f Kennedy jr and +Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was nominated by @Duhsj to post covers of #7Books that I love: no explanations, no reviews, just covers. Each tim… https://t.co/sZaN3x6geD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @Prissytxn You are a good man Mr Gaetz. And, no the threats are not less worthy.  Pls continue your effo… https://t.co/458BIMwQKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great chat about mystery writing from @lindasands @EmilyCarpenter @carriesmithnyc @hankjearly @swannyauthor at… https://t.co/yGhrS5IXnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenpellegrino Finishing up the HBO doc right now thinking the same thing. Incredulous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Hillcrest timeout. Patriots trail Blount 34-22 with 3:50 to go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canada is cold but beautiful. #igshotz #travelandlife #instagood #ig_udog #worldshotz @ Neville Park Photography https://t.co/KG6D74gsxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be getting talked bad to on insta 😂😂 “ bitch you think you to cute to text back “]]></document><document><![CDATA[And @SamfordMBB was up by 6 with 30 seconds in regulation and up by 1 in OT before last second heartbreaking shot a… https://t.co/QAbXHrq0kc]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Peter Tork (1942-2019) bassist for The Monkees @TheMonkees. Thank you for all the decades of entertainment and… https://t.co/PZIGTfLUS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first Inkpen Lab experiment - testing a dye-sensitized solar cell prep for our Chem Nano Lab course. As a maste… https://t.co/mG20HQFEtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[book worm - #PhotoOfTheDay #Photographer #Photography #PhotographyIsArt #ArtistsOnTwitter https://t.co/rnL98wRIUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diaz_manuel Y el problema es que no veo cómo esto vaya a parar. Yo ya estoy haciendo un plan B. Esto es una bomba de tiempo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet A very wise woman. In 90 years: * Teddy Roosevelt * W Wilson * FDR * Truman * Eisenhower * JFK * Reagan… https://t.co/MyvpAUPzE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/GzEwPeDDVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surfing... it’s a balance thing!  #pcb #panamacitybeach #gulfcoastsurf #30atribe #surfing #floridastateparks @ St.… https://t.co/icazX6JOMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gunnerswiftie13 Yellow like the morning sun Shining Light on the beaches there you find Swifty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like it will be a pretty quiet day for the #Blackhawks. If anything, they could move a Hayden/Perlini/Forslin… https://t.co/vMkwM6e6vY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ServantLucas Know a guy from Huntsville that could help the pen for the right price 🤑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sari- what else for a draft? C- most big tournaments have a pair that take the entire time.  I often bring a trade… https://t.co/CQTikpVmUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hardware Happy Hour (3H) #Chicago is tonight, 6:30 to 9:30pm, in Ballast Point Brewing at 212 N Green St https://t.co/r3y6i6o0BN #3HChicago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concrete Jungle  . . . #Brutualism #brutalismarchitecture #brutal #brutalistDC #brutalist #DC #architecture… https://t.co/j7eMI6kQZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st show of the night 🤘 Packed house and a fun crowd @vhcomedyclub 👏 #Ventura #Comedian #standupcomedy #jokes #805… https://t.co/4G7G3bKsPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BustersBelly @tommybyrne8 @WayneCGolf I think that’s photoshopped the sound it makes isn’t real it sounds like whe… https://t.co/EmSmlCoYi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisbjsmom Good point.  We offered cake.  And there was plenty junk food for her guests.  She just feels better from healthy eating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZibaLady1 @leach_deanna @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Great idea in real time so Trump could rebut each Q &amp; A!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opinion: I was one of the 500 people Michael Cohen threatened  https://t.co/33S6mFUhmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCPolitics And she shouldn't have to. If we can allow Bernie, Biden and others to hang around why hold her to a different standard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huskers Host Iowa on Senior Day Sunday Afternoon https://t.co/oBB0qc5mJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kristileenews Thanks for that. Some days it is hard to find these stories in this world. Wishing you much happiness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[bring the laughter. Chiste de Brocoli https://t.co/EGhme3h1UO... https://t.co/iJiixZn0La]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Refinery in Austin for a talk on global collaboration for future mobility #SXSW19 https://t.co/06ezOVgDCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fringe tulips on set with @kohls!   A perfect way to start a very, VERY chilly Monday! #MJSmoments #SetLife… https://t.co/l8VfqLjxdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Vienna Lager by @dbbrewingco at @bwwings — https://t.co/IDk2vwvYUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world is watching the @FTDWorldCup2019 @PhilaFlowerShow. Winner of the prestigious competition will be announce… https://t.co/CJFDOr95Rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[no sleep, just #hardworkanddedication #hardworkandsacrifice #trainlikeachampion #NGU @ Never Give Up Training https://t.co/3ftJp8SLLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ex-NFL player #JoeHawley @ManVanDogBlog gives it all up and travels the country with a dog 🐕 he rescued and a van 🚌… https://t.co/xUo7eDXm5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Draw The Line At This Demo Shit Letting People Swear In On Sharia Law Book For Congress! To Hell /W PC BS Pussy Foot Shit, Enough/W It?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 "If you would have put your coat down for me, this wouldn't have happened!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sounds like a great deal! Too bad @NYGovCuomo couldn’t give Amazon enough of New York City to satisfy the beas… https://t.co/41PWs3yRnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[End 1st: Dallas leads Pittston Area 19-9. Impressive start for the Mountaineers. Freshman guard Nick Nocito with two 3s and eight points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting #ManUp this morning and my brothers. @ New Life Church  &amp; Community Center - Decatur, GA https://t.co/L7QSjwlncA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackAftaThis With the 6th pick in the 2019 NFL draft the Giants select Mickey Rooney from Bowery Boys University!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBCASTX 😅  HOME!  WHAT A PRETTY GIRL SYLVIA IS!!! YOU HAVE CAUSE FOR CELEBRATION!!! PLEASE KEEP SHARING...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget about those still serving overseas. #RED https://t.co/hsvbVYgDmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right there inside that building Johnny Cash, Carl Perkins, BB King, Rufus Thomas, Charlie Rich, Conway Twitty, and… https://t.co/aeMZHG4FtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlakePriceTSN Sounds like 100% of the people don’t know what they’re talking about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoucheTimothy @_Drew_McCoy_ @JamesGeschke @evil_mara @NickRiccardi And 5 or 10% is low because many impulsive kill… https://t.co/cDjCVlCMyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canonlawyered @ccpecknold @cnalive The source and timing of #McCarrick's " Annuities" is important and could be et… https://t.co/hu6knbQoSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redhead4645 @DNC  n @DNCWomen : UR sick n twisted #FakeNewsCNN will not help U in 2020 U R TOO FAR LEFT that stinks 😷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LordLampington @Twitter Your profile pic looks like marshmello, just like him you'll crash to stay on my level. Harsh? I know. 😂😂😛😎🔥!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frightclubber  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kind of hope that Jussie Smollett gets sentenced to some jail time for this false hate crime attack just to boost himself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When she’s been actin up so you gotta come through and blow her back out &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barbara Roff would love to show you the #listing at 177 80th Street ,Unit 201 Avalon, NJ 08202 #Avalon #NJ… https://t.co/UO7MDBY9zh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby I only dislike Republicans because they are idiots! Who cares? Please Retweet! Keep it short. Brevi… https://t.co/uY8Dr21y5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sodjacket Incomplete picture. Success of the women's team brings in sponsorship revenue from directions that that… https://t.co/dXR2vW8vEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not ask me nut ass questions while we havin sex...   that ass fat right??   Shit not really ma 😂🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay, Dr. Foster!! Such a fantastic show that far too few people have even heard of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time the damn alert tone goes off at work I stop and pray it’s not around here. Not cus I’m a little bish or… https://t.co/UTPHbwkIv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yankeessarcasm1 @Patriots @NFL Lets go New England Sports!!  Cheaters at football and cheaters at life...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cowboy/Levi’s themed shoot. Going easy, natural light, just hanging out, walking around chatting and shooting to ke… https://t.co/ODZ3jh7pFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp can’t add either COMPLETE IGNORANCE MAJORITY OF AMERICA(70%)know 100%that trump is a life long criminal c… https://t.co/IG5yLfE2NK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jleigh40466485 @JonasAfrend @alllibertynews @OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1… https://t.co/lsd47ddG2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to think Trump was Putin's puppet, but now I believe he's his used condom, the one he used to screw America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt nine years ago. #music #guitar #liveshow #stage #musician #musico #valleyarts #biggercheeks😾 @ Upper Eastside https://t.co/OtLWpg32uR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndyMama8 @_NASDAQEnema_ Would you rather sit home &amp; do nothing? Just wait for a government check that allows you to exist?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normal people setting up a Skype video call and avoiding the camera perfectly:  Me: https://t.co/NOB27cKvIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharkhaywood @AOC Got a hundred bucks you don’t read it.......it’s much easier to live in this bubble of “corporat… https://t.co/ixP7BNPtl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AddisSaltyDog @RayGunVoss @THEJeepMafia @Legendary1941 @TopJeepers @ItsaJeepWorld @Jeep @SolarTJChick… https://t.co/pXHrQoMho9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Garporeon @TheDylantula @CerezaSkittles @ulalapudding Self-reflection makes you a good person imo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know some mfs who dropped out &amp; lives was never the same! This college shit a blessing but it’s really not for everybody]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethyrogers129 @TwitterMoments Teens who do join ISIS...there Parent's often have nothing to do with it since they… https://t.co/r459iBojeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmeltzer can you confirm the report that Simmonds found out on TV? I know it's not new in sports, but I don't w… https://t.co/QGVMCRZZdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FastLayne Layne and Zora are learning so much. VIN too. Can you see more adventures? Yeah in three more episodes?… https://t.co/B9a4ie4aFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Founders Day Brothers. Let’s promote Brotherly Love and Kind Feeling this Founders Weekend. #φφκα #PIKE151]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fayroberts No first person evidence, but I have heard one zillion stories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 1919 - German Freikorps volunteers in the Baltic port of Libau (Liepaja, Latvia), which they have captured… https://t.co/jGdfgFepcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, nunca vi tanto mamador en la vida como ahorita que entre a las historias de Torreón en Insta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's 'Word on the WAY' is 1 John 4:18-19 from The New Living Translation of The Bible. It says: ....   https://t.co/JRu7uI8vBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecl326 @TedLeonsis @NHL @WillieORee1 @repjohnlewis @Capitals That was 60 years ago!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not think this Anthony Davis situation in New Orleans is very good look for the NBA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ScottPelley  So is McCabe a ventriloquist with his hand up your ass, or did right that twisted anti trump intervi… https://t.co/k5HSTFoOL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to chat about a lot of my favourite things with Senator @DonnaDasko this morning! Engaging women in politics (… https://t.co/1fCJkYkZDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[En la cancha más fría de Mexico llevándole algo de calor 🐯🐯🐯💪🏽💪🏽💪🏽 https://t.co/hMhygnzJGb]]></document></documents></author>