<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thanks @KeriBarnum great idea. Mine is a #nonfiction using farm animals to tell a story about people. It’s an adult… https://t.co/lihMSqr5h0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SavannaSavage has been great at the plate so far this season for @lake_softball   In pre-district she hit .571 whi… https://t.co/gVsWlwumpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello, 16 weeks. Let’s be sicker than ever...sounds super fun 🤰🏼#sosleepy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilabachrn @pamsinfinity I’ll have to keep an eye out for him the next time I’m riding the subway...you never know. 😉🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLprintheritage Thank you! “Cornwall is a poor and very barren country of all manner thing, except tin and fish” I… https://t.co/TKv2lwGkFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am very jet lagged and don’t understand why I have an overwhelming desire for pie. Is that common for a 20 hour journey to get home?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help this Lonely Gorilla: Tell The Gorilla Foundation to Let Ndume Go Home... https://t.co/HBh9DrKYuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not love the world or anything in the world. If anyone loves the world, love for the Father …… https://t.co/JWoVxx8YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to senior football player @Keon_Jordan3 who just signed his NLI to play football on scholarship at… https://t.co/MXyeLTybiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@womenforwomenUK You Are Not Alone! #MessageToMySister 💜💌🌎 https://t.co/bAhJ3196Vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAST_UA so proud to extend our partnership with Barberton Schools ! @BHSMagics #AcademicExcellence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@segraves_todd @adalyfrey I’m still dying because he actually said men were systematically oppressed 😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TereOrt51687394 @ElbaklySami @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @gabryluce @Alcioni5 @evakoosiglesias @PucciaPatrizia… https://t.co/FCMcJSIANT]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy international women’s day to my bf because he always wants to act like a girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could you attend the wedding of any of your exes and be genuinely happy for him or her?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PA_Maday @kathleem @POCUS_Society @the_TOTAL_EM @EMinFocus @francisconorman @MedEd_PA Need someone to come to your… https://t.co/v3u0TzPGge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do i hear hypocrite? You make many mistakes and are forgiven but when one big mistake that equals to all your small… https://t.co/xz5KY9cHA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindachilders1 Humpty Trumpty rolled off a hill while playing golf, his dentures flew out, his hair nearly came of… https://t.co/U3CBe5q08v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bennnyv @schneidermayers Thanks, Ben - it's a fascinating study. Watch this space for an interview with Matthew, w… https://t.co/Wf9yot7x83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigbangtheory @WilliamShatner @ThatKevinSmith @kaj33 @JoeManganiello @wilw Love your characters! Love the show! Thx!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASEDawg89 @hind_leg Just my opinion. I think almost all food poisoning is from undercooked food. I grew up in the… https://t.co/OrgmFK5Oai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social Media Isn't a Silo - How to INTEGRATE Your Digital Marketing and Social Media Plan  https://t.co/7MbublOPeR via @mktgnutz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude slides into my insta DM’s then comments on a bunch of my pictures calling me a “lezbian”. Ok you right...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the breeze #persiancat #persiancatsofinstagram #feelslikespring #winston #winnie #newcurtains… https://t.co/AoGSjJXCKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know the streak has to come to an end at some point but I reallllllllly didn’t want it to end tonight.....and to these jerks #stlblues]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s happening tonight!! 🙌🏽🙌🏽 @Pink here I go 🤟🏾🎸#letsdothis ❤️ https://t.co/uSeitTVbQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOAL LADY LOBOS!!! Kiki Molinar knocks in a corner with 13 min left in the game. Lady Lobos Lead 1-0 #focus @LEISDAthletics @LittleElmHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prichardsonla I worked with someone once who had a clio.  I did news media production in DC for NGO and worked wit… https://t.co/7i0Cyf9d0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acosta Jim Acosta the reliable leader in fake news reporting we all can see?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OohLaTina I think everyone is extra sensitive now a days lol. I wish I would have waited to have a child. Obvi I l… https://t.co/xYjBR9paHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoganRutan You can still order online if you’d like https://t.co/4IRnWBVrP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigascg @FedEx It’s happened twice now.. im@about to feel the same way!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBROINTHEAM #CongratulationsYouPlayedYourself let’s hear the list Fam! 👂🏽👂🏽 #EbrointheMorning @HOT97]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyGilbear I’m a big baby??! The one who left because he wanted to catch a fit for whatever reason ?! 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnlegend #VoicePremiere So glad Matthew chose u as his coach. His voice is amazing! He’s definitely in it to win it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpokesmanSports @vinceg55 @ZagMBB I for one love Bill Walton — always have. He has fun and enjoys it all. Plus a r… https://t.co/Bx6uYyIkKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dat’s a pretzel necklace. 📸: sar.achaa bag o’ tricks @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/o98EVwBHMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@internet_gril @funder I don’t think he really does. It’s ratings, Baby! Reality TV!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between Wade’s buzzer beater 3-pointer and this #ForTheThrone poster I’m getting nothing done today. Sorry, boss. https://t.co/HfO4HZ7JbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayxCxV really came to MY school wearing a USC hat &amp; had the nerve to ask me why I was there, like I don’t go here????]]></document><document><![CDATA[since we bringing back everything , let me go try on my apple bottom jeans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parents,  if your child is a finalist in the Gavilan Peak Mandarin speech competition for grades 2-8, here are the… https://t.co/B4CqjvkJwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Sports industry has now died. It’s just unfair because of this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KailLowry You're a mother of 3 children, a crazy busy career, among other side projects, I'd be more shocked if yo… https://t.co/RekuD3thw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaryasCrystals Girl! I had one but he went to the Navy two years ago and said he doesn’t want me waiting but, he’s… https://t.co/pUujfNCskB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschreibz24 Girl keep pushing yourself. From one SPA major to another, you will thank yourself later for keeping u… https://t.co/AUi2YOjUDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadziwillLee Your such a giver !! That was awesome!! #LoveLee #FirstClass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonWyden @senatemajldr Its time for all U.S. citizens to speak up now and call your senators and request this be b… https://t.co/1Xu9uClHeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YogaArmy J HUD was amazing. I shed a few tears. Sitting here by myself watching all emotional. Pass the wine 🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[My only band related tattoos are Himsa, 18V &amp; Nick Cave. I’m okay with this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@american2084 @IMapatriot4ever @adnilxa @Archaeologist03 @CajunBlueAZ1 @BalueCat @L_a_w_a_n_n_a @thewebbix… https://t.co/XUtbJkSGS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeopardy First, best wishes on recovery. Second, what doctor does Justice Ginsberg have- she has battled this disease twice &amp; made it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left Delaney alone in my car for like eight minutes and THIS is what I find on my phone...btw yes she’s single ;) https://t.co/prRmTfrMG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m leaving Brandon’s wearing his sweats, a fuzzy robe I wore to bed and a zip up over it. What a look]]></document><document><![CDATA[People will fall for anything. Come on guys 🤣 Don’t quit your day job. #PutItInReverseTerry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I Film/Edit/Upload In one night?!   Yes I did because I was excited   NEW SEWING MACHINE UNBOXING -BROTHER RLX3… https://t.co/qaTzZ8YGpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiveImaginative @AndrewYangVFA It's not fair to assume that about people who don't need it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuicyJitsu @LKrauss1 It must be amazing being overprivileged enough to part of the outrage/cancel culture that is… https://t.co/7zPRCo6d8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will forever love this cover. It was a very bold choice then. https://t.co/5vG9pDeYwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The soundest lineup gets worse and worse every year. Lil Wayne is not relevant anymore. You guys need to stop takin… https://t.co/Ir5M1Lanek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please enjoy your weekend. I don't work a day in my life because I love all that I do. I wish that for my… https://t.co/d1PB26sRsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimsteinhart Man... I was so excited to go! I had just turned 21 lol and I notice this fine ass guy. Turn around a… https://t.co/XDxFa6o3CK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vestal grads in North Carolina! What a great place to reconnect... great to see you @CoganTeam4th !! #NCTIES19 https://t.co/Yvv36FeS3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Business tourism related messages (thx WP for hosting event and great view) I suggested Mike P and John B to hire g… https://t.co/8ioiJY959O]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Bast double spine rings. These are vertebrae from a deceased cat my in-laws found on their property. An entire… https://t.co/dtTWQ4InhK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lucedilucia It’s fricken wild. I don’t understand. 3-5 years experience or hell, even 10, is NOT entry level]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best channel on YouTube!!! Axe Truth.  Breaking Jussie "juicy fruity" Smollette orchestrated attack... uh oh U… https://t.co/0WWZTkcKm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wrote a review on COMBO: Pony-O  https://t.co/iLZxsATNsi via @yotpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm gonna be here at Venus Faire waiting for you today.... https://t.co/jbmY1jNpeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[the strangest things give me an ounce of peace. temporary but peace none the less]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanadensisMax @medical91 As an American viewing this thread, my heart goes out to my Canadian cousins. Please for… https://t.co/jRotVzFSBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so get this... this bitch dmd me talking about can u help me throw a party and she just turned 18. Like no sor… https://t.co/SsNtSwKq4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE ARE OPEN TODAY MONDAY FEB 18 10A-6P!! Come shop with us 💃👰👔🤵 @ Shannon Renee's Formal Wear https://t.co/YEQTbLJoE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[No puedo creer que en un area como sociología la administración sea una BASURA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino U r right! Our schools and colleges r teaching them that socialism is good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[MGM in Maryland and Global C happened the same year guys. This is why you see my simbols everywhere at MGM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starbs_n_carbs @momo_kenzz @baileyrae97 @Kensyi1234 if we see her, we throw hands ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know if it’s confirmation bias, travel weariness or suggestion but I have shit to do this weekend so please… https://t.co/GaVsNj9VdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods Also her saying HE kissed me like that doesn’t just happen he’s 10ft tall she put some effort into it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so conflicted because Alex hasn't come home from work yet because I know he's still sleeping like I wanna call… https://t.co/0cYq0BwLuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vendaval @KenJones707 @PlanetLuvie @neeratanden You keep misunderstanding me — twitter makes this conversation too… https://t.co/re7aedzLrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My h e a r t 💔 You can do this, Alex Trebek! What a positive response to such a frightening situation. You’re truly… https://t.co/7zZymDktj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Lolyouwildwyd I do have to work ALL 3 DAYS but they not tryna hear me 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnv378 @HillaryClinton @BernieSanders I am a grudge holder...the grudge I have with Bernie is personal! #neverbernie]]></document><document><![CDATA[This stupid filter is forever my favorite💕 @ Pearl District Downtown Portland https://t.co/uJ9l03rMBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don’t know if I’m gonna get there”  means - I don’t love you and I don’t know if I could.   #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MondayMood Stoked! Thanks to @thedavidcook with @andyskib 😉 Check out Dave’s IG story😘🎶 https://t.co/hsqGnhxjkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Z100NewYork has your chance to win tickets to see @Pink for her Beautiful Trauma World Tour show at… https://t.co/0yhdhcB0Ff]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel sad today so i wore hoops to remind myself im a bad bitch :,) self care]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should go out bc my feelings are hurt but ima stay in and be a good girl 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[When he knows he is doing the best thing for our country, no matter who’s against him, President Trump will find a… https://t.co/UaBeM3jGen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirefightersHOU @Esther188rod  I VOTED FOR PRO B HE TURNER CARES ONLY FOR HIMSELF LIKE POTUS44 NOW I SAW TURNER TE… https://t.co/TlJ5XcedJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tapered &amp; READY!!!! #ryareadytolookgood #ryareadyinc #robinreadycuts #ryareadyinc #coils #silkpress… https://t.co/EaxrspmlrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for this! You do such a good job and the topics are always fascinating!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oprah please PLEASE ask Stater Bros to start carrying your products! Please? #OhThatsGoodPizza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blown away by #FindingNeverland well done @HBO and @Oprah! Please watch this series plus #Oprah interview and educa… https://t.co/8JsM3rPoIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#toungeouttuesday #mood #funny #puppyoftheday #plotthound #insta #dogsofinstagram #famous #photographer #model… https://t.co/q38cUlgJC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends left me alone at the bar with gays and I’m scared https://t.co/47GSz3caHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[اللهم استرني فوق الأرض و تحت الأرض و يوم العرض  لا إله إلا أنت سبحانك إني كنت من الظالمين]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MajorMainex @Lil_Kimmie_Vert @JoyyUnSpeakable The process just took me out]]></document></documents></author>