<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What if you could educatain like this?  Amazing dancer JT!   I need lessons. @ Pechanga Arena San Diego https://t.co/mIcfFywRwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonHuffman @PylonEliteCamps @bangulo @GregBiggins @ArmondSr @gogettadarion @RyanClaryFSP @HeirFootball… https://t.co/F1i3bv8daw]]></document><document><![CDATA[it is a time honored tradition for my mom and i to be in a constant debate over whether Bohemian Rhapsody was accurate/queer enough]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WTEN @LexiNahlTV This is really scary for me because I frequent this Dunkin’ @dunkindonuts @DunkinNYCAP location a… https://t.co/3xdogPwPjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny how the only time this bitch will acknowledge me is when she’s in a locked car 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deanjnorris which brewery are you making your beer at? Is it one of our local breweries? BTW it’s always nice to s… https://t.co/orDijScLka]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christian LaBossier takes it to the hole for Abington, pushing the lead to 14 late. 64-50 Wave. @GlobeSchools]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, Kliff Kingsbury has been fantastic in QB evaluations/development by not overthinking things. Does the kid dom… https://t.co/YocfPSRkNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of the leadership Jesse and Tess provide on campus and at the conference level for VU student-athletes!… https://t.co/3tQZZepqZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family Dollar will close nearly 400 stores - CNN https://t.co/lRMAuAKYxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Proteautype I hope so and yes, I thought that third period was the recipe for how to potentially beat Boston. Comp… https://t.co/bVoTZ3DrSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barely made it (@ Charlotte Douglas International Airport - @cltairport in Charlotte, NC) https://t.co/OfT1l3rNmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@znwright @mmelgar09 @DrDixonFtW @DrRobDPC @DavidBalatHC @Pilchard101 @adamtabriz @TPPF @kksheld @VanceGinn… https://t.co/ocFHlwQflg]]></document><document><![CDATA[And my boy balled out too, then raiders are dangerous. Final 4 mark my words]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very impressive beatdown on that maggot Stephen Miller by Chris Wallace. Miller represents EVERYTHING that is wrong… https://t.co/qyEdzK5hzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SIL_Silvilau Hola Sil..se ve que este es un "woolly mammoth" quizás ! Buenos noches Sil 😁😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harmonix Please be at PAX East! Please be at PAX East! Please be at PAX East! Please be at PAX East! Please be at… https://t.co/KWJfZXHhja]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gary Barta, Iowa AD: gary-barta@uiowa.edu 319-335-9435  : Reinstate Gary Dolphin: Iowa Hawkeye Radio Broadcaster -… https://t.co/Gfck72ggEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magagary687 @wattswebedawgs @JoeBiden Should have said America is embarrassed. And sorry, will fix with next election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debralazebraa I use almond milk, I have almost 2 years with out drinking regular milk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irvingact3 @PainvsGuilt Thanks Peter!! Me too, quite comfortable with a great design! 👍😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reppin @cougs4recovery in Dig D! @WSUPullman @RyanDLeaf @ARHE_tweets @YngPplRecover https://t.co/Qdah05XIqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los que no querían amnistía para los delincuentes estos deberían estar contentos porque hoy confirmaron que prefier… https://t.co/UNMTSAk6ry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Butts: only involved in SNC on a few decisions. Now he outlines why PM thot this was a “public policy issue”.  “So… https://t.co/uBQfkzXnfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork @AP Filmmaker Ava DuVernay  tweeted that she “can’t blindly believe” the Chicago Police Department. Even… https://t.co/VrvgJLuDkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alonso7349 Sorry to hear that! Seems to be a common occurence these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heilung | LIFA - Krigsgaldr LIVE https://t.co/3GjhsdiRdO via @YouTube As dusk nears and I am walking through street… https://t.co/Nzi5iXHqCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's probably going to vote with the Dems, you know he's not all the way in with the POTUS / he's got lots of never… https://t.co/5tcwzW5476]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmamas1973 @CMichaelGibson @rwyeh @DrTimKinnaird @TarekOmarNafee @dr_mosama @DrHBulluck @NickCurzen @robindharia… https://t.co/BnwqragigM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Notice they didn't ask him whether he thinks that Russia stole the emails from the DNC and leaked them to help Trum… https://t.co/qHbf9SH81i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sports_Shorts why does it feel like eveyone is getting punished but the guy in charge?? He did hire Wade right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuzHaggerty Once you pain control it takes awhile to get it back under control. Of course you know this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[pet peeve is people on level two who correct my usage  I usually respond with "say that out loud and tell me if it… https://t.co/7e5gS2Bwee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ricerocket Fug iiitttt!! If she’s not enough for you take initiative, she aint the one brother]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the top-100 NET team rankings based by conferences. (Minimum: 2 teams) https://t.co/J5kqDWucnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TTPLOADING I'll be around the Sacramento area soon if you guys are looking for some scrim guys. Good luck!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson I am not saying he is guilty but this would not be a surprise if Trump were doing something unlawful… https://t.co/bGjQ6N7m30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathySue17 @benshapiro I think the bodies he would lay to waste would be legendary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard most things break By the ends of these types of nights https://t.co/NhQtpCoSi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phx787 @jeff_gluck @NASCAR @DISupdates @LVMotorSpeedway @CocaCola @CLTMotorSpdwy @ISMRaceway is also a track I wan… https://t.co/Xo3K9dziLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nkotb #karaoke #giveittoyou @jordanknight @donniewahlberg @jonathanrknight @joeymcintyre @dannywood @ Khartoum https://t.co/V8T1TKRJun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAM_Barrett This makes Kay Bailey Hutchison the ghost, which seems right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldlakerss what’s your realistic preferred starting lineup next year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iOS 12 Jailbreak just came out today, real ones know what I’m talking about😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living my best life.  #lasvegas #lasvegasstrip #vderahotel #ariahotel #hairstylist #miamihairstylist #vacation… https://t.co/6sSP2V7fqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular preseason prediction tweet... if the @cubs don’t sign @Bharper3407, they don’t re-sign @KrisBryant_23 at… https://t.co/yTB0C1SzSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking point Venezuelans Fleeing Crisis Face Desperate Hike to 12,000 Feet https://t.co/OBXmP1gQBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 new caps made in America all for 5 bucks different sizes different styles @ Robertsville, Missouri https://t.co/9sIPCJ0FQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine if conservative media held the president to the same standard as journalists and the entertainment industry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 Facts About Roy Rogers, King of the Cowboys #FunFactFriday @CoreBTSLI @CoreBTS @DW_Educator @mtvisme  https://t.co/VsmXwrDbBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am blessed and honored to say that I will be continuing my tennis career at Southwest Mississippi Community Colle… https://t.co/V0IyHuoENW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@polishprincessh You groping little girls is what’s embarrassing you old fool!!! https://t.co/pEoVK8daqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[To my neighbors, those trash cans rolling down the street are not mine. Mine are tucked safe and sound. https://t.co/R3aHSL6DXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very powerful and moving talks by the Rise Up Champions at World YWCA @Millennium1UN with #CSW63 #YoungWomenRise… https://t.co/ywG8QGwmpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#weekendrecap📸 #firststopsupport @leggz1075 #allwhitebirthnitecelebratiin 🔥🔥 @ White Eagle Social Club https://t.co/EDQNfvGhRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisJohnson135 Not quite that far, but we have an on-line ordering option for delivery that I can shoot ya. :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm having random flashbacks to @kylieminogue's NYC pride show because it was just that amazing. And I remember whe… https://t.co/LKCqx5M1wa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BecketAdams Basically every early 2000s Will Ferrell movie. https://t.co/NuTqicJdZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WGR550 You guys need to expand your commercials on the Radio App. Same commercials over and over and over and over again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Irra_UberTigre @LaClasicaChica Nel, perro supongo que ya viste tu error 😂😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the end @KHSGirlsBball hoped for, but a very good season nonetheless. Thank you Seniors for laying the foundati… https://t.co/IsqlTtuKYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let no man deceive you by any means: for that day shall not come, except there come a falling away first, and that… https://t.co/J61rrSnf98]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is @colton actually Andy Dwyer? #BachelorNation #NailedIt https://t.co/DmCfLHfnq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[IN THE U. S  WE HAVE WHAT IS CALLED A BLENDED ECONOMY - some capitalism and some socialism - THE TAX CODE IS HUGELY… https://t.co/exsBgAfoJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarryIsFunny @TheProducerNick @PackManJoel Dude, I would totally watch this!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryancurtis @ringer It's pretty simple.....  He still wants to play and rushed himself into retiring, because he landed the MNF gig.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConstanceM2015 @ArmorocCA @TenaciousPita @lisa_kirkby @TPSOToole @Jenny2Hugs @BrentCushman @arek_janula… https://t.co/8Aioro3zut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradrobinson8 Exactly!! This is just not a good look in multiple ways for Bob.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida Bar Will Investigate Matt Gaetz’s Threat Against Cohen: Democrats said that the Florida congressman’s sugge… https://t.co/05RFd4L00B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence So glad you can go back home and rest, get plenty of it. Can’t wait to see you back to full health! Als… https://t.co/s5sIS0VsEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guptanator @yungsids Slap put a minus sign on the right hand equation in place of the plus, and put the resulting… https://t.co/DbXYTK7rK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't care about Brock Lesnar, If he wins at wrestlemania I will stop watching Raw all together and just watch Sm… https://t.co/sUzImVS2LC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t slept this good this whole week lol what a refreshing night it was. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lululemon Will you please make me a hiking jogger? Belt loops, rugged material, thermo and light versions. Why we… https://t.co/rkq2G9SZW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayBilas enjoy some of the world famous @Rupp_Arena ice cream at @KHSAA boys basketball state championship. https://t.co/9GkmSsAtJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making breakfast for my wife. Breakfast includes mimosas. Had the flash of insight that mimosas for breakfast means… https://t.co/nL4ft77Omd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregShugar @DonaldJTrumpJr I'll take that bet,  there is a sucker born ever minute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kah1071 @FireBoBahnsen @ClayTravis @brantleysalter FBI wiretap and providing prostitutes for players is totally di… https://t.co/v4qYSpsEsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bundle up out there today, and @TwitterBoulder Tweeps don’t forget you Boulder Office beanies. A warm head is a hap… https://t.co/bdTO77xyvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Really? No democratic billionaires? Are you friggin serious? AOC you’re nuts. Trump 2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't get me wrong, I'm STOKED for Star Wars land. But let's talk about this "food"...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when you thought the #cbus couldn't get any more exciting #Satchsquatch is at @COSI discussing movies with… https://t.co/RznmGhUhBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senarosalie @lrroze89 It was about Benny Beaver transitioning to Magic Mike. Way to miss a Joke, about as bad as y… https://t.co/Yzscmj27U7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether Jaeoydeoans dad sends a hitman after him because ant keeps commenting on his insta or ant dies in Afghanist… https://t.co/pVeuC5Z2dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Apple's new #Veteran and military affiliated store shows how they care for us. Thanks to Apple's commitment to UD,… https://t.co/8KufRuJJel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ameen!!!! #AsaalamuAlaikumWahRahmantuillah #Alhamduillah #Allah #AllahUAkbar #ProphetMuhammad #PBUH #Quran #Hadith… https://t.co/eV1unNJdHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiamiHEAT @miaheatbeat @ThisIsUD I can’t believe LeBron left this. He was so happy. He could have won two more rin… https://t.co/RlADdPoMES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteTyreekHil1 @TalibKweli @LqLana @spaceboyxL I am so confused as to what the white version of a black man is. I… https://t.co/qeh5hclF7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is really low of a mother to do, I hope you get instant karma for this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump, Love him or hate him, how he continues to function with all the negative BS happening]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is this sassy fellow who showed up in #Istanbul? https://t.co/WX4ksRmPPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash They should put Schiff on trial. Liberals are like gangrene.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really shocked by this. I thought he was exceptional when I saw him last month at the @CanadaGames . Plus, he was o… https://t.co/6O8fEj3dbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe us when we say it is coooooold out there this morning!  With a -5° start in Wolfeboro, wouldn't a hot cup o… https://t.co/ibW3JLfWVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspirational steps at my secret Monday location #allengittelson  #mentalwires… https://t.co/kzrAzvax8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[U kno i gotta stay ten toes, i ball like LaMelo and Lonzo https://t.co/mbxwPXZzci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ian Lynch- Pay Dues (Prod. Ian Lynch) by IanLynchMusic | Ian Lynch Music | Free Listening on SoundCloud… https://t.co/cABg0byKFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MastercardCA @Raptors Congrats to the @Raptors. My son and I attended our first game ever a few weeks back. It won… https://t.co/umGQ58mZva]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @inesison Obamass was nothing but a talker and you know this. Then he feloniously gives Number One na… https://t.co/ocyE2U9wIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaEgan5th @FlakePE @Tabschools @KidsHeartChall @tabernaclehsa @LSantoroPE @barrykid1 @DrPatersonTES @SueGrosser… https://t.co/QQGfRgnlk8]]></document></documents></author>