<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JeffGordonWeb @NASCAR Stumbled on this tonight and relived the era when I first started watching @NASCAR   Flooded… https://t.co/KpTroIjfXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried a new machine at the gym and got my @$$ kicked. #Worthit #HealthierandStrongerEveryday]]></document><document><![CDATA[The NCAA Tournament’s first four automatic bids all belong to teams who were NOT the top seed in their conference t… https://t.co/Vofo72a1ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @MT_for_delegate at the @VaDemocracy meeting tonight! https://t.co/UCdUFflO9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Invest in People and Systems for better Results  https://t.co/k4a9w5ohxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiggerHall @PattyNCaddy Thanks for making my day! Means a lot having some fans back home!! @DiggerHall]]></document><document><![CDATA[America could ease some of it's sanctions ,following NKs moves in ending testing and dismantling some sites.I am no… https://t.co/snpYsVeGP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[kurtvile always makes it look so easy #Prettypimpin #concertphotography #Denver #Dnvr #Canon @ The Ogden Theatre https://t.co/WhnbBJ8VsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check Out Mobile Alabama’s First Wax and Wellness Bar Candi Lash... Owned and Operated by @candilash ... Book your… https://t.co/0P1AzHjTIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are a creative agency focused on inspiring people through seamless experiences and we are currently looking for… https://t.co/Ditg6D6xPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cognitive dissonance of the right is pretty incredible to see in action. At least we admonish our own when they… https://t.co/px0kRVFqwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baseball_life26 A guy who may have never had a real chance of nothing happened last year vs a guy who thought he’d… https://t.co/XeOLnpl7He]]></document><document><![CDATA[All things considered, lovely day to be outside. - Drinking a Haze by @TreeHouseBrewCo @ Winterfell  — https://t.co/wQ8seHI2ZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewGHaines this is who I mentioned to you, he does great work for the @FL_Everblades 👀 🔥🏈?   @STBVisuals]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commercial Duct Cleaning! AdvantaClean offers a FREE MOLD inspection. Call AdvantaClean  MOLD REMEDIATION - WATER D… https://t.co/oKmePaYs0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your bosses, the American people, are tired of all your excuses, all your self-aggrandizement, and all the whining.… https://t.co/UrcUIoXsEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funnels make me money, websites made me broke 🤑 #DigitalMarketer #FunnelHacker #Clickfunnels #Bootstrapper @ Philad… https://t.co/7KWXTwINry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Too Drunk To Funk by @105westbrewing @ 105 West Brewery — https://t.co/Q8Z96IAXBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elgatopolitico_ Apoco no..desvergüenza la del canallin..ese cabron ya no hace contrapeso..ni con su vieja..mejor c… https://t.co/zDzHDSGFZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks so much 🎶BigTime Radio🎶 Vegas BTR International for spinning my single “Livin’ It” 🎶👍. Written with Amu Chen… https://t.co/dgOEO6mzrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are already in the Communist totalitarian regiment. If you are from Trmp’s circle, you have Muller hunting you.… https://t.co/5H0YXtA8Y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE = No Black wwf wwe champion in the history of the business. There has never been a black man as wwe champion.… https://t.co/KzcxI2PJVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[agency became my favorite word when jerks kept trying to walk all over me. Know it. Demand it.   You control your… https://t.co/vkGLJMHX0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingrob619 .....are you sure your school wasn't just messing with you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too good not to share! Thank you tobymac and @HonestlyBex for this! C'mon! #GiveItUp #HeCanHandleIt #SpeakLife @ Fr… https://t.co/F3ZAPul0C3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Telcel Que pésimo servicio tiene en Monclova tengo más 40 minutos para hacer un par de renovaciónes y a la 1 se va… https://t.co/6tMZie3f9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RochieWBZ @wbz Watch out for @JackieBradleyJr. I think he's going to have a monster year, and he's already the best defender of the bunch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toadsanime Super Baseball Simulator 1.000 (create your own teams and players, and fun power ups)  Super Mario RPG:… https://t.co/nkoEufvExf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel very late to the game but wifey and I discovered @mulaney tonight on Netflix and can't stop laughing. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnKAG2020 Dems are the obstructionists? McConnell kept the shutdown going by not bringing up the vote. Republica… https://t.co/Z7ZXSKr2dX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TToQEsther Read the book of Ruth. That will help. Ruth 1:20 NKJV [20] But she said to them, "Do not call me Naomi;… https://t.co/bIISA7EH7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murggg @CauseWereGuys Saw it and thought about it lol It’d be so eay to make]]></document><document><![CDATA[No triunfarán más: los "líderes" en solitario y alejados; los equipos en silos; las ideas no fundamentadas en datos… https://t.co/Qtyuefqubc]]></document><document><![CDATA[~ ONE WEEK AWAY ~  • • •  2019 • • • Tuner-Evolution  ~  So Cal Anaheim Convention Center February 24, 2019 12pm ~… https://t.co/uFy44pq2yP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DurhamNtx @isis_whitehead @ladyhawkerfinds @Minervasbard @Verumvox @SlythSeeker @tracyreynolds67 @LacieChainD… https://t.co/Phc4nK1bNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmendy23 @bencoker24 @RorkeFinley 5 weeks in on his road to recovery. Thanks guys #teamACLrehab https://t.co/VBMFigEkns]]></document><document><![CDATA[And that’s what that option is for . POTUS understands this and has exhausted all other options thanks to the Democ… https://t.co/I0pk27iJc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks like we're stuck with #Monday again. Will try to drown it in coffee...hope the rest of you have a good day… https://t.co/ioNxU0HRiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawnareynolds3 @Sprite At your local gas station... at least in the Dale]]></document><document><![CDATA[You completely stole my heart, and now you won't let go.❤🎶 https://t.co/CWZinYY7D0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hhendersonphd I still think they need to sit down and handle it like men, behind closed doors.  It would work bett… https://t.co/WoH3tMQ5Ye]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #BusinessMgmt job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. eDiscovery Senio… https://t.co/B2tz5xY5rh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an IPA by @livelybeerworks @ Penny Hill Deli Bar &amp; Char — https://t.co/dG73USwVrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeloncholy @Ballatw It's legit the "iPhone" of Androids. I was a Samsung guy for so many years and now realize… https://t.co/F6RpWwVyFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never walk around security with me if y’all wanna kill me try and finesse me go ahead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven't smoked in like two weeks but I'm lighting one up thanks to you. Fuck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[During #CohenCongressionalHearing @GOP went full “Liar, list , pants on fire” mode they even brought a sign!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want the Ducks to go all " let's pretend we are playing Montreal" tonight and Tuesday night!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bellagiotime If it snowed, the wiper tray would stick a lot of the time. Designed without snow in mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsSaraMeshmesh @realDonaldTrump “global waming” - he’s not to up on #GlobalWarming]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS Did someone say Mueller report? Is that why the Nosferatu of New York visited you last night?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Seahawk faithful is ready to go for the #CAA quarterfinals against Northeastern. https://t.co/baA935Yvys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see what I’ve been music directing the past 2 months https://t.co/NiWxofKVhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy nuestro presidente exhibió a los Panistas por oponerse ala guardia nacional.   Estan cabando su tumba cómo part… https://t.co/KmyzsoBG87]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your children, scratch that, if you are not watching the Magic School Bus with your children you are missing out… https://t.co/FCvkn61PNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ckinney8_ @JArmadaMusic @_CameronHayden Bro he from Jacksonville and tryna act like he’s some sort of killer LMFAO… https://t.co/9RK0QyX8sq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlvaradoSheny Muchas gracias Sheny e igualmente deseo que lo sea para ti cuídate mucho,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okcthunder goin all in this year! Congrats @DeandreAyton ... I mean @Keefmorris https://t.co/JsKsIG3eHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@livingdeadguy I think they still have a couple of inches. they’re warming the next few days so it’ll melt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing to see here. Just a blown V8 powered bug #vwbeetle #vwbug #bugout #bugtussle @ Famoso Raceway https://t.co/5cwqSyxqKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicken pie at Mydo Pie, the Chinese meat pie chain from Singapore in the Puente Hills mall @ Mydo Pie https://t.co/M7OYYUwxkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in Salem, NH, check out this job: https://t.co/kiIHAObpbB #Simon #Marketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dems can not win the elections of this country, with the Americans Vote, so they want to bring illegals immigra… https://t.co/hjO8aF3ITk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday’s are for the boys @ Morehead, Kentucky https://t.co/xKXExrjARE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMErikaNGIRL07 The Police were there before ..... Glory to God and thanks to those that Pray]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValleyHoosier @Jones1213 @SecretMarquette @Snewb22 Curiosity question. Does Texas belong in? If they lose to Kansa… https://t.co/x4SqBGFgkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinHowell71 On that night, I did make @MattMorganESQ  my Bitch, but just that one night.  I am so sorry Matt. LOL🤩👑🌟🎳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBabylonBee Whoops, I was wrong. https://t.co/J5UUuaqoUs is back up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working  hard @ Red Lion Hotel Orlando-Kissimmee Maingate https://t.co/lilbkL6iNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perhaps even some of our local schools have succumbed to these pressures @CatzAthletics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @Todd_Gutner temp in Topsham is 23 we only have 1" on the ground roads in Topsham just snow covered right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gorgepulse @trimet So you want to single track every station.  Even though in the NEC and in Japan, high speed tra… https://t.co/aZMsyiMvil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wrnielsen @PressSec Jealous of such a strong woman is what you are little minded man! Did you get beat up by the girls when you were young?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrimDawn Perfect! My birthday!!! Can't wait! Thanks for all that your team does!]]></document><document><![CDATA[apenas tengo tiempo para decir que, es muy grato volver a ver al @ManUtd volver de a poco a ser el equipo grande qu… https://t.co/jkkfHppNSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aqualung21120 @PanovskiIvo @LordSmile_ @wessel2008 @StardustPokmnGO @REVERSALYOUTUBE You know what's funny... befo… https://t.co/XzCUdYx87k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone know if @brunelldonald is still a supporter of @potus? If so I would like to see more of her in the med… https://t.co/oAw3bASobS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of unhappy olympic hopefuls today after @iaaforg posted the qual standards. They are TOUGH and if you’re not e… https://t.co/ZYvdOYYUov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missouri women up to a 5 seed in the latest ESPN bracketology. Tigers are playing in Marquette in the latest predic… https://t.co/vpMR8QBEYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Metrobusinfo I sort of feel like you should be able to check incident reports from last night. The X9 at 6:45pm st… https://t.co/e7ZLFDxXh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ninja Yeah and just wait till they get comfortable with you cause it all comes back. Bad fart messy hair allat 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahSpain I see this and it hits me why so many are trying their damndest to talk up KD possibly leaving and the… https://t.co/dEyaxcclYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @WiDS_Canada and @ChiefBordeleau for the opportunity to attend the WiDS Special Memorial Scholarship Brea… https://t.co/RuMWV0iG1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for Kentucky fans and the Reid Travis tweets. SmH take that L graciously Slaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sophiegeorge23 came up big with 15 pts in a hard fought Lakes Region win for @TiltonGVHoops #keepfighting… https://t.co/d03mMutcuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful start to the day... #canhardlywaitforspring #thegraylife @ Seattle, Washington https://t.co/YJWEEZm9za]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it being a level 7 #google #localguides thank you for the socks. I will use these everyday. @googlemaps… https://t.co/pL7ceoC76R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squattchie The short answer. Yes.   A maybe answer would take several pages.  All the pros and cons]]></document><document><![CDATA[Assuming @realDonaldTrump loses the 2020 election 😏, not likely at this time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewieGilchrist I mean if this reality “Star” beat her she should hang it up for good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apiecebyguy My guys he's one of those that thinks he's gotta train with other weapons for when the libs take all his guns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwardSpiker Thanks for Following! Like a good spy thriller novel or know someone who does? Please check my author… https://t.co/gulUmlRKkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The recently terminated conference in Warsaw had that objective, which was clearly expressed by Israeli Prime Minis… https://t.co/1IjaDrjP4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[TEAM NATIONAL  Are you an Automotive Dealer that is looking for a great way to expand your business? Please review… https://t.co/5UGy6yiiwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tellement de belles conditions ce soir pour le #clubdeglisse @LoupsCCMB @CcmbOrleans Une belle neige légère agrémen… https://t.co/BgjpsEhFgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who needs @strandbookstore? @QueensChronicle story about secondhand success under #theEl. https://t.co/8hmsmij5yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Auguroni amore Mia... Non hai minimo idea quanto ti amo! #FCIM #1nter1st1 ⚫️🔵 @Inter_en]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are supporting abortion every day that we work.   Our taxes pay abortionists to do their Satanic work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could all of my mutuals who will be at #SWCC please wear name tags that include your Twitter handle? I hate that we… https://t.co/Nf0ZG2oBNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flip side not to be rude. I feel many gays these days live in this heterosexual norms lifestyle fantasy that truly don’t work.]]></document></documents></author>