<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Darling? Whatever happened with That? Did we hear anything after this  EVER .... ? It’s just about 6:00 PM in Hanoi… https://t.co/6P38Yghzep]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so a pet peeve of mine I pay for it so why the f!?$ u keep stopping my show every 3 episodes 🤬#netflix… https://t.co/iyurrFmlHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HSugarCookie How about boycott IG and Facebook? When fake accounts flood the market, that’s when new media/social… https://t.co/Pud0RHEdT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Peter Ruckman - The Good Shepherd  #NowPlaying on  Final Fight Bible Radio ,  https://t.co/cQASaMMxWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm Jewish and I find the hypocrisy of GOP Islamophobes hounding IIhan Omar breathtaking.  - Rebecca Vilkomerson,… https://t.co/Hj1Ekx8ggd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whole body aching. I should be getting hazard pay just for smiling at coworkers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahjaswim @amazon @ConsumerReports @CRAdvocacy @NBCConsumer101 @ConsumerAffairs @Sheugs @barbaramills1… https://t.co/2yTwmxlvjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just reminds me of all the people back home trying to be an entrepreneur with selling healthy items to gullibl… https://t.co/eoZ7qVBCu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice Working Life article @CarolynTrietsch but I was struck by feeling like the article was gender neutral (👍) but… https://t.co/Fi0HyXthEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[tonight my friend met me for a lunch date and he literally said “every time i see u i just wanna tackle you... but… https://t.co/16veecIhUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers @LindseyGrahamSC Awesome!!! somebody sent him the message. Look a more sane Lindsey. Awe Lindsey yo… https://t.co/o8IiHt2QQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for a fun night out &lt;3 @ Florida https://t.co/o3guyNQf0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen The Asshat is paying out $$$$$Millions to feed, clothe, medical care, dental care.....what was tRumpty dumps plan?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted the challenge from @drchrisj2012 to post 7 covers of non-fiction books I love.  No reviews-just covers!… https://t.co/Es0DLMj6Wp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's chuckle a bit. Tips for Traveling with Babies and Toddlers -   I must remember this when/if I... https://t.co/HbWALQhzzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ramón Agüero Coach en PNL. Teléf. +584167639203. Forjarse, Purificarse y Brillar…Visión Sin Límites.… https://t.co/2ij8BS6wDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LahavHarkov Sure, but you ask from a professional distance. You can be friendly, but maybe it's better not to be f… https://t.co/eSsYghIUtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports Please keep your poison on msnbc Andrea... we are praying for good negotiations and no one worth anything watches msnbc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Salt Lake Community College in Salt Lake City, UT https://t.co/DTEDFoEzil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enterprise, Mississippi, is full of history and beautiful historic homes like the Stephenson-Allen House. 🌸🏠… https://t.co/2oBwoDolC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good grief. @realDonaldTrump is off on an international trip and tweeting about the Oscars. His mentality is that of an immature rock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I skipped lunch sooo yeah (@ Farm Burger Grant Park in Atlanta, GA) https://t.co/AWMekfNQGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parking and spectator passes available on Columbia swim club website https://t.co/9QehpbovLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buncee @NCCE_EdTech @FutureReady @All4Ed @Algreen5thVM @vmlibraryvoice @vanmeterschools I’m sending to you now in… https://t.co/BxzlN7hM73]]></document><document><![CDATA[As women, sometimes wearing no makeup makes us feel vulnerable and insecure. When I was younger I didn’t think I lo… https://t.co/3wq5XycmIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley It is a sad day when D's are okay with letting a failed aborted BABY just lay there and die.. Once outs… https://t.co/I5VaxLIhW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Venezuela belongs to the people, not those who think they are powerful! #KeepFighting #KeepHoping #ThankYou to all… https://t.co/TY356yuGpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Registration is OPEN for our Looks Leads Lifestyle March 7th event.  . 1 speaker 🔈, 1 date 📅, 2 venues, 2 times ⏰.… https://t.co/74lSVBV9Zy]]></document><document><![CDATA[A DSO weekend! #dso #lovethemusic🎶 #detroit #bakersfieldtacos @ Detroit Symphony Orchestra https://t.co/3yAHR0twWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss people not going through garbage.   Look out the window and theres a woman going through the trash cans I to… https://t.co/ivVZlc2Osn]]></document><document><![CDATA[SLEET REPORT: About 0.5” sleet in Lincoln, MO! 📸: Christie Ross #mowx #kolr10wx @NWSSpringfield https://t.co/vltAQ72McZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[She has this convo, interestingly enough, with the same rabbi who asserts that Esther was Mordechai’s little lamb / wife (Megillah 13א)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mary_sturino @flutist_kim @AndreePoppleton @TallShipProds @OutlanderWriter @STARZ @SamHeughan @caitrionambalfe Exa… https://t.co/PFnAWhvttt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @theladysitter for an unforgettable night💜 mychellecharters1 stellapawley  #womenscancerresearchfund @ Bever… https://t.co/61HBsjTbiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#COMPLACENCIA TOTAL En relación a la comida también las cosas han cambiado, aquello de que se hacía una comida para… https://t.co/apUMtm4Trm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love seeing black men do stuff like this with kids in the community so adorable]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love ppl who inherited their wealth insult ppl who worked their way up and school you on “all you can accomplish”]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you feel when you destroy something you wanted so bad all because you were mad.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@felderk says it is not safe for kids to be out in the middle of the night, Support’s ordinance citing parents as… https://t.co/YGWI7sy8Qm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennife79438627 @nahmias @AOC @errollouis @NY1 She's been in office 2 months.  Give me a break.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A friend sent me this about six moths ago. So fitting that I found it today again. @UMChurch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was hoping this wouldn’t be the outcome after we received the amber alert last night.  😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andrea_Gabriel_ I didn’t either!!! This makes me so freaking happy. I hope they treat it better than the 2007 movie did!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect!  Writing a grant and this will help us get data on who watches our training videos! @MSDMartinsville]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left my heart in San Francisco. ❤️🌉 See you in a few hours Hollywood! #sanfransisco #california #goldengatebridge… https://t.co/EUYGJ5neEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liams car alarm goes off whenever you open the door so now he’s just using his window]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton sounds completely disinterested when he’s asked both these dad’s so far for their blessing ughhhhh #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soapsindepthcbs About time. Shoulda never have made a  farce about such a serious problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Tuesday! Let that sun in, it’s good for your skin. 💯✌🏼☀️ . . . . #albuquerque #nm #goodmorning… https://t.co/8UFtVAbgMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soolieskiller @andizeisler The comments tho!!! The 90’s references are KILLING me!!! 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mamma also told to me fight for what’s mine. so imma fight for it 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Industry: Delays due to regulations in oil/gas bill could cut tax revenue to #CO schools, local governments @denverpost #coleg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The view from my room! 🦚✌🏻⛰ This will be my view through the spring at least...lovely green pastures and rolling hi… https://t.co/Wipx0N9BbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why isn’t Tayshia the new Bachelorette?! 💔💔#TheBachelorette #TheBachelorFinale]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redshadowpr @deddieromeropr Ay ya cambió la hora y los oigo más tiempo!! 😁❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wake up around 4 or 5 am every morning because i have heartburn and i’m hungry. and it takes me forever to get ba… https://t.co/tPyKu58gZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetgeorge48 I was trying to be helpful!  Pick &amp; choose what works for you!  Sorry! My heart’s in the right place☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maaaaaan I love pretty bitch energy , if feel so good when a pretty bitch compliments you like yasssss bitcchhhh you pretty too 😭😭❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAuthorGuy I like to leave the poo flinging to the current resident of the White House, while the rest of us try… https://t.co/OARp6FLTTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[love when I decide to not go to class and then you get an email from the professor saying they are canceling class 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I jumped out of the car because I saw the name. Almost fell, but then I took a couple of pictures. Couldn’t find hi… https://t.co/oHyXusYj7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[When he gets all the things about you... What an awesome Valentine's day! Thanks babe! 😘 #notarosesgirl… https://t.co/phO1J4hDhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DangerouslyDrk He got a lot of kids but that by far is the most trash ass thing ever 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@znerdforever @psalm420 My favorite was the professor who said to our three groups that she’d give which ever group… https://t.co/3O3ASwmnQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoulofMaga @bedevilme666 @billy4ever9 @SpriteJ11 @redmartagons @Patti_Sc60 @SealeyGerald @kevin_ponton @jonz970… https://t.co/oAAKY4IQud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Wednesday! We are halfway through the week and Friday is on the horizon! I want to share the cutest pink blaz… https://t.co/IoBj3y2ZxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ashleigh163 @Shifty_TSwifty @kyle_jamesb You can probably figure it out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProminentDaisy Repeatly I am grateful.  If my docs are to be believed I really shouldn't be here. So everyday I wake up, is a gift]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chad_bowen It’s kinda mind boggling that there’s a reconsideration for Simple Plan and not CCP? I’m missing something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJonesCLT EXACTLY. We will deeply regret it. Because most burn out and leave and thrive in other environments.   H… https://t.co/PNB4zFWOvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Aaron Brown was fired after doing a segment called "dead wrong" about pre-war intelligence in October of 2005. A… https://t.co/Y6zjj1WCqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahora que regresaron los Jonas puedo ver que a muchas les gustan. Eso es bueno]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing everyone’s stories at the beach in FL while I’m stuck in Muncie is really taking a toll on my mental state 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being in college is cool until you’re sick but have to continue to go to class because the professor basically tell… https://t.co/kyWzuZ6rfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissypearson9 @MaryKayH188 @woolloomoolo0 @CommissionerEMV Very brave!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What you do and how you make things work in your life is what matters most. That is your priority. You're the one w… https://t.co/YZeW5blk5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a 4 hour shift at work today so Benjamin is at my place cooking us Shrimp Pad Thai for dinner and I have jus… https://t.co/I7fsGTRMyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter the #SLAMDUNK Sweepstakes daily during March basketball madness for your chance to WIN $250 + a variety of… https://t.co/lgqO8WL855]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalReporter @PinePeach18 @Sunxrae @Ohtheliesofukp1 @scobie @theroyaleditor The difference between the US and the… https://t.co/P7P15Xz8M9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA How dare Jon Karl refer to the international meeting as “the strangest”. What a biased jerk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timely reminders for a busy challenging week.  Thanks for the reminder #wildwomansisterhood @ Montgomery Plaza Resi… https://t.co/rIp2qMGvRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish people would stop sharing that momo picture around social media. We can talk about it and warn parents effec… https://t.co/I27cYRGuwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElderLansing @BibleBeltDarlin @Alyssa_Milano I agree 100%. She is off the wall.  I truly believes she needs a psyc… https://t.co/IkMVYZD2ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchOliver8 Aww thanks Mitch! I'm excited for everyone to hear  it! Luv ya too my sweet friend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spacecowgyrl I got the Budget email. Have to check text now that I can relax a bit. Miss you already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaPustor123 @AthanasiaTrian1 @NancySimonds1 @mymtbrain @GalkeSabine @LiseNilsson2 @SanjaHirkic @MakkOlga… https://t.co/1WcimSdsQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haigh84 @raisedontv @sheilalussier https://t.co/DWrGCNh38p #thanksforthelikes #haigh84]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you and your mentor are both in Trader Joe’s procrastinating writing 🤷🏻‍♀️ #maybeiamcutoutforthis… https://t.co/1otj9KcN0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @Liz_Cheney She is such a trumpster. Her father is the devil]]></document><document><![CDATA[General store and repository of history. Vinegar Bend, Alabama.  #williamspender #vinegarbend #history #herstory… https://t.co/svvVxdzbjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will NOT accept Kacey Musgraves slander on my tl y'all better take that somewhere else !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to bump into fellow board member Brian from Seatlle @demcountyoffice ar @NACoTweets https://t.co/Gn7ygqzDdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[(yes he is mostly sitting on the dog) (yes he is at least 8 lbs heavier than said 17 lb dog)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our boys need to go after 51 with a quickness. #coyotes #vengeanceforstepan @DerekStepan21 I hope you're okay 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙🖤♥️  #R3KO #Resp3ct #LetsGo #Day2 #Finals #LetsGetReadyToRumble #CaliAllststars #CA #Dallas #NCA #CheerLife 💥 @ 20… https://t.co/KlMZYhVaEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the verge of starting a brand new adventure that I am very excited about.  I am trusting everything will work ou… https://t.co/3VXGHeGX9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jinkileaks Lol yeah shes one of my internet friends who i helped get into shinee (I wrote her like a 60 pg paper t… https://t.co/F25wDqFgLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Benefits of Being an Octopus was truly inspirational, especially for a preservice teacher like myself! I hope t… https://t.co/vFhR4rhYOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[my two least favorite things ever to buy at the store are toilet paper and trash bags and today I had to buy both rip in peace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @mitchellreports @VP did you resign for your hatred toward LGBTQ or Latinos? What about speaking against Ste… https://t.co/YocUYwZvha]]></document></documents></author>