<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@GSarafan @pookietooth @realDonaldTrump @mattgaetz We protect all animals at safety Network including humans but ye… https://t.co/oEk8GmKxks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @RepPaulTonko for meeting us today at your office to discuss issues. #NACoLeg2019 @NYSCounties @NACoTweets https://t.co/HGsN2DJ6Eq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWNAV @notcapnamerica @jackjonesbabe They want him gone. Look, I don't get the Beto thing myself but their feeling… https://t.co/GDSLPqHsGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndylan1 @mtylr23 @ericgarland natalie: what is interesting many of trump's circle did not want to work for their r… https://t.co/Bq59nOt2he]]></document><document><![CDATA[Middle linebacker @RusneyCastillo looking forward to his move to Worchester from @PawSox #RedSox #SpringTraining]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmyjamny @thomaskaine5 @Mikeystrikes300 Lmfao!!! You act that’s a lot 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @mhsARMY @montereyhs #PlainsmenPals and all the #PlainsmenHoops family and friends for coming to support these young men! 👊🏽🏀🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[My whole team is winning and that’s just fucking goals! ALV #everyonewinning @Chuchainz8 @lucerozavalax @louisV @bigO @Kone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ETCanada @ParisHilton Even Yoko One says “ please don’t” ! @etnow @ETCanada]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the ad and brand execs who are quoted in this article don't know why @SXSW is the way it is or what it is.… https://t.co/7jW7OuiVNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlwesterfield Another fake David acct popped up. Well I assumed that it was fake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@webb_sears @clairlemon emojis used to be generic key strokes, devoid of any ethnicity ;-)  ... now we are all very… https://t.co/Kwg7jhQF1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBudden you shouted out the truck drivers on your podcast so I’m gonna listen to every single one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mazap4n solamente dejo que al que le gusta el rock la haga, me explico?? Si el fin del movimiento es la igualdad d… https://t.co/tCDTWE3Z2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tsplant @bobbyolsonjr @BuschBeer @bbrown129 @Rick_Splant https://t.co/rF1xmpw6Qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badnecklace Oh I agree.   I just think they’ll appear someplace else at some point]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICE reviewing anti-Ilhan Omar social media post shared and liked by 2 agents Seems like the FBI should be investiga… https://t.co/C2QV4TntxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gabriel was crying and sobbing in fear by now and my wife kept saying he's asleep and to slow down, not to worry. I… https://t.co/gbuxXWtfR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianbeutler If Hickenlooper keeps spouting this nonsense, he will be gone very soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiffInDelMar #Biff uses his Bert(&amp;Ernie) puppet hand to jerk off into]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boarded at 6 am and still on the runway at 7:20 am.  Oh yea we have a 5 hr flight ahead of us.  #loveflying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tao has a bar by the bathroom and it’s the most brilliant thing I’ve ever seen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Propelled by 22 points from @brian_collier_, #6 Grandview Heights upset rival #2 Worthington Christian in District… https://t.co/QihA92a56x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly think @KLab_EN is running daylight savings off calendar recently for #LLSIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KIRILL_aka_KID Блин, адреналин же в вену надо вводить, а такой малышке в вену попасть очень сложно, даже человеку… https://t.co/3ERxUqImBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[T-Mobile doing there best to make us hate the song Beauty School Dropout.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dulcemariaPrinc @pepitobarcelona @marcorubio Que mentiroso su propio gobierno está derrumbado y todavía diciendo embustes revolucionarios]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raphkoster I remember a guild mate was featured in the WSJ for being one of the first notable examples of account… https://t.co/Hr2O9dN74I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overhead recently at a local coffee shop:  "Wait. Your church is called 'Bear Toss?'"  "No. It's 'VERITAS.' Like Latin for truth."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennkirschner2 @roripierpont1 Whitaker as Acting AG begs the obvious: How hard can the Bar Exam be. anyway?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black people are the only ones to do something super lit then get embarrassed and run away. Bitch where you going ?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna take a weekend trip to Atlanta this summer. Maybe Labor Day weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a rap battle, Eminem would kick my butt. Marshall Faulk would destroy me. I probably could take Marshall Crensha… https://t.co/eopT156bTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Bahraini FM says diplomatic relations with Israel will happen 'eventually' (Haaretz)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gerry Dulac's Steelers chat: 03.06.19 https://t.co/X9HYHEnnh2 via @pittsburghpg @gerrydulac #Steelers]]></document><document><![CDATA[2) Not going back to football tryouts at PLU. I assumed I didn’t make the team and was to afraid to hear it for mys… https://t.co/UYeHFdlqVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MathewNoKnowles The riffs. The runs. The vocal layers. The phrasing. Brandy is not called the vocal bible for no r… https://t.co/4x54eGNAyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Natural Bridges in Vallecito, CA is a beautiful serene location that we shot using the DJI Mavic 2 Pro. There was p… https://t.co/HP5FCzyT3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her: Run for president.  Bernie: I already did. I lost.  Her: Amazon will pay no Federal taxes on a record 11.2 bil… https://t.co/PfaSt12JCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Jewish Agency to help its gay employees pay for surrogate services overseas https://t.co/1xQgcbUC0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Booking ja rule was a strange move. It goes without saying that no one got their money back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlatoutiRacing @chriskwright @Hzzardous @SkyTheSenpai No, they didn’t. You have to turn the layer off in Photoshop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up late... well actually all night. That being said, it is with good cause. Closed the bar down with Brendan Casey… https://t.co/sGb5Kkrwil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThaRavShay You're next I saw the Devil Blood and Bone Flash Point https://t.co/Sdu0lcchz6 Walled In Hush Ladybugs… https://t.co/Yd0e0FCgGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlongenecker1 The gay hierarchy needs to go and be replaced with celibate men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Schiff announces investigation into President Trump 'beyond Russia'  https://t.co/U2mBH0g9Y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like #RogerStone isn’t the only one who’s #MadeAFineKettleOfFish @senatemajldr #InAPickle What will you do no… https://t.co/bnjtIUcqfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some historical context on #Haiti https://t.co/18dlD6zVsW https://t.co/wWO4LNrP58]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I was gonna have left over pizza (again) for dinner but my high ass left it out overnight. Welp.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fryemuso Truly a moment in time that will define the future of politics in this country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mccabe-He May be working for Russia! If anyone who was in a position of power, it could be him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump doesn't care about America. He only cares about amassing power and conning money out of rubes.… https://t.co/cmqOc2On7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when bam margera dropped that song about bending his dick to his ass out of nowhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wanda_kid @GlobeEarthToday @flatearthboy @ResistanceGold1 @rokro111 @T__E__S__L__A @robandflat @tjm2529… https://t.co/11EoB42QOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve traveled ’em all Each and every byway We could really use a plan To fix our state highways  #ARlegValentines]]></document><document><![CDATA[A&amp;M is trash, we all know that. But at least Kennedy has two Sweet Sixteen runs. Chris Beard is a the state’s best program in Lubbock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se Fue // @BrendaBezares // @IndepeMusic   Ya disponible en todas las plataformas digitales… https://t.co/wAfDPMNczv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnRalstonSaul Sir, this comment is so bias. Sport shooting is the fastest growing section of ownership. Do you k… https://t.co/A2wZbGXCcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[this specific photo of robert really makes me weak WHEW maybe he is cute https://t.co/dcEHPNS1bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr What you mean to say is taxing more from the uber wealthy to to redistribute wealth back to levels th… https://t.co/0eeDRyaje2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HilandDairy liked my tweet, and that has made me unbelievably happy :) https://t.co/f7MTqNh1Sj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithtweetsalot I always just give them the wrong directions and move on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsmeaghangray MISSING WOMAN - Gabriella Antoine - Missing since Jan 23rd. She has a medical condition that affect… https://t.co/3PMwQIlfxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will vote for any Democrat over  tRump. ANY Dem over tRump. We must stay together to get through this unbelievabl… https://t.co/H8UDBZ2WLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t trust people who can’t ever text or email and insist on talking by phone only.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please pray &amp; support the efforts of The Ekklesia of Oklahoma in Abolishing Abortion in Oklahoma! #abortion… https://t.co/IXFt3yHWTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hardest thing to do will always be hard.  You just need ‘to do’ to get it done. #leadership #inspiration #motivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[All thanks to the Man above and constant praying. Counting my blessing everyday and taking nothing for granted anym… https://t.co/A5dhrgJX3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los Martes maetabaco manito_menudo  Presentan  En madeinmexiconyc La Voz De tonybravo15 Y Las Mezclas y la Buena an… https://t.co/lMRrrXC5ck]]></document><document><![CDATA[[watch both videos]  First video is of me failing for 1 rep of 405 The second video is me getting it, with the help… https://t.co/3e5j4fxTUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just know. You fuck with them. You fuck with me. It dosnt matter if there with me or not.  So don’t go runnin your… https://t.co/Risx4LQ47V]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WashingtonDC #WhiteHouse #WhiteHousePressCorps #ShotOniPhone @ The White House https://t.co/2b7AmGjxvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jtfawver You’re wrong on this one man. Well documented. This is total cash every year. Way under market. I agree t… https://t.co/QluWQEfWUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susanmanners @JillWineBanks @BarbMcQuade @Mimirocah1 @JoyceWhiteVance I like chris but he sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JodyBrownArch @PaulJones3 But we really don't know where that client comment actually lands on the reality or truth continua ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got to chat with @KyleLarsonRacin &amp; he remembered me!! What a day😍🙌🏼🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost dantalentgroupflorida ・・・ ❤️ @imagescjp ❤️ @dantalentgroup ❤️ @Hailey14135736 godblessthechildmagazine… https://t.co/EDLtCRyNGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laura Ingraham coming out in support of Planned Parenthood is wild even for 2019 https://t.co/1rtgHb5GAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NSchneiderAZ13 @BologneNoodles @RepJoeKennedy Please, were you raising these same alarms when Obama was flexing hi… https://t.co/EEA4MUNTLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFKexPresidenta O sea, siempre has sido bien hombrecita para tus cosas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry!!! I’m watching interviews with Haskins and this kid is the real deal. Awesome QB and his character is unreal! #DraftHaskins]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #WWEChamber beer! Always delicious! - Drinking an A Little Sumpin' Sumpin' Ale by @lagunitasbeer @ Wrestle Cave… https://t.co/r73cz1WACK]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/35 Tamiya Panzer II Ausf.C, Polish Campaign  Weathering has started in earnest. Panel lines washed, drybrushing d… https://t.co/nKpeCHAYLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our biggest event of the year is coming up. Come out and learn about artificial intelligence. You must RSVP in adva… https://t.co/qvFAgrlNte]]></document><document><![CDATA[You left out the 9 of the 21 Sixers turnovers Simmons had tonight I see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[am i the only one who thinks it’s shady af that basile and daphné supposedly left the party to get laid bc judging… https://t.co/5iV1xfFbYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonBisca  gracias por su buen trabajo saludos a mi hijo Albert sermeno y mi sobrino Aiden que se que daron dormido… https://t.co/wmKdT7Zbp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[No it is not what the text says. It is what you say the text says. The text is right but you are wrong. The Bible i… https://t.co/t3XpsqUckB]]></document><document><![CDATA[All we should take away from all of this is that, @SpeakerPelosi understands The Art of War and the Macro, @AOC doe… https://t.co/7WoSwzknrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NASCAR Fans! @JTGRacing is giving away over $20,000 in prizes in the Flavor Fill Up Sweepstakes, ENTER NOW! https://t.co/baYWjDOVCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerhikes Clarification: The stormwater entering the lake is at times one-quarter the salinity of sea water. The… https://t.co/Q7PhWT7uxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simple data viz that communicates information effectively and immediately:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Knighter01 @McDonalds @RPMotorsports @BubbaWallace @amsupdates That’s good news Chris! I hope McDonalds will partn… https://t.co/ATlAbbDF6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question was posed asking had you ever heard of a product that the developers would not let their kids use? Answer:… https://t.co/cmfsCwpes8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristophersZen @DatManMays @KierstenJ1994 @PhillyGator1 @champagnehann @MoveBackYouSuck @_stevenrod @NotoriousGator 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hog #frog #horse #colorful #drawings @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/jDajbRQtth]]></document><document><![CDATA[This team is doing great work building bridges to success in Washington D. C.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There have always been bubbles, there will be more bubbles to come, but man does crypto feel like a unique bubble i… https://t.co/DxiqsxD76X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shakiguani i love it though!! i love to be told i'm right!! who doesn't!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get ready to listen to The Funniest Intro @bobbyleelive has gotten, at least to me. And how @mazjobrani s dad creat… https://t.co/1OiTNwEIdA]]></document></documents></author>