<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[And a fabulous space indeed! 😉 #myspace #realestate #charlottenc #charlotte #milliondollarlisting #dreamhome… https://t.co/O4Jm6MvPFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to bust some ass today. #PrayForLukePerry. @LAFitness @KOPTownCenter #Workout #GymRat #SilverSneakers… https://t.co/kwHMxBjPA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm really starting to see my value's worth to some people and it hurts me when I'm like the sweetest person that t… https://t.co/Ka9p7232aV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#forgiveness #postabortionrecovery #healing #freedom #peace @ Tabernash, Colorado https://t.co/trlvoGWuo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t wanna get to know someone new yet; i don’t wanna be close to someone else :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[click the link to RSVP for my show Friday night 💖  https://t.co/qMTEl9lgpc https://t.co/OlO3vBKsFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackieChenault @oakridgeboys @wlgolden @DUANEALLEN @RASterban @joebonsall Yes😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[De mal en peor .... todo un dolor de cabeza y nadie da la cara, nadie se responsabiliza.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamiebroman2 @HrhOrchid @AlVega10 @dkurtenbach Ikr such a drag that we don't like seeing women assaulted and a bun… https://t.co/sCEJJO9GKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud that our magazine covered the #MomoChallenge and the history of other recent social media challenges before i… https://t.co/47w8JNQFrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[No.But they interview maggots like Chris Christie and Roger Stone and blather on about whether or not women candida… https://t.co/htp5JKtj0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[i remember being so sick freshman year while having to present and my voice literally evaporated in the middle of the presentation..]]></document><document><![CDATA[#isabellechristian figured out that you are supposed to jump. #adalynashley #oliviaadale #altitudetrampolinepark 🤣😁… https://t.co/X5PSgFhAaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I’d except nothing less out of myself to not just get pink eye, but get pink eye in both of my damn eyes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @VP @FoxNews @JohnCornyn @SenTedCruz @senatemajldr @GOPLeader Trump's henchmen are tired of coveri… https://t.co/X3PzV7DnyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump fuck you asshole. I would trade you to Gina in a heart bear!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!!!! 🙌🏻🙌🏻   Following @Joe_Sanfelippo led me to @KimGriesbach and @gcouros  Love that twitter connects educators… https://t.co/jfYgFRj7EE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If people can’t figure out how to use #BirthControl to prevent #UnwantedPregnancies, then let’s focus on saving the… https://t.co/Zu7bhpXxKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grammabz @JudicialWatch You are not a very nice person are you. Probably why you only have 1 follower]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bourgeoisalien @GeoffMiami @FaceTheNation Yes!  Oh my God - that was hilarious!  I have to watch ALL of it again.… https://t.co/BvMJt9mNGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time in high school my mom told me to go get ashes at the nearest church as soon as I got out of soccer practic… https://t.co/R1PVJgHXWU]]></document><document><![CDATA['Arrow' Star Stephen Amell Releases An Emotional Video Saying Good-Bye to Fans https://t.co/eQrgWPLBmO via @ComicBook]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kartos @ImFastnt @VoltronStore What I mean is a lot expected a high quality well written show instead of something… https://t.co/SVE5baUaaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soulpunkps My name is Stephanie. I was born in the same place as the other side. My age is still not a bad idea to… https://t.co/HmpPY5FcXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#poetrycommunity #poem #POEMS #poetrylovers #poetrywriter https://t.co/fOoTckP1KS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therobbg @JewelsLuvsTexas Well Trump is bringing back asbestos.  Ordering it from Russia although it's still outla… https://t.co/ULbEzWi08s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarpeDiemCyber @bobgourley @mtanji @allanfriedman @Joseph_Marks_ @ericgeller @timstarks @Bing_Chris Promise?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @nonlinearnotes for perfectly summarizing everything I’ve been feeling about #LeavingNeverland. https://t.co/ynTKUh7hl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravadoSpice @Sur_La_Table so awesome, congratulations #teambravado 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Milaviles Pa que la gente baile el son que le toque y me dejen bailar el mío, que la vida es bella y yo me cabreo… https://t.co/1ED0ZuDiCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleytisdale I hope you have a blessed and amazing Sunday. I love you sooo much 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being diagnosed @ 18 is scary but seeing someone else putting their head up high y todavia echándole ganas ❤️ gives… https://t.co/Ol4ubv38Lp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently interesting in nothing other than the 1968 Fiddler on the Roof soundtrack, ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayEllaBaby Yesssss!! 🙌🏼 I just wish someone would say what she really does, because I don’t see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pratrp  I'd be honored to have your follow !! Thank you for serving !!  #ArmyStrong #MAGA #VIP on #TEAMMAGA IFB… https://t.co/kJqZCHMM3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gave my business card to my @Uber driver. Hope I can help him out! #travelagent #travelblogger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMeMP @jay_riddle @HollisBaufc @Ninja @timthetatman @DrLupo https://t.co/R2PCvLaUmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ain’t going back to no one that ain’t good for me! Ima just have to miss them until i don’t miss them no more !]]></document><document><![CDATA[In addition to his many talents- you can add “statistician” to the laundry list of talented skills @DrewMeyerUSC ha… https://t.co/N1RqkjRRRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let’s complete the collection!” -my mom talking about getting a yellow labrador bc we already have a brown and black one...lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m confused. If you can’t even afford rent how can you afford a thrift jack.... you know what... it’s none of my business]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows President minus need to take himself to jail and feel free to escort him personally if you must. Wh… https://t.co/pWRzX2GtcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s hard to support a vendor who doesn’t support me, the practitioner.  Who doesn’t see me as a colleague, collabo… https://t.co/HbSnhfomxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Council president’s support was critical to Bullard’s land purchase because, by law, the sale of city-owned lot… https://t.co/i3Aew5byLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[other actions needed to prosper in the competitive economy.  President Donald Trump has proposed modest reforms to… https://t.co/QQ2S9UCLiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outlawjw @LauraLaura1650 She has no clue what's she's talking about! Gets her information flying in wind!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people you have to thank 5 times for them to feel appreciated “I’m just saying I never did this for anyone bef… https://t.co/lpohLFvAQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[a guy just walked past me going to class wearing National Lampoon’s Christmas Vacation pajama pants. nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pdoocy First time I’ve been able to watch you report in a longtime.  I’ve missed your grade A work Peter!!  Btw, t… https://t.co/jtrcxEg4Lj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaBeep @ItsJustJill That is some mess up stuff! Somebody should be fired .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cathy Jacobs, Principal and Lead Learner @MatzkeElemCFISD. “Effective instructional strategies are like chess piece… https://t.co/iYYXO7KbhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zalokar_runs @jbwhite777 @ZeeTravelTales @VictoriaIdoni @Ltd_To_Two @travelpantspair @BrendaFlournoy1 @skipr619… https://t.co/PAzD5tQ2KV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine How about rude, crude &amp; not funny. No one cares as much as you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kab_fair @dir1957 @johnrobertsFox @realDonaldTrump No claims of falling onto the ground until your tweet...  Try i… https://t.co/PNh5YUmgsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perdón por ver estrellas donde no había, y por ilusionarme con tus besos de papel. Perdón por confundir amor con co… https://t.co/4T96g3JIKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lloydkaufman @kwzombi @Fradice @NicoleCesar_ @grindhouse8 @Troma_Team I didn't know you found a #goldenticket !! https://t.co/3eAtADULEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKatieHill @RepPeteAguilar did you vote for this😡😡😡 I can’t wait to ballot harvest you out of office]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dariathedon He murdered Donna Dalton Castleberry too. That goes to grand jury indictment April 4th and 5th.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight's #LivePD theme is wasting officers time https://t.co/wchyDP5Bid]]></document><document><![CDATA[roommate 1: “when I was 13–“ me: “I HAD MY FIRST LOVE” roommate 2 (100% serious): “Miriam, I’m surprised you even K… https://t.co/RpLSjxeI7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarefootWine @nathanfielder @ComedyCentral @HaagenDazs_US @hungrymanfoods @Friskies @Kleenex @someecards… https://t.co/668AeuXHSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nowwwww we are talkin’ This is a #MobileMornings type of guy! This is fantastic!! @fmtalk1065 @daltonorwig check hi… https://t.co/eyQfSGzGJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream last night i was getting married and i ran out of my own wedding and went to Starbucks to get the fre… https://t.co/c0iaX90PjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thinkprogress Wow now that is truly with the moment!  Strongly recommend that you take the time to review your not… https://t.co/j4c883CVGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashenthorn @ForecasterEnten Anybody but any neoliberal corporate ass kisser 💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fendi_Gucci_Gal @GovMikeHuckabee @repubfan @foxandfriends @FoxNews Me too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not BS. Are you fucking joking?you’re supposed to be financially stable before having a kid. Period. I will no… https://t.co/TdqVU09uT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally saw #BohemianRhapsody and omg such an amazing movie!! Love bio movies like that, long live QUEEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so true, lol. #5SOSFAM #BestFanArmy #iHeartAwards https://t.co/caiDgBJDIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was a great session! It could’ve been twice as long. Love thinking classrooms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrangeBrew @EmilyJaneArts Lol, the race is on! https://t.co/LAteiTPVKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perk is absolutely capable of surpassing the assist record tonight.  Kinda don’t want him to, ‘cause I really want… https://t.co/7K8tK1h82b]]></document><document><![CDATA[whether you believe Cohen or not isn’t it a little sus that the president is involved in so many scandals]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn't this be a better convo with his agent?  I would think he would want to tweet his stats against best pass d… https://t.co/2Ctr25cxe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never forget that time when Jeff Goldblum was robbed at the 68th Academy Awards and don’t even bring up the 59th Ac… https://t.co/ju0Jc11UhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiloVentimiglia meet @ChrisEvans  share your mutual love of Space exploration ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe  Great discussion with Tom and Mike. More of them, please. @RadioFreeTom @mikebarnicle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe its time for a “literature drop “in Spanish warning these large groups of people being encouraged to head to… https://t.co/uW8YprLOvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preparing to create a mindful space at home with our @vosswater mindful glitter jars. It’s never too early to have… https://t.co/ApBKrRjYDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Both are too damn expensive! 🙄 But I couldn't resist 🤷🏾‍♀️ #collegetuition #baddecisions #igot5onit #EbonyKnight @… https://t.co/U2Xa7OEegr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, come on people doesn't Michael Cohen deserve  a little bit of respect from us again? @MichaelCohen212  He's he… https://t.co/Pj9Vr4YUVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh and I’m SINGLE btw... By choice and loving it. 😻🔒  I honestly am just not with the shit right now. Soon though,… https://t.co/NMWlxBJFhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[She came from my side in which I was holding my phone so she saw me on the phone, and actually stopped me while mid sentence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You had the flu and decided it was good form to spread to others so you could play? Wtf? I can't come up with right… https://t.co/OpRYNMta0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt Patton, sorry this week was bad. I am right there with you. I had PTSD on Thursday, after being shot… https://t.co/tovmjqqLxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the #wolfpack for winning the Winter Slam tournament 👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾 seppsaddison @antaddison @ Rancho Do… https://t.co/mQRR8EgZ6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mardi Gras mambo!! For the $10 today #whereyaAT#YAHEARDME#hearddatlove✌🏽💙♨️ @ Heard Dat Kitchen https://t.co/Q4rvPsUiOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WisHolsteins annual convention tour of The Rahr-West Art Museum. In awe of the Georgia O’Keefe, Joan Miro, Andy Wa… https://t.co/vddQ1wK3Xa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny how the @Delta app is telling me now, 3 hours after the plane with my luggage (finally) arrived, that my bag… https://t.co/fudWTnHKPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be going to see @SawyerFrdrx @thewarminghouse in MN on Friday 2/24 and I will periscope the show😊Just thought I’d let you all know❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel soooo bad and sad for my baby 😪I HATE seeing her sick like this especially because she doesn’t get sick often]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lady_Red_2 No thanks, and no.  Of course anyone can be ambushed with a knife.  But not spray into a crowd.  Guns n… https://t.co/irkS0VD6G9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leighmlorien everything. moved out of handmade and into supplies for a while, but I'm doing handmade again now and… https://t.co/ipFbBMSvoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SienaTavern I am considering driving from detroit right now to try it 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me &amp; Nina are in Miami &amp; this feels like the movie spring breakers...I love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Do what you must. You will find nothing, but let me just say this....Standard Hotel!  Q sent me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so now this blockbuster should take over @loneblockbuster and its legacy will live on forever 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have so been Kate...home after a long day and longing for peaceful baby snuggles...only to find them just as exha… https://t.co/1IQxbm7SDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[[world history class, 6th grade]   One day, the teacher said that all the girls needed to wait outside the classroo… https://t.co/neeNCwf3ox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gormogons More rain heading to Missip, and 20s next week. #NoahAre YouPrepared?]]></document></documents></author>