<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Literacy Festival 2019 Writing Contest Winners!📝🎉 Tamsin Gambone,Rose Fontana, Nelson Nnana,… https://t.co/dHv11ENY5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ones who say that “you can’t” and “you wont” are probably the ones scared that “you will” @ Raleigh Studios https://t.co/KaK9hWFMwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the only person I’m actually afraid might steal my husband 😂 @MARTIZZL3 https://t.co/jUnxWtOAUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait till my @BeisTravel Weekender bag arrives!! Legit waited months for the restock!! 😍😭👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTS_twt #정국 Hi my sweet Kookie, how's my babe tonight? It was SO good seeing you for a bit today, as always, wish… https://t.co/NF2z8RMUo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that Hozier isn’t afraid of time signatures. He will play in 6/8, he will play in 5/4!!!! He is not SCARED. What a musician.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @realDonaldTrump - WHY DON’T YOU EVER MENTION THE AMERICANS OF WHITE MEN COMMITTING MASS MURDERS - ALL WHO ARE AMERICAN CITIZENS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special prayer from DWC for ALL couples today! 🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾 I Corinthians 13:13 “Three things will last forever--faith, h… https://t.co/bQD8e4GfRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp @realDonaldTrump LIES. The fact that you and his enablers won’t call it what it is, emboldens him to cont… https://t.co/LbE1q7bRKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao jokes on her bc that was a steal for all that extra stupid shit on her nails 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[why does boris johnson look like trump tried to draw himself https://t.co/87NN5b4EQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how everyone my age is out there getting engaged and I’m over here like 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalHigdon Thanks TEAM! You are amazing! We appreciate ALL that you do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took me 21 years to realize conditioner always has the lid on the bottom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[*in the restroom*  Me: turned around looking at my cousin Sadie: what is that presence close to me??! Oh its Natalie's ass 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[About a yr ago a guy told me that every time we went out, no matter where, we always ran into someone that knew me.… https://t.co/623eeAwvQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gonedelete Once you learn piano the other will be cake. Work smarter not harder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We leave for Florida next week and I just realized I have NO idea where I put all my summer clothes? Haha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay but who thought to sit down and cut slits in soap...you know what I mean]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these girls roll into my 8 am class hair and makeup done and here I come looking like I got hit by a bus 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk Also be careful of words we use. Mocking "so and so is crazy" or misuse of terms like "schizophrenic" feed… https://t.co/YaXUK3sOz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I earned this award again! I’m so excited to be getting closer to my fitness goals! ⌚️🍎💪🏻 https://t.co/5YkBWmUCI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Seattle! J/k, I'm in Knox but I'm waking up to rain....again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panda Bei Bei Having a Ball at Night (March 2019) https://t.co/hJWESaCDj4 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WHSCI @AdamParkhomenko We're paying her a salary to AVOID questions; Plus, she gets benefits, she goes on DT's stu… https://t.co/tqTp1yLoYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LannyDavis @dgmuir Please tell Mr Cohen to not talk back to the Republicans! He’s going to come off as rude and di… https://t.co/QAT2njsS0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayMartorelli @bealeveratto Ya sabes yo escucho el horóscopo fiel los domingos  en mis caminatas con mis amores 🐶y… https://t.co/GVN6kbke0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicolette_O @Sostraveluk @HHLifestyleTrav @poetixtrip @Adventuringgal @travelwithirine @sl2016_sl @JulesHalvy… https://t.co/SQ6mq5bMRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to this year’s #EdRevExpo in SF with @ChildMindInst. Who else will I see? #1in5… https://t.co/JjwysC31VL]]></document><document><![CDATA[any netflix recommendations? i been watching criminal minds again lately.. need something new]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLS be VERY careful if you must be on the roads.  @DominicBrownTV @GregWISTV @wis10]]></document><document><![CDATA[be with someone that accepts you on your bad days as much as they do on your good days]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly I need to re read by bible 😂 ....and try a Heath bar @GitRDoneLarry]]></document><document><![CDATA[The. Jonas. Brothers. ARE DROPPING NEW MUSIC ON FRI.😱😱😱 https://t.co/4UYAzcwtl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Pigeon Happy Birthday🎂. Big fans of you both!  So glad I get to share your work with my son👍🏻 Staring down 50 myself-it happens🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quintessential self-important elite Ottawa bureaucrat. Believes all that is important happens within a 10 mile radi… https://t.co/J3kNtCZhZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Refuel! After hard weight, proprio, and plyo workout. Let's GO! 🏆 #homemade #goal https://t.co/QtlS1Nrb3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a lovely way to authentically connect RISD students and  honoring Joe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jendeben @realDonaldTrump Nothing ever added up. Bad numbers coming home to roost.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am completely offended by this..why is this allowed to continue prosecute her and the John's to the fullest exten… https://t.co/pKlmo0hmpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their Posturing is SO PATHETIC! They haven had ONE -not One Constructive Decent, Original,ok idea. Instead they pre… https://t.co/YrQoJPeE5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally can feel my body shutting down . But it’s so much I still have to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus did more than talk about forgiveness; he lived it. At the end of his life he offered an amazing petition amid… https://t.co/AIuVx5kaI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deja de sentir miedo y sal a disfrutar de la libertad de manejar hoy te damos la bienvenida a un nuevo concepto, po… https://t.co/MLx8thcW6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karma’s just sharpening her nails and finishing her drink. She says she’ll be with you shortly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol people at work are CONSTANTLY expecting me to know the whereabouts/schedule of my supervisor. It’s been a year… https://t.co/uFiKtqi0Sl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another successful event in the books. The @SOBEWFF Tribute Dinner presented by @BankofAmerica did not disappoint.… https://t.co/OHeX0rNpic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @KamalaHarris This is part of the climate of hate that Smollett has kept alive w/ his hoax.  Since y… https://t.co/ELfXBGjEvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewScheer what can Canadians do to ensure a full INDEPENDENT inquiry is launched? Why have criminal charges not… https://t.co/uUcCaSSJEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the mother of the year award goes to Laura.  #Dateline https://t.co/t6PtIJnLCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdb2 I don't think I've seen poll/focus group findings on one vs. the other, but that would be interesting.   Sort… https://t.co/XbxEg3choO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thu, 3/14! @TuneCore Takeover of AMF’s Home Brew: Coffee Chats for Creatives  Link to RSVP in bio 🎶📓🎵🧠🎶 @ Kimpton H… https://t.co/XOaQxkQPt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casssi1 Or that Jaden Smith’s foundation is finally bringing clean water to Flint.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure getting hit with a nuclear bomb would help the climate. Can they be that stupid? Yes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.Ex-W.Va. official who made racist Michelle Obama remark defrauded $18,000 from FEMA: report https://t.co/aVyOz33d7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a little under a year ago this was the Los Angeles skyline. I took this at an event called design LA. I’m a li… https://t.co/8fzjGW7RH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AAlshareey كل المنتجات في العالم لها تاريخ صلاحيه exportation date حتى الشمس سيأتي يوم و تختفي ، إلا حكام العرب ال… https://t.co/RMtDyE83Qw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ChristainScott #Jazz #NeoSoul  #TheRhoxy @ The Roxy https://t.co/0YRXLiTyFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbachelet ayuda humanitaria a #Venezuela ya! Tenga compasión por el pueblo! No la #dictadura haga su trabajo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ViernesBotanero #friends #LigaMX #viernesdeselfie #twitlike https://t.co/QbwIhs38Ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Create a home at school for our students...” #nowignite #middierising #thisiswe]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of progressives are guilty of this. Think what you want, but quit fucking calling people stupid for not havin… https://t.co/MzK91vNQJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday Hello #chicago #brookezanell #windycity #chicagotgirlstransgirlsevents #sandymichellenyc… https://t.co/T992fPjdIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ENL after school parent engagement session!  @PS22si @ArtsEd_SI_BKS @FollowCSA @SIBOD31 https://t.co/zX4Do9pYVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PacificStand Thanking God, for leading to the @GaHouseHub to pass #HB481, the Living Infants Fairness and Equality… https://t.co/WPih7EBKO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casualstaring @angellwings Me during the entire run of #Fringe https://t.co/aRwgkcfFsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help my daughter and the rest of the UCONN Huskies to meet their goal for sick children!  No donation is to… https://t.co/SqfBcXSgic]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fur-cast today is cold! No hot dogs, only chilly dogs 🌭 @KTULNews #OKwx https://t.co/WCR1KH6wT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leronorme @Badfishanarchy @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump I wish it were your ranch then we would see how you feel. So… https://t.co/n2J9VwJrN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I wasn’t going to have a panic attack this week, #FreeSolo definitely made sure of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People that go to restaurants are so damn rude...like ight ma’am...you and your party can go back home and enjoy a… https://t.co/t4CdxtFcbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hah. I love the subtle “bye Hillary”. It’s about time America learns about her treason, and pays the time for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onestrangerock one episode in and we (family and I) are hooked! #amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe it’s already Friday but I can’t believe it’s barely Friday you know?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two whole months without you and I miss you every day 💔 https://t.co/UOC5MvNC81]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_stephencurry @tomwatson Riiiiiiiight, fighting for $15, Medicare For All, social security expansion. It’s all so… https://t.co/OgOUnbVTeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[shout out to @cmace30 for showing Siss the love he deserves 👏🏼 #mostunderratedpredforsure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@droctoswho To me Jodie Whittaker is not the Doctor. She is just a mediocre actor doing bad imitations of the Tenth… https://t.co/ZvVB5opCa7]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite feelings is that first week after new music comes out and you have to try and learn the lyrics t… https://t.co/nCPsgeY3GS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monicaashby7 : when someone is killing you, you’re supposed to look them in the eyes!   Me: why?  Mon: it makes them feel bad😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorleigh1 @QuinceMountain @EmCoo55 @JamesFrye @SherryH87 @T200SledDogRace @SportsSled @OtterRunKennel I am late to… https://t.co/qhEM21JOJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@happy02013guy @DrJimmyStar @PattiBrookd @ZanbranoJorge @PatGrant7777 @Jonatha97947998 @sherrig108 @Jilliemary… https://t.co/SJF7WDLw14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Fellow Readers, I accepted a challenge from @sdc_explorers to post 7 favorite books, 1 per day for 7 days, no… https://t.co/d0ouIINHEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a HopStorm® IPA by @bjsrestaurants at @bjsrestaurants — https://t.co/UPNNz67Psx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m such an easy person to please. The little things mean A LOT to me. 😩 So for my son son to include me in his eve… https://t.co/kwgt9EEMQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want to see Angel Falls in person. It really has to be spectacular.  Now would I climb it? Um... I'm the s… https://t.co/fHwp3RbHUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[you having an attitude bc I have one ain’t gon do nun but make mine worse 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT She bought the place in Florida before Trump was inaugurated.... So much for spin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Oh this is so awesome @EdKrassen!!! I am totally on board with all the other states following!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Ameristar Casino St. Charles https://t.co/gB1dTwBYf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BangtanMD @BTS_twt Same...I can’t sleep. I could have slept another 3 hours but here I am https://t.co/u1k8U3oJv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My moms 1st NHL game went to OT and then a SO. Unfortunately no win. But seeing her reaction to everything Kings wa… https://t.co/I1kR8nIPP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting woken up to my titties getting sucked on is how I wanna wake up every morning 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi my shoulder has been spasming for 3 minutes now and what point should I be concerned]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a matter of time till the red states turn blue.    Ohhhh wait, they just did. https://t.co/74QOngHPDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turquoise &amp; Ivory Glass Pony Beads on brown distressed leather with a silver paw print button. DM to… https://t.co/FmY8mqpkNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Virgin Voyages Wants to Build a Party Scene in the Bahamas to Rival Ibiza https://t.co/XWJ7ZfjAU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TeamUpToCleanUp #HollySpringsMs! Let's #worktogether this month to make our city #Beautiful! While #walkingyourdog… https://t.co/GAAJ2RiyRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me too. Ashamed of our injustice system in America. What message does this send to #RealityWinner?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My face will likely be sore tomorrow from laughing so much and I’m not even mad. johnbcrist and co. you did not dis… https://t.co/iQG5Aryrnk]]></document></documents></author>