<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy to think how this little (not so little anymore) dude turned 3 today!! I remember when you were just a s… https://t.co/qOdGrSGJY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a huge talent on the LA comedy scene. Always a fresh perspective. I can’t believe I’ll never see you at the St… https://t.co/08O0XZRKgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary omg 😮❤️❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/ylR5hVGoN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it has to do with death somehow and time... finality and a disconnect from time itself. 4/4 #SerialKillers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Monterrey, Nuevo Leon, Mexico https://t.co/cQWDAoqumF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fbf to our first car ride together! @ Fort FunBags™ https://t.co/jxlvaU2a0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[So in class today people were talkin mad shit on the Kings and I feel personally attacked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi! @Fly_Norwegian  I made a terrible mistake and booked my flight to Barcelona a day too early - on my best friend… https://t.co/OyJUcwrhee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live look at me every time lawmakers go into caucus meetings for an indefinite amount of time https://t.co/nU5hjUiBa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmurphy4284 @Matt_NSR So are restaurants, and movie theatres, and arenas and professional hockey teams. They balan… https://t.co/kxMENg6Uwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[An oldie but a goodie on the incredibly talented Phoebe Bridgers. Also, a good reminder that’s she’s been raising a… https://t.co/X0Pq3dq4d1]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Stanley Donen who had one hell of a filmography, including one of my all time favorites, TWO FOR THE ROAD. https://t.co/fZ0tYIb7RW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking @Alyssa_Milano So much corruption. Clearly cops pretend like lives don’t matter. I still can’t get over… https://t.co/CDgGortwsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poniss_CHET i got a 360 and a one my guy 😎 n tru af it rained here earlier when i was in my car n it was all peaceful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any senior show kid...Definitely worth the read. https://t.co/aOoHAibS9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Congratulations to you and SpaceX. It was a beautiful launch that brought much joy to this space enthusia… https://t.co/Pzs1IZLFeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i really do annoy my friends with every detail of my life whether they want to hear it or not]]></document><document><![CDATA[The happiest times are with you ❤️😘 @ Pacific Beach Pier https://t.co/IiYXlKfjCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My store has been open for 20 minutes and I’ve already been told I don’t know how to count. Yikes Monday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiladySkye @NPR NPR was the first news I ever listened to, and thanks to their one-sided reporting, I had to activ… https://t.co/tFnM0VyBEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulLeo14128526 @OkCallMeAL Neither do we-whatcan average citizen do? It is a living nightmare-and #GOP could stop… https://t.co/Wsys9bm8mI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally! TY to the youth, Sunrise, AOC &amp; GND....keep shooting for the stars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms. Elizabeth Viola Peacock made her debut on Valentine’s Day February 14, 2019 at 6:19am, coming in at 7lbs 15oz a… https://t.co/fQmyNiaZh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mamiadventure #songoffcompetition #funtimes @ Coral Gables, Florida https://t.co/EkVhY7UsKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcbridemelissa What a beautiful trip. Meslisa, I would watch you do any show with Norman. You have such chemistry. I love you both. 🥰😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh poor babies are you mad that you and the #crimelordtrump cant get your hotels? You've pimped the #whitehouse eno… https://t.co/pdDrkEnKWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danalthor @MrFilmkritik You’re right, what I’ve seen MSNBC and CNN both did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tommy Ash @mstommyash #tommyash @minglewoodhall #minglewoodhall #nolacountyradio #nolacounty @ Minglewood Hall https://t.co/m2KZtogEwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My day &gt; yours! 🥰  Bathed, lotioned, &amp; both in owls for nap time. 🦉 Watching Disney’s “Coco” @asarmiento123… https://t.co/MFtB0vZXlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel like the exact wrfs fit my life,&amp; I want him to go errbody up https://t.co/Ii4dKTB98s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash Juan is an idiot, a big racists, Good job Greg, hopefully Juan will be fired, he belongs on left cable… https://t.co/lQt03O5t4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[In all seriousness can somebody teach me how to save. It’s getting out of hand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiffistrying Any rocks I found! I got a rock tumbler for Christmas one year 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[“although it represents a somewhat un-american thing like secession” is the most whitewashed thing i have ever read… https://t.co/J3aWDkP4cY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read where someone referred to her as the #Democrats #trump...I agree. Except she's scarier than him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who better to inform a library collection than the those who use it most? Thanks @pacifickle and Mrs. Vetter for em… https://t.co/yRU4BL1QsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MauiWahini Get in line...If it were Bill Clinton there would be hearings‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my baby daddy i felt like my ex was tryna set me up when i went to take him his stuff so i was gonna drop my… https://t.co/ahBckFmgZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flamingophan2 You've got to be kidding. He was jailed 4 witness tampering, fraud, +working 4 despots against US in… https://t.co/qjwpQUoNYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[And to go off topic again, I get to see my aunt and uncle tomorrow and I'm super excited because family is love ❤❤❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EITMonline I was a picky eater as a kid, still super picky. The only change is parmesan cheese, I love it now. Sti… https://t.co/gakPNkt8kg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Oh my fuck the president if the free works just addressed his “HATERS” to the entire world.  It’s… https://t.co/u1rBLGoS8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VillainsCoach @Ryan_moon2 @NCHSAA @NCAA @d3hoops Always loved watching Ryan leave it all in the floor!@Ryan_moon2 proud of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[DiBenedetto’s odds are at 125/1 today. At some point he’s going to win a race! #TicketGuardian500]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder I was shocked to hear that Trump's new Labor Secy. was the AG who let Epstein off for raping and traffickin… https://t.co/y3dARoVjxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[In upstate NY it should be illegal to have gas pumps that don’t have the the prop stand so you can wait in your car… https://t.co/nJsr0i8z75]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realdonaldtrump, you have no right to control my body or my decisions. Your gag rule keeps patients who get care… https://t.co/Qcq4pbWq6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the ones I love tonight leave tonight was the most heart breaking thing ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LBComicExpo no my Triton  aqua boy. Hehe @prideofgyypsies where you at ? See what I had to deal with 😝 https://t.co/vWUp4mdAA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wash your hands and say a prayer because Jesus and germs are everywhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenRonJohnson Republican. Sen. Rand Paul of Kentucky revealed this week that there are at least 10 Senate Republic… https://t.co/0B9CrOjG2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfessorGrains That should inspire u. You have good ideas all the time, follow through w them and u can get your… https://t.co/vyxP95gZva]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NASCAR Fans! @JTGRacing is giving away over $20,000 in prizes in the Flavor Fill Up Sweepstakes, ENTER NOW! https://t.co/Uk04pEGLZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gotstratosphere @pintocomics @GalWalks @VctmsAndVillans @DoYouEvenComic @ComicCrusaders @2mancomicbook… https://t.co/LEIL6XvsiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collaborating with our mainstream friends #buildingsocialskills #guesswho #jenga https://t.co/TOMV0vCATX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Bill, my heart goes out to you, I was with my mom that last 17 hours of her life. To watch the woman w… https://t.co/QW7utYO995]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadevetts @LoriJONeil @Cpeuterb Yes I got it finally! And I got my tickets!!! Thank you 🙏🏼 I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation I pray you dont get hurt. They should be charge as assault on a police officer. You wear a badge 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders enters crowded 2020 presidential race  https://t.co/Oe7sutLd6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimbetech @JeffreyGuterman @missykender @tedlieu @nytimes @FoxNews @CARandDRIVER He got away with sexual harassment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@livverino @karinakayr liv, and I cannot stress this enough..,u the realest one https://t.co/VeMLJx0PBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregNorberg @OscuraPraetoria Please someone start a petition to get Pelosi out NOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at this diner in Denver and one of the waitresses came up to me at the bar and said "did you know you're absolu… https://t.co/dBF4ebtcR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GSoteloT48 @Telemundo48 @nbcbayarea May God bless you in this new chapter of your life! 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WakeUp__MrWest 😢 it does lol but the pizza was worth it so it’s okay 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magioneofkind i need these in pink and you need them in black maybe red]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldmanliver @EveScottGarner @HondoResists @kaysintBB @mccunecicki @ommatid @Ldogls @illegitamatepr1… https://t.co/XJ8E7CRReV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Основными племенами, населявшими территорию нынешнего Лондона были племена Ирокезов, Одауа (так же известные как От… https://t.co/qFyJcibDlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My youngest grandson  so proud. For all my college football coaching friends. Check out heart over height  by Leste… https://t.co/kryGZc4vAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎵 𝗖𝗢𝗠𝗜𝗡𝗚 𝗦𝗢𝗢𝗡 🎵 #TwentyOnePilots ● #StressedOut ★ @DaniBTheDJ Vs @DobViscoMusic #Bootleg ★ • #DaniB #DaniBTheDJ… https://t.co/iAj3DeMG34]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan used to work my nerves...and he turned out to be oom best friends. Goes to show, your friends don’t always h… https://t.co/aFurZQqQ1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billboard @RandyRainbow   @StephenAtHome don’t you think he should be on SCs The Late Show to share his taken with… https://t.co/ygD84HOrxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont you love it when its a bunch of clones @ Fort Lauderdale, Florida https://t.co/0zwGQzsCqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickDurbin Unfortunately, Type 1s like myself can’t change insulin type or brand on the whims of the market. Nor i… https://t.co/iXVTDDLgAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg... I didn't know. I feel sick.  Now you do. You should.  #missunderstandings]]></document><document><![CDATA[The motivation for going to work on a Saturday is reallllll low right now.. 🙃😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just now realizing that my aesthetic includes Southern homes with fancy staircases 🌷  So happy to be at Tri Sigma’s… https://t.co/Tl3u4OrDvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting Pretty Sick of the Race Card  Scary the Bar's soo LOW!! And to think We will pay THIS MISCREANT a Life Pens… https://t.co/e6UpMYI84B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tower of Power Rochester New York 7-05-2012  Only So much Oil https://t.co/62cFwMlUpW via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul This Sir is what you should be working to expose. Not standing against our @potus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Socialism is not communism, people!  Communism was to be the end result of the socialist experiment. That, never ha… https://t.co/0i3iUaLPi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PierreProudhonJ @JaviSiman @ARENAOFICIAL GANA el primero como ejemplo ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Yeah.... Then there will be plans only the rich can afford. &amp; our care will go to crap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bayleelong3 You are the cutest. I get a mix between hybrid and volume! I want them to look natural and not too fla… https://t.co/iwxcx6d7ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was literally about to quit my job, but like I have hella concerts in May so now I need to hustle lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful #MarcJacobs show . #theartofbehindsthescenes #nyfw #zefashioninsider #Love 💫✨ à New York, New York https://t.co/TAaCRAkdbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@historylvrsclub Beautiful lady, inside &amp; out. She didn't deserve to die. 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sixpackspeak @BizzieBaker @Rustyhampton Sadly so many Mississippians sound just as uninformed as the people that e… https://t.co/VpncgXdfnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[My view ❤️🎵🎶🎼 #jazz #bigband #fabforties @ Paris Center of Fine Arts https://t.co/ahey9kBsti]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Everybody @NikuKazori @AudreyKENS5 @ForganySarah @barrydavistv @MHurstKENS5 @HenryRamosTV @PaulMireles… https://t.co/0ydMscz9yA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me ready to burst when I have to keep a juicy secret! 🤦🏽‍♀️  As Latin@s, many of us grow up with someone in the fam… https://t.co/46fGZH7FaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattwasfunny I love Family Feud! You would make an awesome HOST for it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UberEats @DubsReviews I can’t refuse a shamrock shake! Feel free to DM me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BullPup2A @PremoJohn I hear yang. Abolish all demorats, socialists, and left leaning moonbats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! I remember this tornado... I wanted to storm chase it and my dad said hell no.... #wicked]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm helping @action4ifaw save the critically endangered North Atlantic right whale. Will you join me in being part… https://t.co/PEm3jY0uT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roger Stone has an estimated net worth of $21.5 Million. He is trying to raise funds for his defense. @GOP, who is… https://t.co/LbRss3BpiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenwissclark Seriously. We have to hide all food. He gets into everything. And I was really looking forward to those!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly there isn’t no other clique like my sisters and I 😂😂😂 we too much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took a midterm and just finished up a workout so..... do I open the Prosecco now...?]]></document></documents></author>