<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[You would think I’m his actual kid sometimes bc this is me lol https://t.co/NluNEWziCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Pennsylvania - @visitpa w/ @emilyaskedwhy https://t.co/p42e0GFm5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t even call myself libertarian anymore. I’d say I’m rothbardian anarcho-capitalist. If you have questions dm me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertoEscorcia @CarlosLoret @JesusRCuevas SE ACABO EL TIEMPO EN QUE USTEDES HABLABAN Y DIFAMABAN AH AMLO Y NADIE… https://t.co/cArerjbkG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[It happened just after 3 am this morning. Authorities have not been able to identify the body.   Here are the visua… https://t.co/KgSsGPX1dm]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But I don’t want your hope. I don’t want you to be hopeful. I want you to panic.”@GretaThunberg - the generation t… https://t.co/Daj0CrIamG]]></document><document><![CDATA[please note that i have been a @kirstynhippe stan for FOUR YEARS https://t.co/vkQR1pqbei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArchCityCMH It’s honestly lovely. While we were there I looked up what it was previously to make sure it hadn’t ge… https://t.co/0upYDkXkyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only thing getting me through work is this Duke v UNC game lol least some basketball is gonna be on]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 week from today is national #dressinblueday So get your BLUE ready!!! Mark your calendars and set your reminders… https://t.co/R559q0KyWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliegere4 @rachel_gere @HumbleISD_CLC @HumbleISD_JFE @Melissa_C_411 @ElizabethFagen @HumbleISD Looks like a succe… https://t.co/XbCuN0xS9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I do makeup for the entire bridal party? Yes I can! Makeup by me assisted by Riker hair by @lizmulvey… https://t.co/lHjIPt1QsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnyosmond @marieosmond Finally my two surgeries are over with. It has been a long couple months. With having my… https://t.co/De4C6wgQI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hightidepods @NaomiDinah @nypost The only problem I see is a bunch of hypocritical judgmental idiots. Beauty comes… https://t.co/qAI2B9bAUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else getting their butt kicked by Daylight Saving? https://t.co/fv92j50305]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered this @disturbed #sweepstakes on #tunespeak.  Follow the link to enter and help me earn entries. https://t.co/FrifGLFBui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrs_Stock Looks like fun! Ss love being able to write on their desk with dry-erase markers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephaniemg19 About damn time someone has the same opinion as me .. idc either about them coming back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaSzatkowski @dog_rates Moxie the Australian Shepherd on a hike and checking out the camera lens. https://t.co/PqXbF4YKvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet @freedom_farter Yes, he is definitely an asshole AND since GAETZ opened his big mouth, he better hope no… https://t.co/Ui0af8hcdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good times tonight @ChrisJazzCafe2 .. the rig sounded great. #bass #viscount #legend #hurricane210 #speaker… https://t.co/RZtaLvnCxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hjj122 @Omundson Yess! Psych is my absolute favorite. I’ve seen a few episodes of Monk- I need to start watching t… https://t.co/9CLUOxUae7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family Ski Trip 2019 @ Whiteface Mountain - Lake Placid https://t.co/zhAo7IgXhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Designing with vintage Architectural Interior https://t.co/f0z5AJf64W https://t.co/g9uLGcpzmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pilar_rod Dile q me escriba un mensaje con la historia completa, el plan q tiene, la ciudad a llegar todo!! ... si… https://t.co/3Wfl4ep5iW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJudy you are so darn popular. Oceans 8 and @WillAndGrace! I always love watching your work. Makes my day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope it’s tomorrow because I’m very discouraged about America tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @deja_berry and @anthony_pops to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations, no… https://t.co/qZ2cwiBhxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StanleyRoberts yup, because that's still better than keeping California...lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realFFK @Underground_RT @RT_com MOST INTELLIGENT MAN!!  EXCELLENT SPEAKER. VOTE ATIKU AMEN!!! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tickets | The Color Purple | Riverside Center for the Performing Arts Tickets https://t.co/UDPvTKzxAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s a good day because I woke up and I’m still here❤️👗 @ Levittown, New York https://t.co/7EAPK3uynO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterTPiazza @Jenna_Tomasello @hechingerreport @AERA_EdResearch @integratedschls Yes! Or imagine if we measured th… https://t.co/wYSggvtTCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aug1405 @Moldsprayers @spaztic1213 @SeniorBoobies @OU850 @mysilmaril @MINPIN8357 @gagirlxo @WylieMcFly @skjewell43… https://t.co/9Gs7yUEDY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerBer12 @FPE66 @aarrrgggghhhhh3 @RevKeithBritt @sharpe115 @USxCONSERVATIVE @KaliS_18 @PreacherKeith1 @Kcty25… https://t.co/gWm7tHR49R]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEED:  - set clear policy goals + measures w/ all stakeholders including those outside tech + govt  - COLLABORATIVE… https://t.co/jtMerOlj3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Depunked ever since Bridgette came out i lost interest the meta is gross]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday night drinks with the most amazing women in my life. ❤️ https://t.co/xd4FaVYyjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @jonahkoslen for celebrating the 40th anniversary of an album I played a bazillion times since high school.… https://t.co/9N58s0uRor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw comments on Facebook saying My Chemical Romance sucks and I started crying because they didn’t experienc… https://t.co/76eFvlkAoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do people care and get so invested  in celebrities and their relationships]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreddyGuevaraC @jguaido Más o menos los mismos años que se lleva llamando a la calle 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd become an advocate for frivolous abortion only if I had a time machine so I could go back and befriend and beco… https://t.co/Pp1pMGLtBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[your “friend” who has caused so much drama yet you refuse to acknowledge it. you’ve lost your two friends who have… https://t.co/FxFvn3MftZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@digitalbookgirl I think his book on the subject should be required reading to graduate high school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton had some BAALLSSS to ask for Permission after speaking to Tayshia’s dad🤯 like bro you just told him about te… https://t.co/iaPmesru0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjrmurphy1 New York hasn't even tried him there yet. His troubles are a long way to go yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro I get it Ana. What a wonderful gift she gave you and what a wonderful gift you are giving her❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKarem nice portrayal on @snl last night! Your efforts in the rose garden did not go unnoticed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gothenem The term I use when I'm feeling that way is numb or apathetic. Hang in there Jeff. 💖 You are loved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taniaaabee If Jose can buy Miriam and the girls pad this girl boyfriend can do it without likes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sydneylkaster @ManMadeMoon Sure, I’m in Boston and can take care of him for a 1/3 of the year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPIXtv @SFGiants @DennisKPIX Did I stop a heart attack? I’ve been very stressed, yesterday walking dogs I had a ti… https://t.co/wQuEvQOexV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terre Haute South Vigo High School students return back to school today. Superintendent Rob Haworth says there will… https://t.co/r9U1iO6Ufb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAW3343 The man I like to listen to (who I may have an inappropriate crush on) is Nick Ackerman.  Why?  Because he… https://t.co/pqWWJBH7Sn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECSchoolofEd @EmmanuelCollege @EmmanuelAlumni Which award did they win? The Sylvia Brown? That's awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allegratastic @snopes Come to think of it somebody ought to create it for real.  Certainly the technology must exist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadmoutray They were doing it in Tucson,  knocking on doors and asking for mail in ballots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KwikWarren Not defending Roseann but I thought Valerie Jarrett was white too]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate acid reflux. Hoping the Protonix I’m getting today will help. I don’t like feeling like I’m going to vomit all the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMTortuga I didn’t get anything special today, but my man treats me like@gold every day so I’m good :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[West Virginia teachers to return to classes after 2nd day of strike over now-killed bill. https://t.co/PEXF3C1Frv https://t.co/LShmRCGoUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends are the most important thing in this world, don’t ever forget that]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the mouse takes longer to go down than the actual surgery takes https://t.co/WzaE3nQ09c]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang amusing. #laughter #lol #smile #hilarious https://t.co/zRmSTpSVtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AprilDawnRaney @burgess_shelley @burgessdave @adr_parry I would like to borrow this book 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a wonderful story! And the chocolate is great too :) #chocolate #helpingothers #refugees #startups]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre @kelly_clarkson #meaningoflifetour @ #myxec  Thinking another band I know should look into this model 🌻🌞🌜🎸😎 Thi… https://t.co/LZJfl13Kne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demand McDonald's increase its minimum wage to $15 - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/rpppkEIsmg via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mehdirhasan @RepLeeZeldin  Is it because he believes in condemning anti-Semitism but NOT anti Islamophobia? Or is… https://t.co/Yy2Kqq9GFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sabes qué, ya no te quiero ver; soñé que te quejabas de mi suéter amarillo y la neta así no ¡Así, NO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j0nyepez i love love LOVE this, keep on slaying, star⭐️ you so deserve this!!!❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilynussbaum Hood to Coast. A documentary movie covering 4 of the teams running a 200 mile relay race in Oregon. It was really good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie is the Tez Cruz of the left.   A reputation of which I'm sure he is proud. https://t.co/RNocRV140R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrH_OnTheEdge @Lenicia4 @EsparzaCL @tsalinas11 @JRod_EISD check out this fabulous teacher and her amazing scholars… https://t.co/49cnOk7xgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Diplomats @travellers #journalists #photographers  @TravelLeisure @NEXTTravlStream @cntraveller @NatGeoTravel… https://t.co/sx53eVL0aO]]></document><document><![CDATA[due to personal reasons I will checking myself into a 1920s style insane asylum stricken with female hysteria]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anneoakli @BillKristol Why don’t you watch the whole clip B4 you take one sentence taken out of context by a suspi… https://t.co/X3oRnWhAq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricSully1037 @1037TheBuzz KY radio just said they (Wildcats) are held to a higher standard 🤔 #WPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nailogical Holo face masks!!! Definitely should try 😀 https://t.co/Afmdk30Qqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[1.  CHILDREN OF PARADISE was nothing short of a religious experience when I saw it at the @newbeverly in 2002. Sinc… https://t.co/X8iKZeirl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCS37 Like her face makes me wanna vomit between all the ugliness and the lies. Her husband must fuck her from behind. 🤮🤮🤮🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot we were having a guest speaker in class this morning.... Didn’t need to stay up to do those readings after all. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever wear pants that are too tight &amp; it like kills your mood completely ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Associate General Counsel - https://t.co/BwGia5ia7V #Legal #SantaBarbara, CA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this time of year.... what’s your Irish name? Oh, do I need a new one? I’m Irish I have a name, what the fuck do you want from me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mal_eezy5 He nice enough to make it happen. Side note did you know there is a deluxe version of Free TC on Apple M… https://t.co/4qekXfhyrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of you smell like cigarettes please stay always from me, I will puke on you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelsBells808 @LittleMissFlint @SikhProf It’s most definitely relevant. This would not happen to a white child. If… https://t.co/p2NjMcrwKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[thisis how matt and i are handling schedule differences https://t.co/WnIZuspFRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever in love with Zac &amp; Mia on Hulu ❤️ amazing job @KianLawley &amp; @annewinters 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[#US looks creepy as hell. Can't wait for the adrenaline rush of being scared, it looks like it's going to bring 🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last of four public input meetings on what people want the new downtown kck grocery store to look like. The UG need… https://t.co/dXEo3Qtx1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilydgyves UGH. Our mother’s 😩. I told mom it was so late, and she was like its okay!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAFIAAFAI Substantive equality means addressing discrimination and inequality in all forms, including sex, race, class, ability ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so lucky to have such an awesome Art Teacher who teaches the students so many great things, including creati… https://t.co/WryUHqZiTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[So - can anyone tell me if there is going to be another #TrumpShutdown or not?  I keep seeing conflicting STORIES (… https://t.co/JA5HbQDJqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay someone literally commited suicide and that’s all you can say. heartless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKWHITEROOM This is something I have noted and have been trying to better understand the history of mushing better… https://t.co/hqVVrztm5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyLeBlanc24 @CupCakeLady1313 @SWISD_PD @mustag_girl71 @njfarmerwife @4judyblue @Pixxydoodle @CMANGO… https://t.co/bLGTARmb3g]]></document></documents></author>