<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The Robyn show I’m missing tonight is the only time I’ve been happy to have my friends’ insta stories inundated with concert snaps.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Written word for word. In addition, I truly have no idea what is going to come next, but to be fair what is going t… https://t.co/CabLKnoTsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Network Automation Engineer, IT Network Infrastructure - https://t.co/EIJ6HXS6mS #IT #FortWorth, TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Yep. We agree with you there... there was also a mention in Chris Steele’s Dossier referencing the co… https://t.co/wvb8JSFQYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShanCamHPE @northholm @chris_bradbury8 @AISNSWWellbeing @AISNSWPDHPE Love this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peekapak I am helping organize a teacher conference for over 200 and I am looking for some fun give aways. Would y… https://t.co/2N6VwaKw47]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cowboys still going to be watching Amari Cooper highlights when the Raiders pick at 27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark my words: Zabit Magomedsharipov will be the featherweight champ by the end of 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellevisage @RepMaxineWaters I'm so glad you're on the mend!  LOVE watching you on @RuPaulsDragRace]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris #Archer warming up before #Pirates vs #Yankees game. #LetsGoBucs https://t.co/YwZ1gSO8tk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cassandrapye @cmarinucci @millanpatterson Didn’t realize her gender was such a huge issue to people.  I get it tho… https://t.co/KJkFblvbOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[After about a 6 hour hike and fishing I’m tired it’s hot outside today!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to make a difference? Want to change the world? Kindness is free and an easy way to START!… https://t.co/Hah0gbGz26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tjimenez86 @TMobile @SamsungMobileUS Wow! Congratulations!!! #TMobileTuesdays  + #Contest]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@debreese is a major reason why folks say that twitter PD is some of the best PD.   A thread 👇🏻👇🏻👇🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAR 13 DEADLINE: Oppose Trump's Arctic Oil Drilling Plan #FuFascists https://t.co/QK6LUujijw #PeopleB4profit… https://t.co/NMndVXHTWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many colleges can you name off the top of your head that offer speech pathology (Just in Florida)??? I doubt ma… https://t.co/qEJ02IoEx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tapbots I can no longer change the Calcbot app icon and the watch complication no longer shows up as an option to… https://t.co/yVNCHL9e22]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilwaukeeMPS  tells me a transformer malfunctioned. Crews are working to replace it today. District expects class… https://t.co/hhXUxx5rwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, #45 has his own comic book line.  #SpaceForce #endlessmaterial https://t.co/ODRW0TfXqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottShap34 Thanks Scott. Bolden coming out of the dark helped. Wonder why he was benched for so long.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ageratobacco now available! ________ AGERA TOBACCO  Agera tobacco was established in 2017, manufacturing hookah to… https://t.co/E2bPWr9Yx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to Saturn. ❤️ Going to get my dick all toasty for #ValentinesDay2019 https://t.co/sDKktCmUnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[No surprise here.  Sociopaths like the Trumps can’t handle the truth about themselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's really funny to see so many people rip a guys 330 million dollar contract]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is one of my greatest accomplishments in life and im not even mad abt it]]></document><document><![CDATA[dafuq posts - funniest posts (lol,summer,beach,funny,meme,comic,girl,quotes,love,sexy) https://t.co/8Pw5BBCQzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kamaubobb @BannekerPride @SXSWEDU @Banneker_HS To hear this man speak is a valuable and very moving experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching a couple peaceful moments with a hot cup of coffee. (@ Kernan Kompound in Philadelphia, PA) https://t.co/6i6PomeBG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kamwhitten wasn’t 13 when she made her Twitter and she just got blocked on twitter and she’s so mad lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markboone219 @MapoTofuAddict @peterjhasson @MeghanMcCain lol literally everyone who voted against the resolution c… https://t.co/LaOuepNc04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Facetofficial ummm y is it that my girl is telling me u told her to leave me at 7:30 in the am 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4/7. Covers of books I 💙 with no explanation. https://t.co/3mpn78aaQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DACHIWAY why did this meme have Johnny vibe energy all over it https://t.co/V1FoqYijzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenBbecT @deadlynitshade @EmmyStar79 It's pop in Canada, but I've heard it's the same in the American south. Sod… https://t.co/lkWS0wwcgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khaleejtimes #Highness (#Uluww) belongs exclusively to Allah, subhaanahu wa ta'aalaa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the 2019 Singapore Orchid Show at the New York Botanical Garden.  #NYBG #plantlove #biophilia https://t.co/hZAa5mSMqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[2001: A Space Odyssey (1968)   I need 2 for this one https://t.co/9xCGf09RuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@viahailey So you’re ready to baby sit Kingston. I’ll drop him off at your place in like an hour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsBoyTony You thought 6 would be at the plunge because you took an opportunity to make fun of Hue for doing it… https://t.co/oMD0ait8G0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SQLAllFather Real devs don't use source control. They keep their peeks and pokes on 360k floppies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Libras. This song goes out to my mom She's very sick. Love you mom. https://t.co/QjHLGzhPra]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rzr #polarisrzr #rzrlife #utv #canam #utvunderground #utvlife #sidebyside #utvaddiction #canamx3 #sandrail… https://t.co/LRW29pdecT]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/eEwkd58x2l  Learn about the features of Yahoo Homepage 1-844-659-2999 by calling us  #YahooHomepage… https://t.co/9EOd9wNaiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michaelblackk12 Y’all have/had a squad full of underrated cats.   Go prove them wrong!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It you see me looking like a glazed donut mind ya business it’s a tad humid and I ain’t used to this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorgerpsuv Cada niño con hambre, cada madre que perdió a su hijo, cada manifestante asesinado, cada preso político… https://t.co/ubVrO4Qfzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jvreeland26 I don’t disagree. But during rush hour the train from Newark is the only reasonable way to get to manh… https://t.co/VIdevK9yPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad to see #BSUCONF2019 is still going strong. I still feel the power of our young people from my experience ye… https://t.co/1t7EKiBVmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Public restrooms should never have lights on a timer.   Sincerely,  The gentleman sitting in a pitch black bathroom stall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GREAT WHITE YOU CRY A BLESSING FROM DEMOCRATS, HOLING AMERICA IN TICK\THE SON IN LAW IN THE MIDDLE EAST LOOKING FOR… https://t.co/QvN9RuEnhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckGrassley Maybe you Republicans should have done that when you were still in power of both Houses! When you wh… https://t.co/hXUT1S2ayK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregMengelt @bawadaba Correct. Nova’s 4 classes that were part of the title run were ranked 48, 29, 45, 28. None o… https://t.co/StO6TnwtIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @IlhanMN Wow, what a sell out.  You should do something really bold to win your supporters hearts back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Chester County, Pennsylvania https://t.co/UektMGReNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hope your view is still good behind bars you piece of shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrTuttle05 @OhioUBobcats @nvalencia30 We have a scholastic warehouse near us were you can fill up a bag of as many… https://t.co/IYiobhz81M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacqueline_xo2 @ColeAnderson444 @ReyleeRodriquez On sight. @Donna https://t.co/Av8euuNoVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicajin_ @HenryFontanier @triketora @azeem one day the term "mansplaining" will go away and I hope it is in my lifetime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Googzz91 @cobystarr @gregorMLB Missing the point you are trying to make. Are you trying to say Doc didn’t care abo… https://t.co/rNW5EO0chf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who needs flowers when you get one one of these!! #feelingloved #bestwife @ Acura of the Rio Grande Valley https://t.co/jNcLFrBbDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MateoCrosby @pjminterconnect @FERC @WndSlrAlliance Know little about this, but my inner lawyer goes straight to th… https://t.co/3rPDSGxOka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trueblackresist @L_tuhda @blaccnificient1 Okay I get it now African Descendants Of Slaves Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found the worst website on earth and it’s @UPS. It does not accept my address as given because there’s a 1/2 in i… https://t.co/8OZp6cJAYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abigailxxxliz I read a little more and now am even more confused. I think I need to read a lawyer's opinion. Do we… https://t.co/PDCjZu6qL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much fun and really cool to be a part of the @SEC channel on @SIRIUSXM since day 1.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Folks there is a concerted effort to censor all of our voices on social media. Its up to everyone of us to get… https://t.co/HvRqkMTaxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blackout20 @Bills_Chick @TrayTray143 @Weinsteinlaw So your saying laws work for those that abide by them? Perfect.… https://t.co/pgdqpI8k7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Dan, watch her videos without sound. She's much easier to take that way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanaG_Dashie Muchas felicidades Jana, espero que estés ultra feliz. un gran abrazo de cumpleaños y muchísimos beso… https://t.co/gW8lNRhoPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I can say is please don't start hating on Michael Bennett know he is gone. He deserved to get paid and he shoul… https://t.co/kqvmdZkys7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dixie_law @ImmoralReport According to last week’s Sienna Poll, an average of 56 percent of people living in New Yo… https://t.co/YOUbfMiFVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Second Dinner by @mainebeerco @ Koch's High Gravity — https://t.co/cLuYjLeZPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikewichter @Ironhead334 Whoever they had as the crappy fill ins this afternoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you accidentally run over a 12 year old  I completely understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[California AG Becerra plans to sue Trump administration over national emergency declaration https://t.co/MjuyJr2v5g… https://t.co/0agHoY1nhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scott__Hyman @7News That is real classy comment . Not Cool bud . The @Patriots]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Cohen brought additional documents implicating Trump of more wrongdoing, how come these documents (and check cop… https://t.co/AXpUAkMq4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast 2022, Democrats want to take away your Space Force Commerative Coin, and Socialism!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmpeyer Still on the road man it's hot here in Miami https://t.co/SjmIp6FBET]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Warren completed the RnR Washington DC 5K! Time 00:30:36 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/kFxRAxPvgk #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm pushing the 25 th. Any president who is open to giving necular weapons to any country in the middle east is com… https://t.co/r1u1VeORgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_grammar_ The “people will move” is more realistic if there are similar jobs in the same area.  Employees want to… https://t.co/yo9mKPmWPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RotanaMusic @faaiz727 Queen of all generations of Lebanon she is #queenofpop @NawalElZoghbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 14235 El Clavel Way #DelrayBeach #FL  #realestate https://t.co/GbT1kjSRW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd like to thank my friends for being my Guinea pigs when I didnt really know a lot of other models . @ Holyoke, M… https://t.co/v9Frdy7dPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRock how comes you do not have any fitted or flex 💪🏼 fitted hats? Haha see what I did there. 😂 I am not a fan o… https://t.co/Ie215Evpy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol they prob wanted to curse him out but was like “let’s chill, it’s LeBron” 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does it make it any better that they were chocolate chip? That’s my only saving grace at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LanceMannion I mean, if we're looking at current polling, Biden is the current front-runner. If we're assuming Bid… https://t.co/IqowMf2IBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I genuinely feel bad for the Lebron haters.   Spent their lives focused on bashing a dude for his every move instea… https://t.co/G74MrgKCja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoanWil57769727 @seanhannity You won a ride forever on phones with PRESIDENT TRUMP  I got fake news. Most valuable… https://t.co/45ay2qH417]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOMAR 2 GOLS DE ADEMILSON 44 ANOS AH EU TO É CHATEADO DEMAIS COM ESSE TREM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penny_schulz @naniof_two @LLinWood @Barnes_Law I don't have the Financial means but I'd be happy that if someone t… https://t.co/h4ckiNcvSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mortgage company sent me an email wishing me happy birthday. Not once did they mention thank you for all the interest I pay!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This @thebukuproject times have me geeked af now. It’s almost here fam!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many volunteers came to our @MomsDemand Advocacy Day today.  Proud to see this movement growing in Arkansas.… https://t.co/kfTGEdsO1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benhamdos Who did Luda do a song with? I don’t pay much attention to country]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a crazy dream that my attorney officed out of the @ArmchairExpPod Attic. As I was leaving my meeting with said… https://t.co/j0cz6CCnUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamAllen_1 @AOC No we don’t. Not all of us. It’s not an effective fix either. Systemic problems cannot be fixed… https://t.co/vA1YvpFM0f]]></document></documents></author>