<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Your known hex That you strained my world So I put this gun to my head And I smile... Smile]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mickluf92 @NanaQwofy @corby_aroma Damn. Ein drug dealer b serious. Pablo shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraLMonroe33 It was gonna end poorly. He couldn't recruit enough shooters for that Princeton Offense he runs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[About the GDP of Japan runs through @IBMZ every year on more than 30 billion transactions every day!  That’s scaleable!  #IBMThink2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meat ranked:  1. #Steak 2. #BBQ (not a cookout) 3. Grilled #Chicken 4. #fish 5. #Pork  #food]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tyus_Jones_Stan @advancedstats23 Teague and two Lynx banners for Jrue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SoBeSunrise‼️ #thursdaymotivation @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/H5X9q7lpqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to New Order playing Transmission. Not the same as with Ian Curtis singing. RIP🙏 https://t.co/RYDN2nH87n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Real9thStooge @ProudResister @realDonaldTrump @RepJerryNadler @SpeakerPelosi @HouseDemocrats He'll never be remove… https://t.co/ul0cA3HcFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody’s pumped about the dunk! #letsgooooo @ Gains and Glory https://t.co/hkXmqyUQ2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[The group exercise is called: turnstile.   The mission is to get every freshman (yeah all 184 of them here today) u… https://t.co/nIv3FCFrYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEHermanCain Dems/MSM are the party of show me the person and I’ll show you the crime. Basically unAmerican...Gestapo-like tactic 25/7.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t wear lipstick ~ever~ but somehow there’s 3 in my sephora cart rn. ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you think #Venezuelans are suffering enough? You are truly a cruel person!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔 True. “... no matter how much you deplore procrastination in others, you can always find a good reason to do it y… https://t.co/IvatAWTOfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 more days till we're BAAAAACK!! 😁 Get those piping hot tickets while they last (and get your free Sid King Crazy… https://t.co/zVdFv66BOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KKen29615 @kimguilfoyle NAH. MAGA IS STUPID.  BELIEVES ONE MAN ON HIS TWITTER. https://t.co/TPhsDF8LyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bluejays add 50 pounds to Vlad’s listed weight, Mr. Not Ready For The Big Leagues launches one-handed double off t… https://t.co/NrnERRrmR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scoring from tonight’s Division III Second Round showdown:  @PalyAthletics: Marzano 16 Shepard 12 Chryst 9 (all fou… https://t.co/beizqgiJLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsAntWright @ismat @Misopogon He said “I’m going to have to speak to the big ten office about what I can do better” I love our this coach]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyMail LMAO. Someone actually got paid to research and “write” this. 🤔 seems like y’all have a lot of money to waste over there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RantingGAPeach Gorgeousness!!! Don't know nor do I give a fuck what that DBag says!!! ❤❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[In our Happy Place at the Peacock Cottage. 💚🦚💚 @ Ramona, California https://t.co/l4CvTZtsrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting on my video guy hat 🎩 for a bit over here! Plus I get to learn a TON!! This month Pastor Brad is dropping a… https://t.co/sy2xN2CpOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexstamos Is there “private by default”? What does that mean in practice (for anyone)?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtomli @polishprincessh Sheila Jackson Lee has never once been to see her constituents since she was elected in th… https://t.co/7njH5qW4r8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the worst team Lebrons ever been on in the NBA. Not on paper, but the chemistry is terrible. And he’s ballin too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maused81 Yeah idk what we wanted, cuz al this holding out for this type of contract is weak in my opinion, Giants… https://t.co/jtWpCemzxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I have spent more time golfing and dealing with my multiple baby mamas than I have dealing with  my insecurities a… https://t.co/zCKgDuFx2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might have worked u til 3 AM but at least I got a free rice crispy treat out of it...thx main st east for the present]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adi Gordon #hysterics #spectaclepic #standupcomedy #losangeles #marvista @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/7wWVjpFI5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing show that night, @Lauren_Daigle !!! I can’t wait for you to come back!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robhughes_ All true, they blew that lead, and he shoulda got the “star foul call” buuut it wasn’t a foul ... it’s… https://t.co/c3qFmPXhn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnandWrites @AOC Right but you have automate and rewrite that contract at the same time. We fell for “we’ll close… https://t.co/F9N3qmGhP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cahill_42 @CincyProblems @Sgennett2 Ok if he hits 290 with 15 homers and 90 runs you faint to say the same thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevesgirl56 @RWPUSA @SteveScalise Yes what a disgrace.  @SteveScalise gives speeches at white nationalist convent… https://t.co/vF6oj1G9Ca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at Cognizant? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and informat… https://t.co/kI5IyNjnSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whiteouts in the hills and some power outages district wide. We will be most likely on a 2 hour delay today in the MCSD. Stay tuned.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Encino Resevoir in Van Nuys, CA w/ @theltmgroup https://t.co/5ywtbavJGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not like there were any ins to the two who went with the lasers... I mean hey if any of those girls would ya e… https://t.co/kQHtBieqD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Casey_Raso @Taggs1404 @masseybritt @tylernas @campbell0705 You guys might as well Venmo them the money at the start of the tourney]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SundayFunDay, #PersonalSunday, #RedondoBeachPier, #KiteFeastival https://t.co/KIhyu4RdKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck I’ll try to make it through part 3 and see if my opinion changes but rn it just doesn’t have the charm of part… https://t.co/1oFwxQtdqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those in the know, this is confusing... 🤣🥂🤨😳 #whatsinaname #truthinadvertising @ Gresham, Oregon https://t.co/eRZrmHC3Sr]]></document><document><![CDATA[He claimed a group of Czech prisoners had appealed to Davis for support, which Solzhenitsyn said she had declined.… https://t.co/3jU25f2uD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC if you want a car that has 0 emissions. All electric; call me Mark Cain your friend in the car business. I can… https://t.co/YjTHqzgbsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobilePark Bring back the Seattle Mariners Clock. No reason that can be apart of the stadium. It’s iconic! Come o… https://t.co/KVgZR9kyrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenPezza @TedNesi Last year, basically the same exact bill was there. It too would likely have been approved.… https://t.co/krQrFkDK3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[My schedule would definitely make dating very limited and difficult. It’d basically be a long distance relation ship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattAnders17 @Silverstar0440 @BarackObama @WeSupport45 When Mexico cutting a check for the wall?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erickwunart @DravenIM @DennisTFP WD40’s complete ineptitude as a HC closed the door on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samfbiddle @Gothamist Wait are these icons NOT supposed to be scary clowns?  We're going to have to totally rethin… https://t.co/OpBr1xITB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenJosiah13 Hes still a large individual.  I took lots of pics.....only threw LIVE BP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao what? A pre-emptive congratulatory tweet? Cant wait to see the shrine he posts for himself 20 minutes after ge… https://t.co/JWlBfObIPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ 1st United Methodist of Callahan https://t.co/2fKOY34IRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wohaaxnicolee You’re twice as beautiful and three times as funny. Don’t sell your sell your self short]]></document><document><![CDATA[Milk only comes from Mammals !!! It’s 2019 and I’m still saying this ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every moon is a super moon to me. Even that one orbiting Saturn that looks like a sponge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APompliano @lawmaster Will you make a “Cranky Czech Coin-hater” shirt for Larry? I’ll go in half on the initial print run 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… #WHERESTHELOVE by The Black Eyed Peas https://t.co/yxjVRa1lC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The constitution is the issue. Ron and Rand understand’s what powers each branch have. Ron and Rand Lean libertaria… https://t.co/iV4YRI1Lok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StopBigMoney I greatly respect Pres. Carter, but this is a bogus and stupidly-designed "poll".]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes @AOC Climate change is  Manufactured by democratic socialists to pass some stupid green deal that make… https://t.co/16xmEOF0TR]]></document><document><![CDATA[70 MIL FALSAS IGLESIAS NACEN DE LA BIBLIA, PERO LA BIBLIA NACE DE LA VERDADERA IGLESIA,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh... this poor man just became Twitter-famous.  Read his timeline for new sports related humor. (The NFL player wi… https://t.co/k6YyXdA6NE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGood90551276 @catherinea1992 @marchbrosfilms @PsychoSkoobz @IsmailDaromosu @EmilyShutt2018 @PatriciaMooreC… https://t.co/BtjfFvcJCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren Love how you put “rap” first so we know exactly how white and racist you are, Vanilla Lady]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain't no party like a technical school party cause a technical school party happens at 2pm on a Tuesday and it's ju… https://t.co/D5wM1YsZo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once upon a time I used to do fucking IRONMAN Triathlons for fun. That’s a 2.4 mile swim followed by a 112 mile bik… https://t.co/K0qKJmWJJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember the days when I enjoyed my job and the people who I worked with now it’s just full of idiots and new hires dory looking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch If you only had some help from our crooked judicial system]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big win Ohio State Women’s vs Rutgers. Great homecoming for Adreana Miller.  14 points on 3 Three’s #buddah… https://t.co/bSKCK6GSzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HJudeBoudreaux Hey Jude! Are you envisioning a restaurant? Purely an event space? I know tons of Uptown options.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATrinKTVU @E40 @sal_castaneda @KTVU You, me and Zill Zill, let's get some of that Oxtail too! #Andrea's or #DJ's in the V!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are really naive in Canada! This situation is unacceptable and critical. The government must react immediately.… https://t.co/jjfFoMPXbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Official_Big_T I seriously admire your confidence, I avoid eye contact at all cost...  Which is kind of difficult… https://t.co/PzzlJZCIQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did the grind all the way til the end, and I had a plan to use coins/rep to finish off my 97 Larry Bird. The coin… https://t.co/iJ8H3AIM3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we get Fergie back for the National Anthem...please? #NBAAllStarGame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaRaeTaglia Good morning Alyssa you look absolutely amazing as always ❤️ Hope you had a great weekend. I know… https://t.co/uqazVv49gx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWhitneyBrown Wow, did you just set Perry up for a spectacular belly flop for the ages.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hufkat @JudgeJeanine Nothing that crooked judge says has any credence. As for working on FAUX NEWS, it would be li… https://t.co/OaJ9CzkyT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calvertnet History Fair Awards.  Thanks to Senator Mike Miller for joining us. https://t.co/zI1TQSOZPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyBeckman By the way... you and I met way back in 2005, when your wife was working for the City Schools of Dec… https://t.co/TCCTajcj62]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThoughtFortheDay — “Keep choosing happiness daily and happiness will keep choosing you back.” — Fawn Weaver, autho… https://t.co/jH3zDmC1Fv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little muscle-back puppy can reach the countertops.... #canecorsopuppy @ Milton, Georgia https://t.co/dEcMCqMgJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mayors Yourh Day was “exciting, informative, collaborative . . . and a lot of fun!” Thanks to @AboutChesapeake for… https://t.co/bgCkPAImZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keeping it sweet and simple for Valentine’s Day ❤️! Come try this Taco Stand 🌮on Tyler and B street in Harlingen an… https://t.co/5t6v7e56CO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandystadt @CHSommers @JuddApatow @myszkaway @mitchsunderland @Penthouse @TheWrap @LevineJonathan Damning collecti… https://t.co/OJGJPZ1Ege]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertredway @ABAesq @nbc @Kirkland_Ellis Well, since I have the law degree and license to practice law and have h… https://t.co/knEVUAy68w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport - @atlairport in Atlanta, GA https://t.co/4mgRGCqnqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolzathugg My mom makes the ones I eat. I don’t trust these so-called Honduran restaurants here in LA, plus they… https://t.co/pAVXESCTNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why it’s funny how narratives are painted. 38-26 and all we could talk about was how the team is ruined and… https://t.co/Tc6aF3U9Un]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiannaLawson I’ve been waiting for something new to drop on your ManyVids store! I will def be picking this one up today! ❤️😍🔥❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WLD01 OLD REPUBLICAN SENATORS WHO FEAR TRUMP:  Sullivan, McSally, Cotton, Gardner, Perdue, Risch, Ernst, Roberts,… https://t.co/KSE8dkxxgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stubborndebater @Hailee88 @nytimesworld @nytimes Opps, guess I hurt @stubborndebator's feelings. Oh well, I'll live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter It would be good to have someone correct “telivising” (and interview @jack about when we’ll finally be edit typos in tweets)]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many more times can @JayBilas say he’s “never seen anything like it”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either your soul will be blessed or your soul going to be required @ Jacksonville, Florida https://t.co/cCLej74DJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BW_Jones - loved the latest podcast. I could listen to @CecilHurt talk about 1980s Alabama football ALL day. I kno… https://t.co/WpwjxZcjtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Human Rights Core is when the APA is used against individuals to defame them which ruins American psychology and Me… https://t.co/T01O8RXmSZ]]></document></documents></author>