<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[We are so excited for Marla! She is starting on her 3 day nutrition plan. Let’s cheer her on! . #wallawalla… https://t.co/qegQv5VlVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deep intellectual conversations, is honestly what you should strive for in life. I think that's what we're missing… https://t.co/0fbf5UrLnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody who knows me knows I love birdies.   Never been this close to one of.... Whatever these are.   Haha.… https://t.co/bdBaFnoTmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 4-year old nephew Isaac is getting really good at skateboarding. #ProudUncleMark]]></document><document><![CDATA[The family got together to have dinner to remember pops. Fun fact about my Dad, growing up we lived in a cul-de-sac… https://t.co/uZMtWWMjX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz something tells me you will be going to jail along with POTUS you wanna be bully! #gaetzclown]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve just learned that there is a human out there that goes by Lil Xan... and I bet most of y’all can name one of h… https://t.co/n2VoRA7VRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s all just hope to hell that our #MPs at #QueensPark know better than to enact a poorly constructed bill that… https://t.co/gSQxMz28Ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we have a president that was totally infiltrated by the Russian government and compromised by the Russian gover… https://t.co/XqbxuWG33w]]></document><document><![CDATA[You love to see it! I’m really proud to share with everyone the vision we have for the #ConservativeMovement at FSU… https://t.co/W0gJIfA4oH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats, Ms. (Luz) Garcia is custodian of the month. Nobody deserves it more!! She is awesome. #wearebucs https://t.co/Pm0W7QutKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EyeAmTruth Just needs to be compared to electoral college math. Just because someone is up 51% of votes doesn’t me… https://t.co/BuqKtRturJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #Frisco, TX! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Store Counter Sales at O'Reilly Auto Parts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul you sir are not working for the people. We voted for trump on the promise to build the wall and you and y… https://t.co/nGc4d4gJVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting lineup for Mitty: Michael Mitchell, Devan Sapp, Joseph Vaughn, Marcus Greene, and Mason Ryan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcusBiel It’s not afaik the same thing in US English: one is dairy free]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjdioguardi @KevinLyman @VansWarpedTour @ameettaylor You have to understand: by the time bands get their cut it’s… https://t.co/dY9MonSCi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mariannoo He colored them joints wit a sharpie like George Costanza https://t.co/8C58cfFwlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've made about 3 trips to my car this morning for forgetting my keys, my badge, and my lunch. The first thing I no… https://t.co/RGaaznfGL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another IG purge. Don’t follow to unfollow. I will find you &amp; I will unfollow back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great dinner tonight with #TeamErosa and #TeamSmolka. Thank you stevenwin145 for setting this up. Excited to watch… https://t.co/Gi6WEOr0XR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout outs to my mom once again  god i literally have a music career thanks to that lady smh  Shout outs to my mom… https://t.co/26ZbaaYQTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wenderella60 @luckymee22 @gatewaypundit That guy has got a BIG problem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC @brazencapital Ten years is an indicative timeline for AI. Iranian participation in it's deadly aspects. What… https://t.co/iysrgZtsKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedBSierra June. I've set a deadline for the world panda meet in Pandino Italy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeCamp .. kind of hard to 'rig' anything when they're all running on his platforms :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Guinness Draught by @GuinnessIreland at @sliceofspice1 — https://t.co/Ribyx6JNiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not follow where the path may lead. Go where there is no path, and leave a trail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can already tell this FB group is going to be fun. #NASCAR #Glasshole https://t.co/75oYvt93DW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marissa_lovex @ShrunkBoy @RTxxlslave @CMP_4U @RT4D1 @DirkHooper @find0m @OddDoctor @rtfindom @Fetish_Promos… https://t.co/XFLYeemv3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sun's out &amp; I'm craving ceviche! holboxlosangeles available soon at @chefmealkits 📦🍽👌 @ Holbox https://t.co/Nk156nWT9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Cherry Hill Mall, New Jersey https://t.co/j4I3HtGAPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my photos with my queen @parishilton. Had so many have to start another collage lol. Hope you had the most amaz… https://t.co/5TUDb5dj5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ndpsaints side arm. #po #27anddone @ Notre Dame Preparatory High School https://t.co/TnJB4rraJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWilderThings I feel like "to us" vs "for us" makes a huge difference?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bleeker185 If you’re comparing 2019 to 1996, then yes, you’re right. 1960? Not so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wanna go to meek mill with me on Friday. &amp; I can say no if I don’t wanna go with u]]></document><document><![CDATA[〰〰 👁👁   🌴    💋  #Military #Growing #Pineapple @ #Home in #Sebring #Florida #Mooning #Smoking #Yellow #Butt… https://t.co/GiYnJr9zzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buckets_magee @ColinCowherd totally agree, East playoffs will be exciting i’m expecting a Boston Milwaukee conference finals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddbrownradio @ovedabrown @deadlinedd Well in a few short weeks we will have a female Mayor and I see that as a good thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Food Network’s CHOPPED (Though he clearly didn’t read his invite beyond the subject line)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Life_of_Nat Every second legendary is a dog looking monster!!! I want more legendary fish!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an incredible night at @TonysofCinci with the @GoBEARCATS crew and @mikebohn_uc. Great atmosphere and great fo… https://t.co/Pw0BZguwRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vaya temporada para el olvido!!!! Hay están todas las malas ediciones tomadas, un poco de respeto por los seguidores @realmadrid #RealMadrid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BizPaul @BBCParliament Mis-typed after a beer or two last night ... I meant, not show parliamentary footage *on co… https://t.co/FlkAbIYFok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fallwestmike No, Package was most certainly one of them. I wouldn't have made that up. I don't think. I'm weird like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone is talking to me about something negative in their life and idk what to say https://t.co/M59476N2GG]]></document><document><![CDATA[We resemble Christ the most when we selflessly give of ourselves.   Volunteers of all skill levels can make a diffe… https://t.co/WZoeBBMMc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowwerevolt @TheEllenShow I hope he dies or did die a horrible DEATH 💀.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCrocker Height doesnt matter. If i am taller, you can climb me like Tarzan. Grab my vine, baby! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwing out a shirt because of a rip is like throwing out a car because of a flat tire.  Clothing and other textil… https://t.co/BiEcwrwxrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[once i started doing what i really love, monday legit became my fav day of the week.   always look forward to any n… https://t.co/Z9IwSUFE3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be joined by #CBJ GM @jkekalainen during the 2nd intermission on @971thefan https://t.co/hsLVud7EPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodStryker @sherron914 She is a women scorned turned into a shit stirrer who will try to destroy anyone who gets i… https://t.co/ZiCCVIP3Jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yagftori i think u do,&amp;&amp; trueeeeee. i felt that when ya said women are crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FearTheWaveBlog Believe the end of Hot Rod’s career overlapped with Honeycutt’s for a year or two]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supernatural-Paranormal: Resurrection Mary - Justice Illinois (travel channel) https://t.co/nQuwDvOAWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got told multiple times today I’m a dick lol. I call it how i see it... i think that’s what we need more of in this… https://t.co/t14CkUrztK]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NPq1xUQDHY 🛑MANAFORT IS A TRAITOR, CHEAT, LIAR, CRIMINAL, BANK FRAUDSTERS, *AND MONEY LAUNDER.*AND CHE… https://t.co/CP0htem35Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjhuntz @DailyCaller If he had the balls to try the Lobster Thermidor at The Knife and Fork he give up that crazy Vegan shit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArrhyaShyanne @BillOReilly You stupid bitch!! That doesn't even deserve a comment. You call me ignorant but your F… https://t.co/sMBsdT5yKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Channing_Frye Thank you Channing! You are incredible and very happy to say you played for the Cavs and helped brin… https://t.co/BlX1PzJ79u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jimenez130___ Well Good Im glad I could make your night even better cutie and awe shucks arnt you slick 😏😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the grind continues. Another victory for UT Martin. The team nobody wants to play.  #A4H https://t.co/o4rdrFUtqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hjsbaker They used to preach team all game all the time h til the argument didn’t suit their player]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OpenHouse Alert!  . . Join us for an OPEN HOUSE:  📅 Saturday 3/9 ⏰ 1-4pm . . 📱Text KIMA to "59559" for pics and mo… https://t.co/15zczk4i1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caleb_Isaiah @BrionesIsSweet Lmao make sure you record this shit. He seems the type to shoot me when I have my hands up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided to kill a little time by puttering around my @shudder queue, and they’re already streaming one of my favori… https://t.co/CxXcr7xrMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a St Louis cold case that’s gaining national attention. Our @JennSullivanTV speaks exclusively with the family… https://t.co/ysfhy1yFDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is cool. They’ve been a big player in the information and data generation in sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter Very true. Here are the players from the AFC 👍🏻  Watch Here: https://t.co/WA9qC2Mjii https://t.co/vjqMPITwgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekKoll7 @DeeByrdmanBrown 26 mph between the 2?? That seems like a lot]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should always have a positive mindset to visualize the positive from a difficult situation.  When we always thin… https://t.co/DDgJVI1CIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby turned 19 today! Being her dad is a great honor and brings me tremendous joy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first issue of The (Pensacola) Daily News was published #otd 1889 with an initial #circulation of 2500. The pnj… https://t.co/ir6mg9kWIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[CBD Oil Becomes Next 'Green Gold Rush' But Questions Linger in Texas: What's In It? https://t.co/p3XBSJn2Ne via @nbcdfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freedom of speech, respect, honor and character...if you were accepted to the University I would think you had the… https://t.co/hrWXpRwSlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tus crímenes son incontables grandísimo HIJO DE LA GRAN PUTA!!! los pagarás con tu vida en combate o en Tribunales… https://t.co/tbEEUpX9tB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un marchand d'art arrêté à Roissy pour possession d'une œuvre spoliée par les nazis https://t.co/VAviNQCeHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1ZiTSOT7kl please help out, this man is my former teacher @dmlkjec he passed away on February 11th,201… https://t.co/zy9vCEUUAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[• • • Happy Valentine's Day to all the yacht lovers out there. ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ Photo via miamiyachtshow.… https://t.co/TtuxehJ712]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wetumpka High’s 11th and 12th grade English teachers on this wonderful Friday morning!! All four of them are doing… https://t.co/SEBowDvcVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@columbiatribune Well duh, he’ll be in prison. Better just worry about protecting himself 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ebron85 is the only one that matters because it was a "terrible" signing.... lol it wasnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@everbodyBlocksU @reason @dangillmor Our country was built on the essence of capitalism: slavery and genocide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supra Special. The old one’s cooler than the new one.  #Repost @HammySpeedShop  ・・・ #1979 #toyota #celica #supra… https://t.co/vgvXRYSwjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megynkelly Well Bill,I guess the Red states will just have to settle with having SEX with your Sister,Mother and w… https://t.co/YR2L7t1tIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pfaff_zach consider monterey jack. simple and cheap yet effective and tasty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LKottis @JDAlmostMD @FrazzleMyGimp @KylePlantEmoji this literally is still happening to me rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump 🌴😎☮️ #RatsDesertingTheShip 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣😂😂😂😂😂 #TheResistance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning!  Find the part within you that wants more and never settle for less.  https://t.co/sX1kohGEsN (Today'… https://t.co/1PzUdZ2eRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinAhrns He will never change and yet he is up 5-4 3rd set. It is quite amazing how he just quits on points routinely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christopher Steele will face a London defamation trial later this year, one of two court cases in which he was forc… https://t.co/Sq3CXoyGzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicole_carroll @USATODAY So are you going to resign? After all, according to MSM it’s the morally correct thing to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFantasticIan @mbrleigh This is the only Mickey Mouse I know https://t.co/AdWEXk4iYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moonstruck = best movie of all time, don't fucking @ me if you don't agree that's fucking amore you bitches]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson It’s horrible this is even happening but in some ways it’s a good litmus test of whether people are… https://t.co/8H8G4dtJoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did this black girl allow the Republicans to make her into an ass at the #MichaelCohenTestimony today? https://t.co/NZteTtCY1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[The transfer rumor I’m hearing out of NKY is beyond anything that should ever be permitted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtBusch @MrsAshleyBusch Way cool Kurt. What a majestic place you've found.]]></document></documents></author>