<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BorderNarcotics @FriendlyJMC EXACTLY !! Burn his Butt !! He needs UP on Charges ALL.of the OBAMA Administration]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buffalo Springfield - For What It's Worth 1967 https://t.co/uLRULFx51c via @YouTube Yes my favorite tenor said it 53 years ago. 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[the California sun ive been waiting for 🌞😍🌞😍🌞🌞😍😍 #nicar19 @IRE_NICAR https://t.co/6Ok321HX4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@static_pulse_ @PalayeRoyale Am crying because I have to wait two months.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really sucks when someone turns out to be the opposite of what you thought they were 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @mschlapp Why in the world would you defend this sycophantic shill? He and his wife are vile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoyRamiro182 @Oscarton7 @herreragonzalo3 @TigresOficial El oscar si se fijó jajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_janet_chrystal @4theloveofTex @slightlyaphotog @_AceShot @TrulyGQ_ @brandontonlu Honored to be on this list 🥰😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rooprajfox2 @FOX2News I feel she thought she was going blind. I don't think she could cope with what she thought w… https://t.co/OQamZ8r3HF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FanBoost #StoffelVandoorne @svandoorne #WeLoveYouLiam #LiamTheWorldLovesYou @LiamPayne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nowadays women show all their skin and EVERY lady line (even the private one)..  This is my Outfit Of Everyday..… https://t.co/9lt9b8kOvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought “morning sickness” was supposed to ease up in the 2nd trimester. Well, jokes on me. 🤰🏼😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did the cell phone challenge! 15 students- 85 minute period. Side note:: 138 texts were from one student- who had… https://t.co/Vc6FZNbKg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join us today (Thursday) for after-school tutoring. Our special guest for Biology tutoring/remediation is Ms… https://t.co/JwAdrB9qeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Nickelodeon is rebooting All That, Variety reports”  https://t.co/maf1KbkY4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[smh no matter how stupid or bad he gets at rapping, his production is always top of the line]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @Apple @Google You ought be used to that being Muslim.  Doesn’t your brother own you ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shopping @friezeartfair #friezelosangeles @ Paramount Studios https://t.co/MZLgYyMmOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renatogironloya Quiero poner un comentario odioso, pero me lo ahorraré.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrNickOFMConv Thank you for this thread, Friar Nick! May God bless you with strength, courage, and comfort as toge… https://t.co/R1aLds7RbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain @andylassner Cadet Bone Spurs will go only if they can golf 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jajoaopestana @Don72933216 Republicans needs to stand together and quit cowering like scared rabbits at the wolf(D… https://t.co/P1yHGqI1Qz]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are Scottish cows so they moo with a delightful accent https://t.co/KNdcL9DaRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I miss Madi a little.   Like he doesn’t deserve it. He’s a POS. But that’s as my best friend through so much… https://t.co/KlwV6wjhg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[CALL the Ethic Committee house, 202-225-7103 and demand Omar’s resignation for treason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGally94 is absolutely firing all cylinders tonight. Let’s go- deserves one]]></document><document><![CDATA[A decent public servant devoted to your State who wants to be re-elected touts their record and works with the peop… https://t.co/ONa8nqNK9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol @ la señora gringa que nos nalgueo y nos dijo putas a mi y a mis primas mientras caminabamos a nuestro carro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering how many Liberals have cut off their nose to spite their face. You can’t pass laws from the opposition be… https://t.co/YxDp4HFgsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[you ever had a nail color to long or cracked one now ya whole attitude messed up cause you want em re done me right now 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. Tracked Activists and Journalists Working Near Border https://t.co/stV087gMC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don't get to see enough of Sec Dr Ben Carson. I think he is doing a great job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lessantman @SteakAndIron Same here with the coffee...but decaf. I can’t sleep with too much caffeine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecj_89 @Miiguel93 Cómo qué tenías un amigo en Albacete y no me lo dijiste cuando vivía ahí???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is y’all don’t already know there is absolutely no power on campus and we have had two firealarms in the past two d… https://t.co/Ggue3kmSTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@felicitysousa I tagged my school but then realized I didn’t want them looking at my account lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I wake up so grateful to be part of this strong united community. @wearetrschools]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I have to go to work????? Where’s my lottery winnings????? I don’t think we have to explain ourselves why we nee… https://t.co/e9w9V7FYPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lou_S_Stools Wow Lou, I just randomly liked you a few days ago… Little did I know you are like a celeb!  I guess i… https://t.co/T9bcsOPc0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nichs0318 @RodStryker @charliekirk11 @dbongino @RealSaavedra @RealCandaceO @Thomas1774Paine @michellemalkin… https://t.co/WG9h7oVLHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this #CustomerService job in Thackerville, OK? Click the link in our bio to see it and… https://t.co/bWokWGVNGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi papá (6am): vengo llegando del pedo.  Ahora entiendo por que me encanta tomar, esta en mis genes. Ni pe 💨]]></document><document><![CDATA[i dont like texting first because i always feel like im bothering the person i wanna talk to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Ya think Chris? A mind like yours, thats why you're on FoxNews.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Arrow #Olicity #DontMindMeImJustSwooningOverBabySmoakQueenAndShippingOlicity 🚢❤🎯👓🍼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to make another trip soon. I really need to get out of the valley for a while. 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really looking bad for @POTUS when @FoxNews needs @RushLimbaughEIB to come carry the water.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stylezpromo @Gorgeous211994 @Harry_Styles #BestCoverSong #iHeartAwards #StillTheOne @Harry_Styles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!! Que interesante! Un reportaje Especial de Nuestra Meteoróloga #ventanaaltiempo   yaralasanta por su Noticiero… https://t.co/1i54xpFh0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our nature walk was a success. Best one yet tbh https://t.co/wwryzlv0nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeystephens81 I just got home Michael. I haven’t opened my skittles yet. I’m not a savage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traderjohnt1 @kidgolferman WHO KNOWS... WHO CARES?!? NO REASON MITIGATES THE CRIME.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on #wellness! Pulling out all the stops for these crazy colds and viruses to exit quickly; my office seems to… https://t.co/0Ptzgjajg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[As has been observed many times before, this is false. Tariffs are paid by the importer not the country of origin.… https://t.co/FNYn34swwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dallas nights w/ D Mag &amp; great gals 💕 @ Place at Tyler https://t.co/MewxhKCvtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was time for another several inch chop! If I keep this up, by 2020 I’ll be bald. Left: hair to my waist before I… https://t.co/QbaMUKdbQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[August Alsina - No Love ft. Nicki Minaj https://t.co/zraDfByO27 via @YouTube this song has good and bad memories..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m blunt as hell so don’t ask me anything if you want someone to lie to you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling better than ever, @ryschad33 is training for draft day. Catch his story on @KSNNews news at 10.  https://t.co/JqMgrTbZHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[You determine your worth. A heart of a champion can't be defeated. 💯♥️Speed kills a new move I realized no one has… https://t.co/dg4o0o0HVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kbrunorunner @poetWOAgun I have bought almost all of her books NEVER AGAIN. BYE ann]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of times people would sit with me when i was alone in the dinning hall made want to scream. All i wanted… https://t.co/RSFwMOWjAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayo leme tell yu. This was my shit. &amp; will forever be my shit. IDGAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficerWilliam4 I sing all the time.. I let people see my heart, who I am.. through my music]]></document><document><![CDATA[”There's a moment in life when a soul could die."  #The39steps #StraightOutta1984]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t really stress about anything day to day, so sometimes everything just hits me at once and i get crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daday74 @Domz_4 @BDtrack @BenDavisBasket1 @MenoftheFamily @mommamcgowan Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[BTS of Another Reel for @50cent @bmf_starz Casting  for the role of "Detective Cruz" . 🎬 ....... #BTS #luluactress… https://t.co/wIURp3MLAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Texas2DC1 @rachelheldevans This whole chain appears to be missing the point of what intersectionality is as it is… https://t.co/DFaQE7P60t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Dave &amp; Buster's team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/vDY2VvzpzO #FacilitiesMgmt #Woburn, MA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our Robotics Team. They place 2nd in a hard fought tie breaker battle. #AHSPROUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielGangi Yo jamás he criticado a Usa !  Yo no se ni me importa la política !  Critico a imbeciles cómo tú!  Inh… https://t.co/CY2lErEHnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liason75 Loved them as lake. reminded me so much of Liason even before she knew he was Jason. (Thankfully that’s all over with now).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 10 On-the-Side Cookie Recipes | Cooking On the Side https://t.co/Gkd02ALePc via @kathystrahs https://t.co/xtVCklalt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only reason I tweet like I do while my mom follows me is cuz she can’t beat my ass from 10 hours away 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bnpparibasopen, Tommy and Mo enjoying a little love..... @ BNP Paribas Open https://t.co/NyKa7SCtPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[You must be a real bitter person if all you do is talk shit about how couples celebrate Valentine’s Day. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@46_Ronin these screenshots are so much darker than how I perceived them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plunkettcat @Michelle_Mic6 This now makes us friends and family. United together we stand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesignationSix They used to sell us about 1500 a month in dental products. Not anymore. The saleswoman tries thoug… https://t.co/QAjOxYQxBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapaTosta122 @jennycohn1 @HillaryClinton @SenSchumer @SpeakerPelosi @KamalaHarris @amyklobuchar @CoryBooker @SenSanders Amen! See #NC09]]></document><document><![CDATA[On KRQE NEWS 13 This Morning, I sit down with a doctor from UNMH about what he calls the largest study done to try… https://t.co/FJzb3uNyx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muddygirl198272 @Lance210 A platform like this should be used for better! Not putting anyone’s lives in danger for… https://t.co/z1kwScdmZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look nothing has ever settled with me more... I am my mother’s oldest child and the first to graduate college and b… https://t.co/9fVnJ7cNkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarrisonNHL @KayNurse11 I’m a journalist....who writes about WNBA ... and researched this .... and her tweet is ba… https://t.co/jGKZQI49Km]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve got the BEST MET Team @homedepot2771 Thank you all so much for what you do each day!! 👊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lame. But delicious. (@ The Lowkey Poke Joint in Dallas, TX) https://t.co/62wRfC2bib https://t.co/yRPtxeRdSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoyGeorge A little belated, but would love a Happy Birthday from you (was on Valentine’s Day). Would really mean a… https://t.co/jCjeY7mWiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So, sure, the economy under Pres. Trump is doing well, but millions and millions of U.S. citizens… https://t.co/pDiADKIOGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg @LouDPhillips @DonnieWahlberg is a BA example of how working hard with gratitude in your ❤️ will ge… https://t.co/WPw0w58f6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikalsr @PattyMurray @HouseDemocrats What country has open borders?  How can we allow people to flow in freely wit… https://t.co/I3HGW9h7xJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FitbitSupport  is your system currently down? When I try to log in it says that my IP address has been blocked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Try asking yourself if YOU love you, and then know God does through it all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KerosLowder @MattDoyle76 Desmond Armstrong Steve Cherundolo Fernando Clavijo Owen Hargreaves Pato Margetic Hugo Pe… https://t.co/V3WhNAq4ao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDaleGribbl @livingstonbat A great movie is not the same as great costumes. Lots of marvel movies dont win but… https://t.co/N0T579PzhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting a little beach time 😎 @ Between Piers on the Sand in Garden City Beach, Sc https://t.co/cyvlOa5Cv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[In all honesty I think there should be birth control for men and not women. Women don't have to be the one that hav… https://t.co/eaqKcJB8Pv]]></document><document><![CDATA[can youtube videos be considered Literature (note the capital L)? before you answer, consider movies/films as Literature.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend "girlfriend" when my husband is out of town. https://t.co/CesZJRmjqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WomensHistoryMonth #WomenSupportingWomen First time ever in ART HISTORY Yolanda D Mozdzen Summer of 2018 till now… https://t.co/ZmEvN2qjTV]]></document></documents></author>