<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@megwit_13 AAHHH!! I’m so proud you meg!! Can’t wait to watch you at UNI 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry I haven't been in my email, having foundation issues. #workinprogress #kswx #springthaw https://t.co/LrFchgWuzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vatican has 'secret rules' for priests who father children, the New York Times reports  https://t.co/u1wkALb2Wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrisMtzgr Isn’t that how it’s supposed to be? You got to take care of each other. Sometimes you need to be told you’re being weird. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Universal Tribe Energiser of the day  "It is more important to exercise your pineal gland than it is your bice… https://t.co/nNZ42tXG5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody from the US should fly over to Iran if they won’t release #monicawitt to us and give her the same treatmen… https://t.co/Gg04aEQbDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[One Minute #BREAKDOWN: @DUANEBANGCOM Creates the Perfect Moment for the Counter #BANG!! #BINK!! . This analysis of… https://t.co/hK1RClzuMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scott: I think I’m still a little hungry  Me: well I’m not gonna finish this so  There, done with writing our vows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[where’s my medal for still accomplishing things and living a normal life even though 99 percent of my thoughts now… https://t.co/I4WRDzsGmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaneKangas @Endoair @RealJamesWoods Blame it on Pres. Bush and Ores. Obama who planted the enemy in Minnesota.  No… https://t.co/tZujMI4JpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff show them who is BOSS.  We live the way you fight for us, the American people! 🇺🇸 👉Schiff threatens to… https://t.co/ED8BkONcEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ll miss you @BruceBochy!! Let’s make this season count boys!! #SFGiants]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBlockWagon @MethuenPolice Hi Kenny! Thanks for the Follow. Thank You for your continued LEO support. We appreciate it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UbbiDubbiFamily @UbbidubbiFest @RealDiscoDonnie @DDPWorldwide @So_TexRagers @pazpaz I would love to bring the loml + valentine 🥰 @HChunko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeleisaP @prsadallas @JeannineBrew @WSSouthwest Love seeing you in the audience and always appreciate your great questions :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[#graphicorganizer for #cer claim evidence reasoning #stemscopes has resources for #Science #literacy https://t.co/nUDQ78h7IM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Natti Natasha Music Is Such A Vibe !!!! When I listen her music I feel like I should be sipping a brew on an island 🌴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldivory @JustJaneinWA That is ok! I use to have a desk top, but now I prefer my lap top. I started off with a des… https://t.co/3s2VogURU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @GregRubini I cannot think where we would be without you and John Solomon reporting truth. You are an… https://t.co/ho05Eb8WJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZerlinaMaxwell what can he do if he’s in prison with duck tape over his mouth...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sully_720 We @MomsDemand are with you💯Thank-you for your voice, your action. We hear you and see you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is crazy! Here in solidarity @PGNewsGuild #ShameOnTheBlocks https://t.co/uFD2PArsrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposting @aolccbc: - via crowdfire  #meaningofsuccess  #wisdom #quoteoftheday #quotestoliveby #instaquote #qotd… https://t.co/5lmzqYD7Om]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayBilly2 @andrewmarotta21 Thank you Jay on your great insight on creating a culture where everyone feels valued a… https://t.co/7vQO4qLH3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting dick all in yo stomach smack that ass grab that hair bitch you bet not be no runner 😝🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kurtimus @CamEdwards @EWErickson You don’t understand what it’s all about.Founding father’s included 2nd because t… https://t.co/YL2qiNhz9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@WSSIatASU can’t wait to see all our #Sustainability #leaders from @GreenBiz #greenbiz19 @ASUgreen @EntrepreneurASU https://t.co/7oApTXsb6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[No the worst is when you get your nails done and they ask if you want your eyes brows done too. 😩😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@felipeneto Legal é ensinar criancinhas a mentir e falsificar a idade, para poder entrar na caca 💩 do seu canal, ca… https://t.co/cXkMckJNjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flyboy84 @SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump I'm sure you got their attention, just hope it's not confusing to their simple minds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selfie of the month? Nah, selfie of the year! #ViceLive 📺 https://t.co/mby53m9QDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sun’s out, I’m not freezing my ass off, starting to remember why I liked Chicago after all]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL! Only in a fool’s paradise! His end will arrive, though. Exactly when it’s time to. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Felt bad for Camille during the divorce then losing all in the Malibu Fire. Now this. Happy for her upcoming wedding v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@montelll13 Well I’m not going to tell you on Twitter, goob. Also, you were picking at me and it makes me want to scream so 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw a Minnesota student run up to Matt Haarms flipping him off with his phone right in his face. So unbelievab… https://t.co/6xwpJ2Rkfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#chickenbroth and #vegetarian #tomato #fennel #broth for our #entree course our #wonderful waitress brought the per… https://t.co/Zcn7zXCTMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a high temperature of 60° coming #Pittsburgh's way on Sunday, and you... CAN'T TEACH. THAT!! #BADABOOM, Bes… https://t.co/nZd1ojZT0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarryNj1 @VP @CPAC God us helping us. If we got what we deserved, we would all be in HELL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Father, you weigh what is in our hearts. Free us from oppressors, and, as we wait for your day of judgment, set a f… https://t.co/kr56Q9l4Ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I hope I don’t annoy my friends on trips with all my cameras and filming equipment 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[like literally it’s ONLY when he’s drunk he snores that loud. like WHYYYYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW ART: I finished the Joshua Lawrence Chamberlain page in my sketchbook today. He turned out pretty well. It was… https://t.co/UKTyMwx35x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you beyond what words can describe and you make me proud every moment of every day to be your mom. I am so b… https://t.co/dCQNMXfVR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to know where all these people on the 91 are going at 230 in the afternoon???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockybalboahp Back to work for a few hours this week after a broken wrist . I can do it !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hicusick @jason_ensler That's one of my favorite things about the show....fantastic music!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samanthakerkman Well there appear to lots of cows for slaughter. https://t.co/PO3wVpeT9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @DonCheadle The same man that signed bibles today is the same man allowing this. Let that sink in. While y… https://t.co/UDx0r9mjwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE when the first thing people say to me when I see them is how skinny I’ve gotten and I look so different!!!! Do… https://t.co/Kt7x6npk32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning beautiful world!! Hope all of you have a nice day! 🌻💛 #bepositive]]></document><document><![CDATA[“At 8 months pregnant, after a process that was nothing but positive, I received a formal job offer for a position… https://t.co/rT3Bx1olHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulmar55722997 @Jmerk314 Thank you very much!!! I really do appreciate it. I’m doing good, trying to stay positive!!!💝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel like people are so quick to jump on your flaws and not see what you’re truly about when it comes to that time.… https://t.co/Rl2q42v8wU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwam1993 @BardsOfWar @POTUS my mind went to Hussein. got the dogs never had dogs before phony]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a got damn miracle I have a wonderful pet sitter. For she is subject to this....   Sometimes I wonder if I lov… https://t.co/dPjCQXJQK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay true to who you are and your craft. Part of being an #actor is all about authenticity.  . .. ... .... .....… https://t.co/sUqA4TWgWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You lie once again Donald. But what else should we expect from one who cannot differentiate between true and false!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrFutureExWife0 @MaurkicePouncey @Dat_Dude_Nix @OfficialNFLShop Do it in the site and you will see your discount depending  on your level]]></document><document><![CDATA[🆕  #tcfstyle #andigetdressed #asoscurve  #boldandcurvy #plusfashion #psblogger #plussizebeauty #asseenonme… https://t.co/4yFWHf6EkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacHammondMin True. He, Jesus is the answer to all life’s questions. Jesus. Say it. There’s power in His Name. Mea… https://t.co/SKfruPzG0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shawn Does not make your stepdad right You're a gay man Nothing changes it Nothing makes it wrong This asshole hurt… https://t.co/yOGVw7r210]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenluit Reading this in the #adhd doctor’s office. Solidarity, sister.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArnonClark @BrokenFiction @SQL_Knievel @SQLJuJu @BriannaWu I listened to the tapes too. Never could understand them, though! 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PsychologyBravo @Andy Not true, watch the after shows where Joe, Frank and Joe B said Marty has never even spent t… https://t.co/yWh21paO9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MumfordAndSons for an amazing show in #Ottawa #Canada ❤️s you 🇨🇦 https://t.co/ZZkcCBJTww]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traveling music 🎼🎵🎶  #ListenToThis: Love Is Stronger Than Pride by Sade #NowPlaying @Napster. https://t.co/e8JrLT8cPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking care of a cast iron skillet is harder than taking care of a living pet. There, I said it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This actual idiot unfollowed me on Instagram and I was about to unfollow her but she’s an actual idiot like I’m gue… https://t.co/dDWN1oAuhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I could edit tweets... I’d change the last one to .... we want the ability to edit tweets...#MyTwitterAnniversary]]></document><document><![CDATA[In light of Karl Lagerfeld passing, just a reminder that his thoughts on migrants, minorities, and fat women are es… https://t.co/vftVHbFgvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @realDonaldTrump I'd like to know exactly why you believe it has been debunked?  Why do you think all tho… https://t.co/VeG0xIAXzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remembered why I don’t stay inside during break these mf need some mental fucking help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oapostrophe33 @fritzakakickass @DonaldJTrumpJr Is that you I see clapping in the background?  Who TAUGHT you that behavior?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok but like imagine a front camera so you don’t scrape your cars chin https://t.co/tOGoRaXWZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[H.R. 1 and dubbed the For the People Act by Democrats, was approved on a party-line 234-193 vote.… https://t.co/LeDfstTUy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When asked what my motivation is, I remember this. I was 46 and had lost most of the movement in my leg because of… https://t.co/68ZyFS71GE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder @Tracy10743406 Biden is a psychopathand he isnt going to win anything he should just get in his rocking chair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarmanSinghWSU @AnthroAtWayne Thanks so much! @AnthroAtWayne @WayneAnthroLC @HarmanSinghWSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the Lottery to win $30 tickets to #FreestyleLoveSupreme on @TodayTix! Enter here: https://t.co/KWWt47LOkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the “unforetunately you HAVE NOT been selected” emails for tickets this year have paid off a phase 1 dook ticket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I’m just a “ I don’t like roller coasters “ ass person. I hate those things even the kiddie ones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Сегодня в 10 вечера моя передача на @studio21ru💕 Эфир посвящён нам, прекрасным девушкам, поэтому я составила плейли… https://t.co/624RynuNvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this! Life gives us little reminders of goodness. We just need to stop and enjoy them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@braincelltwo @noturtherapistt Neil could cut me with his razor sharp cheek bones and leave me for dead &amp; I’d thank him]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Here’s to strong women. May we know them, may we be them, may we raise them.” And may we also teach them to lift e… https://t.co/7hMfG2KOcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@librariansylvia @GustavoArellano @hragv @cmonstah @LoudenStudio I don't own a big yellow hat.. https://t.co/5NOTaxnMvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m picking up my white boii Dillon tonight 😭🥰🙈 my heart is beyond happy. I might cry. Today is already a great day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday will probably be the last @Braves spring training game I get to see in Orlando ❤️💙😭⚾️ https://t.co/MmcLRgNbmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried the BLT McMuffin from Canada at  the international McDonald's in the city today and it was very good! @ McD… https://t.co/WaBdXuMpSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite thing about med school is looking up the dead white man who named the medical thing after himself 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE never fails. . . the greatest of these is LOVE. 1 Corinthians 13 Happy LOVE Day, daily. #L5💗 @ God's Divine… https://t.co/yF0cswoGpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Des noms féminins en vigueur au Québec depuis... 1979  || https://t.co/HQZDXwpABj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thus with your mouth ye have boasted against me, and have multiplied your words against me: I have heard them. https://t.co/9ub0J63j0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[99% of the time I’m right with my gut feelings... I just hope this time I’m wrong..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game time has been changed to 5:15pm live stats: https://t.co/wx6BjEJFsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realjoeyfatone @TMZ You realize Brian is right. You guys need Justin. Sorry to say that but you guys do even thoug… https://t.co/fXNsgRWnRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL @realDonaldTrump Sorry, but one wonders what kind of help could he possibly offer. Because there's… https://t.co/Boc3EROktE]]></document><document><![CDATA[📱#Samsung Galaxy S10+   🤩  Check out in store for #unbelievableprice 😵   128GB/512GB/1TB @ https://t.co/fnBCMSnBhc… https://t.co/YXRhJkn12O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KerriWingert @AcesseProject That’s my first reaction. I just feel that assessment literacy isn’t a strength in gen… https://t.co/AeM2hiS1ht]]></document></documents></author>