<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Statesville was #crushingit this morning  getting leads and setting the tone for Wednesday!!!! #Biz#midatlanticTAKE… https://t.co/vQNZxdV0Bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fras99 Their Jesus is the one who turns water into Old Milwaukee, slaps the lame on the back and says “walk it off… https://t.co/qJ6tHMMsTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmclymer He should pressure the moderator to fact check everything the Donald says. We haven't had a real presiden… https://t.co/Xej0ZWXcRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamSeoltang3 @BTS_twt YOUR 1 TWEET CAN MAKE DIFFERENCE!   #TwitterBestFandom⁠ ⁠ #TeamBTS #SoompiAwards⁠ ⁠ (@BTS_twt)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@farjad99 @SarieAl @Turki_AlOwerde @RealthingUlli @B0RedS1 @305local @Alkofide @ceasere @awwadsalotaibi @travlnjak… https://t.co/XkMOjBvd2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp @SpeakerPelosi @Ilhan Maybe consider a new minority leader as well https://t.co/i5wUcgKwy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too bad the protesters from 2009 who died can’t do this Ten Year Challenge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerichoSims You’re being wasted at Texas. Chris Beard will get you where you want to go. You would thrive in Lubbock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump But moron, you hire the best people, you hired Sessions you deranged pedophile]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're off on the road to Columbus...@MyJasonThompson @DanielGoddard @sharonlcase @MelissaOrdway @HollywoodCbus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAFrench @benshapiro 10,000 military aged men approaching the border of a not-country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaxAlemany and @KSoltisAnderson look like two gorgeous sisters @Morning_Joe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop and go traffic in #WakeCounty on I-440 EB between Jones Franklin Rd - Exit 1 and Western Blvd - Exit 2, acci... https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters @CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNEWS @FOXNEWS The Communist, supported by the Communist, U S… https://t.co/vtfTvCCSPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngeloRayGomez @DonaldJTrumpJr @johncardillo @realDonaldTrump Sit down Angelo]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @UberEats get your fucking shit together. Wife and I have had two orders cancelled after getting picked up this weekend. This is bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[400 laps at Richmond's 1/3rd-mile @SouthsideSpeed was a test. When Late Model Sportsman cars came along, 100 laps w… https://t.co/LZ8qow7o4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you believe RKelly should face charges 20 years later?  Attorney Albert Soler explaining all of the details on @FOX29philly #fox29goodday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dailybible_app Matthew 5:29 - 30 If your right eye causes you to stumble, gouge it out and throw it away. It is bet https://t.co/OUtxOBolbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[15 years ago today, @GavinNewsom started the Winter of Love in San Francisco, w 1000s of #LGBT people marrying @ Ci… https://t.co/e6E3Bmhi50]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moments away until tip-off at the Stephen C. O’Connell Center for @GatorsMBK! Look for the Gators to get out ahead… https://t.co/2CnqL6huN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skau61 @RedactedTonight It doesn't help to fake like it's not real T C. The more people that know exactly what you… https://t.co/x2LjBD3DNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanvhennessey @FiveThirtyEight Their sports’ takes too often use anecdotal evidence as the basis for their claims… https://t.co/aVSu5qpBzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The order is signed, he says. "We will have a national emergency, then we will be sued," in the 9th circuit. He s… https://t.co/G4fAdjXqII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louisgregoire10 @jp_tvasports @CASinotte @PereNoelPOKER @joeyalfieri @MitchyGallo Je pense que le problème est plu… https://t.co/DolzHQCcrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrchrisham @BWGleason Transitioning from orientating into mobilizing. Awareness of the literacies allows for purpo… https://t.co/rwulOMV28C]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Phillies walkaway from the Harper bullshit, its apparent he doesn't want to play in Philly besides hes not worth t… https://t.co/rpVzYbM0oP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I use to work hard but I’m a work harder 💯💯💯💪🏾💪🏾✅ #3amVibe GO GET THE 💰!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGoodGodAbove @bethany_bardon Hope it wasn't with a Gang cause than it would be..... Oh forget it!?!? 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NobelPrize She was a Polish Champion and a million light years away from the toxic feminists who populate our worl… https://t.co/dXrKDZ7YMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrysanthhee thank u, I try. &amp; ur gonna do great. watch it turn into a book eventually.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are angry because they’re losing the narrative. Everyone has come to realize that they’re just nuts! There is… https://t.co/YbyyW8iR7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes freebies #captainmarveledit @ The Shops at Atlas Park https://t.co/Zuim7RqotO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It gets even worse in FY23-$136 Million. That’s $60 Million more every year than before the assumptions were change… https://t.co/0r3KaRi3lB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrownSound69 I wish... Not quite yet here. But soon. Send some of that FL weather up north.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne No. The military there is already starting to turn their support to the new incoming president. Not a ques… https://t.co/EabDp8jEfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will start by saying this: any airport that does not have a Starbucks does not deserve to be utilized]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bambrose90 @VicLombardi Let's hang. I'm at a swanky LA bar at this very moment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RocketMortgage @QuickenLoans I ain’t giving no one named team rocket my money]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC Joe you work 10 hrs a week, 2 hrs a day yet it seems you have a hard time to actually make it to work like… https://t.co/oDGiGkxDV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin I don't care make Angelica look like a stalker I will show proof otherwise I have so much proof you haven… https://t.co/QTMT8Tbr4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikaVonDoom But did he say "Uno" when he laid that 1st card down? https://t.co/0ppVf6DNZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMannyDJoker @MarkDice Or he don't care.  I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of P… https://t.co/aBn5g2ykv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Boston weatherman just showed us a "coefficient correlation" snow map. Where is @cspenn when you need him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to tomorrow night! @BensonTechPride @BensonAthletics @PILathletics #gotech https://t.co/2zvnQhLOWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I get two people to follow my twitch please 😍 https://t.co/xpT9GzvNpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewMcCrac18 @garoukike @evagolinger @ggreenwald Like most generalizations,  this one is not accurate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turn off the TV...stop listening to selatoius sound-bites... and read the transcripts of democracy in action...sobe… https://t.co/QlclX9VxeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[how can y’all do a mf dirty when you listened to them tell you ab they fucked up history  shit like that is what re… https://t.co/2HmF5PgoFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s not a debate. AP was a generational talent, BeastMode was a very good running back with great moments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basedshaman Sure thing!   Happy you got a kick out of our commercial, that made my night.  E )]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_me_and_d @MrsTyler78 @KristinaNadia @LifesStyleBlog @judyohtweets @iluvtacos822 @AKAMOOOOOM Encouragement https://t.co/nDF7dADurI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uh_bruise_oh Haha love it. Well, we talked about this at New Years and I thought he would go Philly. I think it’s… https://t.co/KeYmVHPTeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright @socasteeswag @SHSBravesSports time to show up and show out! Don’t let an opportunity literally come to you… https://t.co/Lw4FRNcMXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sethblink @NateBehlen @DavidRutz @benshapiro Having grown up in Chicago and experiencing the power and control of… https://t.co/Cr0yZ26GNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Bipolar Disorder's outlet.   #SocialMediaIn4Words https://t.co/1iMr8n1hQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj A third party candidate would only help Trump get re-elected, to finish destroying the United States.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG @buddyhield!!!!! #3pointchallenge #NBAAllStarWeekend #SacramentoPROUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @Dannaja64Danny @JaackSchitt @OutlawedMind @Happy19111 @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1 @billcrowley3rd… https://t.co/Zf40b5pk0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got my @VarialsPA bag today and feeling cute. Might delete l8r 🥴🥰 https://t.co/JryLjF2uSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we Go to War !! God and Me will Intervene too Stop It Fast !! Sincerely yours me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBReich @senatemajldr and the rest of the @GOP are idiots. One huge reason why I switched parties is @senatemajldr… https://t.co/fn4YpAcqOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEJermane @jaevionn Lol as mi madda woulda seh: Dis ah Sunday morning!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WEEI I’ll give him the benefit of the doubt.  Hope he pays someone to cut his lawn so he doesn’t get allergies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No, Donald, that would be that nasty episode in which your mentor and personal lawyer Roy Cohn participated]]></document><document><![CDATA[@760barry @charliekirk11 @SerSereyn @realDonaldTrump If that's the case why did we not create more jobs less regula… https://t.co/XJwScK520D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TP4myBunghol @TerrenceEdwards @LakersNation @Lakers @MagicJohnson No sir, the lakers should be on another level of play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DaylightSavingsTime is here, and so are week. Back at it to bring you the #GoldDomeReport. #gapol #coffee https://t.co/wZAKG3HEVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hdhernandez @gymnation @FallingEmpire77 @NBCNews Thanks ❤️🚔🇺🇸 https://t.co/fFonw7V0XH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMAFighting I can’t blame ref. He looked out. Lifted his arm and just fell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BroAndre78 @jensenoffcampus @daron_russell Blown away the performance! Sucked to be on the other side of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems the more I try to connect with the world, I am feeling more alone than I ever have felt before. #alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's rehearsal time! .  #rdgrocks #kieselguitars #roland #theydontsuck @ San Diego, California https://t.co/bVhTHFPG43]]></document><document><![CDATA[The outline for today's message, "God Is Watching!", is available at https://t.co/nv5RmrZlff.  Click Sermon of the… https://t.co/9wsZEiUNSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiverHawkHockey 's Christian Folin had an assist and was +3 for Montreal #HockeyEast]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of 1Q: Kittitas 22, Brewster 21. Ravet with 15 points already. Caleb Harris has 5. #wabkbscores]]></document><document><![CDATA[how you supposed to figure out what i’m goin through ? you can’t even figure out what’s goin on with you .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Global_Montreal @La_Casella I don’t get it. Successful countries in Scandinavia, Asia, etc, have higher rates of a… https://t.co/koGDX5GyFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACovelli5 Lol every guy in the country nodding their head in agreement as they watch this]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never picked myself up off the ground, eternal struggle remittance and repeat. Now the light shines through my… https://t.co/UU6zGnDklt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP_U @CoachKamC @BleacherReport It can be yes. I'm not arguing that it isn't. I'm stating that over coaching is p… https://t.co/DGb9AGoNLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muse got my ticket 🎫 for the #SimulationTheoryWorldTour I may bee in the nosebleed sections but I’m there for the… https://t.co/M47n0fR462]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDCPope @tomgara I’m sure @SenSchumer @SenGillibrand both from NY are just thrilled w/@SpeakerPelosi’s tempestuo… https://t.co/yhhlKHncmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MallaryCaudill “Sometimes you need someone else to show you the beauty that exists within your own life.”  - Me, right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuffyMeh @AquaVelvaBoy Go ahead and post this mugshot to any of his posts, takes about 20 seconds to get blocked lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Too bad the GOP was even slower to do the same thing to one of its members.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶👿LONE🌑MOON👿🎶  new track 🖤😈 🖤🤘🏼 DROPPING SOON🤘🏼🖤 Engineered by wavymaui . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . #moon… https://t.co/YBcKVDo5Ea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched #BohemianRhapsody wow! Best movie I’ve seen in a long time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebrook24 how does mr Erie dress for a chilly baseball game?60 in WV yesterday nice. I guess I’m still mr WVU Pitts… https://t.co/GTcl9NYR2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practicing gratitude and truly being thankful for the people and blessings in your life right now will transform yo… https://t.co/tSxehOz7Dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Home #Idahome #SunValleyResort @ Sun Valley Resort https://t.co/QCwdEMi9LH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Randy’s ————————————————————— #englewood #losangeles #california #randysdonuts #sunrise #breakfast… https://t.co/In5toWsytM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Digitalnun Five years on, dear sister, and I still remember you in my prayers. https://t.co/9jmxjakGcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[(New Episode) The Anatomy of UFC 235 - Episode 10: Making Championship Weight: So much content coming soon ft… https://t.co/72yD7JJUBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[When God's priorities take precedence in your life, the rest of your responsibilities will fall into their proper p… https://t.co/xxGxme3gVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CherylTuttle59 @realDonaldTrump Maybe they could stop paying 118 billion a yr for ILLEGAL immigrants. That would g… https://t.co/rFXm6HlfMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now it’s time for a AI/Social Media cocktail of a panel. #sxsw (@ Fairmont - Congressional A in Austin, TX) https://t.co/dzlfNya41b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Science_Hooker @CarbonBrief The crisis is looming larger and larger. My guess and that's all it is, is that we are… https://t.co/ozjgcvjESD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am beautiful.   , https://t.co/cl47rQnuIt , , #murrieta #murrietamesahighschool #temecula #mesa… https://t.co/A81SHSP6Ij]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are taking Twitter way too serious..... I’m just cracking jokes, the whole reason I’m on this app. I don’t care… https://t.co/Vu8bMj2kgb]]></document></documents></author>