<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I got asked if I’m single I said “not really” 🤦‍♀️🤦‍♀️🤦‍♀️ https://t.co/HNGFoDS2ES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LovedByBrittany 😂😂😂😂😂 Im prepared. I gave this show 8 years of my life. Might as well give a few months]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a child of Irish American parents, I grew up eating some form of potato with every meal... Every single meal. No… https://t.co/fitJMjhvSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going through my old Summer Ever After photos, and I spotted @Cornbreadcats 😂❤️ https://t.co/dOaF4z5Qyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3d_mhs @JoshuaDrews @theartofed @lpoppart @dpbrown99 @ARTschukei @Wy_ArtisLife @NAEA @Jesbooth @ArtsFCS… https://t.co/b859PEcIfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeachingForward thank you for a great day filled with GOOGLE GOODNESS! #Googlepalooza @masscue https://t.co/TsnUku2Q6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only female on the planet that regrets getting their nipples pierced or 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trungles Literally me in my later years lol 😂  ( considering I’m getting an MA in art history so I get to deal wit… https://t.co/E7ar8Ib8Hz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchwartzApprovd ❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤ Thank you! #DontMindMeImJustWatchingArrowAndShippingOlicity  🚢❤🎯👓 #Arrow #Olicity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: the guy &amp; I went for lunch today. He’s weird, but I like it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah, jackhammering right outside my window at 9am on a Sunday morning. The joys of living in New York. 🙄😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lev_Llylgamyn There are some nice, recent pictures of them together. There is one of Luna also. If I find them I'll post them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning ☀️ Here’s a superset from last nights lower body workout using the leg extension machine.  Full workou… https://t.co/MTMcJpVJyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[For sale!  Hybrid owls and bees.  That you definitely do not have! Only in a single copy!🦉+🐝 36$ +6$shipping @ Wash… https://t.co/HLVxkSh7kE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lennyginise All time, Eddie Guerrero. Currently, Johnny Gargano 😊 https://t.co/b6Npx1waJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well what a nice day. Went for walk with my power wheelchair since first time the sun been out in 2 weeks. t the ot… https://t.co/RASsWFrFex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @Do512 for featuring my #SXSW session with @GA_ATX as a top pick for Day 3!  I’m not worthy! #gaatsxsw https://t.co/FWVHc95zS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 6300 S Falls Cir Dr # 209 #Lauderhill #FL  #realestate https://t.co/scUIAq6Ip3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliasToufexis What! @EliasToufexis I guess those men will hate @MarisaRomanov cause it’s a kickass female lead but… https://t.co/dxvsMvhJvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Doug knows he’s going to the dog park he get SOOOOOOOOOO hyper I can’t handle it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump .... TRUMP'S 'ONLY' SUCCESS..IS GIVING 'HUGE' TAX BREAK TO THE 'WEALTHY' !!!!...ARE YOU… https://t.co/rfPwxz9M3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se tem alguém neste mundo que me conquistou foi ele! Como é lindo meu Deus! #bradleycooper  e @ladygaga   #ladygaga… https://t.co/eY4Z5C8LU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MykelCesare @Lisatay00225424 @TimothyImholt @AOC Here is what ppl fail to understand. Love for a person and a frie… https://t.co/7oWPKJQVHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thc1776 @KimKardashian I don’t pay for TV and hate reality tv. But it’s just such a hater thing to say that she is… https://t.co/zIKTzhxLV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I think any time one of my friends asks me if I compost. The Earth gon have to forgive me because I’m… https://t.co/0fGXPghkow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Theodora8 I want to know about the biological father. He’s never mentioned. Also, only one of the twin girls is in… https://t.co/OxGMNBSMx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little Junior. I have mentioned him before. The "giant alligator" that lives in my dreams, that I have been seeing… https://t.co/6h09i0PyPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You love righteousness and hate wickedness; therefore God, your God, has st you above your companions by anointing… https://t.co/Dme59DcAEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XLimit230 @RevDead2 @HaveFaithArthur That could be.... @RevDead2 he DID try to help me out of the coach!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sminero Nearly one out of two friendships end over a misunderstanding about money (and what if we could find a way… https://t.co/9TXxBVZXJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias por este Twitter, exactamente eso pensé también, @lopezobrador_ es en quien mas confío y por ello creo que… https://t.co/cH3fEdnhcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patrickhusting @nattyover No one can predict exactly what will happen in a complex system. Scientists don’t even f… https://t.co/BGjr9u8ak3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find you a man that looks at you like Bradley Cooper looked at Lady Gaga when they finished singing! 😜 https://t.co/gYFiyUhgxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are powerful, inspiring and are doing just fine. Don't be afraid of your own power! Takeaway from the panel ton… https://t.co/P0sbrF4c8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShepRose @Alleykat1957 Well when all behavior is ok ... Then this happens.. Politics in this country are a mess. E… https://t.co/cvQPNJNWju]]></document><document><![CDATA[My jaw line is so prominent on the right and nonexistent on the left.. wut tf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RissaBriggs This is a fact. Drinking milk and eating chicken is also killing you. People still do it 🤷🏾‍♀️ Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess opinions can’t be wrong but Crowley isn’t full of white trash but go off]]></document><document><![CDATA[TEXAS IS A STATE, NOT A CITY🗣 TEXAS IS A STATE, NOT A CITY🗣 TEXAS IS A STATE, NOT A CITY🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mallorywiest_ We are going this weekend to look at SLU. Meet us there!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sums up @wi11iam_dunn season - triple teamed and still made the basket! #DunnZone #thatsmynephew https://t.co/Pv9BlSPzqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/ Also fact, #Republicans want to take away your #cleanair and #cleanwater, your #nationalparks, your… https://t.co/63iCvV2cFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[✈️delayed 3 hrs hw it is I guess fml hurry up 9pm 🤕 https://t.co/cNiPLsu7at]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LastGreatAct @mitchellreports ALL of the republicans.  McConnell is taking foreign money for his campaigns too.  H… https://t.co/NjxbStUuva]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julito77 @latinorebels @Maria_Hinojosa So a Stripes. You went to Stripes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @kayleighmcenany The thing is the GOP know Trump's idiot followers are too dumb to understand. So if they call… https://t.co/Oac8mCcTrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ejporche @hallmarkchannel @GrahamWardle @HeartlandOnCBC @CDNScreenAwards Funny. I did my votes for him also while… https://t.co/UMBxIvWXwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frostbitecra @ChiefNoelPratt @MGPDFL @CeceFrazer ❤️❤️ you @frostbitecra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaBartiromo @Petco @MorningsMaria @FoxBusiness Adorable 💜💜💜 And glad to see you choose AT&amp;T✔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making lasagna &amp; sweet tea for family game night tonight. @Price_Morgan @JayLColwell @a_l_e_x_1122]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was just on the phone speaking Louisiana Creole with my mother and a really cute older white woman says “Oh you’re… https://t.co/7PdRXrkiDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sydneywilson74 Bung hole is classic, but heeve and yaw is my favorite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Judy_Lincoln @JJcolemanMD Thank you!   For me time in/near nature, cardiovascular exercise, and laughter are huge. 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[White mint chocolate chip ice cream is THE best and only way to have mint chocolate chip ice cream. #fact]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to have to look up stochastic.  Other than that I completely agree.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I manically bought some films today since I got paid and let me tell ya:  I made some choices https://t.co/mHdUuO9CeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instant French vanilla coffee mixed into fresh brewed coffee means hearing the wings of butterflies but not seeing them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneAndOnlyLEE1 You rock, I feel the same way about trying to help others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Never mind I’ll find —“ “SOMEONE LIKE YOUUU I WISH NOTHING BUT THE BEST, FOR YOUUU”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hinojosabears Pre-K Moms join us tomorrow (2/28/19) for Muffins with Mom at 8:30 AM. Kindergarten moms please join… https://t.co/WnisAI5pD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scratch A2: I start mine over on @code.org (big fan of Classic Maze) to get them used to the idea of Block coding. #scratchinpractice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came home and everyone in my family has plans..so my mom gave me $20 for dinner cause she felt bad 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con Sue Photography and Design  🚚 Like our photos...Follow our IG 🚛  This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/kidIjBvbVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[next door but the chimney company told me that the leak is coming from her side of the property.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want my degree so bad but CUNY literally is making it impossible for me https://t.co/HOWduxZoCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[For my birthday, my 16 yo son ... my joy, my heart, the light of my life, gave me ~   His cold.  I'm so sick *cough*  *sniffle*  🤧🤒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCo36734193 I didn't cut his hair. He doesn't strike me as the kind of man who'd be impressed by a Patrick Roy tattoo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I was ready for spring break but waking up to -7 degree weather in March makes me READY for spring break]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stage three run, part two. @nationalninja #NinjaWarrior https://t.co/ZWOe1pnkg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re doing this on purpose for clicks and comments, right?   RIGHT?!?? https://t.co/GHWk21kZsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roberts is not listening to taxpayers sorry he is a Justice retire noe Hold the Revolution: Roberts Keeps Joining H… https://t.co/1WfcN87xAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @timothywmurray To republicans, paying a living wage is socialism because it eats into their profits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@infinitechan @THQNordic https://t.co/pe22OTdppB An Invitation to the Great Awakening]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OseniUnlocked @ChefLajan @TheNameClicks @melpillard @KeKatli 🤣🤣🤣😂🤣😂🤣😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[and the Low Countries. Mercantilism was a system of trade for profit, although commodities were still largely produ… https://t.co/HIFdHLeTKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think my neighborhood bodega is gonna have a problem if they aren’t carrying this. Because I want to stockpile my… https://t.co/si4rvB7SRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HowIStartMyDay #Breakfast #HappyFridayEve #EatMorChikin (@ Chick-fil-A in Chesterfield, VA w/ @bryan_warren)… https://t.co/UgW5cNFjzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julianzelizer @washingtonpost @HowardSchultz Howard believes both parties r “broken.”  So instead of working with… https://t.co/eJxXeEBMrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russiangymstan @cherity1313 lmao i was just waiting for a Valentina comment after seeing the first video of Aliya… https://t.co/ZrIcRh0w6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garrettgreen Same. Makes me so mad at myself for being so unthankful for all the times I could breathe out of both nostrils simultaneously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBraeden Congrats Eric I know you must be so proud of her! I am sure she has a good role model!😊FYI fantastic cour… https://t.co/m3LkmU5Yjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelOsteen I pray this will come true for myself. After moving back to Houston I have found it difficult to get ba… https://t.co/Up0oEBK095]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 hour into Valentine’s Day and I already hate it, let’s try this again next year]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to wear heels for almost 5 hours and I’ve had them off for an hour and my feet feet are still throbbing.  😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s one of those weekends... going to be homebodies, get stuff done and do some cooking. Meatloaf and mashed potatoes on the menu today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone at unt wears flip flops in the winter and rides penny boards to class]]></document><document><![CDATA[El Chapo Says He Is Victim of Phony Witch Hunt https://t.co/AENxDOg406  #AndyBorowitz is a genius.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iambeau @stassi You guys are such a cute couple, dude, put a ring on her already.💍]]></document><document><![CDATA[First night I’ll be sleeping w/o my baby since Thursday, ASK ME IF IM MAD ABOUT IT 😤😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now, #SundayBunday ends, as always, with a photo of the breathtaking @_CARTERDANE 💜💜 https://t.co/trdH6esakR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm raising money for Tom Flint. Click to Donate:  https://t.co/kneDZwydBo via @gofundme]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I steal someone’s seat in class cause the bitch didn’t get there early enough https://t.co/tyqnwc1odR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at friend over here representing Heat Wave doing big kid things :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw So legal representation may now become as difficult to obtain as health insurance for a significant  port… https://t.co/esn24SZAoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SGcrimlaw @AttorneyGriggs @rkelly Tell em Mr. Greenberg they trying to make you be everything that you aren’t!! He… https://t.co/LnZPSLp0V1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creepy. And cool. marqueenhotelseattle @ Marqueen Hotel, Seattle, Wa https://t.co/c08WTVic6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[B R U N E T T E salonfivefortyeight #ottawahair #ottawahairstylist #ottawahairsalon #salonfivefortyeight @ Salon Fi… https://t.co/ZDaseE3Hdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[dear loml please like me back, because @sstephxnie__ , @emi_emmmms  and @Little__Giggles  are tired of me ranting h… https://t.co/hnyUXZwvBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is retail therapy an actual thing? If it is, I think I’ve had it all of February.😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMeetsWorld That was my first choice, but i also need a backup plan in case they don’t turn out very good lol]]></document></documents></author>