<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[There's levels to me. If I'm going to mix genres up I should be able to mix up emotions too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate writing opening paragraphs for papers. I spend most of my time on just the introduction and it’s never good enough smh. Fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[My preschoolers love it when I  serenade them 🤣🤣 well maybe they don't ¿ lmao idk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with this. Rubio is on the right side, but he’s ham-handed, and also expresses Trump interest in being the… https://t.co/UpplneiYlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @RobinhoodApp and we'll both get a stock like $AAPL, $F, or $S for free. Make sure to use my link.  https://t.co/OlM7rcYCsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSScottWhite 12 tm points roto roster size value never changes.  Keep 3 Machado Rd 8, Springer Rd 13, Eloy Rd 13,… https://t.co/uT1VXA8lNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I #awake?  I don’t remember normal sleeping patterns! 😂😂 is it too early to get a #workout in? 😴🙄#wideawake… https://t.co/SlqA1Hxv0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanLegion Indiana @AMLP83 This is how our Flag is Honored by the Indiana Toll Road in both directions. https://t.co/WsvP82rkNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AccuRayno Bernie thanks a lot for your analysis about Sunday if you have the opportunity please include any commen… https://t.co/hLQfNUTOdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calientan elección del PAN municipal https://t.co/p86Jh2RXaE vía @PeriodicoZocalo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woods has 2AM wake-up call to 'start the process' on Sunday https://t.co/xdVrg3lEgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Wednesday #overbooked #spectaclepic #standupcomedy #marvista #losangeles #cai #love @ Timewarp Records https://t.co/tcJKGmlDfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn it - now I’m agreeing with Maureen O’Connor ....   Help me understand @DavidPepper ... I think something is ha… https://t.co/jzqDg0N6GV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the day! Come hangout with the @ymcawnc nutrition team at @wickedweedbeer for a pint of “Nutritional Value” https://t.co/idAusoTUVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talbot was fourth in the Vezina voting in 2016-17, but has dipped the last two years. #Flyers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaGentryLV @NevadaCurrent .22 cal is the best and permanent solution]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenAtHome I had to burn in 2016 I've got to burn again but this time I think it's in my crotch I think I have to go to a doctor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HEYJWOLF @ttujmr @TexasTech I guess. I just allowed my 18 year old to make a grown-up decision and he did which hi… https://t.co/n6mmDUdvxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[And LL joining @dennisfithian and I on @971theticketxyt right now courtside at the Bres for late breaking updates]]></document><document><![CDATA[if it werent' for hilarity . . .  32 Tips For Taking The Perfect Wedding Photo. These are hilarious! Mildly inappro… https://t.co/2r5QnXV04u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmurphy6abc @karenrogers6abc I have a flight tomorrow morning at 6 am, will the snow delay it? Thanks! @6abc]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Pig worthy of Good Beating where the stains are his real Blood💪🏼💪🏼💪🏼💪🏼👊👊👊🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸👍👍👍🍀🍀🍀👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soma Joe beat rey mysterio and r truth and Andrade still United states champion #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheChristinaKim @TheChristinaKim  You would be amazed at the "Horrid Attire" worn to Headquarter (IBM, APPLE) Civi… https://t.co/muRCUd7a5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwinPeaksRevolu I think that the running girl might have been completely unrelated to Laura. The magic of the clas… https://t.co/CHUA3il3wE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OnThisDay in 2006 the last Mobile Army Surgical Hospital (M*A*S*H) was decommissioned by the @USArmy. “Goodbye, Fa… https://t.co/7aJBkwsRaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confederate railroad   Daddy never was the cadillac kind lyrics https://t.co/gkUSm8baHM via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptainJackSzn That is probably the funniest thing you’ve tweeted idk why😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty interesting that McSally is underperforming Trump. If Kelly gets nom, she could be in deep trouble]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun time shooting with @kimiberman  1/2 of the #amazing #duo regiandkimi   These girls have #amazing #harmony toget… https://t.co/H77JPaqfGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packing ALL THE BOOKS because I’m not certain what I’ll need once I arrive at my prayer retreat. Can never have eno… https://t.co/cAPF7s32qZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you a motivated go-getter with Excel experience who would love to help facilitate our day to day corporate meet… https://t.co/nF4HZthTzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are the boys basketball sectional pairings for Howard and Tipton counties.  @ADTigers @Taylor_Titans… https://t.co/FRI6E8EgXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haslametrics would Monmouth be the worst record (14-20) would be 15-20 to make the NCAAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please make una wait for me,is like i wan join for this journey oo 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonnyHMH @BrackAttack78 You work at a hospital!! Have DR write ya something!😂😂 https://t.co/VHmXqZQoqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Ted democrats are far more nasty ! You know that right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreakingBrown @SandyDarity @KamalaHarris She didn’t lie she just said descendants of the slaveholders and the slav… https://t.co/HlGTPzWjpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yet here we are less than 12 hours after claiming I’d never do this again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CiCiAdams_ So steve Harvey is saying ill serve the illuminati because im not gonna be poor nor my children and the… https://t.co/hyDgG7gJlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JABell27 This phrase has so many valid applications.  “penises caused most of the trouble.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein What BS! You are a bigger security Risk than Global Warming! https://t.co/N2fbIGMom5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Swazi4 It's more than just those 2, it's the entire market.  https://t.co/IY9xR45ZFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hollywood is now irrelevant,” says IAC Chairman Barry Diller https://t.co/RkH3UvN69q via @Recode]]></document><document><![CDATA[.....@Oscars2019Live_  is taking exception to last weeks comments by Barry Diller that “Hollywood is now irrelevant”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uhhlehlee Smh I'm expecting at least $50 to hit me in the head during my speech]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kkerwood66 @AltNatSecAgency @Top_Sergeant You've never served and it shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just nominated @Alanaevansxxx for 2019 @XBIZ Cam Awards presented by @MyFreeCams! #xbizmiami https://t.co/G5S7FRZIsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a day for @YaleLacrosse season opener. Hilites and reaction tonight @WTNH @YaleAthletics @Vchun https://t.co/NQCc2tDueE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosswil @TwitterBoulder Thank you... as there absolutely was a baby seat in my truck!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2: I hope my peers in this profession thru networking, sharing ideas, collaborating, and more. Possibilities are e… https://t.co/FvTqc1UAiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my desk flip calendar today is Philippians 4:8 " Fix Your Thoughts On What's True &amp; Good &amp; Right. " Y'all have a Good Weekend!☺✌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayzoMusic thank you for bringing Unleashed to Houston!! Amazing show🔊 WOW! https://t.co/tZdnBKKMXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CY25_Skipper @RussInCheshire @emailtimw A huge number of those who voted Labour last time did so DESPITE Corbyn. H… https://t.co/yqvLy2mE2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenSmartt @StevenBeschloss @rhymeswithred The time is rapidly approaching when it will happen by spontaneous combustion]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have class in less than 7 hours and i plan on brushing my teeth twice before then]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stranger_Hanyo @BuzzFeedNews The end-users deserve far worse.  Those that use rhino horns, Pangolin skills, and ti… https://t.co/F3HBorzwyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I found out about this thing called Snapchat, so follow me if you want. It's mostly stupidity and guinea pigs.… https://t.co/yQPkkl8toK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I told one of my Snapchat followers DMs are for NUDES! Keep sending me your damn story posts and imma block you]]></document><document><![CDATA[A huge fashion inspiration of mine has passed away . . . R.I.P. Karl Lagerfeld https://t.co/TmZUXZvbki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Given his catastrophic #BreakfastClub interview, I have trouble understanding how @SenSanders could move up to thir… https://t.co/2PLxIY3k6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtschmidt83 - Awesome owner - Awesome dog name - Awesome bandana - Awesome treat]]></document><document><![CDATA[The date and the temperature are incongruent... @ Toledo, Ohio https://t.co/U5Yywp7noC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraKimmel It takes a special person! What an awesome age group! #LeadUpChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Todo es un plan q Chávez tenía pre-concevido. Su hija ya tuiteó en favor de "la defensa armada de la sober… https://t.co/vfot1kLFor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JavierEnrikez @levantamiento1 @Polobson @luisaguilerahmo @CARLOSEES @nhaiper @ulisespena @tonymarquezroon… https://t.co/AKUfJLA43I]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to drop another jam from this set. Tune in! https://t.co/yXD9B4yZ3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to this crazy guy right here 😂💰 @DDashark https://t.co/cJAW9BFcCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LOVEHALFBLACK Dude moves how you would imagine a 65 year old retired hooper would move lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F150SuperSnake @BHOAdventures @dj_mac_nificent Even with a full load she's running like a demon... cant wait to re… https://t.co/JYVqxEqg8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom asking me about the menus of restaurants back in my hometown is peak mom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlottej_0_ Guessing Photoshopped, Mohawk skull just doesn’t look right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRock Lucky number 13 Dwayne did u get some rest and relaxation. R you ready 2 get pumped up. Fruity Pebbles the… https://t.co/3gYxCIk8Ax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHELSEA_PROUD @bar_yilmz @CL_football @danlevene Sarri wanted to be 100% certain he had a keeper in who could dive… https://t.co/YURHhqpAJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateDiaz209 I’d love to see you fight again, Nate, but I honestly could go the rest of my life and never see Conor… https://t.co/ssWTzLa4q0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1… https://t.co/CTGooWnnnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CCTDTweets A round of applause for the Games Coordinators and Hosts for putting together all of the pieces needed… https://t.co/X0QuyXnwGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late last year, I moved—with my wife Beth and our three kids—back to Wisconsin. Friends will attest that I've been… https://t.co/MAueP9aq8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t see myself dancing for no hood niggas I know 🤷🏾‍♀️ unless I get a flat fee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best was santino jbs couple days ago I’m at 23rd shaking the boys hands he comes up to me we do hug me brotha Deek… https://t.co/QaMVgQgbq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll have the Play by Play Broadcast with a pregame starting around 6:50pm, for Game 5 of the West Division Semi Fi… https://t.co/N513NxXMXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was just told by a Southwest agent at a gate in Phoenix that @SouthwestAir doesn’t allow military members to boar… https://t.co/DrbYNZLlBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[broken clouds -&gt; overcast clouds temperature down 54°F -&gt; 47°F humidity up 54% -&gt; 93% wind 11mph -&gt; 2mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brad_Cummings Totally. Two TV stations now seem to be on the same staged attack narrative]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mar. 5th, 2019 Day 2988: 30 min LISS Cardio with Shoulder Work with My Brother and Mentor Sagi 👊🏼💚💪🏼 • • • • •… https://t.co/OiMb5P3mWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very cool little museum of Neon Art in Glendale California. They let me in for free for being a retired first respo… https://t.co/ew7HkuCQHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been extremely disappointed and sad before but today is one that goes to the top of the list of disappointments...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have substantially enjoyed video games more since I stopped sweating OW.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Send- Jeremy Riddle &amp; Steffany Gretzinger Worship Session https://t.co/YgE6aFoq2f via @YouTube  You’re welcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boom - Drinking a Deth's Tar by @revbrewchicago at @libertinebrew  — https://t.co/a5KfySVwUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dodgers Fans “YOU NEED HARPER TO WIN!”  Huh...Boston won with Mookie setting a WS record for at bats without a hit,… https://t.co/zVyF0Q1eME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really fucking good at watching tv shows half way through and then not paying attention]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulianCastro is the candidate for the future. He’s bold and laser focused .... 👇🏽👇🏽👇🏽 #Julián2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never give up!  When things get hard or don’t turn out exactly as you plan, keep going.  That’s when magic happens!… https://t.co/rgNDeo6C4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgaNagrodzka @zatontadeusz Zostal odznaczony przez Aleksandra Kwasniewskiego Krzyzem Odrodzenia Polski.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antoniopbfm30 @bjryan3 @Gary_PBF @PBFmedia @Krod013 @joeantesberger1 How Do With Nothing But Respect For All ... https://t.co/1xC38TNH4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBM929   You can't make chicken salad out of chicken $%&amp;@!. That's what the braves are trying to do with these "coward ball" tactics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was around seven years old, everyone in my Cub Scout troop brought in their hobbies to show off at one of ou… https://t.co/d1pRDHvyzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbon90 If I didn’t think it was funny I wouldn’t have posted it but doesn’t mean it didn’t slice me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattlewis92_ Nice nice I see someone played with it on a Calendar library 😎]]></document></documents></author>