<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@aerin_leigh I ORDERED IT A MONTH AGO TODAY I DONT KNOW WHAT THE FUCK YOU WANT FROM ME THERE IS NOTHING MORE I CAN DO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gang is all here after a great show for the @fdny in honor of #blackhistorymonth . Supporting of #firedept https://t.co/Ir398Pce8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeBatardShow @Stugotz790 @roybelly Oh God I thought Sedano with his Lebron hate was gone far away. Now you brought… https://t.co/K4M8JUVyyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr You mean this hammer?  @TheDemocrats https://t.co/rEjllK54w6]]></document><document><![CDATA[📸 @sarasaldivar  . had a blast at the niterinse x tons_and_tons anniversary 🔊 . let’s keep the party going this Tue… https://t.co/nuYS72sHgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandanicol3 Yeah think that’s why I can’t stand to see her now. Disappointed and shameful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gave this mug a #GrowthMindset upgrade.  Everything tastes sweeter now. https://t.co/fuyAnWORYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Have you not known? Have you not heard? The Lord is the everlasting God, the Creator of the ends of the earth. He… https://t.co/0iSelAKGvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonnieHSHOW @610SportsKC @cdotharrison @bradfanningshow Ford can’t effectively play against the run in their new s… https://t.co/qhzK1KyFQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[She looked up to the heavens sometimes when we were talking and tell me bout all her dreams]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MahgdalenRose I don't know but the fiber has some wear and tear in it... we have everyone from Faith Goldy to Ben… https://t.co/J7DC0YpoRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solange releases 33-minute visual for her album When I Get Home  https://t.co/FJwZGyl0F6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettPayne23 @bucknut27 😂 after seeing the deal Harper just signed I would’ve called the A’s and said I made a mistake!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Montz El Elvis Presley de la salsa, una seda de voz y un repertorio de los mejores dificil encontrar una cancion mala d Frankie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbeveridge13 @_nolan_grose_ @MorganTepe Some lukewarm water, that’s ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods No she isn’t. Just another liberal idiot who shoots one weapon and is the master of them all. Then… https://t.co/ohRxbat39m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback with La Cueva XC to State Meet in 2011 at Rio Rancho HS https://t.co/edTPAEIKUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMichaelLBrown DR BROWN PLEASE PLEASE TOUCH ON THE RIDICULOUS CLAIM THAT WE ARE BECAUSE OF EVOLUTION. I look at m… https://t.co/Yx8wrbnBVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drew yet another legend in the sport! Tomorrow is going to be really cool! Thx @FLWFishing for an awesome MARSHAL p… https://t.co/1hpSZSy2e4]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I can quote a movie I’ve seen one time, years ago but can’t remember the lyrics to a song I’ve bumped every other day is beyond me]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Love 4 Music 2 is out on all streaming platforms  spotify  @tidalhifi  @applemusic  @itunesmusic  @soundhound d… https://t.co/J8SV2VeHQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinwatson @RitterChris @TedRay80 @chad_bowen Kevin didn’t ask me, but I’ll take a stab since I’ve grown to suppo… https://t.co/X4zMNZREi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChairoMexicano @FelipeCalderon Toma tu vino chairo hediondo... te lo dice la Zopilota primera caracoles de México!! https://t.co/PBpP1iosEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pptsapper X-Wing may be the dominant platform of choice but the Y-Wing is the dominant platform of no choice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreakNastyBttm @bondagepupslave @phatrabbitkill2 i sucked both of them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sebastian Aho (CAR) will go to the box after committing a slashing penalty.  This will be the third #Avs power play… https://t.co/EkAuYvzeZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Día sabrosón con conectándonos con la naturaleza montanas_nuevoleon cerrodelasillamty  #elpinal #chipinque… https://t.co/IBY2QoiB0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tbollers Led the B1G in fumble recoveries last year, had 9.5 TFLs as a rotational player. He's got big-time upside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKarem @realDonaldTrump He respects nothing but power, control , his lying and cheating demon family and cerem… https://t.co/xjmHg7f7wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabbSports @echavez000 @ProFootballTalk Except Carr is Gruden’s guy. Reggie didn’t want Carr, Gruden told Mark to… https://t.co/5WZBbD4hvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to reports from #SkiLiftPitch w/ @goABQid @TaosSkiValley today! #ElevateYourPitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrassleRap @emiliosparks the crowd at Full Sail that saw Black v Roddy and Dream take the strap of Johnny Wrestlin… https://t.co/9QcAzo1MT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pomeroyfire11 @LanceMcAlister Witten was so bad.  Anybody will be an improvement.  I won’t miss him saying “Rodger… https://t.co/iN12KAOejV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rex_N @Steven_Swinford @Martinglasses Lily livered or realistically apprehensive?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsyakafluss @LauraBenanti You think you know how theatre and kindness work, @mrsyakafluss, but you don’t.… https://t.co/oPvpjjNUxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lafresa_zoe El mío es grande para que dure caliente todo el día !! https://t.co/koRCxh0cml]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Margarita Day! @ Tres Hombres Chico https://t.co/ih9Crh3iWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lawler: "I hit him with good shots, beat him up pretty good, slam was pretty good ... landed the elbow, cut him up… https://t.co/z7OESCCBWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillianmele I slipped on ice last week when I stepped off the curb by my car. It was so slippery I couldn’t get up… https://t.co/Potuge3DCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it only Tuesday?  We're already thinking about the weekend! Check out our Weekend Getaway Package and in just a… https://t.co/c129mujSJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RossGraham555 @brucegreene Do YoU wAnT lIcOrIcE? oR nIgHtMaRes?! https://t.co/Fb0kkArLK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already host @EmpireStateRide @RideForRoswell @TourDeCureBuff. Adopted #CompleteStreets policy &amp; working on… https://t.co/vCGkqa4bBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hittin this jacuzzi at LA Fitness before my OTAs with @gcfirefootball today, gotta keep these legs right! 🔥🏈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icehockeystick That’s the hardest lesson I had to learn when it comes to equality: LISTEN TO WHAT OTHERS HAVE TO S… https://t.co/hg7pvgkQMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bucketashit @RepLanceGooden Good idea! Your google must be broken.. https://t.co/ytwaBpZHZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a queer, Latinx millenial. I believe: • #BlackLivesMatter • healthcare = human right • in affordable housing •… https://t.co/aT2ItuZdRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indiana (STEM)State Champions were crowned at Vex Robotics Championship on Saturday. Inspiring to see and talk to t… https://t.co/XY1VzvaQnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn Nope. You over estimate your own intelligence, and you know damn well the level of intelligence of thos… https://t.co/gHPSq2Vm5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogerrTht Fasho. I should probably write what im thinking then come back to it sober.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carliiiflower @zobozebra @chrissyteigen So when it gnaws on its 4ft by 4ft cage then what? At what point is enough, enough?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just found the shirt that a manager gave me during one of my stints at temp work. Well looks like I'm going to volu… https://t.co/szZTdmQ4Yy]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are all here to celebrate one of the best to ever do it... And yes my shirt says ricflairnatureboy has 10 more c… https://t.co/j6PSneEIhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vitowitdagang x Heartbreaker   https://t.co/YcmlvooZv5 @ Rochester, New York https://t.co/LHGfB8MdnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericaPatriot4 @TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch BOTH. The liar is not going to lie about something he k… https://t.co/443p10C8lW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJ_Miles @geerawrdohh You can’t be talking about Post Carter II, Dedication 2 &amp; Da Drought 3 - Weezy F. https://t.co/jSFHFVMziz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @brendenolson18 on his commitment to @MavHockey. Well earned buddy! #TW https://t.co/UruXHcScW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tu as entièrement raison encore les revirements qui nous font mal @CanadiensMTL @919sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just learned thermogenic plants are kind of thing wtf my biology degree is completely out of date now]]></document><document><![CDATA[This mysogynist piece of shit. Unbelievable. #boycottfranktieri https://t.co/2JvUpfk3hZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BNphotographers @SharonCantillon @TheBuffaloNews Looks like a screenshot from a Tim Burton film]]></document><document><![CDATA[So abortion is murder and now murder is abortion. The circle is complete.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blink155pod Holy shit. That fanfic part is the most insane thing I have ever heard. Who wrote that, and worse, wha… https://t.co/lp7TPporOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonStehle @TOWarrenton @CityofFairfaxVA @FoodNetwork @Virginia_League We aren’t #scared here in the @TOWarrenton,… https://t.co/9uzax2rASV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@honey_dulce @PuestoLoco @MarkWarner Once again, Your watching to much Fox news. Your tweets are inaccurate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today has just been taking little but consistent shits on me so I’m just going to go to bed before anything else ca… https://t.co/AJqeBVjRND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskAQueerChick Clip ons are your friend. Added bonus: dramatically removing one earring in order to speak on the t… https://t.co/JNfqgrmAMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @NBCOUT She shouldn’t be in leadership role at a university if her views align with 1st century not 21st! #myopic]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was never about anything but the benjamins.  Report: NFL Paid Kaepernick $60 to $80 Million in Collusion Settlem… https://t.co/jqmKaxgSnq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EaglesInsider @Eagles Andy Reid thought “greasy” implied Arby’s #wegotthemeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0weddy @starrymlm "We don't have a clown statue, that must be my mother coming over to see the kids"]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sun came out to shine over Foley Field for a Wednesday game between two in-state teams, Georgia and Kennesaw St… https://t.co/jpC0vhxzLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are literally kids in some of my classes who just turned 19 and im gonna be 22 this year holy shit we got old fast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prefiero ver morir a mi gente en una guerra civil que ver como nos dejamos matar por estos bandidos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cody Stamann d. Alejandro Perez via unanimous decision (29-28, 29-28, 30-27)  #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adel-Thank you for bringing a Customer Focussed Attitude every day! I appreciate you snatching a customer away from… https://t.co/BnK0ILiFuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonPresley Blue background might work if all words were i white.  Red writing for position makes logo too busy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember this day, when @realDonaldTrump and Senator Wuss @senatemajldr paved the way to declare nat’l emergencies… https://t.co/1voidDlIos]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sooo disrespectful to hang up on people 🤦🏾‍♂️ you can be upset and courteous at the same time...especially whe… https://t.co/ZtQlf0H3aG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Automotive_News We are sold out!! Fantastic vehicle that has bright people into our showrooms.  I admit, I was a skeptic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charless_94 @DLineVids @juliuspeppers_ Nice.  But stop throwing the goat around just because it’s an emoji.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Tuesday. Which means 1 days closer to seeing God on Friday @ericprydz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turn him loose Huggs!! @JordanMcCabe5 playing with no rear view mirrors...]]></document><document><![CDATA[New high score on the Waze application for iPhone and Android device s https://t.co/8ameMPYKDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win or loose, we always support the boys @DetroitRedWings https://t.co/5LdJ2dhTrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome video. The last movie I teared up during was Shoplifters but there was quite a few movies this year that di… https://t.co/AHgXvxSsZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zach_goodall Exactly what I was thinking like did he want out of Jacksonville that bad he took that cheap of a deal]]></document><document><![CDATA[The memories... I remember waking up on my birthday at 5:30 A.M. to watch the opening game, Mexico vs South Africa.… https://t.co/ur8oYMmzDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clara_Bella_ Al final los mexicanos despertaron, no lograron asustarlos con Mexizuela..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still havent gone out during the weekend and it's been like two months since I have lol how do you meet friends as an adult?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrinKerr Not to mention, again, that the president had repeatedly and publicly stated that he couldn’t use his aut… https://t.co/JdiVVz835N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @Arauz2012 @realDonaldTrump It did ! It really did die after the few greats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @NVHumaneSociety @FieldHaven @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @EMluvsPibbles @msmorgan1968… https://t.co/TCYobTg9yJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mhoni Siempre Brilla Junto A Estos Grandes Conductores Hoy Mhoni Nos Tiene Nuevas #Predicciones 🔮👈🏼 #HoyconMhoni… https://t.co/4TaCSmx1M6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnn so @JussieSmollett lied!  I thought he was lying!  No one is going to believe anyone because of this fraud!  #LockHimUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaraGay At least you know you’ll never have to run into him at Junior’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are all so excited to worship together with Mt Olive Baptist church this Sunday night! If you are able to please… https://t.co/0TMqjqsL9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Annuals Lost Their Appeal https://t.co/0wimgdmw9X #plants @WstLondonGarden @SIGardens @GardenMuseumLDN @GdnsIllustrated]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 days or so before we get to go pick up this little guy. ❤️ https://t.co/zsmJKVa8IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebeccagrants @UNC_Basketball @DukeMBB Hate to see a player like Zion go down like that. That dictated the course of the game. #LetsGoCuse]]></document><document><![CDATA[People 👏🏼 who 👏🏼 make👏🏼 calls 👏🏼 on 👏🏼 speakerphone 👏🏼 on 👏🏼 public 👏🏼 transit 👏🏼 are 👏🏼 the 👏🏼 fucking 👏🏼 WORRRRRRRRRRST]]></document></documents></author>