<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Alright, Jared Cunningham did the best Axl Rose I’ve ever seen. There, now I feel better and thank you for your time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colin_dunlap Just have a glass of your world famous hawt takes..... should clear ya right up]]></document><document><![CDATA[The captain!! @SdLandon to @KraigChiles to make it 7-2 Sockers! #TheSockersAreAwesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sickness Log: Fever broke, sleep sporadic, voice continues to be unintentional Tone Loc impression.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOUSE ROOM RENTAL NEAR DOWNTOWN DETROIT 323-673-0606 $450 MONTH Detroitglobalnetwork@gmail.com DAVE SENT YOU.  NO C… https://t.co/h1VJ9Qah1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aegoxn @kylieminogue Creo que los sencillos que salieron no fueron los correctos, yo hubiera elegido #MillionMiles… https://t.co/FomTdeYgMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dog is wearing me out. Like girl do you have to bark at everything. Like the wind ain’t done shit to you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Catholic Academy Of Waterbury - @bsswaterbury in Waterbury, CT https://t.co/LTZIewRF5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[True love showed me who I was in the end. And she could never think what we had was true love. EVER. and I genuinely accept that fact.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@songbirdocarina @Roxyrockstv I like the fairy ocarina because it breaks from the norm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CryinHayward @LAKings Toews and Kane are leading by example. Doughty is close to leading the league in +/- with a -23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_RudyLara_ @PrichardShow Accurate, I would think that was all worked out in negotiations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Superhog32 @RushJohnNabors Don’t know. This Russellville native hopes so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeffrey Toobin: Roger Stone is 'playing with fire' https://t.co/K67m1lvsI8 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning, Baptist deacons all over the nation are scrambling to make sure the clocks on the back walls of their… https://t.co/PQBZeIAlnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ford F-150 might see a legitimate challenge in the near future, if they neglect to prepare adequately for the arriv… https://t.co/WE7Rqgmb9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am jealous of @MrJacobCohen.  He doesn't have to listen to annoying Florida Wrestling 'fan' tonight while enjoying time with his wife.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beingkarmin @THEREALCOLDCASH @Mrs_Roadrunner @RoaMarta2 @DivaSalewski @MARTINISUNSET @OBPantah @inthecutwjay… https://t.co/7dxpWDtn3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[A champagne toast and private tour of architectural treasure,  theperrybelmonthouse to celebrate our 7 year anniver… https://t.co/SSgvR8vY74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boogiecousins and the Warriors with the W in Charlotte. https://t.co/lnM1vWXsdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad I can stream @ShreddandRagan on @1033TheEdge on my way to work. I cannot stand listening to @woodyandwilcox anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoo no lie I love the way @ChadHorton always looks out for the genre and those who love the Lord... Thanks bro 🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachchumphrey Nice! There are a few options to go on this board, like the sleepers they have further down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTLA Remember that National Guard clawback, Newslumb?   We hear the Colorado Supermax has earned the reputation as the new "Alcatraz"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MickiMaynard @GM Part of the "for whatever reason" are incentives created in the Trump/GOP tax bill rewarding comp… https://t.co/5TmDS3ane2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up thinking of that absolute hammer Gomes threw last night and am doing parkour around my hotel room. https://t.co/Pa42e7z20i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders supports a women's right to choose except for the women who were sexually harassed on his campaign a… https://t.co/Noh3GogvGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to be lost yesterday was the performance of @prosperhoops, which was a quarter away from heading to #UILState.… https://t.co/ZQYswaLzYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#occupytheneedact #NeedAct to end #sadness #despair #depression #suicide. #theNeedAct end the present #systems the… https://t.co/wzFFGSRPRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean I haven’t seen it yet and I know old white guys run everything but that’s a terrible ratio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real talk though, do you think Rude Girl Carol is still a mini skirt girl or nah?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamiejbruno @JWN16 Can't believe you are entering your 5th decade...catching up to James and I #Yankees]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take it easy baby, make it last all night (last all night) https://t.co/SavBp99T2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[After almost six months of training I officially graduated from Air Force tech school this week at DINFOS and earne… https://t.co/D2RiMrZuXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes automatic doors don’t open for me and it really makes me question my existence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_real_dgraz Harpers a bum and i hope he plays like it all season long]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juan 16,33  «Estas cosas os he hablado para que en mí tengáis paz. En el mundo tenéis tribulación; pero confiad, yo he vencido al mundo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwall006 @samhillegas99 @julian_chlebove @PAPowerWrestle @PA_wrestling @FloWrestling No, they will separate them.… https://t.co/rcWWrpekqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HOLLYandherEGO Shiiiiiiid I’m trying to get my girl to make me a stay home husband]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump thanks Kent Brockman but you are not a news station dude. we have those already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life has never been the same after I discovered that one of my ears is higher on my head than the other]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRather That bump was using the prime time state of the union appealing to his minions saying all the things the… https://t.co/937jRUMaXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cpholt52 Most troubling.  Greetings from FL by the way.   Signed, a trivia partner]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leander ISD is hiring in #Leander, TX! Click the link in our bio to apply: Substitute - Clinic RN Only #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[How long will Americans put up with this atrocious behavior by politicians that are bought and paid for to sell out… https://t.co/hv0WMrOd0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abdavis @2020Hindsight3 @hawkeyenation @darrenrovell I was speaking of the $500mil being 10% of net worth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[philly loves you forever BDN. we’re forever grateful❤️🦅 https://t.co/qM0uR0N7gT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve said this once and I’ll say it again... @JimCase26 @JSUEvanBush and @murphree_mike run a First Class Program a… https://t.co/X8Dgx7S1Fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noelleacoss Let’s hit the cantina sometime soon for lunch👍 only 2 blocks away]]></document><document><![CDATA[5. The origins of reinforcement learning were in the 50s, mainly, eg. Selfridge’s Pandemonium architecture. (Don’t… https://t.co/ZSzM4n2VMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was by far the most boring Xfinity race I have ever watched at @DISupdates and so far from what I’ve seen on t… https://t.co/k9QZqO80FK]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had to pause the game to get myself to stop breaking into tears and process this entire thing so now it's 4 am an… https://t.co/5BUwe6n3C0]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are still looking for a team  https://t.co/4L3iPBcsaB Here is the available roster to be picked up. https://t.co/zxDmEqv6lF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN you ungrateful B*** your family escaped from tyranny and a refugee camp and ended up in the United states… https://t.co/CG1mDDqauD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobmurphycbc @CBCMaritimeNoon We need to start treating transit like other public services. Why does it get treated differently?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Guess you never read our constitution, or listened to the national anthem, or our pledge of allegiance. If… https://t.co/DA7ZXqfvdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @MBurgosNews @LaurenRozyla @AmandaVega @TheMilldtsp2016 @TBBJJanelle @CarissaKranz @sbelsole @WTSPJenny… https://t.co/zSWJzGsdH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillianMichaels I don’t mind if you don’t like CrossFit. Not everyone does. But it is irresponsible of you to spea… https://t.co/tVM9Sg1aEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big win in a stadium we have had issues in over the years. What a win. Phenomenal performance. #FCBayern #MiaSanMia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBaker129 @TheRealMassaro lol your attempt to belittle my intelligence isn’t gonna work bud. White people with… https://t.co/hAwUOqaIrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrannyJoanna @IloveShemale44 @PassiValerio @EliteTSCams @Tgirlfan69 @SissyNetwork @FistFuck73 I would like to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b_surp You never see this with @cchsloslocos. When titles are as normal as a sunrise/sunset, you eventually learn… https://t.co/XoBgStKaoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compelling footnote to the narrative around Bitcoin's transaction volume surpassing PayPal's.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cats_meow100 @SaintRPh OK. But I'm unclear about what else to offer to someone for whom facts = "a totally bs excuse".]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tears of joy roll down the cheeks of #Benson junior Bria Dixon as time runs down on the Techster’s 66-42 win agains… https://t.co/0LsjbcnBf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came home and fell straight asleep.  Now I'm up looking stupid...   And Horny....]]></document><document><![CDATA[My opinion and every other HS Hoops coach in OK about the weather #OKPreps @PGHOklahoma https://t.co/cO6WQvc2LJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7Brandi @ABC7 Have these people contacted the German government and ascertain the fatality on thier autobahns?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ya_boy_moondog @ZachJones_ 1800 is a ritual for us at this point, we have a checklist to know if a song is going t… https://t.co/WiIzwhvAA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flying into #tuesday like a jet fighter! . . . . . . reesecycles65 📷✌🏼 #ibikekern #zag1 #activelifestyle… https://t.co/obuIXZIlM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@columbo12man @joelpollak I was just thinking the same thing. The photo just seems off. Can't put my finger on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I, for one, am amazed to hear from Gary about this little known ‘grass’ that covers America.  I guess I must be an… https://t.co/bNzjg5fTHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IBJIYONGI And despite this, she’s doing a pretty good job herself, and with allies calling out the bullshit. #Strong #Confident]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kelly_Gretchen How about we go to Florida instead??!!  #GoOss #Oriolesmagic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joaniesagriff @jeff_downie Love the courage and passion to compete part too...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se acerca. Para muchos la botella es el verdadero amor. en Sherbrooke, Quebec https://t.co/WshG2aD10F]]></document><document><![CDATA[When churros be popping! Check out these awesome Oreo Monster and Rainbow Signature Loops from pop_churros . ▪︎… https://t.co/UOYfk2rBD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few deadlift videos from last week. 495 lbs in the 1st vid, 475 in the 2nd, and 455 in the last one. https://t.co/GrQgQQAGRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you were going to create a man cave, what’s the first item you’d get for it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cormorán orejón (Phalacrocorax auritus). Area Protegida  Balandra, La Paz, Baja California Sur, México  #mexico… https://t.co/4pL62QKRk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you know the value of a Father in a child's life, then you know we can no longer ignore Fatherlessness!… https://t.co/lhpA0hmOAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The only wall uv built is between u and the American people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Strnglss There's only one Celtic symbol that I recognize. https://t.co/7Pt3uHeulr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScarletEnvyNYC @RuPaulsDragRace @RuPaul @helloross @michellevisage @VH1 @OddlyYvie 😱😎🤓 https://t.co/5Tj2Slqem5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iVexful @SuperStarRayy @TheHoopCentral The Lakers would of been just fine of injuries didnt take over. Lonzo was p… https://t.co/K8K9m0VcHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alsboringtweets Moose looks like he ate the Chrysler building he’s got to be 300 pounds]]></document><document><![CDATA[The New Group Gala honoring Edie Falco @ Tribeca Rooftop https://t.co/t0HckpC3il]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory Trumph deserves the same treatment any ordinary citizen would get for al the charges to be filed includin… https://t.co/lxOUM57KuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[BTW, Jeff Sessions was one of Trump’s most loyal supporters, and this is how he treats him. Not just with this twee… https://t.co/sjdUubPl4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Romans58 @mightyones1968 @BreitbartNews I think this man needs a sedative and a long dirt nap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Visa estimates a 100 million pieces of plastic contactless in the US this year... So much good information on… https://t.co/hFB5Dn73ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom thumb was out of @naturallight. It was absolute garage and I had to buy Miller lite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldmctNFL are there any players the chiefs could trade for or trade away this off season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wbpictures quick question,  who would win in a race? Speedy Gonzalez or the Roadrunner?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 93rd Birthday grandpa! We love you, miss you and think about you everyday ❤️ #march8birthdays @ Mount Olivet,… https://t.co/lBKhQvxla2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having fun celebrating.  dashonda_w birthday @ Rainforest Cafe https://t.co/PXq74gNZT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yelmelnobrainer @xitoliv i remember when those were up on bgg a few years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRNRHazelwood @HirschyDave @jhbedingfield @WillardFlashes @ToddLillo @MockFred @NReflector @RegisterSports… https://t.co/edncinRHlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittlestar @AmandaLang @CTVNews @BNNBloomberg @RichardCrouse @bdthomson Me watching you watching @CTVNews… https://t.co/ZaCDSJwRAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJansen_PHHS @LRamirez_MHS @roboaztech @JShindo_SHS @liturriaga_HMS Great job all.  Hard work and dedication pays off. #TeamSISD #SISD_CTE]]></document></documents></author>