<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[time for some more r&amp;r @ the ocean at Cherry Grove Beach https://t.co/3GOpalmunG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe in if you really want someone you will make it work no matter the situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeerJeet You're adding Lovecraft in now? Yup, this thread is definitely about Code Name: S.T.E.A.M. now. Nintendo/… https://t.co/p1bcQnEmgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @STARZ is trying to shake up the game this year. I'm loving this premiere. @americangodsus is definitely somethi… https://t.co/YhL2XBY4Wp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch (@ Moe's Southwest Grill - @moes_hq in Enfield, CT) https://t.co/uswhDgOCcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spiciest trash talk in the NBA this year? I’m going with Westbrook vs. Embiid. #ThatDeservesACrown]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chalk Islanders gonna get a million power plays while penguins get 0 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it will help my asthma, I'm down with this. California Grow Solar! #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #Solar$]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KampaignCelly Hand ball don’t literally mean the hand, from your shoulder down to your fingertips is considered ha… https://t.co/CgCFz1JFU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo. If you leave a Comp match in Overwatch for any reason at all in the middle of gameplay - yousa punk ass bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_oise @jacquesjazz44 Oui je vais en boire avec Shayne à la santé de @jacquesjazz44 pour souligner sa crémation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like the Kremlin is feeling pretty comfortable here in Washington these days. Maybe they’re just in town for… https://t.co/JjwKGwoUVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormyVNV @EnigmaNetxx @veterans_i @YouTube @Twitter I remember this picture. Love it just as much now as I did wh… https://t.co/8IsvSc1Ymr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianDMZ @greenbookmovie Yeah... but it was no SOLO: a Star Wars Story. https://t.co/K5mKjHj3ea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live look in at @CP3 running the Houston offense:  #Rockets⁠ ⁠#Raptors https://t.co/8CnL7Abn4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best chicken soup (@ Lourdes Mexican Food in Escondido, CA) https://t.co/Y6TWa158oe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@motilona @NTN24ve @jguaido ahora cuéntame lo que pasara mañana, cuando y por donde llega @jguaido a Venezuela? El… https://t.co/1BFa2Mh8vX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regular TV is not for the faint of heart. Waiting A WEEK between episodes??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsbgm @RevistaSemana @IvanDuque @CConstitucional Cállate #PetroCatrehijueputa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds like Tom Crean thinks the Gamecocks are the best thing since the Walton-era UCLA teams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go, apparently constitution of Pakistan protect rights of all minorities 😒🤫🤐  https://t.co/QQy41X27uy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like the @ottawabluesfest lineup will drop next week!  Who thinks we’ll see @thekillers in #Ottawa again?… https://t.co/ROyZM9PN2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Cassie!!! Hope things are well. Miss you lots... @clbristow99]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NumbersMuncher Is it just me that thinks the girl’s opening salvo is rude and sets the tone for the discussion?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird The Joint Chiefs of Staff declared Climate Change a national security threat years ago. U may find… https://t.co/GC9mzVSddV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi @IlhanMN is being attacked by the Democratic right wing just like they’re attacking @AOC, the… https://t.co/TEUMgLFwmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me- I judged soil one time In Arkansas and all I can say is that it’s messed UP down there   Kid from work- like cl… https://t.co/l8Xr5aOnqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom At least young people don't watch fox news ,so they're not brainwashed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there is a market for smith ceci and anderson... shouldn't he #Sens be all over it? I mean over rated or age wis… https://t.co/bY7wCjPEMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicholasFerroni @MakeThemMastrIt When you take it upon yourself to look for the paper jam and never realized there… https://t.co/9yB6906wbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WolfieSmiffed @kath2cats Sure ...hope you know the real answer to that statement, otherwise get in line for your 7… https://t.co/Tbh9uThHnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelGotti5 @tedlieu On the other isle they would like the American people to believe that there is so much bad go… https://t.co/G0a9jLwdFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettieRiot @Cptnrwrpnts Not sure if Twitter brings it out or if it’s the release valve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bita1372 @TG2TruthSeeker @gex_daniel @Sissy4Trump @Jetsta812 @Caliicoder3 @Cali_Tracii @lovebaldeagles… https://t.co/TzcCq9PkNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Props to @sophaller what a performance this week. You’ve put Mizzou Women’s b-ball on the map. Good luck in the NCAA’s!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southwestbsu is in NYC!  Excited to work with mnyba_ this week and help local churches and ministries further the… https://t.co/AwRco2qw5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pollak: ‘Legitimate Criticism’ of Israel is Democrats’ Phony Excuse for Ilhan Omar’s Antisemitism https://t.co/JmsHjmzy95]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Michigan #PureMichigan Join @circlethecrown #Band from MICHIGAN live on @RealCaveRadio radio show Thursday March 7… https://t.co/b1ldiOngge]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Happened to All the Black Farmers? | NBC Left Field https://t.co/yGxa1WoAbL via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bebummineiro @007_hemal @spectatorindex I had to Google that one to be sure it was accurate. Surprising. https://t.co/BP9W7et04n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #TorontoDay! Cannot believe it’s been nearly five years since I moved here and my eyes were opened to a whole… https://t.co/ILXzZ8UVZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all. @ChickfilA didn’t give me a heart shaped chicken biscuit today and everybody else I know of has gotten one..… https://t.co/bqoN0S4VEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@svdate @jeffmason1 @JonLemire Preview of coming attractions (I prefer "Midnight in Moscow" to "From Russia With Lo… https://t.co/iwCe3GwkRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi yes hello I officially need to visit Bar Harbor, Maine it is one of the most gorgeous places I’ve ever seen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Staff Tec… https://t.co/jNK0qn91jK]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦎Grow Thyself🌿 ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ The growth process has never tested me like this. I risked losing everything I’ve spent my… https://t.co/HmvAHxkSOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Shantel_Ro @lotettabhrb @IlhanMN I like your way with words!  Carry on Patriot! 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Sanofi team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/xabM4apcnL #BusinessMgmt #Denver, Colorado]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftAction I don’t watch, but only a Stalinist would want to silence her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Lunch by @mainebeerco at @BCs_BottleLodge — https://t.co/HLOJVdxYZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to say that my art is the best around and if you think other wise you’re wrong. https://t.co/5xVAjhtmoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 TDs, 0 ints, 2-0 today. Damn proud of my team‼️ ⚔️🔴⚫  #KnightRyderz @CoachDLombardi @Coach_Davis3 @MHS_Knights_FB… https://t.co/pAclKhWzxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the passion and heart this man has🧡 I’ll be ready to see this man lay it all on line and make a run for the Na… https://t.co/9dOwRQAITA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Impeach. Cohen. FBI. SDNY. Obstruction. Money laundering. Inauguration violations. Tax fraud. Slee… https://t.co/lkuIbQdL89]]></document><document><![CDATA[HBOs "curating excellence" vibe. that's an excellent snippet @BillSimmons . Loyalty in an era where that doesn't exist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poker Apocalypse. On an 8TJhh flop in level 3 of @BicycleCasino @wsop circuit main. I got allin with Q9dd vs top se… https://t.co/pASTEq94Gx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz Stop kissing Trumps #Ass you #SuckUp #BeAMan or does Trump have your #Wilanders in a jar?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristieC733 @CarmineZozzora @Braveheart_USA @BarackObama @realDonaldTrump @PressSec @DonaldJTrumpJr @EricTrump… https://t.co/fDSqyOeZSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[When obstacles arise, you change your direction to reach your goal; you do not change YOUR decision to get there..… https://t.co/xCmkeyle6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier GUYS have tits too...B.UT GALS have tits too  WHAT iS AN EGG Coeptis AN NUiT     A-----------L ask "… https://t.co/bnoGLIR1BC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaraniDuncan Classic LAZY AMERICAN doesn’t want to (checks notes) work until they die.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@troy_andrea @AllTimeEDM @EDMSofa @Edmism @AZRavers @PreciousPetts https://t.co/BUWbPi4Qid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Next Coast by @GooseIsland @ The Quays Pub — https://t.co/f3ot1X3nHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justinifcation I dont think it works like that but I could be wrong. Both plants operate totally different]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I know myself enough to know when I need to come home and calm myself down now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harden not feeling ref Scott Foster ‘shouldn’t officiate Rockets game anymore’ 🚀🤷🏾‍♂️🤷🏾‍♂️🤷🏾‍♂️ #LakeShow #Rockets… https://t.co/N2v2y9gOim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnYeasu @williamfinnegan @tedateconomy @ACapwill @DonaldJTrumpJr @MSNBC Post the CNN/MSNBC quotes, without parap… https://t.co/UAhdGeaCOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AliensAreProbablyThinking Smashing Pumpkins is the name of an anti Trump rally..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @PressGop @AOC Well said sir! Thank you for educating that poor and stupid woman!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Public safety training at @ThePavilionTMF @IrvingPD @IrvingPDChief @GrandPrairiePD @FBIDallas #activeshooterdrill https://t.co/6ldLaI93y6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile Maybe R. Kelly and Jussie Smollett should get the same lawyer]]></document><document><![CDATA[nightcappin’ (@ Rye - @ryesf in San Francisco, CA) https://t.co/nJTic49xZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it me or is the WiFi here horrible? (@ DLA Columbus Fitness Center - @dsccmwr in Columbus, OH) https://t.co/hPMmJ1hgXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrinaDeLaSuerte In high school I talked to people who worked with him and they said his personality off camera was… https://t.co/YwP4vCYiCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kindness can make sure a fantastic difference! Always be kind! ❤️This Father having trouble with cashier at Walmart… https://t.co/Vn3XPL9Vax]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Faux Power That Comes With a Video Camera in Your Pocket  https://t.co/WHa9BTKxxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[These bitches be nasty asf y’all niggas be tryna impress stick to one solid clean woman and good lookin to lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[The University of Charleston School of Pharmacy Presents Medication Adherence and Safety Radio Series Guest ​​Tyler… https://t.co/mqfneaxwqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ICYMI @EmmaVigeland has some #ThursdayThoughts about ousted #ny14 rep #JoeCrowley's #goldenparachute lobbying for… https://t.co/D4ruNHNDh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! cute! c… https://t.co/36YziV7DJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 It is about time we call the exterminator. https://t.co/9NVzwgmDbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willsommer Then I'd imagine the protesters will well shadow this band of fools.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hughhewitt I’m not even sure we disagree since you’re one of the people who contributed to my understanding of bias. Disclosure is a must.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to Orlando! Looking forward to hanging out with over 1,500 Kingdom Advisors! Excited to hear @bobgoff ! Will… https://t.co/QUwWimJT2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm getting more and more excited about my @DisneyParis_EN trip, but I'm just hoping I can have my birthday dinner at Walt's]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current lightning strikes, Virginia Beach, Virginia. https://t.co/nh8x9tiB9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hamonphilip @mzemek @protennisfan @enricomariariva @accent_tennis I honestly think history will look back on this… https://t.co/tbKRFpGrGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottburton Also, he entire live album at Carnegie Hall is pretty great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well Josh’s looks and body have yet to be proven relevant to a certain gender of this earth, so..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michigan and Notre Dame in the top 10 and Ohio state not even in it. The bias is real showing espn. Everyone hates… https://t.co/kQXlfATkuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPIEST OF BIRTHDAYS TO ONE OF MY CLOSEST FRIENDS I LOVE YOU PRIMIS TO THE MOON AND BACK AND BACK AGAIN I HOPE YOU… https://t.co/vL9xwryqiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Trump administration will have to prove in court why a national emergency is necessary to fund a border wall. T… https://t.co/aZ9BoHVgyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC Uncle Joe is part of the CROOKED HILLARY AND DEEP STATE ORCHESTRATED coup. He is covering up the paym… https://t.co/sFZKi4ZiSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matmenpodcast Kinda hoping he and Rusev are both off to better things soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steelgateaus @RepDebHaaland I lived in santa fe and testified in many committee hearings for years.  Anything belo… https://t.co/pfAOJcBd0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImagenTVMex @imagenYuri @YuririaSierra Y los reporteros chayotines como ahora el @PRI_Nacional dice que si, ustede… https://t.co/4w9304Cl5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamtheBullFAN @DustinFox37 Got married in August for $129 at the “Welcome to Las Vegas” sign]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @Caittt23 @KatyAndNews @CourtKhondabi @ebhowe5 @K_Westbeld33 @StaciaWSYX6 @elleduncanESPN @kateflaherty24… https://t.co/pSbD6mil9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[$3B off of $27B in estimated total money expected to come to NY because of HQ2 is not analogous to $300 off $25 piz… https://t.co/oaglRo7SY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy 14 de febrero día Nacional del #AMLOVE ¡Saludos desde Tijuana  B.C., Sr. Presidente @lopezobrador_!]]></document></documents></author>