<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Whatever that was that Meadows tried stunk to high heaven. Unfortunately he used another person to get to Cohen. In… https://t.co/nG39k0RXEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyRainbow @carmen_cusack @54Below Man I love Martin Short! Very cool,  you rule!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janasanchez @thomaskaine5 @BetoORourke @amyklobuchar I’ll vote BLUE, No Matter Who!!! 👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DyaneHarwood @wendyburn @BLawrence85 @BekaLombardo @WellMentally Happy to!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't found evidence of #paidoff found attorneys Were committing fraud while unsupervised by @wellsfargo #ohio… https://t.co/7A4Mob8g33]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaineDobieMom Thank you for RT! We’ve been waiting a whole year to proudly wear her Bully Valentine Bandanna! ❤️🌹❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hericium2018 @alpipkin Dont the muslims own ALL the countries around a small strip of land and they do not want Is… https://t.co/Yo4C93mo11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zeee #SpanishTownSerendipityShop is now open for business https://t.co/IgVdTFmlGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me psycho because sometimes i really just enjoy silence, like sitting alone observing and thinking with a clea… https://t.co/ykZt9WTkY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicsepulveda @bjcreigh Just to correct this a little: I believe that’s called “cheese food”. I believe it’s some weird vinyl though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobMajor4 @JStein_WaPo @damianpaletta @ericawerner He has absolutely no empathy for people that depend on these programs. So sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elijah Cummings just quoted Martin Luther King Jr.: "There is a time when silence becomes betrayal." Excellent way… https://t.co/Odxd3LFiFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wish people knew how I felt and what I’m truly going through but I don’t wish this on anyone. I don’t w… https://t.co/wOIjc4bOWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5CrazyHolts @bobstokes12 I’m so proud of the work you are doing, Alanna! Your love of Mathematics permeates the cl… https://t.co/vfxUvzYSws]]></document><document><![CDATA[We headed to the semi’s #wbb  Great team win. 70-68 in OT Bring on.   #MississippiState @ Cedar Hill, Texas https://t.co/nPAQz687xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LesleyKempson @andibeth012 Sparkle had a family for 12yrs. N they left her behind. Any grandparents out there who… https://t.co/xLcraiIItB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @JudicialWatch I’m sooo HAPPY‼️THANKS Tom, keep us posted‼️😘🙏🏻👍🏻 @POTUS @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/5ICHS5qVR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travistritt puts on a great show!  A wonderful night out. The real deal. 👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flickerofhoty @LilyElizabeth36 I hope you have a kick ass time!!! I'm sure it'll be fantastic. 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Glendale Technically the Valley? And Other Angeleno Thoughts now on Audible]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not rly been feelin myself today so catch me gettin a new piercing or sumn tmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Jitters Trump is the weakest, most sniveling coward President ever. He’s too afraid to stand up for an American… https://t.co/DLpKL48EYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewKanFilm @robertoblake @TubeBuddy @NickNimmin @owenvideo @DeeNimmin @derraleves @salmajafri @PhillyD I read t… https://t.co/VP1q13ccmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fun game I like to play is am I psychic or is the government just listening to my conversations again and giving… https://t.co/B0o16ZsJgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewKirell @smartdissent Twisted f*ck.  Was he an adult 10 years ago? If so, then it doesn't matter.  Douche can… https://t.co/6tjMSmBqLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My liver hurts. #MessyBoots @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/EVrxFo5rEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[HHS CTO, Ed Simcox, speaks about the importance and power of data in driving health outcomes at wrap up of… https://t.co/DK1IPnzOiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[5:30 am and currently getting ready to head to Sacramento to shoot some content with @Gennifer_Rose 😆 https://t.co/JR38WOkzHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaRealGrizzle Who would buy his dumb book, anyway??? Hillary, Comey, McCabe, no thanks, I’d rather read Fiction! More interesting!! 🤔😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it that I can stand up to a 6 ft middle aged man but I can’t stand up to a friend who treats me like shit😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeWhoWait1776WW @POTUS Hope they did. POTUS &amp; the good  guys are bringing them out again. Thank you so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Crooks12 @mirandadelopez @_aroyalove @_paolaa_m @randaroorooroo I LOVE YOU SO MUCH ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never a boring day out in the field... 🇨🇭🇺🇸 #68whiskey @ Fort Riley, Kansas https://t.co/NB24Ta9MC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I wish this state would just break off.” -@lindsfrances thoughts on Florida #iconic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women’s #leadership Initiative of @ULIPhiladelphia got the story from two of the women behind the Philly #amazon HQ… https://t.co/Sfpx4xiFxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I lost like 8 pounds since starting school and my mom asked me if I’m taking diet pills and my stepdad asked me who I’m buying crack from 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mario415 @LukieBoxing All lies!! Espinoza who told boxing Twitter Pac vs Broner wasn’t $74.95 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet Maybe if the Children were about 9 Years Old, this would be OK, but NOT AT 5 YEARS OLD.  👽👽👽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_Rice_HuHa @liquidsipher It's really good. I know you will get into it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luc_jac Thanks Luca! Keeping an eye on queen Mariana Alves for you! https://t.co/pf7ge3qSqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoGet_ThaMoney idk who has worse daddy issues you or these bitches out here ... that’s sad good think you’re not i… https://t.co/thyoLEh8ja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsMiido Straight up.  My parents don't get me. I can't wait to move out.  High school sucks.  Everyone so fake.… https://t.co/Qoi6ps3EMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a huge event for my career tomorrow so if anyone can teach me how to effectively market myself by tomorrow n… https://t.co/CkvEnFHXAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking outside the box - #watersupply #waterresources @KeithPerryFL @RepTedYoho @MyFDOT Paynes Prairie 'causeway'… https://t.co/LKstAT5pqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AyannaPressley @IlhanMN Which is not to say I think an official who lied to Congress for any reason should ev… https://t.co/5OVEP0nXwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caviar brings you the best restaurants. Sign up to get $10 off each of your next two @TryCaviar delivery orders in… https://t.co/d3EnSbLGtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This year has been a major eye opener so far and I see much more clearly than I ever have]]></document><document><![CDATA[all I used to do is get high and eat McChickens and candy and now I haven’t smoked in two months and my ass is growing so whatever]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Park Place Apartment Building in Seattle, WA https://t.co/WextkwdKgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ummm, trump values are not American values. The world knows you are a petty greedy treasonous family and your name… https://t.co/03218HEGHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching Kids to Regulate Emotions! #SEL #ilovemyjob @2ndStepProgram https://t.co/fHXGGJ7NH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to press play on the next episode of #TheBachelor on @hulu but I’m just sitting here feeling like I still ca… https://t.co/grIzUlC6G8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect day to enjoy a cup of hot cocoa and finish my baby registry 🥰🤰🏻#snowday #saturdayfun #mamatobe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aidan, really bro? 🐶 #dogoftheday #dogsofinstagram #instadogs #instadog #instagramdogs #instagramdog #pet #instapet… https://t.co/EIbr8u7uzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really just want people to know that if we’re collaborating and you drop out for any other reason other than your… https://t.co/iLwfORVZyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[So no one I fuck with fucks with their zodiac sign but seriously if you know my sign I’m the type that WANTS to go… https://t.co/3CPzl36C1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else has a really hard time getting rid of old notebooks? When you spend a whole quarter filling up the pages w… https://t.co/wsefcO0BKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LelandOrser I utterly adore you!!! Will be on pins and needles and putting some much positive energy into the univ… https://t.co/goBB5qot7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it funny when the people who used to make fun of me, compliment and try to hit on me now.. funny how that works..!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@welcomet0nature Good morning 🌞 sweetheart, 🥰 thank you beautiful!!! 💛 🌷 🌼]]></document><document><![CDATA[if anyone from ONU wants their taxes done FOR FREE, plz lemme know. I need clients for class. 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now is the time to get your dream home! #realestateagent #atlantarealestate #firsttimehomebuyer #realestate… https://t.co/wbwFodBUBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my favorite President, James K Polk, will not be there, I don’t care]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm currently obsessed with this album 😍 It's a press play for me! Can't wait to see @LilSkies live in EP😁🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Denver show is 20 tickets away from selling the fuck out.... https://t.co/azuQQmCN5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of y’all mean girls are bitter. At what idk. Y’all don’t know how to have fun without someone else being the… https://t.co/Cjwy2aXfnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband went to GW. This is the one game he watches with me every year. 🏀😳😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Total nullshit Rudely!  How much lower can you sink?  The Trump investigation is very much warranted.  You, on the… https://t.co/o31w1k1bKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[spongebob quotes | patrick spongebob Nickelodeon poem scene tv funny pics pictures pic ... https://t.co/gLJV3UbE27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stillgray @IonaItalia Yeah, its amazing how many people still believe in it. Very new age religiony.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSforALL @SIGCSE_TS Will be following. One day I hope to get to CSTA conference. #CS4All #satchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one excited about daylight savings time?  #springforward #readyforspring #running #runner… https://t.co/0hMcHbuo5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blow ye the trumpet in Zion, and sound an alarm in my holy mountain: let all the inhabitants of the land tremble: f… https://t.co/vM5jqUuAot]]></document><document><![CDATA[last night @JoshJhu gave me my birthday present a month early and I cried in his kitchen from happiness… https://t.co/iVF3fxTBmj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pancho_burquez_ Nada ha cambiado, solamente el balón (poder) pasó a manos de otro equipo, pero el manager sigue siendo el mismo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2:30 in the morning and I’m finally going to bed.  But the yearbook is done 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like waking up at 5am to go to the bathroom and finding a spider on the toilet paper roll.… https://t.co/mWbSx5tZur]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so high I shoulda stop smoking but I keep saying “one more hit then I’m done” like the last 13 times]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCAntlers THANK YOU FOR KEEPING MY KIDS SAFE WHO ATTEND DCHS!!!! LOVE OUR SCHOOL DISTRICT🦌🦌🦌🦌🦌🦌🦌]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need Adam to buy me some patio furniture so I can sit on my balcony with a good book and some coffee 🥰💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexHolleyFOX29 how about its so hard to say goodbye to yesterday...for Nick Foles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SVPolyAthletics @Parrotsbaseball Proud of Poly's Boys Basketball Team! #greatfun #greatgame 🙌 @artin_arhanian… https://t.co/yb159AO3kR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rodriquezpr In the context of health (insurance) policy it’s relatively unambiguous ;-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world is much less joyous without our own #YoshSchmenge. #JohnCandy lives!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think she needs money!!! Ha ha Love you Taylor! 💕 we appreciate it more than you know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@___Leliane___  #SHOWNU #ShownuBombardment #BiasBombardment #MONSTA_X #MONSTAX #MONSTAX_Alligator @OfficialMonstaX https://t.co/qhx6kR8txZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephen Marley #stephenmarley Love ❤️ 🇯🇲 @ Gas Monkey Live https://t.co/DFlAQP42Xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyBurridge I’m actually shocked at Paul’s statement. I would have never took him for a flip flopper. If anyone… https://t.co/yfmXl6KUnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would take down Jamie Lynn Spears solely bc I hated hearing “your name is jayme? Like Jamie Lynn Spears???”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence I think of you with every joke tweet I send to liberals. Please get well soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @Jacamina1 @realDonaldTrump @CPAC @DevinNunes @ByronYork Agreed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadGuyPlays @JeremyMartinCo3 @NianticHelp I totally agree. My schedule and location doesn't allow me to participate very often.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosepvssy my friend recommended me this place not too sure if its what u were looking for but they do a lot dealin… https://t.co/DxmGvzmRwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlakandBlack @lilith2u @Erambiboy He’s only believable by his 35% base.  If his mouth is moving he is lying.  He h… https://t.co/47Q3A6hwdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just found out the NASCAR race on Friday night starts at 7:30 and my life is ruined.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 18542 PERKINS RD #Prairieville #LA  #realestate https://t.co/5o26ImHZH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[comedy at it's best. HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!!!!!!  so creepy... I am literally laughing out loud at this I don't know w… https://t.co/Mg2zIFubKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CollaborativPGM - get involved with local communities by identifying local organizations. Yes, that means using y… https://t.co/diydgyg430]]></document><document><![CDATA[@its_pinkie @JessGrossman @EvaRedpath She’s always been a floozy that Sharon, can’t trust her with your man or your secrets!!! #YR]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are well over 100,000 students with special needs choosing AZ public schools. You champion these children whe… https://t.co/ZOUqzMXQDP]]></document></documents></author>