<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I finally saw a whole #johnbarrowman panel at #gallifreyone on Sunday. I didn’t get remotely close to the stage, bu… https://t.co/5vJQijptKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t tried oat milk yet. Milk technology is moving too fast and I’m being left behind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LPfamily @mikeshinoda @TalindaB @AnnaShinoda Love to All 💕💕💕💕💕💕 https://t.co/lC6RKPBaiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooking with Adam results in some of our most delicious dinners: Creamy Garlic Pasta with Roasted Tomatoes and Broc… https://t.co/erFTBJCYXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was at mamas rn, and there was really a cop behind the counter watching them flipping tortillas like “pinche madre you’re burning them 🔫”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Really? She is saying this because they know they have nothing to impeach him on! Trying to save fa… https://t.co/v6IOLKF1m1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO @suthernangel2 @LukePerryIII Sorry baby girl.... it hurts so bad to lose someone,  all we can thin… https://t.co/p75b9xGZ1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HotPockets4All I understand that you feel that way. I feel differently. That's all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudLibPat @alspro @TheTNHoller Exactly. As a sexual assault survivor control of my body has been forcibly taken.… https://t.co/QU36ehBdUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Atrium Health? We're hiring in #Concord, NC! Click for details: https://t.co/Kyoumnuyg1 #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JW_Branding @emmanuelobi476 @Carole77777 @hickoryhill8520 @radioshowccc @jlshine5 @karmalchambers @Tennyso73797371… https://t.co/a7JFL6h7Si]]></document><document><![CDATA[I brought my mom to Aldis for the first time and she don’t know how to act lol 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: @LisaKudrow looks better than ever. Also this is been my fav podcast episode yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CookingWithCarl @shitfoodblogger Guys poutine and champagne is a for sure deal before 11am]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that Riverdale played dance with the dead makes me so happy (s2ep16)  #dwtd #riverdale #primarycolors]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ermagerd!!! I never get tired of this view! 😍 Warm weather, right around the corner - can't wait 😊🌞🌊 #thatsocallife… https://t.co/kkaKIbaphr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PushkinPanther @PetsatHome This is an excellent look for Pushkin.  Very dapper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Blessed Wednesday Everyone!! @ Edgy Girl Fitness Studio https://t.co/uvwUPu17dw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michelina321 @DonnieWahlberg @NKOTB @LeenaTailor @Variety Hi 👋 You look very handsome with the scruff look… https://t.co/r6fH6bPagN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SyracuseCrunch Sec 103 Row FF Seat 9 #tullyspucks https://t.co/TPOUZHeRZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKarem @realDonaldTrump The press created him to a great extent and helped elect him. You were complicit. This is your reward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I consider myself a #BornAgainCatholic I was raised #Catholic when I was 23 my #Nana came to BR &amp; went to her… https://t.co/Ha5F2kaMbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary to this amazing and beautiful couple!! 🎉 @DeaSevilla @KevyWinz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob Evans Restaurant 2/2019 Love those little girls!! @ Hilliard, Ohio https://t.co/KP0uXz59IY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this on prime or Netflix?  I’m just so fascinated by it.  The church burning stuff was just so extreme.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachBroderCOC @YoungHaynes2 Ima screenshot this and post it when we back in the race]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espocampus we’re overdue for a new pic huh :/ anyway did someone say birthday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blending green stormwater infrastructure and placemaking https://t.co/0LWh3jAyJy via @wordpressdotcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eCapitol_Shawn See you there at 10am—but this time in the Blue Room. #construction Thankful for better than expect… https://t.co/A3dhMro9bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbeyDiaz_says @MenziesResearch @garvey_gail @Lisa_J_Whop Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thomas Goff, a veteran and former firefighter is now using the program available at Echo Shelter in Atascadero to g… https://t.co/gn3ylZOcRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffOFace @ms_ericav @FunnyVines She’s a comedian, this is her character, Carla. Still hilarious!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenanthompson @MaskedSingerFOX @kenjeong @NicoleScherzy @robinthicke You were hilarious on there! Glad you are on there next week 🙂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[After analyzing a @USDAgov map, researching current solutions provided by @RonFinleyHQ TedTalk, and discussing the… https://t.co/rKZjFPuxl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[When he brings you flowers and says that you are wonderful. 💜  Just knows how to make me happier https://t.co/Nwi5e6ZHcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did this but for a week straight... I got nothing caught up over spring break]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xEman87654x But he perjured himself, again, in this testimony!  Said he didn't seek a possible pardon from Trump,… https://t.co/nR5dtztHIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffMerkley Please! #Nielsen must be tried for #CrimesAgainstHumanity along w @JeffSessions]]></document><document><![CDATA[inability to overcome shortages of food and medicine. The aid is supposed to be moved into Venezuela on Feb. 23 by… https://t.co/Gn74EyJ8D9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awwww bless - Schultz really is trying to get Trump re-elected. #CentristMyAzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RIHouseGOP @Blake_Filippi Federal law ‘trumps’ state law, so, for example, when @PeterNeronha prosecuted Erik Joha… https://t.co/AzEDzJlktd]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you can release what’s in your hands then God can release what’s in His hands.” Man that’s so good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[👉Scholastic and college chess is growing every year. More kids play chess and more students either with scholarship… https://t.co/11TLa3FiDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[folks been telling Jordyn her father deserved to die? wow. y’all folks are hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse What do they have over u Trump? They don’t do anything because they r nice. @KarenMoscato #TrumpCrimeFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen of New York State,it is time to fight for your constitutional https://t.co/8FNuoqqcT0 you care… https://t.co/sqM6gmV95H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunkissed🌞☀️  #publicfigure #loveyourself #washingtonstate #model #sunny @ Tacoma Narrows Bridge (1940) https://t.co/C0nK2EgPn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just an example of one, but .... Roy Williams, the men’s basketball coach, will receive an average of $300,000 a ye… https://t.co/bqEiWLmFho]]></document><document><![CDATA[treats for your Wednesday morning, ℅ @tattebakery 🥐🍰🥖 @ Tatte Bakery &amp; Cafe https://t.co/FwTJfWIfal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cimorelliband @ChristinaCIM @KathCim @LisaCim @AmyCim @LaurenCimorelli @DaniCim I just wanted you guys to know how… https://t.co/2eHunPrlJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glampingin4th We love you! Love hearing Addi’s fun stories from your class!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjs1951 @sahilkapur We promised it at @emojination and it was shelved by the Unicode Emoji Subcommittee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell More importantly the public isn’t powerless -or clueless - anymore.  Time’s up on your teams lawlwssne… https://t.co/T8543mWeBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elisabethjlane It is a good book! We read it last month at 57th Street books with @JenReadsRomance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to buy a $30 of baby simba when the live action movie comes out]]></document><document><![CDATA[we all want some laughter. #mirth #tee-hee #grin #laughable https://t.co/HsCFzbfljr]]></document><document><![CDATA[the first dance at her wedding was to a thousand miles by vanessa carlton https://t.co/0lfybGWDnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Omg, this is really bad for the city, health reasons and safety. I'd be a shame]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such an honor! I am humbled by this recognition 🙏 @ike9_Eagles @AldineISD @drgoffney @tdavis_aldine]]></document><document><![CDATA[I put in work to get these A 1 choice USDA grade breast checked every year @ Kaiser Permanente Medical Center https://t.co/fNF8qtJQHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom changed my life forever when she introduced me to mini saltine crackers with peanut butter 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Insanely jealous of everyone working the Soulard Mardi Gras parade today. #hurricanesfordays]]></document><document><![CDATA[listening to @charli_xcx’s spotify playlist while waiting for @charli_xcx i am at my peak]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s your favorite strain of flower?❤️❤️❤️ #Quebec #laval #bud #budtenderlife @ Laval, Quebec https://t.co/uEsnXv4Gag]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which Jonas Brother you liked growing up says more about your personality than any Meyers Briggs test]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Waldorf, MD? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/yBW6J1wJH7 #Sales]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theglowingstars Omg that white truck nearly ran you over! I’m glad you’re okay.   Exhibit A on why ktown needs saf… https://t.co/YBh1WPJwh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bernieogorman1 Heheh.Our right wing arent much better. And I’ve heard our right wing have begun to “infest”… https://t.co/1ZVjEs0BJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Velvet Room Hookah Lounge https://t.co/aoZtOT1tFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TulsaMBB is 4-of-6 on 3s and 2-of-12 on 2s. Hurricane leading Memphis 19-16 midway through the first half.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews is propaganda   The Making of the Fox News White House https://t.co/ZGqCGzr43D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting to really hate being up so late at night. My mind races and I can’t sleep. Then I’m exhausted all day. 😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilShea09 @ludgecorrea @innavhaj @jordanreyessss Her best friend gave it to her. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT ✍️ Prime Minister Imran Khan : Kaavan has Secured Sanctuary at No cost to Pakistan - Sign the Petition!… https://t.co/uGV733V26I]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #WisconsinDells, WI! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: PT Flex Security Offi… https://t.co/JZpjD2C8Tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fashion Week runway  Beautiful Design :@camillewoodfashion  #runway #fashion #styles #gowns #classy #fashionstyle… https://t.co/IuLGd0vIpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HallieJackson what a useless statement “if you will” that you continually use. Seems a journalists would not want… https://t.co/7fT4JGRj8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElPocho @LaCasaAzul__ As if that matters. Plus she doesn’t. I saw her eat. Cuts damn pasta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appointments available this week.  616-206-3155 . . . #advancedclinicalmassage #pain #painmanagement #manualtherapy… https://t.co/M2klnD7sw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelagarland76 @Kissimmee RSVP is open https://t.co/QnBgFsjYrl #MyKissimmee]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left a candle burning in my house all day and all night and now I finally understand why my mom wouldn’t let me have candles 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrinceD_Rok130 I was so mad!!! 😂😂😂 I was like oh shit she got it on the radio!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo Thankful for my new position, I’m learning so many new things. #upsworldport was fascinating, the amount of pa… https://t.co/MZBKnBG0fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree..disgusting that the woman was placed in jail...but not the people that support killing our animals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t keep this secret anymore.   Every time I see “Oregon State” I definitely read Oregano State.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just had one of those “i wish i had a boyfriend” moments ew self hate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariecountryman @renemjclarke @lilith2u @bunkybun @riotwomennn @cliffpotts @Dennis_Lintz @haloefekti @KatG4… https://t.co/V79gqzZU3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[American style 🤩 . #livinginamerica #trinitytransportation #schoolbus #michigan #puremichigan #washanddry #medium… https://t.co/KKfMJ37YPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Portland! More delicious food, a lovely walk, fine company. @ Portland, Maine https://t.co/rWsjIVbo1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win a Trip For Two to Miami This Winter! @h2oWireless and @1035KTU want to send YOU to warm up this winter in Miami… https://t.co/MfczZ8QQE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachZihlman @taylorswift13 @CarrieZihlman I used to do the exact same thing! 💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobOldisTowel Port Charlotte,Florida. I'm guessing that a sizeable % of students are Black. And that the administr… https://t.co/TvFR04WBNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need a reason to #visitrichmond  —-&gt;&gt;&gt; @rbrexperience March 3-10 #rva #rbre19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lowe's is hiring in #IndianLand, SC! Click the link in our bio to apply: Receiver/Stocker #SupplyChain]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Message From Alex Trebek | JEOPARDY! https://t.co/BIuCP0WiQA via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Disorganised1 @Union_Jacky @doskey64 @jessix @LilyLilyMaynard And who decides what the appropriate use is? Oh righ… https://t.co/m9g13v1XWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so nervous about my final grade that I made Chris check for me, but it’s okay cause I got a 98!! #Anxiety #grades]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you need to see Tucker is just as big of an disgusting asshole now as he was a decade ago, here's your proof. He… https://t.co/XxHvJzaR2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff I don't know if you realize just how bad it is out here the Democrats out here... The country is out… https://t.co/CSI4fusHSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Stay strong; ask for protection if you think you need it. There are more of us than there are of them, and we… https://t.co/5VT1P4N3jV]]></document></documents></author>