<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I just need an oncall gym partner who can go with me, motivate me, and keep up with me at all times :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Except in this case it was unconstitutional because the VP wasn’t involved and their is no evidence to support his… https://t.co/AkXmj1yIk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we're just going to sit here and act like @pepsi didn't glorify the pedophile known as #michaeljackson not to lo… https://t.co/VcpUchzegs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wreck: delays heading out of selma in #WestSideOfSelma:JohnstonCounty on Hwy 70 @ the Neuse River Brg near Buffalo Rd #traffic]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 2019 “RussoOnTheRoad” https://t.co/0ESppsuXIh @vwmedford @alfulchino @ United States https://t.co/7qzJ5ZmnpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Podcast is out! W/ @Eric_Riley8 @Joeboone10 @collincc4 @dashing_drew1 @FlakeNick https://t.co/mIQ8UP532o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@browntailedhawk Meh, that's deceptive. Sure she lost Kent County but the Margin was still insanely better. It wasn… https://t.co/F024OzrdEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bradley81627698 @JimCarrey Yes he is. But he was granted US Citizenship 15 years ago. (October, 2004).]]></document><document><![CDATA[absurd adjective ab·​surd | \ əb-ˈsərd  , -ˈzərd   1 : ridiculously unreasonable, unsound, or incongruous  2 : havi… https://t.co/sG2UCoxfnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guilty part of the shedding of Jesus' blood was the cup that He alone drank to the dregs. He now and forever sh… https://t.co/1auEOvNhWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to tell someone how fucking stupid I think some people are. I’m so frustrated]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning I had breakfast with 4 princesses and a queen. https://t.co/qKYO6S7Fkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[No temptation has overtaken you except what is common to mankind. And God is faithful; he will no…… https://t.co/xWRiKK8IDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Southwest flight makes me feel like I’m in school hoping someone I like sits next to me. #Stressful #GameOfOpenSeating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucetVeritas @SuperEliteTexan This is number two for #Smollett. That should mean jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw the true pettiness of females and all I gotta say bros is y’all better think twice about being a fuck boy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 to 1 shoot out win for the ship shoutout to katillacc for making a sweet sign @ Schwan Super Rink https://t.co/TQyARrjdC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedCon1Official do you have an account that I can send a DM for a question about a product? Twitter is not letting me to this account.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @LeVeonBell, @RealSkipBayless has been talking negatively about the @Raiders and @AB84 so if you want to win th… https://t.co/jfRp9o2TcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__jush @SealTeamRiks I hate twitter cause I can’t read your tone thru my screen smh I feel you lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[#enough #snow #mnwx @ian_leonard @CodyMatzFox9 @KeithMarlerFox9 @McDermedKMBC @AlexLehnertFox9 @macemichaels @ Broo… https://t.co/0F443kGemP]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lil #snow falls and out goes the lights @PacificPower_OR welcome to the 21st Century @KVALnews @ThatOregonLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flipping over 🤸‍♀️ this focus group for upcoming PD in @SpringISD @TeachSpring]]></document><document><![CDATA[i WiLL LOVE THiS GODDESS FOREVERMORE  WiTH ALL MY HEART,  JONATHAN POPPY LÜX @JonathanTreylux barker3929… https://t.co/fQL3Nw3IFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UniNoticias @patriciajaniot No le hagan propaganda al progresista Jorge Ramos. Ese puto ha sido una piedra en el z… https://t.co/KFn7ll0V4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moonwalkertvmj esto es alarmante, no quiero ser agua fiestas, pero el documental a sido una bomba y una compañía c… https://t.co/oZrYZ70F55]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @realDonaldTrump you forgot pedophiles ... liars, crooks, thieves and pedophiles]]></document><document><![CDATA[China and Ethiopia have grounded their fleets of Boeing 737 Max 8 planes.  Shouldn’t every Air Carrier, after anoth… https://t.co/npXwFt0ZRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come to theuptowntheatre! We've got Captain Marvel (the toy, not the movie), and a bar! Look at all these empty gla… https://t.co/0YJ8MFnczk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when you think @BenSPLATT can’t give us any more feels with his vocals, he does this. So powerful. https://t.co/NVBNhdaRK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristinaLucciM Damn baby I guess at that peep of your nice beautiful ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthernEvents_ @ISpeak4Me_HBU @BhanLiz @thekaptainbee Spot on. The mass media is really fueling hate and anger. I… https://t.co/0vTCSDhjoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also I got every major category except actor wrong, and only won my party's Oscar pool because I killed it in the minor categories]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vlad Jr pulled something? Forreal? We gonna believe this? Somebody change the service time rules already so we don'… https://t.co/dehXVamWPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#notmytucson #arizona #snow #goaway #instatravel @ Tucson, Arizona https://t.co/mEq5HIxixA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MarALardass  #MarALardass  #MarALardass  #MarALardass  #MarALardass  😀😀😀😀😀😀😀😀😀😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the Jungle tonight. Go Komets! @ Fort Wayne Komets At The Allen County War Memorial Coliseum https://t.co/uP7rekC682]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 Spring Training: Day 3 Frames @ Tempe Diablo Stadium https://t.co/wAAr1EiAR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started from the bottom, then I got a shovel and dug myself so, so much further ❤️✌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarronSports @Pellomaldonado @lucas161984 Estoy contigo Pello.QEPD tu querido padre mis oraciones y mis condolenci… https://t.co/9zJ7XpRTW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Celebrator by Ayinger Privatbrauerei at @cloverleafinfo — https://t.co/sg6yoPuk9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PRINCE_OF_NY I hate that show.  Have never been a Carlin fan, Gray is awful and obnoxious. Bart is solid with NFL… https://t.co/Fj2uoWlST6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got all my settings pretty much solid with the test stream I did. Definitely going to do a real stream tomorrow alt… https://t.co/WgtXaBk4K8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is important for everyone’s #health nowadays, regardless if you’re losing weight or not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladyfox14 if they're not important, then it doesn't sound like it'd be a loss to you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking to Democrats in rural eastern New Mexico this weekend (yes there’s dems our here).  It’s time we started s… https://t.co/PyCRgdoQNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strawberrytofu You played along so well I am concerned wether I did you wrong LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanesCanes @TheWholeF_nShow @CutlerRidgeLAZ @Becky080711 @lockhart_jesse @HeavySmoke239 @SportyMama @kellycanes… https://t.co/HowaW0e5NE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Courtcantwin @HFoleyOnIce @freddie9583 @Mimi4Pres2020 Well the Latin part of me is sad but the fat ass part of me loves this idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@think_again_7 I don't see anything that is wrong with your link,..thanks for sharing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliciakeys https://t.co/8uzDkvIyJU  👔🧞‍♂️👊🏻🌿🧕🏻🦷🧙🏻‍♀️🙇🏻‍♂️💃🏻👩‍❤️‍👩👩‍👩‍👦‍👦👩‍👧🧕🏻😶👊🏻👩🏻‍🔬👄🤮👔🤘🏻🧙🏻‍♂️🖕🏻🦷🤫😀😃😄😀😃😀😃😀  🧒🏻🤓☺️… https://t.co/ZzuCe6SIhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pt I think we’re overthinking it. Congress should pass a law that gives them enhanced oversight over any company w… https://t.co/xG8eCu4psN]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK, I'm sorry, I can't do the notifications anymore. I swear, I'm liking them, And they pop right up again. Frankly… https://t.co/vDHK1qB1IG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMichaelKay check out your buddy @PaulONeillYES in @LBPRC ....many moons ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty sure if I were to not brush my hair out I’d have dreads by now]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just wrong. Alex Cejka is disqualified, the first victim of a new rule limiting scale of green-reading books https://t.co/oX37hRQU1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellievan65 @Sky_Lee_1 @shossy2 @TheUSASingers @kimmyifuplease @mommamia1217 @nickiknowsnada @lc1_summit… https://t.co/w4VbocuFSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[snicker for some stress relief. #humor #lol #grin #laughable https://t.co/8LZMM7QDf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nancy, Chuck and their buddies should be kicked out of office for not living up to the oath they took to defend the… https://t.co/KTOacZCwjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacyandkacy This is crazy. And it’s at that same Target you girls shop at too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Casen_Doss There are two options: Either the nails be poppin and she’s jealous or the nails grew out and it’s time… https://t.co/Xpms79qUVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gusta_Gusmao @TheLastFabeo @fuckinmadhatter @hollnald Gente, concentra só na bandeira q eu falei 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing an online concert tomor. to help raise funds to make 3rd album!Playin acoustically 6-6:42 p.m. CST at… https://t.co/GfJfs4j1Af]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier I'm glad I wasn't there cause I would have put that coward to sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu business interests in blind trusts and updated emoluments restrictions]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BORN DAY SIDNEY POITIER!!!! He was the First African American to receive an Academy Award for his Starring Ro… https://t.co/UaoomXw8Gj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#penoftheday #pelikan Go! #fountainpen @ Selma, North Carolina https://t.co/Zfj3zDFqKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LawDogStrikes I’m GM’ing a #TTFRPG campaign using a built from scratch world using some home rules over ICE’s Role… https://t.co/lB4XaRSlrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYounker @findhorror @PromoteHorror @QueenHalloweenW @bringbackfear @isaacrthorne @crashpalace @GothGirlVonDark… https://t.co/jyJI7iVR3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stock Buybacks Are on Track for Another Record Year. Corporate America is still in love with stock buybacks.  That… https://t.co/4P1J32j0TE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to #GetOnRed! Rooting for the @RenegadesBBL here from the States! @BBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My old boss at @nbcchicago @KatySmyser is talking about FOIA and showing her big "You Too" story...the public cost… https://t.co/VpqMueueYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@collegevill @EricRWeinstein @paulkrugman But the concept of political wings don’t have any bearing on any ideology… https://t.co/zEs7HOjRO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you're working with the PM, the government and PMO on this, and are doing everything to cover it up. The libera… https://t.co/u8iOLiCPbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigjayoakerson really excited to see you tonight in Albany!  Crackle crackle...@TheBonfireSXM https://t.co/IMmwBJCWAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do Not Disturb by @Halestorm sounds a lot like Hungover in a Hotel Room by @LukeBryanOnline #Halestorm #LukeBryan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hersheeyss Same here but thankfully I have a Smart TV in my room so I am watching YouTube for now !!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, why does the cat wear a hoodie in #PatTheDog?  I get that its name is Hoodie.  But, why?  @DisneyXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @Julianna_glass @thatsVeryKari @ccatmpt @AkronWineGuru @cowineco @CaththeWineLady @Cbp8Cindy @SLBriscoe… https://t.co/GDhkDBQYta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT Thank you for pointing out the damage that Brexit will cause, and many are totally oblivious to. https://t.co/skfDfji4bB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC 74,000 people attempted to illegally entered the US in February. Even the @washingtonpost reporter assigned to… https://t.co/iaUeMuKQwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Kylo is rebellion, adolescence and sexual awakening. Kylo killing Han is a heightened metaphor for trying to forsa… https://t.co/nBBbySTk8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You have more simultaneous investigations into your crimes going on than any previous president.   Also a big deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @anchorwendyryan @RoxanneWilder @TeachPR @shawnavercher @LeclairChiro @Christieo @KKucyk @newsbycruz… https://t.co/I5fYFscDMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I’m trying to gain I lose weight, when I need to cut I gain weight. No winning with my body]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse You're a runaway crazy bull-shit artist in a "china shop" I personally sense that beca… https://t.co/KLSvpKFYQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hawks have 8 more losses   Trae for the season 16.9p 3.3r 7.6a Luka 20.7p 7.2r 5.6a  Trae 40.6%fg 31.2%3p  Luka 43%… https://t.co/ro8TKjS0ET]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandyCariello I liken watching/listening to Trump to getting a root canal. The big difference is that after the ro… https://t.co/fVZ6GD353d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buzzman888 @LadyRedWave Not going to happen. He went to little Brooklyn College and barley had a crowd. Try to fill up Barkley Center!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today my wife said I was aging into a distinguished looking man and I'm really hoping I don't have to act that way now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @alstontaine! Babski Creative deserves the credit along with @SYPPublishing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cuse_MBB I remember when we used to LIKE playing at home. Man up or they're gonna set a record you don't want to b… https://t.co/C4EFe7Kydp]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is random but @Sensodyne_US toothpaste is BETTER than advertised. Just sayin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rewards4Justice @FBI @FBIMostWanted @USEmbassySyria @USEmbassyKabul @usembislamabad @coalition @INTERPOL_HQ fu bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[*cleans room*  Mom: *says in disgust*  “you need to clean your room”  Me: https://t.co/jq6zspgsDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’s comin, y’all! #InJusttheRightLight @ Youngstown, Ohio https://t.co/lmh8uPMuKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Imperial Maple Porter by @backwoodsbrewco @ CCSD Clubhaus — https://t.co/dhOBpN9i4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though I don’t talk to my CS squad as much. Always gonna support and be there for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke It’s LOADED with LANDMINDS that will hamper or even handcuff your ability to execute the wall even i… https://t.co/hSAQGitppZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#US #Usa #UnitedKingdom #Australia #Italy #Illinois #Chicago #Vegas #Hollywood #LosAngeles #California #ListenTo SH… https://t.co/nAszP0mk69]]></document></documents></author>