<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This thread: everything you need to know about the Smollett case right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woot Woot!!! Received my order from @buyIegaImeds today! The lip balm feels amazing and I can't wait to try the Iso… https://t.co/cMlXPUu6UQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wohhh look what showed up in my feedly feed today @mrBobbyBones !!! I know and love him but its so awesomw other pe… https://t.co/bnNvzpd0kO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Investigations of the nervous system continue... worms going to the dark side @HofiusKISD #soaringinscience https://t.co/nxdnP8esql]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I give katy aux I regret it within 10 seconds of the first song]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elsie_lachlan @equalizerpm Thank you for your service and support of the constitution!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought of the day: why is it that Demi can make the headlines for being on drugs, but now that she’s cleaning her… https://t.co/XFhHjMzEQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sadly at the age where I respond to your 10:37pm text at 6:05am the next morning 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Presidents always run off to Palm Beach after declaring a National Emergency. On our dime. You friggin mòron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I listen to my father on an outgoing message. His voice effects me. Why? Simply because I still have British in me.… https://t.co/1vmbyg7Ugd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DHandyJr54 @EileenWittig @PearleVision @hulu A mama always knows how to locate her son😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve wasted so much time on people who most definitely didn’t deserve my time 🙃💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NBCGoodGirls brought me here...@ginwigmore’s voice is so unique and strong...#loveatfirstlisten https://t.co/9x7GsWFrWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 I have been thinking about this - and pondering the possibilities - ever since I heard about next week’s travel plans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to wrap everyone from @taylornation13 in a giant hug because they are all so incredibly amazing and kind to us. ♥️🥇]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I’m very Twitter active this morning. This is what happens when I cant smoke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisapniewski Didn’t watch, never will again! Could care less about these Fairytale characters!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylan_mccartyy I’m just tryna be livin like Larry 😂 https://t.co/C60MNBS9BP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oreminsteluspl1 Aww, I am sorry for you.  I have 2 cats that should be rewarded greatly for their companionship.  I am thankful for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still can't believe Jordyn Woods really fucked her whole shit up for dick. For a basketball and NOT EVEN A GOOD O… https://t.co/JpHdqBFV9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm crying real tears 😭 Not only are these literally my FAVORITE bands, they're coming to VA on my mfn 21st birthda… https://t.co/vxqjuhP8pT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden I guess you took a page from Obama’s playbook. On an apology tour huh? Poor taste Joe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_JeanPierre @shaunking Yes!  His racism is hurting us all!  https://t.co/vUtpzGrDOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurenhard exactly! Super low socks and a bit of ankle is okay. I just feel like some outfits call for it haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamsCancino @jguaido Ya no más marchas estamos como la época de cabrillea y tantos otros no te quemes. Esa gen… https://t.co/gHHFAxjWwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you post a pic on Instagram of your body positive photo shoot and try not to stare at your phone wondering if… https://t.co/dqJABUtacQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doublegshoots @Swainwright81 @TomSteyer @realDonaldTrump Take your double G'S and flaunt them someplace else you a… https://t.co/lFbUfIvz0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Note to self: don’t fall asleep at 8PM for an hour because before you know it it’ll be 1AM and you’re wide awake.. 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tired of renting? Ready to make the move and find your dream home? @ Jacksonville, Florida https://t.co/orOqn776WV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rockermom1959 @LiaisonMilitia @MazurikL @Jim_Jordan @Jillibean557 @TWITMO_INMATE @trumpovic02 @Trump454545… https://t.co/IMYTbbaMZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenuineJLY @soledadobrien I read that about 10 times and I still have no idea what he was talking about!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkronZoo I love our Zoo! Thank you so much! ♥️  And what I'm hearing you say is that they *could* be tiny alien ba… https://t.co/Vy3IsUHP3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Hannah G never got her fantasy suite date? Or we have to wait til next week? #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rare picture of our sweet Belle. #catsofinstagram @ South Carolina https://t.co/ZevwuQlRWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bingliu89 @MindingGapFilm congratulations on your Independent Spirit Awards! Good luck tomorrow at the Oscars!! #MindingtheGap]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU Are To Be PRAISED YOU Are To Be ADORED YOU Are To Be LIFTED HIGH For The World To See YOU Are KING LORD SAVIOR… https://t.co/7ObI7mFnK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going for the day’s special - sweet onion chicken teriyaki, in salad form.  #MartialArtsNight. (at @SUBWAYFreshbuzz… https://t.co/aaWnbwmeXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @NerdPyle @MargaretHoover @CNNTonight Don’t get me wrong, some of them ( Rick Santorum) for one I don… https://t.co/pngGwcGs1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lights will always show you a way. #museum #lights #losangeles #LA @ LACMA Los Angeles County Museum of Art https://t.co/AsMS0iZPxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so prepared for dnd tonight, but tbh I want more dice. (Tryina finish my ep of #CriticalRole before our session… https://t.co/2BbCKBaVuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AprilDawnRaney @tamaraletter #MLmagical #gratitudeSnaps https://t.co/YLawuWLy95]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day to all the badass women that I love out there 🤘🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrazyCarl003 I’d genuinely love to see you stop butting in on a conversation that didn’t concern you nor involve y… https://t.co/OKNXjnWypP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleRichards You're one of the wolves biting at LVP's heals just like the rest lead by Lisa Rinna.....look at her… https://t.co/ojtSKC4JE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[SDNY accused Trump and Cohen came with receipts/ Trumpsleays controls the narrative that we spend time trying to de… https://t.co/nf6QH31OTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy crap. A full blown thunderstorm. In February. https://t.co/X2i1O6LA8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary to my sweet pain in the neck husband! ❤️ I love you to the moon and back. Thank you for always be… https://t.co/ENITeka9D1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bundle up! It is COLD out here! 🧣🧤🧦  Less than 10 degrees in Auburn.... @AmandaWGME has your forecast on… https://t.co/6wsZwSKBSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[La compañía @SpaceX ha lanzado con éxito, con la ayuda de la @NASA , desde Cabo Cañaveral su primera cápsula comerc… https://t.co/Xo7IwMs9S5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unfortunately this would be used often when I’m cooking. Would rob the kids of their chance to mock me and dance ar… https://t.co/87yIhwfhGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooooooo Joe Biden is running for president. I’m predicting Obama will be the vice. Quote me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“How do I have Better Than Ezra and Toad the Wet Sprocket on this playlist but no Gin Blossoms,” she exclaimed incr… https://t.co/QcJoO4Eso6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShamusMc1 As @HannahfanBob would say, "Let's not blame any of this on thinking."]]></document><document><![CDATA[i sadly think he might be in WH a 2nd term I am seeing a pattern In all these investigations, including the inaugur… https://t.co/AYXMGgqupz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder What about opioid crisis? Or gun violence? How about the humanitarian situation? Walls can be scaled, tunne… https://t.co/pZ7dIb03U9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new lash lady gave me a new set in an hour...... we’re getting married]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all be retweeting porn at 9 am like .. have y’all even eaten breakfast first?? I’m concerned for yalls well being]]></document><document><![CDATA[@me_sherazi I wonder if these people were as appalled when this NS was stealing money and buying property abroad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We dream in colors • borrowed from the sea 🌊 an ocean breeze • puts my mind at ease #sandiego #california… https://t.co/m5qSoMDKgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally disgusted with Judge Berman and our corrupt court system. Tired of hearing she was afraid or being careful.… https://t.co/PqH3XWfuSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to know what the weather is going to be like today and this week? @KateWentzelWX is talking about it right now… https://t.co/7blAUmN2v8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald Putin and Trump knows being “willfully ignorant “ = easy “Russian Asset”.  And why Betsy Devos runs… https://t.co/rKxnxuQr1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCMayor Use your incentives to help small, local, businesses. You will realize losing Amazon will be a blessing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steellt78 @frenchifry @sara_utu @HoarseWisperer So allow people to mistreat and bully you your entire life in case… https://t.co/eayiXqInbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A mi ni me gusta tomar, siempre son mis amigas q a la fuerza quieren q tome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything happens for a reason!!! I’ll always stand by that because I wouldn’t be in such a great place in my life… https://t.co/Orpd6h0E34]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent way too long on my makeup for tonight to end this way. Was under appreciated so twitter here you go https://t.co/68SUUcaX1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TearsaSmith Watching you this morning! Is there a list of roads closed due to flooding? Trying to determine best w… https://t.co/eJb92rK7gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @WhiteHouse @PressSec. @NSAGov. @FBI  @CIA. #intelligence #Uk says Facebook willfully distributes info they… https://t.co/hxhdbdqzkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahh yes. When my mom found my twitter and made me have a meeting w/ the Dean cause I tweeted "my deans a bitch"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queennaija rt this to vote for @queennaija! #iHeartAwards #socialstaraward #QueenNaija]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burd71 @davidlclaytontx I never see my toxic family anyway. I would like more time off for rest. I'm tired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk where the heck these people got this from, but i do not think that my amazing best friend @JennayLeslie looked… https://t.co/TZHWspCa9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBCOpelika drop off is at the Humpharies Building (old appliance store) corner of 8th St and Ave C. Water is not n… https://t.co/oWnWaND58r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChgocadChic Follow me, I follow back all #MAGA #KAG #MAGAVETS #DEPLORABLES  #TRUMPVILE #TRUMPSUPPORTERS… https://t.co/V0PT7inBxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[My tongue piercing ripped to my original hole and now this shit hurts more than ever 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mediumformat #120film #acros100 #expiredfilm #nyc #Manhattan https://t.co/ZUF1F9xvuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kelmarie2003 @DanielC2903 @Natstrange73 When I bought groceries at Walmart yesterday I saw there. It was by the sa… https://t.co/USeFNGSEl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loosen your belts because North Italia opens 2/27 in DC! @ North Italia https://t.co/tHL66sSQ6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEMON 🍋with my new blog design I'm starting a new series feature. Each season will be a different theme so for spri… https://t.co/xZHMgXQCjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna be 17 again sitting in culinary with my friends not stressing over everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigachievers2 @ACESKilpatrick @AbbottsCreekES Love you, Shelly @bigachievers2!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My queeeeeeeeen😍  She got me thru some tough times over 3 years ago and she still gets me through every day! Love h… https://t.co/zEux3MKm20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyterabyte @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump A bot? I am a proud registered nurse, working class American. I am so embarr… https://t.co/IYA1YaCtm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree .... such a wound that won't heal....  The ulcer that makes you nauseous .... A face that resonates EVIL !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuneBug88Fan @hallmarkchannel @brennan_elliott @IamLaceyChabert Absolutely! Sigh. It's just so good! #AOMH  #AOMH4PLZ @hallmarkchannel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw Shout out to the Bible thumpers and religious right wingers this is ok but God forbid he was gay- then yo… https://t.co/L0F1fAj2VL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shortman5427 @WayneDupreeShow And you ms Dryfuss are the worst kind of fake. Have you offered your home to the res… https://t.co/xvuqN0OKq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning all you beautiful people!!!! Today is gonna be a great day! Job interview at 4:30pm then my son game a… https://t.co/78tOlW3hRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scolo @RandyRainbow @NobelPrize So true Scott ! Randy truly makes me laugh .. and these days not much to laugh about !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scontorno @MiamiHerald That's Trump with his #MinisterOfMassageParlors]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rrbc #rwisa #bookboost #readme #circleofbooks #bookreviews Come join Rave Review Book Club as we search for our "p… https://t.co/MjHoKVN4WS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve officially decided I’m too cute to only be getting kissed once a week. https://t.co/RPsh1EwC04]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Cara Maria or Paulie win the million at the end of the challenge I’ll SCREAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This app pays you to listen to podcasts: https://t.co/NdUNfAbEBf Join and we both get 150 Podcoin. Use invite code Stephecp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anypennynick @wendykloiber So I’ve heard! I can barely get time off from work in the summer but when I can, I’m th… https://t.co/dCImkLKJuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out with manager of @AATHSBC just before the @HumaneBroward #WFTA2019 https://t.co/MUrHPlcH7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Key to Manifestations | 08.09.15 https://t.co/UkZulSfTej via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[But also I’m super nervous for my man to meet em. They’ve never met a guy I’m dating but I’ve also never felt the n… https://t.co/03Igukwguk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I’m done with Liberal Activist Judges! 1 Person in a Black Robe makes decisions 4 over 364 MILLION… https://t.co/2SNFgBiCDW]]></document></documents></author>