<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tyler_white44 You right, this just isn’t the generation to have a daughter]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best friend and I sent valentines to each other by submitting them to the Mercury.  I love that they related so… https://t.co/mdGv8kH2Cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@infinityloop5 @LockrCockr Nice. I'm also permanently locked also. Nice feeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[my latest on @espn  Ortiz faces Hammer, looks for Wilder rematch https://t.co/FWovR9HXJv  #boxing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Baystate Health team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/vlqbs3DrwT #Springfield, MA #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenKelsey13 Imagine Jordan have to deal with all his career that he can’t shoot like Bird or pass like Magic. H… https://t.co/d1TXtlba9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nerooze @BobbyBounce Kind of like how many times you catch a motherfuker reading a Playboy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personel is policy.  The appetite is there among the faithful for drastic reform.  Yet stripping numerous bishops o… https://t.co/GK4xwAbCdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words to live by. I have 3 times the life experience of this child. I’m doing just fine, thank you. I still can’t g… https://t.co/2OlGd7Z9bx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bfriendlygiant If you prefer free roaming Fallout style over story, ND is for you.   It's a sandbox. Story is meh but tons of freedom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stayed up late with @aarenelizabeth &amp; watched #CrazyRichAsians &amp; thoroughly enjoyed the. Worth being tired for! ☕️#wednesdaythoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally, a President that will stop the murder of innocent babies.  Kirsten is one of those murderers!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Louise M. Davies Symphony Hall in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/BgfddBfSzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stu007gots @lisabisex69 Definitely beautiful!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rotten Princess #animalovers  #chaweenie @ Southport, Florida https://t.co/2uhUSb3AYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why should she care?  This lady will be dead and buried in 12 years. No skin off her nose if the rest of us burn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emily_Is_Moore Well, at my age, my bladder is always a factor in a 3hr movie. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drugmonkeyblog Don't forget paper sitting in a drawer syndrome. That can kill a trainee's enthusiasm for the paper… https://t.co/cVoUe2y5gX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YasmineBri83 Lmaooo yes, that night Darl said he looked like he was wearing his daddy shirt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsDon_ don that’s not true that’s like saying Syracuse is better than duke simply because they beat them]]></document><document><![CDATA[. . . . . #saliceroseiswifey #salicerosefanpage #saliceroseliked #saliceroseforever @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/Qrk3BKuVOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well isn't this just adorable as heck? The answer is yes, it is. #instagay #gaystagram #gayswithglasses #gayboy… https://t.co/iLi3DN8nq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@08analau En los años 80 Santiago fue vecino y amigo mío y de mis hermanos allá en Miraflores de Heredia.  Qué époc… https://t.co/eFnKq5ETEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisWasson4 you’re a fucking moron!!! You think Kraft was a pimp or trafficked underaged women!!? Aaron Hernandez… https://t.co/YzCeoCYeaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am beginning the building of my first Dyno Dinamo Geared Centrifugal Spundge Stator Generator Flywheel bicycle hu… https://t.co/NqiSfNZlG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gettingtrump @hagenista @LisaMei62 If the mayors office wasn’t up for grabs it may have went The actors way! The c… https://t.co/0M2FEMJIl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So...I have a playlist with #RKelly that leads right into a #Jackson5 song. You can’t listen to anything anymore. T… https://t.co/NQJ7IxfRLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@griffhanbury @ACTforAmerica Both of them are bums! Both of them are rotten]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Mystery Photographer: left my camera charging and filming while grabbing some Fish n’ Chips from Barbara’s FishT… https://t.co/qGOPtCmyge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerDinucci The entire final season takes place a few years in the future. Samwell sits on the Iron Throne. Every… https://t.co/BLLMpK8dNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone. It’s Thursday and one day closer to the weekend. Have a great Thursday! 😎 @ Guilford, North… https://t.co/YYJEzqtbRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling you get when you Antonio Brown is out of the AFC North with Le'Veon Bell soon to follow https://t.co/x2ilKlmnGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love to see our kids getting a taste of #authenticlearning and impacting their world!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lights Out 10: The Finals https://t.co/vB5aVu7IDC @hotrodmagazine https://t.co/sfUDSLgaH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdbergman36 @YankeeSource Wade not a great hitter but lefty bat. Plays 3 infield positions and outfield. Fast runn… https://t.co/iGsCm5za0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tropical fruit and lots of bubblegum sweetness. - Drinking a Kinda Famous Hazy IPA by @HopworksBeer at… https://t.co/Nk4xYWY5UF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update to my tweet yesterday: My local @dunkindonuts decided to “say it with donuts” to this meteorologist after al… https://t.co/obYytdbQDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParaCG_909 You have to!  I must show you my favorite vampire bar of all time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kinda forgot Isle of Wight county schools snapped with that whole bringing home your own iPad thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm?🤔#Tesla #teslamotors #superchargers #teslasuperchargers #ev #electriccars #elonmusk #electricvehicle @ Gwinnet… https://t.co/Gfewixw80d]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Valentine's your second chance at hump day, time to sling some dick and eat some candy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy fuck @BleacherReport you guys are guys are dumb as fuck😂😂😂 it’s impossible for anyone to be 1.6% body fat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JadaTTate @BlaneErwin @neixannd @DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump It still doesn't subtract from Mueller's empty investi… https://t.co/8vhG06XHmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFWAirport , what’s going on at the north end of the 17C runway? Memorial services?]]></document><document><![CDATA[First game studying Devin White. 2nd play of the game. Let’s hope it’s only up from here. https://t.co/VCK6Pzldlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaphodgjd Yeah, I would actually love your thoughts on these two games now that you have played them so close together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sgtbilko6 Over 6 hrs+ 😉. It's like 5am now... I fell asleep. Reek of cum 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nationalsoaringmuseum 😁 #prettyviews @ Harris Hill Overlook https://t.co/uGfxbC4jnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not as many major characters as I thought died in season 7. I expect a lot to die in season 8. Season 8 is going to… https://t.co/qpqlalRIUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods In 10 years James the voting age will be 12 if these lunatics get their way. They’ll be buying vote… https://t.co/IliwNRobUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[(1/2) Thanks to all those for your patience and support. As an editor and writer, I look to bring voices and storie… https://t.co/N4Pu40WFFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 Never tied a knot in anything but a shoelace; never built a fire;  never cared for an ailing paren… https://t.co/Yc6IhXIc0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryRecco Instead of being funny maybe you should tell anybody the Islanders a playing tonight since you let them out of your update]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do underwear and socks come in resealable bags but potato chips don’t? #dadbodseason]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don’t want to work today so I’m just gonna be late as shit oops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson You do know a lot about acting like a third world dictator.  Your assaults on the 1… https://t.co/ftsbZ7Fu6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanImmergluck @WestmorelandATL @parkpride @tpl_org @gdusenbury @UrbanLandInst I think the answer is “yes” unless t… https://t.co/6vd93uDvkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeOutHereRN don't delete any snaps I need to watch them to make my day tomorrow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[like @hughhewitt and @henryolsenEPPC , to find a platform: https://t.co/6laqFou19T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jandbdupree @pirates4lyfe001 I mean he does have an $8 million insurance policy on his knees that pays out if he f… https://t.co/FQGtPxssJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teggerling1 I am going have to learn. My Dry Cleaners does not seem to do it anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to @UVMwlax and @UVMcoachdalton as they open up against Colgate today! Keep an eye on these Cats in 2019!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitter world. Have a Blessed and Beautiful Sunday  " LOVE LIFE " Blessed to be Blessed https://t.co/ttC4d9Zsvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGildedJester @SinBinVegas @ErikVegasVGK I wonder if the goalie can take a shot at if you go through your whole bench 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real legend Rest in peace Red Wings legend and Hockey Hall of Famer Ted Lindsay dies aged 93  https://t.co/jxpv7jrXnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@costareports I will not vote for Sanders, even if it means not voting for president for the first time since Nixon won.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Indianapolis  has declared #gunviolence to be a public health danger. So why is @IndyMayorJoe allowing the #NRA to… https://t.co/p7KfNQlxgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tool_shedd @murdermittens_ @ChloeMelzo White people aren’t the only ones selling their food stamps but that is an… https://t.co/BS7NpFrfKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Beilein when the clock struck midnight last night: https://t.co/MfzIcfy0AL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krazykeithrules watch and be amazed. he was the best.  https://t.co/Mf6aim4IYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[✔️JUNIORS This is a reminder to complete your registration for the ACT by Wednesday, March 6.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaredRosenstein @FLSERT @JaredEMoskowitz @GovRonDeSantis Great work.  Very nicely done Director Moskowitz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micklejacob I’m happy to find a quarter on the ground. But I get it’s a business decision. Just a lot of money to… https://t.co/fpL9AhZN3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to board a flight with the family. Different level of travel intensity when it's going on Vacay...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DenzelWashngton We all know that God said: "Vengeance Is Mine!" (Romans 12:19)  But watching someone else suffer b… https://t.co/nXFHLyGVsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseCardenas1 No le pidas dinero al Pejelagarto a ese le gusta el fútbol las carreras de carros de fórmula uno a n… https://t.co/SBokDGy6EJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJr Crossing fingers its a first time winner, @KyleLarsonRacin  or @ClintBowyer .  Bowyer would be a very memorable Victory Lane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In part 119,889,227 on why America should focus on us rather than other countries....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Wrong, you along with Democrats are trying to limit the constitutional power of the President. You should… https://t.co/9XdVZ4MHRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iTransxript @zackpierce2006 @TheRushingDino @FortniteGame I doubt you see 2-3 a game. As a fishstick owner I look… https://t.co/9t9nFPP3az]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOTE TO SELF: Look out for anything that enjoys dinosaur eggs for breakfast https://t.co/N7fDJBHyJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly reminder: if you woke up in daylight today, you’ll probably be waking up in the dark next Monday morning s… https://t.co/H7mzHYIOSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freakdam I thought the idea that a manufacturer  be responsible for the life of their packaging was startling. Har… https://t.co/YEZ4H4c6yQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @mlong42947 Jorge's Univision's and Methico's problem. A few more media a..holes like him should visit V… https://t.co/lf6HjH8B7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller _ @raider_rob24 needs more bits, this dude is ABSOLUTELY HILARIOUS, man!!!!! “Oh I’m not gonna have time… https://t.co/BWvNReBZuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[When 2 of America’s experienced law enforcement officers question the loyalty of a President whose election legitim… https://t.co/BO8GORAKv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time in Silicon Valley, so I was thrilled to read this article.  https://t.co/xn64UkVNt3 Perhaps m… https://t.co/5WvwA27yYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glass. #AMCAList (@ AMC Starplex Ridgefield Park 12 for Glass in Ridgefield Park, NJ) https://t.co/Xd2quXT4gQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliacmiranda3 Shit, my mom would throw me in the mud for pretty much any reason if it meant Jalapeño got luxury treatment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought there could be so much stupid all in one place. Then I joined twitter and realized how much  stupid… https://t.co/iBgz2OedIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nic0lix The only kimchi I like is @KimChi_Chic https://t.co/faWs3oddYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly hate running on the treadmill. I feel too much like a hamster on a wheel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovWhitmer I can't believe how stupid you are. You really think the gas prices are going to stay down. Get your head out of your ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @AE911Truth @CNN GN vic  I'll be chasing the hour they steal Tonight...  If taxes=theft  DST is surely ta… https://t.co/epRQMGWy48]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone tries to make a case for why #Cryptocurrency is a bad investment and they get so caught up in the politics… https://t.co/a6IlwtrLd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bz-  what do you think we will do? C- you like the system we built.  You seem to even like me.  I am being annoyed… https://t.co/BAy7NaJBAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember the Bret Kavanaugh hearings. Don't lecture us about playing politics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know how took this picture since the Ninja photographer photogian_ was getting promoted. Whoever you are, t… https://t.co/oVegDv45sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fucking a show! Y’all threw down in Orlando @diontimmermusic @Dubloadz @Kompanymusic]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS: Ocean Resort Casino shake up continues as upper level executives depart  https://t.co/3uTjNBwNrl via @thepressofac]]></document></documents></author>