<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@nickisnpdx @LGin412 @CV_Social @byQuartzEvents They are a bright, neon pink and not the cotton candy pink of your socks. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to point out exceptionally well written #Tweets today. Funny, insightful, little bursts of thought in my scr… https://t.co/9lF11tnpZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 45% Off Mani-Pedis at Safas Salon &amp; Day Spa https://t.co/x1RPeNgwLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 116 FOXWOOD CLOSE #Milford #CT  #realestate https://t.co/u8rmHcwPmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[no more broken phone📞 back to the social media shiz oh also, wanna see me live at a private event? DM me for info 🖤 https://t.co/sz2xmT2QhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for Prince Charming to come take care of me ... #INeedASmoothie #IceCreamSoundsGreat #MilkShakeYum #FeelingBlah]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can't argue with that. Just because someone claims something, doesn't mean it actually happened. I could make u… https://t.co/TaxAfni52B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaaaand last but not least, the Galaxy S10 5G, which has the biggest screen and biggest battery of any Galaxy S and… https://t.co/woyk0qtt68]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trentemay I think this might be about a mile from the theater? https://t.co/v9LuyBh3MP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ they took you by the toes and sucked you in “  - Mod quote of the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Donald Trump's tone likened to Hitler by Mexico's Pena Nieto https://t.co/XuTEK5iiBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gettin’ ready to head into @DISupdates for @XfinityRacing to cheer on @NoahGragson &amp; @CBellRacing! Why? Because… https://t.co/odY51c4aAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[you hate immigrants but still wanna be consumerists but also don’t want to acknowledge that our economic system and… https://t.co/24WdYlnXFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS if Congress passes the resolution to block your national emergency declaration, VETO the DAMN thing!  God he… https://t.co/tMu6sTEa19]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is an energy right now that won't let ego be the priority of your life. And, to be honest, a lot of "Spiritua… https://t.co/V3UYPyy3wQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, Senator @lizbethkb, for taking the time to meet with our volunteers for #FLCancerLobbyDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardEGrant @melissamccarthy @foxsearchlight Congratulations! I so enjoyed you performance in Can You Ever Forgive Me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd @Jim_Jordan did you ask him about sexual assault in oregon that he ignored????/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAY4_ @deeswizzz Go to church and join a Young Adult Group or a Singles Group in your church.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby lights do wonders 💫.  ________________________________________ . . . . #chinohair #chinohillshairstylist… https://t.co/iA4ByznBxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[chizoba by rudeboy has been on repeat all day. that song is so meaningful and literally touches my heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[I listen to his music, but I realized I've never actually taken the time to see what Shawn Mendes actually looks like]]></document><document><![CDATA[State Class A boys hockey quarterfinals: East Grand Forks Green Wave 5, Minnesota River Bulldogs 2. Shots: Green Wa… https://t.co/yUPRTstPTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my amazing friend @neverfallapart 🙏🏾😊 hope you have an amazing day! https://t.co/cduM5AQkPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been sick for one day and I’m beyond over it. I don’t have the time to be sick this week 🙅🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Impeach Tlaib; she is unacceptable, dishonorable, misplaced and an unfit representative  in Congress f… https://t.co/SC3y2ho2G6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paddy_asquadtv @ForIAmKing78 @charliekirk11 Once the child is born,  it’s a human life,  there is NO choice!! Depr… https://t.co/NAK3RglSb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s not direct admissions but I’ll see you soon Aggieland👍🏼 https://t.co/YXG08MTXrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[What was I thinking making this appt during nap time?? And I’m not talking about John, he’s at home napping with ch… https://t.co/VL1U9IBhGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Falkor  #puppies #leonbergerstyle #leonbergers #leonbergersofinstagram #leonberger #leonbergersoftheday #leonberger… https://t.co/3wV12bBNdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one fucking thing I ask you fuckers is the first fucking thing y’all do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marissawyant @ArkansasBlog Maybe it’s called wanting to be a dad.... Choice must only apply to women. Got it!  Hypocrites!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigmylesMob @thehicklife @BackTheLEOs @LivePdBlueLine @IndependenceGr1 @DonnaJamesRye68 @TrueLivePDFans… https://t.co/mFWzLdDS9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Taylormcneill42 What the hell is ur Twitter name hahahahaha also ur name in my phone is literally Teezy Mcneezy so… https://t.co/5Na6SOHe5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiness is when you have open house and a parent brings you dinner! It was delicious! I love my career! 😍😘 #WeAreClintISD #CowboyStrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished doing laundry and was hanging T-shirts to dry and nearly every single one of them is a… https://t.co/EUghIatby4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paying off my credit cards by winning this G.O.O.D. contest #CreditCardDebtSucks  #GetOutOfDebt.com https://t.co/sjlGRIXgpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardhine @realDonaldTrump Says a man who looks like he is part of the resistance movement and gets his facts fr… https://t.co/382xxfomE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ckkoch3 @TVMoJoe @Lawrence @allinwithchris @NicolleDWallace Handsome Irish Fella ☘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yay_leen6 I did that all the time with my friends. Like before it got busy]]></document><document><![CDATA[MERYL STREEP. Yes!! Also very excited to be in one of the first horror movies to win an Oscar. (I always knew I sha… https://t.co/tVFEbMM9m2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter got engaged this morning and suddenly I’m on a wedding budget 🤦🏼‍♀️💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gloinmelanin1 @AJL0926 @astrog1rll @chrxstianx So what do you make of the movie "This is Us"....We can't even trust ourselves 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 17222 WESCO LOOP #SanAntonio #TX  #realestate https://t.co/H6AUCU2wee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr @w_terrence @lyft @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse He is proof that there is a living God. What a mirac… https://t.co/mD5olb2Gka]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Tyler and I both wore our @WeAreTheWrecks hoodies tonight - completely unplanned- and some guy that we ran into… https://t.co/BMsbdmWTCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cop admits framing two black men as Florida town’s false arrest scandal widens https://t.co/aeRCLe0NQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunbabe08 And for the record I don’t think he’s going to be inserted back into the until  picture until after mani… https://t.co/t0XAa7BPCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better Than Ezra - "Desperately Wanting" official music video https://t.co/UmzSJyBd8p via @YouTube  #90smusic #loveofmylife #loveezra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horry County Fire and Rescue Dispatch - Live Audio Feed Web Player https://t.co/aAHxc6zVoj via @Broadcastify]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long leg culture is knowing u can make it somewhere 10-15min prior the ETA]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your @jcrew pantsuit is set be delivered on International Women’s Day 😏🙌🏾 #whoruntheworld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OilsandsAction Not for bitumin, sorry.  Refine it if u want to move it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta hermosura saldrá adelante por que tiene ángeles que están haciendo todo lo posible .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel so validated by this. I can be around someone who speaks with an accent or has a unique way of speaking and… https://t.co/K8Lddf3gxT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracyn told me I was being basic because I took a picture of the coffee.  So I’m tagging her. ☕️  #imokwithit… https://t.co/BwUMxlAMDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tinker_Bell_04 @PressSec She is comic relief. Her lies are just funny!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SpeakerPelosi! I am sure your feed blew up yesterday after @MattGaetz scummy tweet yesterday and his lam… https://t.co/L9be57b921]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching them youtubers eat and play video games is kinda weird to me.. why watch someone do any of that, when you’… https://t.co/qNePOCSRM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJ60080420 @AbbyMartin The US is fighting again for labor rights via teachers. And nurses. Strikes have got to… https://t.co/rO0lxSmvZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just started watching #sisterwives recently. Is it just me or is Robyn the brown nose of the group? I wouldn’t tr… https://t.co/OVIdztqhX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[REAL hard facts trumpets digging in support immoral nasty   man even MORE  The country has over 62,969,000 racists… https://t.co/eTTG86avK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful for the opportunity to learn from @WGE_Principal at Walker Gamble Elem. These Georgia girls are excited… https://t.co/MldA7mmJcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s so orange... looking like us white girls after we get our spray tans for prom😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. I FOUND OUT MY BOSS HAS A TWITTER AND IM NO LONGER SAFE IN MY SAFE HAVEN PLACE !!!!  2. MY WORK CRUSH GAVE ME LI… https://t.co/gKauMlZfLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themarcusskane The funny thing is I have the son on my iPad and I love it hehe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally finished @gris_game. What a gorgeous, elegant and breathtaking piece of art. The balance between puzzle, pl… https://t.co/DiGt2r1ps2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time does heal. I don’t think about any of the toxic people that were in my life.  It feels so damn good. 🙌🏼 https://t.co/pcBmlqAJRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little bit of good news mixed in with some questionable news. Trump's approval at 46%? Really? I don't get it. https://t.co/XwAEu1KNqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “I wonder what she must feel like, knowing she’s the ugly sister”  Me: *is the ugly sister*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lying Trump attacks Mueller, Sessions and Comey in lengthy speech  https://t.co/mnkN8baCiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoCoats88 @RepDanCrenshaw @benshapiro Because having a car, driving a car, etc is not a constitutional right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaldyViewROP staff, instructors, and stakeholders participating at 2019 Educating for Careers conference...bringin… https://t.co/0HyQZqWo2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Jerome PreK celebrated Pedro’s 5th birthday.🎂Happy Birthday Pedro!🎉 https://t.co/aaFHX9oeh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristyCarver79 @bushofficial @GavinRossdale @CT3GUITAR @robingoodridge @coreybritz @Baba_Prod @DAcuna21… https://t.co/C4aLsH5WyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert &amp; Hunter meet for the first time! #brothers @ Dallas, Texas https://t.co/4f7j0dhM46]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only women who have a problem with this is the ones who actually fit the description of a hoe when she was in high… https://t.co/yhHPYNVdAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melody Angel @buddyguys singing Ball N Chain by Big Mama Thornton. I'll be opening for Bobby Rush and Buddy Guy tod… https://t.co/5oGxPAI7yb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@durpnad It’s is true. The back of my car is wrecked because of some negligent jerk and now the hood is scratched too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothin to hide right trump? COWARD, I bet your as stupid as you look. Best words? I know for a fact that isn't true… https://t.co/4NuFwfegaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t see how the problem is the amount of minimum wage and not the apartments standards you’re an idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Restore the civil right act of 1964, and this will guarantee the right to vote for every American that is igible to… https://t.co/5jMPkvFXjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asshat. And I thought George W was an embarrassment whenever he spoke… And back then I was actually a Republican!… https://t.co/V5Et7bbjx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may have gotten @ArianaGrande #cloudmacchiato from @Starbucks &amp; it’s so pretty 🥰 https://t.co/I56sl4UViJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Genie115 @TheDemocrats @SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer @senatemajldr @GOPLeader @SenateGOP @HouseGOP @POTUS… https://t.co/B3STp5oEaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, this morning, my phone shut down after updating. I woke up at 0644. My work day starts at 0700. 30 minutes from… https://t.co/cGgwUzEg8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a line to sign in for today’s #Augusta planning meeting #halehouse #greenmeadows @ Augusta, Georgia Governm… https://t.co/IaKGzdUVJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was accepted into being a @Seesaw ambassador! I’m so excited to be an ambassador for this transformative teaching app❤️ #TeacherLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA I agree. And contract employees. There are speciality jobs that are desperately needed with higher pay, you… https://t.co/WMNABLzTY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfpelosi @rhonda_harbison 185 republicans voted no to try and “make sure” a mental person doesn’t get a gun. I’m s… https://t.co/CMbSiu0fab]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day at SML even with Carl Perkins!! Always working... #CTEMonth @TCWPrincipal @TCWCTE @AcpsGeraldMann… https://t.co/bt11ChVyhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maria and i message each other every single day even though we live together 😂 all you hear is laughter all day lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sistercircletv this discussion must be done early. I was 8. Now 66. I have stories and survived.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One blessed woman 💜 #letthembelittle #momswithcameras #momswithiphones @ Olympus Park https://t.co/fUd9G8R5hn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I forgot to post this last week🤷🏻‍♀️ cheers to 21 years🥂🍾 @ Bloomsburg University of Pennsylvania https://t.co/rGwhBtW6GQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PTVNewsOfficial It is sad to see Pakistan turning to mafia rule. I am still President gold and money back here wor… https://t.co/z3wwReQ8ca]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole working in healthcare to get extra experience under my belt better be worth it for my job interviews bec… https://t.co/8iSrMROmKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TereOrt51687394 @ElbaklySami @Jose93571656 @PucciaPatrizia @enriqueiglesias @Viviane6677 @mich_onelove @janaplauen… https://t.co/0PTu5ReeHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if you like boys that smoke and choke you during sex? Asking for a friend...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Woman’s Day!! therealmickrock photo  #fashion #style  #ootd #sequindress #gold #girlgang… https://t.co/dGNajMeCQM]]></document></documents></author>