<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MargannaY Не, я про другое. Одно дело подарить подарок деньгами, а другое дело подарить деньги вместо праздника.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Am hoping Roger Stone gets  the same treatment or worst...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @WTWBoysHoops class of ‘17 Jason Aigner @jbutter3_ and his CNU Men’s team for punching their ticket to the D3 Elite 8.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buck and a quarter for pizza and a drink. Cheapest way to rebel as a teen bc I got caught and got sent to ISS twice… https://t.co/ilOgTgGbit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooo fam comment below where you guys are from! I wanna visit EVERY SINGLE ONE OF YOU before I die😊🔥👍 I live in Tuc… https://t.co/HKWpzGexpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to catch up with some of the @NACoTweets past (and current) presidents! Great Legislative Conference! https://t.co/NE2RbJETfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talented 3-year-old filly Chasing Yesterday headed to Sunland Oaks per trainer Bob Baffert]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not too worried about Kawhi getting another day off, and I hope Lowry and Ibaka get a few also in the next month. W… https://t.co/yXczfIenkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods It’s enough to make you wonder about our kids/grandkids futures. So sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irvingge19 Imagínate así estaban del carajo para que un profesional QUE NO SABE CENTRAR sea líder en asistencias.… https://t.co/hALKg6DBaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sucks, but sometimes you just have to accept the way things are... from now until my birthday I'm focused on mys… https://t.co/zxac7U5F6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just replied “echo, that’s what she said” to something my amazon dot relayed about how much snow to expect this w… https://t.co/7cWdKAb0JK]]></document><document><![CDATA[And oh hey, what do you know, there's nothing a good reboot can't solve apparently.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to us hosting the first ever Coach Developer Diploma with @UnitedCoaches and @etcconsultants  🔴🐂🔴🐂🔴… https://t.co/DOpHKsSpsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zmohlis I know MNHS has many items of historical/cultural significance to regional tribes, and because of the law… https://t.co/G3NJ6sFDyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loudwindow The single player campaign is one of my absolute favorites, do it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MUweather Snowhorse?? I think not. The snowman is legit. Amish appear to be stuffing the ballot box.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traceyquitman @TheOpening @BrandonHicks_27 @freddierch8 @DerrickDnix @_UnderTheRadar_ @CoachBynum @Boobie24Dixon @FBU_MS Yes Sir!]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I stated a few months ago.. women need to be punished for this.. they should have to serve the time the man woul… https://t.co/V3kQuvwDdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blanca Ocasio-Cortez, the mother of socialist Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-NY), has fled the state of New York… https://t.co/3K8EMDf54n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MingGao26 @tazarae20 @LindseyGrahamSC #PityPatGraham My Stars and Garters!!! The scandal of it all!!! https://t.co/ugpj5aQVFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[CareLinx acquires Providence St. Joseph Health non-clinical services platform https://t.co/9lyVWpr8HA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a good day to be a #Pokemon fan.  #PokemonDay #pokemonswordshield #scorbunny  https://t.co/tPAPlvS7MU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorningsMaria @dagenmcdowell   why don't you ask @TheJuanWilliams what Medicare for all means.  Medicare pays 80%… https://t.co/OypKG9Tqfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sea_Baugruppe @raludwick @Nullthread Yeah... I don't understand that...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Angelica by @LordHoboBrewing @ Pints &amp; Quarts — https://t.co/WYlgOkQnPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philcrews Phil, I play golf at WYCC 5-6 days weekly with a guy named Tom Haislet.  He’s had Waldenstrom for @ 21 y… https://t.co/d1OSG0zuex]]></document><document><![CDATA[“God’s grace will expose what you want to hide, not to shame you, but to forgive and deliver you. Grace shatters ou… https://t.co/vKQlrhhnVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sjokotof1 @larryelder and what about the black slave owners???  https://t.co/CFRlc0VVMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHIKKYTO @vampirevolution @OMARCHAPARRO @anzua90 Sales tu en em video compadre @CHIKKYTO https://t.co/yl4Vy9zzog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calclarke1985 Then get him out your club. What’s the wait. His body language is a disgrace. He doesn’t want to be… https://t.co/pO41cGhpdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im talking like 3rd grade i got brownies on a tuesday and Friday rolls around and i get valentines. Good stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems like only viable Republican strategy was to convince him to withdraw and (eventually) sub in a new candidate… https://t.co/dQOPyoNYOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sol y Luna, Sol e Lua, Soleil et Lune, Sonne und Mond... Sun and Moon - I think you understand! 🌞🌝 @ Cancun Mexican… https://t.co/O5fAw0qNlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamMujahidShah @KoblerinPAK @AAyazofficial @HamidMirPAK @peaceforchange @AmirMateen2 Beshak he really deserves it bhai]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is dope  and I get what you mean but this isn’t gentrification this is Community building.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lucas_Jadin helps our @ANTrackandField sharpen their mental skills so that we compete at our best when the stakes… https://t.co/7PU8I2q4UQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaygosTommyT @rcc1000 @JJ_ROOSTER @Padres @Bharper3407 At least our football team stayed 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[WATCH: BERNIE SANDERS Asked To Name One Legislation He’s Passed…Crickets! [Video] https://t.co/qF616kcslE https://t.co/wnXBAYgJbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bighugh53 I knew ole boy was lying when they said he getting snacks at 2am in a polar vortex snow storm in Chicago. Nah Nah]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are currently discussing 2019-2020 school calendar. Multiple board members are asking questions. #livefromtheschoolboard]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharrnat @danaygarcia1 @SonyPictures @SonyMovieCh Awww @danaygarcia1 is the best!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorTwellman @ATLUTD Don’t need to break down teams when you’re winning. Koch is content to play long balls and… https://t.co/7OXoj7TGR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@floradiosa @TWOCharmss Riiiiiight bitches uploading they pics for nothing but online validation. Imma validate you alright]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days are just #blackandwhite #vintagemilitary #contemporarydesign #lipwatches #bulgaridiagono… https://t.co/WuaIFrRlAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like when people use the “well, if you’re so smart...” argument because at worst it’s an opportunity to prove mys… https://t.co/Winv5C52Ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Fleming Centre Beamsville https://t.co/Yy3a2FE23C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sifaoui Vous faussezla situation car il y a des femmes qui se sont opposées au port obligatoire du voile dans des… https://t.co/ByKrtuTw2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mel___dub Major on the first two. Which is why long distance is a huge issue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerry_jtaylor @murphymike @BulwarkOnline They sure know how to play the crackers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved watching the home opener for #ATLUTD yesterday with my daughter. Fun afternoon @MBStadium https://t.co/FU8y2Ri0kh]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For what saith the scripture? Abraham believed God, and it was counted unto him for righteousness.” Romans 4:3 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AristeguiOnline El tema de Venezuela causa intranquilidad en América Latina pues el señor Maduro abona con un clim… https://t.co/Bfeq1sZKnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieSHasson @missbrown111 @klarebeechwood @ElisaBostwick @hansappel094 @DrJStephensVP @MrsRackleyCCMS… https://t.co/WdjzChYP0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look gcrazyadaudhal...hold up....I said it that way she can understand.    To us normal people... Looking crazy as… https://t.co/8zKGox4I7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cenkuygur  Evangelicals do not DISCRIMINATE against women and make then hide their faces and make them subordinate… https://t.co/fNZ4qXWFKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los compañeros que hoy comienzan a trillar un nuevo camino, tienen la ventaja del apoyo de un gran líder, el Dr.… https://t.co/N8SUCHpMW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DOM_Frederic 79 wins I think they meant 79 tanks for the 2019 mvp right here^]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siri google search how to transport dozens of plants without hurting them or me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overture Awards - Visual Art https://t.co/DCy3wVeMdy via @YouTube @MBK_Alliance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, my friends, #Believe it!  This #Leafs team can win the #Cup   Brought to you by #GetAldo.com… https://t.co/sYFktXSi25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA She is dumb woman (looks like one) trying to find herself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Karloff &amp; #Lugosi marathon! #EgyptianTheater #Frankenstein #BrideofFrankenstein #SonofFrankenstein #Dracula… https://t.co/NGFbIwQDrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pvwhit01 @NASCARONFOX @NASCAR @FoxNews Politics aside, this race is being broadcast on FOX afterall.  If the race… https://t.co/Jgr54pEnWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could have made a lot of you money already hit my line if you trynna cook this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't believe it with today's 37° temps, but the first sign of spring is here!  Found this little sweet daffodil al… https://t.co/MjMUS5SVh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 2 great classes of #yoga at @wildsideyoga it's time to #relax before mrteufelhunden #spaghetti #dinner at… https://t.co/BQStvTQVyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimacquaviva @PaulaKagan @Radical_Nurses Oh it’s been part of British comedy routines from music hall days to Netf… https://t.co/APd9hooSa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Straight to Redbox with this movie. At least Stan Lee is not around to see this nitwit try to tank one of his movies !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FBF #FlashbackFriday #CSUPueblo #ThunderWolves #D2  I miss the days of grinding inside of CSU Pueblo Wrestling… https://t.co/gy83Y8Qkqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried to request a Las Vegas DJ to play Bird Flu hy Lor Scoota and he laughed in my face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are only 600 short of our goal of 10,000 petitions  Join our quest:   https://t.co/e1czljfTm9… https://t.co/tNs0GlPKyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hotel haa big hanging poster w/ all their "about the hotel" info. You can call a number to get a bedtime story read… https://t.co/yVWmlffasP]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a old man sitting on the side of Garners Ferry Road with a BB gun.  I can’t wait to watch the news tinight😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was 16 years old I remember sing/screaming around the my house “Shattered Faith!.. A trilogy!...The Devil ju… https://t.co/HO2NarsG2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weight watchers has been put on hold for the evening. Apparently the large Bavarian special is actually quite large… https://t.co/oWxIFLXERg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Empezemos la semana en Paraje San José Sector Montañas https://t.co/LEhgOqw6Vc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Getslayed3 @ufcfightclub @ufc Montel Jackson the only other interesting fighter fighting that night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discovered today that @switchfoot's song #voices from their new album #nativetongue has the same tempo as my car's… https://t.co/kqrCb8PBCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SkinnyB lol I can’t with yaw. I got a 4am curfew my body will shut down lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @IvanDuque @jguaido Thank you @VP "for such a time as this" @POTUS #MAGA @AmbJohnBolton @jguaido]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/xKQY6irxDk SHE A MORE SKILLFUL BLACK ACTRESS, THAN TARAJ P HENSON, SHE CAN PLAY MOVIE AND TV ROLE MORE… https://t.co/aCktNoebM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentines  day...  at the  #torontoautoshow2019   thanks myersandco #ipace #lincolnnavigator @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/PMl3BKgMUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m following folks live tweeting about Roger Stone testifying about his Instagram post.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jung Ho Kang just crushed a ball to left for a solo homer...huge response from the crowd here in Bradenton. #letsgobucs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WassmannBill @stephen_richter @JenniPrickett @XStreamFisher @1MonsterMission @MattLFishing @M_J_Fishing… https://t.co/a2qRmD2VH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got a mani/pedi for the first time in my 21 years of living. WHY DID NOBODY TELL ME HOW GREAT THIS IS?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone flipping on Michael Jackson like we ain’t have the trial where the kids said the parents lied or that the… https://t.co/BieMigRL6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrici10041368 @Nacion321 @LillyTellez No se va a cambiar el mundo de la noche a la mañana, pero así como ya se e… https://t.co/SbuSyQGUFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1963hollywood @DonaldJTrumpJr What part of his tweet do you not agree with or feel is unworthy of pointing out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gett’n shots with noedewitt @ Madison, Wisconsin https://t.co/vv27gFOqTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[FROOT????? i thought it was FRUIT this whole time... are u kidding me? is this a mandela effect?😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never tell someone ur next move or wat u doing lowley. Cuz they gonna fuck ur next move..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fighting wars long over @ Central City, Los Angeles https://t.co/2z7xBF6aUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZackSnyder Plot twist: you actually have the famed “Snyder Cut” of Justice League and you’re going to show it there 😉 #ReleaseTheSnyderCut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwo84 Reminds me of my .@BarefootBoogie years, + dance floors full of happy smelly vegetarians. #youth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel Lol. The WSJ OpEd Page is a clown show.  You have even less credibility than the other Murdoch lunatic crew over at Fox News.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeDavidsonJr @PatMcAfeeShow @Keith048 Lee I’m going to have to watch the movie again. I scrolled through the soun… https://t.co/lCcIyRtDlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[My current situation. #DontJudgeMe #HappyBirthdayToMe #TeamPisces https://t.co/ZnORio9521]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, Tennessee, Kentucky is SEC basketball. You were once upon a time pretty good at football. STAY IN YOUR LANE BRO!]]></document></documents></author>