<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@aaroncarter thank you for sticking up for Michael even when it's not the "in" thing to do. especially when he can'… https://t.co/7iFhZUBNB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RagingGayCons @Barbiemacs1 dont they get paid already??? Why do these dems look for more financial support to prot… https://t.co/AhKDR3L0wI]]></document><document><![CDATA[ Um, excuse me , I'd like to inform you that I'm the cutest baby in the world  @ Montreal, Quebec https://t.co/KtPi3SsoAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching every girl tell Colton she loves him on their hometown date #TheBachelor https://t.co/CIi4u22lYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our @POTUS doesn’t mess around😎  Trump to expel dozens of Maduro loyalists from the US https://t.co/2qfLuUIFgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[THATS A GAME! Pitt wins 16-13 against UCLA. Liz with 4 goals! 5 panthers with 2 goals each!!!! WOW what a team W!💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TealHeather Happy Monday dear Heather. Have a lovely new Week. 😘😘 https://t.co/Ju9YI8f9tL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“3 Children are a heritage from the Lord,     offspring a reward from him. 4 Like arrows in the hands of a warrior… https://t.co/xbtPXKRkVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@bababooeylover #fatty #rufus #BernierNation #DonaldTrumpSoldAmericaOut https://t.co/9lW5BBrRXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[50 years of making her life a living hell,Ann passed away before her time. I don’t know why they married. She was G… https://t.co/H91yKG5vZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tburgerd @mrub22 @DevinNunes @TomFitton @CPAC @ByronYork @LynnePatton He wrote personal check. Cohen even said tha… https://t.co/QZGrHVQqQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GioWFAN @Alsboringtweets Evan and JJ together remind me of a Discover Card commercial.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gallerychapel @kimguilfoyle I don't know what's bigger, her fake boobs or her lips.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neumannsj Pero,pero a quien salio el nene? Jajajaj Imaginate, hijo de gato caza raton. Felicidades al campeon y a los orgullosos padres.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Home Design your own dream house in My Home! https://t.co/qTxjMheRTq https://t.co/4vKurhqRnq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretHart @wrestlecon @NYHiltonMidtown AWESOME BRET !! Can't Wait !! See Ya There !! https://t.co/FhCWjVmXxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was just ranting to some girls about how in love I am with my girlfriend on PUBG lol I’m in love love]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks honeyrs for taking a break during your busy work trip to visit us. It meant everything! Jack enjoyed you, to… https://t.co/CKLiUTVQtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We decided (last night by the skin of our teeth) that this household will observe a sort of pagan Lent for the next… https://t.co/31UmjzCauF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmmm, melania plagiarized Michelle Obama and trump plagiarized HRC. Jealous much???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerturbSecular @clhubes Or a camel or alpaca - she delicately rode any animal, riding like sex personified, yet al… https://t.co/pC6KdFmyjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 ways to use #GoogleForms  in the classroom #1 Opinion Surveys, #2 Quick Poll to check for understanding, #3 Autog… https://t.co/lNxif3pysz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC How interesting! #NBC is crying that FDA chief #ScottGottlieb resigns. Look at their explanation! Gottlieb, wh… https://t.co/r8MLIubUc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This beauty, my granddaughter Kaitlyn is 18 today!!  Where has time gone? Graduating HS in 2 months!!  Onward and u… https://t.co/yiDQN0GirE]]></document><document><![CDATA[how im gonna be waking up today, knowing i lost an hour of sleep #DaylightSavingsTime https://t.co/ScuRDR0Vzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have a small to medium sized dog sleeping on my chest. i'm in love w him]]></document><document><![CDATA[grin with me. How Cute Are You? I got charmingly cute with a panda as a result. This was... https://t.co/p3uggcZ4yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crawlergraphics idk about 10 but i'd love to see rico nasty, megan thee stallion, 070 shake, saweetie, and sno tha product forsure]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hurray for small worlds! A million heartfelt congrats to @jacquijarrold and the whole company of playgoeswrong - En… https://t.co/M7iTLJEeOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ONTSpecialNeeds @SPCToronto @TVCCfamily @mykinark @ErinoakKids @CHEOhospital @mch_childrens @HandsFamilyHelp… https://t.co/T94GwGC02c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bttmlssmmss I mean, one patient sat in a wheelchair by her door pointing and spinning her finger at me, so I can o… https://t.co/ai2BxuzujK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brother I don’t want to hear about how my real enemy is the system. I’m no genius, but I do know that system you hi… https://t.co/z0i2vRhj2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST LISTED! Look no further! This stunning 3🛌 2🛀🏻 detached home in Old Markham Village is a show stopper! Quality… https://t.co/giFgjy1rhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, this is pretty fancy! Srsly, very proud of this multi-page spread of 13 photos by Jeremy Liebman. Thanks… https://t.co/2sgjVBsZFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop letting your past define you, and start letting God REDEFINE you as you continues to work in you and through y… https://t.co/AYXoqLjIhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also you can be bi and only fuck men/women/no one. Why the fuck would I care? Being bi is neither beneficial nor pa… https://t.co/p0dnJUYeIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plans for Spring Break are to remodel our laundry room! And of course rest! Lol #ceroarschallenge https://t.co/melkURSJvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's an understatement,I love the picture of Mayor Tory,it reminds of when he says "I did this,and  I said I woul… https://t.co/vPBBxohm0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[bro ok i live with my plug and he “takes back” sometimes and i’ve noticed but been quiet about it and i’m in my roo… https://t.co/mWipyfvNJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shawn172510 I’m on the 4th and nodding off. Looks like I’m going to have to finish it later today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC The art of selected amnesia has been perfected by the democratic party!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yaysh gonna regret drinking last night. She gonna say she done drinking but its gonna be a lie 😩😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuenta la leyenda que si ves a Said y está despierto puedes pedir un deseo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_nykki_ @ExposingDanWarp @SHEROKS @TheHimmmm But was Whoopi even there? No pictures.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that's some CARnage right there #Daytona500 #TheBigOne #LameJokeAlert 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOOO adventure-ready... 🌍 Adventurous boots ☑️ Map print leggings ☑️ Globe necklace ☑️   #ootd #ootdbloggers… https://t.co/vxqOroJpho]]></document><document><![CDATA[I 💗you Spanky! #Repost adoptspanky • • • Guess what guyz!!! I'm supes happy in mah foster home!!! I snuggle on da b… https://t.co/QXyoYYo43T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiiii 👋 I’m live now @ https://t.co/lcfw744b3E  #fortnite #girlgamer #SupportSmallStreamers https://t.co/hQZKBH0K2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skyline Urology to Pay $1.85 Million to Settle False Claims Act Allegations of Medicare Overbilling https://t.co/n5ls6mGbCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kanthil is amazing.  Half of Bollywood relies on it to soothe sore throats and keep a strong singing voice. I just… https://t.co/5a37dtGnLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosie_trew just be honest and tell him what’s up. he might be upset right away so give him space. if he’s still up… https://t.co/CgYLVxKmdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy how it’s ready been 7 years since we lost my papa.. that fuckin sucks 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rotskullrich who I birthed at home in our tub, fully submerged as our midwife rubbed peppermint essential oils on… https://t.co/EkOvuUVWGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep need to retire that FOSSIL McConnell because he has no thoughts of his own anymore he is 45 PUPPET like 45 is f… https://t.co/yRG9YagZbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhpostman @850Sunny @LisaSmithTX @BibleAddiction @threatsr @Sammieheals @Comfortwilson1 @tracy_sherrod @rbstill2… https://t.co/c8iHveNP9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @CNNOpinion Yeh right he has gotten out of his country to cheering crowds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great point from @SpanbergerVA07 on #TheHillWomen116th panel. Female lawmakers stick together, but obviously there… https://t.co/7LnuU4ZVCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattmorain yes if you s/light beer/hard cider and s/dogs/cats, but I assume those are non-negotiables. ;-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emotwink666 La película es Gentlemen prefer Blondes y la de negro es Jane Russell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going into Saturday like 💃 🙌🏼#aggiebaseball #familyf1rst #baseballgirl #ballparkprincess #growingupattheballpark… https://t.co/c2ONEcvCzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catiemonster I don’t remember what that is like, I only know this frozen hellscape]]></document><document><![CDATA[#releasethevisas #saveh2b @realDonaldTrump @SecretaryAcosta @SecNielsen @IvankaTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amiraabutuniss bout to sign up to perform for whatever’s the next event !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babilarat   https://t.co/hiAf2ZPj1j (los lyrics de la canción salieron una vez que me quedé a dormir con ustedes y… https://t.co/ZSZgvSJquQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a cop in a Tahoe pull over a Smart Car.. if that didn’t just look like the school yard bully 😭 #CanTheyEvenSpeed 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I proceed to watch law and order: SVU when I work late? Knowingit gives me the creeps when I walk out to my car]]></document><document><![CDATA[Event Hair by Susie@Hair Lounge Salon Washington DC @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/N66M6uU5Fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go figure on my day off and I’m wearing wedges. But I needed a day to dress up to look and feel cute. Also.. doesn’… https://t.co/gxAvhMCxYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight is definitely going to be spent crying all night :-) &lt;3 how is your night going?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unhappycanuck @humourme1234 @JustinTrudeau Uh huh.  So many "credits" under Harper.  Looked good but did not much.… https://t.co/Z4X7QC1eyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MADITCHIDA  You realize everyone can see this post about dying for your boyfriend😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always #NationalLoveYourPetsDay when Rico is here... https://t.co/oMbDOmjOAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my bitch period 😘😘😘#Legal @nahbrizzle__ https://t.co/JVyfj5nyqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkHertling I love that you’ve done this. This old teacher has learned a lot, and I’m grateful for the time you’v… https://t.co/736PHfOiZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, after listening all day, @NKOTB The Way is giving me @MusiqSoulchild Forthenight vibes. That groove is too good… https://t.co/RibH8XyjXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙌Raise your Hands if you LOVE LIFE THIIIIIIS MUCH! . In this Grand Space - the GC - I found TRUTH, INSPIRATION, HOP… https://t.co/4H4NaW5dpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all need to use this site! You enter the batch number and it tells you the date it was made. I just checked a sma… https://t.co/JmvzOp6UA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DomSyndrome55 YES! So short ribs with sauteed onions and mushrooms with maybe some garlic? Deglazed with maybe red… https://t.co/F32LmaiAd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday my roommates are in the kitchen whipping up like 5 star meals and all I can do are breakfast scrambles. I… https://t.co/D5z6ZiO2xJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeirinDC @jesse_marioneau @eshaLegal @AOC @IlhanMN My RT was not support-just saying🙃 Soo many people were asking… https://t.co/DeBYqEP0gB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 10W-40 by @HiWireBrewing @ Beerthirty — https://t.co/TheKfJHvy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HolyTrinity_97 They give me life everytime th3 crackhead hitting you in the head was my fave]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love bubble sequencing night! Can’t wait for #j262A &amp; #j262W to work with DSLRs... so soon...but so far...]]></document><document><![CDATA[North State AAA girls third place game is underway here at Heritage. Starkville Academy taking on North Delta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PearlMiskel Oh, geez!!! Hang in there, Robin. We’re backing away from the gate now for the 4th time in 8 hours, so… https://t.co/11nnUAXJxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m not the only one who watched 1/3 of Baywatch, and immediately just wanted to watch high school musical]]></document><document><![CDATA[I not know that the 1686 Peeps with Meee read the information contained I just sharing that the information is avai… https://t.co/yMIJlQ2wqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I’ll be heading to London to visit the University of Oxford in less than a month 😍#DreamChasin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeeganMKey We were very upset to hear friends from college was canceled! Any chance it may come back? What can we do to bring it back!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 1134 10Th Street Court #Hickory #NC  #realestate https://t.co/ydfie89KRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Say, why don't you pressure the WH to get Trump to testify under oath? THAT would cause everybody's head to explode!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pskills43 yo this guy stole your kicks! @Raptors #RTZ https://t.co/RDqLve2kWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job is now open at Charter Schools USA in #LakeWorth, FL. Follow us and turn on mobile alerts to hear about jo… https://t.co/VSNrEw0nIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisChristie You are the perfect man for the job. He can be your personal project. I’ll wait to see how it turns… https://t.co/VeoPKiORSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewhamLynn @CheryReeks @PressSec @BennieGThompson Yup...but he continues to lie to his posse of kool-aid drinkers]]></document><document><![CDATA[sang Umbrella by Rihanna at karaoke and I did her justice hahahaha lemme tell you]]></document><document><![CDATA[April Dominguez crossed 20K. Time 01:49:03, pace 09:01 min/mile, est. finish 8:57 am https://t.co/4db9a4RUQo #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #Fuentesfriday and #SanValentin2019 the gossips are on 😋 And I’m listening 🙃 so I would love to hear my follow… https://t.co/HE9SEJqDnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heroes Judy and Dennis of the #matthewshepherdfoundation They are dedicated activists and crime survivors who to… https://t.co/pbKVMjM92z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chelsea_Elaine_ Wow, the answer was right in front of me the whole time. 😆 https://t.co/hWZ1IpVklV]]></document></documents></author>