<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I wanted to speak the truth so I went outside @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/abuUJd4Bu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charles__LaRose @DusseCognac @TIDAL @planes @RocNation @S_C_ My boys bought me that a few years ago for $350, they… https://t.co/Um9EgX2Khw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Adi Penugonda on being elected DFL Party Secretary. @ Eagan High School https://t.co/7rGuVZAnjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[”There is no doubt in my mind that I will beat Rhonda Rousey” -Ruby Riott  #EliminationChamber… https://t.co/jGIvka4JvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in Incline Village, NV? https://t.co/EcszyAuoP7 #hospitaljobs #Clerical]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Stand By Me by Ben E. King on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/xLv4zi5FGc thank you dad for dave]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristinBTate is a total bad ass. She is a brilliant writer,  and probably smarter than you. @FoxNews… https://t.co/T5Uv5E2out]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best way to pass time at DanceBlue #DB19 #FTK #itreallyDBlikethat https://t.co/RS9BxcMZz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLFlyers @ctalbot33 zippity doo dah.  We traded a young goalie for a over the hill mentor]]></document><document><![CDATA[What people forget about 2016 is that Trump was afraid  to run against Hillary so he targeted his ads against Bill… https://t.co/zCHm9R4pSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am grateful to my parents for raising me on Classic Rock.  Really let me relax on car rides or CD player.   Just… https://t.co/r9Gb2nnacZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sean Hannity and other idiots that makes a living telling conspiracy theories and just plain lies to keep their sho… https://t.co/0nEktkEk4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really wish Doom Patrol's Cyborg was on this Titans' show, and this Vic Stone show is cooler looking than the film… https://t.co/sTV9RJBh3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from @layubraska  -  Solo el que ha pasado por esto entenderá y valorará todo lo que ha vivido , y a los q… https://t.co/avMz7WPu06]]></document><document><![CDATA[New map shows every forest matters in helping save the Javan leopard https://t.co/u6fcKXIfwM via @Mongabay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@summitfred Quand tu restes pris comme ça avec des Summit y’a de la neige en ta 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every one was very vocal about Trump supporters and particular "situation" now that is proven that he lied about be… https://t.co/goWUIfncnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google, Apple Called Out For Hosting Saudi Government App That Allows Men To Track Their Spouses' Movements… https://t.co/P395t9mG0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Samiam1321 @EvelynNFarkas @MSNBC @kwelkernbc @NBCNightlyNews Cleaner than any Trump Hotel! In Trump Hotels, all th… https://t.co/BWCoD2c7kc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaySaidYeet I wanna ask why you do things like this even though no one gives you attention for it but that would b… https://t.co/HUn3RjWiBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nature of The Town #mural spotted from the train #ArtFromBART #SeenonmyBARTride (@ BART Richmond/Millbrae in San Fr… https://t.co/3NczbUM61t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah you got the hood Trippin, hollerin good riddance couldn't run a business if you had assistants...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are all the brilliant liberals who bought this clowns story ??? How about condemning what he did with as much… https://t.co/9pyKiVBOKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been watching some documentary’s about white supremacy and it oddly intrigued me how they think. I wonder if I… https://t.co/hUHBKXiVHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are there legitimately people out there that believe Claude Giroux is better/ just as good as Crosby? Like people l… https://t.co/iAQy5AsVUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[last full week in Kentucky. get at me while ya can @ Owenton, Kentucky https://t.co/MEgxeZjLME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 @Top_Sergeant Give me a break. Stating if Trump is impeached there will be a civil war is another… https://t.co/czCkZtCNpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sully_Mane They didn’t know how long it was gonna take Goku to recover, they didn’t know how long it would take fo… https://t.co/9TfqQNCWOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry your delusions are unfounded. Remember Trump is for the rule of law. The tactics you suggest are only used by… https://t.co/O6LLmEalr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goss30Goss @sianoresist I went to a military high school. Nobody ever fired a shot at us. Not once. I wouldn't tru… https://t.co/bZzs6IFeHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cole_westwell26 @Ottawa67sHockey Agreed. DM me your email and I'll send them over]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 9 @NashSportsRadio , it's the @TSU_Tigers Basketball Coaches Show with @TSUTigersMBB @coachpenny1 and… https://t.co/n5Zozp8b9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mfs be showing up the computer lab 5 minutes before class to print a fucking bible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @SteveDucey @JackNece @basilsteinpdx @Cameron_Gray @IlhanMN @RacismDog Interesting. So can you help me… https://t.co/qQ5qb6fPWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[get you a man who tells you you’re beautiful while you’re walking to your car after rolling out of bed 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza Just the democrat party are in full fledge crisis. It will get worse in 2020 when Trump is reelected in a landslide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johniadarola @AOC We live @AOC! She scares the 1% we her common sense. Real facts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shiftygrifty @SimonBranney That was too cool to make production, you know how this works.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HPluckrose @Panda85Myers It will take that kind of zeal to attempt civilizing such clearly culturally bereft souls😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mick_muldoon @Scarlett_Ohar3 @MikeStuchbery_ @gillksharp1 @tom_watson Snort.. I have friends in high places in the… https://t.co/4e9rduZngp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsTheBrandi Lawd, ain't that the truth! She's the most relatable. Older Black woman who works at the post office?… https://t.co/udKgCQn7m8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it me or does this look good in every driveway I park it in.  Maybe it will sell this house today.  #forsale… https://t.co/pXrfBUq4Bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurtMyers I sure did, growing up in john fortin &amp; chuck steuer’s garage, chasing around my father.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crusaders: Thy Will Be Done Review @ETBoardGames @TastyMinstrel https://t.co/ieewzZ1cBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[104 Wilshire Blvd 104 Wilshire Blvd, Santa Monica, CA 90401 https://t.co/bTEI1uoSBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #Pittsburgh be sure to stop by @TMobile at The Pointe in Robinson for FREE pizza, giveaways and amazing deals!… https://t.co/jjrWhL5e4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know this, my dear brothers: everyone should be quick to hear, slow to speak, slow to wrath, Ja…… https://t.co/PP2lDLcb1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight! No-Gi Jiu Jitsu @ 7:30. AL are welcome. We have a drop in per class price and a monthly price that include… https://t.co/xVGefk4T6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Manchu Mile by Bullfrog Creek Brewing Co.  at @BullfrogCreekCo — https://t.co/Zz4P7cpXrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a young woman doing her make-up on a moving bus, and I dare say I'm impressed. #Buffalo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Who paid for Omar's college education? Inquiring minds want to know]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited for all the excited newly admitted students to @ucdavis class of 2023!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFromCranber That about sums it up. Sick of her. Like to see her in prison garb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sixty One by @dogfishbeer @ The Thirsty Beaver — https://t.co/kQM5APzUvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol/omg. The ‘online knitting community’ (what???!!!) mobs her cause her excitement over a long desired trip to Ind… https://t.co/WN1Y7QTAkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open! (@ The @PretzelBakery in Washington, DC w/ @esussna) https://t.co/6CyAm8XOBY https://t.co/6pZzfNuxHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kodak mentioned weather control... he got locked up ....21 immigration and flint water...he got taken away ...there… https://t.co/wCwJ9LCN2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 11 Texas Tech wins 7th in row to stay atop Big 12 https://t.co/mWeToY9vJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we just gone  skip over dude getting popped in the head with the ball ? ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AprilDRyan @MichaelCohen212 See Gym , he takes responsibility for his actions, unlike you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pyramids sets include a lot of volume. Following an ascending set scheme, increasing the weight on successive sets,… https://t.co/hH6QHR9qhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHARITY ATTACKED Because Vic Mignogna and GoFundMe! Jessie Pridemore And... https://t.co/5VCNzePCSm via @YouTube #AnimeGate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennajameson @1776Stonewall I think he did it for the same reason she gave this statement. They are both nobody's… https://t.co/dnIjxFtH44]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveWeasel I have had my #mustache since 1967, long before it was cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhein_wes @RussoHockey @BDifronzo I’ve realized that a long time ago. Most fans won’t. We need another answer to t… https://t.co/yDLb6hVPvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look gorgeous and feel amazing in my vintage Chanel. #redcarpetarrivals #oscars #chanel @ Academy Awards Red Carp… https://t.co/qGRUWwgy5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatchworkNerd I have yet to make it to a single reunion. It was 25 last summer. There are about 10 people from hig… https://t.co/qyrEM0anEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@republic2019 @gkboyles @sawyerspeaks @nytimes Maybe so, but the hat in your profile photo makes a great portable toilet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes The indifference or distain shown to “others” around the world will soon be thriving here at home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnAr59452888 @GeekToMeRadio @UpToTASK @CBNostalgia @GeekVibesNation @BrianLeeOkert @MikeSchmidt09… https://t.co/jDc84LaWT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLongCon777 @FindMaleficent @amvetsupport @realDonaldTrump He stayed in the country and didn’t run to Canada. He… https://t.co/7rflN4vMrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@96TiI_infinity_ @Millican123 @TheLesterLee Odell team isn't out here winning championships]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelodyMonae Figured this might be an easier solution instead of assuming you know who I am https://t.co/ePZb4YAhlS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FalselyAccUK However, a federal judge ruled Alabama’s sex offender internet reporting requirements and branded ide… https://t.co/voDhxgbWdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@airforceneil3 @MSUWineGuy42 @blainewheeler21 There should have been a trail ref with a better view. I have reffed… https://t.co/YIhiyNcuCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s tart, but it’s nowhere near a “shake.” Buyer beware. - Drinking an I Quit Solemn Oath by @solemnoathbeer @ Rad… https://t.co/IOQ5nu8NFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul What did you do for you "Day Job". Did you cross paths with @VDHanson He is offering his Trump is a good ca… https://t.co/xj6Z148qrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤦🏻‍♂️ Look, I can't if Tulsi is just super zen...or if she took a Xanax 15 min. before she went on. Again, she's sa… https://t.co/KqAjqz3VZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaytDomschkeWx @NewsLink_BSU @BarstoolBallSt HAHA your face at the end 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abdalla24983350 @dwnews They are the scum of the universe and I have zero compassion for terrorists and their grou… https://t.co/VmKuI31DEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish it was video. She CRUSHED a 2 RBI triple just after... @ San Marcos, Texas https://t.co/c7rAFwRZEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was lucky enough to speak with @rox_anne_b at #SXSW. She's awesome and I'll have the full interview later, but sh… https://t.co/Hj19FKdz13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Get well soon!! We are praying for you! And your family too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oscar it's your turn Sampson, "Wakanda Forever" https://t.co/CwqDgfTQMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HDTimRamirez @Michelle779601 @THD_LRHarris @Tenney1R @Mark_Cuccio0358 @ChrisBergHD @ThdKelly Congratulations Laure… https://t.co/b56weCcuNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @HIVAIDSCaucus @CDC_HIVAIDS @sexpartnershiv @HIV_AIDS_Bio @CehpaKenya @HIVStoryProject @AIDS_United… https://t.co/MTdDo2lqRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulmares72 Please you guys do the same. I’m just one man but we are many. I’ve been putting it all over. Help me… https://t.co/X8KpD6VkSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fl_invest We can not wait for this conference, looking to take advantage of an oppty which will not be available n… https://t.co/Nw5358mDk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Maybe because most people fear the unending attacks from idiots like you and the media]]></document><document><![CDATA[23. Best place to meet awesome people? Twitter, obviously. https://t.co/LFVqHbszc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[-sometimes you have to go into the abyss to break the habit, because finding your way back may make you better...-NACHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen. Lakey just admitted he would kill the bill to get rid of mandatory mnimums. He will not allow a hearing.… https://t.co/AabeWB8t8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cg_patriot @Ray7Cincinnati @realDonaldTrump Yeah man our President is something else. Man for the TIMES. MAGA 🇺🇸🔥✅]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨PSF✨ are here at @HomeDepot Store 4164 East Reading Pa doing a Sika Self-Leveling Underlayment demonstration with… https://t.co/jR8arY4jjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlobeChadFinn Do we know if the Celtics are on Kemba Walker’s list?  Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I have to say right now is I’m currently hyped up on way too much caffeine and getting work done, waiting for the inevitable crash]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out The Green Book: Guide to Freedom on Smithsonian Channel Plus @SCPlus https://t.co/77WVDhynOw #]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessewente To paraphrase Neil Young...  🎼 Trudeau, you’ve got a wheel in the ditch and a wheel on the track...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los invito a escuchar @RadioValparaiso hoy a las 10:30 AM, estaremos conversando acerca del deficit de infraestruct… https://t.co/fOxaEYewaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omgggg  Our first Christmas season sa elbi.  2008. God. It's been a decade! Hahah.   @blmckttnz @nielasedillo https://t.co/XLtEReMzyl]]></document></documents></author>