<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Eat pray love... esta es una de las mejores citas que he tenido con el mar.  Abierta a las infinitas  posibilidades… https://t.co/88fWiVvSA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucked up my knee, had to get emergency oral surgery, and got dumped all in one week so the past 3 days have been l… https://t.co/a2Jq1P9Ila]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come home to your heart and soul so that your mind doesn’t get in the way🦋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still stuck in a Disney mindset, but is that such a bad thing?🥰✨ @ Walt Disney's Magic Kingdom https://t.co/rbHBuZNxr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klerdanes @boojiemainedoza U dont get it do u? Maine wasnt expecting that. She thought they were friends already a… https://t.co/Dnf7JlC9ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of SPIRIT WEEK! We have Ss who have dressed up as their hero's! Batman, moms, Michael Jordan, Serena Williams… https://t.co/aBjv28FyrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[and then Arnold told me that the Pastor had them rewind the videotape to those mornings bc he thought I was going t… https://t.co/xXo8sqXjb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RottenClinton1   So can you elaborate on what Trump has done that is worthy of praise from someone that is not ben… https://t.co/gH6kEWoblv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The former high military leader in #Venezuela tells he will recognize #JuanGuaido as the President of the republic.… https://t.co/Vn4tSGI50Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielmarven Thought the saying “sleep tight don’t let the bedbugs bite” was just a myth to scare me. Until my gro… https://t.co/yQGRt30LcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE IT. Need this all the time. One of my favorite sours ive had in a long time. ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ - Drinking a… https://t.co/291jeAbgjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow @Bravewriting if you don’t already. Be warned: she is having no mayo. Zero on the mayo. Carry on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman The President selling Chinese access do the GOP approve of this? How do you explain the sex raid own… https://t.co/y2o3iXMMGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love @target  @targetstyle marktaylorresidential #marktaylorsweepstakes @ San Cervantes by Mark-Taylor https://t.co/jsLJoeQgTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And she dealt with one of the most difficult periods in the Observatory's entire history – – in effect, 2 different… https://t.co/5qoxps3NA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekend Update: Smokery Farms - SNL https://t.co/yafeKVpI3A via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grupo_Bronco Como  siempre seguro serán unas súper canciones  como solo Bronco sabe interpretar éxitos  seguros y… https://t.co/dXE8mEy9Ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realtor life X milage...... to say that I drive a lot is a understatement. From Lake Mary to Celebration, from Wint… https://t.co/JAXvlImRu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long time coming...but this #SundayFunday is my very FIRST show on @MYQ935 from 10am-3pm!!! Sooo excited to be back… https://t.co/FYai8V2qqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk who needs to hear this, but turn your fucking keyboard click sound off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImpracticalOni @GamefullyUn Indeed! It was still fun, though! So was walking out and trying not to say anything to… https://t.co/bzX7AX4Q1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Southbound HWY-99 traffic is at a complete stop from olive drive to white lane]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DuluthCurriculum in @nytimes story about batterer intervention classes https://t.co/hNqLTaqiXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@G_Spenny4 @Red5xStandingBy @ChelseaVivian12 Bernie’s got my vote because he’ll destroy America the fastest. I can’… https://t.co/znEzK2zd9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhiles2760 @ProudResister @realDonaldTrump They were having a meeting‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yikes! Flooding at Reelfoot Lake @LocalMemphis is serious, be careful folks @local24john @Local24Chelsea @Local24Ed… https://t.co/aL30zoQjM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just impulse purchased a discount Dutch oven so don't listen to anybody tell you I don't know how to party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashliwilliams12 *only takes old tennis shoes and a dog puke covered towel and leaves half a graham cracker*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uncontested...winner of the Gr 3 General George S. at Laurel Park 2-16-19...Trevor McCarthy aboard for trainer Jen… https://t.co/a073qDPoVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roheblius A player, I can’t tell who, has the OG Falcons half-zip Starter, like Dave’s Sharks one! Fresh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SupportingConti @TaynaraContiWWE @shirai_io Thanks for using my photo for your icon! I hope you like it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisarinna When I saw his interview with Robin Roberts from Good Morning America I could tell he was lying he was b… https://t.co/0wOkmaIZg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lyricoftheday  “I wouldn’t if I were you. I know what she can do. She’s deadly, man. She could really rip your world apart.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your anxiety when you’re finally having a good week https://t.co/Va1Mm7vzlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VancityReynolds @goaliefitness @ChrisCandy4u @TheRealJenCandy Love this guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t get too close, cause you won’t find what you’re looking for. I’m in an independent mind set now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LisaBerry Just so you know @_LisaBerry YOU are a big inspiration to me. You have such a beautiful soul and big he… https://t.co/lhZSHrATGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[As an American, you have the right to and you need to visit your State Capital to voice your opinions and make your… https://t.co/yWRbHl3XfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful thread that is worth reading. It’s hard to find reasons that make life livable when times are dark. Rea… https://t.co/RMaNflQbsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThankfulFor The sanctuary of refuge and renewal that my home has become for me reminds me every day why I go throu… https://t.co/hAYQDuqUNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manueloliver00 @NRA How brave are the people like Pelosi, Giffords and similar who stand up to meaningful threats… https://t.co/lGOv40r064]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guillearcay @guillearcay envíame tu número por privado. Necesito saber exactamente qué está pasando con don Franco… https://t.co/mrWju0mT9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Further, it wasn’t just pro-lifers who she ridiculed. You’ll find a more complete list in my piece as well as all t… https://t.co/V3AUhtaOuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiseleRoberts1 2 pairs of shoes because it doesn't matter how comfortable they are it will hurt. Have fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MistyChristie08 @Kimberleannn @thenikihughes Just make sure to take it into the post office to double check  :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris apologize to conservatives‼️Lynching law? You aren’t fit to serve in the senate. Resign☑️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my lunch today- did you?   Nice to see a few vegetarian options for us folks. Great job everyone who particip… https://t.co/jzwcrEo4tO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lindsey Sharp M D Bariatric Medical Director at UNC REX Hospital Raleigh NC runs a 6 month training schedule for Tr… https://t.co/GF2vR3mXT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fun day reading to our classes! Can’t wait for the book characters parade!  #ReadAcrossAmericaDay #gatorgreat… https://t.co/Gnob9Nm2Ts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parody is comedy, comedy is apparently something you don’t understand.  Besides, why are you even watching #SNL?  A… https://t.co/s00U40KhSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SideHustleWino @RedWineCats @DivaVinophile @GailBenzler @magee333 @Julianna_glass @boozychef @wineNweather… https://t.co/cEG6J6z0iB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1! I’ve accepted a challenge from @RakiyaBrown to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews --… https://t.co/TYczDIZQEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[And thanks, as always, to @twsobey for instigating this fun madness! #unsexyvalentines]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Federic80124621 Buenos días @Federico  un saludo a distancia..!!👋👋👋👋👋👋👋👋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @misschris_ED for adding to our French Fries cup! https://t.co/kv7dknj9Fp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my Goobers.....Coco has Fern have the Life don’t you agree??  —————————- #adventuresofcocochanel… https://t.co/cGtgsavyDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[God has called us to be the light! Let your light shine bright and help others do the same! Life is not a competiti… https://t.co/w0IRilaqLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha it’s gotta be my hoops!  My chola hoops as Mickee calls them.  #takeoffmyshoes #takeoffmyjacket #wait… https://t.co/pJdGoatjxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj "Police" what Joe Barton said when he yelled out "You Lie" at an Obama SOTU speech...And then you can "Pol… https://t.co/3uENoHCj1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another beautiful Saturday hike on the west side of Phoenix. https://t.co/vJ913mh36o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved Valentine’s Day even when I was single for twenty whole years strictly because my dad always had something… https://t.co/KM0oWkFfAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #personaldevelopmentjunkie Tuesday and this repost from abraham.louisehayquotes really caught my eye last week… https://t.co/KK7PU5ObaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My last card of hands to play, and my biggest project atm, all about to be unveiled shortly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Validamentre @MoishesMom Vale, pls tell me amt, #nycacc. I'll help. Mary Ellen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABMartinez1985 Of course! Stacey is our 2nd cousin and when I saw this I knew it was him. I’m going to share on FB… https://t.co/k15khA49FY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to step up to the plate and be in charge even if you don’t think you’re ready! @Levine_Alison  #CUNAGAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn't watch but I completely agree with you!!! Painful deaths for all of them!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is whack. #CrazyBernie #Socialism #AmericaWillNeverBeASocialistCountry #]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krislynne1001 I will be outside your office rocking this later 😂😂😂 #somepeople #wtf #trueromantic]]></document><document><![CDATA[It does make a HUGE difference if you send me a text, snap, a tag, call, mail or an email. I appreciate you for thi… https://t.co/ARtoXgaiE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I’m eating a hamburger while wearing hamburger socks how cool is that???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LacyClayMO1 Thank you, Congressman!  You have it absolutely right...whether D or R...this is a giant con game.  A… https://t.co/r9a3I87XwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Lauderdale, Florida https://t.co/7gkwBUTzxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playa Vista,not far from Culver City. Sad irony is,it's a predominantly Latino and Asian area. What a racist piece… https://t.co/C4qf6pB5j2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NELLY822 Please help by ADOPT/RESCUE/FOSTER/PLEDGE/DONATE/Before its to late for this beautiful little one and she… https://t.co/Uyd6UF4k95]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next stop on my learning journey @nearpod. T, stopped by and was gushing about it... That kind of teaching exciteme… https://t.co/3Cow3cUcQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Springfield wasn’t shady af at night (really anytime of the day but especially at night) because my ass is r… https://t.co/gHRHDc14It]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LintermanLab Glad to have such a cool sister lab. Definitely need to plan a joint retreat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Port St Lucie new homes mid $300’s text/call 772-224-1634 or communityinfo@comcast.net #floridarealtormillie… https://t.co/VZYCopliU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers This statement reminds me of a chapter in Roots when white ppl broke into the family home and excla… https://t.co/9QRYSOs6iZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liv: So Drew Gave me this Chewbacca bow this means we are going to get married right?  Me: 😳 No it means he’s a goo… https://t.co/nrRf5d8dDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just read @kaytichristian’s article on @thegoodtrade and I am hooked on this Enneagram stuff! Brb, going to go list… https://t.co/3PRBvi4O4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hastings Broncos WBB just beat Dordt Defenders WBB! This will advance them to the semifinals of the conference GPAC… https://t.co/YOOyQDl95m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry but if you don’t speak spanish you are missing out on the real chisme 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[look at her driving a motorcycle off a fucking bridge https://t.co/H6FhOmBA2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susan_artiga @Vovchick22 @FLOTUS @HillaryClinton @AOC @IvankaTrump Well, he is who he is,  and he does good things… https://t.co/S6maLReAUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[having to forgiving someone is hard, but the hardest part is learning to trust one again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeblow745 Had to buy my first reading pair. Not happy about it but it does help!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise Yoga! Happy Sunday!! #happysunday #thestruggle @ Olympix Fitness https://t.co/IFmYkw6CFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1: I feel that at times, time management can get off balance if you don’t balance time at school with time at home. #20StrongChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giselle1900 🆘She looks like such a sweetheart just longing to share a couch with her best friend‼️, hoping she get… https://t.co/I8Kk0OPLIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I like other tweets people I follow like because I just want them to know that a random stranger like me… https://t.co/R13cVZrLW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Abortion’s should be illegal!” Okay Brad when you knock up yo side piece and your wife start asking questions https://t.co/Ec9KcJ2glv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am... brave. blessed. determined. a dreamer. fierce. fearless. thankful. strong. 💕🌟💕  As women, it’s important we… https://t.co/z7hys5TFKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad and I always talked about going to see the ducks at the @PeabodyMemphis. I thought we’d have more time. He’s… https://t.co/WYZlaw8ZJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter 3 money wires from ole @MittRomney would probably change anyone's mind #hack]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pompeo rejects legal claim by ISIS wife: 'She's a non-citizen terrorist -- she's not coming back'  https://t.co/SGS0gksslx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattLutz93 @IronPigs @PigsRadio @VentingDaily @LVFoxSports Thanks buddy! Hope all is well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaithWalkPeace @Brenderm1 Congulations Brenderm! On Reaching 39k! Way To Go!💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[damn snapchat gotta have a “don’t be eye candy, be soul food” filter and gotta make me wanna be more wise and shit]]></document></documents></author>