<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[One of the biggest pieces of shit in the country. The black man who’s not even black raised by white people in a ri… https://t.co/gYRAQPslVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing I got for Valentine's was from my apartment complex... Sooo, yeah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m cleaning out my desk drawers for the first time since this summer.. and I just found a $100 bill... god blesses those who suffer... gd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok but the mental breakdown overtime, that’s not one thing, that’s multiple things.. those are SIGNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolfChannel @WGCMexico So to get this straight, even with a cable subscription with golf channel and NBC.. you are… https://t.co/YcwDzCZnzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another customer who chose to be proactive about securing their loved ones and property ...... It should be a rathe… https://t.co/5cNi1QrwpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse WHAT?? You are standing beside a draft dodging coward. I hope you understand that he can Rescind an exe… https://t.co/mIagb9nViP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Outobro #rir #19 😉😎 en San Nicolás de los Garza https://t.co/dY4jGU7Urf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#morningrun #jaxthedog #happytobehome #jayny #adk @ Jay, New York https://t.co/IKhP6AsxbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[real talk tho what happens if you don’t nut for like a month, do ur balls fill up n explode like a l4d boomer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ese momento cuando alguien te dice: "Cuéntame como era eso de los Raves, solo lo he visto en películas". Las canas me delatan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curious to see how much money the Chicago PD gets from this scumbag @JussieSmollett for their wasted time and resou… https://t.co/QfS8w3Fg3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claumarop @mlaboy15 @jibarobragao @jayfonsecapr @melissaivelise @ricardorossello Un poco antes como del 2011. Esa… https://t.co/1xPmU4mNXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Girlsurgeon I kind of feel for players who don’t like the franchise tag. So few players are candidates to be franc… https://t.co/8CZN2EkcC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StorybookColors @IAmUltimatePred You two are awesome. And I only met you via @FisherJillian 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTBritt Do you have any idea when and where the Pennsylvania High School Hockey AAA State Championship is being held this year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ted Staton, former city manager in @CityofEL has died @WKARnews https://t.co/5px0pTSXmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @TrumpsDC @mymynags @nancy_hamm1 @BRella315 @RoseDC11 @Rbigzs @heyitsCarolyn @TexaLonestar @Sekusa1… https://t.co/Nb3OVfKbTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another learning about #nyc...  It’s not as expensive as everyone thinks...  There are ways to live cheaply.   Whic… https://t.co/4G4zXEH3zE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billsweet When politics becomes religious expression, things can become dangerous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compelling video from Noah Ross. 4k Aerial shots, people evacuating cars in the streets, as well as footage of extr… https://t.co/1Y6OoOp9EF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morant is the 45th player in the 1,000-point club. He is also the 11th fastest to reach it.  Made possible thanks t… https://t.co/fkKtgKYta2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RGVReagan Completely agree. I imagine people upset with the truth in a report still hold a grudge with the person… https://t.co/aWoZPV82qI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why is there a question mark at the end of this jibberish?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vamos rayados! #semanadeclasico #clasicoregio #rayados https://t.co/t8u4mvD4mS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom Fitton: DOJ &amp; State Dept. Fighting Judicial Watch on Benghazi/Clinton Email Scandals https://t.co/dmwErZ5Z86 via @JudicialWatch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delusions_of @creaturelives33 Gummy vitamins. Of the cannabis variety.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar It is not working in Seattle. Employees are getting fewer hours and the jobs are facing automation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Bledsoe how are we not twitter friends?? Someone tell @realDonaldTrump I found the REAL emergency!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bniceloco One of you Twitter niggas please make a beat out of this PLEASE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks EmJ ♥️♥️ next one will be even more fun in a couple weeks. You the best!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lavendermee3 The tickets were free, from a friend, and, still, I was just miserable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #SmallGirls are excited to see snow on their school. Dad is excited to see school open. Who really wins 😂 @ Gre… https://t.co/YFvH48KNVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bru_lynn It's mostly the same. But they show more of his childhood growing up with the Danes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still sittin pretty at that 3rd worst spot and didn’t let the god awful Knicks win one. I’ll take it.  #Cavs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tevis_tevis @w_terrence @realDonaldTrump Of course, magamorons are STUPID I got fake news,called freedom Most valu… https://t.co/Aj9ZAMCo9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[This team is something special. Let’s hope they are gearing up for June hockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me queda claro que cuando emprendes un negocio es cuando terminas de conocer a los verdaderos amigos 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders What do you mean by “our”?  Government is not entitled to privately earned $$]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laceyadunn We should give God all our battle and let him fight them. He does not need our help to fight the demon we need his.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @TrueKofi doesn't win the #EliminationChamber match,  they should put him against the @WWE champion at… https://t.co/XJp8cO6smW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got to say @UncleCharlie5 Adam Wainwright is one awesome guy, and is great on Twitter too. If your not following… https://t.co/XvnT9eNEht]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moment that started it all. TB...whatever. Britain's Got Talent a few years ago. #collabro https://t.co/w3aupihzRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Channeling @scottbuscemi and @bbogens at Kona Club https://t.co/7Nn7WbIUoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indyzach89 @TheLando__ @NBAOfficial If it was me, I would tell these cheating refs call game fair or someone could… https://t.co/CWLay8vfj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CocaCola Y'all must have not learned anything from July 1985? Trying to fool this new generation, huh? Well the ol… https://t.co/F5P3z6GX4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second star to the right and straight on 'til morning.   #Disneyland #Fantasyland #PeterPansFlight https://t.co/Zv5mdS1vtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the set up for #Oscars2019 #AcademyAwards a lot of work going in there! #cameraman https://t.co/HJELsGd5An]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you stuck with technical mishaps and other issues, then don't be stressed. Dial our… https://t.co/8xseKeBSgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s creepy is Muslim men raping 6-7 year old and little boys look at shit Hole Paris UK Sweden. That’s ducking E… https://t.co/cJdbSxTimO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great memory from just after we got home from the hospital with Chris ... Yes, it was almost two weeks after he was… https://t.co/RYTWdUnIEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing what @janelmwrites has done with her @aintilatina platform. Onward and upward from #AfroLatinxFilmNight https://t.co/U6vKRy45hT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outside of #CMDR decks and my Cube, this is my entire collection of  cards 💪🏼 https://t.co/BNd1rCl58U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Thru Our Scars by @FApocalypse on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/IxBvFKYv5N https://t.co/5zf6sHUpmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donovan stayed the night at his homies crib and I already miss that little goon... 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeGinoB @BklynBckstretch Isn’t that the problem? There ARE other gambling vehicles that do not involve equine f… https://t.co/2souEOpmXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[You almost had him #paulfelder #UFCPhoenix #ufc https://t.co/92B064sulW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A friend loveth at all times, and a brother is born for adversity.” Proverbs 17:17 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[From my 2013 archives, my review of MOTOR HOME MASSACRE https://t.co/RVCbE05pRX https://t.co/66bGy5iKf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgetteHaupt @kimguilfoyle BOSTON MEDIA STARTED AMERICA I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Ea… https://t.co/VN4lB2jNep]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it's meant to be it'll happen 🙏 and I'm really hoping it's meant to be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mxhdi I had the realization a few weeks ago that I’ve never seen it either and that I really need to fix that — th… https://t.co/xnL0xnrsil]]></document><document><![CDATA[I... completed treatment back in January. I see you can read, but... just not that well, huh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jvn The only thing that’s problematic are you racist white gays. The next time you want to attack a black woman fo… https://t.co/3TP2y4tDge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look how bad A my pappaw looked in his leather jacket @ Weaverton, Henderson https://t.co/rpD0xB8i0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Says Borum has tried raising money to pay a voodoo healer in Raleigh. Threats were, "much different" than they orig… https://t.co/M9HyFmL6gx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meg_Y12 @DonnaNoble10th @GaladrielResist @DanaScottLO @tizzywoman @EffieResists @pru_fallows @porpentina2017… https://t.co/doE5Im6wKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbgraeber You wait like, a hundred and fifty years after you die and check back then. Also be sure to die of typhus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only love and respect for this man! I’ll see you skippy in 30 for some more rehab🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickwallace7 @CodyMullins34 Other things matter but nattys out weigh some things. But if you haven’t done anything… https://t.co/jGhh9n5EHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[When he doesn’t just “TAP” he sends a message too  https://t.co/peGg3fEM0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex_Fabiilli @BaySean @Shannon_Penn @TSteele814 Very factual though. They are both very much fraudulent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t been able to use @SinemiaApp for 4 months because I keep getting this. @SinemiaSupport  I’ve emailed you 5… https://t.co/W1RAo6N3qQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[if anyone designed a medusa head tattoo i’m sorry i can’t give you credit but yeah i’m getting that designed tattooed :)))]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurbedLA Because renting is smarter... It keeps you fluid. #SmartMoney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_christiannodal coming to Beaumont next month . I think I will be making that drive 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[The OG Shark, indeed. Glad your dad is back on the coaching staff. Feels like it’s 2008-2009 all over again. Coach… https://t.co/0lOsSazeuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @Reuters Hope they get their dicks knocked into the dirt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are as hard headed as I am, sometimes the Lord has to take you to a place of dying to really get through to… https://t.co/ru6zra31UW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey followers: I will be live tweeting an event for class using this Twitter handle around 3pm. Just wanted to put… https://t.co/ZwgPlDHNXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr @9975Ts Thought I'd help so I retweeted. Ha!! Mr Biden I sent an angel to watch over you but it cam… https://t.co/d9sfdv3qo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonSharpe Something U should know about Us Jordan/Kobe Fans...We don’t care about the “All Time Points List” w… https://t.co/cENINO4VUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoadRaider3 3 out of the 4 movies on there I've seen. All of them are terrible examples of relationships]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gus06paul Ugh, the only thing worse than that is freezing rain. Well, okay, about the same. Both not good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnVu47116461 @Chargers @blaqbadger14 Weren’t ready. Moment was too big and most Boone on the team had that kind… https://t.co/cnYGNpsUaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TabiTeach @ChrisMurphyCT Insurance is the primary difference there. Guns get registered if they’re purchased legal… https://t.co/ObYQ28EQLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lil_cutiee__ @_Gigisocean Dumb asses yall going to see each other bc were all going to be at yutz house lmao, I’m… https://t.co/tLmmr6g8eS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking my shot here: Titans trade for Josh Rosen. Let him compete with Mariota in camp. 2nd rounder if necessary. M… https://t.co/ZIvQVJVhZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loose #Leafs. Two #Oilers goals in the last 2 minutes, but Buds prevail 3-2. Geez. #TMLtalk #LeafsNation #LeafsLunch #LeafsForever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradTakei @GeorgeTakei Why do you call it gay marriage @BradTakei marriage is marriage. People fought hard for mar… https://t.co/oZMJDb3goK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joe_Rossi777 @RapSheet This is one of the most inept takes of the 21st century]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great win for @MiltonLax tonight over Cambridge! Cambridge made it competitive, but it was awesome seeing the boys… https://t.co/ywMVObxatR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also Lindenwood going 2-0 over that span including a win over #10 Washburn certainly earned them a spot in the top 8.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paw Patrol Live y'all (@ Fox Theatre for PAW Patrol Live!: Race to the Rescue in Detroit, MI) https://t.co/0cZ4cGGrkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redban @joerogan @BrodyismeFriend Suicide is crazy man. It makes no sense. I don't get it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad is building a new garage and he’s thinking about putting a lift in there. I would be so happy. There would b… https://t.co/5n7UrZpBJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaolaTrov 🖤 I think I read somewhere that summer is about 80+ days away I can't wait beautiful girl 👙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@exoZafar My hot take:  goodness yes let's colonize the solar system.  Move fully off-Earth and turn IT into nature… https://t.co/fiHXo1sf8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattvogt Working on slipping a double double in to a haiku? #SlamPoet #SnapSnap]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel really frustrated when @facebook , @Twitter , and @instagram Bloc me from their sites for violating communit… https://t.co/6pVKbZNysI]]></document></documents></author>