<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Two years ago, after going to the animal shelter.  We took a walk around the nature center.  It was so relaxing jus… https://t.co/oANA1su4nE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was greeted with my FAVORITE EASTER CANDY, from my granddaughter #koolkennedy 😚 someone put their trash in my 🗑 c… https://t.co/S1SHupcSEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing is better after an 8 hour workday, 4 hour lab, and drive home in a blizzard than coming home to a clean apa… https://t.co/VVdNe0KtlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelalucard666 @Michael53991477 @PDunn99 @Alyssa_Milano So you didn't mute me, just checking, all of you Trump su… https://t.co/hQk45FQw5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for voting for me on #musicash ! (See link in bio ) I’m going to post this article on Facebook tomorrow but… https://t.co/SLnKm0OUdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SherylArellano6 @PATLIEPATROL014 @patrickquiroz_ @itsmeangelieofc Oh my god 😍🥰😘😜ako ang kinikilig]]></document><document><![CDATA[L2 Youth All Around Champions, Lily Richardson and A Natural Dancer https://t.co/Ck4lxsgwpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richzeoli When people flee the North east, you are one of the things they take with them b/c that Phila-NJ irrever… https://t.co/gW94ANg1I0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh... you know, traffic in The City. This light has turned green six times now. I’ve moved up 4 cars. Hope everyone… https://t.co/184yuGDmXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuxsiempre Yo aquí tengo mis bailarines !!! 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🐶🐶🐶🎶🎶🎶#DiscoBebana aunque Otto no sabe el pasito !!🤣🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/46F8p8ibIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@defrostedshrimp OH 😂 see i didn’t know cause I thought he got it too but... 💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I managed to get some chemistry between my hair dryer , brush and hair. . I did it all without suffering a bump on… https://t.co/hrC4HAiO6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have my first night shift today. Pray for me and if you’re by Banner Desert bring me coffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coal’s other dark side: Toxic ash that can poison water and people https://t.co/POzYNmeYSx via @NatGeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canadiandaws83 @cathyhadenough @alisoninsco @Mommandem @CunningSq16 @ShapesBlue @DoloresManley4 @roseoleary58… https://t.co/YatTcIfNd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg every 5 seconds I was screaming “WTF” you will be left speechless 😦😧]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Mondays we makeout. Join us for #MAKEOUTMONDAYZ tonight presented by #rhealitre we are serving up $5 drink speci… https://t.co/KYbS6n3Zfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jadabird I did the same thing, walking and texting at night on sixth street and fell flat on my face and busted my lip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fizla718 Have you ever seen Misfits? Klaus plays a similar character in that and it’s 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[7:00am: top of the world, direct deposit came in, feelin wealthy 11:00am: depressed because of sorority dues, going… https://t.co/vwBE66a9Yi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan  you sleazy fucking slimeball. Your questioning of Cohen was a LOW point in the ocean bottom low of the… https://t.co/2bDCWyJb5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you love when you are talking about something specific &amp; the other person talks about something totally unrelated? 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sino pa bang magpapakalat ng fake news tungkol sa #NasaanAngYolandaFunds maliban sa nagnakaw nito na wala ng iba ku… https://t.co/03rwK0r05U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cards on sale now! $44! Here is your Guardian Angel of the Day!   **Link In Bio** for more info!  #fairydusttones c… https://t.co/ze8BFtwNsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prayingcitizen Hi Lori, I just want to thank you for your videos and your commitment to God, it's beautiful.  I fi… https://t.co/qVGjIWL22K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter What exactly is your problem with Trump’s emergency declaration? Need more publicity for yourself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw this seal back in September while running on Bridge Street. I can totally relate to how content he looked:: f… https://t.co/9EMgQtFI2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[a fewness of words &amp; an abundance of deeds. i love it @justinbaldoni]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is  in my calendar, excited to attend this November https://t.co/ssC1u7aVon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blensky35 @chefsymon Wonder bread, ICEBERG lettuce, yellow mustard, bologna.    And scene.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FinanceBuzz @OrderChaosLife @thehill I understand that you made a statement that you would go to a jury with a pre… https://t.co/KpYhhL6jyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gray  went gray.   My first full on attempt to transform an entire head to blended Gray @ Jupiter, Florida https://t.co/9biChdWvtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have lost a fish. And not as in it died, as in I have no idea where it is. Like he's not in his tank. How does th… https://t.co/jQkhrzD5sw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ClientBrittneyP @brittneybad_azz  is getting in some personal training live with #GloryFitness #gotthatgodjuice pr… https://t.co/CnKOf5fgz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the feels 🥺😭🙏🏻♥️ • Today was just the beginning of a really challenging week and set of weeks. And my ♥️ has fe… https://t.co/x5BDu8fmKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Valentine’s Day — First date night since having Addison. It was a lovely evening! And it’s so true what they sa… https://t.co/oHulIGc6ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the @ZipsFB players who volunteered today to give our students an extra special PBS incentive!  Our Bu… https://t.co/hvILgA8M8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier More like What you are now allowed to do, when and how, or, you WILL forceibly and possibly painfull… https://t.co/5a75VIn1bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cómo es posible que alguna gente no hable español... si se ven más latinas que mandadas a hacer. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytdavidbrooks Before tweeting responding think about reading the article along with https://t.co/Yp0IP1hJeE and https://t.co/7aj5YIzwJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[if anyone tries to pull shit like this on our flight @LilMsAnalysis I SWEAR TO GODDDDDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought my google docs apps was the notes apps, so I was talm bout some shit on there. Wellll, I forgot to share a… https://t.co/YgzU2JOd0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio No one in US or the world can imagine how terrible the situation is in #VenezuelaBlackout]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m over here worried about the game tonight while @RybaFlavin and @John_Fron are upset that it conflicts with The… https://t.co/bmTtfCMwkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be careful not to underestimate me. My heart is pure and I love hard but Idgaf even harder!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuntsmanAbby I disagree that because AOC has the biggest following that she is the face of the Dems. Just because… https://t.co/z7DLT8KnQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect makeup tutorial for Spring /Summer nights with my daughter, Katie Moreno! WATCH! LIKE! SUBSCRIBE! Thank you… https://t.co/xzuBn2SFJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so excited to have sun again but that means i have to shave my legs and i just really fucking hate shaving]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently emotionally eating pop tarts and Cheetos like I just went thru a breakup. What is wrong with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ltvargus I feel like I screwed up my cats socially. They meow at other cats and I’m sure those cats are like WTF man??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HC_Turk So was y’all boys you know we gotta put on at every function ‼️‼️‼️‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow looks good on you, Boston. @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/GOW74jlOod]]></document><document><![CDATA[First recipients of the #women #entrepreneurship #fund announced https://t.co/U2x68jvLLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waited 364 days to post this picture 🤷🏼‍♀️ #burntthepizza #itsokidealcardsnow @ That's-A-Some Italian Ristorante https://t.co/LFJqVv2oQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thangel77 @VincentCrypt46 Yes but remember red gave us Bush! So maybe it's red now because it's the lesser of two… https://t.co/dxunlo9xq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieDiCaro I wasn’t into football at all whatsoever until you and @maggiehendricks started your show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscars week wonderful time  at the Oscars gifting party hosted by Wow Creations thanks to the @harristwins… https://t.co/R4brmuCgxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCHLunch They hand the kids breakfast every day! It’s a way for our counselors to see everyone of our students everyday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 years ago today you left this earth so go see our heavenly father. i’ll never forget any of the times we had toge… https://t.co/VDVLvSKOqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally all I want in life is to be able to fight like this but I lack the motivation. I wish Kakashi would mater… https://t.co/KPPkJy6iti]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all pray for my girl @madyczarnecki her heart is hurting and could use some love]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 39th week of my pregnancy I have been active but I am becoming more and more miserable. This baby needs to come… https://t.co/7GNVgpmm5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyinternationalwomensday from #cougarcon at csusm! @ California State University San Marcos https://t.co/9SaJR3gva0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cut my 2-mile run time to the lowest it’s ever been today and I could not be happier]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr @rwallace19551 Why do tax payers PAY for PRIVATE insurance for Congress? Most of you are over 63, GET… https://t.co/Dsgp5h3aKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[😋Yums indeed! Lord another “commercial” that is out for the kill.💀  This is unfair! Illegal even @BTS_twt  [롯데면세점]… https://t.co/FLZzlun8eR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A cat has been coming up to our door and he’s stray and needs a forever home!! We would keep him but we already hav… https://t.co/f9sFLPw8kW]]></document><document><![CDATA[California Earthquake Authority @CalQuake is one of the world's largest providers of home earthquake insurance, 1M+… https://t.co/al4ilsLxHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posted withrepost • @boyengateam Happy International Women's Day to all the #PropertyNerd women that keep our team… https://t.co/qs6376cdnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perks of being a homeowner: a shit ton of shingles blew off and now it’s going to cost a couple hundred to get it fixed🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s only 8:30am, and my day is already completely made. https://t.co/p0MYn9yW78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *is trying to be healthier by eating better, working out, doing yoga, meditation, going back to therapy etc.*… https://t.co/PsFZ2BmFCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Y9TD1lk2ch #impostersyndrome #notgoodenough #yougotthis @ Maximize Wellness Counseling &amp; Coaching https://t.co/Epx1F6cCnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw Isn’t It Romantic today...and it was ERRRRRTHAANG! Go see it! @isntitromantic @RebelWilson @ADAMDEVINE… https://t.co/zI1BnTBh4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hotelsdotcom I’m Getting Tired Of This F#$%&amp;#g Snow. #WinterSwearJar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejosephkeith You’re tripping if you think banning people is a form of promotion. Promotion is building people up… https://t.co/kh2QIPjGhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiremaCtlink i sell fiber optic patch cord,drop cable,splice enclosure ,welcome u send us inquiry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I suddenly obsessed with @ShawnMendes ??? Particular Taste?!? That’s some groovy sexy sounds right there 👂🏼🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abrishvet @Rachell30632434 @likemelak @TamagneB @AlMariam1 @Achamyeleh1986 @AlemuReeyot @reyotmedia @eskinder_nega… https://t.co/Gi0WuMtcEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collaborating with this dynamic educator is always my pleasure! We appreciated the opportunity to share research on… https://t.co/Iz6VHHN6cN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baja_bIast I had a paleta de arroz con leche today and it reminded me of you LMAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DHWrestling6 watching Justin Oliver wrestle for NC State in ACC championship https://t.co/4kied7IARv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are a CROOK!  Trump raised with acting AG Whitaker the idea of getting the U.S.  attorney in N… https://t.co/fBx2Dk18SY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHPRA Looking forward to working together - MCNZ and AHPRA on some common issues]]></document><document><![CDATA[Julie Miller started the Princess Fairy Tale Challenge! https://t.co/pHfx4gSlk4 #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff This is the guy this bunch of grifters should be very afraid of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First real meal in Phoenix and it was delicious!!! #culinarydropout #pretzels #cheese #ribs #deviledeggs… https://t.co/zfVIbePJ2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered The Ultimate College Giveaway from @Contiki x @Groupon https://t.co/WXzBDYV4rB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciation post to these kids right here❤️ Beyond grateful for them! Thank you for making my last year as a coach… https://t.co/6rWhN5TS8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArchyArchJ @AnnaNotaro22 @MrDane1982 @HillaryClinton She’s walking as though her feet hurt. If she has plantar fas… https://t.co/YwoSwvz7ZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notkerouac @LONGER_DRIVE @EJF_215 Hi there, first time long time. Was wondering if @EJF_215 wanted to role play as… https://t.co/9KcSkkviko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Most everyone i know, Republican or Democrat, wants better border security and to fix our broken i… https://t.co/GLmiKOIyW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Help I’ve fallen and I can’t get up.”  #TrueNorth provided free  @Life_Alert and monthly service to income eligibl… https://t.co/FFNLkrvX8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simple Salad Dressings That Take Your Salads To a New Level - https://t.co/cggA5NXZKK #salad #healthymom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askUHC Yes approve my chronically ill son his relizorb medication for his feeding tube. To get a letter denying hi… https://t.co/QkyvsUWzED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending my first gymnastics competition today.  NHS is hosting. ISHAA gymnastics state competition 2019. https://t.co/c6Oe93Rufs]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the privilege of being an American? The right to vote. Why should an illegal who is not an American have th… https://t.co/qaQArOKeGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always convince myself I will wake up early the next day to do what I am supposed to be doing right now lmao and… https://t.co/vtDV8nfU9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes im genuinely convinced ill just never be good enough at anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Premiering a BRAND NEW video today on my channel to #LetsShutUpAndDance by @jasonderulo! Set a reminder and come wa… https://t.co/GkQdUMeiVF]]></document></documents></author>