<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ChicagoBearPaws @MasonEaton16 Patriots Kicker would be a great Fit in Chicago 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkoCortes @AccionNacional Gracias por tu apoyo Presidente #SisePuede]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did volcanoes contribute to the demise of the dinosaurs? - CNN #volcanoes #dinosaurs  https://t.co/JoIuTVY5TP… https://t.co/gkbU4QwLDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#threescompany #studygram break #actorslife🎬 #actor #writer #producer #director #screenwriter #saturdaynight… https://t.co/TVhA1kO9kv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 whether 'tis nobler in the POTUS pate to bear silent how they investigate or blithely tweet with fierce r… https://t.co/fh7XQAvOXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You need to go to better breweries. That’s like saying “Cabernet ruined wine”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@komali_2 @sh4rkface @AirMovingDevice @zerohedge Your right, I forgot about CERN.  Wasn't that started by two perso… https://t.co/iLrM8Up4wD]]></document><document><![CDATA[No jumping in the pool this year @SufferinBa5tard https://t.co/wPDmKq1YBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@business Our first #Vulcan President failed miserably, but he did so knowing regardless of how poorly he performed… https://t.co/amyAz3XiX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antoniehodge @stephendpalley @NeerajKA ...and what's the dress code?  Thinking of having a NOT YOUR KILL, NOT YOUR COW shirt made...  :P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicsluo Gabbard is really good, perhaps Tucker Carlson could be her running mate]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, yes, tomorrow’s game to decide who will play in Saturday’s CIF Open title game at Golden 1 Arena will be played… https://t.co/QF6yuBvW0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgeltzer @CNNOpinion He’s going to win in a landslide. You’re worried over nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fras99 Put them all together they spell M O T H E R  oops almost forgot the Jack Daniels.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re not getting rejected all the time, you’re not applying to enough things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afdcaptrb Might be a little warm in @NHL_TampaBay  in June for the Cup parade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferJJacobs @nwadhams That and the fact she was woefully inexperienced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deputy whose rehiring spurred outcry is ordered to turn in gun and badge https://t.co/Wdio7SOlh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CJMitch73 Personally no I don’t think that makes him better. I can get similar power numbers and steals from likel… https://t.co/YzMfl9FKUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cashmere, Chinook, and Sabro.... Solid offering. - Drinking a Coercive Forces by @3magbrewing/@SingleHillBeer @ Cra… https://t.co/s3XkYKiIvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppSame @realDonaldTrump @HillaryClinton @JohnBrennan @FBI @infinite_scream this whole system of lies and backbiti… https://t.co/5RqJwTWp8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best developments from last nights draft had to have been the connection @ScottColeShow and @Dirk_JDR ha… https://t.co/Bu05LCWruQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every team that has played us in the past month and half has had players that turn into Steph Curry and Clay Thomps… https://t.co/NoaiOOdanD]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much for the snowpocolypse 2019 @ Bogota, New Jersey https://t.co/AqwlUfs2kW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spike's in hell. Spike's in peewee hell. #LittleGiants https://t.co/lNuxdK2lSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBurneraccount @excitable_mike @StapeAthletic He's actually been above average, which is respectable since coming… https://t.co/aaf9gGHUoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvonnaCadaver @YoutooAmerica @AmericaTrendsTV @TheRedBoothShow Earth call Marsha? What sort of name is that for a… https://t.co/7glbQIajxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[No porque digan Fuera Diego Alonso lo van a despedir, y si no les gusta lo que ven, simple, no vayan al estadio 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rickyprep @TexasWBB @statesman @Big12Conference Warren is tough and I'm proud to have her represent the University of Texas. Hook'em]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today  Later  I will travel to get closure on a 2012 and a 2013 open case  RIP JAMS + D  -Steve… https://t.co/RapGQVactQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me - “We should make like a we want you style poster for CEO volunteers rather than just asking”  @PheNOM07_:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet everybody says I’m crazy when I talk about the athletes back in MJs era not being near the athletes in today’s… https://t.co/gPhFDo9EQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump is there a law against these people? put them in prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ktheintz @mehdirhasan @IlhanMN You seem oblivious to the fact @IlhanMN's thinking and @DrDavidDuke 's thinking are… https://t.co/3fCgFG1RNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DEADIEGUERRERO_ Took the hoe from the top ropes.. I was in the school resource officers office like this https://t.co/OcXvthxOmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine getting your ass cut from the age of 5 ..... just for being born in the country your whole family has lived… https://t.co/12rrJaF0OK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @pattirod55 @OutlawedMind @Dannaja64Danny @JaackSchitt @nuwriter @caruso_ric @alllibertynews… https://t.co/BVssDoZy0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pitt historian Sam Sciullo reminds this is second triple OT between Dixon and Huggins. First was 2010, won by Pitt,… https://t.co/fQY71vqvtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sino hay detenidos y procesados políticos de alto nivel involucrados en los actos de corrupción citados, todo segui… https://t.co/lCi6XkZrrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work 3-11. Day 2 of 5. (@ ROCKTENN-Mishawaka,IN. in Mishawaka, IN) https://t.co/EjVdsCpiil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliansRum Same tribe, different state (Connecticut).  A lot to unwind here. Quite the number of mindmines to unra… https://t.co/uNbPlFDmpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDailySampler Have some coffee. All kinds of stuff will come to you, probably ruining your day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where in the world does Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez live?: https://t.co/eR16Co0xtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micheal_hester @Mavs_FFL I get the whole modern day center thing but I just don’t see it working well with kristap… https://t.co/ZyN9uxCyyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshliePJackson @MNPS_STEAM @hadleymiddle 😎. If you can ever get some of the stronger stuff. I used to get it off a… https://t.co/mM0FBWI4Qu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes Hey dipshit, do you want to know how I know that you don’t know what “socialism” is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pixie_casey They think it was all Nirvana and Oval Office blowjobs. We’ve successfully hidden the horror from them… https://t.co/CW4k3uWMCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oasis65 the mix line is exactly where it was modeled to be on all the high res models last night. They said it wou… https://t.co/0Za4bw2iLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tomlin_Sense @AB84 Unlike #bABy84 I listen and show up when coach says!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hop’ville Elementary (Vic Secret) by @lastingbrass @ Lasting Brass Brewing Co. — https://t.co/c7qhnsnAjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Convicting piece of evidence: the bullet that matched the murder weapon was found in the flower box.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMaherNews12 @News12 @eyesonislesFS @Offside_Tavern @Section_329 @IslesGirl3 @islesfanrico @gothambatman14 This is terrible]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of our @AthleticsSLC WBB team in last night’s effort against the @FanshaweFalcons - Both teams put on an ente… https://t.co/71Q1pPiQw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[A couple of my favorite shots I took at the KISS show in Dallas last weekend. #endoftheroadtour @ American Airlines… https://t.co/lmVbYar0a6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unless you want to make a suspension bridge. You probably can’t make a suspension bridge. Maybe some of you could make a suspension bridge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torrabbit @chapchae Same reason it feels like Black Panther came out four years ago and it's up for Best Picture a… https://t.co/0yi0SW0RLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraDonchey @ChrisVHolmstrom Uh oh....it's like an Eagle's Nest redux.  5,4,3,2.... where'd the love go..🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithGrossman @cacy_kasha @Justin_B_Smith Congratulations and best wishes Keith.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delicious - Drinking a Collaboration Without Representation by @DeepRiverBrew @ Bottle Revolution 3  — https://t.co/c2Vg8SWas8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keiramunsmith @MLSFemale Did you see this thread? Informative about FCC’s and kits in general https://t.co/75ThH9lF7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught an early screening here in Philly. Crowd forgot their were watching a movie during that part 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[the fact that i’ll never get to see avicii perform live makes me so sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secos @brooksrunning Nah. Those are perfect for the Lincoln Half Marathon on Cinco de Mayo. #RunGuacamole]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh wow Players Only broadcast of the All-Star game on TBS yeah no thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@potsiegirlsarah Mine was condemned too, but is now being rebuilt by #meat &amp; water! #MeatHeals🥓🍗🍖🥩✌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[!!!! @thekillers in Deep Ellum sold out in 5 minutes but I got tickets for @emilyastack and me!!! 🤗🤗 https://t.co/KB9NeHNyjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @trashtvaddict @pitsagainst @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/4qSzT8VOyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sleeping with my girlfriend is @CyborgAngell sleep chilling my bedroom life forever. https://t.co/W50FIRRB9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[We want to congratulate or WCMS Athletes of the Month from January. @wchsathletics https://t.co/itshoy6QxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treywilson757 I know u love @virginia_tech . How’s their baseball team? I’m off this week. Start a new job w upmc… https://t.co/VCXyMnIyeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[proud of myself for always loving w my heart instead of my head but somedays i think my head is gonna put a stop to… https://t.co/6VykPO40MC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn't get any better than #beerschool friends, sharing cellar reserve list treats after school! - Drinking a N… https://t.co/oAHSYftAQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hatchjenn This is definitely something you @LuciHasFun and @Perfect_Tommy26 should check out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to be on GOOD DAY NY on @fox5ny talking upcoming song, film, and life! Thanks for having me! 🙏… https://t.co/gjnHxUcWQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJ_Swagg07111 Refs making their own job hard in b-ball. Too damn sensitive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alanreid87 @TheEagleist Pipeline, Amazon, Google’s Spy city... Canadian politicians will trample over any ethics f… https://t.co/RWlR0apojA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me with my alternative music workout on this Monday morning. I had good workout on this Monday morning by celebrati… https://t.co/M1BDlZivFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsnebulabee You should check out Project Gutenberg - tens of thousands of free books.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when I want to check in with the writers on shows I like and be like, "Hey, do y'all need us to send yo… https://t.co/0opRrD0tv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDash109 @CBCNews #cdnpoli I sometimes  wonder which independent journalist , newscaster , or pundit has been off… https://t.co/s1GUGNIvH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dallas @NBCDFW had a story about gas meters close to the roadway being hit by cars. *3600* (THIRTYSIX HUNDRED!!!) r… https://t.co/VcoETh23cq]]></document><document><![CDATA[take time to smile. Trying to keep a sense of humor when faced with "helpful" advice :) https://t.co/DZ2qmNqper]]></document><document><![CDATA[This hand shook simoncowell hand! @ Pasadena Civic Auditorium https://t.co/0rN3Sd8qMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to my one and only. I know I can be a handful at times but you always are there to remind me… https://t.co/od6hrvZHTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coach_fc Hello mate. It is a copy of The Boot Room magazine by The FA. Here is an online version - issue #1. They… https://t.co/ANp9AMjZ4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery I know they are philanthropist, so they could take their additional tax savings a donate it to non-pr… https://t.co/tqlTDHSYUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@JTaggart02 layup extends @McQuaidBball lead to 71-68 with 1:46 left https://t.co/63DajPyz3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris__Forsythe @RobynUrback @acoyne Pure conjecture, since they haven’t been in power. Maybe, but until they actu… https://t.co/CtVsmRXzRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literate ApeCast Ep. 72 — The Death of Luke Perry, the Humor of McSweeney’s, and Rolly Pollies  https://t.co/wAmPfa1Ky5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aidachavez @sunrisemvmt He's putting it to a vote, what more do you want, you morons?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomp_julie @maya_cantrell Chiming in as a recent TikTok user ... I endorse it v much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetsbyCoachP Logan Montilla, class of 2019 pg/sg 21ppg. 5'10" hard worker, sharpshooter, 1 of the top players ou… https://t.co/Yc0zrCymwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi You’re just a piece of shit!  Maybe somebody will squish you with a San Francisco shoe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALL BROWNS REMEMBER ROOTS TOMMY A MAN REALLY WANTED FREEDOM=THE MAN GAVE THE WILL TO BE INDEPENDENT\MY WIFE AND I W… https://t.co/9KwHZLawdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Discover on Google https://t.co/IdvJdfdPm5 Early Access did not hurt anthem what's hurting anthem and bioware'… https://t.co/I1y7sHjvCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw a FoxNEWS clip with Devin Nunes. He's claiming it is not Trump, but Obama who was Putin's best pal. Devin… https://t.co/fKeo6foMUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk how I’ve done it the past two weeks but I’ve literally got out at 2 in the morning on a school night... I look… https://t.co/Cz6AGgCZFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happened at 'baby church?' Toddler sex abuse probe ends without arrest at suburban Buffalo Sunday school  https://t.co/lcLcc7yA2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JEB_244 @Skins4219 @cbrownrun11 @RedBankFB @RBHS_Lions Congrats @cbrownrun11 !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially when, legitimately, contractors are supposed to pay for their own liability and commercial insurance.  T… https://t.co/lMTNoLxIvN]]></document></documents></author>