<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Majority of Americans do not want this to happen IMPEACHMENT is needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wordsmithI I know, right? It's crazy up there. Thankfully we are on I25 now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how this collage of Rowan turned out! 😊😍😘💙💖💕👌💯 (Please do not post or tag without permission) #RowanAtkinson… https://t.co/KnbY2F8muN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Twitter and Facebook videos in class is the ultimate dare devil move. One wrong click and it’s game over for you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kingdom for a writer-friendly coffee shop with cozy seating and long hours!!! 😭 https://t.co/LBqy76KVo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComicBook While it was a good film, it wasn’t great... but it still won awards. Be grateful not hateful...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrenIShiKiddo Good! Exactly what we want, get the hell out! Do you think you were threatening us with leaving? You… https://t.co/tSIRKtAsfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shipwrckdcomedy @BlakeSilver @JoeyRichter @heyclaytron @LaurenLopez1 @mkwiles @hartgracesarah Not surprised that… https://t.co/bYdOzlsOBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you pass through the waters, I will be with you; and when you pass through the rivers, they will not sweep ove… https://t.co/MI4ejCzrBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonsantamaria @sandentotten @abookapart It’s pretty great, yeah! I love a good reading book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just love getting home from works to no food, no left overs no nothing. But it’s cool cuz I brought them Starbucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stanagstevlfan @StanAgainstEvil Everyone I know. Because it is awesome!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajoeltaylor I’d say be glad you’re blocked haha, not missing anything there. She’s got gun girl vibes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only I would be stupid enough to buy a ticket home the week @AustinLeavens isn’t there...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emelia Fleck is a finalist for the 2019 AASL Social Media Superstar Award! Endorse her at https://t.co/zTNjfbvd11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyLovesTrump @teli707 @SusanDuclos @Kansasgirl1 @DLindsey2 @harjo111 @theblackpills @MistyLynn67… https://t.co/o8aPZcPZof]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think I can stay up much longer but Austin gets home soon so I gotta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aquariaofficial @shotwithsoju Since when is it a photo review and not reviewing the looks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FrielForAll: my boss and #KTLA news director @jasonrball had me as a guest on his podcast #thenewsdirectorsoffice… https://t.co/FD3xapU7nC]]></document><document><![CDATA[for someone who’s straightedge i do have an alarming fascination with heroin films]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to swing by the office to pick up these beauties. 😆👏🙈 Ty M.M., T.N., and a secret admirer... 😯🙊😬 #thankful… https://t.co/HGuoxjcaaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, I crossed the picket line so you didn’t have to, as a journalist... all I wanted to do is work on my rocket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Judge Napolitano Fox news says you have OBSTRUCTED JUSTICE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollywoodTed67 @lukedorrisWPLG @JulieDurda Awww like a hundred times!! Its a classic 😃👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry about my Snapchat, but @kelly_clarkson was so fabulous that I wanted everyone to see. 💞👑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milligram_c4d @JanePalpatine And notice the anti-Semitic imagery. Anti-vaxxers have a LOT in common with Nazis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @GOP @GOPChairwoman @RPRC - explain again why you don’t have time to read a BRIEF document? We will not rest unt… https://t.co/SVuTskVyEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time change is preventing me from lounging in my robe, at my normal hour 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[My personality is wearing a camo patterned Canada Goose... I leased a hummer and drove it around jersey in 2004! !… https://t.co/2pgALCl4SI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frangeladuo here’s Diamond and Silk at the White House today with Trump.........what a crap show this photo op is… https://t.co/IoFbHbQrWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMeadows #MarkMeadows #Meadows #CohenCongressionalHearing #CohenCongressionalTestimony #MichaelCohen #Racism… https://t.co/gPdFLpRDLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must Pray Believe andTrust God which creates our Faith that gives us strength to survive the obstacles that come… https://t.co/TbeOUEQk1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a rough night... just wanna go to my corner and cry out of frustration. By the way, thanks jackass. I sur… https://t.co/qrllrVOIKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamYouTube @BallingerMom @YouTube @YTCreators @PhillyD So in essence you’re punishing the victims and not the per… https://t.co/Y8oPgVyZbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crissangelNews Hi I'm making plans to see you soon I have to get some medical issues resolved in Seattle but I will be done by the 29th]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know what. I’m just gonna say it. a fever you can’t swear out really hits different knowing that brandon did no… https://t.co/EC0zeXnhOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which rentals might face inspections under three separate ordinances that will come before Omaha City Council?  We'… https://t.co/cGlelRX1Yx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSSacramento @LemorAbrams Look beyond your challenges! Wow what a beautiful message! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans coming for the haunted museum tomorrow!! @hauntedmuseum https://t.co/GDf5pJ34Fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don't need to get frustrated, it's slowing down our rhythm. We can WIN this game! I BELIEVE!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thenorthfour @eremiticjude I was so disgusted. Like genuinely ready to vomit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the next time I get to eat Wawa I’ll be living in Florida again 💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I’m mean af, so my girl gotta be just as mean... I don’t want no friendly ass bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gypology That good to hear.  Its starting to warm up here but who knows how long it will last lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half of me just wants to apply and the other half says I need to finish college first... https://t.co/gDsS8xKSfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“No corto los arboles” #KirbyShino #Lorax #DrSeuss #firstgrade @donaldjmock @ERESPrincipal @APSWorldLang… https://t.co/q47zv3yNJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattMurph24 We can’t let #45 win again!  Do not wast your vote, he might not be your choice but you are voting for our country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4thomsters @mmilky400 Ohhh I see!! Learning so much tonight lol https://t.co/ryuxK8NdWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Flex Friday peeps!! 💪🏼  I’m not one to take my shirt off regularly...but when you’re this proud of all your h… https://t.co/di734Th7GZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @JailTheTrumps Chosen by the Devil himself! Putin’s Puppet !]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not just their panic that's showing, their asses are hanging out there also!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieMartinSVU @Noochone @SVUWritersRoom wow good idea for #svu21 when we get #renewed tackle the rkelly saga #RenewSVU21]]></document><document><![CDATA[For you @DonaldJTrumpJr #loserson and to all standing behind you and clapping #shameonYOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it even a #texas #roadtrip if you don't stop at bucees ? #texpat @ Buc-ees https://t.co/IlfgiCayRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Share to complete your entry into the giveaway! Enter to Win a Cheesecake from Junior's Cheesecake! https://t.co/0EcmpYx4UT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think @SIRIUSXM knows I’m having a really rough day. Both times I turned my car on tonight, the @foofighters (aka… https://t.co/2mMYIQMw1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fedupperson78 @TheBeatWithAri @MSNBC @glennkirschner2 @SpeakerPelosi I read through the entire WaPo article. What… https://t.co/f9y4mjF9Yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tuckwitme10 Green Run did it with no problem bro! Teams at home want to play like LB plays and get up and down 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL I knew he had to be clowning.   the real Xhosa phrase apparently translates to “White people dont know I’m lyin… https://t.co/broricd7vB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckWendig My name is on my main course and I’ll send it over again to get the details.  I was born in a high lev… https://t.co/JKBTW80EHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have I ever mentioned how much I love Everytime by @britneyspears ??? And how wonderful sad and ICONIC the video is… https://t.co/oeXWTOChYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out my relatives stayed in the same hotel as Serena Williams in NYC while she went to Meghan Markle’s… https://t.co/toPKbkun5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[#shoptalk2019 Few of the retailers are thinking about this enough. Clothing and Textile Drop-Off - https://t.co/FslYeL4sN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsPeyton__ If it makes you feel better I have an online midterm due at 12 and my gps says I won’t be home until 1… https://t.co/DmkJRJCbxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirstenAcuna @UndeadRandy @reneenee652003 @HerculesHandy @jenben415 @LostSisGrimes @m_serda @boondock_girls… https://t.co/iBlaALi1KT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TedNesi @AGNeronha He’s leery about cannabis but ready to leeeegalize baby killing?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapCapra @BryanFonsecaNY @NetsDaily If they were real fans they would know what to say! #NoCueCardsNeeded 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Netflixhelps my tv app is loading my shows and then says this for every single thing I click on 😫 HELP PLEASE https://t.co/9nPI5XIi1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve only ever felt love once , I don’t ever wanna feel that shit again .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SantaDrunk316 @K_paige2017 @WonderKat365 @katton6750 @BreeannaKahoun @katiestereo @ScratchPaper8 @kelly__le… https://t.co/LTOUdQs9zq]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my newest #listing 6818 CROFTON COLONY CT, CROFTON, MD   21114-3275 #Crofton #MD  https://t.co/I7LOcHvikh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo The GOP today act like deaf mutes! Not one questioned Cohen when he testified before Congress. They wer… https://t.co/bJRK4Vtabd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oonziela @thereadingzone Vox me, too, Oonz—even though I don’t think I have Vox! I’d love to hear some titles you have in mind!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephDill92 We all forget! We are human! But making it right is the key! #champforkids]]></document><document><![CDATA[@softly_sighing2 I like cutting the tops off and eating them like giant oreo cakes😋 #🧁   #frosting is a must for me😔 https://t.co/h5txWsDLaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neck muscles are tight and popping. Anyone have a good cure to fix this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be careful, be courteous, obey the law, respect everyone; but if someone puts his hands on you, send him to the cem… https://t.co/SJS7hr7ViX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talktotuffy Good Morning Dear Friend How are you Hope you rested well Hope you have a lovely day 🌻💛🌻💛🌻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdegen8 thank you. i appreciate it. just hope it passes sooner than later. i hate feeling this way and not being able to do much about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorilegault50 @topboxca Thank You Have a Wonderful Weekend and yes Candy Crush tonight for sure lol 💗🥰😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2RoseAnn @KPRC2 Doing my Happy Dance for this fabulous family who adopted this loving adorable dog! Lots of Love !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snuggle monster... 💕🐾 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/JvhQZBiP5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[water or wine? don’t make me choose @ The Angus Barn https://t.co/BcEG1MFSTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're being use like Kraft's little sex worker in Florida.  You probably should stop taking the calls Lindsey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesley_jordan I'm so sorry for your loss. Sending love and hugs to you and your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carynsmart2 @marieosmond Praying.  I have a cousin who needs a live kidney transplant immediately, so I understand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are the new beautiful..y lo sabes EL EVENTO @roxanagarciatv dianam.espinosa #mujeres #mujer #roxxxywine roxxywi… https://t.co/lwpA6MmFVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Indigenous immersion program launching to teach kindergartners Kwak'wala | CBC News https://t.co/f8wXq7T4sI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else's dog try and eat their own nail clippings after you trim them? #grossdogs #puppylove https://t.co/ziO34DZEFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hurts me so much how I could of seen you 11/21 damn bro wide awake thinking about you bro, I love You mac shit kill… https://t.co/Hu9ftxXxrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[40° outside but we have wine and the sun is shining! @JRFabbio @Twtrlessavvy @dcn829 @ Truro Vineyards + South Holl… https://t.co/om9YmHp32n]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt to the days I had #siblingswhoswim and I spent 48 hours straight on a pool deck for the #khsaa #stateswimmeet… https://t.co/Zx1LGoG6EZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Car Seat Headrest 3/1/2019 I went to this show by myself and it was the best decision I have ever made https://t.co/zfERvya8FO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Site going live sometime this week...might even drop some lo-fi as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorTimScott is what I envision when I think of what a politician SHOULD be.  A person who is willing to do wha… https://t.co/H4gVyXDR98]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all oil is great. (Coconut oil is my preference) SOME of us have more issues with the blood sugar from the… https://t.co/UW2yUyKFCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdawsey1 Been there, done that. Talk about sore. Suggest” Break “in on HBO. Watching “OG” now. HBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[left Jackie’s astrology themed party and my face is covered in glitter....  the cane’s cashier said “what’s wrong with your face??”]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You can’t keep dancing with the devil and ask why you’re still in hell.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no idea how much I needed this song and video! #sucker #jonassistersarebetter]]></document></documents></author>