<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Usually I don’t post things like this but things need to change visit https://t.co/4bAsKIQcE2 to see how you can he… https://t.co/S4b7sug0iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day Emmanuel...I love growing old with you 💜🙏🏽🥰😘 @ Soho House Toronto https://t.co/golR11qc1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s finally spring weather in AZ so tank tops and officially back in the rotation! ☀️ 🌈 🌺 🌈 ☀️  📸 kathleenstagrams… https://t.co/7uCGsxxfA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: “Trump Declares National Emergency in ‘Slap in the Face to Military Families’” https://t.co/CWReuwj8q3 via @AmericasVoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@decolonize_this Ended up being able to make it, even if a little late 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oceanicseavey oh god aksks i hate layovers so much especially when they are so short oof]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need a date for a wedding next month... a dancing/ drinking partner to be exact]]></document><document><![CDATA[@streetartmagic @it_is_my_case Such artistic work, 👍🏻 it’s fantastically beautiful!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶 Hello  @TeachersCollege our old friend 🎶  were so excited for Dr. Michelle Knight-Manuel’s lecture!… https://t.co/X1HW0DvWIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul I am sorely disappointed by his stand as I believe failure of Congress to adequately address the immigrat… https://t.co/pCDSRghHJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Union_Jacky @jessix @Disorganised1 @LilyLilyMaynard Psst: recognizing that children have gender and ensuring they… https://t.co/d4a8HiCXKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[the official @VANS_66 man @JakeChams said it doesn’t work and if that doesn’t prove a point idk what does https://t.co/gJUjltWotm]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The cost of college is too high and has increased 300 percent in inflation-adjusted dollars over the past 30 years… https://t.co/m7mIFpANVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew I hated Vanya this whole season and boy was I RIGHT fuck that dumbass bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Takis with cheese just don’t taste the same without my boyfriend and a movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay but that HALF ASS NO EYE CONTACT salute?!? No one wants to talk about that?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[despite the crazy month i am having, my heart couldn’t be more full of love for this little valentine of mine! 💕❤️💕… https://t.co/7YTYLl3XtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, this is how those with deep pockets who want to manipulate the playing field and electoral process roll.… https://t.co/vxT465bdNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miami treated me SO well for my birthday 😍😍❤ #AbsolutelyAmazing ❤ https://t.co/kZcbWHVRRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HHLifestyleTrav Ugh, I was so disappointed after returning from Rome last month that I went to Spain two weeks lat… https://t.co/rifPHQpvqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Twitterverse! We are more than halfway through this action-packed final season! 😱 Its a MUST SEE! #ForGotham… https://t.co/U4vG67sGtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[SALINAS: Who all went to the grand opening of @Round1USA this weekend?! I was lucky enough to be the FIRST to hit t… https://t.co/RQRuI6U9BR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods And we thought this was as bad as they would get!  2020 ought to be a real circus! https://t.co/VQoZA0swCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[In between the hundreds of photos of poker players I’ve taken the past few days, was lucky enough to glance out a w… https://t.co/bxGlPyZAci]]></document><document><![CDATA[News of #AlexTrebek’s cancer diagnosis has hit @Jeopardy fans hard. For many who watch him, and even some local con… https://t.co/XQXCpXFiYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bryce Harper looks like he grew up somewhere between Roosevelt Blvd and Passyunk Ave. Welcome back home ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te cuento que pase mi vida entera buscando lo que por fin he encontrado❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Jade_Hugs_Trees in case you haven’t seen this - she’s so good!  The disarming case to act right now on climate ch… https://t.co/6Yenght6FH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wish things didn't go the way they did and I would've still been working with the kiddos in Zuni. Can't… https://t.co/mLh6sphOS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @MrsGroves23 to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations-just the covers. Each… https://t.co/FXvh5QT7QO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My car has to be jumped off every Monday morning if I stay home on the weekends. I wouldn’t be asking to borrow my car.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get to take my regular post work Saturday nap today my life is garbage]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4 I see a trend for @PlayCraftLearn, that would be my answer too. Use what they already love, Minecraft, for educa… https://t.co/eZKUqNdpq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kristinrssmith Lol, I know she said she’d be back before LGP’s bday (26th).]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you at Lululemon Westfarms on Sunday March 30th for Flow Yoga! I'll be representing @sr_yoga! We're getting cof… https://t.co/eCzsd1wiHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our farmers, worry about gold diggers, thus, can they afford to keep their parents land and work it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjfaison just watched part 4 of stalker video. Stay safe brother. And just want to say I have to translate you into southern lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Constant HARASSMENT....  UNAMERICAN...  WE HAVE LAWS PEOPLE CAN'T CONTINUE TO DO THIS HIS ENTIRE TERM.! NO PRE… https://t.co/6bnCp0eMOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win or lose as a team Rise or fall as a team 👑 @ The Downtown Hall Of Fame https://t.co/uyjwOMktNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dsmyxe @nattyover @blakehounshell It’s not assumptions. It’s the result of research meticulously undertaken by many scientists worldwide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathygriffin It’s not a spelling error when Cathy is spelled with a “C” and a “K”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever just have those days where you’re not feeling your workout?   Today was one of those days. Usually I’m… https://t.co/QjtIbcmcHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovHowardDean @realDonaldTrump is ALL ⤵️⤵️⤵️⤵️ https://t.co/C6cN6oYGn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RHamilton44 lol! I love when they want you to quickly give an idea of classes you could teach with a list of readi… https://t.co/S61JufULk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPaigeWWE @FightingWMyFam Hi paige I am going to see ur movie u really inspire me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are the greatest political hoax of all time. Sad, believe me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby SO?!?  Why does that matter?! He has been fighting for equality since the beginning of his career.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump @PressSec The national emergency is in White House. Not at the border.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, in terms of traditional media and the embracing of UGC, which forever changed how / why traditional media gatewatches / frames...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a man with a @GoldsGym membership that hasn’t gone but once since he got it to shoot his shot #bumpingbellieslove #shootingmyshot]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: Virginia 64, Louisville 52. UofL was outscored 37-15 in the second half. The Cards went 2 of 17 from three i… https://t.co/1Iqdoxc2YT]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 5995 E ORANGE BLOSSOM Lane #Phoenix #AZ  #realestate https://t.co/Y5o9Tmi6iT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer is this how AOC became a congressional representative? https://t.co/uczMVaYdn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dureyes @TransBridgeBus Yeah, that didn’t happen. They didn’t even bother to clear the ice off the top of the busI… https://t.co/qkztNkAbbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrOkpala @dremilym Some of the responders to the initial thread wrote many examples. But 1 of most obvious ones r… https://t.co/Bn4VbSbc7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come out and support the girls basketball team as they take on Glen Ridge today at Glen Ridge! JV at 10:30 and Varsity at 12!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waltrich3 Haha understandable...😋 Sounds like you’ve got a fun night ahead of you. Lmk what you decide on! 🤠📬🖤🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew this scene looked familiar 🤔 @JeffreeStar https://t.co/rgactWkGla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlphAthleteMgmt @EvanOdeseye Idk why I’m just seeing this. Let’s chat soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things are just amusing. #hilarity #tee-hee #grin #humorous https://t.co/JhLJ5qj5mq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martiwag @lesleyhenders @AmieLusher @ChelseaRochman @CezzaLew @PlastispherePod Refs to this paper should be struck… https://t.co/aiAN6kHIMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day down. Three more to go. @ Walter E. Washington Convention Center https://t.co/bZmwaLKuIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's just like, he moved on and all of a sudden i have a way different view of how much i must have not mattered to… https://t.co/lRaTSV9eej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wym? It’s like 2 conversations on snap and then a whole different one in your messages. 3 complete different conver… https://t.co/LzL6nS9UGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the Taxpayers money!  Give it back Gov Newsom!  #BuildAWallAndCrimeWillFall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surgery went well. They repaired the tearing in my meniscus. The outside of my kneecap was good but the underneath… https://t.co/we09yjqKRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluff_sports FB Varsity Tennis... its on!  Go Bluff! CPH https://t.co/mcoUYr9sIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sell like a girl 😂🌝❤️💜👱‍♀️ Roni B Sterin 305.942.7446  #internationalwomensday #realtorwithaheart #ronisterin… https://t.co/AzOGeZlkfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/0zUHK4TDT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday you Princess Warrior Goddesses! 👸🏻⚔️♥️ Love you girls! #lq#eq https://t.co/u3aNKJZ2kI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dejasoverit Chicken and wild rice soup, the modern caprese sandwich, and the fuji chicken salad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t label me as anything I ain’t your cousin, niece, homegirl.. I’ve only met you 2 months ago man..]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one ever gets upset about cancelling classes. Delaying.... https://t.co/r0Nf4GI2S9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeyLeyonce Ima wait til the summer so I’ll have time to get it right lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thouse of both Parties wanting to create Hate and Discontent should be eliminated from Office and replaced.  Includ… https://t.co/7ttUmdhk5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Intbel @realDonaldTrump Thank God that you are seeing how they are getting in around the Democrats areas! I still… https://t.co/mEgxWxKkJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerranceWill2  it stinks nit having family  when we go through a serious illness .. it was so hard for me but the… https://t.co/3e1yr0yIkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Becominggranola @_kaitlin_s Definitely! Travis and I haven’t asked for help from family since college, and wouldn’… https://t.co/MXt8t0lcxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dems consider President unfit because he brought back jobs strengthen military builds wall to protect border, broug… https://t.co/LmAFBDe00f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahaha I missed my flight so now I get to take a greyhound bus at midnight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caracowanwatts It would be great to have some of these teachers and students volunteering at the Tahlequah Public… https://t.co/TeydlohDXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abc27News please share Adams story.  Make the Selinsgrove Walmart listen.  We don’t want to lose him as our greeter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleScherzy I have 2 disappointed little girls who blame you for Rabbit’s demise this week on @MaskedSingerFOX… https://t.co/2C8ByLCADK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LincolnsBible @TurtleWoman777 Can I have it? Boston Cream Pie donut from Dunkin Donuts is MY FAVE! https://t.co/pb9SNg9DkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey life is overwhelming and the world is stressing me out but I’m safe in bed and I hope you’re doing ok friendos]]></document><document><![CDATA[SMOK series available Nord Kit #vapeon💨 #SMOK #vapelife #nordkit #podstarterkit #vapefam #hotselling #newstocks… https://t.co/m3NfYDX32m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaitlynbristowe Rosie’s not a golden but she is a retriever 😂😂.   She is the sweetest🌹🌹🌹 https://t.co/uTNwf03vxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have four dogs now and two aren’t me and Wills but honestly they all come to bed with me and they all are my babies💓🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[I WAS CHUGGING BARTONS VODKA BY THE HANDLE AT 18 WHO GIVES A FLYING FUUUUUUUUUUCK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec @realDonaldTrump What can we do Mr. President. Voting will be out of control in 2020! We are with you 110… https://t.co/qdOteXs83p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@56blackcat Ann did you see the Mardi Gras floats from around the world? We are scaring alot of other countries. Th… https://t.co/KRHZhWNxl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So no matter what our president does even the areas the Dems bitch about they will block his every move - it stoppe… https://t.co/AJlLq9EJ0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andyblack just took my breath away with this picture 😵😍 https://t.co/cpCn3SotvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jason Momoa is wearing a scrunchie and I have lost all ability to even. #TheOscars2019 #Oscars2019⁠ ⁠ #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJohnKennedy @SenHawleyPress “constitution” 😂😂 I’m sure there a law to remove that! Like Louisiana RS 13:4163 Le… https://t.co/LNIlKNJ7Ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[soccer tournaments and the bay&gt;&gt;&gt; @ Mobile County, Alabama https://t.co/wQoxu43418]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chick_N_Picker @john_mason_ Oh like the 1st Amendment? #FakeNationalEmergency https://t.co/uAL4Vl1wEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first time painting a bicycle! I spent 15 hours of hand sanding and 3 weeks learning intimately about how she wo… https://t.co/hzKsYsBDo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scot23 Who counted those votes and this is key. Whether they circled a selection or made a mark in the incorrect a… https://t.co/VAHLMflioP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish sent me an email regarding a refund on an order and i opened praying it wasnt elenas party decor,  thankfully… https://t.co/tnVYu0JQu7]]></document></documents></author>