<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Q: “What one policy would you recommend to reign in big tech?”  A's: –End centralized databases –Fund humanities –S… https://t.co/p8QaeF2Oss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @johnwar05431185 In the end we are all going to have to meet Jesus and tell him how good we were on… https://t.co/mUyBULscae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VZWSupport 2nd Ave in Lexington, NC. I have not checked with anyone else. My iPhone is not going to LTE as it normally does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Bobo Doll Experiment. 1960s Albert Bandura wanted to Investigate, whether children could imitate aggressive beh… https://t.co/cluTVNGC08]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING AMERICA TRUTH I LOVE YOU IN TRUTH ABSOLUTE UNDER TRUTH GOD AND TRUTH JUSTICE JESUS CHRIST. NOW NOTE DI… https://t.co/xV3pbBbhrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love these days! I get to bring my Son and show him my new listing that just hit the Market and what dad does for… https://t.co/q8MOLPj3kW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LawDogStrikes I know this as I just played a session at #GaryCon and it was incredibly fun]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can anyone explain the @instagram sponsored ads? Lately I’ve been bombarded with the most ridiculous ads. This has… https://t.co/msWX6XiqzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TKHoops12 @rex_rexchapman Brothers appear to be teammates. Looks like a screen gone wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Making my way downtown, walking fast, faces pass and I’m home bound.” . . . . . #photography #photographer… https://t.co/a1eexRfST8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren Yes we know all his achievements. He tried to destroy this country and damn near did. Are you celebrating he's not in jail yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeahawkScout Especially when he runs to the locker rooms after losses. Incredible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gfordgolf Nothing better!! Was fortunate enough to play there in Nov early in the morning and we had the place to… https://t.co/evnUMVGDvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCMacriNBA @joeknix They’re are all so rich. Enhancing brand matters.  Only one champion ...rest are padding stats… https://t.co/KqJ5liw9l3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarnivalCruise can you make reservations for the Dr. Suess breakfast prior to embarkation?  Leaving 3/17 on the #Magic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always admired Netanyahu   His love for his country and its people is unsurpassed. I always thought that if a… https://t.co/qvzzZR7HEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DPSecretariat1 opens office in Gulu. Congratulations @Teamsiranda @AishaWaliggo1 @norbertmao @Mbidde @JSsewungu https://t.co/a9jf1D2GwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know we all one day might just be millionaires/billionaires so we better keep laws in place protecting them so… https://t.co/UoKrhtgvxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Nah I don’t think so, more like chewed out.. I’ve been chewed out before”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruthandArtTV1 I love your daily videos on You Tube. They start my day off right, better than a cup of coffee. WWG1WGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another winner with West Virginia...lost our free pick with Celtics ! rolling and check front page at https://t.co/j2sncF0uSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetJill22 I may have just been bumped out of first class.  Was this your doing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signing these record breaking deals and destroying cap space won’t win you championships. People are so stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Oscar for Best Gentleman goes to @ChrisEvans. #Oscars https://t.co/i1xFKhHMPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a weak and political hack. Afraid to do her job bc it might hurt her popularity with certain political parties… https://t.co/uMBNXDzHEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@McFaddensPitt @CupidsUndieRun @CupidRunPitt Fun time to #EndNF #CureNF #ImWithCupid #Pittsburgh https://t.co/pgBUkdUa9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimmWrites @thejessegreyson @Arrowhead_Lib @Jarrett_Lerner @BeccaJonesTeach @dylanblackradio @AmeDyckman… https://t.co/qM7hkL7pIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuffaloSabres Time for another disappointing month. When will you guys finally win back to back games? It would be… https://t.co/A8ms9xOtYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferKorey Um, I think you need sensitivity training. You took the time to yell out a window to a brown man hol… https://t.co/X9ODtYYzPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm ready for valentine's dinner. Getting my wife truffles from Violet Sky Chocolate in SB. From @purpleporchcoop… https://t.co/wOGoMuPTTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t matter if #MichealJackson never touched these kids. His relationship w. young boys was predatory. I don’… https://t.co/pMvVJRAey2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Itshaber Played Fortnite the other day...I had zero fun. Used to love playing it but it’s beyond a sweatfest now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need someone to psychoanalyze me and tell why I’m such a HUGE SLUT for true crime podcasts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwjoehd @gatewaypundit @DonaldJTrumpJr @TuckerCarlson I'm super confused. In normal, due process world where polic… https://t.co/jV3Z0Sa0KQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so the @apollo11movie was basically a perfect documentary. The footage was so compelling, there was no need for… https://t.co/iVY6nDzNte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJoeMarino Gettleman doesn’t have the best rep right now. Buffalo is on the up. Go get him McBeane! #BillsMafia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday’s damage!  When the family is working out together, it’s nothing but motivation. #mistaspyda🕷💪🏾 @ Marine Co… https://t.co/nvISTXciit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seguin with his second of the game into the empty net to make it 3-0. @DallasStars are gonna win this baby! #GoStars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusanSegalo @TomMillerKXAN @KXAN_News @AustinISD If this is real good tweet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darby_Crush @itsavarose_ @Ilhan Man, it is not hard to get the MAGA crowd riled up with fantasies of white persecution]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por supuesto que puedes expresarte, de hecho, el problema no es el machismo sino la hiper-sensibilidad en los tiemp… https://t.co/blZgKQPTFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/cnsU3Gm0Lr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warning: reading the unintentionally clever things that people toddlers say gets old really quick]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly, I kept calling for the parents to get the same justice too for dangling their daughters as pedophile bait]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have always believed that Paul’s thorn in the flesh was literally “ the messenger of satan”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJFSLtd Its fantastico mate! Skiing, snowtubing, huskies, skating, swimming, snowshoe-trekking, so much to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow...just wow.  Watched it again tonight.   No. 2 Duke pulls off 23-point comeback to stun Louisville  https://t.co/tSLOYkV6tp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRather @rusty_hodge This guy has always been a CROOK!!! #NoWall! https://t.co/sElwmkYdqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TanyaLouWho @XtianEmiIiano I don’t think the movies would be any different honestly, but tough look for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobFoxThree It’s absolutely not the fault of the fact I put jalapeños on everything and anyone who tells me otherwise is a hater]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what socialism will end up once everybody else’s money is gone. Pray for #Venezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vladimirpadrino @jaarreaza Contra esto es la lucha, un grupito de “generales” traidores a la patria reunidos en un… https://t.co/0xF3xknAAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldsthoughts92 Somehow she has become the victim in this. Go back to work or do whatever you want now. You have 30… https://t.co/MiQh6CRfkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickHussion #People are glad 👉getting this every day https://t.co/NqNOcnGffM #going #worldwide #cut the cord ✂️… https://t.co/CkFwCfVSED]]></document><document><![CDATA[WW II Vet Richard Overton piece almost done.  Will be finishing it this week. DM if you are interested in purchasin… https://t.co/XvAWB6iZgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how Carly Rae Jepsen’s career would be different if ‘Call Me Maybe’ didn’t happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, @Ancestry, I think I can top that. Let’s play “Who is really your father?”   I’ll take “Not the one I thought… https://t.co/PYToyUk6ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcwva @RMFifthCircuit What happened yesterday? Did she get hammered?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeqExecutive Yup. Not one person said he won. Couldn’t even beat a random nigga named Ugas smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday is new @DDMDcast day! We record episode six and you get to hear episode four. That makes it Double New Dice… https://t.co/v46qsXh73T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmcdonell14 @AwaltonAmy @mnnowicki @bradrobb @cfredal @scmspto @lkhannon32 @nflynn #miched #MEMSPA #MEMSPAchat… https://t.co/osPuo270zE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennylattimore #kennylattimore #kennylattimorelive @ Chrome Showroom https://t.co/mkO5XHg450]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final: Sierra Canyon 76, Sheldon 53  My 127th and final game of the year is a blowout. There are good teams, there… https://t.co/xTpIeL8XCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trish_regan @VP @IvanDuque @jguaido That are starving in Syria. Dying, where the reporting on that.  The United St… https://t.co/oyG5y6ayxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoRibsNoRice_ Gotta capitalize on his stock rn and hope they know more about Corbett’s development than we do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cliffnationwide the 1st Tuesday in Nov 2016 was also the 1st of the month.  The election must be held after the 1s… https://t.co/2oEIc92jz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msandrew23 You up! Let’s go get snack den nay lol jk. I just randomly woke up 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesusJhector @eldeforma Jajaj que culeros, ni pedo, ya los agarraron como a Arjona]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCITLFrAphorism Yikes. Father Kevin. I believe though of course we have church doctrine which does change I believ… https://t.co/mV53p3SsCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tenía rato sin ver un partido tan malo del @realmadrid nos van a eliminar de la #ChampionsLeague 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone call PETA these animals are being held hostage forced to perform like circus animals!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good job Bg school board.. Losing one of the best coaches, mentors Bg will EVER have. Good luck to you coach and TH… https://t.co/zuteMwimfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noche de comer elotes🌽🌽🌽 #Amigos en Ampl Las Flores https://t.co/BVhlPRvCAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsaiTheDude @Mr_TP22 the other thing to factor in is that the CBA that we currently operate under will expire in y… https://t.co/YbEcvnl9H8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got hosed! 😂 #sprinklers #golf #golfing #golfer #golfaddict #golfobsessed #twitter #nofilter 🏌️ ⛳️ @ Seattle, Was… https://t.co/PORUP06NPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you told me 10/20 years ago I would be eating sushi today I would have told you that you're nuts. Sushi and Bona smoothie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarlboromanMat @MarkYoungTruth @chuckwoolery If this is true then do away with all the illegal immigrants in the c… https://t.co/VvMhqp8eUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It may not be snow like northern Arizona is having, but this rain I had on my commute home was awesome. #azwx… https://t.co/9EbqD0DLnq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google:  Alpha Group Russia  Alfa Bank Russia Alfa Group Russia  They are 3 different entities  Read:  Page 25 of t… https://t.co/MSiKIGxc8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @EMluvsPibbles @AnimalFarmFndtn @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/sNAbR6AdBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, whoever invited Discrete Mathematics and Probability, yo mommas a hoe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the pleasure of witnessing a special moment yesterday. @ClemsonUniv planted a direct descendant of the same a… https://t.co/ZEqTOMKC0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rileydolan @NMB_Baby_Watch @JunksRadio @moneymetalcakes @EBJunkies @GlassJoeJP @drabtshirt Give me two minutes and… https://t.co/8dbRYa8VwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've never talked about dicks,or vagina so much in one day in my entire life. We need group therapy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chardy_44 No doubt.   Orangefield has witnessed that next gear Val the last two games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerbusJames @wiguy45 @The_ClaireWitch @LogicalReterg @Tinman_73 @Watsdecraicjmac @keigh_see @def732dan… https://t.co/iurep43VmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Team Memb… https://t.co/8sB52l0hsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A reverse angle of the avalanche vid from Colorado yesterday. #Colorado @4029news]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fox5dc Got too be more careful something has too be done ✅ we losing people at a alarming rate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump ALL THIS WINNING @realDonaldTrump IS SO..... TIRING 🤣 https://t.co/Ix5M3IKFN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Good Trouble S01E07 #GoodTrouble #freeform #abcspark https://t.co/4jBwePgHFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phelpsbecca @lexi4prez I'm not gonna push anymore. Good night. I love you 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico And dummies his money didn’t make an asshole like Trump president.  It was because Hillary was an awful c… https://t.co/nZRTO1HE3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSamethyst Ooo, have a link to the article? I want to get into it but haven’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried taking photos of the super wolf moon in January, but it was very very windy and difficult to capture from my… https://t.co/5JP5YnOUry]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no idea when I asked you to marry me how hard, how fast or much endurance we would need to run the race of li… https://t.co/kFu1KliQHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin 47 months for Paul? You said 20+ yeare I call this social injustice. Sends the wrong signal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Greater Upper Marlboro, Maryland https://t.co/ByV3rX57mR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexanderJN Media will figure out a way to not call him a terrorist...... misguided soul etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sassal0x Any idea how rent will affect existing dApps?  Will they break?]]></document></documents></author>