<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@HenryRothenberg @NC5 @NC5_HMathis @NC5_JKraus Quick nap of 5 hrs:/ up since midnight. Welp it'll be easier for Mon… https://t.co/8ueY8Lhysf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias Only because it’s still primarily public-run education. He wants business led education. All very ALE… https://t.co/iMOm9ofNO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This IS a HOT TUB, folks! #QuickDraw. Winner with my Kinders! #GottaLoveKinders #VikingsGoVirtual https://t.co/0ByQD1X6lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y ahora nos toca andar asi, q importa meter lo tenis en la nieve total 🤷🏻‍♀️❄ feliz domingo gente... #HappySunday… https://t.co/tvW3TO0rZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Show Evening shifts!  Peaceful streets to you all a good night!   Good evening (K)Nights !   We All know Night… https://t.co/1uxF7s5Z0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[going to trader joe’s on an empty stomach is the worst move i’ve made all week and i haven’t even arrived yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN This is exactly how one way black slavery has always been started, (in Africa). Black parents selling black ch… https://t.co/ypGkiiJlEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was younger I had a bunch of stuffed animals I would sleep with and every morning I had to set them up a cer… https://t.co/h7slhi0XUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RedWings PPG: Vanek (13), Kronwall, Zadina, at 19:56 of the 2nd. #TBLightning lead 2-1.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikinthesandbox @psychdr100 A big “if” at this point, I’d venture. Very iffy, the whole god thing is now. God’s im… https://t.co/2P1yrOc83O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCock_ @harmonywonderxx @RileyReyXXX @KeiraCroft @MissCaliCarter @noitsdanuu @GiaVendetti @AlanaCruisexxx… https://t.co/zLDlWfX2q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grey_jarvis Why are all y’all hating on this girl who is just hanging with her beau on Valentine’s Day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard @THERESAM453 I am very surprised and disappointed in Ted Cruz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve come to the decision of getting high after work for the 4th work day this week]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see @thisisphangs @ my house!!  ⚠️ DM for details! ⚠️ https://t.co/jkfvwWasQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaOrdway just saw u in the Last Song... You were a mean girl...😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wise women told me never hit the snooze button and if you have to get up early hop in a cold shower. Fuck those cold showers 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING - @Patriots owner Robert Kraft arrested in Jupiter in a sex sting operation, along with many others according to MSNBC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This a Song for the weekend......👏💯  Filmed this New Dance Video today at the Gym and filmed some shots of a Basket… https://t.co/okq8Nc8Npa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concern:  Is Trump "believing " various autocrats because then they return the favor by supporting Trump when the i… https://t.co/ZHhdrZebx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s me fucking crying because @palomamalave FaceTimed me as joan was performing gtg cry even more bye https://t.co/DrQS3yWOOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knicks owner James Dolan has security handle a fan who told him to sell the team  https://t.co/Y0b8uZbH5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drug Flop House? Deputies arrest 9 people at this house and find meth.  Neighbors described seeing “zombies” leavin… https://t.co/WWIMcDKdeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The MOJO boys and girls each won 1st place at the West Texas Relays. #MOJONation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating a shared understanding and creating a space to ask and explore around Race, Equity and Leadership… https://t.co/L41QkGo1p2]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all love bitches who do drugs lmfao &amp; they b looking sick asfuck 🤮🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you see my car on greek row yes I’m aware it has a boot on it thank u for all the kind messages]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Davis_Boy12 @Bwb_2 @Therealvinoo @__Austinwiley50 @AuburnMBB https://t.co/9gmYCx0eTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a productive Saturday morning, ready for an awesome air show next month! https://t.co/MQdVNLT9of]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Buddha Garden at Seasage” in Seagate Estates at Delray for the Delray Home Tour #delraybeach #delrayhometour… https://t.co/J3u6Xm2TLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Power of the #jewfro actually I get my hair from my #Ukrainian side #naturalhair #dontcare @ Boulder, Colorado https://t.co/EcbHuKlCzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now let’s figure out how all those proposed tax subsidies can benefit real New Yorkers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely worth a visit. Beautifully done, and I'm so glad I got to see it while I was there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our team of 24 @JoinTeamAPS teacher recruitment ambassadors are the 💣 #teacherleaders #growleadtransform #k12talent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martinamcbride @KentuckyDerby So jelly have always wanted to go to the derby 🐎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessIndy500 @500Festival Congrats @HaleyBegay 👸🏻 #HendricksCountyProud 🏎🏁 #IsItMayYet @myHCICON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another life sentence given back because of the #firststepact!   Amazing work @MsBKB &amp; @BuriedAliveProj!… https://t.co/aNUQ5i9mh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pulperiaboi Marketing outsources their videography team so no bias there. I can't speak for certain university off… https://t.co/rotaug7YGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[US spy plane, with 6 Russians, flies over Russia in first surveillance mission since 2017: https://t.co/3lANNwe6bH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Buffalo Wild Wings Club in Minneapolis, MN https://t.co/loelW1n8bK]]></document><document><![CDATA[These 'scene stealers' made unforgettable appearances in cinematic history  https://t.co/po9Y97dcoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomansDay! Let's empower and encourage each other! #FelizDiaDeLaMujer #BalanceforBetter… https://t.co/ltLoh3pbaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow.  Glad i binged all of it. #TVD gone in March. Wonder if @cworiginals too. I want to work on.a Vampire show. https://t.co/n3TTxYLzVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiewr31413491 @CNN My son had MMR and has no immunity to said diseases - had titers checked. Possibly her mom’s… https://t.co/SK8vfVhOOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love how @USMAN84kg goes down in his stance getting ready for every new round. Every wrestler knows this is our way… https://t.co/1aJ61iBrjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wing stop is decorated with plane/aviation related stuff because planes have wings...... I am stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Payal &amp;amp; Dipak's Indian Wedding at Hilton Pearl River, NY  https://t.co/kAKVoc25TH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Cheney @SpeakerPelosi @IlhanMN Murderers' Row - that's what that cover represents.  Use it as a dartboard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deej2771 @AOC @AyannaPressley @IlhanMN So the questioning is bad... not the actions... gotcha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silviadanzante Jajaja siii mama yo siempre estoy bien tú eres la que debe cuidarse esa diabetes, pero nunca haces caso caray !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 There are so many other preposterous and grubbing for fame things about him who cares who he disappoints in the bedroom ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just after Ash Wednesday Mass - #Remember that you are dust and to dust you shall return.” 🐾 https://t.co/5u2tfIs4Uz]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 stages of an actor: - Who the hell is Don Cheadle - Get me Don Cheadle - Get me a Don Cheadle type - Get me a you… https://t.co/p3oV8lyr74]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else feel like we look as the end of the week nears 😝😝  Happy Friday-Eve y’all 🥳 https://t.co/ekrpkKXkvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parenting Text Fail - NoWayGirl #mirth #chuckle #grin #playful https://t.co/xyLuA7b569]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stand a mean person and a liar automatically ur shit just my opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJeffMerkley @realDonaldTrump And it's going to trial. Hope RBG makes it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Relaxation with Mom. Thanks settlebenjamin for the awesome Christmas present ! ❤️ @ Planet Salon and Spa https://t.co/a7a84VoS8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think that Putin won't sell Trump, Republicans, the NRA, etc for  the right price?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BryceHarper Development #Dodgers  Dodgers did in fact offer 10 years to @bharper3407 @dodgers @ Camelback Ranch -… https://t.co/nux9WwmWey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidiMac Oh My! I need to contact you for one of these with a November birthstone!! 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikapaprika He said it's technically curry cause anything that's tomato and onion based with some type of sauce is considered a curry 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You asshole. You are a despicable human. Richard Blumenthal has served this country in the militar… https://t.co/ynHcGpDcY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt #throwback allisonsummerclay #daughter and #JohnMichael #son #mama #sailboat #ocean #stillspendingtimetogether… https://t.co/QMaxD3UBWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Notice he said MEGA churches and don’t think they just bad people they just want the fame and power like you do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s a beast on the mat and a young woman after Jesus!!! Love her! So proud of you Taylor!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw @UROCKlive1 Disagreeing respectfully while supporting vigorously is called contradictory. I tell my respe… https://t.co/4D16K5Pfqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican Congress are you listening. The people are pissed off and we don’t forget]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were stumped in ALL block of EL today by a unfamiliar (even to me) word! We attempted to use our strategies like… https://t.co/WS9An3VDhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Unfortunately you will find that life’s troubles don’t stop because you get older.  The bright spot i… https://t.co/aeMo4ht6Id]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tart_cherry1 @alisongrippo @TomiLahren @AOC Oh no? Please do teach me? You MUST be an expert]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow.  This is amazing.  Why is this being covered up. Democrats illegally paid these Pakistani IT guys $7million do… https://t.co/82JBVyNVvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always been different, but in a good way and I just love all people, but don’t take that in the wrong way , I… https://t.co/09mIZp7wji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I a Peggy? #madmenstyle #peggy #1960sfashion #elizabethmoss #doilooklikeher #ladiesofcinema ♥️I have tons of Mad… https://t.co/gFIqnvyeZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying for the #Ordinandi2019 @archtoronto this evening. https://t.co/n2zzH5NnUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Senior IT Software Engineer(Kafka)" in #Mooresville, NC. Go on informational inte… https://t.co/mcMdqkPJiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kross700 @laura24fan @JudyJ31830202 @Chrisracefan1 @43324FAN @ToddTPrice24 @chevychevelle48 @jonesbrent570… https://t.co/E2U4t3uFpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janelle_gd @RolandPerron2 @adfo @cscmonavenir @EricVGenier Je pense à toi!!! Bon samedi!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohmajelisabeth He’s bad at his job as hand, he’s bad at being a single parent, he’s just bad at stuff south of the… https://t.co/qHH1HxWqFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Granitescatpack @ThePhightins33 Did you ever see so many people? And why when you already had a ticket did they ma… https://t.co/YxPO3eXnYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateHipHopHead Up until this point I just know I haven't experienced it. And given how much people divorce/breakup… https://t.co/Hj2TVpCgym]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creo que mis tops son quiero olvidar, lleno de nada, por amarte tanto y soy como no soy🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnneWheaton Why would Wil have tickets to the Grammys. Is he a secret musician?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you cringe during my date in Lex’s episode? 👨🏽‍🎨😂👨🏽‍🎨 #DatingAround]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama's a liar,  says what he thinks people want to hear, then do nothing. Trump has kept his promise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching a 4 year old how to ski and I suddenly want pizza and French fries...🤔 https://t.co/xbHyCqh2KD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattDeCourcey @JustinTrudeau @jimcarr_wpg Remember TPP was CPC party .#cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same women who go for trump are the reason lynching is now illegal,same women go for snake handlers]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to show this to every customer who couldn't grasp the concept of not talking to their servers like idiots an… https://t.co/Q4yce0x4lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to the person i can simp to country music w and the person i can really get faded w i love you sm ne… https://t.co/qXhEnAEr3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um papo com Mara Coimbra, colaboradora internacional do Lolla, sobre como é criar filhos na Europa.   https://t.co/x0rZF0uwmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s my real Godfather’s birthday month 😎💙🍻🍾🍷🎂🌭 https://t.co/P6SGxhBiP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning world.  Grab a cup and let's get energized.  Have a terrific Tuesday and make this day the best it can… https://t.co/vsN3jumbjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussEmerson @irinamoises @KayTaylor3 @SethAMandel He can only do that to Roger Stone, because you know, it's okay… https://t.co/FwyKh4LN9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @peterjhasson @DailySignal Democrats have lost their minds, they are dangerous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheedyali we learned the black Greek letter organizations were started to uplift and change the community that sur… https://t.co/DhL00OSA4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cedes_kayy When she was on the floor she said it again as she was getting her face beat!! When she was talking shi… https://t.co/MHJlkWSW8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[my current state right now YEEHAW and no i’m not cryinf im just tired https://t.co/B1NsiGRJ2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCNews_ @NYCReporters @NycNewsOK @MercyForAnimals if you know this asshat in New York City turn his ass in please https://t.co/hbpmLLv9uM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinebluffTeam @KAMOkonnects 😂😂😂 the stretching...the cartwheel...so amazingly extra!!! nailed it!!!]]></document></documents></author>