<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I think my worst decision was joining Kappa Alpha Theta. Yall’s definition of sisterhood must be different from min… https://t.co/spizIzWzyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already missing the best vacation of my life. 💖🐭 #TakeMeBack #Rus2ndBdayTrip #DisneyFam #Disneyland #RubyJoy… https://t.co/JQtYWVXNBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jazmine_Ruth Where,when and time from there it's a little easy. Like Vegas then best weather that's summer of cour… https://t.co/tcie0dBKh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[1950's Whisky Dispensing Machine- what happened to the good ole days ?We need one of these... #comedy #chuckle… https://t.co/aCWCOlREsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women's Golf Honored as Preseason Favorite in NEC Coaches' Poll https://t.co/3eWt9wIzv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[مووت الصباح جت عيني على كلمة قلت هذي رسالة ربانيه بتجي بالاختبار♥️ جت بالاختبار وحليتها غلط 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadGWagner @isabamahope Yes. I could write you pages on the evidence and email it if you want. But it won’t fit here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Los arkangeles puerta del sol  422 in Monterrey https://t.co/m55ZCgDAlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadefrazier @EustisHeights @BruenerMarie @lakeschools @purdygirly444 @HeIsLight01 @susan_emrick Congratulations @BruenerMarie]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Because you are here, and you are men, and while there are men there can be no peace.” https://t.co/68p7q15NIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A company that purchased the plaza plans on renovating the space and eventually bring in a new retailer. https://t.co/Jmgp1SmnDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrogProtection @ItsGucciBro5 Yeah it’s honestly a damn shame that their wasting all this talent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got my alarma bodysuits in the mail and the verdict: they’re amazing @ravewithmigente]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatachaFanClub Yo veo tv y claro que supe de su muerte ,y la verdad si había no se sabía no estaban así las redes… https://t.co/1hYeRxE7Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg Ok so you werent the bunny... then you must be the peacock... or the monster... JUST KIDDING!  I kn… https://t.co/0CawSkH1TH]]></document><document><![CDATA[New federal regulations impose gag rule on physicians, restrict access to critical services https://t.co/rdufIkyoho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to We Are One by @Raheem_DeVaughn on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/idPV8KS3x8 https://t.co/X6OsnYY8GL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheapest tickets to the Duke UNC game are 2,500. Yet we can't give these kids some money. SMH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eric the older one from where I used to work has been the one to constantly has tried to keep up with me and it’s greatly appreciated 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was a Magical Week! 😊 Now going to keep that magic going at home! 🙃#Disney https://t.co/ZLz8dTE79w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsVoong @shelynsharks @HeidiGallegos19 Congratulations ladies!!! Well deserved!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misskubelik @NealShusterman @alphabeticallie @catfriends I just checked last week and no release date- then was lo… https://t.co/tRsLjw69w0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blake Shelton round 2💕 @blakeshelton @LaurenAlainaNow #BSOKC https://t.co/NwH8Zf9kXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamdeVry1 Housework and chillin with my pups then two singing gigs later.  Hope you have an amazing day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom Go get’em Governor Newsom!! Thank you for speaking the truth and putting @realDonaldTrump in his place… https://t.co/l8b3O274RG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days are bad but the good days make up for them. Thankful for the wonderful opportunities my life has given me… https://t.co/zwqhunnl0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well yesterday was my annual reminder of how many people don’t know when to use “women” vs. “woman”]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it’s your first time joining a twitter chat, know that Questions will be labeled Q and you will want to start yo… https://t.co/zrnQkAoh6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radliberal Yes it is. But we don’t live in a pure democracy. That would be a nightmare.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze And because of everything you just said means you would be a viable candidate. One I can trust and believ… https://t.co/7ZbiuSDK5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrishMayhorn1 @Jim_Jordan You are not seeing the truth. Dems/libs/rinos are ruining America and unfortunately peop… https://t.co/nobQzFLaD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trexinchicago “Pressing question, a matter of fuckin national security” ended me 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UuppityNegro Thanks !!! You too! I hope you get shot by Cupid today 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening TODAY! @mainlinetheatre  #festivaldelabêtenoire #festivaldelabetenoire #Montreal #theatre #storytelling… https://t.co/QbX9qEQt5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#orgy #orgymusicofficial #prettyinkinktour #seattle #showboxsodo #band #concert #music #tour… https://t.co/cmIwfLZdtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGreat2020 @whereisjustice0 You folks better know we now have an informed electorate. You may be on your last leg]]></document><document><![CDATA[PERFECT stay (@ Holiday Inn Express &amp; Suites Bismarck - @hiexpress in Bismarck, ND) https://t.co/xSbSD9ODIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s paper: @madelinesingas @USPISpressroom charges 5 in credit union loan fraud. 📸 by @NYCanonShooter.… https://t.co/Pu2v9CYCdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#polloftheday #Poll: Do you respect people who apologize when they make a mistake?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RuvvyMyLuvvy @timzmom @TREEIAmTree @RatesDaGoldfish @GiraffesInc @CoriSigma @IAmBoxTheBox @A_affirmations… https://t.co/O4GvV6C4bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ @Maggie0210 No where in the Bible does it say God created the white man. God created Adam and Eve. Who k… https://t.co/c6dBXCvn7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to hearing the panel today @nawboindy’s Diversity luncheon; especially our own @netlogx.… https://t.co/qtgonW2tsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmithCliff999 @redsteeze @neontaster Nope. That guy was a rarity there. I used to live almost next to ZP and spent… https://t.co/Qv1lptMLyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thx to our rockstar @FDAOncology project mgmt staff &amp; @ASCO staff who organize &amp; execute… https://t.co/eGRWUqgw9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiguelAlsol @DonPorfirioDiaz @lopezobrador_ No pues si, el famoso PRIAN está en Morena. https://t.co/FGJN9c1BdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite person and my favorite food? Sign me up #DBBwithMyBetterHalf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThrowbackThursday  to the ‘Canes first ever home opening game against the flightless birds from Pitt  during the F… https://t.co/9HcUjnsDsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mfs think calling asian girls “mulan” is a form of endearment LMAOO is that the only asian person y’all know 💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[did anyone else have the sTrAnGeSt day yesterday like the vibes were soo off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@owenhumphreys1 @NorthLightAlert @chunder10 @StormHour @ThePhotoHour @lakedistrictnpa @Lauratobin1 @CumbriaWeather… https://t.co/BNzSSbtjqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Dinner tonight we had:  - Bourbon Glazed Salmon - Kale with Roasted Pork Belly and Sweet Red Wine reduction - G… https://t.co/I2c5GJAuhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth! My oldest is a welder and has done very well for himself https://t.co/vAavedk5pR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalanguEmmanuel Mon frère il est grand temps de s’arme de vraie connaissance de choses. Le but politique ultime du… https://t.co/7V3lJ0PPRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's 6am. I just read a comment on Facebook that a "natural alkaline" diet and "herbal detoxes" will help cure you… https://t.co/3dXBAfs4Bn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madsatan6969 @beers300 @Shawn172510 @The_Fool_Monty @Bubba_Henson @HippieVol @DollyVol @MelissaFincher @magnumCJ… https://t.co/DDEAj9XMp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Jacksonville International Airport - @jaxairport in Jacksonville, FL https://t.co/Zjy86rho8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimashleydj  Hey Kim so a 3% raise to minimum wage based on $10 an hour comes out to less than $50 a month not sure that's a big deal]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cuzn just through some damn ice cream in my hair after i just washed it.  Now i got to wash it again.😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you soon #canada. ❤️ @theShoppingChan @isaacmizrahi americanexpress #fashion #jetset @ Amex The Centurion Lounge https://t.co/o3iD5D1VdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newsmonkeygirl My cat is really interested in watching this video for some reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsricovidal @_lexalt @ImaniOrWhatever Appreciate you. Lex and I had a date last night!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalvoSensu @Stonekettle I ate hog brains on top of scrambled eggs as a child...Hell we all did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 5amers ready to tackle their day. Zazaam! 💁🏾💪🏾💜💃 @ Sculpt Fitness LLC https://t.co/Hqs1YHIT9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSFrier Check out @Larryferlazzo’s website! He even has a podcast on #familyEngagement 👍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtneymake ohhh I did not know, shit sorry :( (but trust you don’t want this one..many years of listening to the… https://t.co/Db4Horgt9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArthurSchwartz @fud31 No your late term abortion bill was Amazon @andrewcuomo was #Karma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rulasboy23 Jaja Una cosa es ir perdiendo con Xolos, otra... ¡Con Morelia empezando el juego!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot my headphones, didn’t charge my Apple Watch, and left my chapstick in my car. So ready for this race!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lawdy! Where were y'all when I had my 15 year renewal?! I always miss the good stuff! #DragMe #DragMeDownTheAisle @AlexisLives]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is OPENING DAY! Do you have your tickets for #Chicago the Musical? We’ve been working incredibly hard on this… https://t.co/M5yr34gvZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey stream fam! It's been a minute, let's chat and draw and listen to #Vaporwave! 7 PM CST https://t.co/PmEr0TzHM4 https://t.co/6iwnBRhc7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign up to drive with Uber and earn $575, guaranteed, after completing the required trips. Use code FRANCISCAS18 😊… https://t.co/55XYp3yg9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly.  No double standards.  Listen to the song and Retweet it. https://t.co/sU6OvyXLl5  @tictoc @MikeBloomberg… https://t.co/YrUrmgmpVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freaking out bc basically two full wks until it’s midterm wk &amp; then spring break.  🤯  I’m not ready.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacK_GingerCat @AngoraBoys Zelda and Loki are happy to follow you.  Welcome to #CatsOfTwitter #tuffcats 😺😺 https://t.co/Bbj1DZAK6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Margosha_S_I @belyi_seryi @poroshenko @MunSecConf Выживаете вы (мн. ч.). А мы хотим жить.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you hear about the slow swimmer? He could only do the crawl #JokeOfTheDay good luck at conference @saintleoswim]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing Corbin Bleu tap dance.....12 year old me had really good taste   Also 23 year old me still has really good taste]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonaldKlain I am a huge Sanders fan and agree that this is a great hire! #Bernie2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those that enjoy the finer things in life. 🥂 @ Mastro's Steakhouse https://t.co/WlwCnMzpTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heckyessica Yep I have a pantry full. I reuse them as garbage can bags]]></document><document><![CDATA[reasons to declare a state of emergency:  - natural disaster - civil unrest - armed conflict - hair tie breaking at the gym]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is a tale of crutches where no one learns to walk. We stay in our brokenness that we call comfort.  How foolish… https://t.co/xOyhhDhxnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IkaRuss6 @AboveTheBurgh @PrimeCreator2 @WYATT251 @2newearth777 @davidsodell @zeola_rose @gil_lawson @HeARTofGod99… https://t.co/x2ssRupVIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebonilla56 @MagelaMeinjua Cómo se llama el Periodista? Y saben algo de él?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hace varios años, Pence era un impresentable. Hoy sigue siéndolo. El único norte que reconozco es: 1. Cese de la us… https://t.co/aJ4zspc4wt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely beyond impressed with all this new music. ❤️👏 @jonasbrothers @BenSPLATT @ThomasRhett]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time I played 2 truths and like with the kids at camp and one kid say my moms friends cat died yesterday and that was the lie like WHAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@symboliansister @i_am_joshyo Awww he's so handsome i want to meet him one day god bless him💯😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hattie walked into a classroom with NO TEACHER. “my teacher is the best, she is out there in the cold fighting for… https://t.co/TjHbX8f7Wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosaannee_ That’s stupid thing is scary, I watched a video and could only imagine little kids watching this]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at George Bush Intercontinental Airport in Houston, TX https://t.co/EcGZhiFkkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogerClark41 @NY1 That building is beautiful. I'm sure they won't replace it with anything as nice. Terrible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Yes he did. Check it out. #AnotherMoronicIdiot #LockHimUpToo #ThrowAwayTheKey https://t.co/pE3pPQu03c]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a broken record with Mother Nature! Ice is causing some slick roads and sidewalks ... again. @michaelkuhnnews… https://t.co/0TGN9tBFiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bout time to watch Almost Famous for the 20th time https://t.co/7a110IWuu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[“...without sex education, students may not learn how to state her boundaries or to respect the boundaries of other… https://t.co/IOyFaNHDMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joehan__ Yeah I’m with you on that but it is nice to see him play better. I hope it’s just the beginning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirstinlcheers 🤣😂😅 I’m laughing because exactly what I told my team when we were listening to it last night. You a… https://t.co/bP7BYKDPGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you hit me saying “ let’s smoke “ and i pull up and you whip out a wax pen, I’m leaving and blocking you 🤣🤣🤣]]></document></documents></author>