<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @JudithParise Why is Israel the only country we can't criticize without being called antisemitic? Total bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is baffling. Mf’s really live in their own bubble of white privilege and delusion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnlockedLive Thank you so much everyone! It was so much fun chatting with y’all. Looking forward to next week!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I have been gas lite by new york.  I do not want to move to NY or live there.  I worked 5 years on sets includ… https://t.co/2Xn6ksfdUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[A brilliant artist and great friend! It’s an honor to be able to have some of my first art showing alongside some a… https://t.co/7BBUaY9GSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, Li Yang for sex trafficking so all my pals have a happy ending! #MarALago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen! Only let in the people that support you and who you are. The rest are unessasry baggage and need to be left a… https://t.co/6Cn1vOAuYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heather Nowels crossed 1 Mile to GO!. Time 01:47:51, pace 08:52 min/mile, est. finish 9:07 am https://t.co/5sE9jPLDoX #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that a mod or can we actually get the Master Chief accessories or Master Chief himself? Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi Generally speaking evil ppl live longer. We can always HOPE that's wrong in this case.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Norcross, GA? View our latest opening: https://t.co/qcj3FfqcJt #Cosmetology]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson As long as the touching &amp; dying last, yes to volume 2.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Song titles gotta grab me...  Then the lyrics...  Then the melody...  Then the vocal/delivery...   Then the product… https://t.co/Q68YuQDVeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time I dressed up as Hannah Montana for Halloween and carried around a guitar case as my candy bag lmai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkPieszak @beeman_nl @ltciro Amazing! I will be here until April 6, and I will be visiting continuously this year ❤️🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyhcmaven84 Someone may have ordered a steak with onions and is waiting patiently]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k_pastorkova @marykk196051 @joannes02439842 @MaryKayH188 @VieraBohacova @julieknowles3g @RoxanneCWhiting @lbordasm… https://t.co/0n8jUzoR7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Victorio_M But I love them so much 😔💔 I want them to be happy... with me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[the person I wanted to FaceTime doesn’t wanna, so does anyone wanna facetime while I take this little study break?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanndennis @Meganadams21 I KNOW I finished it last week and agree 100%]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyday i learn something. everyday. @illujanist always with the little tweaks that make a huge difference. high h… https://t.co/FMqVIBOmKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[and from Jesus Christ, who is the faithful witness, the firstborn from the dead, and the ruler of the kings of the… https://t.co/EwGHEENUQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[really need to figure things out soo I’m going on a social media break *execpt Twitter bc I love it!  But everythin… https://t.co/zt5pgtIhu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took ‘em three to do it, but @DriveNation_Dfw 13 Red survived the first round of the 14 Open Gold Bracket at #AVC!… https://t.co/CkTWSgn4yI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suppose I should just be thankful for being alive and not complain about being tired. Time to crank some tunes and get my ass in gear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courageous women sharing their stories on #IWD2019 @WCHospital #womenshealthmatters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cinderrhellaa @FDACosmetics @claires Thankfully no! She only has stuff from @ultabeauty 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[The problem with peoples relationships is y’all are too quick to post every little thing you do or tell everyone ab… https://t.co/kXfySAHOh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[We made progress on inclusion when we stopped leading with gender. @FranKatsoudas @Cisco @ellmcgirt 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻 #GPTW4All #ForALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[REGISTRATION FOR SEASON 2 IS STILL OPEN MAKE SURE TO SECURE YOUR SPOT! https://t.co/FLv1JKjENO  https://t.co/hRbOC6Fb45]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justin on #DatingAround .Knew he was trash from that cat story. Gurki is a queen. https://t.co/tLSpPK2jdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Revitalized_Dem @CapnMAGA @swicklepus @1Beau1969 @BwaHh @ricklundl @cspanwj @nytimes @katierogers Are you reading… https://t.co/srG9M7ZjBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao there’s a company on instagram trying to sell holograms as VIDEO PRINTS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@negnance @frynaomifry you have a sweater?? i only have a t shirt. i need a new one too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer @yashar Now, I want more towels &amp; more towel controversies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lawmaker Scolds VA Chief for 'Stonewalling' Probe Into Trump's Mar-a-Lago Crowd https://t.co/Nyf14ZA7kQ via @Nextgov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppleSupport Omg thank you (I found them and will set this up for the next time I forget them in a jacket pocket)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiiii friends!!!!! Missed you guys!! So happy to be back at work from jury duty! Hope you can join us as we all cat… https://t.co/BjrIF5BNnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocupó 911 al señor de los elotes 🤤🤤🤤🤤🤤🤤pa comerme un esquite 😋 (poca Mayo, sin limon y poquito chile de polvo@☺️)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayleighAnnG16 I sweat I'm dysfunctional. No matter what I do, it looks like shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_whoisashley awe hell no. she’s gonna whoop them w a chancla if she finds out who it was]]></document><document><![CDATA[On #IWD let's take a moment to recognize the beauty in all women and gender mon confirming folks. Let's also rememb… https://t.co/PimNsCuk1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ONCustServ what happens when the items I ordered are not what I received? Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do the bleepers on this week’s Bachelor look exactly like an episode of The Office?]]></document><document><![CDATA[something to look forward to - mid 50’s by the weekend! ☀️ https://t.co/NnnyUoq3BI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where's the DEMOCRATS on this?  Where is the MAIN STREAM MEDIA on this.  They both should hide is shame.  Here's th… https://t.co/mycJIsFSAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@707bigjoe I usually brag about my gifts on Instagram which did u give me baby??? 🤗💙🎁]]></document><document><![CDATA[cute date idea: cooking together?? sounds boring but I feel like it would be so fun 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may be out the $300 from my @interjet flight but at least my health is my first concern and I will NEVER fly them… https://t.co/qkq0QZYVQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO CHILD. YOU CANT JUST NOT DO A COMBO THIS ISNT SENIORS YOU CANT PUT IT ON THE FLIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[PURE EVIL: Here Are the Democrat Presidential Candidates Who Just Voted to Support Doctors Killing Babies who Survi… https://t.co/oY6jKp5tIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[when your barista looks at you funny because you said your drink combo in the right order......yes bruh. I used to be one of you 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[couldn’t wait ‘til spring break🏖☀️ @ Siesta Key Beach https://t.co/XfPgehi5ZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's full filling his duties better than any President has done! @StormIsUponUs We are ready!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hels Get the spicy chicken sandwich!!!! Many spicy chicken sandwiches in fact 🐔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basha_botnick @JudgeJeanine You got that right!   Judge Jeanine for President in 6 years while i'm at it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard times help you really enjoy when things are going good  for you I’m so fucking thankful 🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t blame @HerbDeanMMA . You gotta do what you gotta do with your best judgement. Refs job is to keep the fighters safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Female celebrities that's blessing unknowns .....   ©️®️❗p @ Las Olas https://t.co/FZ5uNPp9oT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adorkableash_22 I give it all of 30 minutes, we finished putting it together last night and she wasn’t too sure ab… https://t.co/mKwQm7yMTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all boyfriends gonna hate luka now.. mans said smash is low tierrrr 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenslinn43 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @roads2 @Jimmysimmonds1 @Iluvinspireu @Peeperpea29 @ClockworkHamma @MyEngland2016… https://t.co/JivJYoNgqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was walking to my car and realized I left my keys in my room smh when will I stop getting locked out of my own room 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chanda_june literally do it i’m moving into my apartment in 2 weeks you can stay with me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @SenateGOP The obstruction from the #GOP has helped to bring us to this point. Now that we are able, sh… https://t.co/CpYwGkUumk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made a Sisqo CD cover in my computer class and when I didn’t get a good great I told my teacher he was racist (he… https://t.co/QEXTF2QIMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conservmillen The only recent race riots I remember took place in Ferguason and Baltimore during Obama's tenure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/g7T7UUHNVE  #shoesaddict #shoegaze #shoelover #shoe #traveler #packing #shoppingstar #shoppingaddict… https://t.co/XT6ECatMHe]]></document><document><![CDATA[escucho esta canción y siento que escucho un opening de anime https://t.co/kHVN2TFm3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NeverBernie #NeverBernie #NeverBernie #NeverBernie #NeverBernie #NeverBernie #NeverBernie #NeverBernie… https://t.co/BCHCkBXhKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a G&amp;T at a whiskey bar, story of my life. Barmaid’s name is Julia go figure it was destiny @ The Phoenix https://t.co/UkNeXLkdJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SoompiAwards #TeamBTS #BestTwitterFandom  Talented Fans For a TALENTED Group! These are so amazingly done they’re… https://t.co/hYMAKroXhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Live2ServeJC Wow did not know there was glazed donuts with sprinkles for pets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to stop in Baker for Ohio Birthday Bash. Bring any non-perishable food items for a free coffee card! https://t.co/qKtd1iNekx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siri, show me a carceral system that generationally entrenches white supremacy through the destruction of black and… https://t.co/r5MgbMoY1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Supporters Despise Corporate Media https://t.co/LwlsRnOIA8 via @KyleKulinski | “And you wonder why people ge… https://t.co/GPUkuvheM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Otozoum @cathyhadenough It was hard for us.  Mom had never been sick but once she was diagnosed, she was gone in l… https://t.co/uhfVS3Fr65]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dateOklahoma #dateChicago  #dateKansascity I'm headed you're way let's get you prebooked through my website 👇👇… https://t.co/QxkGCz1pmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad I was able to give my nephew Eli, and brother in-law @jablowsmeats a tour of my work. It was great to see t… https://t.co/Jn6OLNwubm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting on the bus to visit my family @ Port Authority Bus Terminal https://t.co/hsmMxBE612]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free agents have chosen the eagles.  Now Harper to the Phillies which will be enticing for other free agents.  I re… https://t.co/QrctXGWCSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj Do you remember the War Games that use to drive Kim Jung Un mad?...Well Donald just suspended them after g… https://t.co/73aqwLD8bG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateBender5 Heartland Conservation Alliance and partners making waves in the Blue River Watershed. Join in https://t.co/lag0vCP0bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey gamers :) if anyone uhhhh knows any fun #discord servers looking for new :) members :) I would like to join]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like the idea of having a baby but not the work that comes along with it :,) plz tell me that I’m not the only one that thinks the same]]></document><document><![CDATA[[A THREAD ]Im at work listening to 5sos and my heart is idk wtf its doing but I fucking love these guys. Like deada… https://t.co/MXFWLe9HeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marzelladeville @DogBountyHunter @MrsdogC @wgnamerica @OfficialDOGNews @DreamsInColor33 @tootlelOops It’s suppose… https://t.co/5pqMgXxW6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look. I mean. Wut?  Her arm must be pretty long to keep patting her own damn self on the back all day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Williams, the man accused of killing a Somerset Co. Sheriff’s deputy returns to court this morning.  We’re liv… https://t.co/mMmZOWDfLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[johnbcrist  #HumanBeingTour in Baltimore with one of my best friends. #bmore #bringonthelaughs @ Modell Performing… https://t.co/hqMUGJiizg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBeatWithAri @cthagod kinda glad @gucci did this, im tired of seeing musicians pimp out Gucci knowing dang well… https://t.co/OTpQMlSfR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmineSabia @MikePoway did you know this? What a miserable human being!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roald Dahl books and coffee are two things I’m looking forward to this weekend. It’s the little joys that bring the… https://t.co/MlStJOx7rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul He has the right and congress gave that right to him, so why not, You need to stand with him or I guarant… https://t.co/J33YbnSNJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oregonfootball @nflnetwork @JalenJelks I have to go to bed so I can work tonight 😢 please post his highlights later!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joe_chapa Ayer tuve que renunciar a un sueño, a algo que anhelaba... Y haberlo escuchado hoy, me hace sentir que t… https://t.co/ySf3VnBkOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t know before today that I was in need of a Jonas Brothers reunion, but here I am, and can confirm that  I… https://t.co/xpns2nENJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone know if Mueller can re-trie Manafort on the 10 counts that were hung?   This was sentencing for the 8 c… https://t.co/jK2I8bscSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino 😂😂😂😂 ok. Hey Barack we tried your change thanks but no thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hunter1988888 @StevePa69464573 @BurneyMitchell @BillOReilly I voted for him the first time because it was not real… https://t.co/caRadufXsy]]></document></documents></author>