<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Omg people on fb are calling Donna annoying and my poor little west wing fan girl heart can’t take it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nilla Almond Milk This is a great all day vape! You will crave this eJuice all day long. Grab Keep It 100 Nilla Alm… https://t.co/m4w7kbIUyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some (I) would say by attending CPAC Van Jones went too far. @TheYoungTurks #TYTLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to work for @PhillyMayor today and everyday. Everything he said in this video comes from his heart. And his A… https://t.co/4oNe0evR4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok but watching all of these older guys run away from captain dads dad and hide literally makes my heart smile, i love it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meowyaaa @justpikeplace 🗣 Preach. Haha. Why do people feel the need to put an “s” at the end of many Seattle insti… https://t.co/pVyWjebaKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunbeltRentals @AppBaseball @GWUBaseball @laurawolffphoto @MiLB @knights_turf @CLTKnightsHomer @CaballerosdeCLT… https://t.co/ftEOhdnQfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbagleague @StocktonKings @SacramentoKings @troywilliams_ @matt9jones I think they're pretty genius.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifeofaaron I was just talking about how annoying everyone who wants and tries to be a thought leader on LinkedIn… https://t.co/EEWl7nvvX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring training @Athletics night game. #Game1 #HellaSpring https://t.co/bnxbZHjVNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh how I love March...it’s my #birthdaymonth 🎂🍰🧁 and who wouldn’t love a #boujee pair of #customkicks 🤪🤷🏼‍♀️👟 My in… https://t.co/GxkLSLMf5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fawfulfan @Katriana74 Hay folks are you paying attention, did you see all those RED FLAGES 🚩🚩🚩🚩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things Our Mother Taught Us brandi_p #mirth #chuckle #grin #cute https://t.co/0TlmNdBAa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain: “You have one of two qualifications to get hired [at mainline]. You’re gay, but you’re not a woman.”  Me,… https://t.co/0BKzMv1B76]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueHazeWSISD is so excited and honored that you will be joining us for Reading Day! We cannot wait to meet you!… https://t.co/VP64myV6mI]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are billions of beautiful hearts. • #lagaragista #allocationtasting #100percentvermont #domainedelaforêt… https://t.co/KTFjiDDcYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entra un venezolano, y probablemente sale otro 😳. 🔥 La cosa se pone buena. #MNTwins]]></document><document><![CDATA[CONGRATULATIONS KEVIN!!  Way to kick azz and win stage one!! 👍😎🙌🌟🎰 https://t.co/XAmz00d7Kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The word harassment should never be used until absolutely necessary. Hell everyone everywhere gets… https://t.co/5g6rd6eUqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you! Excited for this opportunity to work with more great educators in our state!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hosting Hope at the Inn at your work is great and everything, until a homeless person steals @Mtrud’s and I’s picture off the staff board. 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to see this talanted genius #greatfuckingmusic https://t.co/4tKamkOgdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just let the dog out again. Over/under on whether he gets stuck again and I have to go outside to rescue him in thi… https://t.co/1fjkY8jlIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, somehow, I got a first class ticket for my flight from Antigua to Miami. First time ever flying first class.… https://t.co/9j05P622HS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are some of the ways we are making gender equality central to our work in New York...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Why would you post the edited version and help spread misinformation? You’ve all learned nothing from 2016.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kweansmom @OliviaVivianne I do agree that right-wing Christians use Jews and Israel.  I don’t like it at all.  Whe… https://t.co/XLQYRaHltD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmfa #byeCNN. All I can conclude is Trumps criticism finally got to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Then let's take the garbage starting with AOC, Omar, pelosi, schumer, Adam 💩, etc.  Deport them to V… https://t.co/XdkzBY8Iza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forcing myself to eat oatmeal without sugar for breakfast. It’s awful! Any sugar free breakfast ideas that isn’t eggs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ross_rlz Yes - I remember being fascinated by my parent's luggage (esp mom's little cosmetics case)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler01582911 @roywoodjr What do you mean? I am not living with him but me and him are still together and this why… https://t.co/xsxZO8iZ1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoniqueTweets45 @DWImpalaOwner @ItsSam1983 Obviously not if you're telling the boys you give up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTWsanctuary @FrasierHarry I'AM TRYING TO SIGN THE PETITION BUT IS NOT ACCEPTING MY ZIP CODE. IT SAIDS IT'S NOT A VALID ZIP CODE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out some talented ponies!   #datenight #ranchorio #wickenburg @ Rancho Rio https://t.co/bKF54G75oX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_hitchka I’m sure it’s good but I don’t think it beats out all the others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chiefsmiles rented us a cute little vip rose cabana 🌹 Lisa Vanderpump is shaking 🍾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch For their on personal dignity I hope not!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working under the BIG TOP tonight for haltonwomensplace and raising big dollars to end violence against women and c… https://t.co/mOM8OWg0Vg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cenkuygur @GOP @TheYoungTurks @crookedmedia @FoxNews @TVietor08 AGREED we couldn't care less about what… https://t.co/LEWrvGKjAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[update there’s a five year old just SCREAMING at the back of the plane. cool! can we at least get this child a juic… https://t.co/8XxsxewTZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micahgeorge66 @BarackObama I gotcha ! Please accept my apology! Truly sorry, keep resisting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a look inside the amazing care available at #CleClinicChildrens! The only pediatric hospital in northeast Ohio… https://t.co/PVOlf6UTo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I am off ( no one text) When I am busy ( friends, mom, calls)   Wondering if that happens only to me. 🤷🏽‍♀️🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovHowardDean #endtheircareers @repJimJordan @SenJohnKennedy #VoteThemOut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colorsxstudios hey. Y'all. Yeah. @Naja_Young. Her right there. FUCK WITH HER]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to start our giving week today! Click the link below, any amount helps!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just like fuck everything kind of mood i’m tired and miserable. Hurting all the damn time i’m so ready to have… https://t.co/CknWOowCW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner Your source of  history knowledge? UR concerns with Obama's administration with  Russia? Hillary? Clinto… https://t.co/5vLaDIEWIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[iFly in Overland Park totally exceeded our expectations today. And of course my dad rocked it his first time 👊🏼… https://t.co/rJfFKN3aDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Funny how there’s never any “leaks” about his report Ed. Hmmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been sitting in my car for the past 30 minutes contemplating if I should go into my philosophy class or not...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nrulason Anyway too late I already made a big payment on my credit card bill and feel slightly more relieved than anxious 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me everyday on the hike into the show as people fly by on golf carts: you think someone would offer a ride one day… https://t.co/do1A3tnZCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The family secret Bruce Ohr told Rod Rosenstein about Russia case https://t.co/rQkwq9mWgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[An actual conversation I just had with Keegan.  K: if you could be anyone for one day who would it be? Me: prob Bey… https://t.co/ZVb6x7t0jN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancyskallywag Ok I found so many comments and memes I wanted to show you while reading the comments to Khloes last 2 tweets 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nerding out at the @AllenSTEAM Center with my mini-me! ❤️ Thanks @steamk8 for a GREAT day 🌎 https://t.co/WYU29pxVeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being depressed and emotionally unstable isn’t fun. I almost ended my life today but who cares.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What God be looking down at me like every time I make a bad decision https://t.co/ug1xsFZq3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barack Obama wants back in White House ... https://t.co/3uZCZIPwh8 via @worldnetdaily]]></document><document><![CDATA[We both always wonder how we still have shit to talk about when we catch eachother on the phone for the 10th time a… https://t.co/D8Eff9ug5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnAndris @NanceRocks @MalcolmNance @11thHour Ordinary Russians' income did rise sharply when Putin gained contro… https://t.co/zUCVbTHtcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelGHodgson I getting used to his gumball machine head atop a human body...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicoleddietrich I love teaching the reverse poem and seeing gifted writers pull it off!]]></document><document><![CDATA[sans déconner, ça me rends complètement dingue de pas savoir ou jvai finir si jprends une décision ou pas une autre… https://t.co/YLVS5xmwVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carnelian is for courage, vitality, action, sexuality and confidence.  Egyptian kings and queens wore it because th… https://t.co/KpEYS2lD6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s those corny people that have to put all thier clothes and shoes up as soon as they get to the hotel]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ladies are out in full force today! 🎉💕 We are SO excited to welcome @lindsarnold to the #SoNWWS 💃🏼 https://t.co/T9DmXJ0ws1]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEWS: Senator @CoryBooker will intro his landmark Marijuana Justice Act today 👇🏼 https://t.co/YZxp0wrRhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrettyBrown_MB I love this show I watch it when I should be workin lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJStylesOrg @RealPaigeWWE I will whenever someone will shove me out my brother and his son are very lazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thrive the most while wearing knock off Harry Styles merch https://t.co/P7hFfYbvgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenSatCisco What’s so wild?! I bet the person who told me this does not remember. Clearly not the kind of dino… https://t.co/tBtoYj9eWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s almost five am and i have to sudden urge to box dye my hair.,,,.,,,,,....,,,,,......]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️♥️♥️Beacause for US every single day is Valentines day!!! Happy Valentines Day My Love!! I Love You krismarie833… https://t.co/gOvZup3Qqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite @fullerhouse ending, I am hoping for a spinoff that revolves around Jesse, Becky, Nicky and Alex Katsopolis… https://t.co/uhFToj9l7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to see the definition of perfect go watch Kacey Musgraves cover Selena during her Houston rodeo performance]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Day and Everyday. #nailsbytashalynn #nailsbyamericans #youshouldbehere #polishroomfl #orlando #downtownorlando… https://t.co/iL5XNQwlcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackieaina Belief vs faith. These people got no faith just what they believe from a book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more curve ball and I’m moving to California and becoming a beach hobo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna be a busy day of scoreboard watching today for Irish fans! @TayBushman @Rachel_Sangston good luck ladies!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christ is the culmination of the law so that there may be righteousness for everyone who believes. https://t.co/k4NB37v40H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every night, Jazel, drake, nick and I have game night and play uno on our phones 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chitownsports44 @Cubs Every other game is televised cubs audio only. Why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day from my little bundle of love 💋♥️ https://t.co/LbnEqAOG5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t she learn anything from the last housing crisis. Some people shouldn’t own homes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarisInigoVFs @kapalmoks23 @NigoMar @AirahAquino8 @Mabelskie09 @maloumunar422 @JudaelB @CharmineBalles2 Hahaha asa… https://t.co/EkyqL54csY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaomiJKrueger And refusal is offensive to my husband’s Cuban family so I have to watch myself. What I think is pol… https://t.co/nqT0lzCKyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alobar2 @GreySkepticMac From my perspective it's more complex than this.  I am an anti theist because of the cogni… https://t.co/UuyKYjaWyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAtlantic @EliotACohen Help us inject some “spine” into American will by doing what’s right and goes to the spir… https://t.co/yds2UQjpAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me acaba de caer el 20 que mi bolsita ya no regresará... Pray 4 mis fotos y las de mis bbys (y mi dinero☹) https://t.co/3qmubaqBB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[These shoes are awesome! Would you wear these? I think I'd break an ankle 😂   https://t.co/5I5aMQpC3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahilkapur really...did U watch the same race(s) I did?  Can U even compare the way Hillary handled the post prima… https://t.co/SuY5aw4g9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not even in class of ‘19 and I’m gonna be mad if unwritten doesn’t win]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopsandSunshine @ReliableSources @carlbernstein it's a lie,  &amp; Carl can't tell the truth.  He makes my blood boil]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re “friends” really be the ones telling me not to be with you though 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @maryamb for this great article.... 👍🏼 grateful for the wonderful experience of working with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Trump’s farmer bailout just hit $7.7 billion – but 'it no way makes us whole' https://t.co/XKOLozr2ZF via @YahooFinance]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're curious what it's like to try and take a group photo of middle schoolers, meet the Cougar Kaleidoscope Cl… https://t.co/tOKixULZKz]]></document></documents></author>