<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Philippians 4:13    I can do all this through him who gives me strength. #Bible https://t.co/YmDLWPA299]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Let us never forget that a president who is above the law enjoys the characteristics of a king or a dictator… https://t.co/7hBH0bf3CZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Koran says that it's perfectly fine to lie to the infidels, if that answers your question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it so hard for people to believe that a man who lied 8000 times, cheated on all of his wives, allegedly rape… https://t.co/6hNoNu8hhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump regulate him Haiti needs administration and access to capital not this misguided BS proposed. Poli… https://t.co/ibtyRHoSD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intro 2 Autumn Dayze - YouTube https://t.co/haVqtsxzep @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Believe It" https://t.co/rxaytC1ah7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The74 @NoahBookman @COREdistricts @libby_pier @AnalyticsEA @SXSWEDU Such an important topic as many districts are… https://t.co/eCYhIijxoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outlazymedia @ekaterinarazbo1 @bahrash @AnnCoulter @JebBush @realDonaldTrump Well I will agree @realDonaldTrump ra… https://t.co/SAH4tfNupR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robklopatek @KCIAirport @41actionnews No comment 🤷🏾‍♂️😬 https://t.co/KbOQcSDGsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForganySarah @KENS5 @mollyzuber @LeahDurain @MHurstKENS5 @LBlevins121 @AudreyKENS5 @SusanAnasagasti @nia_wesley… https://t.co/ZU6RtHtER2]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Maurstad FEMA CEO of National Flood Insurance Program.  NFIP has big debt that’s cost 1 million dollar a day… https://t.co/6365CnVN6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@david_dorner @AOC @girlscouts Too bad they didn’t teach you basic spelling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: The carefree #Cats are hanging with @BoilerBall. @NUMensBball down 20-18 with 7:35 left in the 1st h… https://t.co/f41fTkECXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulmiranda73 Y aún así dices que Green Book es mejor que Blackkklansman, Roma, The Favorite, Vice y A Star is Bor… https://t.co/qaiSwdg6Y1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does it seem like Pominville does more coaching during the game than Housley?]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wcXfYkBxvh Yum... Thankful... #HollywoodRockStars #JamesPaulRowland #MotownNow… https://t.co/VBmBbs0nf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW! What an amazing few weeks we’ve had on our very first cruise. Yes, we may have lowered the average age of the… https://t.co/CbgWDmodwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gueryyah Buenos días Erika, que tengas un excelente miércoles 😀🌷🌹🌺. Abrazos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[With some research any non fighter coach can give a decent game plan. “Stay away” or “throw punches” or “go” or “kn… https://t.co/NJSa071wSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Syracuse beats Louisville 69-49. Louisville drops to 18-9, 7th in the ACC and still has to play Virginia twice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, Mount Allison has some light accumulation of snow! Snow was seen around the foothills of Mt. Hamilton, Mt. Umu… https://t.co/PxXHOEMPYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[You so fake lol but I’m ready today 😜😂😈😈 I have time for you today miss and I’m not calling no one for you I’m smok… https://t.co/GFvR690Q0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cause is a more complicated debate, but the effect is pretty easy to see...  2018-19 BOSTON CELTICS  DEFENSIVE… https://t.co/IyxWoqEECW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please share with #educators in Massachusetts @MBAENews @teachplusMA @massupt @MASchoolsK12 @MASCSchoolComm @MASCD… https://t.co/b8c7fg3L9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these boundaries are vulnerable. Market-based valuation metrics can be exploited with information warfare techn… https://t.co/ebFkqsJKhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been working on this project nonstop for a week and it feels like it won’t end...maybe my hourly singalong to… https://t.co/jCwxBbTFI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristiancmc @MDpor_elmundo seguro es una estrategia para subirle el precio al PSG.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are there any good papers on skepticism about social justice philosophy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sprdprsam @Whataboutblaine So flying and water types are all I need and GG?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillianArthur9 @truTVjokers @jamessmurray I’m a girl lol, my profile pic is my photo op with @mikeshinoda 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mathewballard @russellquinn This is rich coming from the guy who literally didn't know what he was talking about w… https://t.co/WaHmU9rvte]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fellas eat no more than 2800 calories Ladies eat no more than 2000 calories, on top of working out watch what your… https://t.co/0nDzJs8o1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IfDaysOfTheWeekWerePeople Mondays are I will take what ever you got ! https://t.co/O86zsUnS04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN listening to your show and you are #FakeNews all I hear is lack of facts and nothing but opinions and conjecture!!! Shame!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How fun to go back as an alum of @USF 's program in Community Real Estate Development (CRED) and present to the cur… https://t.co/Q4FqJYYC3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[True. Btw the story of ‘the boy who cried wolf’ is a decent (albeit culture dependent) reminder which is which.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mandalorian_Ren @D_resists @Putzy2010 @MrsRabbitResist @LA_Karma1 @GregCowboys @BusyBrain_Very @robintallfish… https://t.co/1zPHkYay1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuantumHumanity @DeadlineWH @NicolleDWallace Thank's for your inspiration.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slowze_ I think at some point, most of us would. I'm one that wishes my older self could go back and smack my youn… https://t.co/1oBWhLgoA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBA_Skits Everybody knows bball players can't fight.. 'Charles Barkley 😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBlessett @RepMaxineWaters Tell that to your immigrant grandparents or great grandparents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskChaki It’s bumming me out that this is turning into a Yesterday’s Crimes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I want to be more consistent- like the guys on TV.....#stopchasingthingsthatdontexist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenjeong @TheEllenShow I got a how in shed at home too but it do not look like his wife !  Submitted by Bobby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nokisden Yeah, he's super chill.  Although, I guess technically, he's your replacement, and we haven't hired hid yet haha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[8/11 #LBJ said, “This principle is the key to progress for Indians - just as it has been for other Americans. If we… https://t.co/LXeUnt5HpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Biden should pack his bags and stay on the other side of the ocean because he is a non factor in 2020!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thinkprogress Shariah Law is progress? Can’t wait to see liberals eat each other because you’ve gone way too far already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on campus at California Baptist today, Tuesday 5th), if any students, faculty or staff would like to know more… https://t.co/pbqU091zo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanBroaddus Help me understand the putting off shoulder surgery as negotiating ploy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tha_rami I’ve been slowly progressing through KH3 and it makes me so happy. Gives me hope that there’s still space… https://t.co/pD3NJI5fSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pcgamer Don’t fret Microsoft. I’m sure @PalmerLuckey is working on something too and has plenty of engineers willing to develop this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need to start networking with more people.   like this post if you are:  • a music blog writer  • a music blog ow… https://t.co/xQPs0lrIiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday February 21 - Morning Report:    DA’s office reviewing 1,400 cases in fallout from botched drug raid;… https://t.co/8OwR1sIgvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝😍😘 https://t.co/NF6gNQ4vE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sourapplemartini  #pinkwine #vaper 😎 @ Eagle's Nest Restaurant https://t.co/oKNXiYOzkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#carsale #cartalk101 #carsnj #usedcarsnj #cheapcarsnj #affordablecars #gothammotorscorp #mandcautosales @ Teterboro… https://t.co/z2gCbByBUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[R. Kelly: Yes sir.  That old Providence, Rhode Island Facebook judge: You see that? Manners. What a wonderful young man. Case dismissed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennisdire @Bethenny They are horrible! Beverly Hills is still shocking me their tag line quality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skiing is in the LaMontagne blood. Tonight, Bailey skied for the first time and killed it! Couldn’t be happier to s… https://t.co/lDUuPGv0WK]]></document><document><![CDATA[PROUD OF OUR TEAM! @CBS is leading the way by utilizing automated AI tech to run and process thousands of surveys.… https://t.co/NXvrJpNdwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace "anybody left with a conscious in the right-wing propaganda operation" The entire GOP sold it's so… https://t.co/AJMAnnJAFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning world! Hope you all have an awesome and enjoyable Saturday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won't go down without a fight #LEOFamily @FPChief @K9Sid @PfChiefRobledo @fcsok92 @MocksvilleD @BomerKelli… https://t.co/FQieGnwBB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnalive Light hath no communion with darkness. Tho that which is crooked can b made straight. Paul was in darkness… https://t.co/CQGomHTF9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MARINE_99ZULU @BubbaJoeBaker You forgot to say that you are on the phone with a friend and he heard everything. Ch… https://t.co/xsNG6KmI5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Hillary my name is Melvin Clark, I'm registered just not a rich politition ,In all truth I know str… https://t.co/iaJdXOorOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trojanhoopfan Well, if you told me ten minutes ago that they'd only be down by 6 at halftime, I'd have been pleased. Hope Jonah is okay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Herro feeling it early. Pure on that long pull-up two. Both shots tonight have looked perfect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Lupe Tortilla - San Antonio https://t.co/EYbXGTAagJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnHolbein1 @BrendanNyhan It also reduced American citizens penchant to learn foreign languages.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss missalena.92 The White RACE Russian BLONDES👑🇷🇺Women Are The MOST Beautifu… https://t.co/gM9xnt4tDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lisa Vanderpump Calls Out RHOBH Co-Stars for 'Targeting' Her and Refusing to Discuss Their Own Issues, Reveals Whic… https://t.co/a1WivYm1hF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not quite sure what's happening here, I just know I'm hanging out with one of my best buddies in the whole worl… https://t.co/6ogw0C1AVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeridianTweets @Gateway2Muskoka The power is still out, any update on when we can expect it to return? Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God will Back Me Up from @roncarpenter really inspired me! https://t.co/cNsQDu2byJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samdaman32215 @_alexlassen I’ve never met someone who claims to be a YG fan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s never to cold for Ice cream @ Crown Candy Kitchen https://t.co/h4U4HGdp6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skb_sara @JJDJ1187 I would only add “underpaid” American soldier!  But spot on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine... the #pieceofyourlovechallenge but instead of relationships... it’s best friends. I would die. https://t.co/4xo2zAxTQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@startrekcbs is doing so great this season, loving it! Question tho who decided we have to have more lens flares t… https://t.co/tjMgBA9lhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harvard @RadInstitute Never thought myself a soldier for a king. From Quincy  I got fake news. Most valuable thing… https://t.co/yMvuvHHdSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some kinda of ocean mappings going on maybe @NJwhalegirl @GrantonGranton @NYNJBaykeeper been here most of the week… https://t.co/DcEhS3u2Z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hereandnow That’s my neighborhood block party 🎈 pictures! How did you guys get them ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Governor rejects twin tunnel projects funneling water from Northern California to So Cal, instead favors a single t… https://t.co/gxu6Kszilh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iszymax It’s a Yahoo 12 team H2H. 5x5 redraft. Draft is Friday night March 22. If you want to DM your email I can… https://t.co/yV1M76pDaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is an opportunity to bet against a wildly over-hyped horse, in Hidden Scroll, in my opinion. Horse freaked… https://t.co/QPpQWE4Vax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KryceksAngel @NatashaFatah Where do you think she could do us more harm without consequences if she so chooses, here or there?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another February #snowday in Easton.  #snow #winter #weather @NWS_MountHolly Photos for @lehighvalley https://t.co/kW900zdeYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueRobotDesign @realDonaldTrump Not me. I hope he is a two-term president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyHargis And he knows the room you are in... https://t.co/IljwiajSqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets If they are too far left I will not. Stuff like free college is stupid. Need to put money into kids not men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao bitch going out swinging hard. Niggas gone say some slush on the news. Whole ass foot a snow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BureauSports Also, essentially getting Duke -1 on the game. I’ll take it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Possums. @ Ron Leach's Living Room https://t.co/ytxMAvCPkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimHank7 @RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump Well to be perfectly honest about it.... Hillary was real mad because she wa… https://t.co/144e81URZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCardConnect Even though the Duke game can be played out as the one that broke Louisville, I honestly think Loui… https://t.co/AruaWDfSi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sizzal loool. one life though. 😂🤷🏽‍♂️ and I know it’s not, but it’s still a coping mechanism. 🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live look at Cassie telling Colton she doesn’t love him and then running away. https://t.co/wdgvDG2AUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouiseCarduner Yes. We use a blend of urea and ESN.  The frequent freeze-thaw here pulls it right into the soil.]]></document></documents></author>