<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ChargersCR @RiddellSports @usafootball CC: @missionfootball @TrabucoFootball @SMCHS_Football]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmydaisy123 @USAmbIsrael @realDonaldTrump @LindseyGrahamSC You don't seem to care that Palestinian leaders are ru… https://t.co/AAlUBaeRAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conservative like any taxonomy is prone to distortion. It has been made a tincture to disguise animus as we know. A… https://t.co/i4DfUMZKaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m following my purpose. God has asked me to help my community, and I do it with the youth. I have a lot of pride,… https://t.co/M9E5rUXJfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beto O’Rourke attends Metallica concert – Consequence of Sound https://t.co/2VxMiMkRQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[El PC llaman a movilizarse por una ley que ellos mismos aprobaron, @KarolCariola y Tellier votaron que Si,… https://t.co/3WDbpCBKKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone give me their extra ticket for @theghostinside and I’ll give you a free 2 day pass for @sowhatmusicfest. I don’t wanna miss this 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClubSantos @ayrtonpreciado Ojalá y despierte en los próximos juegos ahora le dieron un regalo y dio pases buenos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mueller is too taciturn and professional to air such grievance aloud. I think Barr is proving to be the Trojan Hors… https://t.co/CEx1efvzVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColinCowherd just said u can’t build around Russell Westbrook because a 10 year old boy touched his arm last night… https://t.co/jiS2uiOuv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain @Kris_Sacrebleu 5 TIME DRAFT DODGER, and yes , we think you’re stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[A. This kid’s mechanics are A1 ... jumper looks smooooove and already working on the euro.  B. He already knows the… https://t.co/4KusQBuDHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiranEC I had this experience last week. We are our own worst critics!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure how 2 theorize, but Trump appealed on 2 issues not institutionalized w/in GOP coalition.  Even pre-16, man… https://t.co/o6iu26zxM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@progressivehere @GottaLaff @JanSKay @maddow It's supposed to be a news show. Save the serial crap for the podcasts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love not the world, neither the things that are in the world. If any man love the world, the love… https://t.co/Ya2bcYGwjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother: Isn't that Miles Davis? Me: That's definitely not Miles Davis. My brother: No wait, the other Miles. Me… https://t.co/14OU395KC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zulu is making its way down Canal Street @WWLTV #BeOn4 https://t.co/RKJOPQm62S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think IHOP, Denny’s, Sizzler and Cracker Barrel https://t.co/W5bGWPZWtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Writing and research for “Welcome to Beautiful Point Pleasant”. My next photo essay hopefully ready in May. @ Lynch… https://t.co/XlHGPAS6kg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pas climatosceptiques désolé !  On sait qu'ils ont été banni â Radio-Canada ! Non disons plutôt climato-réaliste.… https://t.co/uXh03jqIxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[From @NCIS_CBS :  @POTUS @VP @senatemajldr “The world is bad enough without you making it any worse.” Why are you guys making it worse?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning I am checking off boxes on my to-do list like a boss AND pursuing a feud on Facebook at the same time.… https://t.co/ja67bEIjdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Did you know in the 1800’s” @kristamarieyu  “No one likes history Jen” @NancyATravis  “And these are the stories m… https://t.co/zZicy0a1dD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BunnyBumBun @Readykins I’m bisexual and bi means one or more so it CAN be two or more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@venuslvnda @NinodaFilipino IM LOYAL FUCK IS U TALM BOUT MY NAME IS GETTING SLANDERED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucy had a great back dive for her second dive. @_shsstudentsect @Shsswimdive1 https://t.co/yg8fge7RLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aelogann Literally just found your album yesterday from that day. We were all so sweaty!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#USC SPRING PRACTICE NO. 1 TODAY‼️   Practice begins at 2:30pm today on Howard Jones Field - Open to the Public  We… https://t.co/KeSodXNRjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeltzerPlease @AnnaProsser @HelloKellyLink @pancakepow @Smix The best folks 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GordonVoit @GQQSE13 @RailerNation @LCHStudentSec @LincolnCommHS @ibcacoaches @IHSAState @TVance09 As a kid, I reme… https://t.co/bx6jmeJk6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Pale Sour Ale by @BreweryOmmegang at @TheBrainIsNow — https://t.co/qgiIou0bnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bracketology Bubble Watch: Oklahoma, UCF pick up critical wins for their tournament resumes https://t.co/ZgSL6WCr18… https://t.co/40uiL2I5uz]]></document><document><![CDATA[By reversing O’Malley, Hogan would do the right thing — commute the sentence of a man who has served 47 years for a… https://t.co/0Wal53FrFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi hermana se esguinzó el cuello dormida nmms jajaja carrilla por 3 semanas]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s just this simple of a choice!!! I choose Capitalism https://t.co/dvHtSKFiIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #FortWorth, TX, check out this #IT job via the link in our bio: Engineer/Senior Engin… https://t.co/K7YSM1pGVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready player one has to be one of the most disappointing movies I've ever seen. One of my favorite books, just awful film]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @sachsau1 Don Lemon Head is Simply another lying hate propagandist extremist. Lemon Head has less commonsense than a rock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a great conversation with @_CoachEmbry I am grateful to earn my offer to Vermilion College ‼️✅⚒💙💛… https://t.co/lnCTNNUBds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge win for @coachscottyp and his wolves! Congratulations and keep it going!]]></document><document><![CDATA[couldn’t be happier for @hunterpence ... too bad the Rangers won’t be coming to SF this season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wonder if the #s10 will sell well. If it does then we have a problem; if people are willing to drop $1400+ C… https://t.co/RY9Ii7LS93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Genderplasmic I DIDN’T DO ANYTHING EVER TO PISS HER OFF MY SHITTY LUCK HAS BEEN HAPPENING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonydombrowski @johvincan Learn behind stafford like Rodgers and favre... could work out. But not for cardinals as… https://t.co/9eeF4Nl2Xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BardicLoreBlog Oh man. Florida is not what we call prime hiking country…. #BeSafe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panic! At the Disco - A Fever You Can’t Sweat Out 1) Lying is the Most Fun a Girl Can Have Without Taking Her Cloth… https://t.co/nBEaxFIDcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @AmyJohnsonNews @AlexBistonTV @joybenedict happy Saturday morning everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@puck_20 We know exactly how it happens the entire genetic blue print is formed at the moment of conception. No Add… https://t.co/tPgF7MOwGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MNCarolina5 I'm glad Caris is getting back to playing. Joe Harris is king.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustSomeGoat1 Looks like firing that second bullet paid off! Ship this thing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve yet to see an Ohio state possession where Kaleb Wesson hasn’t set a moving screen, yet he only has one foul in this game🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are KJV Only people who actually think it is better to translate the KJV into other languages rather than tra… https://t.co/iyCaa9G7bl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gate C35 for @SouthwestAir at @DENAirport is my ticket to #BigSkyInBoise!  Fast turnaround after @NAUBasketball's h… https://t.co/kqeUyqtyuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad has an Apple Watch and sometimes I can’t figure out if he just doesn’t understand it works or if he just str… https://t.co/MuIuViGebZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Really Schiffty?  Really?  I think you are the arrogant idiot using the government as a tool for a v… https://t.co/EAHPbG2Tl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just catching up on Big Brother!! Amazing job @TamarBraxtonHer!!! ♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigVT @nflnetwork @NFL @AB84 @LeVeonBell they still have great players in Connor and Juju, they won’t be bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun surfing small waves today after skiing all morning. @ Newport Beach, California https://t.co/WDvcWX6oS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The map in here makes me surprised Chicago has so few dog parks. Or is NYC weird?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timshamrock13 @reddmac9 @NateInSports @JoshBloomer I believe this is true of every school in an open enrollment district though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[12-Minute Indoor Power Walking Workout @SparkPeople https://t.co/1jqT3sZM2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why I’m glad I don’t have to give winter outlooks on television anymore. :D]]></document><document><![CDATA[problems.  He is an unselfish man. He understands our problems more than any recent president including Republican… https://t.co/sVnG9puRIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the type of blatant, unnecessary and constant lying Trump does that is an embarrassment. Anyone who saw the… https://t.co/68MxZjqKrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreyOnTop Depends on the circumstance... a club is def not the place that I’m trying to spend money on a woman with substance at Lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why The House and Senate are separate Bodies of government, if the Republicans in both bodies when they wer… https://t.co/TancTdw48H]]></document><document><![CDATA[These five made pitchers shake in their stirrup socks. Soak in these staggering stats - combined lifetime: 13,478 h… https://t.co/lHpD0s8Z44]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see the power of sport impact a community in so many ways.  #SportsBiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt_lansford Used to have awesome burgers, closed in the mid 80s? https://t.co/MicygrKmmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stagosaurus @CoachGoddardFM Those speed numbers are generous to say the least.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a patient tell me him and his wife were married for 70 years and when I asked what his secret was he said “keep your mouth shut”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[these 2 have made living in nyc even more special @krownvic7 + lightningbands ❤️😍. love them to the moon and back 🥰… https://t.co/C8K3SSfDP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Its been a National Emergency for decades. The Republicans are as guilty as the Dems of allowing our nati… https://t.co/Bauaq1qDFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterVogel You transmit on LSB and receive on USB so the sideband is inverted by the transponder on the satellite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @AOC @IlhanMN Wow, David Duke likes her, that’s just what democrats need, the KKK comes home to roost .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Nani moments away from having some fun onstage. Kisses Nana. #eugeneonegin #lenski #Fillipenya #nanny #crone… https://t.co/SmeTTY8ACH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport Well...alcohol IS a gateway drug, right boys?  @GOP And Roger is just expressing his right to free sp… https://t.co/Ip8B9A7gpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC @GMA Another Demo Governor enters... governors are the best path to the White House]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder what could have POSSIBLY driven them out of NYS?!? This place needs to encourage biz growth, not stifle it… https://t.co/V9JJzagexi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RVLife #RVtravel #rvwithtony #camping #Campervan #travel #TravelTuesday #Vacations #vacationmode #vacationtime… https://t.co/0wpOFp8Kff]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RAVELL and #Friends #LivingTheDream with #KingSizeLED @ Academy LA https://t.co/0bYr2rhohT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every good lawyer knows do you build a case. And as you build the case and you build it well and you get all the do… https://t.co/xl6Yq74MwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Necrot - 3/10/2019 - Baltimore Soundstage - AWESOME and CLEAR guitar tone! #necrot #deathmetal #baltimoresoundstage… https://t.co/PvRhOnrKvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KianpourWorld New lies to Congress could certainly lead to new charges. Any witness needs to be very careful about… https://t.co/JQenCI8x32]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just gonna tweet this everytime the lakers lose until he’s gone https://t.co/EZ8yp7ywRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @Boyle33 on his first start and first shutout in the NHL! 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrRDMartin Thank you for the clarification. Do you happen to know how the US as a whole compares with the rest of… https://t.co/FUr9GKWi8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Your Motives can be a Rocket 🚀 that Launches you to Great Things or Missile that will Immobilize you!’~Daniel Doster-Mann]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reds So happy that our son was able to spend a year learning from one of the greatest to play!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@still_rambling @TorontoStar Interesting. So you mean, what are the parameters of severity within a DPA? Good question]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday February 19 - Today's Headlines from The Boston Globe:    Trump warns Venezuelan military they could ‘lose… https://t.co/Hwp60gq913]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Exercising is fun” - President Meathead at his summit press conference]]></document><document><![CDATA[10/ Until it can be proven that CO2 emissions are settled then any debate of premature closure of nuclear power pla… https://t.co/lGRfSm5Rr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What now? Who should be doing the condemning? 🤷🏼‍♂️ Maybe someone should act the honorable adult and call what’s wh… https://t.co/rGm2PU7DJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisG86275919 Agree on all points there. Many people messsure success in monetary amounts. The emotional side is… https://t.co/Ng5J5iWWTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMSTechGuy Thanks, good morning &amp; happy Monday 😊 Have a great day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denise4607 @KindeandTrue @jarue369 @masksofeternity @CharlieCanFly I had the honor of visiting and praying in the… https://t.co/YWgYtzMe54]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oopskye it was the best option bc if we didn’t take drastic measures the japanese would have retaliated. that’s wh… https://t.co/i6RAkL4CnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had all intentions of doing something tonight but ended up doing nothing... let me go ahead to sleep 😑]]></document></documents></author>