<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Big thank you to the staffs at Georgia, Clemson and Georgia Tech for opening there doors to us to watch a little fi… https://t.co/yP7PddiFSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulMac0413 @krassenstein Lies? Excuse me?? So you condone the top officials in the FBI orchestrating a plot (coup… https://t.co/3QX8wgAyrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[A shorter time span which I will enjoy more, and be better able to afford.  Not seeing the downside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope this story doesn't go away under an avalanche of money like it did several years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#notfromtoday #gameday #865life #basketball #collegebasketball #collegelife #sports #sportsphotography #vols… https://t.co/unVQ1Cn4Ri]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you kind taco for always coming through 🏍🍻🤙 https://t.co/ailBSTpNln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good To My Earhole, February 28. #musicjunkie #beatles #themodernlovers #jonathanrichman #bobdylan @ Parkade, Colum… https://t.co/xjwbpux01I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPJannyBarrera @Fanny5661 Estoy totalmente de acuerdo EU y compania acorralan no a lis politicos pero si al pueblo… https://t.co/OtquGzb87t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@howiemandel Hi Howie, I was talking to a young lady [sister of friend] and discussed my desire to help Children's… https://t.co/xemtPr7Z9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check it out! I donated to 'Sheliba’s Memorial Service' -  https://t.co/lKIcd7pejv via @gofundme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hilbay was my student when he was in 2P EHS. He was an excellent student. His formal themes were beautifully writte… https://t.co/IyglPDaNaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wyndspirit @SandySh69661491 @RWPUSA @the Well said. Neo christian ism. Form of religion with no content.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jocelynnhe @edtamhe @MtzGuizar @EmilianoCantS @Redfoo Ya cálmate Beatriz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chemigraphik Oxydationsprozess by Kilian Breier... @ Museum of Fine Arts, Boston https://t.co/U8tV0TaRIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foul count 9-2. I’m not saying that we didn’t could KU. I AM saying that we didn’t foul them 9 times. Like 5 at best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iaindwelch @AliceDrawstLine @NTCroftCastle @StCuthbertsMill @JacksonsArtTalk Beautufil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraigKreindler The great irony, of course, is that he was one of the most cerebral of baseball announcers after a… https://t.co/5ypj9HC0Bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me win this awesome giveaway from @GunWinner https://t.co/duIKuRmF8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for some craft beer  #birthdayweekend #beer #cheers #drinklocalbeer #drinklocalcraftbeer #ontariocraftbeer… https://t.co/84Co8Sr23A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 Let me think about that for a--- No not a damn bit. I'm sick of these wealthy assholes that think the… https://t.co/03oCXJazjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[no matter what nothing will ever be as easy as me and him. that’s it. that’s the tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews I need to get cable TV, sounds like MSNBC is a great comedy channel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dog day afternoon with #hunterbeardykman @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/5pOI0Q6x6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sassmasterstaci A gym closest to your home or a gym   Between your work and home is ideal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going through older pieces and decided to clean up and color this one. #dnd5e #drawing #animation #characters… https://t.co/OJC30HVpc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 10, 2003 – AC/DC are inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame by Aerosmith’s Steven Tyler.  The band went… https://t.co/naWGxg5aKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning laughs.  #troyvelez #model #me #modeltroyvelez #sexy #selfie #hotboy #chocolate #handsome #boricua #body… https://t.co/3tVPuk8rku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newark Catholic girls lead Northside Christian 40-2 after one quarter @NewarkCatholic #nahss @NCWAVEPOOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[....Zion had to be laughing all the way to the bank. Also Skechers next hoop shoe will be it's first one. https://t.co/nXDkwgY1i5]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd goal of the season for @Matt_Grzelcyk5 (who had 1 point-an assist on Feb. 6 at NYR in his last 15 games); 52nd… https://t.co/S8WJ50GWRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you need a public speaker for  upcoming events? Please consider Lawrence Hamm 973 801-0001 #Speaker… https://t.co/EG7iloVrGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moving day! @OklahomaBway #2 #dressingroomselfie https://t.co/upwizEq6Ek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwlz @drbarnard Yeah, that would suck if Twitter were like that for me. Good thing it doesn’t have to be like that… https://t.co/Yv7HAwEQs2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cumminsatyalive: Are you a happy baby!?!?!? 😁😁😁 @Jett butnotaplane: AAAAAAHHHHHHH 🙂🙂🙂 #ParkerPosse @ Colorado Spri… https://t.co/FSSFgZvYX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve learned more about business, from selling my old Jordan’s. Than I did in business school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess the saying “9 to 5” just flows better than “9 to 5:30.” We all know we don’t get paid for our lunch break]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwwdotLB @TraiDay79 There’s a phrase in the sign language handbook that I’m pretty sure would work as a response to this......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 I literally can't fucking believe you're a government official]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave In the past I have referred too many politicians most of them Democrats as political whores, who else… https://t.co/AhYV1OpMjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finnc94 @Storyful Yes the video was taken by me. Yes you may use the video. It is for public information only.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lending my voice for the visually impared on a new project today @Point360 #voactor #film #narration #roadtrip… https://t.co/tP9kVzBRyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[💩 #deadleg 📹 haleyisaak @ Simi Valley Town Center https://t.co/cugqeFn2D9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just want a cute Mexican boyfriend. Is that too much to ask. It shouldn’t be hard in Dallas fucking Texas in the ga… https://t.co/H6VFHYFv78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading this month's @NatGeoMag &amp; I am mesmerized by a pic of a glasswing butterfly. So cool. #iheartnature https://t.co/S4pAGKerPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stizmaster @HeathMayo @jed20004 @FoxNews You’re a little slow. The issue I spoke about is much bigger that the ant… https://t.co/Q7VlUTvYIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Episode ft @Cody_Nolove @lionheartasmith @USMAN84kg @Ruthless_RL !!!!!!!!  The Anatomy of UFC 235: Vlog Series… https://t.co/navdsfOcRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeafsHub @leafknowitall64 Everyone said Leafs have goaltending issues they picked up Freddy  They said Leafs don't… https://t.co/bSFhu9vZmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Night shift has me so fucked up, I can’t even go to bed at a decent time on my days off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lopezobrador_ Pienso que en el pasado, se cedieron demasiadas complacencias al gobierno de USA, aún por encima de… https://t.co/VkXxgU7IKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always afraid of this. Ready to side step. Also fire escape ladders. And collapsing sidewalks (there were like 3 of… https://t.co/8Zq0U7lgvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AHORA #coffeetime #24Feb #DiaDeLaBandera #FelizDomingo #Gratitud #Grammy2019 #GuardiaCivil https://t.co/j9ROCpDiUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dzeoli @CoryAlexanderVA @lebrownlow @AlexFarmartino That is a correct statement but he has many options to choose… https://t.co/n3qMqfGG1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not even my eldest #patient. Cannabis can be very helpful. #mmj #Boston #health #wellness #sexuality]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyLiberty2020 @AOC Free speech is probably one of our greatest freedoms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickMahomes @nfldraftscout Get-that-DOGGO! 😂 https://t.co/ufxVzSxbMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nykofr "Carol even became cosmically empowered and took on the codename Binary. The Binary powers faded over time,… https://t.co/NFJAtcImlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WolverineCorner @jacksteph777 Michigan 64, Michigan State 61 Poole with 12.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IfeJohnseen And this is why more people need to hear about the wisdom of God in the Christ,even if it’s a totally different approach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VHSL Girls Class 2 bracket..  The field shrinks again. Then there were 4 https://t.co/EIkG2egPLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alex Honnold is rocking a The North Face tuxedo for the Oscars? Epic‼️🏔 #thenorthface #bestdocumentary… https://t.co/96GqA2Vspe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirtualBondGirl @10holte @5klp471 @Mikel_Jollett That type of foreign participation in American politics is acceptable?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kid slept over at Mimi and pops. Wife has work. Whole house to myself on this fine Monday. Nice little break and reset.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNnewsroom @Acosta @BrookeBCNN I'm asking for the emancipation of the infant. You gave to the helpless slave now… https://t.co/U7LmTFBlpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly really happy lots of people see me as "that guy that obsesses over Ryougi Shiki" (or hisui)  that's good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FPPTim So. You say...why CALIFORNIA... when you are maxed out in NY... Do you think the DEMS in NY dont know you a… https://t.co/B81MgYmNCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't know who made this but I saw it on Facebook. https://t.co/Aa0hjqeFw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll never understand why one-bid leagues send their tournament champion to the Big Dance and not their regular sea… https://t.co/H1gSSujGf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: In lost season, Kings can at least find some answers: The strong temptation now, after a 4-3 overt… https://t.co/5PZwbmPnfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattwhitlockPM I’ll play them This Song right here By @JABBstract https://t.co/8nc8U9T4Cq]]></document><document><![CDATA[New shaving soap #allnatural #traditionalshaving #wetshave #safetyrazor https://t.co/pPhZwQTUOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proverbs 31:25. -She is clothed with strength and dignity and she laughs without fear of the future. 💙✝️🙏🏽… https://t.co/uk9eFZfuaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonBrownstein @CNN Here’s what changed: a lot of fucking people were murdered]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C1231Will @nfldata Herndon and Hooper were nice Waiver finds in redraft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@infinirama616 @DuckTalks @kc_cornell94 Yea, if it has all 3 retail volumes, there should be no reason why there ar… https://t.co/mPuTSqXXry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EAEO that prompted that mostly ha. But the Trail of Dead ‘Madonna’ set as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice to see how many people are as crazy as I am to be waking up at 4am 🤟🏼 See you in a second, Lincoln Tunnel. @lyft #LyftLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidakin This is profoundly disappointing. I expected so much more from the cabinet then abandoning our PM. This… https://t.co/JOnOMW8Fny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivianvalverde @Phoenix2124 Pongo la alarma y apenas suena me levanto. No lo pienso mucho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toll from natural gas disaster in Merrimack Valley passes $1 billion https://t.co/R1wEDypMFg via @BostonGlobe]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was thinking 💭, “Crap, I’ve got to find some excuse, any reason to appoint an independent counsel so Mueller can… https://t.co/2LaYqvx8WV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell pilot you all have dialed his 2 outlast in all over the track surface. #ToolBoxFilledCorrectly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday morning I snapped this picture as I was rather proud of our period style Novgorod Street path inside our m… https://t.co/Ux7bfIzBGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. Questioning the power of aipac is not anti-semitic #pasttimeforrealdebate #hatersprovepoint]]></document><document><![CDATA[people change &amp; people go. but new ones always appear and will be there forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got some great pictures from #WWEYoungstown tonight. https://t.co/xntdBkTQT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If they only had Best #Jerkoff Award .... @ImNoRoleModel #SpikeLee #Spike #Oscars #OscarAwards #BlackKlansman ....… https://t.co/HPnUWpcLra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celtics are going nowhere. Lose to the 16-44 Bulls. I truly hope Kyrie jumps ship. They were better off without him… https://t.co/iv8lY5Loor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe Philpott and Wilson-Raybould could have taken one for the Liberal team?  #StandWithTrudeau #LPC #JWR… https://t.co/hMeON47fQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buffett’s line this morning—“the business does not earn more just because you pay more for it”—pairs nicely with: t… https://t.co/YqL6LUi84t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PNWchappie @karmakrayonn @MMFlint @AOC They're carbon copies and 100% yes to both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings Trump gives himself a grade of 'A+' ▲https://t.co/C46rWTG3Y3  #Anomaly? ▲https://t.co/vjeJzG7zkU  Trum… https://t.co/0VKxLogKlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[CLIMATE CHANGE IS A HOAX AND YOU SIR ARE A JOKE AND STAND NO CHANCE WHATSOEVER OF WINNING ANYTHING !! 😡😡😡💩💩💩🤮🤮🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apasionarme de mi propósito! En mi POSIBILIDAD 68/365 elijo VIVIR. https://t.co/ZY7hFQ3oL1 #santos… https://t.co/LOICzeEiqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh you haven’t signed up for our winter seminar yet?! This is @CoachKevinCarr look of disapproval. What are you wai… https://t.co/YNcau9n4Vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I plugged it in to the back of my TV 📺 again I thought it was tragically broken now I have it back on to watch… https://t.co/RYZgQRvjVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tereneh152XX 😂😭😂 the ancestors wanted you to see the horror of the past 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows If it’s not declared a national emergency @realdonaldtrump will lose his base @potus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did every one start fuckin with ynw Melly when he got locked up lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rheddroyale @SaVanity__ @rozierdusse I can’t tell you that on this app.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adashtra @liopleurodonic i spent 30 minutes looking for ONE photo of the dragons winning and ended up using yours… https://t.co/t1J3BY1a7R]]></document></documents></author>