<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Sylvia @SenatorSinema office. So great to be able to talk about access to affordable and adequate healthc… https://t.co/ar4FlIeTxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anniecox_ If this is asking if u can be in the feminist five head gang of course bb yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many more disasters are cooked into Socialists Green Manifesto brought to America by @RepAOC @SenMarkey… https://t.co/w8xwPalAeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ufffff this shit hurts 💉💉💉💉 working with one of the best in Miami @fametattoos 🐻🦍🐻🦍🐻🦍🐻🦍🐻🦍😍😍🐻😍🦍 @ Fame Tattoos https://t.co/Xuq3NuZu32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @ow in this week's @chargedtech edition, you've mentioned the Mate X but written it as though Xiaomi launched i… https://t.co/9Crs0RXcC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the @DNC does @BernieSanders dirty again, I'll want to unregister as a Democrat.  #2020election #Bernie2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smittyfooledu @JimCarrey I saw the capsule take off away  from the moon and saw the spacecraft  land in the ocean… https://t.co/MjH1lMXKfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our executive producer came in to the studio to explain how the top of the 7 am would play out. This is the way she… https://t.co/u4koZxLzYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the winner is ...@JumaaneWilliams #publicadvocatenyc #1010WINS https://t.co/Go5G18xbmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was v disappointed that Mike didn’t reference Good Place (even though I told him to). Very easily could’ve squeez… https://t.co/2kdSKsKEbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Norton, OH? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/OqFW3RGTkt #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TinaDaheley really enjoyed my chat with Rachel. Could I trouble you for a retweet please? Would be hugely apprecia… https://t.co/7Bro7aFWbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[APARTMENT FIRE: Firefighters w/ IFD are trying to get a burning apartment building under control on Orchard Ave nea… https://t.co/z02HcwvSNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 Oh yea....a nice big chewy bone for my pal there. For every day of the year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is only one response I can muster today thinking about the total DISGRACE the #DemocraticParty has become. I… https://t.co/P7cLQHJmeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cormorán orejón (Phalacrocorax auritus) Balandra, La Paz, Baja California Sur, México  #mexico #mexico🇲🇽… https://t.co/cnNLls7pee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everone now on the count of three-1-2-3 : JESUS IS LORD!! Now enjoy His Peace!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guitar667 Do you make shirts with your art https://t.co/ZkpAhRZwXn amazonmerch teespring dazzle red bubble]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re supposed to be calling out Trump supporters for supporting such a racist piece of shit 🗣🗣🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would love to take one of these through the obstacle course one more time @LCFR_DCTRAINING ! #oldtimer… https://t.co/UVNnsf4kyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy hell, yeah, I did miss this. My fault for not being more plugged in. Don’t go to That Party. https://t.co/7ZkC12zioD]]></document><document><![CDATA[3. of 4.) Some of the none major networks, rent, some of the junkies movies. It makes no sense. There are so many g… https://t.co/drguwfvrW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Ravenna Urban Italian Restaurant - @ravennaitalian in Dallas, TX https://t.co/evD7sEH6g3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatkid_diff @Jared_Carrabis @playoff__b Pipe dream bro. Got 26 million for this year in arbitration which set a r… https://t.co/LrWOsIa78F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Harrah's Lake Tahoe Resort &amp; Casino - @caesarsent in Stateline, NV https://t.co/kTZwnygnFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c_isforcynthia @gopherit007 Yall are boujee thats why. Yo soy de rancho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TFlo3422 @SoniaAzadTV @News8Daybreak @DJLC_Dapper So glad you’re back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonWSOC9 @wsoctv The previous @NCSBE apparently warned the Bladen County Improvement Association that they wer… https://t.co/f5Gw3hmelz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como último consejo, disfrutad de la cuaresma y no preocuparos por el tiempo. Sirve de poco. Es mejor vivir el mome… https://t.co/HJnQa3jJM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISSSTE_mx @LuisAntoRamirez En Nuevo León También https://t.co/sHAja9mYDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash Who in the Hell is watching CNN anymore? They report news. Just lies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why, yes @LittleDebbie, I'd love to be your Valentine! #HappyValentinesDay https://t.co/3pDa6yITvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of yall rl be doing too much. We are grown adults outta high school tf I look like still fighting?? 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thewrightleader @teacherasleader @tamaraletter @LevineWrites @MaireCervenak @BiscottiNicole @Mrs_Gilchrist… https://t.co/MF7oUZPzay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chagolo78 Ella no está loca, ella sabe que eso no le va a afectar a ella]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm...I get it, it's a #message in a #bottle!  #Darn, if I could only #hear what she's #saying... :((]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hey druggie,SPACEX is a privately owned company that has nothing to do with the… https://t.co/dIb9ZSAdJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@intelligencer This piece definitely fails the Marie Kondo test; it does not bring joy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezraswifey Pretty sure I have no recollection of this. But I have been known to say things like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[McGregor knocking out Aldo is still one of the craziest if not the craziest moment in sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- what is the worst theft of thought? C- people will repeat what I had said exactly and try to claim it was there… https://t.co/lyYl2ZUPRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends Or we have a president who doesn’t pay attention, ignores intelligence he doesn’t l… https://t.co/PHPCv50TnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdiane01 @mick12346 @FPVaughanIII @kinsellawarren @MaximeBernier @KinsellaWarran WE all have this bunch has no… https://t.co/t5Bf6FBQiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachzipfel @dennisdoddcbs “Just a blip ... we’ve never lost a recruit because another school cheated.” - K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had fun at the Heinz History Center today and seeing the traveling Apollo 11 exhibit!! #heinzhistorycenter… https://t.co/xEcNPaTQZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLWPres @JLWDC @JuniorLeague A President deserving of the Day for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mindy Davey- Morgan's Song (Anti-Bullying Video) https://t.co/SKe1utWNBN via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madgic79 @jjmid04 @william_huitt04 I don’t take many things personally. All good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[STL ❄️ -&gt; MIA ☀️🌴🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎🦎 (etc)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madeleintlSUR @vladimirpadrino Maldita rata obesa, de cerebro pequeño, lento y que con gran dificultad emites soni… https://t.co/KnAFlLlRZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t worry, The Mayor is taking care of Federal and world issues!  Plowing and taking of roads is below is job !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanyadua Makes me think they don’t actually want you to take the name out. They want the recognition for having th… https://t.co/uf2aKchwbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LonepineTom And a variety of ongoing Federal Investigations from Manhattan and DC, to Virginia. All important.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I start scouting this weekend for Evolution Metrix and I’ll be back with SJSU Football Video for spring ball in March. Lets get it. 🤑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zamoose @williamsba @jeffr0 Back in my day, it was still XBMC. #getoffmylawn https://t.co/0RpsKkGFub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerseyTom @Pullthepocket @o_crunk @jeremyclemons Well i think the concept “one size fits all” was a huge mistake.… https://t.co/cOoA80ZoCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TheDeanAmbrose wants @DMcIntyreWWE in a #NoDQ, #FallsCountAnywhere match! IT’S GONNA HAPPEN! This is personal. #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@British_Airways @ShannonAirport You are doing an excellent job with these retrojets, BA! Such a fine heritage to celebrate, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting. I’d rather see the NFL remove the “no game airs during a team’s home game” blackout rule.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good point! Well noted. Great campaign add for the DNC MEDIA to put out. Average Americans all saying they have wor… https://t.co/QEfVmDZ4Q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theculturecraft @EHRC So being anti-racist means you get a pass on Antisemitism?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 No @DonaldJTrumpJr, America just really hates @realDonaldTrump for his despicable acts, treason, raci… https://t.co/hyNPTBAVnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFromCranber Only way they can win....cheat...remember Donna Brazille??? Not sure why any network would give he… https://t.co/lYhXduh3bH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aappel @jockowillink @AOC @jordanbpeterson I trust Jocko's answer. I'm not a fan of the total Petersen worldview.… https://t.co/c04cdd6eZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austinkleon I crack up about the story that the “cello cello cello cello” was meant as a placeholder, but they end… https://t.co/GU3wuFb3pH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There Are More With Us” Don’t be overwhelmed by the pressure, there are more with you then against you. Today’s de… https://t.co/5OdBR21yRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elena_aka_MizRo That is my hope... my fear is that nothing will happen and this will continue for 2-6 more years.… https://t.co/qZFCgeO8eA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Englewood Elementary dedicates special section of library to Hudson Fife, an 11-year-old who was killed in a huntin… https://t.co/HdWe2yApn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spoiler 🚨: If you spend more than a few minutes around me, I’ll have you laughing uncontrollably. #YouveBeenWarned]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctothep20 It’s more intimate when they person at the deli knows what you want and still gives you a sample]]></document><document><![CDATA[Schedule &amp; Info for this morning's Girls Soccer scrimmage at Monticello is here in our 'Virtual Program'.… https://t.co/eloLNz1u3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the nostradamus effect before work and now I’m completely convinced the world is gonna end in 2012]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2DoisToby @James_BG @hugh_knowles Indeed. There was a time when the signal was subtle and discussing it required nuance, but no longer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning everyone ☕☕☕☕.....never enough sleep...at least I get to see my son today after yesterday's shit show...not… https://t.co/ukDVUzoLGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our neighbors took a trip to the Vines in Mendoza last year...it sounded amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judyvinson612 @Alyssa_Milano @NRA @realDonaldTrump Don't look in the mirror and you won't be so disgusted]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldn't be where I am today without the opportunities I got from @hampshirecolg's CBD program. They funded my ex… https://t.co/6o6mdHRDP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please be on the lookout for my new book “My Struggles With Water Retention in a Soy Sauce Heavy Culture or ‘Fresh… https://t.co/dqYBWys6Nj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just saying. Bitches are coming out like woodwork lately. Why can’t cockroaches fucking die.]]></document><document><![CDATA[messy, problematic, expose you if you piss them off gays are a BIG PART of the reason why  homophobia is so strong.… https://t.co/916stDIqqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[That part! 💯🎯 #FoodForThought #OneToGrowOn #Inspirational #Motivational #Positive #Powerful #Affirmations… https://t.co/j6c8cuYdZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2501Wolf @Danie1607 @JUBILEE_7DOUBLE @RoosterforTrump @AmbDaniDayan @DaveSchreiber3 @IsraelUSAforevr… https://t.co/YGQGxKJE4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the dad of two AMAZING daughters and the husband of an AMAZING wife I know the present and furlture are brighter… https://t.co/LUlp8HD0O1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mockman That's me! I get up, walk around the room, get into it... it's my players that are low key!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought and re-watched this movie tonight.  If you haven’t seen it, do yourself a favor and watch it.  One of the… https://t.co/PaGl4QpLFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rlujanloveless That’s basically what i said to a popular Christian pastor 😂 https://t.co/ITR45EJO2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫String Quintet in A minor Op. 25 No. 6 (G300): II. Minuetto by Europ… https://t.co/dtXAyNuoEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of our students and staff. Today's evacuation drill was a success.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahs_43 @KentStFootball @CoachZacBarton @TheOC_CoachLew thank you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travelchannel something is messed up with the travel channel it says a makeup show is on but that starts at 4am it… https://t.co/KHNdgUJcyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[With that said, a total lack of adjustment, a Kadri suspension, and Andersen having a rough series still got the Le… https://t.co/uglrNwPO4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Basso488 What is the shoulder patch?  I never saw Purolator in an Indy car before either....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeMikalsen There's room for a diverse range of views in the Democratic Party today. A pretty stark contrast to w… https://t.co/1eL6FHvKxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, @GibranMaciel and I are doing a #caleg and #capolitics news roundup on #SacTownTalks by #TheNooner podcast… https://t.co/8VRiEBnyTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Domestic violence is not a funny issue we can just drive over with mildly hilarious meme 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tired of seein these black kids on the face of Fox. And fuck CNN, they don’t wanna see us win 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valspar prep akshaybhatia_1 @ Dustin Johnson Golf School https://t.co/UFB1JjRXdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilovemgjc @kjngofpops But he could have been embarrassed to admit it happened, grown ass women lie to protect thei… https://t.co/QvKvwtoRqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewSitman Welp, I wasn’t offended charcoal face masks before but you betcha I am now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shazzilla44 @AllenAmericans Too bad he’s all business now, front and back!]]></document></documents></author>