<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This kid’s got moves!  #BlackHistoryMonth #OaklandHeights https://t.co/5jO5Tn3LKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rock n Roll Jesus #WSCruise #tompayne #rossmarquand #savedbytheband #twd https://t.co/QrGAqg8Mzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hodgetwins awesome night at the Ontario Improv https://t.co/y5ywUqF8MV]]></document><document><![CDATA[what dad? had a biological dad and an adoption dad, neither one was shit. you niggas can’t hurt me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed @DrMattKutz talk and the opportunity to hear more of his story this weekend! Looking forward to diving into… https://t.co/C3qRWBYFOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so on-point; the stories of traumatized and grieving people that I've heard from bring tears to my eyes. We… https://t.co/2v8fLqP9Ke]]></document><document><![CDATA[no more being nice, treat me like shit you're getting punched right in the esophagus]]></document><document><![CDATA[في نصيحة نصحتني فيها مدرسة مصرية: كانت تقول دائماً خلي وقت الناس الا تحتاجيهم أولى من وقتش، عادي لو ضغطتي على نفسش… https://t.co/e8201ROg95]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acabo de ver a una chera que tenia unos zapatos que decian “I adore tacos”, y pues nada, I really felt that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladyfleur @cyclelicious @drivingmzstacey @schmangee I was so ready to buy one last year, but was discouraged by my… https://t.co/nDOAV20EKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great game to lose my voice at! Singing at church tomorrow is going to be rough https://t.co/P5p6xUBMEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTVNews Oh no!  Praying for the families and friends of loved ones lost.  Worried about colleagues in the region.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidDobrik yo David can you help a girl out I’m trying to see the love of my life in El Paso  🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[And this shit going on right now about talking shit to my parents about my social life is not helping 🖕🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix @Netflix  #JuanitaNetflix exceptional everything!! #Outstanding #lovedit https://t.co/d8VAkb3PsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know @ShannonSharpe is watching this waiting on Bron and them to win! 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learn about our new Executive Leadership Doctor of Nursing Practice (DNP) program @CapitalUNursing @Capital_U… https://t.co/XtTinyuIQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one is above the law, unless your FBI, DOJ, Hillary or one of her minions!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you seen @gwenstefani at @ZapposTheater at @PHVegas yet? Win your tickets NEXT! https://t.co/3Qc9CEUS4H… https://t.co/R15mNA8VX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s pretty outside if you don’t mind walking on a poorly blended Slurpee. 😁 @ Longfellow (neighborhood), Minneapol… https://t.co/MF7pC2oYhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldnt watch this. That little boy was harassed, chased, and beaten bc he told an adult (y'know, the proper thin… https://t.co/uqAI0ZcGIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Remember folks voting has consequences so please turn out in 2020—we need a new administration!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SMendesQandA @ShawnMendes Like I can pick one... https://t.co/r9kfhy0ZG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisdameanor19 @Cakedaddy4ever @MrDane1982 @Rednuria And powerful women. Screw them we’re taking the White House in 2020 ✊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @RalphNortham God bless you, constantly under scrutiny but you move forward in full force]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannah and I have been sick for a week and a half. Now my husband is sick I feel like we're never gonna get better 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Delta Dawn playing*  Me: isn’t this the song Monica sings on Friends when her boobs show?  My Parents: ...what??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nafsnep They better step it up if they have any hopes of making playoffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photographer feeling at one with nature during the final round of the Honda Classic 2019 Photo by Me. #hondaclassic… https://t.co/4k4NO2e759]]></document><document><![CDATA[This idiot really just rode my ass, acted like he was gonna rear end me, to then speed around me   ONLY TO GET PULL… https://t.co/loG7tTF9iZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every hour of every day, Trump, et al, will do something despicable...guaranteed.  Something that would be outrageo… https://t.co/i7cPAcublj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tom_Parkin_ Oh what a tangled web we weave...story changes every day #PMJT #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_FLgal @my3monkees @karmasenz @RodHillis1 @misspunk63 @GinnyGinny_1 @KamyMAGA @AW95NJ @Serremmy @briantopping66… https://t.co/GvYDq4fgqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those eyes... they kill me! • • • • #puppydogeyes #puppyeyesfordays #sunset #oysterdome #oysterdometrail… https://t.co/C3U3YQJkX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[having to pray for the strength to keep existing is a different type of hurt]]></document><document><![CDATA[double chocolate chip Frappuccinos from Starbucks are literally equivalent to crack]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barbara Wyatt completed the Half Marathon P/B Sprint! Time 02:11:10 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/vlVXUxlCU1 #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenna_Marbles thank you for uploading 30 minutes before midnight you’re a blessing]]></document><document><![CDATA[YAS! @DalaiLama — I’ve always firmly believed women are more empathetic (and stronger 💪🏻 ) managers + leaders.… https://t.co/ZqiG1Vv8l7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who got @MorpheBrushes X @JeffreeStar as one of Valentine’s Day presents? Me!!!! So excited! https://t.co/eHupJpaeVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[New business cards for Stoned on Rocks. Come for a visit and leave with a treasure @ Dania Beach, Florida https://t.co/g2G2Nj3grq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RusevBUL Can I kindly say "no thanks" to this as well? The man is gonna get himself injured again, or worse!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePRwriter Idk I had a bunch in my back yard &amp; I think they made me 😷]]></document><document><![CDATA[my uber driver has playlists for different cultures 🙌🏼❣️ im here for it !]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He also makes a gamay to die for” - now that’s a quote! Come back soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, so MZ didn't inherit the fame from  his parents. KJ is NOT self-made. MZ really revolutioned the world with one… https://t.co/J2G9c8orbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy hour at @wildfingrill in the beautiful waterfront in vancouverus 🌊 🐠 🍷 so yummy  #saturdaynight #datenight… https://t.co/bm0yDMZpZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Set your goal so big that if you ever achieved it, it will blow your mind...#lift450  #texas #Powerlifting… https://t.co/HlyOUnc2tv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump Absolutely,  I also believe jail time is warranted]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us for our #podcast Voices for Change 2.0 this Saturday at 11am EST  We're featuring the amazing… https://t.co/R01h8ZNOwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew669691 @char_stokely Be still my heart ♥️ https://t.co/B7k35dpvVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else block people on social media if they post photos from a vacation more than once a year? I don’t need your joy in my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Femme de carrière que vous êtes ;  oui le look classique on le fait avec amour juste pour vous ! Prennez rendez- vo… https://t.co/8GWRI9MTWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the next show!  Justin and Jadyn will both be in this one! https://t.co/zvGtn92uGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox News: Democratic freshman lawmaker Tlaib raises specter of racism during Cohen  testimony. https://t.co/Fh6u29hsMS  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[alguém me da uma camisa do kirk cousins de aniversário pf 17/05 ta chegando]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Stay off my social media. It won't work out well for you. Him: I love the way you tag random facts. It's great.… https://t.co/5L1LksHILn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody Thank you. Inspiring. Many said it was too fast. Gave us 2/4/6 months. We are so close still. I adore… https://t.co/8MlIk3HiN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[so manager talks to lucias (the next day) and is like "why do you call them bitches? aaaaand can i buy them off of… https://t.co/lBW5ibiF5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanshrinks Now u got me thinking about mini flavored marshmallows 😞 it’s 2 am I can’t do anything about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dude stfu..start doing the job that the electoral college elected u to do that being the PRES. Of the US.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonkeyLairLabs @shantellebisson wow about no salt but loll about spring stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for @Ryland_Adams to win the #ShortyAwards. That is all. https://t.co/sDKra7aXyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m without power for the first time since Hurricane Michael; haven’t missed this a bit 😩. Fingers crossed that it is restored soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump is a great leader &amp; a very astute businessman. That’s exactly why we elected him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejournalista they said that was the reason given for the check and that’s what’s on the memo but texts showed no… https://t.co/R3zMpfgY9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve honestly never identified with a celebrity more than I do with Glenn Close in this moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Toronto friends, help me share this great opportunity to create safe and inclusive communities for all!… https://t.co/uoJsnhhUaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delegate Lisanti, Out of the abundance of the heart 💜 the mouth 👄 speaks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen It depends on the kid, not the age.  Daughter escaped from crib at 17 months. Son will be 3 soon and… https://t.co/0FnEXfwkYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo un amigo que sólo telefonea conmigo cuando su roomi no está, será que soy su secreto de amor ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YaoiMaster42069 I'm actually having a pretty easy time with this one but it's still. Not great 😷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu I thought it was bad when Hillary and Biden and Oba ma and Schumer all said there was a crisis at the bord… https://t.co/vwTV6JPHOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I luv when I find music that matches my mood PERFECTLY thank u universe my 5th house pisces moon appreciates u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Smollett is a disgrace. It is hard enough for gays to be accepted, especially minority gays. And along comes… https://t.co/Ai7njuJmlv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up and Nate was staring at me waiting to say “happy valentines baby” with a cute little smile, I look forward… https://t.co/OMYggIyVXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Minimum Wage Can't Support a Family  ... because it's too low. Time to raise it. #RaisetheWage #15andaUnion]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite things now is when penny wakes up before me, and she’ll crawl right up in my face and start nuzz… https://t.co/Kiz2AzHqML]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shawn no es solo un chico con lindo cuerpo y en ropa interior 🙄 sin tan solo se tomarán el tiempo de apreciar su tr… https://t.co/t8WXiuXEDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fine, I'll post. Happy Valentine's day to Malfoy (@rachela_adler)   Cc: @EricHSchwartz good job being a chair. ❤… https://t.co/IZP8RjFTBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama @NASA @SpaceX @Commercial_Crew These are things a REAL PRESIDENT shows interest in, even when he's not… https://t.co/vD3YcsOqk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting married? Need flowers and decor? Give us a call!  843-312-0313  #weddingflowers  #bridalbouquets… https://t.co/HAmaRnG33b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve not yet seen the interview yet, but it sounds as if he’s eaten some #HumblePie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never understand why guys where winter hates but don’t cover their ears...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveODonnell1 @WoodmenLife @FNBOmaha @midtowncrossing Love our pretty city!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zack_Garcia2 told me and @yenttirb01 that we can eat beef today since it’s not meat. Wut? 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maximiliannn @tweetgrubes Max, if we ever go back to Portland I'll have to take you there. I went there because it… https://t.co/ok2z0rOzmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Nancy trying to assassinate the president and vice President is TREASON and the PENALTY for that is DEATH!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly If FREE SPEECH protects YOU, it surely protects a Pulitzer Prize winner with more poignancy and though… https://t.co/IPifw0PDJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LHVanhorn @Beatlemaniac201 @BackTheLEOs @NCMtnGirl8 @LivePDPuns @FawnIOrr1 @Michael28710212 @Max_n_Ruby @Jager2019… https://t.co/2Rq1Vo8Ju1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pero cuando sea día de cono gratis te vas a acordar de mi porque fuimos juntos el año pasado🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShelbyKStewart @McneJames It is outrageous. How much of a threat do they think this patient and his capsules are t… https://t.co/m2cfVfBB1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabifresh @meghantonjes @callyrgf Tbh, I do need more dog content. That little sweet muffin is so lucky to have you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else’s spouse bring you things you left in the “wrong” place at nonsensical times? Like I’m sitting on… https://t.co/XKA3rBFXP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had a panic attack about university and i’m just not having it tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_tonyjefferson @BagSznEverySzn @_tonyjefferson what you did to this man for him to be big mad like this? 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because nobody knows the UP exists doesn’t mean we aren’t still part of Michigan😂😭😂😭 https://t.co/X6YAqim5GY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaHoyt2 I literally just talked to Derek about this!!! Come on @SamHuntMusic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Under the dome and way better than smelly cheese! #rosetriplebutter #oatmealshaelinden #sheacitrus… https://t.co/AzXbbyPGFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Accounts… https://t.co/IkxXiGyMah]]></document></documents></author>