<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I feel like a full draft beer on a bass amp is a bad idea but that’s just me]]></document><document><![CDATA[My conversations can be so mature and deep but niggas wanna ask what i’m doing 8x so Ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dogwood; by @authorbutterfly they just can’t put it down ...  https://t.co/YvuIdScadK https://t.co/6CRRBHfIRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notgreatjustok Great attitude. The #lawofattraction is our greatest ally. It never lets you down when you fully em… https://t.co/yVj5KlceFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only thing I'm watching on freeform is our show after that bye-bye freeflop #SaveShadowhunters #Shadowhunters https://t.co/7ToUFY1kyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Day, Mate⭐️❤️  @Brothers_Gibb @GibbBarry @MEGMediaInc @GibbCollective https://t.co/ON8hIsnvsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[this was my boyfriend all weekend long. never have I heard someone snore so much or so loud]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad just called me and told me he lost his car keys and like threw them away now I know where I get it from]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CindyHess65 @DearAuntCrabby What is her legal status? Shouldn't she be in jail if she runs a prostitution ring and… https://t.co/HVs1xd2Car]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet @joncoopertweets @realDonaldTrump That’s sickening‼️😡📣🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: she claimed her throat got scratchy but there was no physical evidence of it being true, I’m calling BS]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these couple posts just made me realize that jose didn’t actually ask me to be his gf.. he just said I was his… https://t.co/7AVvDQdQEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the pressure of getting exposed and thrown in jail is building you gotta find something to take the camera off… https://t.co/K8XzSJnORn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExcellentBarba1 @nowthisnews No. The way our country treats innocent children is not “on” anyone but us.   Check your privilege.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Climate Leadership Webinar: join the discussion with Greenpeace @greenpeaceusa on March 7th!! https://t.co/ArD4rbyoVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up next:  “Dream team of depolarization” -Edward w. Maibach  #aaas #aaas2019 #aaasmtg #scicomm https://t.co/1bATAqZYgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the worst things for smart people is not being rewarded for your intelligence. You think you deserve the wor… https://t.co/SLMWlYXIH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legitimately had a dream last night that instead of releasing an album, @taylorswift13 released a book and went on… https://t.co/pVyaSHpFnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[💦☔️ Well when it rains this much, and Sea World WAS closed today, the Orcas come out to play!!  Boy was that a rain… https://t.co/z0ajm7cPkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_superdupermac @itsindysev How to afford to travel: •multiple streams of income (Indy has a clothing line, worksho… https://t.co/Eg1SBfMu5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIVEAWAY Polymer Clay Project: Undersea Medallion Tutorial https://t.co/Tfs452BZSp via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, don’t worry about going solo. I went to this #ChallengeManiaLIVE by myself and made friends immediately! We t… https://t.co/udsPKbKv4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[grin. The Bloated Bride- great post and blog on how to be motivated to workout! https://t.co/8TZuNuKzwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbr9596062 @fogocinti Good morning my brother May God continue to bless you and your family]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love how @JGSchneid said @Teresa_Giudice "you will not win a war of words with me"then right after that almost on c… https://t.co/OqtgoPu8a0]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I greet people when they come to my house 🏡 https://t.co/Hsp9arEvey]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Build Your Voice Team is ready to go. Get The Voice Official App to play. https://t.co/CTk4LhBpnD Hannahyou have the most amazing voice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because it’s ok to be yourself. And it’s even better when you know you have someone who appreciates it when you do… https://t.co/2iPZbTOt4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monitorLATINO Voto X #CuandoTeAmé de @julionalvarez para 1° lugar en el #TopNorte @SAPSGrupero @ChulasDeJA @EEnrique_F 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1a @DrEliSheff @crystalbfarmer @BlackandPoly @janetwhardy The paradigm of monogamy evolved to support the stabilit… https://t.co/TwRXrRIlVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rumorsofmeaning Bruh i've had a fear since i was a young child, like deadass used to cry bc terrified and WOW FUCK ESCALATORS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brycetache The pile on the table keep getting bigger. It spilled onto other furniture. 😀 https://t.co/kDbxfi43e3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird how some guys will call you crazy and every name they can think of once you turn them down lmao... so you mus… https://t.co/D1uN3zzLjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Capitalism... colonialism... racism... administration inaction/resistance... empty conversations...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FeedYourFandomEntry https://t.co/477gVsjIGs ❤️🧡💛💚💙💜💘💘💘 Ends 7/31/19 ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonkries Easy!! Data!!!! I want to know when jeans are interacting so I can interact back with them. Does anything else really matter.?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My gramma leaves for Florida in less than 6 hours. Helloooooo peace &amp; quiet!! 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbagump324 I was frantically searching for a new post of #PoppysPuppies. Thanks 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump Vulgarity from the pathetic, ignorant left as usual]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannongailmc @howllr @nicosgranny2000 @ShapesBlue @canadiandaws83 @cathyhadenough @alisoninsco @Boatoptional2… https://t.co/WFsHn5uJ64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlaLovejoy @OHDems @OhioBATs @SandyTheis @RepGalonski @dawnintheworld @RJECempower Carla, we all must up-lift th… https://t.co/vN6vEM2gJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman The House is out of control. They are abusing their authority.  They are going after trump supporter… https://t.co/lJxztXyYzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow will be just as good considering my baby nephew will be borrrnnnnn! I think my excitement is stronger than my sisters🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seen that too because I wanted to go but those prices were dumb especially for them 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was there a curse put on today that I missed?? Nothing has gone right for me or anyone I talk to?? https://t.co/l4fjKd4a0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had one overnight shift this week so now my whole schedule is thrown and here I am drinking coffee at 1:45 AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to par-tay with y’all at thefedcommunity TONIGHT in downtown Clarkston, MI! 🎉 8:30PM!  . . . .… https://t.co/coophkwPyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to go stay at Mystic Lake for 2 nights so I can watch this Law &amp; Order SVU marathon in peace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stayed to to listen to#RedRoom by @OffsetYRN . WELL WORTH THE WAIT! GREAT VALENTINE'S DAY GIFT!  Already a whole… https://t.co/rsGq1rYWDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an awesome first act of Into the Woods! @220Arts loved running into former @BMSHistSchmitt students in the sta… https://t.co/Cvikhw9sMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe there’s people who wake up and put bras on lmaooo i don’t even think i have any in Gainesville 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Helter Skelter. Charles Manson's race war where the blacks [insert  todays hated groups] are killed or… https://t.co/Ews08OvYJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into this guy today! #rockchalk @ Gilcrease Museum https://t.co/hf0PCBujCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoyed spending the day with some of my very famous friends! #biographyday #thirdgrade @MadeiraESPrin https://t.co/FISxHfkmbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world, and the galaxy, speak cat. It’s the universal language. #CaptainMarvel https://t.co/aC1uZ26gQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day!  #beyourself #happyinternationalwomensday #women #impowerment  #happywomensday… https://t.co/oQjEYEm9J6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @Advocate4Tech to post the cover of 7 books I enjoy. ... no reviews or explanation… https://t.co/8I4PFyBDmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost been a year since you’ve been gone... My black pants seem to be missing your fur. Seeing your pictures… https://t.co/D98lTrqYvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wear my retainer every night like I was told too and my two front teeth are slowly separating what the fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jillniki @Eaches @Corporate_Mess @BitchWithA_W And seriously in love 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keeping secrets! This 🌹 Rose Peach 🍑 melted with Lilac has got us sharing. But she is one #hot #prettylittleliar wi… https://t.co/VsSU99EkSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter says good game to old team mates Anthony Donatella and Chris Colarossi after the game✨⚾️✨ @ University of San… https://t.co/IBVtqnXqd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a queen crowned in my curls  Hair by curlyhairdaze @ San Diego, California https://t.co/rHXn3gjfSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized starting tomorrow I have to work 8 days in a row and I’m just thinking about how by day 6 I’m proba… https://t.co/b79Nx2dLd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TribLIVE Why didn’t she call police before this happened? She could have called police when he called her to clean… https://t.co/mUgdVWiuwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1lamegirl I go to SF often! Maybe I can meet up with you in the future!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Annnnnddd "persistence" is 90% finding excellent  mentors 👫👬👭👫👬👭+ 5% stubbornness 🐴 + 5% curiosity 🔍 #academiclife 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @DonaldJTrumpJr @RepCloudTX Cohen already knows why he was there? He was credible! All the Republicans did was… https://t.co/qMJ1nDqNkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milagro88136168 @marianaboggion @Psicovivir Total.... es un tipo tóxico]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to go check this out in person. So cool! Minnesotans you are amazing https://t.co/FfwUdORnYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@creektothewest @_withoutalcohol Oh - can't wait to see pictures of your turkeys enjoying your snack! I love wild t… https://t.co/34E5Qi7vxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who does jeff think he is changing his name to king Jeffy? @jriedlinger_08]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still haven’t deposit my check yet 😂😭 you know I’m sick sick I need gone and deposit it though so I can pay my rent rent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dazjaaavilaa @emillionz_ Can you guys send me a pic of the smart tv? Or are they both smart tv’s?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiSixx @MotleyCrue At first I thought it would be weird seeing other people play all of you guys..but the more… https://t.co/Ezw3mihXFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amara🌺 #easylikesundaymorning #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy #blackcats #minipanther… https://t.co/QCiiu5M9NT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was interviewed by a researcher from another country who is interested in understanding the history of… https://t.co/ZruMcxWxSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magastorybook @RodStryker @BreitbartNews I haven’t heard about this band since 30 years? They can go to hell for a… https://t.co/lzqUtIu3vt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamajdgreen @Lily_Atkinson95 The LAW says otherwise . Your word doesn’t go above that .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@L_ibarra2003 @mellyolsen @RAUZW @grahamsucha @OpenSocietyEA Glad things have changed!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My most common recurring nightmare is that i'm enrolled in a class I forgot about and am failing it and ya I don't… https://t.co/J91gMTDHMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ektor1021 @Bentnews @CarolynBruckTV So many gorgeous beaches in Maui! Napili is one of my fave as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/ @SURJ_DC stands with @EmpowerDC  in urging that the Council revamp the bylaws of the DCHA Board of Directors to… https://t.co/VT4NuIcNcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFISD_Fishtank @AggiePuckett @MrsLaurenBohm @CFISDWells @E_Sheninger Is there a 5th grade math teacher that you kn… https://t.co/WhBMhvqpB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[bro they really up and stabbed my girl like how you gonna do some boof shit like that??]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone wants to send some money to fund my travel addiction I would greatly appreciate it!!! Venmo: hayley_lariv pls and thank you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important factor for getting more females involved in discussion. #genderequity #academia]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am going to kick so much ass today, I can feel it!  (And by kick ass I mean work cooperatively and respectfully w… https://t.co/zlHHdnRDSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMAZlNGNATURE She is very special to so many rescued animals, kindest ever💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelbcooke @MalcolmNance You know who else is “eye rolling climate change?” EVERY. SINGLE. GOP. SENATOR! Don’t… https://t.co/FaMQstTO2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Digitaldogmal @mightyheidip @UROCKlive1 @realDonaldTrump By the way, I did not vote for Trump, but I sure as heck… https://t.co/JkuXQvFsch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday! #promotepositivity #goodvibes #appreciatelife #appreciatewhatyouhave #sunday #happy #behumble… https://t.co/7WDDocnQK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFAaction @RashidaTlaib @IlhanMN @AyannaPressley @AOC https://t.co/B9Wj8HrtdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacLeodLisa And the Disabled kids that are NOT ASD?  Where is their funding?  When do they get the Therapy they ne… https://t.co/VlKK1rWN2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[can i be a part of someone’s #KadenangGinto group message so we can rant abt the episodes together 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[#California deputy state #CIO resigns - https://t.co/6JBILfFGjr via @FederalNewsNet]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is playful. My favorite but least favorite part at the same time is when Cassandra kisses the Doctor...… https://t.co/USWY87Yvpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSGrandFaith @RobertW48787695 @wecanmag @PrezesPan @DanielBrasilia @DavidLogan2020 @XandraXandraBX @GiselleMarks1… https://t.co/IPsuPklsX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸Con Sue Photography and Design🇺🇸   🇲🇼Like our photos...Follow our IG 🇲🇼  🇨🇱This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 🇨🇱… https://t.co/SuNFdulyGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[➰Curly vibes ➰ ☆ ☆ ☆ ☆ ☆ #curls #curlyhair #coils #bighairdontcare #naturalhair #wavyhair #curlyvibes… https://t.co/faJfWLqP9L]]></document></documents></author>