<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@quick13 @bethbrez @mfloyd21 It was so much cheaper in the past. Stupid supply and demand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a great time riding the Santa Cruz Mountains Challenge https://t.co/oqtG7P0RGK via @scmcbikeride #SCMCbikeride]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don 101 quote of the day: If you’re going through hell, keep going. 💚💯🐍🏀🤐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THOTSOFADRIAN na imagine getting raped and having someone with your dumb ass brain tell you that you need to keep… https://t.co/HPcCpATnUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReeceMoten @TomDekker2 @TheKilling99 @t_inker58 @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity No, between them, diabetes, problems… https://t.co/n8riACnuNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@majornelson I like Dante a lot but my favorite capcom character is Zero from X series! Hope your day goes well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelinaMarie_B @WWE You what the good thing about opinions is? They are never wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was literally looking at the clock like bet, six hours to sleep before church]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dollie_london @fs_stevio I get 4 chips something to drink and some candy for $4 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveFultonWrang @LilRedDave @AllWaltrip @DiGardRacing @Gatorade @MountainDew @HollywoodJeff @RandyLHallman @SouthsideSpeed EXACTLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalShort @RepAdamSchiff Is anybody going to investigate Bernie Sanders he could’ve been turned when he was h… https://t.co/OTa0mQts7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillMasse @uneeda_marg were yall there was yall stuck in there ? were yall there? case closed!! you gone believe a… https://t.co/AoO2pTOj6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren You left out. TERM LIMITS.   Best way to stop politicians from enriching themselves 100 fold from 20 years in office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shadowwinning @SethAndrewsTTA He is also right about the FBI investigation. MJ was investigated by the FBI for 10… https://t.co/WvQtGBLBN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elastic vSAN solving the data gravity problem!  https://t.co/JubqR1ORJF #vExpert]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eddie is my early favorite because I am very attracted to him. I can’t get video bios to play since I’m not in Cana… https://t.co/vqrHaLkrIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Avevaios Ave, independente do propósito da ação em si, tem um certo teor pornográfico que é indevido ao perfil de um PRESIDENTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fleccas @billmaher @AdamSchiff @TuckerCarlson @seanhannity @IngrahamAngle @TuckerCarlson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mum you know I miss you 😍😍 you're always in my mind. #ILOVEYOU  #LoveYouMama https://t.co/q2yh1V9BXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you break up with someone over the phone and not in person, you’re a crappy person, I don’t care who you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexShupe @UBcoachBryan @nate_oats But if they can take it all the way this year I will tolerate a rebuilding year… https://t.co/V4ar03rCp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joannamucha Pani moze deprawowac swoje dzieci dowoli ale od moich dzieci WAR zdeprawowana pindo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlangsOnSports @statcast I also wanna see:  -accuracy throws simlair to the QB challenge at the Pro Bowl.. could h… https://t.co/fnLvcrUX5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think I can express how much I hope the host of #WrestleMania is @PatMcAfeeShow Announcing it in his Home Taun!! Electric!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gunnderrick1 Looked at radar earlier &amp; saw it was hammering y’all &amp; a lot more behind it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwalsh838 @hullboydan Danny was the dumbass that brought up IQ but put an apostrophe in the word "Types"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarissaaDeLeon @CaramelLicious_ Don’t be a light drinker now 😂 and shit you might as well wait until April for Schae birthday 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC AND NOW YOU KNOW WHY I WAS OPPOSED TO NANCY PELOSI AND HER GRABBING THE GAVEL ,,SHE IS OLD ,SHE IS TIRED AND S… https://t.co/r3fepL941K]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SPFC Se não fossem as expulsões, a suspensão do nosso ídolo Hudson, teríamos classifica. Fica para próxima! “O Lec… https://t.co/ZJ6KVZBat2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how we roll at Coco Loco Lounge Fiesta Henderson on weekends. Let these images of our February 2019 Sixties… https://t.co/vjKiYpmAm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcusedelstein  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmmily_e That being said, I will forever love Glossier's "G" logo mark.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukecombs Luke, you knock everyone out that sees you for the first time !!! Your a killer !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Time for President Trump to kick some Liberal ASS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, rule #1 never leave your laptop open at the bar (with your phone next to it) halfway through an email whilst yo… https://t.co/Vr5yKIxy6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogerClark41 @NY1 This Roger was a very interesting report had no knowledge on this and I’m sure many others did not either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snizzbone_62 Ovation was pretty loud for JT. But Leaf Nation in the building does not do the 60 minutes of screaming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But fr yall notice that even tho its snowing its still not as cold as it usually is in the morning?? This that government snow smh 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tamaraw68415067 @AOC This is the same woman who wants to eliminate fossil fuels in 10 yrs.  yet she can't even thi… https://t.co/sJxDs5uCZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign ideas for upcoming NHL games  3/7 BUF: Hey Dahlin (or) Ristolainen, a puck from you would be pretty Swede 3/24… https://t.co/QWyLIidw1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so thrilled that @AOC put up The Green New "Deal"usion and that Satan's Turtle 🐢 is going to bring it to a vot… https://t.co/fLN0Fuqp1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Garland: clear sky, 74°F 73% humidity, wind 10mph, pressure 1009mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BayerUS That 2.2 billion new people will be replacing the several more billion who will be dead by 2050 because of global climate changes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We thought that it could never end We'd glide above the ground before we learned to run, run Now it seems our world… https://t.co/cr2uwwj35F]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you declare with your mouth, Jesus is Lord and believe in your heart that God raised him from the dead, you will… https://t.co/nIFU8gIS6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard work pays off. Finals on #beam at #state #wiaa #wiaagymnastics #gorlssports #sports #gymnastics. #gymnast… https://t.co/Pb52CFuoQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunflowerinsea @norwegian76 @sportlily1967 @tonyposnanski Why would you assume I wouldn't?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brent Willis wants to inspire and educate the planet to live healthy. Here's how @NewAgeBeverages is doing that ...… https://t.co/7ocxsRDeuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnlegend  better critique and honesty since you came on board IMHO FWIW...enjoy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@db_electronics @retro_cables It's all good, I'm having a hard time finding the Phoenix connectors.. besides overpriced Ebay for 5 each]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amaryllis78 @4uConservatives @SportsLogic82 https://t.co/AuMUSsGYRC GcMAF is an answer to cancer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@james_mclamb @brandon3263827 @steph93065 @RandPaul @LindseyGrahamSC To sum up..... myself, like millions of Americ… https://t.co/z2ImV0YemJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The magic castle at night. #losangeles #california #hollywood #membersclub #magic #magician @ The Magic Castle https://t.co/pcJdjOTHSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, Bear Nation!! #BearClawsUp @ucaalumni @ucabears @UCAPurpleCircle @ucasports @UCA_SGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you listened to the newest episode of my podcast, #MemoirsOfAGaysian? This week, I interview Lex from… https://t.co/tfvvr1z1zu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassyDillon All my conservative supporter friends from Missouri be like... https://t.co/mvGblupiIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Trump, it is simple. He never cared about the Constitution to begin with because he didn't know anything about… https://t.co/iKV9Xo1hqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun time today supporting all the awesome @RunRocknRoll runners on H Street this morning! Congrats y’all! https://t.co/vdQO3GTnJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisHayesTV @MatthewBetley Ok, what the hell!? Please tell me at the very least that this woman is no longer working around children!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ikawaiishopcom we are the factory of ceramic mug in china… https://t.co/v3h4nAMVrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Erik Haula started skating last week and is on the ice a few times a week, Gallant said #VegasBorn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Avalanche Wow my two favorite teams going at it 👀👀 May the better goalie win!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuchAngerLilSam @LoudenSwain1 @TheFamilyBeer Be safe and enjoy your night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me in middle school after realizing I may have dropped one too many hints about my sexuality https://t.co/ctj2kMeZPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpacedOutRadio I know your all done w thought of the day brother BUT I think we BOTH know #SkinWalkerRanch is the… https://t.co/ekgMZ5DtBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alabama is returning their most highly touted DB's this year (Patrick Surtain, Trevon Diggs, Devonta Smith, Xavier… https://t.co/A07UNXuHhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @dilruba_lees @DLees28 @CynthiaMark14 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best @cheryllyndunn @TBGTNT  LORD, WE THA… https://t.co/Z5NJ5dCAbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This article specifically calls out schools for their social media use as a part of the problem for today's student… https://t.co/cEAcH1xsWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a goer day to be out on the links With chase_swanson44 !!! Unfortunately my dog has chewed the hell out of our… https://t.co/FMr92tmfUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The masters who create the rule, value it the least. That's why they know when to break it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fvck____ 2 things. A girl that just wanna hunch me but wouldn't date me fr &amp; a milf 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[its 4pm rn &amp; i’m currently getting in the shower just to cry in peace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jose23jronberg @fthemilenials @yanksjets322 @bostonbetterson @BleacherReport https://t.co/rk1v24cDVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes, swimming in the "water under the bridge"  is worth the risk of drowning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fr33dom_fight3r You’re a red piller, too! Oh, this is too funny! Keep going!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Who cares.  When was the last time a Republican won NJ?  George Herbert Walker Bush.  This law will howe… https://t.co/qtVi1hNQGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CryptoNiceGuy @OCDecaf @FymCapital @RampCapitalLLC @davidcrosss 😆 https://t.co/1I0xngGzrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff While our president was negotiating you were tearing him down. You would rather NOKO have nukes than… https://t.co/98eZE2S0ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me last night and then me today. I hate when I get a cold. #goofymemes #etphonehome #ettheextraterrestrial… https://t.co/KARAmqk84G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffWilson83 @THefferman I wish I could replace the Batman symbol with the new Saluki logo. https://t.co/BvGUfnYGKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[These four photos were taken about 25-30 miles &amp; about 45 minutes apart from each other... https://t.co/jSb96Z276S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Ran Ranriscro 👋🏾 #goldengatebridge #sanfrancisco @ Golden Gate Bridge https://t.co/GRbJAhCVU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[No sé porque se emocionan con el beso Aristemo si de seguro va a ser lo último del episodio y los van a hacer esper… https://t.co/7H2nJpiotA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antes me paraba y comprara cualquier cosa para comer en el gas station ahora tengo que mirar si es gluten free mierda de dieta 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another boring review. See what I mean. “A must read!!!” Clark F. Tucker https://t.co/GUs2It62S5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwherron10 I’ve told you this for years, glad you’re finally coming around!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure and vote and give us a call this morning with your thoughts (256)382-0724]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malavejm @Roddijai Best wishes to him ... and to all of your wrestlers. Thanks for allowing me to come over the other day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccb1212 😂 having been to Montana once last year, I say no deal.  We should keep Montana. As for North Dakota, it’s… https://t.co/kxnl5LMCL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ephoustonbill @StoneBrewing @JohanBBT @zappafaye @cellmavin @ManvsAle @JonMontag @scottydog57 @cedarflats… https://t.co/WPFDPZBCH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcmorehouse @MurphyKeith Great respect for both of you. This has never been about Dolph the broadcaster. I actua… https://t.co/N8aafByAiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out what I'm selling on letgo! https://t.co/vJIWmyGWQN  - Canon EFS 18-55mm Lens]]></document><document><![CDATA[Virginia House Democrats propose legislation to allow abortions up until the moment of birth  Todd Gilbert (R): Whe… https://t.co/wFPwRf0ywp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best birthday ever. New pens... must  be broken in. • • • • • #sketch #draw #sketchbook #instaart #ink #pen #doodle… https://t.co/NmLFF8fIaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachbarnhart The guy posting Alt-Right flyers in Brghton promoting Identity Evropa, which seeks to protect “oppres… https://t.co/TMVGcYTIPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pats are going to only suit up two wideouts for their game tomorrow. What is this team doing??!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fantastic friend # RebeccaHoffberger director of the amazing @TheAVAM celebrating #Love]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Glorygirlone @nurseregank @Timpanist Wow you stumped me. I have no idea. Where did you find them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brie Larson definitely just asked for more diversity from film critics and in the press room ctfo Ashley.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 10 Horror Films of the Last 10 years:  The Conjuring  Mandy  Get Out Hereditary Drag Me To Hell Antichrist A Qu… https://t.co/Ni41JsryBc]]></document></documents></author>