<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Could not get up for spin class this morning .... leftover pizza for breakfast it is 🙌🏻😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don’t blame Jordan and the staff for getting upset. Especially if it happened 2 times. Utah ST should’ve m… https://t.co/cO3eNvCJ1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leserbaloo Now, now. Although I agree that millennials get a bad rap. The millennials I know/work with have a tremendous work ethic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check this out! Former @OdessaMBB Wrangler @Lj_Figueroa helps St. John’s get the win with 24 points and 12 rebounds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream last night that I worked with my dad in St. Mary's on third shift...I didn't actually work....I sat i… https://t.co/84sW7uTjTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m torn. I’ve been debating on bringing back the blonde but ugh the upkeep 😭 I don’t have enough time https://t.co/FX7QtCti3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland I DO think SNL has the correct crowd-sourced solution to your conundrum. https://t.co/xIv1kz33Ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBrandonDurham @Mattheu @desiringGod And finally, your metaphor of marriage as an act of military protection fails… https://t.co/RRmjkLxjH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched Got 2 Believe with the fam and i just realized putcha ang cute talaga ni rico yan di pa ko over jk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenLee2329 @erikajayne You’re telling me my daughter’s loans are incorrect and the Alabama football players also… https://t.co/txwP7b4JYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fudgeboygrayson I love you too. Self confidence is the key to anything in life. You're beautiful, embrace it💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[tortilla w/ butter &amp; tajin is the greatest late night snack don’t @ me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanneelHarris @JensenAckles Your relationship is such an inspiration. Thank you for sharing these special times wi… https://t.co/hne96zMh2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s international #polarbearday ! I thought I’d share these pictures I took back at @ColumbusZoo . https://t.co/OyLgxSt5wG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Cendejas A man with great taste. You’re welcome https://t.co/q5mDVvFu4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am literally dead @JeffreeStar doing his makeup in the woods 😂😂😂😂 (yes I know the video is older) https://t.co/Ufze7xSUoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣 ET turning into crackheads too! What world am I living in? 🤪 @BTS_twt]]></document><document><![CDATA[2, 2, 2 Boomerangs of our Winter Wonderland. Son #1 got here just in time! @ Empire, Colorado https://t.co/2jZs9nX0sx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinMBarlow Absolutely, there were quite a few points though that really should not b dismissed. It was clear too… https://t.co/GWGyLX1Px6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tv7israelnews @netanyahu I'm just making sure it stays fair I'm not falling for the lies of those out to coverup o… https://t.co/pe7ENgRwZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥B•E ❤️ Y•O•U🔥 First I want to say I am SO ready for Spring and SUMMER! ☀️ This Winter cold ❄️ has got to go, but i… https://t.co/ryEELGynUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to pedal! Team ⁦@DairyQueen⁩ supporting ⁦@GilletteChildrn⁩ Kiddos. Thank you! ⁦@lifetimefitness⁩ https://t.co/L7oU5n3vKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[12 Things You Are Doing Because Of High Functioning Anxiety https://t.co/ekMxNZlI04 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about we slap a big retroactive #MeToo on Jerry Lee Lewis and once again forget he is still alive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRULY a travesty I was born poor and passionate instead of rich and in the near vacinity of a kardashian or Jenner.… https://t.co/mnFhDUqpeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump #Trumps absolving Kim of responsibility for #OttoWarmbiersMurder brings shame upon the US and your #crimeFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi there, i made a playlist based off of my zodiac sign: sagittarius. so @ my sagittarius brothers and sisters, giv… https://t.co/heraIObk3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said bro in a sentence and a Californian asked me if I watch  ketterkenny because he’s never heard a girl say that before]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EinsteinMaga @ShawnG927 @ImabitcSumtimes @SealeyGerald @BlueSea1964 @Chrisconsrv1776 @Lady_Vi_2U @PatriotRocker69… https://t.co/HV6EmGDBRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[How he get bit and just gently put the snake on the ground?? I woulda yeeted that bitch into tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cityofwspolice Don’t want to waste police resources; just asking for a regular beat patrol maybe. The panhandlers… https://t.co/35Gq6iJKhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[La bondad es el lenguaje que los sordos pueden oír, y ciego puede ver. Mark Twain https://t.co/d8DHtCoVhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I have beat your ass in the past don’t follow my family on any socials you weirdos!! k thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maddox had a great 1st “field trip” to meet some Kingsley Cougars today! Missed you @Whit_Griffith! https://t.co/DxSdimbIwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case anyone was wondering I hate everyone and pretty much all people are fake]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chains fall.  Fear bow.  Here.  Now.  Jesus you change everything.  Lives healed.  Hope found.  Here.  Now.  Jesus you change everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just made another GIF of @CharlesEsten w/ fans at #chopshoplive. 😍🔥 Really love it. One of my favorite shows! 🎶💥 Ch… https://t.co/KuL8Q5Qxtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lottery win two folks! #meangirlsbroadway #onwednesdayswewearpink @ Mean Girls on Broadway https://t.co/EXPhtILfOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking it out (@ Punch Bowl Social San Diego - @punchbowlsd in San Diego, CA) https://t.co/T5FwHfwjqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved Carson. A class act. The losers on late nite today should take a hint.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficerCMacias Cause they think they better and can get away but you have to be careful cause don’t forget you can… https://t.co/b7cuxc1AQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[New spring styles have arrived! In addition, all clearance footwear and apparel is an extra 20% off! Show this coup… https://t.co/BZv7w6lObf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This article used the term “blue-collar cosplay” about Ivanka. 🤣 Love it. https://t.co/x3zXr9XPat]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always think I’m being unattractive and then it hits me that the food is just so damn good]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @kimrosamond on your COY award! So proud of you always- glad you got the recognition you deserve! Words ca… https://t.co/vsgI3Zowtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is usually also #tonyawards weekend so this is gonna be the best weekend of the year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATT so unhappy with service. Can’t get a resolution. Overcharged. Still waiting for credit. Customer service hardl… https://t.co/rBW0NnvFsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Addisunnnn I kinda just want her to serenade me to sleep and give me a kiss goodnight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibbySchaaf Stop the school closures. #KaiserSchoolStays #Unite4OaklandKids]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogueWolf2001 @JSG_54 @NCLady50 @jmkillingnyc @Anthony4242 @AuntTritsy @TheSarge11 @louisanamom @StarvinLarry… https://t.co/eWZRPzPPdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meriaahhh She knows!! She made fun of the design I want lmaooo! She don’t know about the one I already have though so 🤫🤫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casperdolla @realDonaldTrump Well yeah, it’s just a little unfair. Something tells me Chinese officials will get t… https://t.co/gIGNW7FGJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily Mail quoted me, as well as Raquel and Karamo, about that Esquire cover story. Two things:  It explains why my… https://t.co/LZ7OMcVtQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the baseball thing goes sour, I see a bright housekeeping future.  With that uniform he would never be out of wo… https://t.co/7o9ZtJo9Cb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Movie touristing in #Georgia with stereostef #FriedGreenTomatoes #WhistleStopCafe @ Whistle Stop Express https://t.co/AxqIvE4fJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upsets in round 1 at Women's World Team Championship https://t.co/g4gxt1i4t3 @WOMChess @FIDE_chess @chessdom… https://t.co/iptXwD1doF]]></document><document><![CDATA[You may not of thought this but a Slip Dress is  👍 for winter. First this 90’s staple always looks cool.Second its… https://t.co/M50MuQ8bR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It won’t be the same without Charlie! He turned Ally into a hockey fan.  We ❤️@CharlieCoyle_3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three of four grands. The meals are getting more expensive. https://t.co/cB1TQA02b0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerimijo Bahahaha but you can’t promise things I can’t deliver hahaha!! You have to be on my side!! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[cathidero @mrchow #mrchowmiami #miami #miamibeach #southbeach #birthdaygirl #birthday #birthdaydinner #limo… https://t.co/4E1yQp4qHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a semi related note, @SilkkTheShocker grew into being @tylerthecreator https://t.co/8mW49jfomp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baileygirl_30 Went through almost the EXACT same situation. Those people will absolutely ruin your thoughts of the… https://t.co/HhnCFzEPtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning Meditation: Like a child...  Jesus embraces children always. We see his reverence for them today. We can dr… https://t.co/4W3b303VC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soccerrun5 @NooooSweat @JussieSmollett @DanCovfefe1 @ReAction10Folds @PatriotSmirk Yeah basically. You like to pai… https://t.co/fvmaFIsW5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[NFL slammed over bad call in Saints playoff game https://t.co/OV6YS5tIXF via @YouTube:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcnutt_g People lie all the time. Even in #LeavingNeverland he spoke highly of Michael.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisEvans What you got against BBQ lays, my guy? They should at least be third after cool ranch and Cheetos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauradovely @joshschultzdc @RuthElizabeth @unfoRETTAble Unrelated, but an interesting problem I came across on the… https://t.co/GeQNbV4TrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swatsejo @magagary687 @DrSueDVM @AOC Shouldn't be too much of a surprise, seeing she comes from the Bernie campaig… https://t.co/MvrekIKmov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grace had her wrestling banquet tonight! She actually double booked herself on accident, so for 2 hours of her 8 ho… https://t.co/SNmEmTsY2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Yeah well they better hurry cause it looks like this planet is doomed if Trump has his way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna buy myself a bouquet of daisies because this week has been shitty but it’s valentine’s day so all the flowe… https://t.co/LJB6Wlz3Ed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump Jesus didn't have sex with his pool boy. Ceasar had sex with lots of boys.  You are relatable to Caesar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL So got to watch this. Even if it's only to watch Ice-T. Love that man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A perfect Nebraska State Wrestling moment captured by @NebraskaStockPh of @BCBraves fans celebrating @marxy2026. Co… https://t.co/iAoX3cx7h9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody seen Jordyn Woods feet before? I like everything else about her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, when did you last make an omelette that you poured from a bottle of liquor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SpeakersDotCa #Showcase2019 listening to some great speakers!  “1 in 5 Canadians will need medical attention beca… https://t.co/Ew7gWt5qWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marlajacob happy birthday my friend! Hope it’s half as fabulous as you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessphoenix2018 ✋🏼my English teacher, Mrs. Lois Magenti when I was a junior at Leland High in 1970 (2nd graduating… https://t.co/yHOapS1jRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful sunsets on the horizon at @SampsonElem @CFISDClubRewind   Tapping into their talents and creativity.… https://t.co/COGPAtN2eX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever wondered about the #vegan diet? @BlaineStewart is trying it out for a week and scoping out the best spots in H… https://t.co/n4aPc6d568]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay I guess I live under a rock, but I’ve never seen the bachelor or bachelorette?? 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner with the family (@ Olive Garden in Toledo, OH w/ @ewillda1) https://t.co/YbsN2zv9Bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenlemons It always rains when it's time for the Phoenix Open.... maybe that's why they changed the date. And… https://t.co/YC9OS8DlB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Ain't that the truth!! And, can anyone even imagine what would have happened to President Obama if he'd… https://t.co/qxTmlUx36G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well...I guess it’s not snow 🤷🏼‍♀️ #IsThisSpring? https://t.co/qHPTLl1HAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[THEY FOUND EVERYTHING, THIS NEW EVIDENCE OVER STONE PROBE HAS BEEN RELEA... https://t.co/8c2Sosunb8 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Auction for memorabilia at popular Mardi Gras Multiclub underway - WPRI https://t.co/xCrfCTKRGc.. .. I wanted a Disco Ball..🤷🏼‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah your military workouts oss. I remember what you and Dre use todo. I’m good luv, enjoy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so over this long ass weekend, im actually looking forward to going to class this week 😍😎 #studyhard #proudofmyself 😈😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dawg what a comeback.... down 23 in the 2nd half.... Duke switched up with that zone applied that pressure got some… https://t.co/lsxAlSLcLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re gonna throw house parties AND let people leave drunk DONT GET PISSY WHEN PEOPLE CALL THE COPS ON YOUR DUMBASS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mangosunshine Suckaaaaa I woulda babysat for free! (Be there in September)]]></document><document><![CDATA[yanno I got my oil changed the other day and only 1 of like 8 guys knew how to drive a stick. and i’m still kinda shocked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Realalyssaclark motorboated me twice tonight and I’ve never felt more alive 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am really excited about the new documentary just released, “Kodály belongs to all of us.” Who wants to watch with… https://t.co/QNv8BuCDzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I feel the need...the need for speed” #McLife #tgif #nofilter #rayban #style #women #fashion #lifestyle… https://t.co/8oX4ul2q9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boo woo woo you don't like him as a person. Really? My God, do you know how dumb and childish you sound? Being a cr… https://t.co/WoPBnuz0Q1]]></document></documents></author>