<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’ve been team iPhone for years but that #GalaxyFold is on a whole other level #SamsungEvent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off to get bagels and coffee for the fam before the @Liverpool_FC_ game today. It’s a bid ine too. #ManUtdVLiverpool #YNWA #UpTheReds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apeman45 @knbrmurph They still have a ton of draft picks to begin rebuilding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to court affidavit, the investigation into Orchids of Asia Day Spa in Jupiter, FL launched back in Oct. 2… https://t.co/zRYlBuss0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever unfollowed someone, then followed them later because you couldn’t remember why you unfollowed them...… https://t.co/rnN8Fp8dpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FloRacing @USACNation watching all the action with 50 new friends #huckapoo #tybeeisland https://t.co/fDDP5ndOGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockmyworIds https://t.co/3H0PfBJnFD  The insurance company fake news that the Jackson Estate has pushed for Jackson's gullible fans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ashhash5 @0xdemosthenes @KimStrassel @realDonaldTrump @WSJopinion @POTUS His base doesn't like California. The sta… https://t.co/atgEKKZ09E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@potato_crisp Omg! Thats so nice of you, thank you!! 😭💚 Im going to be wandering in the gaylord this evening]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smerconish your guest is going to tell me that melting and reusing a wad of aluminum foil has more environmental i… https://t.co/XtPfvT8h5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rio ATP 500 is currently in a rain delay. Carballes Baena / Jarry at 4-3 in the 1st and Felix / Fognini to follow.… https://t.co/DZS4YClG2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olsonEVO24 Just was saying this the other day ML Shaw’s has good MILK...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love pickled things, especially peppers. When I first went to Tel Aviv for work the hotel breakfast buffet had th… https://t.co/2FkUIH9RRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenhorRaposa My problem is that she likes to pretend that she’s the consistent principled one and that everyone el… https://t.co/kPQ42guCUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could get thrown off twister for this But I would like to track down using any means any resources  To find an KI… https://t.co/ynUKE7fm5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just read #DoomsdayClock issue 9, and while all it’s delays suck, issues like this one make it worth the wait. This… https://t.co/hhFnweaSQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quality will always win over quantity when it comes to hiring your #Charleston #Wedding #DJ  https://t.co/QkMiYdTdSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fcfootsteps @k_eckrich @_twiceborn_ @Delmarva123 @stickyhammer @TheAmericanLef1 @ThomasS37982821 @celtgunn… https://t.co/zM9Ks9UZvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timpitt100 This is so strikingly similar to the #StarcourtMall advert you’d think @Stranger_Things producers had u… https://t.co/FFCOPH1dTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glozee1 Parent also from India and Jamiacan don't know where she was hatched]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lanedfunk @HD_TheShore4912 @jeremy_gehrke @MrHOMERDPOE @rollin_slagle @CaraScheibe @Rickpet29972325 https://t.co/PZdNb5WhDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up in the morning is rough sometimes, so today, I let myself sleep in a little. Now I have twenty minutes to get out the door. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely when the enemy is at the gates it can be harder to defend against]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Correct_Again @Prime_LeBron I mean I’d rather be a diva then an alcoholic gambler. But then again i doubt either one cares what we think]]></document><document><![CDATA[@London4Williams @SCTCC_Hoops @CoachPetermeier Congratulations, London!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayrosen_nyu @ChrisCuomo CNN has been compromised by hiring a Trumper as political editor; boycott CNN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put that ball in the College Basketball Hall of Fame in Kansas City immediately]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meeratweets @sejorg @ElizabethaRush @brookejarvis @KendraWrites @eilperin @chriscmooney @deborahblum @KSJatMIT… https://t.co/g8C9KaEhdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#memelord #spicy #art #coffee #frenchpress #magneticsensingtechnology @ Southwest Harbor, Maine https://t.co/jqqbgtxpEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow He’s a socialist Communist and talk about Russian collusion he will not even record the record on Ve… https://t.co/ZtiGJufomR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheeHeartthrob Girl she entered the wrong letter 😩 I’m getting a refund back. 🤣 https://t.co/XT0G3MR7WO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone get Diane a green screen and some weather clip art this woman is a STAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[These days it’s hard to meet women, feel like love life is finished. ✍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Priscilla_MR21 First thing I see is EEH so I’m pleased 😂 #TCMParty #DesignForLiving]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vekstra @AEJMC_LAWP We are lucky to have such great mentors who have led the way! Glad you could see my talk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nation tunes in for Michael Cohen hearing, instead gets primer on parliamentary procedures and congressional grievances]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CassandraRules @jack @Timcast Nah...@jack blatantly does what he does...he doesn't care, he likes controlling who… https://t.co/UaiiL7qhON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to find #Sherri for my next Quick #Unboxing #Review. For now, here’s #RubyRiott! Check out more toy unboxing… https://t.co/Q2RvcJgdRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bleacherdave yeah Boogie defensiv..ehh you know what? No. Not to a great extent at least]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Colton loses the V card in one of these fantasy suites, I will be greatly disappointed in the audio person if th… https://t.co/CYb5331aMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denbron77 @bordesa1 @ColoradoMelodyG @mwharris70 @ArtLovato @MileHiRunner @milehighprophet @MileHighKerri… https://t.co/yO7OtDPdX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell she’d like another drink 🍸 after all she’s replacing Hillary D’Drunkard 👿👿🤥🤥👿🍸🍸🍸🤡]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 14yo has those shoes Zion was wearing. Time to break out the Gorilla Tape]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I was driving on Ga-96 just past Bonair, I remembered that I needed a few tools. So I stopped at the Lowe’s Stor… https://t.co/EoVmbvO9Qz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entering Sunday, NBA teams were 85-1 as a favorite of 17 or more points in the last 20 seasons); only other team in… https://t.co/T0WQeFTy5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto I’ve made up my mind she’s the head recruiter and mouthpiece.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @ryangrim @IlhanMN Has nothing to do with color its your allegiances]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soldier_Cynic Sounds like if I reclass public affairs, and promote I can make my way in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LHMUsedCarSM @spidadmitchell @BucketsONeale00 @GeorgesNiang20 @Klayt20 @crompres @Crompton21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwHallywood @ethanhall_13 @CougsTrack @cougs_fb_track @Cougscoach Go get em E!!!!  The hurt only last a few minutes!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another picture of us sober🏝 @ Myrtle Beach Boardwalk https://t.co/a3vnJRnm0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Libro 📚: Una Vida Sin Obstáculos  Autor: Erick Torres Disponible ya 😊😃💯👍🏻🇺🇸🇵🇷🇩🇴🇨🇴🇲🇽… https://t.co/jXlqnFUp77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@autano34 @Csau1nier I prolly would if I end up drinking enough during the shuffle 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every table that orders their steak well done is hell to take care of and never tips more than 10% lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeopardyGuesser The category is 20th Century Newsmakers.  M says Jonas Salk, and I’ll go with George Marshall.  #Jeopardy #blindguess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SanaMello @annamariesporch @ManeatGrass @BestEverYou @berracahband @helen19242686 @RobinsonWoodrow @edengirl58… https://t.co/SXIpeCnHVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch Need to cunter sue this man and take every thing he owns!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fredo6940 @_waleedshahid @SenFeinstein @sunrisemvmt @AOC @SenMarkey @CNN Liberals can't, it's who they are. https://t.co/77t03SR33j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will not vote for him because he missed a great opportunity here to rhyme and be grammatically correct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to being back at Broadway Donation. Come dance! @RichardJHinds #richardjhinds #danceclass #nyc… https://t.co/PspkLI7Eb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday Morning RC/PH Ride @ Roseville Cyclery https://t.co/ex4sBjIYtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[today has been so exhausting and i’ve only been awake for an hour and a half]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELL YEAH, MADE IT THROUGH THE CRASH!!! YOU CAN DO IT TY! AND ADIOS KYLE LARSON!!! #NASCAR #Daytona500 #TD13 #Larsucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dirk on his NBA-wide receptions: "The reception at home is always special. That’s where we play 41 times a year. Bu… https://t.co/YOYjutctFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulObrienUSA @realDonaldTrump True, but, we're also attempting to send in humanitarian aid, and he wants his peop… https://t.co/KFrUHxGnbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anissapenaa i wanna say something inappropriate but like background checks... https://t.co/nnReaGaNjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachGran 1️⃣Evaluate 2️⃣Recruit 3️⃣Develop 4️⃣Implement steps to success in any venture &amp; @UKFootball under… https://t.co/BOjJ3Y5Q6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyMail So does much of the rest of the country, unless they're racist, homophobic, xenophobic, just plain stupi… https://t.co/dwPIY2rnHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[New UVM president learned under innovative, but controversial, Purdue chief | VTDigger https://t.co/AiyF4cBJGK via @vtdigger]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you love them, pray for them. No matter what y’all are going through]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Idie14 Tough to bet against 3 of the first 5 picks and an above average coach. When all you gotta do is beat Mid… https://t.co/gNrlgfamvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to work every day with this talented and dedicated team!#WomenInSTEM #WomensDayTODAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tlahuicole1318 Ve por un especialista. No es caro si haces un balance del costo beneficio. Por si las dudas pregun… https://t.co/g5cYAJ7gd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astralprjecticn @rubberchild Literally me all day https://t.co/X9jiTR9bUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKhalilU I’d love to receive some money I need gas and food 🥘 https://t.co/vXKRo0nIZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyfattuesday #paczki #paczkiday #stillwarm #cbusfoodbloggers #cbusfoodscene #cbusfoodie #614eats @ Buckeye Donu… https://t.co/p7fx2A382p]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reaction shots became necessary (this is all Fredric Jameson) because the SNL audience was now too fragmented t… https://t.co/acY1pgjVr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[WIN A FREE Uniden Pro 505 XL CB Radio #giveaway #win https://t.co/RA6nWRwvdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think you’re burying the lede. 58% of republicans are admitted homophobes and 25% are admitted racists (25% and 7… https://t.co/zaXPNlIKi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙂🤙🏼T.O. Snow day!!❄️🌨️Trek'n w #DobeDante 🐾🐕💙  - ⤵️⤵️⤵️ How's Weather by You??👀 ⤴️⤴️⤴️ - 🔔Follow ✔️ @itsadamevans… https://t.co/xN8SWNQ0B1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eleven days, till ACDA did i, lost weight how i wanted to? No, but it’s fine,  it’s fine everything is fine!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willsommer He’s had way beyond his allotted 15 minutes of fame and contributed nothing to civilization whilst he had it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@America1stGirl Which means he can lie, Special Counsel guidelines exist, if Democrats play any games with those Ru… https://t.co/mWtEpgeBYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure Sentinel SIEM Tool Uses Machine Learning to Fight Malware https://t.co/PHI7S5PMDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered this @ICENINEKILLS #sweepstakes on #tunespeak.  Follow the link to enter and help me earn entries. https://t.co/Q25a83gxkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏋🏻‍♂️5:30 AM/WE woke up like this🏋🏻‍♂️ 🔥FinD YuOr SquaD🔥Equipo bodypumpofficial midtownchicago Precious Angels!!!!… https://t.co/tKVomk3PgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOP Christian Academy Black History Program! #topci #nolimits2019 #topchristianacademy topca_100 @ Tabernacle of Pr… https://t.co/3XBPTzZ66M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaiitlynzhang Fjdjdjd I was just going thru my google photos and I found this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier This keeps on showing who the real racist and violence people are and that's the Democrats and once… https://t.co/IwclwiMpgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Former Finance Chair of your party. Do you really want to disparage him right now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhoIsPierre @MartyrMal @sowellburneracc I don't recall. But 62 games and playing all 82 while rodman was mentally… https://t.co/C8S5VvGYXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's been sick for a few days but stuck it out the first of at least three games this weekend. Taking a lunch brea… https://t.co/ygBgQpiTtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perrysetgo Also, if you need some people to roll over to you and catch up. Let's make a lunch party]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevsmets @JPDeez @TeamActionShow @KristianHarloff @TheSchmoedown @KaiserSaysSo Wait, my ex-roommate turned out to be the Smasher?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally...our voices will be heard.  #wedontneedyou #LGI #yesyesyes #introtzwetrust @ Nassau Veterans Memorial Coli… https://t.co/SNq93kR4Fy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stickii_Nickii @DonnaBerghauser @nasponline @MOPreventionCtr @sldemarchena Thank you so much for attending!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankLevesque09 @NiltonJorge Je suis zéro fâché. 😅  Mais il y a tellement de détails de coulisses... (un jour, il… https://t.co/fBFo5V810g]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was wearing the same ring in all three pics my MINDDDD https://t.co/yILQSVBUlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leboudervincent @department22uk @RocaLONGallery @guardianscience Nice to see the term #agritecture going mainstrea… https://t.co/L4XLvM3LFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇦🇪👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss @keisidrenova The White RACE BLONDES👑Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The… https://t.co/kznimxstNx]]></document></documents></author>