<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[We’re coming to you from the Windsor Devonshire Mall where we just wrapped up our Tag Day at Indigo with our fabulo… https://t.co/KJETXCEZ1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, and every day, we #BalanceForBetter. Our people are celebrating International Women’s Day with a series of i… https://t.co/nLms2hV8Ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz Do you think that Cohen being coached by Cummings and Adam Schiff is the real witness tampering? @seanhannity @FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delcerebro @AHAHibbard With deliciousness and lots of fiber. #TraderJoes]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @warwick_la ・・・ for all you lovers out there. 💘 @ Buffalo, New York https://t.co/LUeXAWsgqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always prayed I would find you😍🙏  I am and always have been a helpless romantic. You better believe every 11:11,… https://t.co/ncvaY49pAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#allaboard aafexpress aafcommunity @theaaf @ Liberty Bowl Memorial Stadium https://t.co/QP8K1AAQ4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angrypanda0613 @Minecraft @mr_aquil1 @MicrosoftEduCA @MicrosoftStore Omg that Naruto tho 😂 So cute, hope you're having fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m supposed to be the only one who you rely on to do those things (create change, challenge the narrative, etc)… https://t.co/PfXmclaNb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: gonna  peacefully fall asleep at midnight and get a full nights rest  my brain, at 4am:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josh_williams09 oh man I’m team Black Sheep, with End Game as of my official Oscar prediction😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[sophie just threw up all over the table... this is the 3RD TIME SHE’S DONE THIS WITH ME]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get this collection and I usually, at least, understand what Abloh is trying to say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@umjeremy If I have done anything intentionally or unintentionally to harm you, please forgive me.  May the Peace o… https://t.co/lSMoSYmc6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zpriebe @WideRtNattyLt I’m a Cam fan. I want him to do well. And when he’s in, he’s in.   The Cam of the last few… https://t.co/RCRNFWGf52]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adriarwatson I am just so proudst of your amazing talent @adriarwatson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids club here is a hit with Mini Maus who just complained when I went to get her that she didn't have enough time… https://t.co/TkX8i9axso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *bleats like a sheep*  Me: babe that was a good one it sounded real  Blake: yeah babe it was good, I’m glad you’re speaking sheep now. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wooohoo @JustBullHere! Congratulations on your first year! Cheers to another year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/0ladAgZ7x9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What kind of place can you not go in the dressing room with your own child! Maybe this is why you are going out of business! Charlotte Russe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now this is a super cool feature and one I plan on using! https://t.co/SylZ1zYqhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasonstickers Trump was caught laundering money for the Russian mafia more than 100 times during his 1st year in… https://t.co/wNe1QFw0aQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@710WOR @NatBatVac circiing back to an earlier discussion The Cosby show is still on the air. For years I thought M… https://t.co/IsKTgpCKt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big smiles and a lot of sparkle last night to support @kiddskids 🎭 🥳 #krewedekidds https://t.co/RmUTRdBWVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper Nothing in Common , Lay Your Hands, Don't Mess with Dr. Dream. Saw them in 1985 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @MichaelCohen212 Con, we know you’re trying to sell your base a bag of sh*t. Truth is, Cohen is go… https://t.co/Z5EYMsBPrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Samcbride15 @cfisdmath @GarlandLinkenh1 @WillbernES @ConnyeRoberson 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GordonRamsay @24HoursFOX Do not know how you put with owner who act so selfish 😔👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[That awesome time White Rabbit rolled up in a red FIAT Spider. 🦄✨😲 . Who could say ‘no' to an #adventure through th… https://t.co/LdEWTmoC8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when people tell me they don’t drink water..that shit just make me feel dehydrated by listening]]></document><document><![CDATA[Equality should start on the playground. #InternationalWomensDay https://t.co/ULScSL3yVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TickedOff6 @poodlegirl08 Besides, she looks just as amazing today? Have you seen The Wife?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu So YOU DON'T think YOUNG GIRLS BEING RAPED IS a CRISIS? Americans DYING FROM DRUG OVERDOSES? WOMEN and GIR… https://t.co/SLpdPNfsAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kittenwithawhip Truth!!! How do they make us look so sallow?!?! That's talent!!! Convenience store bathrooms have better lighting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No... I am sorry @Mary Ann Lisanti everyone has not used the N word and I grew up in Vegas, Never used it  whether… https://t.co/wMnu55oCAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GHS_Geneva World Lang students &amp; more R raising $$ 4 Puerto Rico 🇵🇷 4 International Week! Can YOU help us?… https://t.co/ZAMSVjedLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice tinted glasses Kiefer. Are you going to wear this glasses during your gigs? @RealKiefer https://t.co/T0egX6y1ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even when I’m sleeping I can feel him hug me n kiss me before leaving for work lol 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 Ita.  It's the same with respect to the #FlintWaterCrisis - that's been ongoing for several years and T… https://t.co/qysDGePQW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raymysterio305 Thanks for keeping on the Truth, Ray J. Doesn't look like the Dems have changed their ways, bringin… https://t.co/9rCj9q47Ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ss making text-text connections during read aloud instruction @OPS_Harrison @OPS_Libraries  @ericlitwinbooks… https://t.co/0P5r3W0j3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[i really want dickies and to also go on T but not change anything else about me]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just wanna find a boy to go to a park and split some fruit w me that’s date enough w the right person idfc 👅 https://t.co/ciBf8gUZQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[$17 ramen, $17 drank #momofuku #momofukulasvegas #momofukuramen #vegaseats #food #foodporn #foodie #instafood… https://t.co/v2EUv78NkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m not going to fall asleep I just put my brain into battery saver mode”]]></document><document><![CDATA[You haters a quick to jump on lying and transparency, when Obama and Hillary are smooth with their lies and their n… https://t.co/lvEEbvwMf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kohoutseks Maybe it was my old music teacher?  Nah, he finally retired.  He unfairly criticized me once, and I sto… https://t.co/qUhLQXqK8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sexist Trolls Are Already Waging War Against 'Captain Marvel' With Negative Reviews - Esquire https://t.co/9tOoxgVSB5  #movies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitter I’ve literally seen the same tweets the past two days because of y’alls terrible feed update. Literally ab… https://t.co/HQYmyNtBqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[EDDIE T. JOHNSON FOR PRESIDENT...A GREAT MAN WITH GRIT, COMPASSION AND INTEGRITY. ALL MISSING FROM OUR CURRENT PRES TRUMP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dark hair has reignited my creative side 👏🏼👏🏼 I feel like it allows me to have a complimentary base to my make… https://t.co/Bp2c5gxjNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iiirdi @WhosBijanT @IntThings Plus you can afford to have many “life experiences” like traveling to many places al… https://t.co/sYamGDCNmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun for families prior to each Cinderella performance next week!  Space is limited. Purchase tickets today:… https://t.co/KlxFka9wy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @realDonaldTrump EVERYDAY would be a good day for Trump to resign or be impeached.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatrinaPierson Plugs having his hands on females especially children is WRONG and creepy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm really looking forward to #dope2019 next week; will any sessions (like the plenary panel or keynote) be streami… https://t.co/j4ub1gjCnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever you are done looking at this, try looking into a vital query all of us... #laughter #laugh #smirk… https://t.co/tld9x5f1iB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyKadiK Oh we will get out of this. It's just going to take some work and getting that JACKASS outta the #WH .… https://t.co/yx4VAHiXjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so glad I’ve never had a drama filled life. Never was constantly getting into shit with people, never really lo… https://t.co/OmrtQYilmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stormingee @NYCMayorsOffice @NotifyNYC Not the same when you’re a teacher and need to know if you have to trek to work tomorrow morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckster2012 What a wonderful and beautiful visit you were given :-) https://t.co/bD3ZHBdm3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tigers win 95-84 over Alice Lloyd to advance to the Mid-East Regional Championship tomorrow at 4pm.  It was a great… https://t.co/yfVKquheCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found an actual realistic snowflake in my hair and it’s the coolest thing ❄️❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for all of the Black Excellence that will take place at the #Oscars2019 #OscarsRedCarpet https://t.co/rejuzyoy8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still have not seen Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse and I think someone should sponsor my visit 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emptywheel Pretty much confirms what everyone knows. There are 2 justice systems. Angry with myself for believing… https://t.co/F1uU1p6gCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr George Duensti talks about LEO Pharmaceuticals goals: to really understand why some patients are super responder… https://t.co/GW2KCar6xH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no sympathy for her. She has been kissing Trump ass for years so she can get the crumbs they throw at her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylaknight08 @NerissaStreet @SXSWEDU I’m with you on that, Kayla! How can we educators inform the public that dec… https://t.co/81UZ9IuAlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[We Don't Want A Socialist Country ~ Caller @cspanwj Please check each Socialistic thing you don't want in America… https://t.co/V7k8bpMMsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Swipe Light by @stbcbeer @ Kroger Wine &amp; Growler Bar Bg — https://t.co/kSwcev0gco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drago237 Gracias a todos ustedes por su participación y apoyo, por los nuestros, por un… https://t.co/lko4Lp0KuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcmullenforus Read all of them.  Or go to You Tube and watch his interviews.  I’m tired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncusack LMFAO! Bernie will wipe the floor. That old man can't lift a broom seriously John Cusack you're delusio… https://t.co/nGVyUUWGiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wont cut ties with you until youve given me reasons A-Z as to why I should]]></document><document><![CDATA[So apparently everyone watches the  masked singer. I guess I'll just have to start next season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cookiebaby23 @Variety And he holds the highest position in the country not county ...but if you can tell me what i… https://t.co/yin8aiB1PL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beachinbeth @CraigBurt15 @JamesWStork PLEASE, OPEN YOUR EYES AND EARS... RUSSIA HATE, RACIST, UNPAID WORKERS, JAIL… https://t.co/wqx8R7B2uN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi All!  I’m excited to announce Jen Sing’s newest Karaoke gig...LA HAVANA in Burbank (formerly “Whiskey Bend”) EVE… https://t.co/5g4pAGUi2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay,listen.... I’m not saying alcohol is the solution butttt having a modelo in my hand while I dance doesn’t rule out fun 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well at least @ClintBowyer @SpotterBrett didn’t get caught in #TheBigOne @DISupdates #Daytona500 https://t.co/o83tpXOdnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amigos si necesitan llamar a VENEZUELA tengo plan para llamar a Celular y teléfono local, puedo comunicarme con sus… https://t.co/nBofbq2BEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This a Mami Wata baby for true!! She ready mom get her a reading and stop being a scary mama😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Electrek: Tesla shouldn’t reach volume Model 3 standard battery pack production until ‘mid-year’, says Musk.… https://t.co/Xuge8Pdns6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenninSage @FL_lewoo @Ilhan Thus, the point is, if you are against trump, you must be against any other politician… https://t.co/jAuAJLtAh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I want you to feel loved” brb gonna go get my bf an engagement ring 😂 fr tho 😭😭😭 ma little icy heart https://t.co/ivsIjp9J3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day to anyone who identifies as a woman. 👑❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Friends of San Diego Central Library in San Diego, CA https://t.co/BNNmoS5rDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether it was #Lorena herself, various witnesses on the stand, or neighbors who encountered her abuse, so many peo… https://t.co/bOLfEL3rNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. Civil, polite, conversation. You may not always walk away agreeing with the other person's point of view, but… https://t.co/DkOLJuOD2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamdeVry1 @RepSeanDuffy @SenBobCasey @srocf It is wonderful you support this ! So sad she was so young]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new study linked drinking coffee with a higher lifespan. Awesome. I'm going to be immortal. Courtesy of… https://t.co/A3NRQkKlNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[La caricature d'@ygreck #JDQ #polcan #JustinTrudeau #GeraldButts #PLC https://t.co/zYqOM2kHLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@audreyjtx A blue night... ?  I'm guessing. I just speak English and a light touch of Deutsch. But as they say art… https://t.co/l1SQ2jIMN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natbourrus Il est 5 h du mat. J ai mis les thématiques sur FB. Bises . A tout !😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to work listening to Christian music with a cup of coffee in my hand. Am I a mom and no one told me??😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir Well now we have a maintenance issue. This is odd given this plane came from the hangar.  #leavingonajetplane]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anybody has any problems reading this thread I apologize in advance because clearly my grammar and sentence stru… https://t.co/L8RHFnWI2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #FierceRobinFriday  Take a Stand Today, for What is up to You... #RobinMills #OUAT https://t.co/kd5PdKgXej]]></document></documents></author>