<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Obligatory snow picture. @ West Hartford, Connecticut https://t.co/6C90DYxOKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notngtolookat @CyrusMMcQueen My Grandmother use to eat it. I use to refer to it as made up of what they WON'T put in hotdogs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Do you really think just because you have a couple of black relatives and a black friend, that you… https://t.co/8lfvJGYj79]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that every verified account has spelt his name wrong has me cracking up.... 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slidin’out da Stu’N Leavin’Dis’Right Here. 🇯🇲🔥✊🏾🔥🇵🇷 #caveosilensartifex #matungeri #matungerimusic… https://t.co/93uihziys0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normani is beautiful and talented and I really hope she goes far in the industry 💕✨✨✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TFP @DennisTFP “Ideal situation for while” - um... mr editor... don’t you mean “ideal situation for A while?”- you’re welcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TRNorth_Hoops leads Rancocas Valley 36-15 at Halftime.  Spence with 15 and Dunszak 13 for the Mariners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at CVS Health? We're hiring in #Lakewood, CA! Click the link in our bio for details on this job and mo… https://t.co/xt7gfO75BG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The perfect bite to end the night at #starchefs #nyc @chefsaninnn elevenmadisonpark #barleyicecream #malticecream… https://t.co/bijDDP0HZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Uber @Uber_Support do you see the screen shots? Doesn’t it look like I’ve already contacted you about this issue?… https://t.co/FbH0aRdMQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big thanks to the folks at @BeckGroup, for sending flowers to my momma. And thanks to everyone for the well wishes.… https://t.co/ZxL5xmwzC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to the #CBJ - Pens game tonight in Pittsburgh.. https://t.co/BBPLfsnRti]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poole: If I believed we couldn’t guarantee accountability/that tax dollars would be spent responsibly in  this infr… https://t.co/bWl0pBioLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge with respect you don’t know so why are You chiming in , I think you are turning left]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recent Nolan Catholic transfer @_mullins33 experienced his first major camp event. The 2020 former LD Bell LB/H-Bac… https://t.co/IUMASSP11Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[quien a encontrado un amigo a encontrado un tesoro hermana glenda https://t.co/R8QCdwnwot vía @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trending definition - currently popular or widely discussed online, especially on social media websites.  Maybe tha… https://t.co/EmI329Iyco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every night, sit down. Pick 3 sponsors and let them know that you are done with them until you see a change. Don't… https://t.co/VV0UBmnuRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZorroBl @EdKrassen With retroactive back pay and monies for pain and suffering having to deal with the insane clow… https://t.co/UPAPvaop0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Giants2019 @g68_charlie @EddyFinnerty @GiantsTBR @sooobad6 @Patricia_Traina 💯 percent agree. Definitey it was an o… https://t.co/BSfBl1iU0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going on a helicopter ride next month. Should I try to suck a dick up there? 🚁 If I do, it will be featured on my premium Snapchat 👻]]></document><document><![CDATA[First thing I’m learning as a fire bender is how to bend lightning 🔥⚡️ #Lightning https://t.co/ATk369ucX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog I feel somewhat bad for him and think it’s highly possible that he may suffer from mental illness. H… https://t.co/wFYVZnUr6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEconomist Heck no.  But, how do we break up the silos? We have subcultures that can't understand each other, an… https://t.co/AQUTY5Iey6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, at https://t.co/TIzDmCvpOv, gorgeous @LilySwan1 gets her first two of FOURTEEN spankings, an ass-scorching O… https://t.co/jBDqBFCD03]]></document><document><![CDATA[For people that still believe that the Democratic party is the party of blatant racism and slavery, i want to ask t… https://t.co/NbFw9Ttqnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usweekly Jealousy is in the air these days, your mad because A-rod is happy and your pathetic. https://t.co/ZetqBCK7nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just made myself look like an idiot trying to park. I hate the snow packed parking lots 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spooner trade for Gagner now opens up a winger spot for Jesse Puljujärvi in Bakersfield.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hammering the letters off a TRUMP building. 1 year ago. @terrifiedhistorybuff https://t.co/8ssIr6wt4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 Strangely, this is the one instance in which Manafort was blameless. This judge was incredibly hostile… https://t.co/oXm7mzleov]]></document><document><![CDATA[keep seeing signs that say "THE CANAL CITY" and it's taking everything in my being to not go around covering up the 1st C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgetJonesPup  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊 #resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kids are getting a slide phone. Not in fifth grade. No they are getting a SLIDE PHONE in 7th grade which was whe… https://t.co/S6KHDGhjTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCFCKnox I’m planning to be there on Saturday so I’d say there is a good chance of a shark team selfie after a few… https://t.co/ApTZrXVCvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with the #profitshare boss #networking #kwfr #dnarealtygroup   #realestate 🏠 #agents #networking #nola… https://t.co/J1gjueQzFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@czabe I'm suprised that these jokers are out of cash in Week *2*.  That's surprising right there]]></document><document><![CDATA[you set the socialist back 20 that is why they are losing their collective minds. There is alot of legislating from… https://t.co/pkrmBGNPhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealUnFeminist @KouInfinity @AOC @thecjpearson https://t.co/29XZLJFnqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pete_coops @jaysonstreet Isn't there an F-35 needing auditing or something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many people knew Bill far better and longer than I did. But even in the (too-)short time that we were on the facult… https://t.co/caEW0MpijV]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are starting our preparation for a great weekend full of education!  #happiness #torobrands #toroenterprise… https://t.co/vIQHh1ZSMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yeseniamend0za @Ricky_leee Just got done with a medium NY Strip. I don’t care if it takes a week to digest-that sh… https://t.co/YmTmcCcTCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonnyBunch I wanna retweet this but I don’t want to have to explain Snowpiercer]]></document><document><![CDATA[He needs to spend at least a year in State prison. That will teach him a great lesson. He and others will think twi… https://t.co/z2mjN2qios]]></document><document><![CDATA[So if we beat Auburn ... us and LSU will be co champs.. but they get the #1 seed in the sec tourney ... correct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurameme having your own fans cheering louder is a bad solution? So your only answer is kick people out? People w… https://t.co/gQwH1CX3zZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moral of the story is no interview with the opening line “Hey Gov how do ya do?” should be taken seriously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SpeakerPelosi doesn’t make gaffes. She makes three moves ahead statements.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateDems @SenBlumenthal the constitution, comes first your feelings should not even be in the picture. as you sh… https://t.co/VWjsqMTHIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ollie_ODea @CameronNewton There's a massive correlation with draft stock, but not so much with play. Manning and R… https://t.co/3RRZRVmV5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter Whew!!! Dont need an over paid old washed up headcase anyway...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@draininbuckets @LaurenUnderwood Nah. Its funny tho how you think I'm worked up. While you help expose Lauren and her pals and hacks!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Progressives like @AOC @BernieSanders @ewarren represent the majority of Americans' views, and @superwuster is righ… https://t.co/kBZsavTfC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kavita1010 @Howdy_Doughty @SailorsBen @DreaVilleneuve @joshmccormack @MrLexJay @JoelRRenner @katyb_spencer… https://t.co/pFwWBgSAh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen retweet for vets! 11% of homeless are veterans. with ptsd and mental health issues. Venmo rob-donley… https://t.co/esZzDotssT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has got to be his insurance agent brother, Cliff Paul.. I refuse to believe Chris pulled up like this for the… https://t.co/sCzhv92Npj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get you to all the right places long before others make you feel good about it. Look at this and the @TheAAF stuf… https://t.co/xXgmfl5d7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timeout Maryvale, 4:14 remaining in the 2nd. Amherst has not made a fg in the quarter but still lead 25-9.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally off... now to finally get my cut hopefully there’s no alcohol today 😂🤙🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought First Man’s Doubs editing was better, but knew Bohemian Rhapsody was gonna win this. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[the site’s users rate restaurants and other businesses on a series of four questions, including whether the restaur… https://t.co/3vVN5ZRFwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poetjames @Augustus709 It might feel like Congress is moving slow.  Because this case MUST have ALL t’s crossed an… https://t.co/TxSNHZIOwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[La joven de 32 años de edad que fue reportada como desaparecida el 3 de febrero de este año fue localizada asesinad… https://t.co/YG6BqapSLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBoyWonerd @Ghost56636874 @AllysonTurner @MarathnInvestgr @LeBatardShow @ESPNRadio @bre_tiesi I regret I have bu… https://t.co/3PxFn2JV67]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost that hour of sleep, but looking forward to seeing some sunlight past 6pm 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #NCGOP inquiry-" what happens if one of our #candidates gets caught committing #ElectionFraud?" State Officials… https://t.co/2NclIMQq95]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidcmcalpine He better lawyer up and turn himself in to police. If police have to go out to find him it will mean more charges.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it very hypocritical of demoncrats to lecture those who know best about immigration by using kids in cages a… https://t.co/Zb1gEIebLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[No3  STOP TORMENTING and TORTURING ME WITH YOUR USE/ACCESS to RADAR/RADIO/HARMONICS ON ME and other FOLKS at the AI… https://t.co/p8plDWB2Nv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettyGordon_ @ovidio_noval @jorgeberry En qué ha mejorado Mexico? , no se si estemos peor , pero en verdad que ha… https://t.co/Tm58G3QvwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bootz1515 @CityMusic11 @MiggyMigggs I’m cool without him https://t.co/c6k86ZBAtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why isn't McCabe being prosecuted for treason?  Wake up justice dept. he admitted his guilt in a public forum!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No you made your money off special interests correct? Look at your net worth in 2015 and now. Hmmm don’t throw ston… https://t.co/LjqocFgXGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Umbrella academy is probably one of the best shows Netflix has created! And the playlist is even better!! 👌🙌🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DraytonToups @DineshDSouza That's a really good analogy but I think Term limit's would solve alot of the Problem m… https://t.co/fYfYblOFuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ameen!!!!👏🏿✊🏿 #AsaalamuAlaikumWahRahmantuillah #Alhamduillah #Allah #AllahUAkbar #ProphetMuhammad #PBUH #Quran… https://t.co/YETf6UceQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[La pregunta es porque no asumió el costo la empresa Eléctrica? Falta una investigación sobre el lobby que hubo en e… https://t.co/8FpiIRjl2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[How amazing are the crowds on libertyoftheseasofficial check it out.  #showtime #cruise   Thanks @royalcaribbean an… https://t.co/AylAaBEDAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@617Report @realDonaldTrump He’s the least popular president ever and his base is about 30% of the population - the… https://t.co/WEfHgP3xUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so busy working and listening to the Cohen trials I completely forgot a new Pokémon game was being announced… https://t.co/P64MBY1sDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @DougBurnsTHELAW All involved plead fifth -all paperworks stop  - investigations are stonewalled,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @CLewandowski_ @realDonaldTrump You mean bowing down to Russia, Turkey, Saudi Arabia, North Korea, so much for a super power]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trefulton I have a legitimate question. What policy does Trump have that is more evil than allowing abortion up until birth?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning on @WDCBPublicRadio we celebrate THE THUMB - Wes Montgomery! His incredible sound, his mastery of the… https://t.co/v3f79LUgBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahClarkVA I can’t remember what was said or what you threw at me. Please tell me! Please tell me why!  Good song… https://t.co/2K7GC2trEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamtmo I would follow any one who posted this. https://t.co/LFv3if54D3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buzy az a bee with squierguitar @empress_effects @bossfx_us digitechfx ehx @neunaberaudio #bass #guitar… https://t.co/asXUR6ci81]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkippersHuman I wish! I still have to buy those mama jamas myself to give away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your #vaccines, folks. It’s 2019. We don’t have to suffer through this. #Philippines #Measles #MeaslesOutbreak… https://t.co/7aEswcX2SL]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Valentine’s Day I’m staying home drinking! Because of the single life😶🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett might want to watch is back... @TheDemocrats or @SenKamalaHarris might want him silenced...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to fail... #teamPROformations #midwestmecca #prepcoach @ Life Transformations Personal Training https://t.co/BhSfNyFGbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Embarrass yourself against a bad BC team while the entire country is watching a game 10 miles away, couldn't be more irrelevant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thirdmanmovies So many conflicting thoughts about that film. If I remember though it was extremely controversial e… https://t.co/E9aHJnQjzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMurphy Hey brain surgeon. Why don’t you do it at night so the people with jobs can weigh in ?  Or would that of… https://t.co/Tv7aKxETDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaniaKhalek @respect65 Including 20 other nations and 80% of the Venezuelan people all askingMadurp to step aside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PanakinCaboose One year olds rarely ever like their first cake. They’ve never had much sugar before.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philliesgirljma He’s quite wise. And potty trained, to boot. And he can tantrum with the best—making strangers in… https://t.co/QxgKADSYjA]]></document></documents></author>