<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@xtop @andykhouri I’m in between. Been watching it since season two aired, but my routine is to skip a few seasons… https://t.co/UBj1Q2GVha]]></document><document><![CDATA[For them to have a Pro Team this city ain’t no bigger den Akron lol &amp; it’s freezing up this hoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy that society makes women change their name after marriage.  But it is tradition so I made my wife change her name to Rachel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Simplicityyyy__ I don’t participate in the Forest fire festivities but I respect your opinion lmao I just wanna kn… https://t.co/sR5lHz4m9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJenRows My water intake yesterday was well over my normal take.  This is good as so normally is just shy of the… https://t.co/jS4ksaTlvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game of Thrones is so legit that they gave us the longest winter in years just before winter comes in the show. I’v… https://t.co/m01PUdbznL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noche bostoniana #noche #boston #celtics #fotografia #photography #photo #night https://t.co/inPUqHPiCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me getting stuck in the snow three times in Eugene OR https://t.co/DwgRVOqwde]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We must stop Trump’s fake emergency and desperate attempt to go around Congress for his unnecessary border wall.”… https://t.co/PEehxuKPmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephsAmusic Thank you for answering my question stephanie you the best!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#truth #wisdom #spiritual #mindset #joy #belief #positivity #jeffreybyron   I BELIEVE! 🙏 @ Century City, Los Angeles https://t.co/27q8ddmxri]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbellaDangerAss hey abelladanger i am ur biggest fan how can i get some pics anvideos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolChief gotta give it to Crow for that performance. Real sloppy out there. Made some big stops. Really want… https://t.co/ubIzXt3REB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commit thy way unto the Lord ; trust also in him; and he shall bring it to pass. Psalms 37:5 KJV https://t.co/zQkze3hkJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a talk with @yuukimurai1 about how I went from being in major pain with back issues taking a butt load of pa… https://t.co/sDChou0CIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwalsh838 @LindaSuhler @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity But I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth.  Day1USA H… https://t.co/43gDWBBLvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scott_canda @DavidJHarrisJr @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Yea it’s being controlled  ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celestiallmj @cherrycastles why am I getting dragged for being a dumbass IN MY OWN MENTIONS https://t.co/b29yTInNzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CabanaClubKCB Will stop in and visit next time down there. Can't wait. https://t.co/mnEB9rwfGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinsey just told me her one cat is a chonkers and that he likes CHIPS. not cat food or cat nip but mfing chips]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hashtag #ashtag  Have a blessed Lent #nygrammer #igersny #igerslongisland #nyc @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/tdyxChUNXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time a nigger trynna be funny,  he look like some character from grand theft auto lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNintendoHub @LonelyGoomba And now that’s 2 GTs I can’t trust anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is more annoying on the office?       RT: Andy                                                    Like: Ryan]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only hit ur phone when I want pussy, u don’t offer shit else, and that shit don’t even be all that ... u ain’t br… https://t.co/1WUlEbIfjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me ask the US govt. something.  OK?  How you gonna have a vote that I'm not even involved in and make a damned… https://t.co/vYnaI01ROm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chouchoutv Me too❣️ Happy Valentines to you both you beautiful ladies💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[CLOSING SOON - Ed Sievers: In My Corner is on view through Saturday, March 2nd.  - Ed Sievers’ later body of work l… https://t.co/I6QyyWEw3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateeForbis I my hate you for telling me about #datingaround I just love train wrecks dates on TV.  ie The Bachelo… https://t.co/uPwwAbBGRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CancilleriaVE @NicolasMaduro Es la mentira un hobby para uds? Uds no trasladaron a ningun niño]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_IAmBritBrat britttttt!!! Happy belated bday!!! Shots on me next time we link 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I hate shit like this. Like obvi were all gonna take one https://t.co/OHER3diKe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lopezdoriga Bravo! A este paso solo tardarán 10 años en eliminar todas! Si es que no hacen NINGUNA nueva...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canceling John Wayne in 2019 is like remembering you never cancelled your Seeso subscription.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrBrianMay rocking the #Oscars! Did you know he is a PhD astrophysicist? His other gig is pretty cool, too. #astronomy @QueenWillRock]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @mrs_freer to post covers of 7 books I ❤️: no explanations, no review-just the cov… https://t.co/dLWovTIkMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin keeping Angelica against her will is slavery. Taking a her on your private jet against her will is sex tr… https://t.co/A5dIcQRW1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love knowing what is going on and why. Thanks @mbta! #traingeek @narprail]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you turn off like notifications from other people?. I don’t care about seeing other accounts I don’t follow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can choose how we’re going to respond to life’s surprises and disappointments when they arise, and whether we wi… https://t.co/8ACvbD0VAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDrGina Someone needs to tell her Christ is the son of God.  That should annoy her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you lose the presidency to Trump, you literally should be forced to only say “I’m sorry, yes I know” when people talk to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory The law and the government doesn't work that way Senator Kennedy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I once had a student who went to the bathroom and came back in with his clothes put on backwards ... I still scratc… https://t.co/3otKlsZysG]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Antonio has got nothing on the beautiful Richmond Canal Walk https://t.co/xKvsUweYtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cindyscott54 It is time to remove from office all that promote hate in the name of their religion, or maybe remove… https://t.co/bCTV4waZDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The habit of passing laws that are outlines to be filled in by the Secretary of such and such department would be i… https://t.co/Bj1qewzQ56]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rare day that I need to be up at 4.. got five alarms set.. of course I’m up at 2am lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManuelaUribe6 que no hable con extraños y que sea compartido con su sándwich]]></document><document><![CDATA[danjbeal ‘s interpretation of recipe number 97, page 234 in the Dali Cookbook for the current @alinea gallery. “Sal… https://t.co/TZb3OJ1Yov]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the little things that turn into big things in life! It’s the thought that counts more than the item. It’s kno… https://t.co/4q5Q4EL8W0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I cut my hair? I haven’t cut my hair since half way through August.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyPastewart2 @Goss30Goss @brithume Sad state of affairs when a delusional spinster admits clinging to guns and bi… https://t.co/Wz2oKsZ1Ek]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't mean to scare you guys by showing you such things you or your kids don't need to see.. I just want you to k… https://t.co/2l786xg5sa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennaHarner4 Don’t mind celebrations however the extensive choreography and props for what some might call a routi… https://t.co/0tKaLOmTu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a great first step to protecting Americans, particular children in school, from the horrific reality of gun… https://t.co/v6QaTS84TL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been up since 3:15 like it’s a work day!   Just up, UP! Legit put in a load of laundry in the washer like it’s 9:30am!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c_crosswell @TimberrWhite @steamtheorybrew Chris Harrison showed up one Monday this month it was pretty cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordan_77546 @Jphan23 @itsbrandibitcch There’s no facial hair so that’s obviously you????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scottie so flip flop. Literally just said the opposite statement last year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMGrubb Right I remember that it was not nominated at all!! Which was tragic too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Janiaapaula4 This has reached such a level of absurdity and still makes no sense whatsoever. Tchau, ciao, adios, a… https://t.co/HiSsJdaC20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elenakoshkaxoxo so did mine. Now I wonder how many other that have this same condition. someone needs to raise awa… https://t.co/OriHXtjqrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3th4nr0th3rm3l @Castaldo2018 @timothypmurphy @AOC A president represents the entire fucking country. Not towns, or… https://t.co/S6hoDUtjaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[DIME CANTINERO TÚ SABES DE PENAS!!! A LOS CUANTOS TRAGOS ME OLVIDA DE ELLAAAA 🥃🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ι just told my girlfriend to give me her worst and she said fucking bet, idk what kind of deal w the devil Ι just made]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertTate1 your hair this year is like a puzzle piece that fits into last year's hair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @USATODAY WE also know what you’re doing, too, you old hag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIL a pen knife is called that because it’s used to cut feathers into quills]]></document><document><![CDATA[SF Preps: Lowell girls’ soccer outlasts Mission for 22nd consecutive City crown - San Francisco Examiner… https://t.co/113HGs1ajK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minneapolis is going the way of Sweden, Germany, France and England!!! Good fuc#ing luck!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tennessee hasn't beaten Kentucky in a meaningful basketball game in 40 years. They can't when there's a championship on the line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill What the hell does that have to do with Russian collusion there is none Democratic Socialist Party is wasting taxpayer money]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonasbrothers I CANT believe you guys are back!! i've waited for such a long time!!!! once jonatic always jonatic #SuckerVideo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillWineBanks @THR I actually met Buffalo Bob. He was a close friend of my wife’s grandfather. He was very nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s start the weekend on a positive note.  Today on #Fox29GoodDay we’ve got #BryceHarper updates, a man running a… https://t.co/55OJVLrVvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand @PaulQuinnTigers You speak of morality, I think it’s not in your dictionary, but I suggest that you… https://t.co/lfD7uN6WCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeighaOsolinski I was actually leaving when I saw you clear the snow from the car beside you.  Then when you conti… https://t.co/eqTHMh8Dms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ridingbluewaves @thomaskaine5 We must be careful about these type of statements. There are some fruit cakes out th… https://t.co/3JQ2WIGK5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[#managementskills #needhelp #prioritize @ Long Beach, California https://t.co/UMysoz4pKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yorobertaa @TwinSpires Your account will be credited the difference. Good bet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[GM @HallieJackson Do you approve of the way @MSNBC incessantly (uncontested) demonizes @SenSanders ? Shouldn't he o… https://t.co/8SURbcZuSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CubsCurmudgeon @KleinschmidtJD Pretty damn cold, they had snow earlier this week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NStonestreet @aaronchan10 Gotta agree with @NStonestreet, I agree it’s ridiculous what the IFB movement is fightin… https://t.co/KgwpKI4bcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lindsey06479125 @VoluntaryVagab1 @BuzzFeedNews No no Lindsey,this wasn't i who said that,I'm only grouped in on said tweet,thank u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askdes @TMobile You’re not still running windows 7 are you?! Time to update! 💪🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I first heard a four-word response to a suggestion while I was in the Navy (Engineering Officer of the Watch to Rea… https://t.co/ES6o3xMxpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get some people hate canelo, but what was just dumb. Every fighter faces smaller dudes at one point in their career.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love me some humor. #hilarity #lol #smirk #comic https://t.co/yv3caIEefT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thing one and thing two wrapping up @NEAToday Read Across America Week! #TCSLearns https://t.co/VgevSZ7rCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[C’est malheureusement un art qui se perd avec le temps @S_EFortin.  Il m’apparaît évident de toujours comprendre le… https://t.co/l42kTfl7LO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know anything about the history of Maltese, but I do know I will never be able to say دجاج or Buttigieg aga… https://t.co/yRbiYaRQc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4 beginning with the assisinsantion site of President Lincoln @PineJogES @pbcsd https://t.co/kjFhs6ofTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, this is amazing troll work by KU fans. #JohnBrownLessonPlan https://t.co/W66wWgQbgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Leeeno_ Mark. He was talking shit, but then starts playing all types of weird music. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for Senate to sue Schiff Over lies.  Schiff has visions of evidence no one else has identified.  Is Schiff the… https://t.co/ZTiS3b3N19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scaloniadon @JerryFalwellJr @AOC I’m coming for @JerryFalwellJr’s cows. All hands on deck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#US #Usa #Michigan #Chicago #NewYork #Illinois #Joliet #Indiana #Indianapolis I'm listening to some classic hit son… https://t.co/q4GWzauhP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now available and #InMyShop! #Vintage #RoyalHaeger #Retro #Cigar #Ashtray!  Want it? Then head on over to The 8th H… https://t.co/JmlfTUtTpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkNagiTDOT I think I just ran through a sink hole 🕳 JohnSevier/NationalDrive]]></document></documents></author>