<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[When my friends take pictures of me all I feel is judging eyes from other females😆😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't  know where you ppl get the 8000 lie count on Trump?? I'm sure he has told lies at times in his life; As ha… https://t.co/8SwqHXvxzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicked off our @penniesforpati1 drive to fight against #lukemia and #lymphoma @LLSusa these proud Norwood Knights d… https://t.co/uXWDgwmiJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy bday @Jakezettergren1 !!let’s hope we pass this english class together 😭🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cslainfo Great bits of info from your own CA state-funded online resource @cue]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am never jealous of someone who gets to go on vacation. Good for you. Live that shit up! #vacationislife #yolo #quityahatin #PositiveVibes]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm watching all these stars from country to pop to rock on this Elvis Presley's All Star Tribune and just remember… https://t.co/44idPMV0TC]]></document><document><![CDATA[FACEBOOK Removed my Acct after Sharing GA HB481 SB281 Life ACT Abortion Bills SB 221 “Religious Freedom Restoration… https://t.co/dKnmpRjNOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 minutes @AmericanIdol @LukeBryanOnline #AmericanIdol #LukeBryan https://t.co/xrQ51dQrvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go again he was a good actor people loved him and oh my God he said something controversial oh my God bette… https://t.co/649E8pV3wi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjane87 I have one for you:  The Crucible  Start with bar. Add 10# every minute 1 Snatch EMOM until failure  When… https://t.co/QhIYF0FsAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@floresbrandon77 I can bet you $100 the apartment was clean when you got home just now 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[No saben cooooooomo me emperra que mastiquen con la boca abierta o que hagan chingos de ruido mientras comen 🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤯🤯🤯🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ate many oatmeal pies by the famous little Debbie and now I feel extremely ill]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been excited for a bong in my entire life but I worked really hard for this one and can’t wait til’ it’s delivered 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need God to come into my room and be like “listen sis...this is what you gonna do”]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Tayshia clearly wasn’t phased by all these girls being sent home because they threw the other girls under the bu… https://t.co/6gjdx0Cee8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The music you play first thing in the morning when you get in the car will set the mood for the entire day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs to see a baby goat to start their weekend off right! Baaaaa!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My visit to the Sowden House! Beyond beautiful and so peaceful. But, the basement had a entirely different feel. Cr… https://t.co/4kkImJP1DO]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing wrong with this world, it’s just people’s narrowed mindset.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I was playing around with @EddyCeetee and now I can't figure out which one I like the best. So I said to hell wi… https://t.co/LNOsUrJTXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mat1Oliver @dom_finland @BixJacks @Sirveaux1066 @chooburns @SharonHepworth3 @sineadmcfc @dienekes105 @Wallpaul70… https://t.co/toxkdNB7gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deplorablem1ke Which makes her a lying slut, nothing new to see here. She’s only proving to everyone that not only… https://t.co/FFMslJe5tQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabriellaR613 @GinnCatherine @Gianlui91580067 @james_anderssen @shlomomeirisrae @KeepSmile912 @lizfebry9… https://t.co/8SV4VrHQ3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllisterDen Lanny Davis is very close to Hillary Clinton and her cronies. If this isn't a setup by crooked attor… https://t.co/PnS2RN3qZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[update: Satan failed me. I had my first mental breakdown at work today lolol someone kill me please]]></document><document><![CDATA[how much money you got?  how many problems you got? how many people done doubted you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smallworld101k Thanks, hon. I have tons. Like this mirror shelf. One of my fav mcm pieces, but I’ve never had a pl… https://t.co/fzgqB5kSdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m reading messages from when Chris and I first started to admit our feelings for each other and it’s god me all in my feels.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence @WhiteSpir1t I'm thankful you are alive too. God will guide you through this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep. Twitter deducts from my followers instead of adding when someone new follows me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kutanks I’m gonna report you @shiftyEightSev you should do the same #reportkutan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still thinking about this extraordinary production. Stellar, stellar work all around. So proud of these artists at… https://t.co/bad1EFLoR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will you be onboard?  Carson Travel will be! #carsontrav #celebritycruises #equinox #caribbean #wintergetaway… https://t.co/4uJMzJGuO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care either. Depression and declining health is associated with aging and Manafort is no spring chicken! Su… https://t.co/EEbTHijqB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[OfficialGym. com https://t.co/OMquPEZT7g #Gymshark66 #Bodybuilders #fitnesslifestyle #beastmode #fitness… https://t.co/7F816dZYIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShreyaInd1an You can mute words on here so you can mute their names and any tweet that has their names in it you won’t see]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GilbertVillar12 We are part of an awesome church, thanks! All the glory &amp; thanks to God!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @jonasbrothers are back together and if this isn’t the best day of the year then idk what is]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the guy who used to write for Johnny Carson and David Letterman e-mails you and asks for your dialogue so he c… https://t.co/7bbuUzx5C8]]></document><document><![CDATA['Empire' actor #JussieSmollett hit with 16 count felony indictment by grand jury  - #ABC News  https://t.co/d4aCVivmNy (via @ABC)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The judge should lock him up pending his trial for violating the gag order.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary wow.. 10 years on Twitter? https://t.co/2p4H1Lhap5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMonteroOficial @NicolasMaduro @jguaido Carlos, cómo te gusta lastimar a los venezolanos con comentarios infelices… https://t.co/45aLrQtKWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[man, nothing hurts more than knowing i’m not the only one feeling this pain but my whole family, FUCK CANCER]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accidentally added someone I didn’t want to add on snap and now I have to wait to see what happens and omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dave__whiteside @SchlegelVillage @hannes_renee @ChristyAParsons @tmahy @jjluhkim @HarbinAmy @SniderMerry… https://t.co/yj28QnO7E3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FLOTUS @ericbolling @WestgateVegas Tell FLOTUS TULSA, OK. LOVES HER!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dropped Ronnie off at a new groomers this morning and they just called me to tell me what an angel he is. My Ronn… https://t.co/CV34phFEgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Remember when you hated Trump? What was it that won you over to the orange side?… https://t.co/09nlogmolf]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you begin to mind your own business that’s when you’ll find peace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The musicians in The Seldom Scene are the sweetest humans eveeerrrrr 😍 48 years doing what they do and oozing with class and grace #joeval]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maine public access stations want their channels back.  https://t.co/0ZjxzoSPF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerItaliano Agree but he’s playing his way out of the lineup. Adams/Servedio playing in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsLuciaG Ik that’s not what you meant, but that’s all that came to mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewmercer This whole journey has been so incredible to watch. I’m so happy for guys!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m fucking crying! My girl just came over with two big ass bottles of wine and roses😍 AND SHE BROUGHT DABS!!!! 😩 I HAVE THE BEST FRIENDS!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gotta be self aware. You have to be able to self check. Know when you're wrong &amp; adjust.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Kensley asked me who got dqed, I told her I didn’t know their name, she said cause they cheated mommy. I have no… https://t.co/IwAT4IujLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Again?  You already said that three times....wait...you have said it to the point of panic orange boy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrs_ingvardsen @CFISDWells @CFISD_ELAR2_5 @lead4ward So do they leave their paper at their seat?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember why I stopped stretching my septum out, feels like I've been punched in the nose, and I sized up 3 days ago 😭.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake up...Drink tea ☕️....and get ready to rock your day!!! #herbalife #herbaltea #greentea #happymonday… https://t.co/fasjs9Cj72]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me out peopleHey, someone tagged you! Your free earphones has been delivered! Get it in minutes! https://t.co/WPxQBG0PGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing this night with the ones I love and those who believe in me is everything I could ever ask for. Thank you t… https://t.co/45zbQrzemj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodtimes#goodfriends @ Bam Entertainment Center https://t.co/HpQp8XYOMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m case you were wondering, it’s a jeezy type of morning.   see you in frankfort 👋]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still singing shallow since last night🤦🏽‍♀️🤣🤣🤣 my capacity of not moving on, never cease to amazed me 🤣♥️ #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helped someone not pass out and get called a pervert. Okay. https://t.co/Py2zqZfcQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[kissing February goodbye and welcoming another month closer to spring!!! Am I the only one excited for Spring? . .… https://t.co/vBBpSQMH0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 at @traffic_summit I have learned a lot, I’ve been inspired &amp; most of all I am excited about the future. #TCS2019 #letsdothis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really need school to be cancelled tomorrow because reallyyyy not ready for this test]]></document><document><![CDATA[while you’re here follow me? or don’t but just know that i’ll hold it against you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stem cell therapy - this is where the magic happens! mayoclinic #mayojr19 nbcnewschannel @nbcnewshealth nbcnews… https://t.co/qoeasMVXjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[My recent searches on twitter are all public figures I’m not fond of &amp; Wilmer Valderaama in a different order every time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who's Ready for Jump Force @AngryBirds #AngryBirdsMovie2 #jumpforce https://t.co/4tOEtYbbqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be real tho he was only nice to Hispanics he was like fuck white people and he was white as fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsKelsyGroover For sure! I’ll be around! When do you get in?? Can’t wait to see you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a45cooper @marcosanchezorg @Zak_Bagans @agoodwincollect @BillyTolley @jaywasley I will. You too!!😀🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still good but not what it used to be. - Drinking a Hopslam Ale by @BellsBrewery at @IceHouse_Pub  — https://t.co/gQWI7b5PRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I get mad at myself for building up a wall in my life, but nowadays people only care about artificial looks and feelings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the ResCare Residential Services team! See our latest #BusinessMgmt job openings, including "Program Director"… https://t.co/5QvozDdwtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[If ya best friend turns into a stranger they weren’t your best friend🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las respuestas a este tweet, que cortos de mente la gente, de verdad que vienes aquí, lees y te asustas.  - tienes… https://t.co/3lE2Mdk7IU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backstage 2019-Feel the excitement Week 2! @weareunited #BEINGUNITED Meeting Great People who truly Care about Unit… https://t.co/ka4Viv0O7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK so this father and son at mel’s jst came up to this man and he said “my son and i r a big fan of u’ n they took… https://t.co/4fUlrpnS8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love that our customers repurpose our macaron boxes! #reuse #recycle #WeHaveTheBestCustomers]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted the challenge from @aadrean to post the cover of 7 books I love - no explanations - just the cover.… https://t.co/BL4l3Ov4ZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taffyakner Only in white trash neighborhoods are Jews hated and disrespected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to use them (I’m adding some more!) search @shaunalynn on Instagram. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @StratfordSBISD’s Emma Stephenson on her selection as a @BecksPrime HoustonGirls Swimmer of the Year! W… https://t.co/h3gmHCMBmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tenntinavolfan @BubbaWallace @DISupdates @Vol_Hoops watching the CATS!! #BBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only we were allowed to actually do this! Sure would be nice for some to see! https://t.co/xBckuMwCIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Only as high as I reach can I grow, only as far as I seek can I go, only as deep as I look can I see, only as much… https://t.co/nnPZYUxp6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoodyWyatt2 @mrcrockpot @Bharper3407 @Phillies @MLBINSIDER_ He said it could be done deal with Phillies never once… https://t.co/qn77APmHOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to flex on y’all but i’ve been watching GOT since 2014. at least y’all finally showed up to the party tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate is so dirty. I cleaned the entire house (by myfuckingself) before I left and now my other roommate tell… https://t.co/KvR09OKICd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CncBhDdubminion @cassie04061983 @naturenohurry91 @shergiggles @JaimeRKOFan @Amy_DDubGirl @jennyraej1979… https://t.co/nErFHP16BU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could tweet this a thousand times.  God adores all Her children. She weeps when they strike each other usi… https://t.co/EiSUAf7sLQ]]></document></documents></author>