<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite non-Giants players that I always wanted to be a Giant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @Hbowman1H @wjxt4 @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487… https://t.co/VhbW48p4Br]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hilmer Td up for saying "Don't penalize him for being quick". Maybe the weakest T in the history of basketball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had such a great time last night at the Aquarium - rode a Ferris wheel, fed stingrays, won several stuffed anima… https://t.co/8MarvLi0qy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen presented a receipt of Trump’s criminality — a signed August 2017 check indicating Trump covered up illegal h… https://t.co/K8u9P0Fcab]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re more  upset about Ilhan Omar’s “anti-Semitic” comments then Trump’s “there’s good people on both sides,”… https://t.co/LbEbXIDt99]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gusmaran Sim, especialmente gás. Aqui por total consumption: https://t.co/uVgX5VoMcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright seriously tho ima need some props for going to my 9am, 3 hour long communications class after always going out the night before.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump lol this sums up this trip!!!😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/cdD60m9khT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best buck! Illinois bowkill in 2017! @ Pearl, Mississippi https://t.co/Jzf5WnmR6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BGECO1 @LONGLIVE_OCT @pistolpete_99 @McKelveyMitch @davielleeee @Hzrris You can’t pull receipts out on em like tha… https://t.co/uJCDBhMGJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 "One who is faithful in a very little is also faithful in much, and one who is dishonest in a very little is als… https://t.co/moTzEsHF16]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate the mentality that “carbs are bad.” Or “fat is bad.” I’m no pro bodybuilder or dietician but good lord your… https://t.co/inx3Q2Zs54]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good win tonight. Let’s hope it’s the start of a late run. Keep it up. 👌🏽💜💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBerman Everyone should run, and then voters should pick who they like best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you really listen to him screaming at his CPAC rally he's trying to cover up for asking wikileak and Russia for… https://t.co/X8NGiCcURZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Torres 1 Major difference though: LSU is protecting football so the NCAA isn’t snooping around...KU doesn’t have that issue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GPSProtects Thanks, Nathan. Appreciate it. I know it's not your fault.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sirdeuce_ Idk man, I bought then bright bomber and bright gunner yesterday, wasn’t as happy as I thought I’d be. B… https://t.co/DNTs0IGXQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaredDudley619 You need to be getting ready for that front office job in DC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScandiBound @MuslimIQ Me too! Check out @UppityWilliamP’s Tweet: https://t.co/VsgMCrRjQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a phenomenal time at @socialsportsnwk #SSIAConference2019 with my @kickball365 team! It was great seeing so m… https://t.co/aO8GuKXXgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best fetch dog the farm ever had. Say hi to Duke, Porter, Lacey, Ziggy, and Jessy. RIP Gunnar. https://t.co/jEblxwX4ns]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradley Cooper and GaGa just stripped each other and did some 50 shades with this look 👀 #Oscar2019 https://t.co/sQqzKYnMGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[SNC LAVALIN. Ils ont compris le message! L'action en hausse de 6% 36,95CAD2,19 (6,30 %) 25 févr. 16 h 00 HNE  Le go… https://t.co/twi6YxHoNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have absolutely no problem with Iceman or Colossus being gay or Johnny Storm being black for Batwoman being gay,… https://t.co/Wid3VZHG5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BubblesVampire As much as I enjoy the cheese talk I can’t have any. I’m allergic to cows milk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[However, nothing’s funny about the allegations. You made me click the story, though. You win!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LazyMeatball @TeedIsMe Why isn't someone doing something about this what the f*** is going on in this country Cavi… https://t.co/ltIF0ZxF0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s Go Time” #streaming spotify @applemusic and err where now... listen to my story... #itsgotime 🚥🔥 #kingp 🤩🗣… https://t.co/Zj2RbISmhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apoetsmuse Oh no please do not hurt the queen! I got you @BrattyCupcakes !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just paid $1,850 for a new clutch for a 25 year old car in case any of y’all are looking for a financial advisor]]></document><document><![CDATA[With over 3,000 #free #SeedPackets on the #PublicExchangeTables, the #FamilyFriendly 2019 #CentralVASeedExchange:… https://t.co/5H2rYSbO30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an An American In Belgium by @HeistBrewery at @HeistBrewery — https://t.co/9Y2JhWzVL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arindube @ModeledBehavior Sure, fiscal policy too!   I’m just saying you don’t necessarily need a “job guarantee p… https://t.co/Ob5QRTVzLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏳️‍🌈 #LoveIsLove 🏳️‍🌈 (From @CapitalPrideDC 2015) 📸 Me 🙂 https://t.co/VN4d6Ztysg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rcg999 U can run those plays out of numerous formations. I always had a blast with the Wing T]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little bro playing games is funny😂.   He sat in this chair an started playing games an before the game started h… https://t.co/ybmpqR99ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vid and I just watched Apollo 11 in  I Max. I am always humbled by those brave young men and extremely proud to hav… https://t.co/Zv7KNBGxhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[More preview of what’s to come. #workinprogress #drawing #dnd @ Anaheim, California https://t.co/7SGxQTVZu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a reminder: it’s Cole world and we only are allowed to exist in it]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/qF8Ac8jdwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ItsMondayBaby!!!! Attack the day, attack your week. Let's get it. God bless #lscsports #lewissalgadoconsultants… https://t.co/TV3oOOsy1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Skonie Skoop   Luke Perry Dead at Age 52 Following Massive Stroke https://t.co/nTIb7aXJIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[South Elgin gets a transition basket and a dunk off a lob to take a commanding 41-25 lead over Harlem  with 6:49 left in 4th]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s Tea:  )         )        )     )     (         )       )      ) _(___(____)____(___(__ (__ \  i’m not getti… https://t.co/VINuBGHcrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spedwybabs @GregTBasta Can’t get it to play, but glad the Yankees didn’t overpay for Machado...think ARod.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Top Performance Automotive, Inc.. Voice your choice for the Best of Clark County 2019! https://t.co/3EZqgTNTGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trish_regan Hoping you can provide your perspective on the growing #WalkAway movement mobilizing #Latinos,… https://t.co/oSOYORZ0JS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenSPLATT @BeanieFeldstein @Noahegalvin @mollyjgordon Ok. Gonna check it out. I like all three of them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flashing back to yesterday’s sun because it’s going to rain for the next few days and my instagram has devolved int… https://t.co/gOddCiHNHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DPiper247 @JWerner247 If he gets a switch then he should drag him to block. It forces the defense to choose, and t… https://t.co/cOlixguRg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SssParody Lordy, I looked... Well clearly that Bra and panties set is not supportive enough. I may never by paper napkins again.. 😳🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsLaurel @GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Not sure you do.  Because your last few Tweets make no sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great catching up today with @RonEdmondson ! I owe this friendship to @CaseyGraham who introduced us on a Leadershi… https://t.co/rZDgL0qoN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chadtronic I'm not sure what is going on but it's very much not fair to you or the work you've done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to unleash your power just pickup #anthemgame for #xboxone at #gamestop it is awesome game you get chosen for… https://t.co/djrShF4ncP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyn_cade @doctor_eon @marcushjohnson Yup. And the large field thing is key, because he can't just "but Hillary" his way out of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raider_35_24 @AdamMKaufman @C_M_314 @kevinarnovitz @CelticsCLNS @CLNSMedia @EvanValenti @CLNS_Walsh @CLNS_Sean… https://t.co/Y83cpghLw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es como robar esta vara... #amazongo @ Amazon Go https://t.co/TU7jTe5xoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxKriegerVG In fairness, I try hard to pad executive pockets a bit less when I'm buying a game where I know the e… https://t.co/aO49gTcJYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dios es bueno!!! #NoPuedesJugarBoxeo @ YouTube Space LA https://t.co/rMAox9gUQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Yup . They just cut their heads off and then the arms and then the legs . Isn't that what they do ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope the Heat use a Justise-Josh-DJJ-Kelly-Bam lineup for a good stretch in the 2nd half]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ It appears that iOS 13.0 will have that option--though it might be limited to the X, XS, XS Max and 2019 model… https://t.co/0Ls8D1vC9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect moment, perfect pup #RoughCollie #DogsOfInstagram @ Turner Reservoir Loop Trail https://t.co/QnXPs80mGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halftime — Wayne 34, Sissonville 22.  Lady Indians have done most of the scoring from the FT line, they’re 11-of-12. #wvgirlsbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I realize now that my failure to develop a successful career in journalism can be traced to my lanyard allergy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it was when he said that straight members of the military are scared of and uncomfortable with fighting along… https://t.co/ILDkA0bBRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC "We don't parade 'them' around"?  What kind of racist crap is that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atomic_elbow @Frankiemon Having just listened to this, I was thinking about those exact horns, and scratching head… https://t.co/KsyAjttHYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first step to achieving your goals is to wake up. Sadly, yesterday people did not wake up, and they will not be… https://t.co/fG3pf9iwmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snaps from the hill. #hollywoodhills #hollywoodsign #hikeLA #mikehike @ Hollywood Sign https://t.co/3aUrk0gZJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theriddler704 @Jontaviusb34 @bobbyhuggz @StephanieG5615 @404girl @AdamMRagab https://t.co/62nVtlx8Up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mootrain00 @GregDiVilbiss @JayhawkSlant K-State has 2 conference titles, KU has 17. KU also has 3 national titles.… https://t.co/YPpqWr4wH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1965vmjw @ADDiane Especially when the clocks are melting.  A Dali-kinda Friday happening over here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Episode 4 of The Second Choice podcast was good fun. Will have to have @WayOfTheQuay on again sometime, we'll defin… https://t.co/tvrgLnxlU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunnyside has one of best boys soccer teams in nation yet must travel to Phoenix to play for the 5A state title tom… https://t.co/HsGO0UseiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP to @ZionW32 signing with @nikebasketball in the league 👀😅 hope the dude is good to go. Too exciting to watch! https://t.co/35m9ApOLHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since hitting 22 trillion on Feb 12, we've added 100 billion in just 19 days. We are on track to be 23 trillion in… https://t.co/YFtNH9l71u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McknightmdEllen @misterchambo I just want to say the one of the most controlling, focus on finance, all costs for… https://t.co/RETllu6FFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not answering no phone calls today or shit. I’m so tired I don’t even feel like talking 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecrankyadmin @Lost_Signal @DeepStorageNet I currently own 3 cars. All of them are red. And I’m thinking about ge… https://t.co/bSNVDZm0Z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kucherov, Vasilevskiy lead Lightning clinic against Blue Jackets https://t.co/kC1WuEDPyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music, movies, drama, poetry and comedy for Valentine’s Day - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/OpLOJZBXGY 💭🔁♥️ @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Alex!  And #PDX peeps,’follow @BlairStenvick. Blair this is a really important article and thank you for you… https://t.co/D6xrmNe0om]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NyXio Pero ajá, les cobran. Hay muchos de esos que supongo pasaron sin medio en el bolsillo porque fueron fue al concierto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankZande @washingtonpost I read storing this energy is a challenge at best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maddygram @donald_j_putin @Mar_a_Hell_No @mog7546 If it True I'll will be in the World of Shit !!! Back to the Future !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Springbreak i think i would like another tattoo.... i have 2 options lol might get both!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders To bad govt got involved cause the need for insurance and then the need for more govt shut up commie]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s the kind of writing I expect from Law and Order,not my president]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Passengershelp That’s a lie because he never takes off from work like i did for the past 2 months and i don’t even… https://t.co/QWzKh9zvtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealkwat 4 sport athlete but I train football year round.  https://t.co/n9Y4GMELvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hm. The first 2 mins on self driving is actually interesting. Just simply putting a solid line in the middle of lan… https://t.co/anqCZhcDD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet @Sunstruk Wait a minute.  Did the story just change?   He said a MAGA hat . A plain red hat is not a… https://t.co/1KuBMfLx14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4thnGoldPodcast I definitely want him for the 49ers! Dude would blow up in Shanny’s offense!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamAyoJuann   Juan my first day at my new job was 👍. https://t.co/KPLunSRMCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sjurcak @JimLaPorta Knowing what troops are doing on Liberty is a good thing. Keeps all parties engaged regarding… https://t.co/D7eWu6TraF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi, my favorite country queen performing a cover of my favorite song from THE QUEEN? I’m not crying, you are.]]></document></documents></author>