<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Not the nicest weather for it, but it was still great to be at the @AlbanyRural for a ceremony honoring the Irish B… https://t.co/NVBbEn0h6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[on a roadtrip now and I have to say — the swag from @aneventapart is definitely some of the most useful I’ve ever gotten #aeasea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaABC7 Good Morning Jessica..  I'm looking forward of going to the bookstore today.  Hope that you have a great day.🌺☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philmyers06 congratulations!!  so very happy for you and Mom and Dad must be so proud!!♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think its a game? 😂 Nah‼️ Full court pressure 💪🏾 all year because I’m #InMyAct ✈️🌍 #YungMartez and the 🐐… https://t.co/crrBFpsxV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gave a legislative update this morning to a packed room at the @HanoverDemocrat monthly meeting. https://t.co/9jqk2qwFYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wsbtv Good Morning! Nice! 😃 I love the photo! That was a very nice tribute to Karen this morning from her colleagu… https://t.co/zwY8Jd9R2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idriselba Why don't you have promos for your debut as host of SNL on your feed? The one with you and Aidy drinking… https://t.co/5q2tdy9rdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeeyaLeah People who make stupid trash plays, penguins or not, shouldn’t be on the ice. Trying to prevent concussions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspired and Engaged by @luannrjones and her commitment to education for #NICU #Nurses through the newest… https://t.co/LU7CsjgRni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doctoralexa I always do think thru issues Doc. I dont hate or dislike people because they belong to a different po… https://t.co/sBP1Ht7Wgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Rebecca said “I can’t be here right now. I can’t be anywhere right now,” it triggered something in my #widow b… https://t.co/5RN3v8M660]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicked 5 am cardio day’s ass. #maxofwayne @ The MAX Challenge of Wayne https://t.co/B8dSQIj6jQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicaPerrone Concordo com você, melhor dizer logo a que veio,é de esquerda compactua e aprova,se te serve veste! Pa… https://t.co/uBHTPlxT6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mamma Mia! 4 days to curtain (March 14-15-16) and you DO NOT want to miss it! Tickets at the door for $8 BUT get th… https://t.co/emonTmFqgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[nobody talk to me all day and I mean it I’ll make it the worst day of ur life]]></document><document><![CDATA[of the US government as part of the Prevezon money-laundering investigation.  In Manhattan, Leviev’s firm also sold… https://t.co/vLDBUfGXFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[youtubers literally regurgitate the same colors plus one “unique bright color”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnrobertsFox @SaraCarterDC @WhiteHouse You poor things. The press crying and whining doesn’t impress us. Most of you deserve worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve come to realize that people who over use the dog filter are the ones with weird noses 👃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Tell me Harrison how is paying government a tax on climate change gonna do anything they just stea… https://t.co/A1XY8mEsw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vance Miller III a senior @LSHSRangers is USPA Interscholastic Polo Central Region Champion and competes at Nationa… https://t.co/O2xAkB6RHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josh_colvin Noooooooo-cheer for St. Cloud State tonight as we are playing UMD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just sang in front of people for the first time in months, like actually sang, sober, musical theatre style, in f… https://t.co/bK2JBqdU8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonoraLori @fras99 @kathid_d Everyday about all things large and small.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe only two more home games! Psyched to see these cardiac kids! #BootUp! Geaux Tigers 🐅! @ Pete Maravich… https://t.co/9HqgSi1As7]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys, I finally met my imaginary “husband” and it was magic. 😂🤣🥰 #bsbVegas #bsb #fangirling… https://t.co/kKNIqqrvzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @ResCSS #ILP students had a great initial visit with our clients @stnkspirit to discuss the Apps they want deve… https://t.co/JSelUeRL9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al Roker picks at Dillon Dryer. He treats her like she is stupid. He constantly challenges her comments. Rude. @NBCNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[These people are trying to remove the history of our country. It's ridiculous. Syria on their terms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC It’s amusing that Trump takes umbrage at Spike reading off notes. Trump’s delivery off of a teleprompter is… https://t.co/eTombj5UQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaanSamantha I went to India on a 3 week vacation and drank coconut water from like 6 cities and 3 states. Harmles… https://t.co/fCPI4hGIu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[And thank you @DeanDeBlois and the entire cast and crew for bringing these characters to life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’ve been conscripted by our polling department to let you know that polling is not dead.” — @washingtonpost’s @myhlee at #NICAR19]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Okay Infiniti you can deal you ducking bitch “ ..”she prob has to pee like me but she’s cool “]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oscarlararocha1 Bien oscar gracias bien feliz y mañana mas y tu lindo dia viernes saludos amigo👍🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also this. via @TrudyGoodman   A single evening of @Wisdom2conf has my cup overflowing. https://t.co/9z6hQ2UxtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really really really just wanna go to sleep for like a year and wake up and not remember shit honestly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Spring break is next week I need to eat healthier Cook at my work: Do you want this entire tub of pepper jack m… https://t.co/E7ehv86KVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I challenge the use of ”polling as the frontrunner.” According to what poll, against what other candidates? He's a… https://t.co/Qal0qgL5EC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay I watched #TheBachelor twice this season and suddenly they have me committing until the end because I want to… https://t.co/8FlOE6OqKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csmonitor Abraham Lincoln delivers second inaugural address, tomorrow 1865 ("With malice toward none, with charity… https://t.co/sKhBw8qiB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have so many herbs around the farm house and each one is my favorite.  Especially rosemary!  The blooming is som… https://t.co/AR34mOlbxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[they didnt show sam rockwell eating chicken wings this is the Real vice SNUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaron_m_lambert @AlisaLittle14 @TiffanyMidge @PKhakpour @maggiehendricks @NatalieGDiaz @SarahSpain @adalimon… https://t.co/CC5P17gpWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Putneyman That's lovely Dave! We're warming from a chilly start, now 48-F and Sunny at 8 AM. 🌞😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias, @norydelano, aliada clave también en esta lucha por los derechos de las personas con discapacidad en la Re… https://t.co/QCTtn9wzoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying it gets approved and available in less than 10 years. I have stage 4 osteosarcoma. #osteosarcoma… https://t.co/rVPKCa24mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a What You Want by @HysteriaBrewery at @HysteriaBrewery — https://t.co/bUIQ4dB6PS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopeDave8 @MYSTIC7 @Jak3Marti3ny Aweeee, miss a good “in &amp; Out” burger...we doing local Chinese fav]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quinncy I’d be down with this if it was a vintage dress previously worn by her mother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to reschedule my doctors appointment.... the earliest they had was March 27 🙃 okie I’ll wait another month 😂 th… https://t.co/0IwDHn9AHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscar's night for Two!! #oscars #oscars2019 #cheese #champagne #adorbs 🥂🍾🧀🧀 @ Lou &amp; Camilo's Home https://t.co/eqwDnts1Kg]]></document><document><![CDATA[So yeah. Join.  GISH Project STFU: Save The Forest Unicorns https://t.co/Rx46J4uCnS via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emtheswiftie @bigrep_22 Idk....for me, Speak Now has been unrivaled for 9 years. It’ll take a lot to knock it out of that top spot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking pictures of the “cattle” 😮 (@ Pioneer Plaza in Dallas, TX) https://t.co/HMI0CSRW0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum I honesty never saw this until Trump became president. People's nostalgia over a life that brought so mu… https://t.co/nautdnSH7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it out of the convention and am back in cell service! What did I miss today??]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OTD in #NYCHistory in 1872 the #MetropolitanMuseumofArt opened. #TheMet was first located in a brownstone at 681 F… https://t.co/068qNR1sSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extremely honored to be in the company of these amazing champions for diversity and inclusion! Love doing this work… https://t.co/NHuyN9l8R3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just successfully parallel parked (with lots of coaching) after only two attempts https://t.co/ors9SAmmCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bootcampworkout #6am and #7am #tomorrow @NoLimitsSports Come #letsgoworkout @ No Limits Sports and Fitness Academy https://t.co/bmLWcnpL4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for all of my friends to get married so that I can reenact 27 dresses (even tho I don’t have that many friends)]]></document><document><![CDATA[If ur not here yet, ur gonna want to run on over to hear @saronyitbarek’s talk, I could listen to her all day, gr8… https://t.co/2mJRmaLBIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[La relación con los hermanos es tan extraña, soy capaz de darle un riñón pero ni loca mis audífonos 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alisiana said she didn’t want to do anything extravagant for her birthday and then proceeds to say that all she wan… https://t.co/wlFXFgUGJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get you a roommate like @molly_fuller08 who yells “THATS MY ROOMMATE” during bows 😂❤️😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Happy 19th Birthday to one of my besties! I wouldn’t trade our many adventures or time spent binge watching I… https://t.co/JTMH0VhNMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever since the news got that snow wrong Morgan county isn’t letting out for nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s that time again 😁😁😁  . . . . . #photoofthemoment #photogram #picofthemoment #picoftheday #photooftheday… https://t.co/53JMbiTNph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisSprowls @Barney_Bishop Ok realized that appeared I was saying you looked a dinosaur 😂 I meant this: https://t.co/a6FjVs8nGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We literally have the same problem. I think the common theme is bad orthodontics/ists. Mine looked like Val Kilmers… https://t.co/ryBmgdLPUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[biggest art review of college is tomorrow and im more unprepared than I've ever been https://t.co/4ypG0Aam7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maxime Bernier on Justin Trudeau (Pt. 2) https://t.co/xifxu0JPLW via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dude thinks poor people deserve to die if they can’t afford health care but I guarantee he’s anti-abortion. No… https://t.co/aeWbdg2k5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about how iKon and Chungha are gonna be in Austin and I won’t be able to see them 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like it’s supper weird that I have my nose pierced but I refuse to get my ears pierced]]></document><document><![CDATA[No meu lugar favorito com a minha nova mochila fofa!l personalizada! 🎡 In my favorite place with my new cute custom… https://t.co/m4zb6b4xi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve eaten healthy all week except for Panera. And today I decide to get hot Funyuns and a monster. Not healthy but… https://t.co/g7RIgaSDnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enséñame a hacer tu voluntad, porque tú eres mi Dios; tu buen espíritu me guíe a tierra de rectitud. Salmos 143:10]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night in Toronto was so special. I loved every minute. Thank you to everyone who sold out the show at… https://t.co/nDzApE89Dh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jade78052492 Running errands ❤️🌪 I gave blood this morning for the tornado victims ‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was just up making coffee about to start studying for my exam at 9 when i heard the news. i then began to squeal… https://t.co/FUZMQ2GlsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loyalty and Respect shouldn’t be upgrades in a relationship it should be a requirement 🗣🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[_ғᴀᴠ ᴛʙ ᴘʀᴠ ᴅᴀɴᴄᴇʀ 💰 dramateurope @ Seductive Situations https://t.co/PN1Y4Hx9Rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dragonfly194 @leeleeb50 Verifiably need 2b committed kind of insane  Not nice, good crazy but stay the hell away scary kind of crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @JNOG23 to post covers of seven books I love no explanation —just a cover for a we… https://t.co/kFoxtpRF2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresh off the sewing Machine right on time to celebrate With Ghana Happy Independence day Ghana  #africanfabrics… https://t.co/nSF21niSwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pneumajustice @KevinGFox I know this is not gonna be liked,I agree it’s a weird tweet, but I’m not equating “act”… https://t.co/k0ireVqG5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 18th birthday, Juanito. 💕 You are someone I greatly respect, tremendously love, and hopelessly adore. Thank y… https://t.co/u84DlgtaIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we’re stuck with lousy #cell reception and #WiFi at North today ~ #FirstWorldProblems @armasylvia… https://t.co/DJR3f4ON1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristaG3 @GoBowlingdotcom @FS1 @PBATour Yikes, you win it is cold there! Enjoy the show!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That Senate wouldn’t even take up a bid on Obama’s Supreme Court nominee. So I don’t believe Trump… https://t.co/ORuoSjHCV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[my tik tok account was taken down bc god knew that i would be too powerful with my smarts, looks, AND comedic page… https://t.co/8fkNsKYKJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[teen derp posts | Teen Derp | RedVooz - The World of Technolgy and Fun https://t.co/oAOnVhSSVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what’s missing from my life. BRB Googling where to buy a piglet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @realDonaldTrump Not just out on the street. On Trial for Treason!]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are filming bad boys right by where I workout, you think I can be become famous and leave u hoes in the dust ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard that @kody_roberson might get his phone tonight and I’m being really impatient. I’M SO READY😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1adultentertainerinNJ. Lady Di Dancers 908.686.2037 Now booking parties @ Kenilworth, New Jersey https://t.co/bnugAuJuyi]]></document></documents></author>