<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What's worse than throwing up? Feeling like you're about to throw up for three hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala Harris panders to the Black community by passing federal laws on their behalf. The Beta Bitch can’t receive… https://t.co/WypzSCGK2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marksilvermanmd @Twitter Everyone should tell someone they love them everyday ♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Little Me,  Never lose your smile. Never be afraid to move on. Never let anyone make you believe you are stuck… https://t.co/2iq07CALOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im supporting @FutureFounders! Help them empower young adults to grow their ventures! Vote now to help… https://t.co/rjnkoB7mLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Spark is not really 10, but when does one need to start counting? Its popularity is growing. Quick speculations at… https://t.co/BkeQSc95tF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamieseh . Proud of this Cuda Alum! One of central Florida's finest young men!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I want to do: sleep on the balcony. Things that are too cold to do: sleep on the balcony.  Do you see the problem?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely need din tai fung or sun du bu tomorrow. One of y'all needa take me for a birthday meal, thanks in advance🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get a good picture with my dog in the snow like... @ Cedar Rapids, Iowa https://t.co/cepaQDj4sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week is already starting off bad. 1. The government took an hour away from me. 2. My car is STILL DIRTY 3. I f… https://t.co/XRLT7jGm51]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m a little lit or whatevaaa… but just recalled that 2 days ago @sabastian_wolfy called me ugly. Honey boo boo’… https://t.co/I52JJoGkzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will in be in NYC for a few days in May for my brothers graduation... I’ve been trying to plan stuff for us to d… https://t.co/cNF4YGDPZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen It’s unbelievable that everything with republicans is race!! Pathetic little racist SOB’s!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I adopted  a beagle who was going to be euthanized by UC Davis. He was the light of our lives for 12 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelGotti5 No shocker here~!!   10-4. . . Lol.. have a ‘good~one’ 🙋🏼‍♀️💞🙋🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outdoor Club will be snowshoeing tomorrow after school. Meet in the commons at 2!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One year after a school shooting that shook the nation, here is a look back at the lives lost in the Parkland, Flor… https://t.co/PSj0iiTWj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ripro63 @Nabil_djellit Ah bon? Donc toi tu es un expert et moi un clown?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You might not like how you look but at least you didn’t grow into a full ass adult that’s going to be stuck in the… https://t.co/LMoMMmACIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockyTopSkiBum @MariahRockNC9 Oh @RockyTopSkiBum, my friend, it’s not mayo I despise. It’s Mariah’s taste in food… https://t.co/tMoGjq3Pow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya' think? NBA commissioner Adam Silver says 'a lot of players are unhappy'  https://t.co/FVbbRhrnCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@budsytalkto @miss9afi @TarekFatah @OmarAlghabra Omar was part of a delegation in 2005 who went to Queens Park to h… https://t.co/gxUoKmrhUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[They have phone books here. 😮 @ Breckenridge, Colorado https://t.co/EWh3WkbJBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank god #InternationalWomansDay is finally over and WE CAN ALL MOVE ON WITH OUR LIVES. https://t.co/W106s8a5xS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOEtheMORTON @GodFriendedMe Great episode!  It had me on the edge of my seat as I was in DISBELIEF that Cara and M… https://t.co/cEBPcZZXQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Stand strong Mr. President!!!  We BELIEVE GOD IS REVEALING ALL THE DEMS ARE DOING!  2020 is coming!! We WB VOTING FOR YOU!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[this branch is seriously in need of help. (at @DunkinDonuts in Somerville, NJ) https://t.co/LLTQsqbuI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump So, are you comparing trump to Caesar?   Of course trump is being a tyrannical dic… https://t.co/TuDp2Cgu1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angrysatan6661 Oh yeah, I couldn’t sleep so I feel like the undead today]]></document><document><![CDATA[They wouldn’t be staring down mass extinction and extreme weather, for starters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is fact especially if the manipulator is smart enough to do their homework on the woman (old or young) their t… https://t.co/u3FA7uoAEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think if one person gave me  a quarter it would make me happy. Sucks I feel non existent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a Capricorn and that’s why I don’t want you to be emotionally detached]]></document><document><![CDATA[~ #Genderreveal 💗💙  ❥One little nose, boy or girl. Nobody knows! Till the end boy oh boy...it’s a BOY! Congrats to… https://t.co/EPcESVvlwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[During Mike and my exploration around Willow Springs Loop at Red Rock Conservation area, we came across these authe… https://t.co/AA0mOQkSrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep inspiring your a #Queen a survivor I admire people who keep it real @lamiceofficial @iamicequeen504 keep Shini… https://t.co/D2ELvTXMUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que triste que la gente sea tan infeliz cómo para andar tirando veneno y queriendo afectar a los demás a lo tonto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time trying out this rolled up ice cream and it was really good 🍨💙 https://t.co/vyPMZB1Y29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeEnglish16 @ShannaNBCLA @DaniellaNBCLA Thanks, #sweettweet so busy and dangerous driving out there! Please be safe, #HappyValentinesDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoralNecessity @JulieReichwein1 People are people no matter their political affiliation. If you an ass your an ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TriBDojel @HSIGlobal How deceived I was, to believe my perceptions were true reality, and not mad illusions I comp… https://t.co/0iiW4wPK6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimDuffy I have 3 towels and honestly I usually just wash the one I'm using and put it right back on the hook 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know your @PeiWei obsession is real when you have to go get an inmate from Texas but you’re trying to find a ro… https://t.co/JMGbNhs3Ks]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the fireball falls out of the freezer you just say what the hell and finish it off! #sundayfunday @ Borelli Ho… https://t.co/v3eL3YnGIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok back to Jerrod 😭........ It does thangs to me! https://t.co/axTruiRjwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethMalicki Wait until she discovers twitter!   #momloveisthebestlove.   FYI you’re awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PezzDeLaGroove The zero deaths from it occurring natural are most likely to due to herd immunity though. Because p… https://t.co/Ul6l9Cuof9]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4: I have to say... the Old Fashioned! I’m drinking one now. 😂 #PantryChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieKrawiec Headed to Gainesville next week for some 80 degree weather 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[The truth from Katt Williams #funniness #tee-hee #smirk #absurd https://t.co/oWgJuzsebp]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Dominator Of The Flesh by One Man Army &amp; The Undead Quartet on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/DpxoWKneds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Why sir i do believe I never have done s o. Lol send Stone to PRISION now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sprintcare I've been with Sprint since 2000. I have unlimited service but still pay over $100 for 1 line. I am pla… https://t.co/mKK9znCXb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel so lost. It hurts to say I have to leave, To find my Way. To God I say, “My soul to Keep. Just say a peep, A… https://t.co/nQsVyOyxwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of Pisces’s season: I can’t even sit down in front of my planner and get my life straightened out. I’m just t… https://t.co/vbUgsauQqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bro2bizee @notcapnamerica @ReginaA1981 Actually I want a Democrat to lead us. But thanks for speaking for people y… https://t.co/w3qc0ouKiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikajayne Check my REAL QUESTION B4...I DON'T  even look at the troll shit...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samstein @Lawrence @whignewtons @maxwelltani ok, then what's the point? because it's not one of those no-show jobs… https://t.co/FaMl3tFmDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[remember when christofer drew made bryan stars cry? what an iconic day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayawiley @NicolleDWallace @FrankFigliuzzi1 @JoyceWhiteVance @matthewamiller I have a reminder on my phone for a 4… https://t.co/P13EYPkJok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyScrivens So they finally get some rain and then have to expend energy running away from you. Great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Bill was dying, I asked him if he was afraid and he said, 'I don't want to die' and I cried. "They seemed, in… https://t.co/rbRi3HDofL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the 85 degree day here in #PortCharlotteFl 😎🌴🌴 https://t.co/1FV2ZpVRWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodreads “Steve texts and asks if I want to meet him somewhere for a drink.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karennn_itzel You are not!!! Look for the boy who isn’t obsessed with himself and what others think of him. Not self absorbed douchebags]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barry Jenkins, director of the #Oscars⁠ ⁠-nominated film "If Beale Street Could Talk," shared a sweet story about t… https://t.co/NYmbyGxYuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg for the last month I been refraining myself from booking a flight to Canada bc I’m scared to go by myself.. I’m… https://t.co/W7U5pbzHn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ptbolabour Happy to contribute, and to spend time with the fem-nomenal organizations that raise awareness, and don… https://t.co/zvmwZG7MFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeltingInMarana @Littlleome @Godsgirl158 @American2b @goofballgeorge @rosered2020 @GeanineC @MAGAELITES… https://t.co/TjU9Tp5AQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k8tidid I leave We’d morn. Staying on the Navajo Reservation in a hogan. Super excited! https://t.co/WZ4f9Ea9Vm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaloney Wonder if NY will be dumb enough to vote for her again??? Probably!!!! You can't fix STUPID.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics @BuffyLWillow I can’t wait to tell my host body ‘ Happy Host Body Day’ this year 💐]]></document><document><![CDATA[deleted oomfs number today and i’m kinda sad 😢 I’ve never had to do that before]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadlineWH @ZerlinaMaxwell @NicolleDWallace @senatemajldr is responsible for all of this. He could have stopped it… https://t.co/djiiTyEJu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShackTS why is Boucher untouchable? I don’t dislike him but with the Sens record any other coach would likely be fired]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewPerry I've always liked you.  I'm glad you are part of this world.  I wish you the best ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evening tunes time. 🎧🎶💙  Fell in love with @grovertheband at @SaufHausDC open mic night. Give him a listen! New mus… https://t.co/qY3pVtkthc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti @bjcreigh He's not apologetic he's a f****** liar all he's trying to do is get himself out of all the trouble he's made]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaBertrand Gee, aren't we democratic, home of the free? Manafort serves another 30 mo.--18 charges?...black,… https://t.co/vRu82SWZqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliciakrop @dalvarad ‘just a little snow. Buses are running, and school IS open’ 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Folks have been wanting a detailed update on Anderson and we've got one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your #courage to stand for your #conviction is the character that #MAGA. It also the #red, white and blue in our ve… https://t.co/DXCwMkaXcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings Thank you sir for your wise words in your closing statement. I appreciate and I hope the rest of our n… https://t.co/ZKMxRAYvpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[2-RBI Double from @orlandoarcia9 outs the #Brewers on top of the Athletics 3-1 #CactusCrew #MILvsOAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camillestyles you should give away passes to your SXSW party to Austin fans! 🙋‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@f1morgancole @NaturesTemper Love his voice and tone. I was listening to him today at work and was just thinking of… https://t.co/fFwUcCiuoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@livs_thoughts This video is the reason why I don’t show reaction to things anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another picture from the Portrait Gallery. Katherine Hepburn. #vacation https://t.co/B2bn6KcIGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you read a novel and it’s so good you listen to the audiobook. And then you listen to it again. And again… https://t.co/4hkjlf18nc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travvie_Dearest The man has stage three colon cancer he’s lucky to be alive I get so angry with this lemme stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked @vgcerf, if you tried today, in today’s environment and with today’s @DARPA and DoD, to accomplish what you… https://t.co/JSUTCFu4S4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating all the #LGBTQ South Florida love at @PrideFortLaud - @WLRN reports Pride Fort Lauderdale wraps up “Car… https://t.co/rd0ezPOnih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FairyQ15 @CajunChick25 Haven’t you heard? Muslims are above the laws outside of Islam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizWill99 The media took down Hillary and gave us Trump, now you are believing them again?  I thought you were wiser than that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Thank God for Obama. Who would Trump have to blame for everything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LJWriter @CoastalDeb @ButterflyWrite @WritingReader @BettyBolte @msavagebooks @SCoryellAuthor @PatrickHempfing A d… https://t.co/Jt0kQeUXBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of our favorite Difference Makers with our favorite 6th grade band! ❤️ #WeAreMedina #GoBees @MedinaBeesPAC… https://t.co/aAH9rFdtbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna hang out with @cthagod he kills me on the breakfast club, love y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dad was sick this week. Don't know what happened. He got up feeling good and by noon he was shaking pretty bad. He… https://t.co/3r1FElxjYz]]></document></documents></author>