<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano   This morning’s iPhone shot of the snowy mountains with low-lying clouds, taken from my deck in Ana… https://t.co/ZLNRxYNvzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[El q va a mi casa y abre la nevera sin preguntar le mocho un brazo @jochysantos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The last thing you ever do is “save words.” You usually repeat easy words over and over as if that… https://t.co/g7luWGVcmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really depressing to know that you’ll more than likely die alone without ever having a real committed relationship 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monterey County has the largest # of homeless students in the Bay Area Coastal Region! We look fwd to working w the… https://t.co/1hqUPgHt2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwainEvent @benmckee14 Btw, there is a court case that bears directly on this issue.  Ioata Xi vs George Mason University (4th Cir. 1993)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks FUNNY YOU SAID THAT!sounds just like dems.  No ideas and no time to actually work]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @FoxNews who is the congresswoman asking question right now and what party is she please]]></document><document><![CDATA[The shit is fucking medicine and legal in a lot of states , don’t be proud you really ain’t doing shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a dozen assorted @krispykreme doughnuts are brought into the office and you choose the cake/cruller variety, I w… https://t.co/VfYlA7cmZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interviewer: so why do you want this job?                                                               Me:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfHartley @ASPANational @ASPA_DSJ @aspaSPAE @ASPA_SICA @EubieBee @napawash @naspaa I’m personally looking forwar… https://t.co/suLTK6UeuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop surrounding yourself with “yes men”. Your camp should have people who challenge you. Make you think harder abo… https://t.co/8DksIhePFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fillmore Central (22-4) Starter  Jacquelyn Schelkopf Halle Theis Erin Schmidt Alexa Theis Macy Scott #kmasports #nepreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quin was watching Peppa Pig, but it had some sound effects that sounded weird so I asked him to see it. It’s called… https://t.co/BUzgTC0FSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for helping me reach 100 followers! I literally couldn’t have done it without you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boy🔥🔥 #6 #soccerseason @ Mt. Zion High School https://t.co/nD13ShdNqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Streaming on twitch every Friday night! Follow my twitch @og_jrich ! Would love for you all to watch! #fortnite… https://t.co/7N84gazXzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer It’s actually at your office.  Right next door to the anti-American club.  #schumerpelosishutdown]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHermosillo27 @Cruz_Azul_FC @joserra_espn @eduardotrelles @Javier_Alarcon_ A veces me pregunto ¿Por qué al Cruz Azul? No sé, la vida es asi]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really cost to be the boss today my off day and I’m already at my second store]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm beginning to sense a theme 👉👉 Ocasio-Cortez leaves parade in 17 mpg minivan — blocks from the subway: https://t.co/IIlyje9TPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeDragonXII There pretty cool sometimes they sell it through authentic auction]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @chrislhayes History recalls how great the fall can be . . .while everyone was sleeping, the boats put out to sea . . .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wertrz three ties it at 53, 7:10 left. Santa Clara finally had a look early in the shot clock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I suspect the 900 adults quizzed for this poll were all at Rest Homes for the Aged in W. Virginia? I totally… https://t.co/c6nogmjnuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish this was a dream....... I don’t want to believe it, I’m heartbroken 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder if they hired Jussie Smollett to give them acting sessions??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[The E! News cast are great people to work with. 😊 #Lovemyjob @ Universal Studios Hollywood https://t.co/50HZkjMbd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very proud of our Wildcats! @sshswildcats @SSISDWildcats https://t.co/V3VQWBxpo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldn’t be celebrating this. Winning during the only year that we need to lose is one of the most Knick things e… https://t.co/NwmbcCt1Sh]]></document><document><![CDATA[No soy fan de la etiquetas, pero por ella si me la pongo y me pongo las pilas 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattOswaltVA Won several wet t-shirts contests, once beating Maureen O'Hara....Held it against her for years!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennkirschner2 We watched this last weekend. Certainly worth everyone’s time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[La destrucción de las futuras generaciones, eso quieren implantar en mi México por presión de la @ONU_es ¿Y tú? ¿Es… https://t.co/6hJgisrMbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Relaxing on a short trip with my wife. Just realized that I will not watch #ElimantionChamber tonight but will probably watch it tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller _Your Vydas, My Vydas, Everybody’s Vydas, Arvydas Sabonis!!!!! #WhoAmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wasram @chitownbuster @DaTailGateShow #Lotalty #KeepinIt100 https://t.co/BBAXADl6vx]]></document><document><![CDATA[May God forgive Hitler for abusing you may God forgive Hitler for abusing you may God forgive Hitler for sexually a… https://t.co/bHtGo0RYXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finebaum Can you ask Jimmy from Chicago to break down Dred Scott vs Sanford, 60 US 393, and he has ever eaten brea… https://t.co/Dv6j7mHvUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on Chuck struggling like that...worse than Who He Play For? 😂😂 @NBAonTNT https://t.co/KV48jFK3lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_Fabiano Steelers get big time revenge.    This is very funny .  Living in Buffalo in the winter couldn't o… https://t.co/oMZz91C7EI]]></document><document><![CDATA[TGIF - "Let's jump into the Weekend" Nichelson Wedding (3/2/19) 📸 by:  @highlightupro timothyjwalkerjr… https://t.co/kDWSI00xc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[But God, being rich in mercy, because of the great love with which he loved us, even when we were …… https://t.co/Vb0ejyGYGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those asshat politicians and loudmouth community leaders have no idea what they did. This project was supposed to b… https://t.co/jb9zMntuTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great recap from the @IllinoisPCA. CHCs make such a great impact in the community and are a vital part of the healt… https://t.co/iPYDbmdp15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer Ok.  Some wacko with nuclear bombs is not, but the Wall is?  Very intelligent.  I think you should resi… https://t.co/1tp9kkpXr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Piano Slam 11 🎹 @DJCardi @ Adrienne Arsht Center for the Performing Arts https://t.co/WvZUbOWlTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extra innings!! Thanks to a $1,300 #FirstResponderNoShaveNovember donation from @NewportRIPolice this year’s fundra… https://t.co/ckznBvZyFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes when I'm alone  I Cry,  Cause I am on my own.  The tears I cry are bitter and warm.  They flow with life… https://t.co/QFioJqohEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone up? C'mon, it's 4:15 in the morning. Insomnia is far more common than this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reddit someone on your site gave out my PayPal info acting as me how do you investigate this. Now im scammed out of $300]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conflict is a reality in relationships. We can’t avoid them unless we avoid relationships. The climate in relations… https://t.co/F4j4IkIvIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelSlumpGod so ass at basketball. The guy with all the gear but no game #no🧢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @IvankaTrump #TrumpsWarOnEducation #TrumpsWarOnScience https://t.co/r1UL5mlaNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does daddy get the easy watch?  That's cause he is daddy and you don't know what that is... thought bubbles, ki… https://t.co/CAp3c9m0u9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qué pedo que mi feed de insta se está llenando de bebés y bodas y sus bebés en sus bodas? Usen condón amigos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frigidreadseri1 I snorted coffee at the sheer accuracy of this comment 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blackyngdave1 @khyatt2876 @bkg1477 @SweetlySmiles @LARRYIRBY6 @genericpanic @SusieQ99345590 @_dopedaneille… https://t.co/6VZa7pHcXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sanpiteriano @JackDeLaConcha @PalomaSenadora @AlvaroUribeVel @PalomaValenciaL @CeDemocratico Pero menos malo que U… https://t.co/mIzMRv74rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Milenio @PoliticaCero_ @jairocalixto Y según tu "experta" opinión de quién si es?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We could all use good morning make out sessions, breakfast in bed, and cuddle sessions before starting the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shooting woes haunt Escanaba in loss to Ludington https://t.co/KuL7PHmi3f via @theupbeatsports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dashboard – Get Your Tail on the Trail https://t.co/M2mp1REfJW  Still getting out there!  Sign up and keep moving!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Errors of #entrepreneurs flagged by @allonraiz are often attributable to delimited perspective. As @daven_md teache… https://t.co/kSgHQZpiUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hickory, Grove City heads up! #blamesixclasses @BobGreenburg @professorbriggs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dailybible_app Psalms 42:11 Why, my soul, are you downcast? Why so disturbed within me? Put your hope in God, for I https://t.co/1XcbkKaNFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoyoteDucks54 @Smittyville19 Yes- I had to say thank you for the Kuzy Jersey...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @indystar needs to come down on @HSESchools HARD. Fishers—the city, the school corp, the high school—has betray… https://t.co/tJ6owtow3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @YouTube. I've been watching on my TV and last couple of days the playback has been starting and stopping a lot… https://t.co/jebNPz45QH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sari- I see, you see more affordable housing C- if a building cost an eighth of what it did to build in coming year… https://t.co/vjIML8Cmng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherrynron @ImabitcSumtimes @CaliRN619 @JulieReichwein1 @sappermartin @SealeyGerald @andrewcbarnard @misspunk63… https://t.co/mEFOR3GDwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Is the number 1 myth that what @justicedems want is ACTUALLY socialism?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NirxMack @goddammitsarah @jchou321 @josswheelin @bennyb911 One quick item of official #bakerdaddies business:  Mot… https://t.co/zN3A8mallP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoriFuchigami @realDonaldTrump Trump is the least “fake” president we have had in our life time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lizzo KEEPS getting better  Cuz I Love You by Lizzo https://t.co/6h1o53Rlxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sullymygoodname @webberlax @haslametrics Write two letters a day. They can’t ignore you forever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @QualkTalk everything @BradOwens41 knows about meteorology, he learned from me and @cobbox while at @AndersonUnivSC  #GoTrojans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls Region 1-AAA Quarterfinals Dobyns-Bennett 56 Jefferson County 41 . @KCS__Athletics @dbcoach2000 @tnsportslive… https://t.co/YiS0a6tOQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also what a find #Valery has been! Our youth system is still top notch! #SaintsFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lynn Haven, FL. Suburb of Panama City that is working class n decent. Lots of local police living behind Wal-Mart a… https://t.co/zqJc2mdNLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The left wing lib dem slugs are running scared and fearful of the excellent job that President Trump is doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HandsomeConser1 @DiamondandSilk Conservative Media Dumb Ass Land failed to brainwash Americans into thinking they… https://t.co/pNGJZlCZZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking out a casino doubling up and walking away is probably the only growth im going to experience this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too much salt... i took most that shit off but my first margarita was 👌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[HUGE Krewe Win at Boca 29-27! Came down to the wire and a very hard fought game.#krewerugby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GriffinJack1 and 2 others have birthdays today. Send them good thoughts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrulyTrumpette @MiesW @debostic @nytimes @TwitterSafety It’s funny because it isn’t true, @williamlegate told him… https://t.co/sQiPjOjo86]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt Patty Smyth: 🎶Shootin’ at the walls of heartache… Patti Smith: 🎶Horses, horses🎶 Patty Smyth: 🎶I am the warrior…]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don’t know if the expression is ‘butt hurt’ about seeing someone else get a hero that looks like them, because t… https://t.co/2R38i0A7En]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am wearing blue jeans today to stand in solidarity for those who suffer from a rare disease. More info here… https://t.co/JBBioYoxoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[here's why i don't like this headline scientist: we're 99.9999% sure humans caused climate change pretty much anyon… https://t.co/fRc3uJpeAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeOJabbattes Know how ya can tell that ain’t #TheRealMJT?  I heard he retired from bartending!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattRJennings @danobrienwriter Thanks brother! Here’s the perfect song for you! https://t.co/MT4rBh9CM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[GSP calls Wayne Gretzky an inspiration, possibly the greatest athlete ever and a gentleman https://t.co/5rO1vwsQQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @MikeBloomberg Hillary... you're a real life MONSTER! https://t.co/wzHTN7VVov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of those moments when you are feeling it... (Leiko Napoli Photography) https://t.co/vOCE4SLjWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me listening to Richard Millie Plain 🔥🌊 @1GunnaGunna https://t.co/gSAknhxHbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsaiahFee_NFL @elevenbravo138 I'll take a new team. It's not a big deal. I don't know who is left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBlueUnited We tried to tell you this before last year but you were all Eli Eli Eli Eli. But the bridgewater ide… https://t.co/5eToDfkIsP]]></document></documents></author>