<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@flushednsticky @EuphoricEuler Simply heartbreaking.  Wish I had the words to comfort you.  Know you are in my hear… https://t.co/KdqriiYHvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS. THIS HAPPENED @disneylandtoday #disneylandafterdark https://t.co/skl55Z9R8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the scene of a bus crash on Toll 49. This is near Broadway avenue. The Toll road is closed in this area.… https://t.co/cdhDU2FWm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Why doesn't @ABC ask @AdamSchiff the hard questions? Why did Schiff meet with dirty dossier Fusion… https://t.co/L1450AIWIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MirellaBrzezins A co najważniejsze nie ma zgody (a nawet jest sprzeciw!)  Volodimira Putina!]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is @realDonaldTrump kinda man! Trump thinks he is a god and fantasies about doing the same things!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain you bring a lot of diversity to the table! You make amazing points that bring value to those watching… https://t.co/wFs4GUQqoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse So loved his 2hr speach-- it was like he was visiting with us all-  s… https://t.co/P0gAiCjsVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[How anyone can have any doubt that President Trump is guilty must have their head up their ass why do we have to wa… https://t.co/BYOP7w3gev]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharismaMolotov Thanks for this link! I still have my POW bracelet that I wore through high school. Right now my m… https://t.co/OnvkNzsU92]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saucyrockets @NHLNetwork I can watch NHL games that are on the network on the app. I don’t get world juniors either but eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beastcoaster91 Yes I know however  it has a way of coming back. And my cancer research hospital Moffett cancer cen… https://t.co/zNnjugIuxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hottestsingles @pamwishbow @stefantosheff Do a Scooby Doo team up issue. Everyone wants this but does not know it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I *never* used to fuck with a guy who told me he was poly. Sometimes you gotta trust your instinct and not get sway… https://t.co/Is92xB3Y0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I put this coffee table together by myself without any instructions. I am the master of flat-pack furniture. @ Staf… https://t.co/sIiuQWGMlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recovery Practice=Soccer Tennis #faithsoccer @ Grapevine Faith https://t.co/zrZ9VQbL2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the performers from the Breaking Ground Cabaret show recognized me, an audience memeber, because it “looked… https://t.co/4O3uFiG3jc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyC35827304 @dbechek1 @casinog71 @Lelein2010 Great movie!! https://t.co/yx34qdIZrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tipo assim né se eu pudesse escolher escolheria a caroline c o Klaus massss né]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good news I just obtained a divorce lawyer so if anyone would like to marry me lmk https://t.co/LKUNICnYVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeslaBand Bought the new album. Listen to all 12 songs under the stars tonight. LOVE IT!!!! You guys still have it 🤘🏻🤘🏻💋❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbrleigh I did not know about the 100 acre wood one I'll have to try it I want to max out my favs to see if they d… https://t.co/MLvW5ERtM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @SLBriscoe @joneill55 @AkronWineGuru @Dracaenawines @Cbp8Cindy @cowineco @ccatmpt @thatsVeryKari… https://t.co/QnYTbRg7vv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinNeuhaus6 Often asked of guests in my house:  “Would you like a drink or a drink-drink?” https://t.co/Z8QVBtND3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes Socialism? Ugh, sure. I got a paper straw at Bru Burger on Friday and you know what I did? I drank my w… https://t.co/bnwZqAiSyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I supported my local animal shelter just by walking my dog 1.21 miles using #WalkforADog app. Get the app at https://t.co/6Ygx5X0i3l.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of many hikes 🍃🏔 #skyhigh @ Chautauqua Park https://t.co/uOcnDV6XRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Streaming party 😎 @Louis_Tomlinson 😽 so excited for #TwoOfUSTomorrow https://t.co/75p4ZktQVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[KJV Verse of the Day for Friday, February 22, 2019.  "O my God, I trust in thee: let me not be ashamed, let not min… https://t.co/rvnsmZWUKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited for this 🙌🏼  @swissmiss will be speaking at #Clemson next week!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@argieeeeee Yes the wind is pretty awful today. I was leaving the mall today... and thought of this picture. https://t.co/qkJ6Bu2B7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mahl1334 Yeah, my neighbor just gave me this pic - team photo with McNabb's autograph on it. I have to get a bette… https://t.co/7d7sxgMAtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susan_artiga @Vovchick22 @FLOTUS @HillaryClinton @AOC @IvankaTrump so do the dems.  No,  my butt doesn't havent ha… https://t.co/rSNWebsCi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al fresco lunch 🍴 (@ Longleaf in Atlanta, GA) https://t.co/K55jMVQ0bs https://t.co/V4rLLKimpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#walkathon #pediatriccancer #hosa #azhosa What a day! @ East Valley Institute of Technology, EVIT https://t.co/Nnt6Ucflzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adrianara5 @JayFloresI JAJAJJAAJJAJAJAJ NO TE PREOCUPES QUE ESO VA SI O SII 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all just want me to drop dead. It's 85° out but that pool is frigid. Lmao 😄 https://t.co/MrtltNw0yQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USAmbPoland „Organizując konferencję, Polska musiała liczyć się  ze sprzeciwem takich podmiotów jak Iran, Rosja, a… https://t.co/jIfl0NFaVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Liar liar pants on fire” - actually said just now in the Michael Cohen hearing.  Live, in full, on @KIRORadio.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: The Jonas brother reuniting is the best thing that’s ever happened...that is all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Week 8 starts tomorrow and I’m still over here having 2 midterms this week on the same day☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s early, but if anyone but @AOC gives the keynote speech at the DNC in 2020, I’m watching reruns of Schit… https://t.co/u9LkLv6PbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[We want to protect ourselves and so we would destroy others and make use of them for our own advantage because we a… https://t.co/MY82WFztvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbozboswell @weareunited Well done @jbozboswell, @david_a_overall and Team SEA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarryMayUltd @johncusack @swingleft @crookedmedia Trying to frighten people away from not getting behind T-Bag’s opponent (unify “or die”)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newgradnicu I like the real techniques ones and get them at target or ulta!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SFGiants sign Harper, Smash Mouth needs to sing the National Anthem on Opening Day! Getting it done! 🧡🖤⚾️ Let’s Go… https://t.co/r1oimLYnfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForMyFriends1 @smerconish @michaeljackson @HBO Actually the clowns are to his left]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great place to grab a bite to eat while watching it snow outside. 😋 I love their sandwiches and enjoyed myself a ni… https://t.co/kfLJ3qMS8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me :doesn’t get something I wanted  Me: gets bitter  Me: cry’s  Me: starts period]]></document><document><![CDATA[So who thinks Donald Trump will lie, cheat and steal his way into re-election? Just based on his adoring fans and a… https://t.co/TSvBYToEzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just woke up from a dream that the sweetest boy was in love with me and i was in love with him and now i gotta fa… https://t.co/3YprQQPSDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics I just want the right candidate. Being a woman is a plus. I voted for Obama over Hillary in their primaries]]></document><document><![CDATA[@panarin_misha @ptdarreldactyl Oh no. You tweeted that wildly popular post for NOTHING]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latinx political identities are linked to imperialism and colonialism. #kellyclass]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you plugged headphones into your butt what song would play?   Just something for you guys to get the mind juices flowin today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CumberlandCoSch @CumberlandAIG @jackbrittbucs @carrieatc #ccsgifted Thank you @Brightstartours for the amazing civ… https://t.co/5bWagqRDva]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhySharksMatter 1. HIV was created in a government lab and released to control Americans. (I'm not even mad about… https://t.co/uZPLtTbTWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @realDonaldTrump Time for congress to legislate instead of lobbyists funded trips and slush funds! We… https://t.co/iRJ0q1t64p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KasieDC @mschlapp @KamalaHarris That's right @mschlapp retweet that statement and keep it safe....it will make a g… https://t.co/gBFXK0qYNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win tickets to @KISS107 #BackToSchoolBash featuring @whydontwemusic at @riverbendpnc https://t.co/VQP85WGcK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also--and I point this out only because the op-ed is in the Springfield paper--the Springfield public schools are b… https://t.co/x7I222hs6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoondriftMusing @43a6f0ce5dac4ea @th3s0ap @LeftistMageman @AuConservatives He was too busy with Twitter and other… https://t.co/uACslBIFQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vachilly64 @John_R_Berna @clovis1931 @EdElam5 @AnnaRosaRegala1 @elamchristy @SavannahBelle01 @LauraL2126… https://t.co/XQ37VJGD6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[A cure for HIV? Stem cells. A frontier that needs so much more exploration. God bless researchers!🔬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lillys_news @southernfriedJ Guys like him go to min security prisons. They have swimming pools and other amenities… https://t.co/ZXCowJ7b4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[johnny, sicheng, and jungwoo in sm’s bedroom @ night asking for lines. https://t.co/oGBMCe1u6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyleshohara I knew your drive to the end of the parking lot for a picture.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner before the show (@ Uno Pizzeria &amp; Grill - Dayton - @unochicagogrill in Dayton, OH) https://t.co/VA2UziV5M9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RRBC #RWISA #BOOKBOOST #BOOKREVIEWS #README #CIRCLEOFBOOKS  Will this Arctic weather ever cease?  Good thing I hav… https://t.co/WMzDXi6lXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[These 5th graders taught me about Spehero Mazes during their STEAM class today! @MunfordElem #DLD19 https://t.co/ql4pJ2LG1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[She admits it started during obama when she said 3 years ago.  Blame obama for the mess in the first place]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our bus boy at work made everyone Valentines.. except me  I ain’t even gonna act tough. That shit hurt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forget to post my dinner last night... nothing fancy just some cauliflower rice and turkey wings... #foodie… https://t.co/PKaNnY54Dn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @TheDemocrats The, haha I won, smile on Omars face disgusts me. This woman is sadistic in her attac… https://t.co/gdlmSBRNQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $50 Roblox Gift Card Offer    Win $50 Roblox Gift Card Offer By A Complete Simple Sign Up,    Sign Here:… https://t.co/mq4zTlKwa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexisgoldstein @AOC YES.   IT'S ****THE MOST REFRESHING THING..*****   lIKE YOUR DYING OF THIRST IN THE DESERT --… https://t.co/9esVOOWV1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my mom says “Awh he looks nice” I know she really means “he’s ugly” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Speechless 😳😬😁🤗😍💍💃🏾🍾🎉🎊💕💒💑 @ Fayetteville, Arkansas https://t.co/AT3AHUd41t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debbies_photos @nuwqO1P1QuabXpa @dimash_official #TWBDimash , #WorldsBest]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day at my internship was amazing I was told I can make coffee whenever I want 🙌🏽👌🏽☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my daughter @maddiesimerly rt this and I don’t think I’ve ever seen something so accurate. Have you ever eaten w… https://t.co/nnp83g5vhb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WootWoot @UCLAWBB #GotGame @KingJames come jump on the #Bandwagon now!  Thanks @ladybrockhard for capturing this m… https://t.co/FU5uY55ufu]]></document><document><![CDATA[if no one likes this tweet i’m going to start retweeting all of my tweets that got 0 likes just to see who my true fans are]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharon_schwan @MrsSpuds @sannbs @72cricket @RidenerTina @BxglL @ACog1984 @rosemoczulski1 @CSonafelt Yes!!!! A shorty!! 2-0 Pens! 🚨🚨]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got drunk and sang karaoke with Zach’s dad, mom, brother, Zach’s dad girlfriend and her daughter and myself. My w… https://t.co/xpoYEn9FQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@van_jamie_604 @mcsmjohnson @RealJamesWoods Because the actual evidence keeps showing up on which side of the aisle… https://t.co/OVGXtdVfJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hated getting up at 3:30 but I mean, we are going to orlando so i’m not complaining]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redknitterPNW @HillaryClinton You are making a lot of assumptions. I don’t know a journalist who doesn’t know pers… https://t.co/dOFdcf9g9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funnily enough, the other side of the bone says “If I lick it, it’s mine”. They have been like this for several min… https://t.co/YEmVES8efJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[the impossible burger &amp; loaded fries... I have to get them every single time I go to green bar 💚🌱 #vegan https://t.co/1c8cEmpDnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing says romance like a passion fruit cocktail and a blood orange one @republiqueLA. https://t.co/bF8UGAGdtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patrickquiroz_ @PatLie_Trends @itsmeangelieofc Salamat po team PatLie @itsmeangelieofc , @patrickquiroz_]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did a thing today. And this time I made shortbread.  the recipe is from Betty Crocker's picture cookbook from 195… https://t.co/5uPl0CuUe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful Dead 7-2-87 Silver Stadium Rochester NY https://t.co/C6vrS6V050 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Omg that's why he wants one so badly. He can't stand that President Obama did and he hasn't. Wow it woul… https://t.co/DcYaBZCkpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Languages in the world need to end. I’m tired of translating or not being understood. I’m tired of not being an Eng… https://t.co/euKAFcyKfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadBitchBait AWWWWWW, are you REALLY SHORT???????? It's okay. GIRLS ONLY LIKE NIGGAS WITH THE EYES ANYWAY. lame ass feetmales]]></document><document><![CDATA[All daylight savings does is convince me it’s okay to stay up later because it used to be earlier]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwinx49r @AngrierWHStaff I’m not sure I trust DOJ at this point in time.]]></document></documents></author>