<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @AOC I think all those who were detained by ICE and somehow made it through AND are being sent to El… https://t.co/xhNianF4R4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parliament of Canada: Remove Majid Jowhari from Parliament - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/pfFhGT5VB0 via @CdnChange]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg 😂😌I thought my Twitter Connection was bad. I was like why is it not loading 😂I’m very slow]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rodeohouston #bestseatsever #thankscolemans #ilovetim #wherethegreengrassgrows @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/83ZACkzy9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertPlant Hello Robert! The photo is my daughter. She tried to meet you last night at the Beacon Theatre just by… https://t.co/03dP3P04ME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Pam for collecting the cards for us, you are greatly appreciated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuziQLeathers I apologize for thinking you needed my help, truly.  Narcissistic much Florence?🙄  Perhaps you could… https://t.co/NfMW0dpXj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katymaiden @VocesFeminista @LillyTellez @arelytm76 @ISBeauvoir @DdeserChiapas @amluqui @jidomi1 @GritaTuAborto… https://t.co/n9lEwEIcyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EinsteinMaga @tallnhnsm @kidgolferman @Kimmerztweets @koopster90 @Lexa_Merica @Lynnoftrumpland @lorraine4trump… https://t.co/yyPrspvFD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I had to finish my shower this morning in the sink with hand soap because a spider invaded my personal space. Ru… https://t.co/21eYLqd4CT]]></document><document><![CDATA[the wind really out here taking down the roofs and breaking windows and knocking down trees n shit and they still c… https://t.co/NbRMrnTi3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are in the 6-10 inches of snow for tonight into Monday morning.  Sigh.  I guess I will be sleeping at work tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And of course, with global emissions still increasing, we’re very far from zeroing out on carbon, and therefore ve… https://t.co/trsqG4VEtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Typically, the tornado warning lead time – the time between when a warning is issued and when the torn… https://t.co/lCD3N9aVsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[any one else’s mom tell them never to try on engagement rings or wedding dresses?! Lol 😂 my mom always told us it w… https://t.co/xNIEI83rMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si algo te hace sonreír, soñar y brillar mantenlo cerca.⚡ en Hillsborough County, Florida https://t.co/JJUZVYTlJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like if I go through a “break up” with a friend, they need break up with alllll the bomb people I put them on to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lydia loves the wind tubes!!! She loves anything sciencey!! @ McKenna Children's Museum https://t.co/1AmUDdOFBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog Kushner was coached by Flynn to submit a simple FS86 form, saying it could always could be updated. Thi… https://t.co/z5jVlo6Gna]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if not @ItsRamiMalek and the  @BoRhapMovie than let it be @ladygaga Bradley Cooper and @starisbornmovie #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VitalikButerin @ATabarrok False. Younger folks have to compete harder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big news day today ... #RKelly finally charged with 10 counts ...  FINALLY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Build yourself up to handle whatever the world throws your way. #okc #fitnesscoach #garagegym #weightliftmeup https://t.co/djyKOOrc7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDice Good question. I can't watch many shows because he is on spewing his bs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF A PICTURE PAINTS A MILLION WORDS, THEN I'LL PAINT TRUMP A FOOL!  'CAUSE WORDS COULD NEVER EXPLAIN,  ALL OF THE M… https://t.co/plOX9amYEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YandR_CBS @TheTalkCBS @MelodyThomasSco It was a good interview loved your pictures]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allahs_SonOfMan @SirDougunefheir @supremekimun @XiJingpingReal @narendramodi I say #YES. #TAMFOUR #TaraAnnMoons]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UPDATE: @tierraonFOX7 has been on the scene of that semi crash/fuel spill for us this morning. She’s reporting tha… https://t.co/HOlKhKIuz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennyst0 That’s the one.  I’m thinking about it.  I love cool tones too.  I found this amazing palette at Sephora… https://t.co/WtycLEhiHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is against everything America stands for. It's time we Republicans stand up and fight back.  Photo id's and proo… https://t.co/ombcQtvjqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandmas birthday was Sunday she is 97 and still beautiful as ever ❤️❤️ https://t.co/3h8AF0DCFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier this week my KCB babes and I got to see the @jonasbrothers for their first #LateLateJonas interview and it… https://t.co/2OEdEFWrj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bye New Orleans. I’ll miss you!😢 (@ Concourse C in Kenner, LA) https://t.co/NQSqmHX4fF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Go ahead and continue defending the #1 liar (trump) this country has ever had to deal w… https://t.co/rGM5nM79aQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[(including producers cut of six) It’s been...a long time When did I start this Jesus Christ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking of selling? Call me and let's get moving! 🚣‍♀️☎️🏠🏡🚚⛵🚪 #realtor #lakegeneva #keeferealestate #lakelife… https://t.co/UiPHUuCexB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christianfrench on #FromTourWithLove at the @TabernacleATL last week. Check out his album, natural colors, if you… https://t.co/U1Qedqe7X0]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yes, I can hear all the footsteps and all the voices through the floorboards ... I ❤️ historic homes]]></document><document><![CDATA[This full Super Snow moon is in my sun, moon, and rising sign: Virgo.  🌕 ♍️ #virgo #supermoon #supersnowmoon… https://t.co/DxWBgLxCv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[also, for any mutuals/friends of mine who are in the boston area: I am doing a lil shindig for the premiere at this… https://t.co/fK1D0OUWjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Orthopedic Sales Representative for Alon Medical Technology" at Alon M… https://t.co/jARn42VhED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @seanmdav You and your network have lost credibility. I didn't go into 2016 not trusting you all, but t… https://t.co/NaKvKCWnav]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great opening night for AMS Baseball - Win over Clinton 5-3 @ Clinton, Tennessee https://t.co/S7m9wKShi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m real tired of my body deciding to bleed once a month. https://t.co/5g5x3a7Uaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gente enferma con el clima a 25 grados, teniendo este clima tan bello #nomamen 😫🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharvInDC Important reminder. I just started anxiety medicine a couple of months ago and it's a game changer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[El futuro pertenece a aquellos que creen en la belleza de sus sueños. -Eleanor Roosevelt  ...20 en Torreon, Mexico https://t.co/2Ry90WuHmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off #NASPA19 with the Certified Peer Education training @NASPAtweets https://t.co/gPvDoQQL9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[So uhh...it looks like they really showed #Manafort who’s #boss , eh? 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just sat and tried to figure out what really matters in my life and all I could come up with is my cat, tacos and brunch🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baddestmamajama @chrislhayes Eat the whole box. Can we get a delivery here for America??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perlmutter is a sexist, racist pos who made them change Iron Man 3's female villain to a man he is what held up div… https://t.co/sIWLDLYlRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG! I really cannot wait! #PartyHeartyWithZachMcGowan is so much fun! I hope I get to dance with @Zach_McGowan thi… https://t.co/LXo4hWbBjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump Ita! #NotMyPresidentDay #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass… https://t.co/PYaMyb3OqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you find your magic superpower, its powerful. Millennials have it right. We are all special snowflakes.… https://t.co/vAt54lqbrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Amen to that! I share your sentiments!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolishSnowflake @paulsperry_ @mattgaetz Get over it I don’t care about your opinions]]></document><document><![CDATA[the BIG EAST tournament happens during my birthday weekend and I couldn’t be more excited 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Wednesday I weigh in to see if my progress is sufficient to not consider me a high cancelation likelihood for bo… https://t.co/GOXvmy7I5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Delicate #iHeartAwards #BestMusicVideo @taylorswift13 @iHeartRadio @taylornation13 i💛TS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little acolytes are ready for Sunday service. These three are my reason for living! 💞💞💞 https://t.co/9NJvVYacLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Black History  #iamallwomanchampion  #iamallwomanunmoveable  #iamallwomanundefeated  #iamallwomanblog… https://t.co/qfVmy6iiQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courtesy of @sprint Rewards, I got a white chocolate mocha for 52 cents ^.^ https://t.co/Rjh2XXzxiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sam_Palmer208 If only we’d thought of that. Epic fail. Would’ve been the crowning jewel of this collection.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#5 March 🍀edition of 5 Things You Can do in 5 Minutes to Get Organized:⠀ Designate a pretty spot to put your keys s… https://t.co/WzRL6iaKUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskMeL8r Congratulations! You are truly brave and strong, it’s not an easy road but so worth it 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChasingLions_ @PeterOteca Center of control and disease = CDC   Department of health and human services. Is that n… https://t.co/ZLInX2WOxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Каждый раз, когда муж подбивает меня посмотреть какую-нибудь передачу на русском телевидении, меня не покидают мысл… https://t.co/nJ3fd0gyWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope you are all ok after the many emergency events that went on yesterday 🤮🤮🤮 I fear for today’s emergency events https://t.co/6JdVHvxtor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamienotis &amp; @DougHehner Can i plz get a HBD from u both 🙏🏼🥰 the little things that make my day ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler Perhaps you should look up the reason why they went after Clinton for impeachment and t… https://t.co/xmxo2hNYp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love our stadium!!! A wonderful community and school district that came together to provide... EAGLE PRIDE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[how tired am I? I just took my glasses off and immediately followed with trying to take my contacts out]]></document><document><![CDATA[whenever i’m sick and can’t even taste anything i crave shit i regularly don’t even eat.  currently it’s nachos w cheese and jalapeños 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mahi_The_Giant Everyone has been asking Me this question for years,when it comes to My gamer tag lol!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entering week two of the @setucommunity  @Indiegogo campaign strong!   Support inclusivity in wellness by backing o… https://t.co/rKbGTiDXaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[why the sick emoji? and by “that guy” i think you mean his husband. your homophobia is showing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trunzika1 my name is sabina   i was born in this world   my age is literally the only one that can be done   i lik… https://t.co/F9mHEIjFDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meanade That’s kind of how I feel when I’m looking for tops, bras and anything upper body. It’s infuriating!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been a @Chase customer for over 10 years but today is the day I will cancel every damn account (3 accounts plus a c… https://t.co/cRZtvVsT1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickandbubba Do we really think Hoda Muthana the widow of three ISIS fighters will be allowed by ISIS to come back… https://t.co/zgP9AV9iRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're supposed to only have one drink and you can't even drive home]]></document><document><![CDATA[Windy and cold 🌊💨☁️🕊 @NY1weather @StormHour @NY1 @NatGeo  #nyc #seeyourcity #silive https://t.co/PIbndqU7X7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pervert alert...Your beautiful REDEEMER is going to flip everything rightside up...ALL U NEED IS JESUS....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QCYNSubs WOW seeing everyone’s names listed out is so impressive. THANK YOU everyone for providing these subbed videos for us!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annoddragon @quiingi Should i take u seriously bec u r someone relevant? Next 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost To be fair he was asked to remember more than just first and last name, he had to know his company also.… https://t.co/HqhKLLKCt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you work in Hollywood or want to know what’s going on with the the WGA and negotiating with agencies, read this… https://t.co/1LNwMm0T1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kind of unrelated but WHERE ARE MY RABBI VOSS-ALTMAN STANS AT  Dude is a testifying MACHINE and he's spoken up for… https://t.co/fDpqeFhLR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are these #smart airplane seats the future of economy? https://t.co/dNjOf2pjq1 via @CNNTravel #travel]]></document><document><![CDATA[HE’S BACK 🔥 @get_buckets05 checks in on @SportsCenter at #3 on #SCTop10 https://t.co/hk96qLB6wy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy potatoes Batman!! i believe I have found @Eminem brothers @NateKane247 doppelgänger @KrisBryant_23!!! Saw a pi… https://t.co/OE3xE8bpXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother passed away after a stroke at age 69. Spread the word to act FAST.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on a balcony and I can hear @BorgeousMusic playing at omnia and I am PRESSSED 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DudekLinda @SarahGould_SA @landscaperstev1 @Itridpm @andrerucker51 @evilgrrl @hey_butter @poppij @delgeo1 @dyny1bn… https://t.co/BJr9vfbCSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn’t know, Sabrina Ionescu is the Triple Dub Queen of college basketball – men’s or women’s. Oh and she’s… https://t.co/96Th3VV3j3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flash back friday y esta hermosa foto con mi hermanito @raultvgonzalez sus padres y mi mami malenaburke  en la prim… https://t.co/51jvGIZg4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[1:28 am update: jordan just sent me a photo of the very back of her throat]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Solidarity Don’t just thank a union become a member! Organize 👏🏽Organize 👏🏽 Organize 👏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think Mother Nature doesn’t have a valentines and she’s crying? And that’s why it’s raining ?]]></document></documents></author>