<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT Who’s ready for season 11? Come watch with us at 9pm! #Drag Racethursdays #hitopsbar #hitopsweho #hitopsla… https://t.co/lIKQkGo1Hs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio @AfterHoursCBS Delightful interview with @blazerwheels tonight. Nice respite from the final 10 minutes of Thunder/Blazers. 😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to be attending this wonderful event for the second year in a row. Such a celebration of young women who… https://t.co/SkXhwvb2D7]]></document><document><![CDATA[IBS and FODMAPs 🍯🥦🍉🍞 . . FODMAPSs are a type of short chain carbohydrates that resist digestion and provide fuel fo… https://t.co/9bhRZr4LmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the Man and legend Sidney Poitier!  Sir Sidney Poitier, born February 20, 1927, is a Bahamian Ame… https://t.co/e1aTYZIher]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for sharing your wonderful students! Such a great opportunity for them! And we appreciate Mr. Campbell's… https://t.co/gWvSJuQPQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews @Winter Now watch  this https://t.co/CU6vwVd0oH   We are all slaves, Trump is trying, I believe to get… https://t.co/avaoZccZOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I messaged my mom my new hair and she was like “I’m so pissed that you can pull off short and long hair” 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[a year ago it was just me &amp; pat, now it’s me, pat, 2 fur babies &amp; a baby on the way ❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else really thankful that March starts this week? January and February are my least favorite months.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthYeoEast @FarmingUK What breed is this lamb? I am a herdsman for a small 4-H/FFA club lamb operation running H… https://t.co/mhLz8wrovk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasLograsso There was a second part that was even more funny but it was too controversial for Twitter 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBaach @NBaach we were out there all afternoon! Hope you’re doing well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pocket Princesses **100**Kegs will be tapped, shoes will be lost. Please reblog, do not repost Facebook... https://t.co/hw9wQSp2ZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GracieMayGreen @rejaniced I 100% think sex work should be decriminalized and safe.   Do I hope that we, as a socie… https://t.co/GdNuCIjjOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important research on impact of policies on plastic &amp; branded waste reduction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; when I walked away, I left footsteps in the mud so you can follow me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be comfortable being uncomfortable. Squeezing lanes today. https://t.co/DINqODSmDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is making me so happy right now to hear the @SanDiegoSockers epic win last night being discussed on @BenAndWoods this morning 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paraprincess77 Right there is where my tongue should be....yep right in that tight lil Brown fuck hole making you… https://t.co/OzEItpm14y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sigh. This pic. That movie was everything to me when I was younger. So sad. So young.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A win/win- Empowering employees with great tools increases productivity but is also a huge boost to job satisfactio… https://t.co/cS5GQ0yjiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmarAMuerteOf @TV_LasEstrellas  estoy esperando la publicación o video dónde confirmen la 2 temporada o Spin-off J… https://t.co/7kuXaAfTSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatGrant7777 @marinavibu609g @NoemRosales3 @GloriaR95633266 @rustamova_zuxra @brendak32405 @robtropper… https://t.co/kWNwB672tV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigitalTrends Wow 😯 @Kimberl38218406  that’s amazing 😉 @DigitalTrends  thank you 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I fed my niece spoiled milk so if anyone needs a babysitter I got u]]></document><document><![CDATA[This blew up! Come check us out if you are in Philadelphia. AWA: always watching anime!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s going to be very painful moments in your life that’ll change your entire world in a matter of minutes. Let… https://t.co/dMYB7ta533]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkees1 @tenzingmckenzie @ThomasSwords @Green_Footballs You need to learn how the different branches perform their… https://t.co/Yd9VMwdOpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DANiELLExJORDAN Oh PS. Up to 1.3K now 🤷‍♀️ 🤘 who knew you stunning Zim would be more popular than Dad grabbing @JoeyRyanOnline  ‘s dong 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Romaniuk and Sharp (2004, 327) define brand salience as the “brand’s propensity to be noticed or come to mind in bu… https://t.co/fqYS5Pk1D4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So not only did I smack my head off a rock wall this weekend, I got some crippling back pain in the middle of Walma… https://t.co/4h7RI10nrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compensation was taken when she had total disability the Niggar killed him because she was okay without her check t… https://t.co/pKa8XIi0w9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKrakensMark @DeepSeaImage I would never imprison them in a tank but it would be so great to be able to watch them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When she feels the drag heat. #coldcash #imafan @ Hamburger Marys WEHO https://t.co/4qV2Zj2yuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LenaaPooh @_whodatsy @savagekeki @kaeSupremee Cursing alone doesn’t but cussing at your child and around then cons… https://t.co/bY7LELumpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Total Body Conditioning! @ Philadelphia Sports Clubs https://t.co/IJkibnmVkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[all I’m tryna do is plan a beach day this weekend BUT NO ONE WANTS TO COME WITH MEEEEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world has been around for 4.6 billion years, civilization as we know it 6,000 years. Before us the world endure… https://t.co/tGz2PLvV2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️ for life! Red eyes, dry lips and all 😫 @ Dallas, Texas https://t.co/cqowRJLFOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikaLSanchez Under a sky the color of pea soup  she is looking at her work growing away there actively, thickly l… https://t.co/rdcj60FRKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be doing a live meditation on @PeriscopeCo at 10AM EST. Come and join me!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s see what he can do... if he does not come out if the box like a wild bull. Then go home..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WittenKristy Thank you! You can get them through my FB page or @JoJo_Rings use my promo code LJ20 for a discount!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $25 Skype Gift Card Offer  Win $25 Skype Gift Card Offer By Your Email Id Submit,  Click Here:… https://t.co/zIIexJXbC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell no they don’t kids supposed to be potty trained at 2 these parents be lazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrewV_Man @knaas @bernhardtsoccer I always tell people I’m from a Dayton suburb bc people haven’t heard of B’brook… https://t.co/75QpU9MgII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boydgaming @UNLVathletics @ThomasAndMack I hope you guys will consider Rick Pitino as the next UNLV coach. I hear… https://t.co/vUDQP7tjN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pimentonverde @NituPerez @xvzla2009 @TAMARA_SUJU @AlbertoRodNews @EAristeguieta @EDUARDO_BITTAR @RoderickNavarro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clairevhill Good Morning Claire; at 5:30 AM it's 23-c Mostly Cloudy, no chance of rain🌤️ I'll be busy with laundry… https://t.co/gBdAArFmnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[DROVE 15 miles to my NEAREST @CheckersRallys that I know and go to, only to find out it’s closed !! Y’all need to s… https://t.co/3Ms4v9k9Gw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the sky is clear where you are tonight, look up at the Moon. Mars is snuggled up right next to it! #RIPOpportunity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mostly we even dont know what we dont know..   #BeYou #LoudAndProud #PursuitOfExcellence #TealSwan https://t.co/Pw2NUsaiDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the 7 Day Book Cover Challenge from @MrsBowlingSci to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations… https://t.co/clUJ9Y7vOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treddtaylor How to enlarge documents for special needs, how to print onto fancy letterhead for letters of rec....]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s 8:40 pm &amp; i’m currently thinking about how cabin 2 had the best chants at camp RYLA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day to all of my fellow lady entrepreneurs! #entreprenurship #womensday… https://t.co/YJpgbF5e7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fabulous chilli by my hubby Napoleon @Art_Bee with organic blue corn chips by Neal brothers-the best a Canadian com… https://t.co/vqAhDD6DwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when I have proteins to purify tomorrow and none of the cold rooms in the building work https://t.co/oHkNh1mkZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevedder Thanks! They also have those frames in tortoise so i might get both 🤓   Good quality for an amazing peic… https://t.co/7IDUQVm1wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TariffMYtaxCUT @Centristchowdah @cspanwj @RepDarrenSoto Prove common sense?]]></document><document><![CDATA[im always a second choice and ive come to just accept it at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Vday to all the boys who drove me to drink so I could find my one true love: tequila]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HayleyBowBeauty @jamescharles @MorpheBrushes @JeffreeStar @norvina1 @ABHcosmetics 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patxu_lee @MakoModding @IstharVegaLuna Jaja! Si exacto. Estaba tan emocionada para verlos porque no los he visto e… https://t.co/6m0Ogh3ROL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexandria Williams started the Cowtown Weekend Half Marathon P/B Sprint! https://t.co/OT3ECsfEik #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlohaHa59067534 @EinsteinMaga @kaci150 @garway95 @ImabitcSumtimes @RevKeithBritt @ekim_yeldarb @OLDFLACO… https://t.co/UVgbvld5Su]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIDEO. Etats-Unis : l'ancien avocat de Donald Trump accable le président https://t.co/d9Ak2gvBgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeniellecook @CNN I don’t even know what to think. Right now I just feel awful for all those involved with the sho… https://t.co/Z1BJe6tNd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #nationalpetday to the #fivepack ♥️ bestest doggies ever 🥰 #nashvillenurse #dogsofinstagram #girlsbestfriends… https://t.co/6G62HcC9fz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: the city has confirmed Mayor Buckhorn’s Twitter account has been locked. They are working with @Twitter to… https://t.co/C4vN8R38u8]]></document><document><![CDATA[WELL ITS OVER   aka me trying to entertain @peterotooIe when she left me in the car in a middle of nowhere gas stat… https://t.co/lG4OqXO2fa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben thinks he’s so clever! Well I’m proposing again! I need platinum or silver! It’s time to put a REAL RING on my… https://t.co/GgPWj4GvgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[What about what she said about @BarackObama ? She is a lowlife &amp; hopefully @SpeakerPelosi will take action NOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @WFXL for your coverage of our after school meals program. https://t.co/Bo8rwBfIMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McCannChiro VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥 LIK… https://t.co/eau8yXS4FC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Gone, Still by Nine Inch Nails https://t.co/uARzsE1maS]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBC REPORTS ANOTHER LIE THAT PRES. TRUMP HAS DROPPED DEMAND FOR FULL ACCOUNTING OF NUCLEAR FACILITIES.  WH CORRECTS… https://t.co/m9laS3EdnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivaVinophile @FionaMorgan79 @GailBenzler @joneill55 @SideHustleWino @Starofthesea007 @hmgivingsoul @simplysallyh… https://t.co/1s89yH3CgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWalker17 no i didn’t. im just saying everybody in the situation is wrong not just him]]></document><document><![CDATA[OPEN HOUSE TODAY Sunday, February 17th from 2 pm to 4 pm  Drop by for a tour... https://t.co/bk7HesHlgC https://t.co/sZfSj5jOGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t sleep so I’m just laying in the living room listening to Tyler Childers like I don’t have a million things to do tomorrow 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karmendiaz178 😂😂 But for real, some of the Ky leaders could definitely drive me to drinking! 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a few weeks, you would have been 19. Can’t believe it’s been almost 5 months. I’m missing you a whole lot my pre… https://t.co/RirvYhhNhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riss_hallstrom @mirandamurpheyy  why did this remind me of yalls mi hoy minoy shit 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@salterfry @BorisEP @realDonaldTrump Leslie bless your heart you know nothing about lee county it’s one of the poor… https://t.co/di9mvweaM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seizures, migrianes, memory loss, etc. she’s calling the neurologist today. I’m scared as shit but trying to stay s… https://t.co/JVhHbJmuRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The youngest of the Barho kids who died in the fire today in Halifax. Only 4 months old. Please send out prayers fo… https://t.co/YsFMIYL3fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2Jonathan @Esther188rod  GOODNIGHT SWEETIE YOU HAD A FULL DAY I DID THING'S LIKE THAT ABOUT 6 YRS AGO ASTA MAN… https://t.co/SEAiPtR8bK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Youth Art Month!!!!  I could not be more proud of my young K-2 artists 🎨 @ West Deptford, New Jersey https://t.co/XhTzZtasLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know this could be a fluke because my side hurts quite a bit  now 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catsofinstagram Love the hat on the cat. Lol. That made me laugh and the look on his face, priceless. 👍😻😻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want a beer?”  “No that’s...” “Come on man don’t let me be the only one drinking.” “Okay I guess...” “Hey those are mine!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at MTA Subway - Union Tpke/Kew Gardens (E/F) - @nyctsubway in Kew Gardens, NY https://t.co/2FMZCsBYHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[He will spew his disgusting vile as long as people watch #dontgivehimaforum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenkruiser That's really cool! Seeing your name up in lights... #Famous. 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Yeah...well...Sen Girly-Boy...you AND Trump are going down (and I don't mean on each other).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyOwn Walking the plank, and asking lots o’ questions. ;) #mindfulofprocess #empathy2action #dtk12chat #SXSWEDU @MindWise_CK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTVNews Ontario was told a year ago OSPCA was opting out.  Nothing has been done.  Protecting our animals not a high priority.  Very sad😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HPZ @JessieSima @ForestLakeVCS @BookbugKzoo Harper says, Thank you Uncle Peter!! 🤖💗]]></document></documents></author>