<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@broadwayonair I don’t know if you’re kidding or not but either way I love this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMAZlNGNATURE I used to have a 3 legged dog who got hit by a car and that's how he became a tripod doggie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaththeWineLady @FionaMorgan79 @Julianna_glass @ccatmpt @SLBriscoe @suziday123 @thatsVeryKari @Cbp8Cindy… https://t.co/IBEJfxzefT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vienna and Claudia’s snap streaks are all going to be from LONDON this week and I’m going to be an emotional mess!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSG_54 @SpicyPurritos @RogueWolf2001 @NCLady50 @jmkillingnyc @Anthony4242 @AuntTritsy @TheSarge11 @louisanamom… https://t.co/MCbHxwBV7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont know about you, but I am tired of struggling, worrying,  about daily needs, forget about my healthcare, and… https://t.co/7xWFgjDyQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[i accidentally dropped to 100 lbs. the weird thing is that i’ve been eating more than i normally do but still manag… https://t.co/fGlp9Dvpu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Inclusionists @RWitherspoon @TIMESUPNOW In conclusion, healthcare is a fraud. Knees dictate health. Muscles reign… https://t.co/fwP2BopeU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[But now faith, hope, love, abide these three; but the greatest of these is love. 1 Corinthians …… https://t.co/rGA3AgBjgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emily was such an advocate for women in the skilled trades. We are all heartbroken at @apprenticeohio that she’s go… https://t.co/0Lc6hBPj4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[What you think about you bring about...you decide! #choose #gratitude #greatness #optimumhealth #ultimatejoy @ Tarp… https://t.co/rRiBMsn49A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who the fuck said that @TheKandyMuse didn’t slay the nail game... bitches square up and fight me https://t.co/o3UbSnZcuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder if Robert Kraft will sell the NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS TO THE CHINESE??]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @mclyte with get_repost ・・・ I’m MARCHING!! #Repost from @lynnrichardson. ENCORE  Over the past decade, I’ve… https://t.co/GYT3ZtweVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, nakita ko si Rashida Jones sa event tonight and ahsjskajahdhhs I couldn't stop smiling feeling ko tingin niya creep ako :((((]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grow As We Go has hit me deep, DEEP in the feels and honestly I wasn’t prepared. At. All. @BenSPLATT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bad liar by @Imaginedragons is an incredible song and I am sitting here emotional and thankful that @DanReynolds sp… https://t.co/Qq9w2goi6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Make love 'til the sun comes up til the sun goes down again 'cause I need you”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macowling @sokane1 Trump 🥩. Trump University. Trump Foundation. Trump International golf Course. Trump Vodka...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar @shanedawson Oh @JeffreeStar and @shanedawson  pleeaase send some to me!!💖💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JorgeGo47046980 @pulitajgb Porque te tratan tán mal?????🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No limbaugh, you’re the jerk. As a Catholic convert, you should know better than to spit lies. As… https://t.co/wzIG3pUfeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worried about all this scar tissue and all the trouble it caused me the first time, but...it was cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great birthday celebration for a classmate at @WonderWorksORL. Thanks for the thrills and fun Saturday afternoon on… https://t.co/iawHOKGhe7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one completely turned off by 0ffset now? He looks like such a yes man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Hooters I’m at your Hooters right now and it’s awful!!! 1. Bad Service- only gotten 1 drink 2. Food is awful s… https://t.co/rkSDfabClC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sis let me know I will be ordering you can bet your ass on that I NEED THOSE 😍😍🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[break up with your girlfriend, not cuz i’m bored, cuz i’m in love with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[McCathy is what he calls his catheter.  The one he wears while noshing a bedtime hamberder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget @TheDemocrats @SenateDems @TheDemCoalition are also a National Emergency!! #TheResistance #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[My FAVORITE Emcee of allllll time from our Generation has taught me to be "low key". And he is the only person and/… https://t.co/fxDtPUepXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish that I could convince my family to do a trip to Seattle in June so I could go to @ACEcomiccon ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[RND:   We will have a twonie for non-uni next Friday as a fundraiser to help bring the Rez Girls to Kingston. 🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CoachCollins made sure Megatron got GEARED UP with @adidasFballUS swag 🔥🔥🔥  #LEGENDSoftheFLATS #404theCULTURE https://t.co/OlsKLrtqEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CT State Police-Troop H is trying to find Christopher Somsky. He walked away from a DOC day program at Asnuntuck C… https://t.co/wP8aNj3v7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KIWKristina @demlyy @BluMoonEve @dgargac Awwwwww thank you so much, I am so glad that I am inspiring people to eit… https://t.co/LneRi98hC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger Actually you started it on your own! And keep@it going with you blabber mouth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can be nice and still don’t get what you deserve so you know what I rather be mean anyway lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #NYFW looks! Which is your favorite? 🖤 #NYFW19 #nyfwstreetstyle https://t.co/0lw4hQXaOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[What about the women that are assaulted COMMING up from South America that you promote hipacret all drama no platfo… https://t.co/MW2eM5tvQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDesmondRyan @CatChow66 @GOLamont703 @michelle_furlow @Dan_Sinisi @zooloo2008 @thecoffeecop @Patty4250_TPS… https://t.co/yGauoRldIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@56blackcat @kjblackhawk He's insane, who in their right mind would still support him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[*not pictured* Maple Pecan and Caramel Bourbon cronuts. #parlordonuts #evv @ Parlor Doughnuts https://t.co/5IYt2GhVwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @GOPChairwoman This is such a phrase; you have to be embarrassed by that Rose Garden charade! I am!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spokesperson from the Saratoga sheriff's department says driver involved cooperated and remained on scene.]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing this live,,,i would have reached the peak of my life https://t.co/rJssyLWg7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time at church camp, someone told me that we eat at least 8 spiders a night and it still haunts me to this day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPDONeill I WOULD REQEST A BACKGROUND CHECK ON THE TENNANT LIVING IN APARTMENT C55 AT 1005 JEROME AVENUE. HE IS L… https://t.co/PPXWkCk2uh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JigglyCaliente @RuPaulsDragRace If they can't even spell problematic, I wouldn't worry about their opinion too much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot even deal with these Republicans on the oversight committee. They should be ashamed of themselves. Also: C… https://t.co/i3WUmbEKvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sayang complimented me at work and it makes me feel so warm on inside. And I’m glad she can see this side of me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wsbtv @TyishaWSB That isn’t a joke.  Why do people think they can do/say mean things to people and say they were only joking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP Do you remember the reporter James Foley that got beheaded by ISIS put out for the world to see old President O… https://t.co/92Y1IBECLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 I have accepted a challenge from @Moonekev to post #7BooksILove-no explanation, no reviews-just cover(s). 1 c… https://t.co/9tM9Q6TE8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending hours in the beauty supply store and online looking at hair, wigs and lashes? Hiding your new hair pieces… https://t.co/MjU4j396bG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Victims’ advocates want uniform church laws to impose zero tolerance for priests who abuse minors and for the bisho… https://t.co/kI4XVvFvNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[ahhhhh why does the iphone have your read receipts on when you got a new phone]]></document><document><![CDATA[But time is perhaps the most mind-bending feature, the worst outcomes arriving so long from now that we reflexively discount their reality.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry not sorry for the spam lol. im just so unbelievably proud of and in awe of everyone who worked on borhap. who… https://t.co/8podQHqRWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Unidine team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/jf0DlrJR7c #Finance #Analyst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icejackel2015 @UROCKlive1 @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump He hasnt mocked any nationality, show us all the proof. You… https://t.co/f25FAU9W6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Art in nature. 🌿❤🌱  . #Art #naturelovers #naturephotography #trees #beauty #HallOfMosses #hohrainforest #optoutside… https://t.co/f5r5dlHchv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plumbing student’s installing a new water fountain! #skills @JCPSAsstSuptAIS @IROQUOIS_HS  @AP_JRLett https://t.co/kPW9ve4v5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tvoti Beautiful Mind and Crash definitely bottom two. The Artist and Birdman are fine. NCFOM is the clear number one by a mile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellyjadron is dexter on the runway??? #fashioncat #catwalk #hautecoutureDexter 😻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whignewtons @KellyannePolls This nasty comment alone should have disqualified her for ANY news reporting period!!!… https://t.co/oQEoMu87Pu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RCReed40 My gut tells me before agreeing he’s a vile human spewing hatred, I would need to listen to the entire pr… https://t.co/pHj7QBqc5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrat party is the anti Semitic party... time for Jexodus...#censureIlhanOmar......she’ll never assimilate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge congratulations to this guy for performing at his very first open mic night, and achieving his goals of laught… https://t.co/ez7xod95Ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir Thanks, Rocky. Have you tried unplugging it, then plugging it back in?  🤣🤓🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Ms. Miller's class for the thank you card!  You guys were great, you all did a great job today and I am g… https://t.co/isPIKSvCl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TasteOfCountry @garthbrooks He’s the biggest hearted, humble singer there is. His contributions to music has been… https://t.co/en1A9qIKuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Either we spend time meeting children’s emotional needs by filling their cup with love, or we spend time dealing w… https://t.co/zCW26uKPkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RL9631 @BrendaNord5 Congrat's on 20,000 followers https://t.co/bNHiEiSUtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of February 25th #dool #days NBC spoilers  Jack drops a bombshell. https://t.co/Cwve13OLg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Well I believe we have Scientist that twist facts to fit their narrative because they are working for thos… https://t.co/X727UmFcEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Hardwood Suite at the @palms includes an indoor basketball court 🏀, professional locker room🏒, game room 🎮, a h… https://t.co/skwb8UZ7qG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kakashi-sensei e Sasuke  Si se lo pregunta si tengo una obsesión por Sasuke si 👾🤤😍 en Nogales, Sonora, Mexico https://t.co/3PDjNo2G5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing quite puts a damper on a nice weekend like throwing your back out 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have no idea what folks are going through or dealing with internally. Be kind damn it. Would you rather be the… https://t.co/aIBisoo45l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kel_______ Nothing compares to NY pizza, NY bagels and NY Deli’s. You could make millions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vetzy1991 @KingJames @NBA @NBAAllStar @IAMGUILLERMO Not that I’ve seen! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this #sugar #skull #apron in my Etsy shop #etsyaaa #DayoftheDead https://t.co/2epMLBJRiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 Reasons The "Done With Church" Fill Me With Hope   https://t.co/qEgPOUFHHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJerryNadler @HouseJudiciary You are abusing, obstructing, and corrupting the power of your Committee. The inves… https://t.co/ETwHJ1e5b2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coffeexdear bro tell me about even my 4 hour class has a 10 min break :’(]]></document><document><![CDATA[This photo is a pleasant look of Bernie! True Old 80 year Bernie is what a real Mad Communist ! Looks like!! #Trump… https://t.co/JCyYUQ1wdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taffyakner @judybattista Oh, way gone. I never seem to go anywhere near Plantation when I am home, tho ... have no… https://t.co/uNyIh5ffzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelsey_caine the funniest thing would be for him to ask you to open for him and then play it off as the ultimate act of contrition]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi, i too, would like to live.  and i (like others) have this crazy idea: i don’t want to pay the same amount (or m… https://t.co/MDW33JGCbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It shouldn’t be possible to shiver and sweat at the same time. Being sick sucks ass🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how the person that rent this place going to explain this to the leasing office 🤔🤔🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyMNorman @shylanott I think I also pronounce it differently at different times, but mainly dayta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Falkor- so happy with his stick!! 🐾 5-month old Big Baby (89 pounds of fluff! 😍) #leonbergerpuppy… https://t.co/IyQBApHhlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LostOnTheFringe I missed the first hour, o thought it was still on at 9 :( LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chriswoj @IWF I said ok.  Not that I agree with you.  However, Its been a good debate and you make valid points.… https://t.co/hFZ5zzHety]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in Atlanta, GA, check out this #Education job via the link in our bio: English Language… https://t.co/9amJG7r7mZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teared up today after a 7 year old told me she was proud of my skateboarding progress. There’s humor here you just… https://t.co/qh2LeJouO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[District administrators are trying to get the language on the screen to match the amended motion that board members… https://t.co/D39G6VVOCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work was actually good today I was watcing Moana which serving my residents because it was on the TV]]></document></documents></author>