<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@NRATV @stinchfield1776 Having guns is not a “God given right” but I hear you guys spouting that one all the time!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[*husband shaving off mustache*  Husband: Oh. There you are Peter.   Me: *spits out water*   😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beautiful_Katty So, you advocate for unjustified reporting?  It's ok to vilify someone based on sound bites and incomplete video coverage?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get so paranoid about making sure my front door is locked and that the stove is off...I checked both 30 minutes a… https://t.co/2htyBgt25c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnjaBlaj Post your data inexpensively on $BSV blockchain at a rate of $100 Mbyte/10 minutes, sustained.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@udemysupport Hi @udemy @udemysupport I would like to speak to someone at your company. How do I make contact?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is beyond dispute that the inferior is blessed by the superior. https://t.co/U9GIMXp1aV]]></document><document><![CDATA[you ever just sit there and think “I just need some dick” nah me either.. just asking for a friend..]]></document><document><![CDATA[My night consisted of a bottle of wine and watching Legally Blonde, The Birdcage, and now The Big Lebowski and it’s… https://t.co/hZkVel4nc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@titygirl_ I always spoil it and find out everything before it happens because I hate not knowing and now i know ho… https://t.co/7edLMeTNof]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's the Best Way to Teach Kids #LGBTQ People Exist? https://t.co/pZSGhanmAd via @TheAdvocateMag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave @gatewaypundit Get this slug out of country. She married her brother so he could claim citizenship. Fraud. Crime. Deport both]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrevorNoah finally being seen for who he really is. Not funny. #RudeAwakening]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so impatient waiting for this final season!! #ForTheThrone #TyrionLannister #JonSnow #SamwellTarly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheekykmk @SiameseCatTwins @Petlover264 @GiveLuckyBack @PeterAskin1 @WildCatFdnLa @straysneedlove @stwissmann… https://t.co/oMKDzq7lTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@esglaude @peterbuttigieg @Morning_Joe Me too! He was the best I’ve seen in an interview yet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ERated_ I felt personally attacked by this tweet. You know i am THE Ebone STAN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is absolutely hands down the most important baseball news this year!!! Go Paloma, GOOOOOO!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Selfpromotionsunday  Novel #TheBookoftheMandolinPlayer https://t.co/ewIn0Nl5no]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is she so dumb? Tucker Carlson analyzes Ocasio-Cortez.    Time to require candidates for public office take and… https://t.co/gmwihu0kJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OttawaLiveCKCU @juliecdoiron @CKCUFM It was so hard not to cry! *muah* thank you for listenting in. xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyBond Its using homeless people as chits in a game that is shocking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#buildthewall I had to laugh; I just heard that trump said he would “have to study” the wall deal; do you believe t… https://t.co/wptvH2dt7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment on Grandparent’s Day 2019 when you realize your age is between the age of the grandparents and parents… https://t.co/Sw7O08Pcrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NEAToday Advocacy or even mention of LGBTQ has zero place in kindergarten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pirates win!! #SHU #HALLin #SetonHall #SocialPirates https://t.co/6aq2iREroA]]></document><document><![CDATA[wrap my mind around how a priest, or any grownup, could molest a child or a Bishop seduce a young man who is discer… https://t.co/1knsciqtE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get her out now.  She and her followers here and abroad are trying to take over our Country.  Wise up! Sure take aw… https://t.co/buWq6JYelf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avísenle a mi mamá que ya llegué a Baltimore #Islandia (@ Baltimore/Washington International Thurgood Marshall Airp… https://t.co/11yTxrEHMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dpbullseye @Kris_Sacrebleu Yea, it’s pretty immature how you fawn over the pretty girls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaiMike26 @WhiteHouse We will send them your way . Your addresses is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t have written a better rationale for the GND myself....we must mobilize and act collectively to survive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my Day 1 of my 7 day book cover challenge from @ShereneSahib Post a cover of a book that you ❤️ without any… https://t.co/23SSr36JVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have different wrestling shoes for every costume and every role in #theringcycle #operaisacontactsport… https://t.co/bYrj12UPRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This homophobic senator really is proof that hate makes you ugly ¯\_(ツ)_/¯]]></document><document><![CDATA[the_real_hannah_banana had a packed house. @ MuSool Martial Arts https://t.co/3tSijvqF4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to get 50 people to like my tbh statuses on Facebook, now I can’t even get 5 likes on a tweet ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Otto Warmbier's family rebukes Trump, says Kim Jong Un is responsible for son's death  https://t.co/DEhYnj9YEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl Scout cookies will be in next week&amp; I will be delivering them. Please stop harassing me😂😂🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[am i the only one that doesn’t like any of them ... it’s all abt kettle cooked salt and vinegar and jalapeño chedda… https://t.co/GJkBr7XJC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Heiner91952920 @michaelshermer @joerogan I'm from Connecticut and personally know people from Newtown. I dare him… https://t.co/eUL9n6MKUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 The evangelical group would try and push that agenda. They tried to deny civil rights,civil libert… https://t.co/IiVivcYX9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bouquets galore #roses 🌷🌹💖🧡🍃🥰 #costco #flowers #lcrfloral @ Costco https://t.co/kA4A9h4o3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParisJackson ..... I would love to make you a hand made quilt !!!! ? What do you think ?????????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Más molesta los trámites y pérdida de tiempo y ver carotas para reponer documentos, que el maldito robo en si. Pero… https://t.co/BL68oxTgJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the “before” shot of our new Bar seating table that just got delivered. Wait till you see the “After” shot.… https://t.co/P6crQ3wEKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ehite_haque Loved your question!  It was about what historical period/ figure, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJerryNadler is my hero! Esp after seeing Caputo last night. Get the subpoenas flying! #TheBeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready for the temperature outside to match the beautiful scene I see out of my windows. 🌇🌬🧥👢🧣🧤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist Oh come on and give this ole southern Gal a shout out. You know I'm a fan of your tweets!! Your friend… https://t.co/kM7YuDU5M7]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHOCKING! The Dark Truth About the US Border EXPOSED in Revealing Speech https://t.co/woIe8uEYSd via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[At what point in our lives do we find those healthy friends? You know those friends you have when married that will… https://t.co/AVsSf5OkHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a bottomless pit today *eats all the snacks* *still hungry and rooting around for more*]]></document><document><![CDATA[To think only of the best, to work only for the best, and to expect only the best. #optimistcreed @ Cornwall, Ontar… https://t.co/WJ5GeYGd6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DomoWilson1  keep being true to yourself! You are absolutely gorgeous inside &amp; out. One of the realest 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC you are a dream (even tho the wind nearly blew us off the edge) @ Top of the Rock NYC https://t.co/td4deagwRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This painting is proof I know nothing about fine art.  #AntiquesRoadshow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@addy_pez @RCSD @OfficialLivePD @LivePDNation @Sean_C_Larkin @danabrams @TomMorrisJr1 @WomenPatrol Congrats!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is something seriously wrong with this...🥶 https://t.co/283607CTWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t worry guys, I found a helpful and amusing article to answer my question. https://t.co/U9eizxvtEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo se que nadie me podrá igualar, me refiero a mi derecho de antigüedad]]></document><document><![CDATA[#greatmorningworld #cannabiscommunity #cannabislatinanurseceo now available my ebook on Amazon by toni Pinedo-Jeffr… https://t.co/6MSw15tfOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let the peace of Christ [the inner calm of one who walks daily with Him] be the controlling facto… https://t.co/PdHfwHsi0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remove the product from the Oh ✅ Smooth out the Bay ✅ Put on the finishing touches and Voila!! Perfection 💥💥 https://t.co/CrKa5ifyLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back and I’m better: yesterday was my first ever tv appearance As a model for the Spring Fashion segment with… https://t.co/mJn1Bs7dsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoSloBux Yes sorry, wazs 0622, I am PST time and i was half asleep and forgot exact PPS, thought my earlier was 063 area.  VYST]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m drunk on NIH journal access power browsing papers on encephalitis lethargica. If you need access to anything yo… https://t.co/OxEnuX6DT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Joe - and yes please come join- we have a really fun #giveaway today! #giveawayalert #freebooks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate this 🙄 last semester a professor gave me a study guide with 60 terms to remember for a six question exam… https://t.co/pPDVy22ioX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter just called me old.... I was born in 1986, she said mom you’re so old you were born in the 1900’s..… https://t.co/UzlFqVhqfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TheRealDooley_ Arent you just sprinkling happiness everywhere, huh?? Did  you forget???  😂 😂 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Amazon you made the right decision by pulling out of New York.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also what is with Colton’s pink diary he is carrying around, anyone want to talk/make fun of that? 🤷🏼‍♀️ #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rlnbeauty @THR The queen of the galaxy is not amused. https://t.co/sK5160vtv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inmylife1751 @ChatByCC @OhatByCC OMG! do you have a mirror if you do better take another look because you look damn Scary!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so much more than soap and lotion. Just like you are so much more than your hair /skin. We want to support a… https://t.co/jO82rwqydX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice reminder that where would Greater Hartford be without #insurance, including #Insurtech?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@animallovr2 @TheTalkCBS @JussieSmollett he will probably be if Proven guilty, killed off the show. My heart aches right now🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can anyone get to work if even mass transit is not working properly? @MTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dear son. Never forget that. I Love ❤️ You. When you walk out of that door. Part of my heart walks with you, eve… https://t.co/79brdA8lEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just woke up with a black Shepard attacking me in my old childhood backyard. Somehow got away inside and I was fa… https://t.co/8kxHV6uVbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scoma60 @CatrinaNecole If it truly was Franco, then I would be all for Lulu and cheering her on, but it wasn’t. An… https://t.co/cdCHv1YCfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conservmillen Why the 🤬 no one helping him?  Everyone just standing around and taping and laughing. Shame on them]]></document><document><![CDATA[this movie is so fucking funny. im quoting and rewatching it constantly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz You are a sad day in American politics. Go make some coffee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonders of the World (DI Team) presents...❤❤❤ @PrideAnderson  #OurFISDStory https://t.co/v0WieByxwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seen on my walk/run this morning. #plants #nature #photography #winter #pnw #morning #islandlife @ Vashon, Washingt… https://t.co/jWeQBvyb64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinKCTV5 @KCTV5 My friend @christygersh and her husband bedazzled this amazing #ValentinesDay box for their littl… https://t.co/Cs9QyGBydb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrpngDeth72 @AOC Give us more facts on what really happened so everyone will know the truth. Give us the facts abo… https://t.co/7IoO3vHKW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many expressions from such a tiny man ❤️ . . . . . . #newbornphotography #denvernewbornphotographer… https://t.co/Hc1xbasB5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[#satisfying #sundaynight #appetizers #charcuterieboard #wineandcheese #charcuterie #winelover #winebar #wine… https://t.co/pQeAzuHbQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats!  #Repost @LunaLaurenVeIez •  •  •  •  • It’s official! I am over the moon about the reboot of… https://t.co/LU7E88mc46]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billieeilish can you please make a quick stop in Texas for your 2019 tour!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#throwmesomethingmister #lundigras #mardigras #acadiana #lafayette @ Lafayette, Louisiana https://t.co/9QIa8nsdkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[COME MEET YOUR DARK VALENTINE TONIGHT! Our Bartenders are serving stiff ones tonight. #FaultlineBar… https://t.co/rk3koTZVGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmonstah @hragv @LoudenStudio @LALOUVER @Saber @vielmetter @myMotorhead @MotleyCrue https://t.co/teuJYD9Opc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Univision Osea,así de verdad ya se hizo México? Que cualquiera que vive aqui,es mojado? Eso es ridiculo,patetico y… https://t.co/WzomXGF24G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne @OldVikingLord I didn't know.  But I remember you talking about a Christmas present you received as a chil… https://t.co/UF1WLPYcYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidGeurin @hansappel094 @smgaillard @pushboundEDU @jeffreykubiak @JayBilly2 @NowakRo @Prepare4SPAlife… https://t.co/odsuktra8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[our boys are all grown up 😭💛 #jonasbrothers #suckerforyou https://t.co/t37cfsKeNu]]></document></documents></author>