<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Courier429 although I'm really excited to get my papers tomorrow morning bc I get both the New York Times and Seat… https://t.co/i8PxmsqTxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roywoodjr Before the," everyone gets a trophy" campaign there was the "everyone wins a tourney." Win one, lose the… https://t.co/OsscI3HH7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[– Mamá te puedo decir algo pero sin que te enfades?? – ... https://t.co/XsRzI53Vp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeff Adachi was a courageous and effective advocate for justice. His passing is a tremendous loss for San Francisco and California.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @Twitter @facebook @instagram Sharia....lol.  Give me a break!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBigCat @PFTCommenter can you imagine being the guy at the water cooler that didn’t bet on Storley last night?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caden_pennick @maritta_oh Excellent words and illustration( thank you good words excellent)👍👋🌞😊😀🙏🙇🎶📖⏫☝💝👑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USL_HQ @NewMexicoUTD I hear they're going to sell out on their inaugural game in Albuquerque! Albuquerque has great fans!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marrone_ca @YoungerGolf @SrixonGolf @ClevelandGolf @JBHolmesgolf @genesisopen Sundial?]]></document><document><![CDATA[LeBron is great rn and he is one of the best of all time, but I will always think Kobe is greater.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And billions for that vanity project, his wall . This is not okay by Americans! @cspanwj @cspan @Morning_Joe… https://t.co/6rde2NtTJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyARusso @chelseacutler amazing in Madison! Excited to fly to TX to see y’all soon!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ucdavis needs to cut ties with their hate filled professor Joshua Clover for these comments:  “People think cops… https://t.co/yEGOf9nEHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurnieSue @ncirish2002 @KimelPenny @kwilli1046 MAGAMORON.  I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on E… https://t.co/mRKx0qtSIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[DRIVER KILLED: An SUV left covered in bullet holes after  gunman opens fire on Miami Gardens Drive near I-95. SUV’s… https://t.co/4UU1TQY1B4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlatEarthExpert @iamAtheistGirl Edit: previous figure for diameter of the earth is in Km, not miles. That said, me… https://t.co/1xAP6Nuepw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blasterlaw @rustindodd Oh I saw that and was totally triggered. I had to log off #Twitter. Worst contract ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go check out the article on MY Reason to Dance! @RileyKids #BeTheHopeNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always fun to see what you former students are cable of. #IBDenton @cms_myp @dlopez826 @ibmyp @CMS_Cougars https://t.co/gwYQpnmifj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FreeRealityWinner #Justice4Reality #FreeRealityWinner #Justice4Reality #FreeRealityWinner #Justice4Reality… https://t.co/TuYDPsdoAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about GNKs and comics made me go reread the Gonk issue of @astarwarscomic for like the 10th time. One of t… https://t.co/Er2CUk6xAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prom Queens &amp; Sweet Mistresses Of CHS #chavezhighschool #classof2005 #chavezhighschoolprom @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/q9VFsQ538n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbiSBrooks @Alyssa_Milano Omg for real 😒😒 but by the end of the week it’ll be in upper 60s with thunderstorms 🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST LIKE OBAMA JUMP BEFORE KNOWING ALL THE FACTS. DEMOCRATS ARE DIVIDING OUR COUNTRY #MAGA #UpRising… https://t.co/ULABM7b0Q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiero estar contigo, no un rato no un día, en las buenas y en las malas, pero siempre contigo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don’t wanna be that person with a chapstick keychain, but @BurtsBees is breaking my bank 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[What wrong with this picture?  #realestateagent #realestateagent #realtor #wresidences #realtors @ Broward County,… https://t.co/2UfrwR9IVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out a recent post by @MatthewHalsted on interpreting Genesis 1 at @TrinityhausCCT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJohnWild @Coach_Rutledge_ @Kreager @mopatton_sports @LLadymustangs @tharealslay10 Dapper...]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS IS FOREVER AND ALWAYS WADE COUNTY 3️⃣🐐🔥❤️ The 🐐 #DWade #Flash #3  Wow❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️❗️ #ThankYouGod  #HeatNation 🔥🔥… https://t.co/QGqVikqKrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starbucks stop putting plastic utensils in your egg bite takeaway bags!! People do not use them - we use our hands… https://t.co/uPgmkCCVE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoxRedFox Thank for for the points. I'll put them in the box with my other ones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We truly have STUDENT-ATHLETES! That’s what it’s all about, chasing greatness in everything we do! #GoKnights… https://t.co/c2NdMiUwvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Luck to @jchsboyslaxteam tonight on the season openers.  JV @ 5:55 PM, Varsity @ 7:45 PM @ Hooch. @JimmyHarkin… https://t.co/16CCaYBPWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so excited to see the improvement that @jtdaniels06 has during this second season as #USC quarterback. #FightOn #Trojans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A__Chevalier @SimonMaloy And yours earned mocking laughter for your missing the sarcasm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olive_pObs Estoy de acuerdo contigo. Dejé un poco Instagram por ver tanta superficialidad y resulta que Twitter ah… https://t.co/WmWjGD4aht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EWErickson And a lot of people have a lot of trouble with lying and spinning or fabricating facts. Who is more to… https://t.co/6Ribz4CtX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goes without saying, but damn, March is awesome. Sports fans are spoiled this time of year! ▪️🏀@NBA, @marchmadness… https://t.co/8ACwUywoOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcsnl @KTLA @realDonaldTrump let’s see if we a skit out of this one tonight on @SNLUpdate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday to me! - Drinking a Hop JuJu (2019) by @FatHeadsBeer @ 295 Beers N'at  — https://t.co/ROvUZjAYgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[jamison told his mom to keep talking to me for him &amp; make sure i’m doing okay &amp; my heart is so freakin happy 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packed house for the amazing @DanAndShay at @UniversalORL https://t.co/RkwPGRCIQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[After becoming disillusioned by the Liberal party being usurped by identitarian activists, I sought out new informa… https://t.co/pYdX96XPEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure if you watched this weeks episode, but it was hilarious! I had to share...😂😂😂#fingerbutt #highmaintenance… https://t.co/tTkuZomBmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jchybow @BenSullins Sorry, I didn’t know how else to get the good news out because I didn’t have many followers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sucks dealing with others that don’t care about anything man, it truly makes me sick and I dislike it so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[N. Scottsdale actually recorded snow.  #Scottsdale #snowpocalypse2019 https://t.co/MXN5bAxQ2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatAngererUSA This dude coming up next is even better! https://t.co/2akpaFb0N4]]></document><document><![CDATA[One word to describe @ladygaga and Bradley Cooper tonight....incredible 🙌🏽🎙🔥#Oscar2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman I know. Racists are the worst. https://t.co/cAYs6ADTAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my girls and how great they are doing at their new school #2of3girls #assemblyday @ Woodbury, Minnesota https://t.co/Q6E7snZP3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr The only reason you are anyone is because of your daddy!!! You are a POS!! You hunt animals because… https://t.co/dBAtZIyHt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final: Thornton 56 Shepard 49. Brandon Hall 13 points, Derrick Williams 11 points/7 rebounds for @TthsVarsity, whic… https://t.co/Qn2SnLWV8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justplaying76 Squeeze the breasts and she needs to masterbate as you hump her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Nothing   My kid: Nobody listens to Spiderman because he doesn't save the day he just plays around with his webs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mango Foxtrot by @cidercorpsaz @ Cider Corps — https://t.co/iuCVeoGu8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SugarFactory @GaslampQuarter @love @socalthrills #SanDiego @VisitSD_PR @SDPartnership @drunkcupcakes… https://t.co/UGfoqgrVRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said my good byes some time ago. They bring on people who they just want to argue with for the ratings. Want to b… https://t.co/olBr0uFbVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Bedford–Stuyvesant, Brooklyn https://t.co/RCsNmlaJ4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[All you girls who drink wine... How many of you know how to use va corkscrew? 😂👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daybreak502 It’s so refreshing to hear actual good commentary rather than a shitty sitcom with shitty sitcom jokes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers Don’t know what lizards thicket is but other 2 should shut down! If your date takes you to… https://t.co/KEdXut4wma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmsalcido Corramos por veredas en el bosque Probemos de sus frutos el sabor Descubre que riqueza te rodea Sin pens… https://t.co/mpA2ZwJbwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The KALB News Anchor who said, "Where I'm from, we don't think like that, we run." Please explain..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rose are red Violets are blue Bryce, if you don’t sign today  Idk what I’m gonna do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CobraElDiablo ....sure I forget you were a nerd so a you probably consider a calculator ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilevin @morgfair Excuse me but the Holy See knew about this piece of filth since 2001. There wasn’t a Vatican inv… https://t.co/OFvlhYavSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna say if something ever happens to me let me die before taking me to South Shore Hospital]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I feel really rusty today playing sand volleyball? No. It was kind of surprising considering I haven't played i… https://t.co/oQuitpqCOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[As always thank you to my friend @Galaxy_History  You really ruined my life giving me access to that shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@likesquirrel317 Yea, specifically over a community disparate impact study we did for a policy change  we are proposing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MassDOT has completely dropped the ball in treating the roads this morning.  Dangerous conditions persist.  We nee… https://t.co/98CxGPTFa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coworke did a drawing of me. It captures my snark well, I think. #NewProfilePic https://t.co/eoNuOzEzSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubusChrisBrown @billyrayskinner It didn’t. I loved it the first time I saw at age 5. Still love it today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went from “I hope Anthem is good, I wouldn’t mind if the division 2 and destiny 2 had some competition. Competiti… https://t.co/JjXqy9MlqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachFuller_44 We went outside. It also dropped 30 degrees in a matter or 30 seconds. It was brutal]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DigiBridgeUS will be there. Will you?  #ReachOurFuture #CTE #Pathways]]></document><document><![CDATA[That @MarvelStudios logo at the beginning of #CaptainMarvel ... So good!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump ALL POWER TO THE SOVIETS! ARBEIT MACHT FREI! EIN VOLK, EIN REICH, EIN TRUMPENFÜHER!   (i.e. Go to… https://t.co/7udpEiseYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christine_sarr @CorpsAfrica @Paroleaujeunes @unicefsenegal The only one picture together 😅 and I really like how we look❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica @movieator wait is it companion or confidante? Lol if that’s true I might have just confirmed that… https://t.co/DGlItbD3Ox]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday morning grind with Dr. Joseph...#outworkyourcompetition https://t.co/tCWMlYBtUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessBriganti 🌨Good Morning @JessBriganti. It’s still snowing 🌨 in Schodack/Castleton.🌨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dk_prabhu @klpkdhk Peaking early, it's only February. Maybe we can get him to tweet slander at Modi and tag him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FAKE NEWS! THEY SHOULD BE FINED OR SENSORED WHEN THEY REPORT EVERYTHING BUT THE FACTS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How could you believe in a god but deny the possibility of extraterrestrial life forms🤦🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UFGoonerAJ @DutchieFlair I don’t think he will have a huge amount of input with Monchi. Suarez was a good loan opt… https://t.co/IkQGM9SVx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isaiah 55:6-7    Seek the LORD while he may be found; call on him while he is n... https://t.co/Z6GDBH1eZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuluTurismoMx @jenarovillamil @GobiernoMX Ah mira igualito que en estos momentos que persiguen y atacan a los que no piensan igual que él]]></document><document><![CDATA[Midnight madness from this Troll. Should I tell him the Vikings have never won a Super Bowl no matter the coach. Ye… https://t.co/fzuUGnqq8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody been eyeing up "The Occupation" ? Looks really unique. https://t.co/mRHPWdnP5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[experiencing moments like these makes me wonder what else God created into this world... https://t.co/2NFbB51hsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Coyotes pull this off and make the playoffs...how could it not go to Tocchet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of great ones on the list for leaders in schools! Which ones do you have and/or have you read? Any favorites n… https://t.co/s7ogKGxvkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tj_hallums  this is something that you would do  bruh! https://t.co/AgeuBw8Pqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Makiamore @lopezobrador_ mmm... A solidarizarse con Los Hijos del Chapo ?..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LTesta_ Happy Two Years Partner on @WatchMixer LT. Keep up the good work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So one of the best things about watching @IMPACTWRESTLING on @Twitch Vs Pop is definitely the quality and clarity of the broadcast on my TV!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelley_loewen @sianoresist @Eathbound420 Oh that’s right. Glad to hear. 👏]]></document></documents></author>