<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@willhenry321 @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump You mean, like, he’ll have time to Tweet? And play golf?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets @tolag The only journalist whom I would trust to be fair from Fox is Shepherd Smith. Other than him,… https://t.co/g34I6hmEYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattkamper1994 happy Valentine’s Day baby I love you so much with all of my heart ♥️ my one and only love and only… https://t.co/WE881j1pK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me acaban de pedir un presupuesto para una canción de un comercial y la pregunta que me dejó helado fue “¿Y para cu… https://t.co/CnaMOvK8UG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I #hiphopdance sometimes. Thanks for another great class @iamthedaisha!! 🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/gFRCCJxMBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s class was fabric painting. I tried my hand at a T-shirt:) #madewithmarabu allardsart marabucreativeusa… https://t.co/NqXJ6sC8TJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meetings Meetings https://t.co/esOoEvHRJy table sales for @AutismWorksNow #weworking #maximillian #charity… https://t.co/G1QfLBL8sa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now before you judge, I was nerve about posting this from my photoshoot I took in November. I never released this p… https://t.co/Saa2LnBAJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kathy: “what happened to my cake?” My dad looks up and in the corner and says “Well... it went to a good cause”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8rproof82 50 will be in the Circle. Move on and let’s go get some young killers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough loss... Final 59-55... great game. @Emekaemezie your sister had 16!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattyB0814 @CuomoPrimeTime Matt knowing the way Chris works it is easy to embarrass someone by putting them on the… https://t.co/59NdQqtC4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all our members that attended @SEATA Symposium this past weekend!! We had greAT CE’s, Exhibitors, Fund… https://t.co/JqPwKtZirE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on Cenk, what's the worse crime? Lying to Congress, or interrupting a rich, white lady's dinner?  #TYTLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is in charge of sellers ripping off customers, if you can't contact anyone except the seller? Doesn't Walmart a… https://t.co/JhHLMONaPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonCharlton99 @grist That is correct. The difference is that now we have cities built right in these vulnerable… https://t.co/Yt1UmXByVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SXMUrbanView Leave Ilhan alone Im a Jew and I question and oppose Isreal apritied policies against Palestinians]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EcoSenseNow @AOC AOC doesn't think before she opens her big mouth I think she just wants people talking about her… https://t.co/oAAzukbGoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomensDay is pretty cool. It reminds us to push ourselves to where women haven’t gone before. But it… https://t.co/r9UnnG12eb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will Gaby and Chloe ever know true peace? (Also I accidentally tagged the Dollar Tree I live next to????)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twisting his testimony?  Lmao, Cohen is a convicted felon  who has done nothing but lies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katlyn_2121 It’s sad I know who you’re talking about... she always drinks Dr. Pepper and she had red hair 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelle_ecoed @moorloc @MCole1008 @marlataviano @KEBrightbill I pasted “checkout” cards on the inside of the books.… https://t.co/OaxdUr9i2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpokeAna @AndreaCthatsme The child will bring love and you will share more love as parents together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DragonMom98 @SandiMarie79 @MsAFromBK @NashBillsBackrs @ByCharlieRicker @JustPlainT @lno09281978 @Jack_WanderS… https://t.co/qFytH2OyyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rexthetvterrier @SaniyyaSidney We can't wait for Enemy Within either...hope it's good or I w/b back for another referral.....Cali....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump I am so sick to death of the msm’s and demoncrats attacks against my President.When… https://t.co/xNtEwobz3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TakeThatCDC @GrumFromNorwich @EugeneBu @AndrewLazarus4 @Just4TheCause @VeritasEver @Boxmenot @itsmepanda1… https://t.co/bsYzKooNMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[me objectively looking at all the things i have accomplished in life https://t.co/U3EfsVhIbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexDonAudio Because I get the social justice aspect which is amazing. I was just curious! I haven’t heard many sp… https://t.co/sJmWj7biL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nynjpaweather 4 inches of heavy wet snow in Washington, Warren County NJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clemson_polk Because who wants to talk about a loser! Duke winning is the storyline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awww, thank you!! We always go early to watch warm ups and she loves when Seth dances, must have got it from his mo… https://t.co/n8gp5r3tVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our athletes are doing awesome things today! @SpecialOlympics @SONevada #SpecialOlympicsBasketball https://t.co/ysQdrfI3YV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimmythepooh @nancywyuen YOUR ANSWER MAKES SO MUCH SENSE.   I just need a hairline on him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RegalFamily @frivolouswhim Happy Birthday! I hope you had a fabulous day! 🙂🙂🙂🙂🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[rico came to see me before the gym, after the gym, brought me a hoodie sprayed in rico smell AND a piece of pizza 😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rinkbabe   These 2 morons are ignorant as heck. Because he was simply trying to simply ask if he could because he’… https://t.co/z52ol054Wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[despite what you think, you don’t need anyone’s opinion. self worth comes from within]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-LEGO Movie 2 dinner (...and cocktails) #datenight @ Tokyo sushi &amp; grill https://t.co/YnquFTP5OX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to I Want Candy (Remix) by @aaroncarter on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/GNFWL3nSbH https://t.co/1OXggcNAJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish armed guards could surround /follow these unbelievable creatures to keep them safe from butchering poachers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved catching up with this human yesterday and 💖watching her team play. Sending good vibes for the rest of OFSAA… https://t.co/fM4xvs4n5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heyyy guys today I got to assist/experience my first c-section. Life is great. Time for a nap. Sweet dreams 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hills are alive with the sight of poppies #BloomsAsFarAsYouCanSee #BlameItOnTheRain #LakeElsinorePoppies2019… https://t.co/dqeptGVM8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[En herradura te extrañoooooooo mil :(, estoy muy feliz de todo lo que haz logrado , TE QUIEROOOOO☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you ever just wake up sick and be like umm excuse me body i’m kind of busy the next two weeks could you come back later?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisperez4109 @jazmin_porfavor not even this weekend probably tomorrow LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you’re gonna date somebody, make sure that you date somebody with the same sleeping habits as you. I’ve been wat… https://t.co/U4opOmAcRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[In this Post Religious Age, Firever, make Your Place Church. It is, perhaps. https://t.co/LP5A8chepw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSoberOwlie @csioda1 @Scott719 @hauntedmuseum @Zak_Bagans @BurgerKing Haha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kelly praised Olson as Congress’s “boots on the ground,” saying she “never stopped working for the American people.… https://t.co/CacTrlDpiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Of course the cops will go free. They were white the kid was black in his mother’s backyard. This is terrible]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped by my cousins house after work.  This one here is as real as they come and I love her too pieces! ❤ @ Saint… https://t.co/zHGaWh8uRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aahhh @benhiggi season of @BachelorABC was my all time favorite! I can’t wait to watch this! https://t.co/8GST8XRuSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Charlotte, NC job and click to apply: EMPLOYEE RELATIONS ADVISOR (PARTIAL REMOTE) - https://t.co/pAgc7AJkZf #HR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Rebels JV Scores from #BOTGB Day 1:  JV Maroon 13 - Houston 1 JV Maroon 17 - White Station 1 JV White 3 - Coll… https://t.co/GPhuh6TxiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second, A MAN WOULD NEVER BE QUESTIONED ON HIS FACIAL EXPRESSION AT WORK. EVER!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mentionstacey_ No I’m saying when you claim exempt (for work) that means that nobody (your mom) can claim you on their taxes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 6 of seven of my favorite books. Today I challenge @ElisabethAlkier . https://t.co/oAovSCKYmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[What “John Wayne” said was disgusting indeed. Can’t deny that. But all this rage directed at a man long dead is a w… https://t.co/v5czlLZhDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[never believe that good things happen to me so when it goes to shit it doesn't suprise me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glambylauren @beautybay @Certifeye @ABHcosmetics @norvina1 @NYXCosmetics_UK @NyxCosmetics @TooFaced @StilaUK… https://t.co/b2N6jDQ4mp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferAydin what would your husband do if someone said to him about what Marty said to Joe? I'm sure he'd have t… https://t.co/0o1Zh4Czz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It‘s #NOMOREWeek Together we can end #SexualAssault and #DomesticViolence We can start by listening, caring, showin… https://t.co/xuK5QS6aFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸Con Sue Photography and Design🇺🇸   🇲🇼Like our photos...Follow our IG 🇲🇼  🇨🇱This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 🇨🇱… https://t.co/CZKbHYpqvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a Service Dog is so rewarding, but BOY AM I POOPED!! I want to thank each and everyone that came to see me, p… https://t.co/Ad4R3NThhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sebastian just felt the “first” hard kick from the outside of the womb. He was really offended and told me baby needs a time out 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Olympia Heights FL Fri Feb 22nd AM Forecast: TODAY Chance Of Showers Hi 85 TONIGHT Chance Of Showers Lo 75]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here for this. And on behalf of anyone with a brain that has any connection to Ohio State, I say fuck Jim Jordan]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy at the hospital pressed the wrong button on the vending machine and got a snickers so he gave it to Colin,… https://t.co/boJNZNhIAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL MÁGICO INSTANTE DE #COINCIDIR  Parafraseando la canción tantos siglos,tantos mundos,tanto espacio y coincidir no… https://t.co/aSRU8gUlNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have so much fun at @runDisney #princesshalf everyone! Wish I was there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNSitRoom @CNN @SenatorMenendez Why didn’t the democrats do it? Why didn’t the Bush do it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being by the water's edge inspires the writer in me. #OneSmartLadyWrites #writers #inspired #watersedge… https://t.co/kjyHZZSav4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me tweeting about a guy I talked to for a good two weeks!! https://t.co/znwnXO0Y4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NORTHER64691120 @BatNatalie @NewsJunkie60 @quicares @EmmaPeele3 @suz_hol @comehithercreek @FrizzleFelicity… https://t.co/10UnzSRudE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tsn @MStoner61 @MelnykEugene  you just said it  @tsnjamesduthie “IT DON’T MATTER”.  Ottawa just lost a whole bunch… https://t.co/TlhYBB6ASp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoDoSlayer @jeffpearlman @mattgaetz He wouldn't really pay you know. He has amnesia in regards to 99.9% of what he says.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Central Bank to meet Vostochny Bank shareholders Reuters reported that Russia's Central Bank will reportedly meet m… https://t.co/EPtstIUCxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn Using a quote from Mussolini- appears to be endorsement of fascism. Not a good look Senator. Perhaps yo… https://t.co/FEQDA0IskP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am calling in to work idc because there is over 2.5 ft of snow outside my house and I am not driving/walking through it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bumper cars are fabulous fun. A message from 747 Seminars taking off daily from #Ravenswood #longislandcityqueens… https://t.co/L2rMNoEdxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you're not making someone else's life better, then you're wasting your time. Your life will become better by ma… https://t.co/7KBLQgzkvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThinkingOutLoud Cod is a very wet fish... Well yeah. Its a fish. #Lent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InHisGripIRest I think you'll enjoy this! This is a group I've known for years from here in NC. https://t.co/sKpuH9fusp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magggiemayy @goldlions_ But do those jeans really spark joy Maggie?! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain America is my favorite super hero, but @ChrisEvans just ranked FRITOS above BBQ lays 😭💔💔💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think those two fans have always been on opposite side of the Rubio fence, FWIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sledding is fun!☃️ Sending me your fun videos MSilva@KVVU.com Have a wonderful Monday🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @PopeyesChicken, we ordered Cajun fries and instead received Cajun RICE and I have never been more disappointed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vin_440 i went into the bedroom and asked him how tf he slept through that and he was thoroughly confused and disoriented lmaooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Beyond the Dyslexia Pilot Teams presenting today @PaTTAN.  Look at Towanda Area SD’s FSF improvements BOY to MO… https://t.co/9uV6p8eIMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvorakoelling Beto. We need a younger generation not the same old white guys. Harris /Beto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRisNumber1 @PikaPriest @djwhitman34 @Barretto24_Mike @eaXLR @BeckyLynchWWE Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to one of my favorite ladies! May God bless your union and your life forever!]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/79rfgtE5f1  Our Amazon Phone Number has professionals 1-855-431-5111  #amazonphonenumber]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure you make time to see Jessica’s weather debut this morning! We are so happy to have her on our team!… https://t.co/s72o4XJtjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissioMusic Yes, there's like an imaginary line and of you cross it you can be arrested. True. I promise!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Utterly stunning view on decent into SLC. Thank-you geology! https://t.co/jGgOaz9nfM]]></document></documents></author>