<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Last night was whatever. Like on a scale from 1-10, probably a 6? Zero fun. @torikelly is just so-so. #JK… https://t.co/o6CvoOgOEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Rick And Barrel Coffee Stout by @brickandbarrel at @clebrewing — https://t.co/Iwxhs0CoJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blanket statements like this are laughable. How about the fact that she's never played a baseball game? Softball, s… https://t.co/XJ2QPtP76r]]></document><document><![CDATA[4x800 Relay Teams. #GoGovs @ Portage High School https://t.co/rZktB8Iev9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ken Jennings: What Alex Trebek Is Really Like https://t.co/taj0NWbSFZ h/t @taylorforan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Each piece matters and elevated mindsets can move matter.#reclaimingourboys @ Foundation Collegiate Academy https://t.co/YNvhNPysJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_Voris ...and we should not simply forget now that it is over. Many questions remain. Powerful prelates… https://t.co/Hvsjt150RN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ochocinco respect ya even more big dawg!!!! Your one of the FEW AND I MEAN FEW big time people that never forgot t… https://t.co/zGhxh0Hnce]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Be Employable Forever via @Getting_Smart https://t.co/aPuCmDVaH5 @tvanderark #futureofwork @OlinCollege]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. Starting day 2 of @StopSarcoidosis Ambassador training. Feeling better today than yesterday.… https://t.co/cyexizLPI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[RWD is too much fun.. i had a hard time deciding whether to try to go fast without spinning out or just see how lon… https://t.co/EBRGaSGxxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Porter_Anderson @RepSwalwell @HouseIntel @HouseJudiciary @AnaCabrera @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/hqYDWq7IBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[let me find out. my best filler i’ve ever worked with, requested off the entire weekend next week.... along with 2… https://t.co/ajByBZfckV]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’ve been uploading videos to the internet now for 13 months straight. I promise some of them are cool.   https://t.co/pHzDnoiahY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nick_ramsey @nytimes Chip off an old lying psychotic, lying subhuman p_g.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update on my new Flag Football league.  Started this to give kids here something special; pooling resources of loca… https://t.co/dWUCWcUATB]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you give horrible service, you don’t deserve a tip, just saying 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasmine26214594 Bout time to retire my Nissan also. We in the same boat sis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just now, someone in a Toronto Starbucks tried to justify Trudeau's leadership (which she did very poorly as there… https://t.co/QBHVHKVaLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[出去散个步，远远看到干干净净的公园马路上，不知道被谁随手丢弃的垃圾！而且只有这么一个… 走近看到这个…你说人家会怎么想？ https://t.co/vMdRtHaqWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DahhBigCat I don’t see the incentive to trade him unless they KNOW they can’t keep him, which seems unlikely]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come have a refresher before the @GopherMBB @GottliebShow https://t.co/WVCS4cSare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klaythompson shot the lights out 39 points and 9 triples #MileHighBasketball #DubNation   . . . #kevindurant… https://t.co/rhy2mGuBnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pedropinheirobr I learned more about that part of the Cold War in 2 plays than I had in almost 37 years of life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladysonder @CColose @PaulRoundy1 I've heard many climate scientists describe all this as inimical to our present c… https://t.co/SwkZzzGT0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I visited EPCOT yesterday. Check out what’s going on at the park.   https://t.co/nFGs7ZJoUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarineDone 2/ People forget that when someone has nothing but bad attributes, synergy can be as powerful as when s… https://t.co/NgPCzVn44J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Ummmmmmm the economy is looking GREAT with DJT @realDonaldTrump  as president. Why would we want systemati… https://t.co/WOay9g4J4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still waiting...Just give me 3.5 more years and $200K+ more debt.   Coming soon...😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[No way the #Eagles bring in DeSean Jackson and keep Nelson Agholor at his current number so buyer beware on the nostalgia card]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it weird that I'm more excited about the Motley Crue movie than the Elton John one? https://t.co/z22gQHQxrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AfterLife is brutally good. Laugh your ass off, then sob a minute later. Gervais is so on-point with the writing a… https://t.co/YX5c83xmPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @FOX61News @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487 @EMluvsPibbles… https://t.co/75zX3bPWoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottybeballin @CheezyMac_ You do know, you can literally call State Farm and get life insurance right 💀 or any in… https://t.co/XOogwJ9rQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@copypastepod really loving the show guys 👍 keep it up, hobo wine and all]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @TheNerdyVixen @iAprilJean @_AngelOfGrace_ @MaekaGaming @Zophael @melomesh @INFAMOUSchez @msZolenaGames… https://t.co/K71dfhPhnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello there my best buddys @ElvisDuranShow @babyhotsauce @ZscottyB  @Sam_Rosalie   How are you guys doing on this… https://t.co/ipF5TPzVFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeORLMagic @JoshuaBRobbins Last 2 minutes but the last 4+ minutes was flat crooked ref robbery]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch rush hour at Columbus north market! #naca19 https://t.co/mdYoKnbO8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[The academic procession has commenced.  #FOJ19 #HUCharterDay https://t.co/JKDzbv4qQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reproductive rights my ass. You mean your right to try to get women to kill their babies. I do not understand why y… https://t.co/aALTcsr3Ka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMek @FiveRights It's a world wide coup of liberty and freedom lead by secret society politicians.  Look at Aust… https://t.co/8M0zl6FjuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parents from the projects....Stateway and Ida B Wells to be exact.....Came along way from the ghetto....Grandma wou… https://t.co/d3wdcU196q]]></document><document><![CDATA[This.   Nothing about the US health system is optimized for the patient.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samuel_parish 1st role: Rean Miku from Machinima Series, “Sense Me Not.”  Latest Role (In Production): Eddie Lopez in “Fighting Spirit.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone: "I miss high school"  Me: @ Smithfield High School - RI https://t.co/eZQdGhetdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well this is pretty cool! Thanks for the mention @indieactivity @FlicksDaily 🎬 #StayTuned for more 😁 #comedy… https://t.co/mYeZZQTchi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOCpress For you to even say that shows that you are un-American. To bad your Democratic parents didnt educate you… https://t.co/Uet8MGhcCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpralle Bad week of sticks for Kings’ Tyler Toffoli.   No Whalers in sight. Either time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sky high in Colorado, our lips were pressed against plenty of bottles Already miss them too much . . . #Colorado… https://t.co/NDkyjqTcFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I strongly suggest you get your ticket for the WOW Festival concert March 15th @ApolloTheater w/ @alicesmithmusic S… https://t.co/H10QIDUKDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who in their right minds goes to Whiteville for pizza and DOESN’T get Pizza Village?!?! https://t.co/S7khKMcydm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii #deepstate is an delusion created by conservatives, as is the delusion that Trump is an effective pres… https://t.co/gz6MKeqmmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_RyanIngram @_AaronMoore_ Yup, those are both almost must gets. Crabtree is easily worth the $5, Tavon was just unreal]]></document><document><![CDATA[So anyway, the Galaxy S10 phone: - Third camera (wide angle on back) - Bigger battery on larger model - Will it fol… https://t.co/aTVc5lXVX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thromout @KasiaGTV @fox5sandiego It did not trip the circuit breaker, I am 95% sure this tweet was misleading.  If… https://t.co/h9iTZvUVYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jack75749305 @RickChathamMBA @Kevin_Faulconer All the time, man. I take my kids too. Yes there are homeless some times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate how camera makes you seem hella far when you’re actually really close at a concert :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yeah, good luck with that Nick. You're bishop may have wussed out in calling you out for what you… https://t.co/FEWKOdm5Ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of loud opinions on this on both sides. I’m not in the league right now so I don’t really have an opinion. But… https://t.co/JEqso3W9om]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StenhouseJr Novel concept the leader working around lappers and not bitching about them being in the way. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Who would’ve thought a man having furniture in his house is a turn on?!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a shame for Wildwood to lose on the wrong call at the end there, especially when it’s been called a charge all… https://t.co/pH0jHRrtbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Halloween_1014 @EnzosReviews @lisatoluna You should be https://t.co/OTCkuIUAXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greggprops @jessewente Name all the great Queen songs. Let me run and get a post it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @EdKrassen @KrassenCast So now it’s not enough to fact check- you want to profit with your podcasts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bernardshuford @THEJeepMafia @Jeep @TopJeepers @ItsaJeepWorld The batteries are mounted rest of the electrical to come for the add-ons]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very exciting and fun to serve @TroonWines to the media at the @oregonwineboard dinner tonight! Also a great pleasu… https://t.co/9ODlV4N99L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@priscilamtz13 Hahaha wey es que me tenia bien arto! 😤 pinché vieja horrible!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missnataliee_xo Good Morning Nataliee Hope you are doing well and slept like a baby  Me...been up since 1am lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big win today vs NWC to head back to the Final 4 for the second year in a row! #panthers #phhs #unfinishedbusiness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toarda I am a gamer and I want to be with you and your ambiguous plans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scifijunk @Jewelsquest Local concerns are not affected by rejecting standards. Why does separating local problems… https://t.co/wygUuw7spR]]></document><document><![CDATA[As long as there aren't any lefties on the set with me to push a socialist political bias and more #FakeNews.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For real some lady tried staying in DR all night though. Like wtf we want to go home.. smh today was eventful to sa… https://t.co/7HTmCmia6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nerd World Order Spoiler Free review of Captain Marvel #captainmarvel #nerd #iamnwo #spoilerfree  https://t.co/YVaSgSwsU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible testimonial this morning at @CareerSourceFL by a @KeyClubhouse thriver following mental health therapy.… https://t.co/41s2I3cUJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate people that lie. I promise that’ll be the number one reason I don’t like you no more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James_NoahJames I've never used one so I figure I would at least ask someone who has lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BbyBananaBreath okay so you are looking for a mommy 👍 that’s cool wish I was a mommy, you are super sexy!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@p0kal0pe @TmanSpeaks @StevenDickens3 @NeilCattermull @IBM @IBMcloud @TamaraMcCleary @digitalcloudgal Hey hey whoa… https://t.co/uexJwShi24]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aktualiak @o_crux_ave I misread it as “Donuts entomb is,” which is much more pleasant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottsavagelive @The_SportsPaige @AZCardinals This would be a Cardinal move]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WesLamar07 Exactly teach all the basics then go.. but you have to do it all the time but some time.. the key to co… https://t.co/4250OpQwtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoniaKont @RGAME2 @doug_schweitzer Completely agree that there need to be a tight focus on getting young Albertans… https://t.co/PMTxhbPeQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FNSLive @indianationFB @McEachernFtball Love this video so proud to be apart of this great team]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buschwhackers86 We’ll see. I’m just going to assume you guys will squander every opportunity you get until proven otherwise]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hatttiegladwell I often feel like a burden, but have "aged" out of most of the shame and guilt. "What are you depr… https://t.co/YMddUyPw6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews @Lmo66Olson Individual one and his administration obviously didn’t know that constitute in the lot toda… https://t.co/ouhm28ITE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[First concert with both my youngins! Thank you @MumfordAndSons https://t.co/sjYhB70AZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Varneyco WE /THE  PEOPLE WA-/BCDEFGHIJK/LL             WA-LL Including The Federal Reserve 12 dis… https://t.co/55BwAIvvKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop.....This is Buffalo Ranch Pizza .....Next up Penna Vodka Pizza with Chicken. #pizza #foodporn… https://t.co/TwlxgtKqZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picture Perfect . . Model @gucciwhore_  . . Photographer @MikeValen  . . Concept @gucciwhore_  . . #happiness… https://t.co/C3GgxbfFA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to my director @sadiebabits and the whole Sustainability Team for making this my favorite semester yet! We’r… https://t.co/ttxDZqdnYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReBourneAgain dammit is any of this stuff even real no it is predetermined colin you dumbass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryNocella @johniadarola If the life saved was your wife your child, mom or dad, yes it would be a big deal. You… https://t.co/hTjoi8J858]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck @Padres Money can’t buy you championships! That’s just crazy! Maybe you’ll win 75 games this year instead… https://t.co/gsBjHFonSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's happening? After months of negotiations, the Taliban’s leadership granted extremely rare access and protecti… https://t.co/Jff3HOkOhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LivePD what is up with drunk people tonight? Is it something in the #moon? Kudos to all the #officers that have to… https://t.co/In0NMrfi3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[6)  6. The Freeh Report is a propaganda piece that has no basis in the facts of the case]]></document></documents></author>