<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@lulex We should fix the lobbyist problem. Everything else will fall into place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FORT WAYNE,IN (FWA) ASOS reports gust of 54 knots (62.1 mph) from W @ 2258Z -- KFWA 242328Z 26032G48KT 10SM BKN029… https://t.co/PwZPX96q6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriotaRoja18 @RomelGuardian_ @dcabellor @RACpsuv @Fundacion_Agora @Expo_Portuaria @Inforojita @PSUVobrero… https://t.co/e178bRtir0]]></document><document><![CDATA[mahershalaali at #oscars2019 @ Tower Grove South, St. Louis https://t.co/QdfZ6SHEGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we can’t even get our line changes under control. This team has lost its nerve. Put a fork in them, they’re done. #CBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beckem1 @Drury7Drury I don't care what you think. I care even less what Merkel thinks. I've spent plent of time in… https://t.co/PQKcRfKWmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toejamandearl @Retr0Joe You know it baby! #switch #SwitcheShop https://t.co/weZ9ycHAlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hast thou not known? hast thou not heard, that the everlasting God, the Lord , the Creator… https://t.co/e0QH6s2E0I https://t.co/0IqwM6LUBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude I'm low key tearing up after watching Alex's video. It's like watching Bob Barker saying goodbye on The Price is Right 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWToday can you send a bus over to Kidani Village... those of us trying to get to the Magic Kingdom have been waiting 45 minutes now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a long while since I had sex that I shook my beer really hard so it would bust all over my face...🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonOsterburg @DGodfatherMoody @NatGeo The oscars is still a thing 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarverHighCBS We all need to see Ladd earn his contract its been a disaster too date thanks Garth]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite bands released a new single today. Looking forward to the entire record. @dangeroussummer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Don't worry he is just going to admit you committed Treason. I see why it looks like you haven't slept  :_)  #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alain_becile01 @Skeptic_j Profite-en pendant que tu as encore tes pneus à clous !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some Internet Campus prep for this weekend!  We’ll be talking about work as we continue in our series, “Marked for… https://t.co/cNwmAIExuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@westernokchaser @OKCFOX @okcfoxweather Where did you get this pic? Wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday!  Take charge, set some goals and attack the week with a positive attitude.  Have a great week peeps!… https://t.co/6ETX5N0ZAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarnabyandColby @winstonCovfefe @sxdoc Cuz it has better stuff than Somalia and I’m quite sure she’s had welfare a… https://t.co/MkaPpLlMWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMargaretS64 Unless of course if the judge is doing those years WITH the black boys he sold to the prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU PEOPLE has BEEN CONNED ABOUT THE TAX CON=THE TAKING YOUR MONEY AT THE IRS\RIPPING ALL YOU HARD WORKING PEOPLE F… https://t.co/ctRVfheSgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half: Walkerville 17, Manistee CC 16 (Boys District 108 Final) @HarrisonBeeby @MISportsNow @BankHoops @freeppreps… https://t.co/EQYDLXK4wV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning family: Life will only change when you become more committed to your dreams than you are to your comfo… https://t.co/NF4UmsSPnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TasteMyFrench1 @HBCUfessions #WomanCrushWednesday  💖💖💖 https://t.co/XwkGGwI9rV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doctormo77 @YouTube Interesting. I'm going to reserve judgment before seeing the actual movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are a #Bears fan and following me...you should be following @clubdubbearsblg I am now contributing here week… https://t.co/ttSJk807Ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wrathofgnon @Jonas_Sota don't worry about it, just start it and post it: https://t.co/xGcR65ojnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good advice. And a new #free #sign someone left outside. I snagged it to remind myself @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/BF4mNC9RHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danagould How's it going buddy? This winter has become a real ass kicker over here?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins @realDonaldTrump We couldn't be anymore blessed than to have this man as our President. If not for Pres… https://t.co/f1pEVq1ocW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatLadyStardust @peta I don’t think they’re in the business of being polite, rather shining the truth where people… https://t.co/dEc5fBPuPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking to Action: Art, Pedagogy, and Activism in the Americas https://t.co/2wtgFI9gF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rocket7k @IGN Wow! I didn’t Michael Bay was directing Marvel movies before this! Where have I been! Grow up, that movie was awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summer where are you, I want to train in the heat again 😫. #coloradoproblems #runnerproblems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@surfnutsc2 @1hodor3 @pjbowles4 @DoingRight1 @RealWolf72 @ElaineEbk @sweetrtweetrD @killabeas69 @tampet66… https://t.co/a8uZ8M41Qh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Boulders Inn &amp; Suites By Cobblestone Hotels Newton, IA https://t.co/2h4cZDJk1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[We do not know how to live in clarity because Sin creates Chaos and Confusion. #Coachval #MyChurch #SundayMorning… https://t.co/OZHOsbIwkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StanfordBishop, are you another Black #Gatekeeper #Politician?  #REPARATIONS2020  #Tangibles2020  #BlackPolitics… https://t.co/YvPFKaeD7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Just say that you want the borders to be open for passage by any number of criminals and terrorists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PabloCarrilloL @Javier_Alarcon_ @Diana_vucetich @elancheyta si realmente es un equipo grande no hay escusa decir a… https://t.co/fxnvGouHPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help I have a problem and it’s called I can’t stop buying stuff for my dog]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man Dies After Subway Train Drags Him Into Tunnel: The 39-year-old man apparently became caught as a Queens-bound s… https://t.co/OLcrzRIa9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karrrrli Lol what was bad? Had a great sear. Assume it was cooked how he wanted it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisAmick I’ve been kicking around an idea, maybe you can help me flesh it out. It’s a series about a cool, funny… https://t.co/26Ii91YdNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 65 of the One Year Audio Bible Experience. God sets rules for skin disease in mildew in the home. Jesus foretel… https://t.co/TuhGgJT0f6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtkrpm @4YrsToday You say "Lock her up" on your profile. Hillary didn't do anything. The Russians, at Trumps request, hacked her server.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJlikestoplay @MedianPolitics @nypost It’s not defamatory when it’s true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbhthesequel Or do they confuse a visiting houseguest into thinking it’s their feeding time when they were fed two hours before?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nine times out of 10 I love the outdoor press box at Red Bull Arena. This is the 10th time @ Red Bull Arena https://t.co/PKJSJM5Wqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougboneparth I completely understand, when my wife gave birth to twins 3 years ago it was very hard on me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took my break extra early to hear #FridayTurnUp @Mrs_R3con78 @TheWoodyShow @MENACE @Ravels @GregGory987 @nick… https://t.co/n0Z9x09dVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScoutWithBryan Also, it is a big deal because their best player is promoting bad habits to a young core who he ope… https://t.co/vq6WY1lhmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shutthefkupdon1 @NathanLerner Omg patients???? Jeez Louise you must be a doctor or something. How could I have been so wrong about you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodmorning Family and Friends. Be Blessed! @ Browns Summit, North Carolina https://t.co/1dpQwPLUW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matisyahu I want to thank you for your music! When I listen to it I feel like something inside me has reignited, I… https://t.co/VIduNEmRLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeSherman Strict Mistress Nancy has always seen herself as the permanent Secretary of State. She was FIRST to ve… https://t.co/4V8N8cMvf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our products include 3D photo crystals, LED light bases, stone slates.... See offer - https://t.co/gKXTy0kJC3… https://t.co/0XDHPTvgzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyaMalinowski Excellent article, Great read, Very Very well written. Thanks @TonyaMalinowski I never knew about… https://t.co/mdtCvXhKGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @LAFitness - sat at your Graceland location for 30 mins. Nobody decides to show up this morning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pin cost you,,,,may have some good green,,,,rivers,,,,hu,,l.o.l https://t.co/kXMEpKEOWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I promise after I get my phone fixed Im gonna keep the screen protector on it this time. For real.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost positive_quotes_positive_mind with get_repost ・・・ Tag👇👇 everyone who need to see this❤️. __ Follow us for m… https://t.co/1SdnlOKG9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanchyAlmonte @Bombi3030 @arielgonzalez79 @Profedeportes #BeProfe team. El olor a bollito llega aqui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uncommitted @BlackSox_Ohio infielder @7lewisjoseph (@Xenia_Baseball, 2020) — #BoScoutDay https://t.co/dswIPkBeHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmazingInsights @IslesRealist @EHawk75 @JoshBarely I didn't say he was elite...I said he was solid...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HilaryKimMorden @DaveH_RPh @Skywtchr @rlamartini @mard55859518 @Iamchronicpain @LelenaPeacock @headdock… https://t.co/OcbFRm7nmj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RollingStone It's funny all you media folks believed the 4Chan white power "ok" symbol too...  So now what?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisWeekABC Explain this... Another high tech dirty trick from the Dems affecting elections.. incredible, if you d… https://t.co/frcwPOrr3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andyswaff @BunkiePerkins @JasonKirkSBN Yes. Yes I did. https://t.co/GfKn6Yh53q]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALF — @NBHurricanes 43, E.O Smith 20. Twenty turnovers in the half really slowed things down for the Panthers. https://t.co/hvuGyNQ8hX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I host another #Meetup game of Cashflow last night.We had the biggest turnout. We may need a second board and venue… https://t.co/hO1sx0gNYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful stuff from the Plymate, Groner and Brown labs providing further insight into AR-V7 biology in prostate ca… https://t.co/tCNDls7pOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm the trouble starter, punkin' instigator I'm the fear addicted, a danger illustrated I'm a firestarter, twisted… https://t.co/G7FPqc7UCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RutgersMBB @Hassel_Chris This is absolutely hilarious. Give it up to two teams willing to see at the end of the da… https://t.co/Y272in6Lg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY THERAPY   my grandson Isaiah @ Frank C for the Second Quarter Honor Roll Assembly😎 @ Frank C. Martin K-8 https://t.co/6Jj1e1oJXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NLLBandits Knighthawks...so bad at lacrosse...you think they would be better at fighting....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tintie4 @stphnmaher Agree. What are the horrendous things that have happened than everyone is losing their minds o… https://t.co/oD6NNvtTW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get better soon @chibbs_1 New York and Baltimore ballers are praying for a speedy recovery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what happens when we show up to vote. Do it in 2020 like we did in 2018, and the GOP is toast for a decade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mesmoudh @FUTUREPLANSSS Omg hi mini-Leibovitz 🥺 *explodesintorainbowunicorns*]]></document><document><![CDATA[No 🧢 but that @2chainz album is trash 🗑 no trap songs. No hard ass beats. Bars all ok. Kendrick didn’t spit shit on… https://t.co/4uQgOY7GgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perks of having an Italian gf:  1. You can eat all the garlic you want, and she’ll still want to make out with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy winds + trash cans is making the streets of SF turn into NYC on a trash day https://t.co/j0RcOGfl5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenannarhi But they already boarded us so now in this small ass space for what’s gonna be 7 hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love #NOLA! I dont wanna go back to #Jersey! @ French Quarter - CBD, New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/lBhkJy7N30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ John Prince Memorial Park https://t.co/2irkjJo2Zt]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD ....MATT (SLEAZEBALL) GAETZ IS NOW UNDER INVESTIGATION .......SHOULD HAVE STAYED OUT OF THAT HEARING ROOM TODA… https://t.co/un6fY3VQME]]></document><document><![CDATA[God has given us the Holy Spirit to accomplish two works in our lives: First, to bring us to salvation and cleanse… https://t.co/U2vFEFL5pH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LyndaVargas Muchas felicidades Lynda  y desde aquí recibe un abrazo cariñoso, hoy en tu día, cuídate mucho .... 😉 https://t.co/bezdLbMdcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  the USA already funds the state that Hates Christianity so much that the Christian UN that chartered to the l… https://t.co/GAG3LR2vLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJetOnTNT and @_CharlesBarkley just predicted the @trailblazers will be in the NBA Finals.  Something nobody wou… https://t.co/zCQt9FuG1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old superheroes &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; New superheroes 👊🏽. https://t.co/qWeDogsgbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @AOC maybe AOC is thinking that if she comes up she can use this case as a defense for reducing her sentence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackiemccaffrey @nikoCSFB @McscNetwork I think Niko shared the Emerson poll the other day.  (One on the right is t… https://t.co/c64m3B5xCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m over here turning up minding my business when my friends are hitting me up telling me that my raiders got @AB84 holy shit 😱dowtown]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% of what I post is for me God does over an abundantly more then I could ever ask for so... #Bigdoggpinc  Just s… https://t.co/TwMdOaoZAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LloydN @realDonaldTrump Offense. Not offence. https://t.co/ZCty5XLKTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chad Johnson lot Quantum Leaf RC Jersey /250  $3 https://t.co/3aZDYWkV2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaIDonnaSiciIy I have meet a lot of sorry lying people in my life time but never one like Trump]]></document></documents></author>