<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Takes less than a minute to show your support and help persuade our elected officials! #HealthEd #PhysEd… https://t.co/N3msxuHZbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump SOME of The republicans are  SPINELESS and do nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I’m learning from All the President’s Men is that in 1972 you could just walk into people’s houses and they would give you coffee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frodofied @HillaryClinton @realDonaldTrump Media is as contaminated with greed as are many politicians. Ratings=mo… https://t.co/h7sALZj0MW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amigos cada día trae su propio afán. Disfruta cada día y no te preocupes del mañana.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Weren't there many that stated they would leave if trump won?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh look my dead father sent me an email.... #suckithacker https://t.co/i0Gy6vNZHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[My goal was to come inside from work and go to sleep... That didn't happen. I wanted to do things and leave the hou… https://t.co/0G3089DXZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y mañana regreso a ese domingo de sumar kilómetros. Cadena de oración para que Todo salga bien 🙏🏻  #CerroDeLasNoas   #BuenasNoches]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been Republican since I was 18 years old because I'm against abortion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess now my favorite Korean drama is more relatable ?? https://t.co/2BzrJ0MH7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, some of our interns are attending a Pack Preview in Fayetteville, NC! It is so much fun getting to meet pers… https://t.co/CQ3wNK8H2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rbrtpnc @ABC Truly devoted to the orange blob? Is his head screws on straight?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Walt Disney World Vacation! https://t.co/12ffNBYFvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love wearing women’s swimsuits almost as much as wearing women’s dresses 👗 @ Levittown, New York https://t.co/uSZaXdXIhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you have a destination you’d like to promote? Check out my collaboration page and give me a shout! I’m filling u… https://t.co/LOhyiwZUK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traded in running shoes for TV time with a superhero this morning! 🌟 • • #itscasual #thatlldo #sorrytriplecrown… https://t.co/7XdyD1yVfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[From a year ago. Spring break in Ohio. Hoping not to wear mittens this year. @ Bexley, Ohio https://t.co/ywhPkYVyki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMcInnisDIT I’d say yes; it gets more competitive each year as there are more graduates and comparatively fewer j… https://t.co/seV0jzuzVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherNation 🙄 his crisis management PR team is doing an excellent job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has espn ever made a bigger deal about an injury over a college basketball player? Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for sharing your popcorn TJ! @ One Night For One Drop @Oiladvocate cirque https://t.co/OpFfQYkJXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoriGodek @cardenasclayton @MayansFX @ReaperGalNorCal @Ah_May_Zing_ That looks like the look you get when you're t… https://t.co/cO3VkeP6th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamCerdeira Una imagen habla más que mil palabras! https://t.co/tlza7bJwVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nick_bennett11 Hope you brought your drinkin shoes😂 They don't call it black friday for no reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sorry to my neighbors, bc my mom turned up the TV’s volume to 100 as soon as @QueenWillRock started performing. #oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[A young the giant song was in thursday night’s episode of greys anatomy what are the chances]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leme go bk to bed now this lil dog wanna eat then play like no sir go bk to slp now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big THANK YOU to our SAC chair @MikeCiteraRN ⭐️ For 2 years, you have led the council with great care and dedicatio… https://t.co/k08bCtmuqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget your sheets tomorrow @WesternUnionES Eagles! #BeTheBest #Literacy4U #BooksandBrackets https://t.co/5tSnXBgVdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ll be real: I didn’t like the jonas brothers as a kid and it kept me from socializing with a lot of girls my age… https://t.co/8bRY40eccE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rosenstein's Revenge: Trump To Fight 100 Duck-Sized Horses https://t.co/Qk2xUdHzgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rodeo 🍾 Uncorked Best Bites Winners @RODEOHOUSTON @713News  #RODEOHOUSTON #RodeoUncorked #bestbites #713news https://t.co/Jfae7TUiuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heather_reindl @cmclymer I go buck wild when I'm by myself with the music (love me some Tupac) but with Motown you… https://t.co/hZTimmwApa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read my own story again and then had to soup up. Peppery pork ball @ Ha VL https://t.co/GYGM3172VX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google’s tribute to Steve Irwin’s 57th birthday has got me cryin in my office rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HADLEY_PANZER54 @spedbraet @CoachCRiles @CoachKli Lookin’ good Hadley!!!  EMAW!! 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Itz up #SavageTies Artist Showcase Monday March 18th at #DjsClubEliteBr Sponsored by #SupaUnit #SavageLife… https://t.co/aVDPGEH0LH]]></document><document><![CDATA[M.Bonnardel sait faire bon usage du Centre intégré instauré par les Libéraux.👍👍👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atingngpex @soompi hayup kkdating ko lng nyan ... cge cge magtira ko para kay rowoon at chani hahahh]]></document><document><![CDATA[funny internet memes #mirth #tee-hee #smile #clever https://t.co/q29a7L6m0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #TrumpBlackmailing #TrumpDespisesTruth #TrumpRacist #TrumpRussianCollusion #TrumpFakeEmergency… https://t.co/fnq9O9nJ3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickyDavila I believe Trump owned an escort service that Melania worked for, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beatles fan returns 1968 copy of Life magazine to public library he stole it from as a kid. He included a $100 mone… https://t.co/NsI16EGL7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2. Our game is later so we're enjoying the early games. #BackTheBirds #REDBIRDhoops #RedbirdTwitter #4in4… https://t.co/BrNE7WlgiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@overtaxed23 Let me see if I can get some better answers for you. @ColleenLindsay Do you know who can answer this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Collection is growing #nailpolish #naillacquer #stamingpolish @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/b4rTwR5hlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I peep, that’s all that matters. I’ll let you know i’ll always be ahead of you when you try to compete with me thou… https://t.co/zxFtxKtMqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Disney's Animal Kingdom - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/itHwqzW4IL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alimariemeadows Oh haha another classic 🤣 Just make a song with the drug names and you might remember them lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if I get traps from doing P90X  These are the things that keep me up at night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Number_Keeper @RadioFreeTom @joncoopertweets Naw just fried his brain somehow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man really just stopped in the middle   Of merging traffic to give us anxiety ads look and we’re al about to die… https://t.co/QFhqrDs6Ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow English professor is really failing me right now after I had a valid reason 🙄 what a bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Houston! @KHOU is giving away tickets to see @Pink at the Toyota Center in March. Enter to win! ➡️… https://t.co/DXb0T3YrAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @BCBSAZ for hosting @Sierra4AZ and me as we celebrate extraordinary youth served by the  @BGCMP. Such ama… https://t.co/qyvR8SjBwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DillionHarper I can’t believe how badly I miss your shows. I’ll be in San Diego this weekend. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Assyria cannot save us, nor can our warhorses. Never again will we say to the idols we have made, You are our gods.… https://t.co/X0ermtNvpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because people do not understand they use the word socialism incorrectly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shesabrasive Really?  I would have thought that...  so what initial was it? I can't believe anybody else there wou… https://t.co/Mqm9xsSehx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday y’all!! Come on out TONIGHT!! The upper valley is once again complete with the NEW season aceitunasb… https://t.co/bMG9l85kpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day in the office ! #livestockcommittee #rodeofamily #complianceteam @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/dvo3YJw6pA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on my 5 year plan and my company is really wanting me to consider relocating to Michigan.....in 3 years Add… https://t.co/AfPdehrSw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely sophomore ladies of South Cobb HS at their 1st Science Olympiad Regional competition! They were very serious… https://t.co/ETS3ZsfA7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkahne I'm so sorry for you and your wife's loss. Sending loads of love to you both. Xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anderson_Astros AHA family Jump rope night! #ALLin4Aldine https://t.co/IDX9OSPlC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pleasure, @CFES2ndRedBirds! I can’t wait to “buy” goods or services at your marketplace! #PBLinFCPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I formally request that whenever anyone texts me to please use a screen effect such as confetti or fireworks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobRosen14 @norskepike55 @TheDeadFilesTV @amyallantdf @stevedischiavi @travelchannel Yay!! thank you so much @RobRosen14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robcesternino @ArmstrongTaran @lashtweets Ah, the recap of the recap!  I have to admit, I fell asleep early and mi… https://t.co/JyWoIEeXLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both of my kids (ages 20 &amp; 17) love the Oxford comma. My job is done. #momwin #grammarnerd #longlivetheOxfordcomma]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WikiLeaks #CometPingPong #Obama #Podesta #JamesAlefantis #PizzaGateIsReal https://t.co/hVBFtBHqTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smalltownandrew @daahmom @GOPLeader @HouseGOP Your lack of action to stop her vile racist comments against a Jews is disturbing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ScienceInTheNews Monday! Checking the weather on #Mars Students also listened to Martian wind. Thanks @NASAInSight… https://t.co/tAZ2tAPjAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[As border battle rages, NYPD on high-alert over ‘serious’ MS-13 threats to target off-duty officers https://t.co/DRWHWm7NNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATMess33 @ebourque7 I saw Potted Potter a couple of weeks ago and one of the best lines was "If Dumbledore was the… https://t.co/71tddRT5IM]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUSEUM DAY WITH THE FAM 😛 @ The Franklin Institute https://t.co/mSXdsJMqLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[my lyft driver: don’t eat meat me: oh okay are you vegetarian? lyft driver: no i’m christian me: ...oh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JazmineLewisXo Invite please  I need to do it!! We were good friends before..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ow @BrunoMars singing the word "please".....gaaawwddd damn!! https://t.co/zsKQdrHXJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BevDiane @corsetmaster1 @MichaelAvenatti 💯 Bev. For 4 years, I went to a lot of parties that looked like that and… https://t.co/J7bEsY3sMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RationalEye @TheeAndyMcGill @PJTormey @PebusPebus @DevinNunes P.S. ..I like your profile pic 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[#8B4 is getting some new stamps and I am super excited! #hpteacher #scienceteacher #quickcheck #stampassessment… https://t.co/kwj36gdZ9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryangrim @Ilhan Yo stupid.. with hate and feeling about the Jewish people she has no business being in committees]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetoORourke  If you get into the race,I will make calls for you and I'm sorry I can't knock doors but I've broken… https://t.co/rOnwtAeKXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janatoliver @chandra_perkins @lester_laminack Love this book!!!! And Lester for that matter! Baylor Literacy Conference ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing, how a different perspective can change the world you live in💕👍💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs LORD, God, Cover President Trump with the Blood Covenant of Jesus Christ Every Day for his Protectio… https://t.co/ozD8BfZvUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the type of thing I love seeing on Twitter - friends supporting friends and helping to promote their full-t… https://t.co/DzE0C92l3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomLazorik @RoArquette So you are saying you think Wade is lying because he remembered but stayed silent? I stayed… https://t.co/SNqVy23tQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man told me to sit on his face three times tonight https://t.co/AzT3YJbr9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rightofmiddle21 @AD_WHITMAN Agreed.  But House of Cards was based on someone....]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we had forgotten the name of our God, or spread forth our hands to a strange God, would not God discover this? F… https://t.co/jlmAlDs0Ly]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t close all the closets in your room before going to sleep you’re asking for a monster to jump out and kill you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Try for 3 hours to go to sleep. Falls asleep for 45 minutes. Wakes up, wide awake, thinks to self “I think I got a… https://t.co/mjhFsvAMKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing so undercuts the idea that courts are impartial deciders, Arpaio’s attorney Jack Wilenchik said.  In appointi… https://t.co/zCcBbFdnAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralCringe @SheriffClarke Again, what black persons are you referring to???  Seems to me you are saying all thu… https://t.co/rTq7pyncFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[With prayer, God gives us the grace to conquer all our hurts, and frees us from all fears, prejudices and hatred. W… https://t.co/rX9R1d1zMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear landlord, please allow cats on our lease because look how happy we both are ): https://t.co/tZ0a7Hqgj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to know more about #Brahms #EinDeutchesRequeim ? Take a listen to the interview below! @AustinSymphony 's musi… https://t.co/9HGpt446hn]]></document></documents></author>