<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[the hardest thing i had to do in lofe was leave you. i was showing you love it had you feeling like i need you😅🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop retweeting those fake ass sugar daddy accounts. No one is giving away money like that 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 Ahhh because he wasn't President during 911....oh the stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[16 more days (and 12 hours) until the next release date... @NASBA  #soverylong #forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank You @springboardw   So true. Thank you @DebCE for pointing me to her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LupulinBrewing I NEED a shirt w/ this @LupulinBrewing skull logo 💀 - is this possible?!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VisitDublinGA I remember this from when I lived in home sweet home...wish I could move back!!!Go Irish!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok #MaskedSinger when is season 2? I need it now! I love this show so much!! 😱❤️🙌  @JennyMcCarthy @NicoleScherzy… https://t.co/wL6kzIWrlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[No todas queremos NI debemos tener hijos, gracias! https://t.co/5x17UbDl2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @Chris3BM @courtneym8216 🌿Good morning friends. Have a great day🌿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbyAsen @juliettep0rter @SiestaKey @thekelseyowens I seriously need to their workout routine..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Ammallon and @SumbulSidd for your caring leadership and commitment on behalf of our homeless residents a… https://t.co/vZAznfOK0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISMRaceway @JimmieJohnson HAVE A BLAST BOOM CONFETTI JOHNSON  .AND GO GRAB THAT CHECKED FLAG CHAMP 👌☝️👊🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[I celebrate this almost everyday but it’s nice to have it recognized!#NationalNappingDay https://t.co/a6QO0rxbCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmAzInGMe22 I neeeeed to hit my weight goal Lolol ok I’m not drinking until my birthday but I’ll make an exception for yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSolariReport Your true vote is when, where and to whom you pay your money. #Votewithyourdollars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicIris @carlosnajarraba Son de los mismos, pues los venezolanos comentan, que Chávez,  llenó de cubanos Venezuela… https://t.co/vh62glBbpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing my family this week was the best thing i could’ve asked for. my mood is recharged 👩‍👧‍👦❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly, fast, fabulous way to fly! #iFlyAlaska #AlaskaHappyHour @AlaskaAir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emrazz Let me guess: Capt. Jack Sparrow impersonator who hangs out at Hollywood and Highland hustling tourists for photos.. .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Sunday Morning!...worshipping the Lord at one of the oldest and historic black Catholic churches @ St. Augusti… https://t.co/12aju5eZsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are black history making history #Periodt  #twins #twinpreneurs #twinchefs #nowurcooking https://t.co/irirvjzbOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raise your hand if you received a baby gift,Christmas present, and valentines candy today  🙋🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathleenodean @annbradenbooks @Jarrett_Lerner These titles are Diversity at its finest!! Thank you for your consistent “Book Love”👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[For justice, for freedom! Alive, alive, oh! #1919BostonArrests #MApoli https://t.co/SYoflroKb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder They just keep trying to change our laws to fit with what they need, do not let this pass]]></document><document><![CDATA[my cousin is getting married tomorrow and let me just say i’m way too excited for the chicken parm im gonna be chow… https://t.co/JU2rCDsziB]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you knew how hard it was and and how long it took to rebuild my little universe of peace and happiness then you… https://t.co/C1rHjuAZxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmoschetti @cnnbrk @MSNBC It’s a nightmare all over again. He is so destructive for his own gains. Don’t know why… https://t.co/Nd8dZkXXWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It drove Marge Simpson to drink but personally I love hearing a bunch of machines do housework that would’ve taken… https://t.co/KtBuoUJ4pT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are y’all also feeling anxious about how long this intro song is!? Lol #GC2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@867x5309 In your situation that makes total sense, but atleast the Mom is on there second, he didn’t put Kail on t… https://t.co/pzQpglyQrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to be queen for a min in the #gameofthrones throne! Not a bad way to end my Vegas trip. #workisdonefortheday @… https://t.co/CK3nOhVQJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Terrorist, who the hell would vote for someone like that.  Other terrorists.  Re -count]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow day no. 5! Work was cancelled all week Lol ❄️  And we have no work this Monday... wow🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo más bonito de ya no salir con alguien es que puedes dormir tus ocho horas seguidas 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot a very important update. Councilmember Foley said that she will be “twittering” soon!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[BEST OF LUCK NHS TIGER DIVERS as you Spring into Sectional action this morning at Noblesville. #TigerPride #webelieveinyou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Floodwood/Duluth bound today, if I can convince myself to leave my blanket cocoon 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[no greater joy than finding your friends dating app profile and they’re using photos you took of them to represent their hotness :’-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jd and cheeks was tryin to get me to come to the hookah lounge last night for Dj bucks birthday.......ummm no would… https://t.co/2ATHJZT94U]]></document><document><![CDATA[May the God who gives endurance and encouragement give you the same attitude of mind toward each other that Christ… https://t.co/GtxVfYqz8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveTONJohns3 @Hermann22 @MarvelNewsCast I’m seeing it tonight too!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reagan_kristin @GOP @realDonaldTrump You mean how many causuties have come from the fruit of the poison tree..I ho… https://t.co/8SjexgBOIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMiear Actually wondering if you have to close now because people may have seen that on WSLS??? Are you required to?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NXDBUDDY @gwenstefani @halliediamond Has @blakeshelton even seen a @nodoubt concert?! Because there is nothing lik… https://t.co/kXOSuHDNPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carinreese Good luck with the wedding plans! Congrats on the engagement! Thank you for the birthday wishes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody: Emma Chamberlain: hi guys I don’t shower I’m so quirky and relatable look at my caffeine addiction LOL what’s hygiene🤪🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your brain is broke. The problem is, Trump can’t go to the bathroom without Putin’s okay. (Nope, still sounds absur… https://t.co/4wkCELsDmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imJGott @AOC You know it’s annoying when you can simply look this up before tweeting asinine comments. Trump donat… https://t.co/X6rDm2Moqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Guys - get out your to do lists and write this one down.  @julesyoga teaches how to enjoy yoga in a way that’s… https://t.co/Vbh3e8ZqnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cos we don’t care about the likes contours or people’s opinions and attention #enjoyingthemomentsss https://t.co/07pz4nrWSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[With every word she speaks she shows that she is the divisive one.  Too inexperienced to be in the position she is.… https://t.co/zRO1OdXQc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Willow Grove Park Mall in Willow Grove, PA https://t.co/qivp1ozblT]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨Video shows man attacking attorney in court after getting 47-year sentence https://t.co/3pAyuISqkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time at #BWTTCon2019 with this crew. @diversefounders @SamsungNEXT #NEXTdiversefounders #ganggang https://t.co/EJzPEsgg3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Told ya I am.waiting for my white privilage and reparations too https://t.co/7wqeaeGsdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Cosmo school this girl who’s been picking on me recently was parading around that she’s a virgin, so I told her… https://t.co/am3PJqhHQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey,  Take Your Favourite Gift Card Offer By A Complete Simple Sign Up   Click Here: https://t.co/y2UazxBM5p… https://t.co/gSysp5tTur]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh but I just can't forget all the evil things the #Democrats have done in just the last year.. let us not forget… https://t.co/1x9ELI4heo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigsullyt Don’t let your brain get the best of you! You may think so but I promise you’ve touched many people in y… https://t.co/gb1rdOOEHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is disappointing when you’re really hungry and you look at the clock and it’s only 11am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@healthmediagal1 @mfarca @DevilsEnvySpice That’s what I thought Lisa but a little bit of both would’ve been okay too 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_krismarisol @JeffreyTheGreek @capuchinster @_youhadonejob1 Nope. Not without a fish.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fear is not relevant if you believe in God!  Ha 🥰🙏🏽👌🏽 @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/o65KeOvoqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[After school yesterday find him here a new favorite spot to lay and listen to his tunes 💙🎼 @ Barnesville, Ohio https://t.co/5XxSKqYzbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gorgeous dress hung from the one of many incredible views @lacasaofmasoncreek! Wedding dress: @camillelavie  .… https://t.co/2NxSM1Ouss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turbotax hey your site is giving me the error message on the college tuition refund for no reason i’m a full time… https://t.co/vy6OdPSx63]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tfdeaston I just can't stay away! 😍 @ The Farmer's Daughter https://t.co/R4WIDg6RFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Wade Robson Project - Michael Jackson Tribute https://t.co/dykxOMhpvG via @YouTube this dude had a show and did… https://t.co/74BDTaKkYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zelliej1 @LidsRodney The understandable desire to explain how or why someone could perpetrate a heinous crime like… https://t.co/erbDG1IddW]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s no better way to spend #ValentinesDay2019 than with a blood drive for @commitforlife Come stop by if you ha… https://t.co/Q15MxuyayT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch Unfortunately SCOTUS Ginsberg is known to review the cultures of the countries defendants that have come b… https://t.co/wlnKOhdtjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I surprised? No. Tie the bow tie a little tighter, would ya Fucker...I mean Tucker?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngusMcPussPuss @catsrule0 @vroberts9 @lynda3035 @Tonithecat32 @fluffybasil @SassyCassyCat @BloomNight2… https://t.co/cD3eOFEy7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Education is more than teaching people to think - it is also teaching people things that are worth learning.” Hattie #visiblelearning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khwaja_adil @emmawatsonnet @EmmaWatson @EmmaWatsonPage @emmawatson_news @emmawatsonperu @EmmaWatsonIndo… https://t.co/EhQzek77sC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perlmutations @JosephOConnell3 Is that man related to honey booboo. I see a definite resemblance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your office is a miracle for my PTSD panic-  your nitrous + full numbing + blanket/neck/head pillow etc is lifesavi… https://t.co/B2RhdtEH99]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your life is your message to the world. Make it inspiring.- Lorrin Lee⁣⁣⁣ ⁣⁣⁣ What will be your ‘message’ to the wo… https://t.co/N7IoD1bgPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz Miércoles!😀Disney Cruise 🚢 Line recién anuncia: ¡Itinerarios de verano 2020! *Cálidas aguas💦 azules y diversi… https://t.co/QUjoLYj1uZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[In order for you to grow you have to stop watering DEAD situations.  💯💯💯💯  Sometimes you gotta GO so you can GROW… https://t.co/PoF4yid7Gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red 🌹 Violets are blue 🔵 Patient Safety isn't always easy 🤦🏻‍♀️ But we're always here for you 🙏… https://t.co/psqnfHSIa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TortureTulsi knew it was torture when she participated I'm conversion therapy.   @TulsiGabbard is not your friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really getting worried with the lack of updates on Luke Perry. I hope he’s ok and will get well soon #PrayersforLukePerry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_kasper23 yup. I use Pinterest for all my storyboards, books, and characters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flwrgirl66x @Sheeple101 @regnans @1blessedbee @alkemikah @ArcaneKnowledge @Just2BiZI @JackCDLee @4everleather1… https://t.co/uFqb4O6bjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton Dumb and dumber. The designations are interchangeable based on comments from either one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cliff is right! Talk issues not personality...and stop blaming poor old Bernie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff Did you write this?  Why do you blatantly lie about Southern border issues now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[And my work week begins... it's a tough job, but somebody has to do it. 🤷🏽‍♀️🤷🏽‍♀️🤷🏽‍♀️ #AgentOfChange #ITQ2019… https://t.co/sjB22fQVhK]]></document><document><![CDATA[And more charges against him after today. A felon now he is and a liar. Zero merit  and credibility . Schiff told t… https://t.co/hvqzj9y6aa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld He is totally supported by his party so I don’t think he will care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's weird when I get lost in life I have to remember W.W.J.D.  What Would Jussie Do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will there be another summit with North Korea? @UnderSecT says she hopes so. #NukeFest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mandos_Mundo @gilalvie10 Are those happy tears or sad tears because I wanna punch him🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you a permanent makeup/microblading artist looking to build a solid book of business in a prime location? I am… https://t.co/T0R7Reb9XS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Son.... walking into manhood..... SAT test🥺....College is just around the corner https://t.co/YWa9YZdfH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TamBouret Omg it is SO UNEVENTFUL down here!! And it’s not even pleasantly uneventful; it was literally 90 degrees… https://t.co/bvpNfi5jvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peady It’s a kit my mom bought me at a Christmas mall kiosk. Super moisturizer]]></document></documents></author>