<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@beansterrrr @toritrice04 I'll spell this out slow so you both can hopefully understand it Keep. Me. Out. Of. Your.… https://t.co/6UHZo7Pl1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s said that the voice we hear the most often is our own. Maybe it’s not our audible voice speaking out loud, but… https://t.co/rEJgrZKhU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luvdahwks @hawkeyenation Today, yes. In three years, they might shave a few minutes off my weekly chore list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How the raiders gonna overpay a WR when they already have an overpaid QB who can’t throw the ball to him 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjlathrop @Zhawk44 If anything, Blame Barta. He should be talking. That is his job. Fran and the team should be fo… https://t.co/VdtaceWxPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonAnthony7 @TaggartRehnn @KingPeachDP @Riopedre31 @FrankBenXXXOOO @woodywood1999 @chance4gardener @MynameisMok… https://t.co/iJA42UUxm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect day for the @StapletonDenver sledding hill. #4wx https://t.co/e4zAzbCany]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be ok guys I promise. I got this!! 💪🏻 I’m stronger than EVER! My work ethic and my health prove it. Actions sp… https://t.co/Y8EYwpa57t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok @DIRECTVNowHelp my dvr shows upcoming recordings but once the show starts it does not record. Has not recorded a… https://t.co/PFt7TzvQSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Bernie Sanders is a fucking idiot! That is a huge hypocrite!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randywedo57 @jerodmcdaniel That's almost block worthy. https://t.co/QgK6vynuaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast before headimg home #m19conference #manaz @ eggtc. https://t.co/J9cuY2Zneg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Killer Whales are expanding into the Arctic, then dying as the ice sets in: https://t.co/Z4si9tiaVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@worldclas_babes Definitely beautiful she defiantly is! She defiantly has the perfect body! The perfect boobs! The… https://t.co/bIIdcReIim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hredriders I should milk it for a day off but I guess I’m going to work anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@domenictiso4 @Franklin_Graham You gotta dig for them.... no longer taught to kids in schools. I did my research ba… https://t.co/6gOFnbmT9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Colten Brewer is legitimate sleeper in the #RedSox bullpen this #SpringTraining #RedSoxNation #MLB #THESyndicate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cici_94Percent @SamKafrissen @SecolaEdwards @mary28brian @maximlott @RealCandaceO @GOP Okay, source please?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timkawakami The fact he is justifying his actions and dismissing the fact he took a female to the ground instead o… https://t.co/8AO0CE991v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @ChampsTrack for allowing me to participate! https://t.co/6aihk0qrOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FortyCal12 @SFGayMom @LULUBELLE1000 @sahluwal Do some research on the Great Depression before you type again please sir]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2012 I had a government apparatchik as a tour guide who repeatedly said “There is no prostitution in Cuba” as we… https://t.co/EkgHxA9RAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wizkhalifa it just dawned on me. you must be back to smoking blunts again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cosburndesigns @voopootech @Ink_Feckted @natetamm600 Thank you SO much!!! 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NortheastBmore vote again fir the @NortheastBmore instagram account in Baltimore’s Best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[La gente nunca se equivoca. Mientras intentaron justificar lo injustificable: Que en la tierra de @ClaudiaPavlovic… https://t.co/2xcOQ7EMn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas wanna do stupid shit but don’t want to get caught. You could literally catch a nigga and not even be mad but… https://t.co/wD1DSwSzJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am having severe amazon Wishlist envy right now!!! #IWantFreeStuffToo 😜😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes @allinwithchris  Ask @SenSanders @BernieSanders why he won't register as a @TheDemocrats if he wants t… https://t.co/dHu5mfk6Yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#trackandfield headquarters @ Eugene Running Company https://t.co/ae6PTdt6zw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Moss Hamas lied. Hamas Paid Family to Say Baby Who Died from Natural Causes was Killed by IDF https://t.co/zAty9F14D0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceMcKenney1 @steph93065 @realDonaldTrump @ChatByCC https://t.co/P8Cdexwct9]]></document><document><![CDATA[They mad when I brag about the cash I got, but I'm used to not having a lot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepGosar Honestly, I’m surprised you haven’t been hospitalized for being such a douchebag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @ORoberson13 ! Hope you have a very wonderful safe and Blessed one! May God grant you many more to c… https://t.co/li7nmMB7M3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Idontgottimefor @illiniracers @JKap415 Just stop being offended by everything online. It's really easy. I could gi… https://t.co/J3VLKv7NgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarketWatch How diligent has the 1% worked to create appropriate processes, systems and jobs in order to create that value and wealth? 🤯 💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marisolglzz Genial la nueva sección Marisol, muchas felicidades. #MarisolADomicilio 😘😘😘.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think they are Nutjobs personally but they may have a point. It seems like they at least wait for them to be adul… https://t.co/e2zOLW4byT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chriswallace I can see why the dems don't trust you. You are a snake in the grass!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThirdEyeKill @_MeerJ_ I’m playing with 2 people so there’s 3 of us I don’t think you have a room for all of us mate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GastroGays LEGO of the US isLincoln Logs.  Explains a lot https://t.co/bvm7W6KPSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cardinals @Cafejr40 @UncleCharlie50 @ACMettler @ehaahn @curtmcq @nrkrause @SSowers25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@argusmattz In fairness, that’s a real hornets nest they’re walking into at the Bax…]]></document><document><![CDATA[💕 I am a lucky man. I love my family very much. How lucky am I that I have something that makes saying goodbye so h… https://t.co/4kt1T5Thu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurbalEN @GuyInACube I have a Dell 5810 Precision Workstation w/ Intel Xeon E5-1650 v4 @ 3.60GHz. 825 W Pwr Sply;… https://t.co/vx91tSB4wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zendaya has a capsule collection?! Oh wait, this isn’t about gachapon. Never mind...]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you’re wondering what a #WhipPur is . . .   Thank you Coach Simoncelli for providing the platform for me to… https://t.co/kaOAP33DMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫Calling You by Hank Williams, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/kYSC5OJejE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewartHaasRcng @Daniel_SuarezG @ruckusnetworks @ISMRaceway Feel good that he is going to #SlamDown some great laps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweet_an_sexy26 @MsJayLee22 @15and9smom @beckresc @indomituslifts @LuAnn_1970 @OSUmommaDOC @BrienneOfKitty… https://t.co/YChKWMDwQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FreestyleWinner #MMDalmation #MonsterJam #MonsterMutt @cynthiagauthier @ Ford Field https://t.co/HQ1KRhuQVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkYuhnke @MeaganFOX31 ya know your I’m something g fluffy clue puts a kink in my Cee-Lo theory #TheMaskedSinger]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to go to the dentist tomorrow for a regular check-up. I'm already mentally preparing for the amount of guilt… https://t.co/yN9KjOKHEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I’m having sexual intercourse with my right hand tonight. Jealous much?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Regardless whom it is by or for the facts actually remain. You’ve cost your own constituents money and jobs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the right move. Have to give everyone involved, including the team, some space. It has nothing to do with t… https://t.co/COiXE4EklT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidYoungTBLA @kengurnick Yes David, give in to your feelings! https://t.co/mZJroaj3Ta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RdNav03 @nowthisnews @KamalaHarris The base of the Democratic Party consists of women and people of color and she’… https://t.co/3bgsw9Ne06]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bionicanadian @MackenzieLitt13 @faylloumi @GjKrefft @365DaysandMe @MartineRichard8 @JosephMKavanag1 @davidgane… https://t.co/d4bUbuciMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep global warming, climate Change! Just laughing @SenWarren @SenateDems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hardbody_neal @spidadmitchell @NCAA I don’t disagree. Just wanted to understand the options.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronzerb @Redhead4645 @crystalbwaters @POTUS They are called elections.  Personally I think someone who spends a mo… https://t.co/Ckwvfz8YYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewYangVFA This photograph sold for 4.3 million: https://t.co/8OHLeqvgvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little lunchtime soak for my boy Tony. #italianleatherback #beardeddragon #reptilesofinstagram @ New Jersey https://t.co/iEN7tbUYal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luxury agents, the question for all listings in 2019... “is this PTSI?”  (Priced to sell immediately).  We don’t ne… https://t.co/U3L1puPvI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PinoCalad Muy ingenuo, le quita la oportunidad  a Colombia de contar con un buen jugador sea Ian Poveda o cualquie… https://t.co/MgXN9T0MLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even want to watch this crap, but I don’t have to work tomorrow and I’m looking for an excuse to drink.  #WWEChamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveSosnaNBC @KrystalKlei @NBCPhiladelphia Steven, will I need to hook up the plow in Salisbury Twp, Bethlehem, Pa? ✌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathancullen @Puglaas We know neoliberals don't believe in solidarity...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@U2TOURFANS Why are your republishing this news. It causes confusion and renewed, unnecessary concern.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nixanadoo Unfortunately, I don't think he's on this committee, which I didn't know when I posted that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! Would you be mine, mine, mine? https://t.co/4aAz66H1u8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdshoemate182 this one is for you, cupcake.   Credit @jenthomas755 for this gem. https://t.co/yh2ra1KfLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Residents of high-tax cities are increasingly drawn to South Florida after last year’s tax law capped deductions |… https://t.co/68husWxp9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FatherPajama At least you had a landlord to call that could help you out in a reasonable timespan]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE that people are still finding #VideoPalacePod months after release!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey fellow Conlangers, what is the origin and use of the #437conlangery hashtag? Is it connected to a linguistics c… https://t.co/3mYcbniScF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an It Takes Two: Galaxy X Vic Secret by @interboronyc @ Jeff &amp; Jill's Home — https://t.co/D3Vd185V3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaitlancollins He’s leaving early because McDonalds has a lunchtime Big Mac special! https://t.co/oOgHXEZw2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PX0CAHONTAS Sure ain’t hard. Never understood why people cheat anyways...if you still feel the need to be entertai… https://t.co/LL1QEZPV8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Daylight Saving Time by spending the weekend in Plymouth at a hotel full of scrapbooking women. 🙄 https://t.co/VjroK9pdlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonincbus @BearcatNeal @Timhinds4 @Bearcat_T What’s the logic behind wanting them to win?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaitlynhardwic1 smokes another one up the middle, this one through the pitcher's circle, to bring home an insuranc… https://t.co/0xVcQRzZsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker Convicted felons can’t run for office. He’ll definitely be one by 2024.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3Sour_Mash @rsmithecu @F3Katniss @F3WinstonSalem @F3WeFoCo To soon? But we can run the VI route back to back to b… https://t.co/jI9TCJE73D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollectTillIDie @Rhino_Records Once I'm able, I'll give you a follow back. https://t.co/u180wXnoIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oknotillfarmer So that’s the trick?  My start weedy stay weedy philosophy gonna have to change?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT Background checks do not hinder sales on the black market. Wake up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well you should notice I’m doing it right before my reality comes to fruition #KnowWhatsReal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlancoIndian @Simons67692003 @holykoolaid But when I think for myself and judge the morality of god or the Bible y… https://t.co/RBCoIhSwFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovInslee is going to save the world from climate change? He can't even save his own state. Goals to reduce CO2 em… https://t.co/2DNaV2XOu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[VANTAGE CAREER CENTER Open House and Taste of Vantage Monday, February 25 5:00 – 7:30 p.m. Tickets to try tasty foo… https://t.co/moZeiQ4dl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DallasPD @NENPODPD East Patrol Bureau NE Division Multi-Family Expo.  Great event. Great community engagement. Gre… https://t.co/3bQ3qi9IkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brand New - The Quiet Things That No One Ever Knows https://t.co/ZYZ2yOxTq2 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wooooowww, I would’ve expected adidas @underarmour not original_sketchers  @nike better watch out for they pull up.… https://t.co/8wy9poWUZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gus’s salad bitch @ The Silver Saddle Steakhouse https://t.co/Xap8KRiAmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a Aries and that’s why I’m not learning anything yet I am just trying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Stand Strong Collaboration Double IPA by @CombustionBT/@LineageBrew at @CombustionBT — https://t.co/O76PrrUEs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaig You gotta check out all the crazy tech attractions at @TwoBitCircus open 1p-1a on Saturdays. https://t.co/NmNREy5ei3]]></document></documents></author>