<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@StormResist @Lady_Star_Gem This is what you get in business. https://t.co/P2nDYVLNaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chandler4Five @Angela_Enders @AOC She is DANGEROUS. The MSM &amp; even FOX cover every word, regardless of how idiotic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Firsttake #mollyqerim #mollyqerimrose #stephenasmith #MaxKellerman #ryanhollins #muggsybogues #deaaronfox… https://t.co/4Uel5HL6l1]]></document><document><![CDATA[All homer opinions aside I don’t see how you can see the MVP race including anyone outside of Giannis and Harden.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting definition of resilience here: the rapidity with which you recover from adversity. @Revkin https://t.co/Tyfd9kKxKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSchmidt9 @ChitowntoOC @BoilerFanTalk @ChrisForman12 @dewey_chris1 @mdavidbrown @CBBonFOX @HammerAndRails… https://t.co/FBg1n2vl9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro my postmates driver is headed away from me 😡 thing said 3 min eta now its 14 min  Cold ass food]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow @BassweightRec threw the fuck down tonight shout out to @faytalmusic @DigitistDubs @SubArtillery @AweminusDub @calcium 🔥🔥🔥😈😈😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah I love the gay scene out here in NorCal y’all Bakersfield was NOT IT.  🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshaWarfield I've based my vote for a president on the character of the man not whether he believes or not!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN is the type of Leader I require. Her and the others like her are the type of representation that I will su… https://t.co/FkyQZhD6ip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fora_flusocio_5 @iihalmeida @gutoscosta80 @Thalles1902 @DeAmoresDepre Mais um motivo pra ir demonstrar apoio!! Ou… https://t.co/ch7vvckd7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makeba C. Barber, a Girl Scout troop leader in Olympia, Wash., scouting became something of a co-parent to her thre… https://t.co/ugsE5nQDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnerlou72 @wayne_tr3a @DTrumpPoll @realDonaldTrump @POTUS https://t.co/jqFKcCIC4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliviaNBC12 @AndrewNBC12 @NBC12 Olivia w/ the clap back https://t.co/NCIE4EJuLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashedUpMike @OrlandoMagic Great idea, thanks again man. I need to get that poster from you also 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[And PLEASE keep your nausating "love" poses to yourself..... Some of us have "sensitive" stomachs.... By the by...… https://t.co/wbub3bLU3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look for the joy and peace amongst us all!  #catTV #Birding #WoodPecker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Coach Burke! You are a Legend and a Great Coach! #ModelofConsistency #GoBulldogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quito_caretas Como dije: he visto tres juegos de duke y los tres los has perdido, en dos de ellos estuvo Zion y no hizo la diferencia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Enabledgrls4God Prayers lifted for you, lift some for me, please. Can I get a follow back, please? Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southendzone9 That, or the ref's all got new whistles and they want to make sure they work...]]></document><document><![CDATA[dolfster made such a fantastic meal tonight that’s so super simple keto! - steak - kale caesar salad  - zucchini w… https://t.co/V4Mvy5TeOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN He was arrested for threatening the teacher. Not for not saying the pledge of aligence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StruckByBelz The more happy you guy were during the episodes, the more my heart was hurting for you guys cause you… https://t.co/xt7caxoGR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarrySanders @NFL @okstate @Nike Whoever #OnePride takes at #8, I have faith in Bob Quinn to take an impact player… https://t.co/n85UR08LYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gee, Twitter is feeling particularly punchy tonight. Somewhere between giddy/punchy and looking for a fight but not… https://t.co/K4JTt1oWBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just in on Twitter  BIGGIE is trash because he didn’t help  Rappers in the 2000s with their legal issues]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACBulldogGolf @OldSouthGolfHH Looks like you have the location wrong—the Duffy Cup should definitely be played in Adrian, MI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Some of y’all might know this and some of y’all don’t.” DJ KOOL. So let me share something. This page @iiturralde… https://t.co/s9TcCRKiLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanWurtzel Rutgers and PSU are good teams.  Ohio State, Minn, and Iowa?  I don't know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  as one Polish person remarked.. 'we could build condos and shops on that Land, but some nut thinks a base wil… https://t.co/SxAdCNIVf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugeneotool @EricHolthaus @NaomiAKlein Actually, solar is Clarkean-magical. Not surprising you show nothing but fear in the face of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@partyf0ul He don’t know good music sweetie 😔 I will show you’s the way]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dangchick1 @TPM Let’s see, capitalism is trickledown economics? How does it work? The rich get richer and nobody e… https://t.co/42EWJ7QR9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YIMBYDurham Is it possible to provide links/context? How big are the homes, price compared to median, how does Fay… https://t.co/nUNItCekAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaheimFire @LACoScan @AnaheimPD @City_of_Anaheim That's a Keeper.... My New Backround photo for my computer... 👍👍😊🍕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day to my three leading ladies. I wouldn’t and couldn’t be the man I am today without e… https://t.co/C3uEYsGtaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerri_lard @Q_UEEEN_ Is media an enemy now, when ya need it?  I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day1U… https://t.co/DLatOn0Bma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Puglaas You're an awesome AG. You standby your principles, and conduct yourself, in a manner that far exceeds, the… https://t.co/7SjD5k2FV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1MonsterMission @F150SuperSnake @DGS_USMC @WassmannBill @archer1111 @XStreamFisher @BamaOutdoors @bassfisher3k… https://t.co/2FabRu3SaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does one date in NYC without going out on friday/saturday nights or meeting garbage ppl on apps? #DatingInRealLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump president Trump why are we allowing this ! This is treasonous! https://t.co/DDZHB7xA9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What greater gift than the love of a cat.” ― Charles Dickens 💞 Happy Valentine's Day! 💖 #Valentines #BeMine… https://t.co/GGNuQMHjb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrishaBShetty @Trevornoah I’m not gonna lie.........I found this kind of funny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man brought back up memories of UC vs Nevada and now I’m depressed... 😨😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBC Stations Eye Growth In Instagram, Voice - TV News Check https://t.co/4XzQUljxAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for the sunset 🌅 ☀️ #saturdayfeeling #beautiful @ Conservation Levee Greenway https://t.co/rTI7iqUHy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DeclanRice Yes but don't let's fall into the trap of replaying incident incessantly for a week. No matter what th… https://t.co/KzjFElOIi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my @Jaylynchphotos on today Behind the 🎥 for @tsuladytigers and @TSUTigersMBB #WeStayBusy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an amazing time joining some Cross Border planning panels talking about financial planning alongside some exper… https://t.co/ELec5yETsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that happiness can only come from within 🖤 @ PIER 39 https://t.co/zAmuzY9SVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck pusha t, if we’re being honest. The man DOES NOT put on for his city and all he helps with us the drug trade h… https://t.co/Gj5c31rKWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@standfortruth10 @DustieDahl @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Can't loose what you didn't have]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenHill_WTHR Chuck looks a bit like Judge Smales today. https://t.co/2ALRAMUU79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PostMalone is killing it on this #ElvisAllStarTribute. After this special, him and @blakeshelton for sure should do a song together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be great if us listeners got a little more than @TBoneWFNZ mentioning “iS dALe juNiOR oN tHe PoLE tHis WEek?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 years ago today, Feb 27, 2011, proudly serving the congregation of St. Andrew's Presbyterian Church by ushering (… https://t.co/MvwKAtEnEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Maybe you need to take @RandPaul with you to see it live . @realDonaldTrump @realJohnMappin @charliekirk11 @RealCandaceO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeBatardShow hey Stan friday night @warriors vs @nuggets is why tour on with @Stugotz790 not in the league.  Sorry… https://t.co/ygtYiAiW4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yulemontana Lol I feel you, you be doing business so I’m sure you’ll get there soon anyway]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG...My daughter got a call from the @Harvard / @RadcliffeRugby  coach today in Vegas...WOW!!!!...Stay Tuned!!🏉🏉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaraotaDigital Piazo de asesino, igual que maduro, diosdado, los rodríguez y tareks ,,, Uds son catalogados ASESIN… https://t.co/evTBvXQMPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see #FLL! silverairways_official #saab340b+ #mikeshot #myunitedjourney #unitedjourney #flyerfriendly… https://t.co/UagVt3XtKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epcotbarcrawl @Twitter Thank you! So there’s a setting for “Allow Twitter to autofollow ‘official’ accounts just b… https://t.co/EU1Or1JMI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger his promises to Putin though ..... https://t.co/C782GZOdvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our desert rider cole_shade continues to impress here in Tucson. 📸 @ckn_live  . . . #GFC #liveyourpassion… https://t.co/b5O9qh3z1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched “The Mule” today and while it wasn’t good per say, I admire Eastwood and his voice in filmmaking. His perfo… https://t.co/tVueXWrIW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's in trouble, but he's not going anywhere https://t.co/nDoiifWG9Y LIES TOLD BY A LIAR TRUMP SAID THERE WOULD… https://t.co/ny9LwpeNIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Won't pass you MORON, YOU'RE AN OBSTRUCTIONIST WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID OF, YOUR DOING WHAT CLINTON DONE… https://t.co/wMpP3o5tFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Week9Assignment #Character #We #Somos @ Hollywood, Florida https://t.co/YOgTh4RU9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought this was Ron Jeremy dressed as the Iron Sheik in some Cockamania cosplay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Sovereignty today.  Sovereignty tomorrow.  Sovereignty forever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[no movie is ever gonna top any of the high school musical movies &amp; I’m not even upset about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lokationnation @vhawk88 @rapsodo I can identity the spin axis if I am playing catch with a pitcher but it is very… https://t.co/mwBcDNK6i4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just let one helluva fart rip in the office today but it was only 3 people there so I think they’ll let it slide]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBigCat I mean NC State scored 24 points in a whole game and they are 20-9.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice to see Shepherd getting a shot this weekend. Nice lead off double. 4 for 7 this weekend I think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrafficAlert Major Accident on I25 near MM132 just south of the Loves gas station. State Patrol is redirecting nor… https://t.co/0qujdOXWFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Manning2Barkley Yall already doing shit in trade market that still counts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC That’s bs. His company done nothing wrong trying to do business with anyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing Luke Perry died at 52 hit a little close to home, not cause I liked his work. Because that’s the same age m… https://t.co/kedxNCcJtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smart dog 🐶 ❤️ best kisses ever and she is pretty hot 😂😂 @AOC #wetkisses #reallove]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feb. 21st 2019 Day 2976: 30 min LISS Cardio with Chest Work with My Brother and Mentor Sagi 👊🏼💚💪🏼 • • • • •… https://t.co/xP3whjehYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm praying that whatever we do tonight it involves Thai pads cause I haven't kicked pads in like a months.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamSteveVander You are going to have to get out there in Morris Park and Van Nest and hit the bricks. Glad to help… https://t.co/9XpUo2Ljut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solace Ugh. His songs will pop on a playlist while skiing and I get sad and turn it down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrlandotheCooke @WeNeedEU @nickylep @MadeleinaKay @manbearpig9282 Brexit will make us better off, because as we cu… https://t.co/Va0yI9UOfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anastasia_do @MarkTidrick @SkrticX @Tribe_XX @TerryMetterJr @juliegabb @librarygrl @auggiewren 1/4 Eternal Sunshin… https://t.co/9lDQdcEfxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#orchids #orchidmania @cbgarden #botanyart #flowers #flora #floral #floralart #floralphotography #flowerphotography… https://t.co/l8aUo9rDzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gnarlyjaffa 😂😂😭😭I’ll be damned, I’ll take it under prayerful consideration]]></document><document><![CDATA[20 Things You'll Only Understand If You Watch "Duck Dynasty" - BuzzFeed Mobile #mirth #snicker #grin #clever https://t.co/cyqvFiJ33S]]></document><document><![CDATA[De pisa y corre a Monterrey a ver #MLB #mexicoseries #amoelbeisbol @ Palacio sultan (estadio de los sultanes https://t.co/BpWaTpFqCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s going to be 50° tomorrow. #ThisIsNormal @ Brooklyn Heights https://t.co/CRrPQeP5qn]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don’t go out often but when we do we go to bars that aren’t even open yet. https://t.co/dgIIp6RuYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[BE~CUZZIE CUZZ #LOVEISLOVE 💙®️⚾️©️©️⚾️💙😘 @ £Ov€ is £Ov€ https://t.co/mnNpXkVBno]]></document><document><![CDATA[No to either and you don’t need to either. Love that hot fur dude woof woof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed meeting many great admitted seniors in the Birmingham area at Birmingham Maroon and White Night!… https://t.co/DMWTbsVHZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: US Forecast - SFGate: US Forecast  SFGate US Forecast for Sunday, March 10, 2019. _____. Recommend… https://t.co/rpOfoAHlDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pequea Valley’s Gabe Miller eyes state gold in PIAA 2A championships https://t.co/oPkzZguwrC @LancasterSports]]></document></documents></author>