<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Verizon Customer Service Phone Number 1 (855) 431-6111 operates 24/7 #Verizonwirelesscustomerservice… https://t.co/MJWG5YRwY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porterfield sat during the prayer today, had Episcopal bishop, rabbi and Muslim giving the prayer. There’s no place… https://t.co/8cxUdBO1OF]]></document><document><![CDATA[joe jonas: grabbing the microphone to sing in the sucker music video me: https://t.co/FDQxfLH3Nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachkruse2 Strange that I haven’t seen pro football talk say anything about it yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelwd I had them 1,2,3 in that order.  Jim’s dnf at UTMB almost cost him but his results were so good at WS an… https://t.co/waUcSYHAfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lahistoriaec @teleamazonasec Hierva mala nunca muere ,  será también culpa de Rafael Correa? Capaz que lo culpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood Jill St John                               Elizabeth Montgomery                     Tina Louise]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadDogRadio @AdamSchein Carr has had the same OC 2 years in a row just once in his time with the Raiders.  The Rai… https://t.co/mTR4XwxhiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenJoy @barchenbeer To catch you up to speed. Basically every few days, it snows here in Omaha. Also, it's been co… https://t.co/A6vdhA8RlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hay que eliminarlos de cualquier manera posible, a algunos físicamente a través de castigos ejemplares de tribunale… https://t.co/nJWIxEDPpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometime’s I think about Roof by @Rico_nastyy and just think wow. She did that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Davefox2 @af_classy @AFCU Nothing but respect for the KJZZ crew. Doing four games in a row including a triple over… https://t.co/GKptogVlNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParkerMolloy @dougstafford It has a lot more relevance of mental case leftist who believes Brian Stelter is "conservative".]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebonnierotten I ain't gonna lie Bonnie, I thought you were gonna spit some Mobb Deep verses, lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryMillerNow Its extremely tough for the public to be anywhere other than work at 1pm and also, as Ned as pointe… https://t.co/OcFcGGFD06]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the 1-2 punch of seeing my personal trainer and my therapist on Thursdays. I wish I also had the time and mo… https://t.co/JfDbRpYDZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxReports @maggieNYT Meadows added: "In case anyone has forgotten, I'm an asshole!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realBobWoodward on @realDonaldTrump: "He's hiding the simple fact that he does not know how to govern,. My intervi… https://t.co/Hd3VlYDSoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[SE 7th and Madison is the Central Eastside Industrial District, fyi.  https://t.co/CCAKzgfKyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSTwinCities All rain with some ice pellets mixed in to this point in Darwin. Which is exactly what radar has sho… https://t.co/29L3CuQ5sc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you had the chance to check out  @Joe_Swearengin web site?  https://t.co/Ag1DZsPeLE #sleepinsundays… https://t.co/fmUtQvmkx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Discript @dickon_edwards My pace slows down immediately when I leave nyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a side note, I'm excited to visit #SUNYGeneseo really soon. The first time since being a freshman in high school… https://t.co/GZRRttLFLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing quite as satisfying as getting to sleep in late. https://t.co/7ADqkltJMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thesportsskribe The question is; will there be enough cast off talent to make two entertaining leagues?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congress needs to stop trump with his FAKE NATIONAL EMERGENCY!  BECAUSE HE LOST THE SHUTDOWN BATTLE HIS EGO WILL NO… https://t.co/vSP09VSkSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyknowless @kevintomas28 Jesus Christ... kevin finna be a daddy. Uncle Rick is here for the moral support.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did y’all not watch the final battle between him and killmonger? The CGI was horrible]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another shot of Infinity Gauntlet LV.  - - -  #infinitywar #upcycle #luxury #mashup #repurpose #indyartist #art… https://t.co/aEpPVWv1Mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Oh, WTF, I’m pro Palestine, that doesn’t mean I hate Jews, it means I believe Palestinians are getting screwed]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t blame him, that’s why I work out at Planet Fitness, the people there aren’t as dooshy https://t.co/9WmToNT2vT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ogi__wan I got it a month ago and I fuck with it. Nice to watch other leagues]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sharkmuffin @thecosmicclash @torchystacos Hey Sharkmuffin I’m in Red River District. See y’all at @EmpireATX?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlatinumCat @DonaldJTrumpJr Hillary is still having daily meetings to destroy Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomnewkirk08 @GCM_Magazine That should help..... greens are bumpy....sorry thats the po....... 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had real plans  to fire up the grill today . Why the fuck it had to rain ?! Smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wsueakes @FieldYates @AdamSchefter @rscamden Can you confirm they’ll still be green?? #jetsnewunis]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of seeing Freaknik on the TL as a means for ppl tryna promote the idea that the 2000s and 2010s weren’t fun... #lame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aitorlagunas Curioso que sea el jugador mejor valorado en el FIFA cuando siempre pierde en torneos FIFA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So apparently there’s a Wikipedia page for the historical Hippie Trail, roughly contemporaneous with the Oregon Tra… https://t.co/OLeCOH70uU]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to #Astrology Pisces is a water sign and people born under this sign are compassionate, adaptable, devote… https://t.co/gLwyXJGiFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely disgusting from @TeamYouTube to punish the content creator for a comment not made by them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't do no fake friends, I can't do no fake bros, I just need the pesos]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate this! Hey Wild, I’d be happy to take the job of talent recruiter and holder. Because who ever is doing it, c… https://t.co/AsMVhcc6jX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steveolivas Don’t be diss’n Ozone and Turbo!!! They were both lit and legit...before either of those things were THINGS!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[nigga took my right hand from me .. I smoke sip lean &amp; drink yo ease the pain 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajanderson91 @ArrogantBuckeye When will Harbaugh take his team to Indianapolis?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nquisitiv You are lucky you exist given your mother did it! I knew guys who fell into the Glace bay harbour which was doubly bad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything in this tweet is *technically* true but i disagree with the subtext that all of this is bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobRmhenry1 @LastStand2019 @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama That looks exactly like the birth certificate I bought at… https://t.co/mK87GJdUx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encourage your friends in whatever thy do. It’s the little pushes that can make a million dollar idea come to life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariel_ortega7 @Vini_veiga5 @cantstopthinkn_ @mattjota so if you’re psg and you’re going into the champions league… https://t.co/8APZ3rYWoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late seeing “Vice,” left hoping Hamilton and Madison didn’t see it at the Pearly Gates Cineplex.#YepPowerCorrupts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Why can’t you look at the camera when you speak? Your body language says you’re lying about Trump tr… https://t.co/rQiDvYVSk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump please stay in North Korea, you are a disgrace and an embarrassment to the United States of Ameri… https://t.co/HVqnwQqRx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[BUSTED! Obama’s Daughter Has Secret Facebook Page Filled With Anti-Trump Messages https://t.co/uJ4qrlj5ky via @ILMForg]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most strategic goals for this morning’s Gen Zers is how to get people to stop scrolling on their streams! #SMWATX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Along with Obama’s Clinton’s Brennen Clapper Benghazi Benghazi Lynch Holder Kerry Comey all of them 💪🏼💪🏼👊👊🇺🇸🇺🇸👍🥓🍀🙏🏻… https://t.co/0G3lWt0Sxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of you Jerry we’ve known for a while now but we are all so happy for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyBrightestAbby @thegreatwebber @ScottWalker @AOC What is it that Walker does for a living, again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wavering on whether or not to add #TheUmbrellaAcademy to my plate right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great having our College Republicans attending the Tulsa County GOP Convention this morning. Always exciting to see… https://t.co/5FoI8QN3c0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyTotzke @DraftNetworkLLC Brian Burns is a top 5 player in the nfl draft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eka317 well, you can call me the garbage man, so I'm gonna take you away]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhofheimer_espn @BaxFootballGuru @JasonWitten It’s called he sucked....and start something else quick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Badflower Nothing should make you prouder than Jester from the first word to the last.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey it’s straight facts! Just wait until the XFL comes around 👀👀 Roger......Vince coming! Y’all better be ready!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrancisGhanime @Rich_9z @DeschenesPhil @Djibourd @ForgeFCHamilton @OttawaFuryFC Non, zéro contre.   Je suis juste… https://t.co/lLCvb11oS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Montreal! :) #Sunrise 06:40, noon 12:07, sunset 17:36 EST (UTC-5), February 25. Day length: 10h 56m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are both bad takes lol he stated publicly he didn’t really want philly. He went there for the most money. But… https://t.co/BvpK745eOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestlingDude98 Big time agreed!  Throw in stars from NXT &amp; 205 Live to help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion for Spring Break: going to Lake Charles Golden Nugget for the weekend and taking @treyterrell51 b… https://t.co/t3JV0rzyNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeeDotally WATCH IT. TODAY. HOLY HELL THAT MOVIE. SO GOOD. The ending legitimately disturbed me. And that's NOT an easy thing to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spaceywaycee Milwaukee🧀🧀🍺🍺 Top 5(Not ordered) Excision ZD Kygo Odesza Slander. Next show :REZZ 🌀_🌀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@r_dame @realDonaldTrump Dude please keep daylight savings all year long!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like bacon on my burger and then put ketchup on that...and my fries!🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning about Durham’s Royal Ice Cream Sit-in from one of the protesters, Virginia Williams. The protest happened… https://t.co/sHvE9J9zHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyFrankSmith @sarahwoodwriter @TomiLahren @realDonaldTrump Lol no I am sick and tired of finger pointing and yet… https://t.co/rpe8Vn6jH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[First wing flap? An eaglet gives his wings a try. He wants to be just like mom and dad! @ Gibson, Louisiana https://t.co/onZoYhBsbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of the Cadets of Western HS.  They performed really well at the All-Air Force PFT meet this weekend.  They… https://t.co/fkL0AY9iFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@koshairby No Bahamas for you BUT we have booked you an in-home visit with the PAIN TRAIN on March 30 at The Libert… https://t.co/rCrmo60RmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you tried these ? '3/16 oz. KKryptonite Tungsten Weight (8 PaKK)' on JaKKed Shop https://t.co/FGdcKUcnAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UDMCoachScott I hope he worked on his dancing/cardio skills, cause that girl is non-stop!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished day 2 of the @YouVersion plan 'Learning Spiritual Discipline'. Check it out here: https://t.co/2fu1QqG6C1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rdrhwke @ProudTiger3 @Frankmyglock @redzonedad @Zlsim1 @DMORTON43055307 @ladyD19235856 @GaulMichele @GeanineC… https://t.co/3p3k4Vf2IC]]></document><document><![CDATA[left my apartment to get a car wash. hour later my car’s still dirty but I have new fairway woods https://t.co/VTr5u2m0UB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beckystorm_wx Couldn’t agree more!! I have a black lab and a chocolate lab.. The only reason I don’t have a yellow… https://t.co/iqGW18atEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at @TheQArena and want to take home the Special Edition @Larrydn22 Bobblehead?   Visit our West Bay at Section… https://t.co/6xfdjZ6kxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry that was a lot of talking but remember Kirito has to get settled into this world again so it will be a bit of… https://t.co/Ob9bAg6wGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perfec10n Welcome back brother! Have fun and please be safe on the road!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Treating myself to a massage today is a whole ass mood. Body aching is an understatement 🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticsWolf @Taniel @JoshuaADouglas Interestingly issues like voting age and felon disenfranchisement make soluti… https://t.co/jzUrutypbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrvolta @TTFMike Because Bruce was being honest and both Barry and Iris still came at him, out of grief, and tried… https://t.co/qGceSC76f9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreggPoppaBitch @StoolGametime If you go on her Insta she posted a story explaining the situation. Not sure if it… https://t.co/bGwURalZ7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mgoblog Teske got called for one later when Murphy was going in for a dunk that shouldn’t of been a foul either]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImVictoriaPratt I recommend Gallatoires on Bourbon Street for lunch.  And the best cheese pizza can be found acros… https://t.co/BISA7wqqKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Cardi really out here giving y'all hope? I see Hoe culture is being promoted and celebrated. I thought you were… https://t.co/FfwW8AHgBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always been afraid of the thought of taking psychedelics but I’ve really been wanting to experiment lately]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNewsRSS Trials could start tomorrow if investigators could remember the sequence of events related to FDA regul… https://t.co/v5Rjh7uAr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CavemanSyndrome @DonYoung48 Let’s go to karaoke! Which of our friends can we convince to pay now that we’re broke? 😊]]></document></documents></author>