<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@eliteuser26 Coming down nicely.. tapping the skylight  through the snow cover lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gac_zelfand I’ve sold a couple shirts so far but not a TON so far. This is my first time doing a big push on it]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIP-OFF: @CBAColtsBBall vs Manasquan. Winner faces Ranney in the SCT finals. CC: @holmdelcntap #NJHoops 🏀 https://t.co/ypV5kW5QsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rlswtpea13 @GrangerSmith @ChrisLeeCountry We need a Buffalo NY date !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[He aquí “Carlitos Way”, el taxista que había dicho cosas feas sobre nuestro candidato a Defensor del Pueblo, concej… https://t.co/ajiM13AWQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickbennett26 @Eurolanche I tweeted @realDonaldTrump about that special visa just FYI😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LockNLoad762556 @JulieReichwein1 @Jenn198523 FROM QUINCY MA ONLY CITY OF PRESIDENTS IN AMERICA  Nine miles from a… https://t.co/9IUBDXWzKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[How tf is tomorrow not national coffee day?  Gonna sleep in so hard tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FactsMatterJack @hrkbenowen You speak like someone who is using feelings and not facts.  #FactsMatter https://t.co/ugB6Bqkiqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biggest test of my life tommrow at 8 am Good luck to everyone taking sat’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy international women’s day to the talent ladies of statusbarbershop. #ladybarber #yyj #statusbarbershop… https://t.co/XBruCuavtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mariana_E69 Are you on the Dallas SI Facebook page, their always posting for bartenders &amp; cocktails all around dfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist @pandorable1968 @lorenopine @CunningSq16 @honest_irish @dwood_bucket @HyattL789 @MuldrowDennis… https://t.co/CdRrQnWy7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you start watching black mirror and no one tells you to skip the first episode https://t.co/DgDS9Ry9XF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markrmcqueen @TOAdamVaughan @biancawylie He’s not in power!! We need to sweep the two old Parties out completely a… https://t.co/58voI4owC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pathindle @RohdeSchwarz @RohdeSchwarzNA Pleasure! Thanks for all the support, great conversations and putting toge… https://t.co/tA7Gvr2nSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently I won this raffle basket? @ Upper MerionMiddle School https://t.co/QNubtDzRa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys are Economic idiots! It means inflation, the value of the dollar drops. What you could buy for $1,000 now… https://t.co/ApUiZ9ScMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[When’s the last time UNM was 9th in basketball? Call me what you will but that’s unacceptable at UNM. You should ne… https://t.co/aBR25mXyyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ Clearly, a women who has no concept of what actual rape is. 😀 Bless her wretched soul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASaunders_PGH Ever since I started going to grocery stores as an adult]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @joshgroban, just between us &amp; possibly @kenjeong, are   you now or have you EVER been #TheMaskedSinger? https://t.co/g0aHmHgxjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been here 25 years...seen Gretzky,Brett Hull,Shanahan,McGinnis: Hall of Famers ...But have never seen a better stre… https://t.co/EblSUNJCNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinVuongTO @Raptors Super polite. It's like you guys are a football crowd.  Mad respect]]></document><document><![CDATA[The future result of surrender is realizing that nothing you lose was really worth keeping anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always keep your head up🌴 #photography #photo #palmtrees #nc #northcarolina #wilmingtonnc #wilmington @ Wilmington,… https://t.co/j1EBLot2C6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like this kid. @RealJamesWoods @DavidJHarrisJr @benshapiro https://t.co/HwRrJlcuUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weeeeeseph Fuck it, playing with house money. Two home dogs. Blackhawks +110, Knicks +145. Twolves won't have Karl-Anthony Towns tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoonUrsin May you find peace in your memories in this transitory time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Orvieto2016 @RealJamesWoods There needs to be an appropriate penalty for a crime. The idea that someone can kill a… https://t.co/vBRR3AECX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbell9968 @KerriBell2 @NationalFFA @iowaffa @SE_District @tlsteinh https://t.co/Oa8MBvsE9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a HFS by @alpinebeerco @ World of Beer - Dublin — https://t.co/p2jG8CnrEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selenagomez @ItsBennyBlanco @JBALVIN I’m so proud of you you’re so adorable and talented]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks like for @SenSanders, it's all about #Bernie and not about the country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That new Cardi &amp; Bruno is waaaayyyy better than their first record together. lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all probably haven’t noticed yet but these athletes from Mississippi are FREAKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alphe89 @PhreakkoSuave I’ve watched this at least 100 times and I still can’t keep my shit together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin do you think it's Jesus Will in your life for you to rape Angelica? @ARTGP  @mercedesamgf1 @haasf1team… https://t.co/t8p2JIamBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[IU was 12-2 w this same roster w some big wins...don’t tell me there is no talent on that team... that is an excuse… https://t.co/oXPWHAwaZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNHOOKSY @UNC_Basketball @MonsterEnergy @Husker_Nick I know it's late but is that the official drink of the #tarskers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Self promotion isn’t always easy but often necessary when trying to grow your #business or get that promotion.   He… https://t.co/BGcC7umzRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly reminder that all of your flowers are gonna be dead af in like a week]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pray for a speedy recovery young man. You'll definitely be stronger than ever and we'll be watching you next season… https://t.co/HB2csxlTKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[and I love Alberto, even when he forgot why we made it when he got here. I am working, my love. https://t.co/C5DiGY4Ds3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caroline_k222 Can we just pull an Ocean’s 8 and steal the most valuable diamond in the world??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigceej33 @AllbrightNFL And if hes ever in Cleveland, well, I'd just get him a nice glass of ice water. #Refreshing 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[30% off prints today: https://t.co/JpKk7SYcuj  Pictured: “In the Morning” https://t.co/3p9OwrbpDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mez_merrill @BEyes60 @robmitc69885060 @cocozzarod @TheScreamBike @junona2 @svetlio_savov @ViktorMochalin @davidz67… https://t.co/5vyxybFKn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made from the best stuff on earth.  #papimilo @makeupbymilo  #sunrise #florida  #💪 #👨 @ Sunrise, Florida https://t.co/b4kTFwc028]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember watching this game live! I was like 15 and I jumped through  the rough when Kobe knocked down that 3! 🏀🏀🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MK_ForeverKing @PNDOmegaK Talking point: MK1 is more competitive than mk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy cow I have a friend who won a trip.  I'm proud she works hard. What is also key is that her leaders recognize… https://t.co/CHwa5u18ER]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @WillAndGrace and I'm worried I'm gonna have to explain what vers means.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnbcrist can you help? 700 retweets on my pinned tweet and I get a free jersey!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mfaulkner43 @HRecruit @Adam_Karpiak Oh and Kris, I love self-evals. There’s no one better to toot your own horn than yourself 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a start, but this campaign is going to be long and hard fought to bring common sense guns laws that are tens o… https://t.co/OmAUI2Fxjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ferny_suave It’s so funny when it happens because then y’all laugh about it and drink more 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCcreepify @KestrelTapes @grandayy @MrBeastYT @DolanDark @VoiceoverPete @pewdiepie @YouTube I don't care about T-s… https://t.co/LCqPZIZ6E4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Human grief, anguish, and love need no language translation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is great to hear a female doing play-by-play and an interview on the @Twins game on @fsnorth and she is doing a great job!]]></document><document><![CDATA[why would i pull up on a nigga i dont have a problem with? whats crazy is ion have problems w either of yall niggas… https://t.co/IkVHM1a2WF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandonbATL Italy’s greatest gift to humanity! According to my wife an Italian home has to have 1- a can of olive… https://t.co/iFfAfNhUmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I've been saying for years: evangelicals, to a shocking degree, have gotten Jesus's message utterly tw… https://t.co/aAwCNrxKz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC, Sanders, and Warren are the real centrists because they speak for most Americans https://t.co/tHYPWZFYCu by @mehdirhasan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParkBrown88 @booyahBREWCO @hass54 Someone needs to call television from 9 years ago and tell them about High Defin… https://t.co/kfe09dMVnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bulked up a bit, now cutting but keeping as much size as possible for Vancouver Open on March 30th, competing Men's… https://t.co/9Vqn7ZiehV]]></document><document><![CDATA[New #YouTube video drops tomorrow morning at 8am CST #red8khelium vs #canonc200 #Filmmaking #filmmaker… https://t.co/Wzft5noHl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJayWilliams ESPN just hating on Carolina by making this majority Duke players...shocker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaffXgrenade @DjChiszle Immunity from partnerships Belching privileges Snorting privileges Farting privileges "Sc… https://t.co/2ZyvO75c9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice hike today at Alum.  #ohio #ohiogram #hiking #turkeytail @ Ohio https://t.co/cXqesKqfxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews That’s so ridiculous. Vote baiting the African American population. It will never happen because there is no $$$]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Volsuck1 @MLBNetwork @YESNetwork @Yankees @astros @nflnetwork All you have to do is follow me I tweet about baseba… https://t.co/55KKE7A3dO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThugPugMom No worries,  take your time and I understand maybe more than anyone.  My bro Lewis pass away August 4th… https://t.co/iC9Pf3C3Q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chartreusewahoo @SavageAmerica_ Haha I know I did, I was just being gross 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[And when big tobacco execs claimed cigarettes were harmless, you never saw any of them smoking. They only seek to p… https://t.co/dEeLA90cMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always great when I can step into the booth and lay down some voices. Can’t wait to show you the next thing I’m wor… https://t.co/pmkUSumu4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDaniel2033 "...Experiment" is the finest book of serious baseball scholarship ever produced. Foundational, brilliant, magisterial...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jon Jones: First kick, aimed for the body. Illegal knee was totally unintentional. Felt Smith's body rising, threw… https://t.co/5jEgESEBCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CubanitoenCuba Le obliga salir por calva , afeaba el ornato publico, la belleza natural de@Costa Rica se veía opac… https://t.co/91dps2EdE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dellowhockey Too bad the guy who caused the rebuild will be making the picks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pontifex I'm not Catholic but I'm following you. Might give me some spiritual balance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ap399 @flywithkamala He is pro gun / democrats aren't and he voted no twice on Russian sanctions- and we certainly… https://t.co/ElZ5Pkthcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYorNothing I hear all islander playoff games are going be at the Coliseum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @abbydphillip @TheLeadCNN Any President w his potential issues should be under the same scruitiny. If t… https://t.co/7VaswrJjEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasDiocese I think you’ve got the orders reversed! 283 in the lay and 137 in the clergy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MindyYmail They can’t do that!!!  They have one of the best garlic burgers in town.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out “The Gulch” — one of the few remaining landmarks of Aug 31, 1864 First Day of Battle of Jonesboro https://t.co/kHesbxuFoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colin Cowherd is the only sports show talker I can listen too and not cringe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask yourself this and then remember that on Election Day https://t.co/vwELJwV1gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sealed Copy Of Super Mario Bros. Sells For A Record-Breaking $100,150 https://t.co/zp5DbgfpNc via @kotaku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh, really?! 🥺🥺🥺 Actor Luke Perry has died at age 52  https://t.co/sMLVxZrjUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slayer - South of Heaven. I played this album on cassette endlessly during the summer of 91 • • • • #nowplaying… https://t.co/Ku48oIgDKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Military Exercises In Multiple Cities, Arrests, We Have The Watch - Epis... https://t.co/hNF7UBpCSy via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[La noche entera es corta para soñar contigo y todo el día es poco para pensar en ti. #cuba #miami #nessconsuegra… https://t.co/raB0CxbMLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nex thing I know some elderly dude comes in, and after we shout “welcome to Rcs!” He thanks ya for the welcome then… https://t.co/JuLiixPUQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickbabb12 @Talley_KiiD @MarialShayok @CoachProhm thank you Cyclone Seniors and Coach for being great people, and… https://t.co/QZRnwfaD0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of seeing white kids create Instagram ads of them free-styling and asking what I think]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #TBT  to 2019 when I let a guy put a rattlesnake on my shoulders...Good thing I had my #ChuckNorrisStuntDouble s… https://t.co/2rjtEYy3Bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stray from approved thought in higher ed and you can expect to be called a Nazi. https://t.co/62kApKC6N9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im sorry that someone you loved before made you think it’s hard to love you.]]></document></documents></author>