<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What a nice night for a stay at home date ❤️ The Humpening presents  FEB 27th! Two Person Improv JAM!🍯 11pm!   🕺Com… https://t.co/wVIkyRXoza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Erinmc33 The last Steelers Jersey I bought was Heath Miller during his rookie year. I hate spending money on a Jer… https://t.co/op50rHXB0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hear from @schmangee who is #Cleveland-based pedestrian advocate  She says before cars people used to walk in roads… https://t.co/AYWWT5r0jE]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a successful country day...got the summer concert lineup stacked now. See you soon @LukeBryanOnline and @FLAGALine #SunsetRepeatTour]]></document><document><![CDATA[a real klutz never uses a kludge they just proceed full speed ahead #artwiculate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer The will of the people is to eradicate anyone like you to every breach the Oval Offi… https://t.co/SaAL3jfrzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoSnerdley Bet you there is more to this story...I think I will “Wait, Out” on this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is beyond fucking stupid i can’t believe there’s actually people with low enough IQs to think this is ok  if y… https://t.co/QbOv6G3ToI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN It is not about them, it is about the victims, the families, the lives destroyed.  To focus on them is doing a… https://t.co/4F7Ge0Qbhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unexpectedly cried w/ my ♒️ Armenian friend about genocide and our trauma n how we WANT to raise children as a radi… https://t.co/O8vMc8pz2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learned that an exam I was prepping to pull an all-nighter for is actually next week and not 9am tomorrow morning.… https://t.co/yX8m1i4m2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump Announced A NOUN ANNUIT or open A United Nations..he said Mexico will pay Fay for the… https://t.co/qx0BLad1Mq]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂 LMFAO @UnoTheActivist and @Thouxanbanfauni stomping out the wildfires on IG Live]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems we have a new doorman. #goose @ Wiring Harness &amp; Cable, LLC https://t.co/2qsq4dqCZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deesnider It happens to the best of us😝!  And you are one of the best!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday night in the studio: And now for something a bit different. Four panel piece almost done. Will be shown in… https://t.co/TtXbHysN8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either change the age back down to 18 so a high school kid who has a future in the NBA as a star can pass up colleg… https://t.co/sNTNlSwKi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old LA zoo. #lazoo #griffithpark #bears #wild #cages @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/zhvCpjFF1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints - @ldschurches in Farmers Branch, TX https://t.co/o6S7KENR2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[The start of my endless baseball tweets. 😃 #DetroitTigers   https://t.co/vjqzPb38Yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch #Mueller is part of the coup aimed at deposing #Trump. The co… https://t.co/noEDCogUEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Your dumb ass wouldn't know real and honest news if it hit you square in your dumb head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An 11-0 run by @PHSClippersHoop promps a @AlvirneAthletic TO. @PHSScores up 15-10. 1:06 1st. @seacoastonline @FostersDailyDem]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Michael Thomas’ coming out party against Maryland. @Cantguardmike One of the best catches I’ve seen. #GoBucks https://t.co/TOPm6gZfCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews I thoufht you were better than that.always looked up to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoFascistLies I guess I am just trying to stop the republicans I am 82 years old and know what the republicans wil… https://t.co/E4B7TGeZpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yg_once your Twitter feed is probably the best thing on the internet. 😂👌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir wow 3:15 hours delay flight 3506. For what? The plane from San Jose was delayed 3+ hours. If you comm… https://t.co/jHMDU4grF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear, I was SURE that Kofi Kingston was winning the WWE title after that Trouble in Paradise counter to the running knee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Micah_W17 @Sinatra_Jay @darrenrovell But that was the expectation as soon as he came in the league. Obviously he w… https://t.co/x3wTwX6BIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[we’ve lived in our house for 20 years and my dad is selling it and mom is NOT having it https://t.co/Ndat3eca9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[THEN, if a tweeter does avail themselves of the opportunity to edit, the original tweet appears in the timelines of… https://t.co/aKZkSmqtC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJ_099 @fastnasty @xKingCy The rock looks sick in this. I guess 50 lbs of muscle missing from his body will do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndrew_lawrence That head is getting fatter and blockier by the second.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ripinryan Roses are red Violets are strange Just for one season They fancied a change]]></document><document><![CDATA[The month of March is Women in History Month. Take a quick break to read about how history is being made through Th… https://t.co/XNfSo3Qj13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Btw everybody hating on TN for “not playing anybody” make sure you tune in to #3 Gonzaga against San Diego.........]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nowooski The original tweet summarizes everything awful about Twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Max was watching megalo box when I got home from work and guess who now has their first crush on an anime boy? (its… https://t.co/8RfiKOJvPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PadovaCalcioSG @PadovaCalcio @Lega_B @TMit_news @apoelfcofficial This is Giorgos https://t.co/0QUEjAnd1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had so much fun today!  And who doesn’t need a Fort Night Fitness Break!  #RISDconnects #RISDgreatness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using the IPL machine at Diamond Vision for dry eye, scar removal, and busted blood vessel removal.… https://t.co/bW85L9vtZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevensashle @RealJamesWoods I’m thinking maybe it refers to being “well done.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@churchofbasebal How does that even cook right though? I can’t imagine that’s going to cooled correctly every time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackMitchellLNK Please post the podcast afterwards LOVE THIS SHOW! Needs to return next season!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anntensity Ann simply to say good morning to ya and also to anntensity yeah to ya both love  and hugs from somebod… https://t.co/bTAu0s9ixo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericswalwell @FoxNews Unlike any @cnn viewer, because if you're still watching that garbage, your mind is made up!… https://t.co/UjEbNmElJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDAYWeather @SSchnellbach_WX Happy National Banana Bread day at 6:00 a.m. it's 21ﾟwith a high of 26°and low of -2ﾟ… https://t.co/3K0EtgzV6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AllForTheGators video 3 of 3 I worked on to tease and then promote UF’s first annual Giving Day. It was good exper… https://t.co/Pt3WRhG1uw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just cannot believe how much of a hack you are. You've spent your professional career aligned with Nazis and you'… https://t.co/YLBefuCRlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brian Warren learned the sneaky James Harden push off on a drive and the refs keep rewarding him with free throws.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In view of what has happened here in the USA and the lengths at which Republicans and hostile foreign powers have s… https://t.co/LgPcPjpqFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some personal thoughts about the sudden passing of King Kong Bundy  #RIPKingKongBuddy  #KingKongBundy   https://t.co/4kCGsbFjpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ETSshow @BrowofJustice @DRsonosRD @MDaware @reverendofdoubt @MenInNursing @dr_larryi @PheoCoffee @sweetmarias… https://t.co/3Neq6DK2kb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyAshburnPFN @Ethanhood1 @Brett_PFN_BX @ChipFolsom @PFF @PFN365 Strictly grading post snap decisions with the a… https://t.co/WFRAbsugVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE: ONE ?? LAST ?? TIME ??  #WWEFastlane @WWERomanReigns @WWERollins @TheDeanAmbrose https://t.co/BhOtyRpq1s  https://t.co/fW3abi0ax9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradleyPClark @onegarion @TjellEirik @charliekirk11 Lol I don’t do talking points my thoughts are my own and you w… https://t.co/fiqoS7WGls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marcus_Porcius2 @DLoesch https://t.co/pB0tzTpbIa Not the best eyesight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And @TheSoundTigers capitalize.  3-1 lead in the second period over @TheHersheyBears]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pratheek_a Will do! The paper will have a lot more details hahah. Thanks :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Meatball Day!!! Chow down and have one for us!!! #nationalmeatballday #meatball #hungry #food #love #meat… https://t.co/1gALIIO94j]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy was my idol as a kid.  Hope to meet him someday.  They called him “The Greyhound” and I loved him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rare quiet moment in the city #albuquerque #newmexico #newmexicotrue #purenewmexico #downtown #downtownabq… https://t.co/Lt3PsxPqxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkTousaw @FeralMiller Personally I tend to look at cannabis as the tonic for the intellect. It can be a great wa… https://t.co/cjK8xbdfi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidbmetcalfe @IEEESpectrum Sign me up maybe it would help in my situation?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, yes, poor folks ought to have equal access to three-day benders. https://t.co/ZiOvDpaVx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pete_satit @NicoSchira Speaking on players from that region I meant. Just to clarify]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have often been thankful that the sun doesn't set until after 9 PM in the summer and have never wished that the s… https://t.co/XitAyvkVFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/pC3lukC7Y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sixers lead 37-26 after one quarter. Harris with 10 points. Bolden and Mike Scott with 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normal people at 4am: *asleep soundly in their beds.* Me at 4am: “How about we bump some of that Ed Sheeran fellow?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LorenzoZaniolo asymmetric tactics - i know a guy who puts out of order signs on wells atms -- he shows me the pict… https://t.co/Rj37ALgT1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bungarsargon @ZacharyBraiterm @Yair_Rosenberg an important read for you to really understand who you are sharing t… https://t.co/4AcbOmmaNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen. Amy Klobuchar is a 'no' on free college tuition  https://t.co/VnKh5AwKJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great kids clinic today for @tftpalmbeaches with  denniswaltersgolfshow and @graeme_mcdowell. Looking forward to a… https://t.co/FhN5FlChYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, man! Thank you to @CollectorPadres for the awesome Allen and Ginter cards. SO many patch cards! Amazing collect… https://t.co/TOpKAOXqdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[a hedge fund guy who makes $1.2million a year is miserable and a janitor who mops hospital floors is happy.  the di… https://t.co/FgiAyUqtEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Lincoln Highway Passaic River Bridge https://t.co/AuYHa4BYXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[All bar food should look like this!! (@ Scribes Club - @hyattlostpines in Cedar Creek, TX) https://t.co/7CG3WVP8xJ https://t.co/MpG7gB8TRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[my roommate and i having manifestation/energy talks 15 minutes before witching hour https://t.co/O4uyxeGgoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukebroadwater @BELBaltimore Considering the well-known limitations/failings of the MPIA, especially with regards… https://t.co/SEzOOXCG6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riu48 I would do the same for any combo of: Havik, Darrius, Ashrah, Reiko, Chameleon, Hotaru Or dairou]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly hate when someone tries to make plans with me the day of. my social battery just can’t take it. unless i r… https://t.co/5cvEJmJQyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitlockJason I usually never agree with you but your take on the girl is spot on!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When’s the last time a team won 3 consecutive games on buzzer beaters?   Asking for a friend...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReefCGB @AGuyNamedNam @NorCalNickCGB If you flew @SouthwestAir, you can change your return without penalty... you… https://t.co/ujmcUzZR1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Twitter family is growing. Thanks for all the follows. https://t.co/PdEYspwtS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a German Chocolate Cupcake 10W-40 by @HiWireBrewing at @RandomTap — https://t.co/9cAyrqYhxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[J. Eduardo Grajales Ma... crossed 10.55km. Time 01:12:47, pace 07:06 min/km, est. finish 9:02 am https://t.co/MchLx9zgJc #RNRMERIDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piemansheps Exactly. FA referees are an absolute 💩show. It’s no coincidence there isn’t a single FA ref in any CL match.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think face tattoos are the dumbest thing. When people are talking to you, their eyes are zeroed in on that tat. P… https://t.co/lyrqi0VwO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTV_PowerPlay @MPJenOConnell @lraitt @MurrayRankin The Liberals supporting @JustinTrudeau are in self-preservation… https://t.co/0LnOskW6KP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This is a faithful saying, and worthy of all acceptation, that Christ Jesus came into the world to save sinners; o… https://t.co/k732O7s3of]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when something goes wrong with check in and you’re stuck in the very back of boarding for southwest....stuck… https://t.co/aWwjMl3LbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worth noting that “socialist” was the least popular label for Democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael OMG these kids are the reason some species eat their young]]></document><document><![CDATA[When, after months of rain and cold, the Old Gods make the weather perfect for ridding. https://t.co/ReHX8nUFoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#February 22, 2019 #ThankYouGODForBlessingMeToSeeAnotherDay #GoodMorning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bout to get our #MamaMia on! #GranburyOperaHouse @ Granbury Opera House https://t.co/ISInH8gmUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did as the voice commanded. And I seen as I grabbed hold of it, the nations of the earth did rise, and they made… https://t.co/dkUPpHU0km]]></document></documents></author>