<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[the day cudi announces a new album is the day i dye my hair again deal? deal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VidsBaby Animals recognize that some are children. I believe the maternal instinct kicks in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The left has abused so many catch phrases when referring to our President - temper tantrum is one I could do withou… https://t.co/7Anc7a9oyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must read.   We as@Conservative have got to have a plan and a story against Medicare for All other than that’s Soci… https://t.co/vQDvJSbFzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this playful there's something wrong with you. Kid in a Liquid Soap Bottle (funny photo idea) - r… https://t.co/7aumZjiDuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Plus we can all commit tax and bank fraud and on a comparative basis our sentence will be 15 minutes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toronto4kids This would be our first time going to the Toronto Zoo..... Hope we win!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Bourbon St, New Orkean, la https://t.co/0s54wvv0gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AjayManhapra @GloriaMiele @brandonbphd @RDashford https://t.co/8kTyhlyz14]]></document><document><![CDATA[This great explanation by @Dictionarycom on the difference btw “gender” and “sex” was in my inbox this morning, so… https://t.co/5IwyI9Fx5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t realize how many there are of us that don’t watch game of thrones. I’m proud of us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How heartbreaking. Idk how we can just sit back and let all this shit keep happening to these poor people]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m working on a show with the most talented people I know. But more importantly they are humble and kind! #BLESSED… https://t.co/4w0IOI92x9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bath_House_Bary @LisaMei62 🤔. In this time even that is possible.  I was thinking he left for the tribunals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope they intend to take more than Baby Steps.....  This man is an Evil Crook, and do whatever it takes to get wh… https://t.co/tr43vZslLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Committee to Support Greyhounds is now Support Working Animals and is working to get Amendment 13 overturned to rig… https://t.co/xiQKeXyMnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all know row 1 is for the dare devils, row 2 is for the ones who can’t handle but still wanna a act hard, and row… https://t.co/3qUXzlN90C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love being a little mysterious @ Fashion Institute of Technology https://t.co/5BPxmH7iBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was pre-camera phone era so no but man, did we have fun back then at Witherspoonz @wsyx6 Columbus, OH didn’t we… https://t.co/vevD763Moi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamXMen on @TyltEnt—can't wait for the X-Men to join the MCU https://t.co/mPcwfb6IE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radiotopia 6 badass #podcreator teams @Afroqueerpod #LongDistanceRadio  @CocotazoMedia @cgbpodcast @lasraraspodcast #WTYH2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC Considering the stats have been wrong before I am not trusting all the numbers. However sadly I believe peo… https://t.co/T5Q5HUzQje]]></document><document><![CDATA[ur kid may be a psychopath. no one else would have that kind of restraint]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do as well, but it’s not simple ketchup on my eggs.  It’s 55% ketchup - 45% Tabasco  Painstakingly blended. Voila!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMarcusP You are out of your mind, or getting paid to say such a lie My sister is a doctor and with her salary sh… https://t.co/gKCbyPrgzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Another lie and temper tantrum from the spoiled brat. #NotMyPresident #Resist #RiseUp #ENOUGH… https://t.co/5Nw9jZC9yF]]></document><document><![CDATA[One step forward, @JulieMann01. Woman jailed for 11 years for performing FGM on her 3-year-old daughter https://t.co/Dy2ktRwJqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flights haven’t been bought yet but I’m STOKED to be heading to DC at the end of March for a few days. I LOVE the S… https://t.co/mBVpZBXv0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Classics: McDonald’s Classics are, without a doubt, the best thing to happen to bacon. #TeamClassics FTW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ultrahottie2000 Brady even when together comes to chloe's rescue! And always there for each other !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t moved from this spot on the couch all day. Partially because I don’t want to and partially because duke i… https://t.co/9XlDElWrxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day!! #toknowmeistoloveme #completemess 💁🏻‍♀️❤️😂 https://t.co/hpNWZQm4ez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActuallyNPH This is precisely what someone who IS the Peacock would say.... 🤨 #ImOnToYou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FernandaLedesm2 @RichmondRCMP Because they heard them with their ears instead :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday GYM SESH done! #emojifaces #postworkout #goldsgym #saturdays #gymfriends @ Gold's Gym https://t.co/ZjkcIG9JiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff @senatemajldr Toughest issues 😮 All you need is PETA &amp; a #FakeNews schlockumentry by @CNNFilms… https://t.co/1YdsJ2VFiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Faith is not believing in my own unshakable belief. Faith is believing an unshakable God when everything in me tre… https://t.co/YRrcfLnbmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always in our ♥️ #missingyou #happyanniversary❤️ #takentoosoonbutneverforgotten #momanddad #cancersucks… https://t.co/TJxyJ49bTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dluthor2 I watch the flash, arrow, supergirl (which all of them I’m behind) and legacies. And eventually Roswell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALZIRALOPES18 @JulgoLEVE A DESOBEDIENCIA civil e necessaria. Ate greves para anular multas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely devastated at the loss of Luke Perry. I never sadly got to ever meet him but I feel like I knew him, he… https://t.co/8NFp0LrzI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sweet to be present as these precious students had this experience! #BISDpride]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JonniJonni @_taii53 and that’s a straight fact!! cus i know a nigga from my old college who did that shit, im rea… https://t.co/AMwVqstBqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamiltonParks17 @THATAsianIC @TooLegitTeach @TechTiesThomas @sblakeney3 @ShastaLooper @psjoseph718 @franguinnrogers @AustinGreene5 I’m in!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please show this right wing nut how a #BlueWave #Democrat influences these polls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out to theater with my Trevi Trev! #momandsondate #aladdinonbroadway #hisfavorite #genieisthebest https://t.co/729Kq1MZ5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband is the guy stopping st CVS on his way home from work today .......... #ValentineDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Davie_Nelson happy birthday David !! I hope today is the best one yet, don’t party too hard 🎉🎉🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[They r more important to the DemocRATS because all the illegal votes that they will use the steal the election in 2… https://t.co/jL6echI5U6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeKellarQ104 @ZekeQ104 @jillianq104 Sorry y'all. Its not gonna be sunny &amp; 75 😂 we could dream right?? https://t.co/lRyV9ef5g9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was one big #fluffernutter of fundraising. #CriticalRole #Critters https://t.co/nXbmSX51Yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muricatveagle @bowlingforwentz @imlost056 @Fourens_ People that are unnecessarily rude should probably roll one to… https://t.co/cOcznoml77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deltadeb9860 @AOC Luckily, we didn't just get out of kindergarten and know only too well that the Green New Deal is nonsense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wedding season is right around the corner and I am getting so excited!! 💕 I am working with some of the most amazin… https://t.co/eKL4UICyX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roach @jaymaymo I totally agree with this on a theoretical level, but on an emotional level I’m always thinking “h… https://t.co/5s06lWHG6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so disappointed in myself I really wanted to be on time for the first time this week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian That girl didn’t do anything but hang out!! Yes he kissed her she said she was ignoring that like… https://t.co/jvtixgQhRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsolomonReports Don't stop investigating - I remember Watergate well, listened to it every day while working as a… https://t.co/c08ILVxqDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who cares????? Think platforn and i don’t mean shoes!!!! @KamalaHarris please tell her @RealCandaceO tell her...let… https://t.co/d4d7hULMCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dark Cherry Manhattan = adult Dr. Pepper @ Fiammé https://t.co/UIwGILawov]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to stop Luna from coming up the stairs so she wouldn’t go to my room and I accidentally knocked her down the stairs 😭😭😭😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want this as a tattoo.  It means "whatever will be,  will be" In French ❤ https://t.co/S9l7znYAAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I watch @starwars I just want a light saber and then want to get a Millennium Falcon to go save the univ… https://t.co/9MOAX4ShWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusanCJenkins @PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump What are you babbling about. 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feels likes the crack of dawn, but it's a beautiful day to do some live announcing. Especially on the beach!  . . .… https://t.co/aVGHb5O53Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[You cannot for the life of you have your own personality and it’s honestly sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevotedPages @lmhalloran @Jolievinesx @NanaMalone @jsamanbooks @AuthorGabG ❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another leg day in the books.... #goodlifefitness #legday #press #squat #girlswholift #strong #weights… https://t.co/RPIhH3nlAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @dbongino @GOPChairwoman @PastorDScott @DonaldJTrumpJr In Dearborn,Mi. the city council voted No Free… https://t.co/xHNhF4CYeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Why has life become a plan To put some money in my hand When the love I really need  Is stupid cheap”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alecmjohnson1 @TCS37 This was a great way to get a ton of pics of milfs https://t.co/YNzgrinZDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone should access to this kind of healthcare. It should be the norm, not the exception.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WBHUAlum will be glad to know that with each link my mom sent about this article included a subscription to @OOMLPodcast #BusinessIsBooming]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t believe Ezra Miller was in NY on saturday IN timesquare WHEN i was... the universe fake AF 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff Yeah we all know what his executive time is for... https://t.co/jjfcc7wJB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noon on the E.Coast- sometimes referred to as 'one of the Twitter RUSH HOURS.'  Can we dedicate THIS HOUR to focusi… https://t.co/cf0zPnf8Mu]]></document><document><![CDATA[i told my uncle i was turning 21 in a couple of weeks and he said “uhhh i think you could pass for 16 or 17”]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was worth risking frostbite to be at this vigil and beautiful memorial.  There was a great turnout  from the com… https://t.co/ShwuKMyEwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when I was going to go back to school? That seems like a whole lifetime ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow guys I really didn’t this the time change would throw me off so much because I slept so much over the weekend,… https://t.co/3F2dp7WQ3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner Bernie, please step aside, it's time for us to hand over the realms to a younger generation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because you have cleaning supplies in a closet, doesn't mean you can't bring in some decor.  #cle #cleveland… https://t.co/PZraHtEbpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your March Kids Calendar: 10 ideas to get you through to Spring https://t.co/nWJ1OGrc4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[The week caught up with me, so I've got supervision to keep me in bed. @ Forest Hills, New York https://t.co/eXp1GOwkmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What Cassie did to you is what you did to me”...say it again for the people in the back...🗣 https://t.co/4bvHJrK49j]]></document><document><![CDATA[having a conversation about the craziest things we did to avoid giving a guy our number...  the winner is: using AS… https://t.co/VN5UV5oliO]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is humorous. #hilarity #lol #grin #jolly https://t.co/sB6yUGi6Jl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose Why does the US still have 22 Muslim Islamic compounds? With connections to terrorist why are the… https://t.co/IMtOrfUv5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mirror in my bedroom fell down and my cat Bruiser didn’t know that it was his reflection. Now I know I can’t ge… https://t.co/5KWqy5v6wN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sofia: wow you have beautiful eyes.        Me: they change from blue, to gray, to green depending on my mood and wh… https://t.co/IDj1Bl1Rwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Debating if I should straighten my hair or leave it curly for tonight someone help me ☹️☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you find out the deep things of God? Can you find out the  limit of the Almighty? Job 11:7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanvir_h @TrevorABranch @UKRI_News @EPSRC @innovateuk Oh what a surprise – not! It would be really nice if there w… https://t.co/YDWwLsuLIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Copeasaurus Wait what, how did I miss this? You're like the only beer drinker I know that is (besides me...pescetarian)]]></document><document><![CDATA[and @SenThomTillis also knows how to do the right thing for the wrong reasons.    thanks, though, thom. thanks.… https://t.co/NgQSMZAVgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just ordered a food scale. Gonna start counting my macros 💪🏻 it’s gonna be over for you bitches soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Workout alert 💥💪🏽💥   I love these 3 combos- they’re all such a fun challenge! Here are a few of my favorite ways to… https://t.co/2XOgVx150G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yesenia_yc Lol but she also posts about Sky so I think she loves her too 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorJohnHagee @HageeMinistries @RepMikeJohnson @jasonrapert @GovMikeHuckabee SEE THREAD of RECENT REAL CENSORSHI… https://t.co/bLMBT99BAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JazzJennings__ @TLC So happy you don't need the third surgery. God is good. Congrats baby girl.]]></document></documents></author>