<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed this one well! A solid sour!! - Drinking  The Eye of SOURon by @resolutebrewingco at @ResoluteBrewCo  — https://t.co/Nmi8gd3W4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proposed Mugshot Rule Pits Privacy Against the Public's Right to Know: Associations Now https://t.co/uvNpjuEMBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HDGibby10 @HomerFundGeek @Lexie2504 @b_mungul @EmgeJim @AndraeSM2510 How Do With Nothing But Respect For All ... https://t.co/daRsWt4vK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: "I will try dating!"  Also me: "Everything about this is stressful and awkward. Tell me why I can't just wake u… https://t.co/z3NiLDtX0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #Westchester, IL? https://t.co/RdGFliTxdk #Finance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raw results for March 11, 2019: McIntyre makes WrestleMania statement by dismantling Ambrose in Falls Count Anywher… https://t.co/OP1B1Pjsy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women in any situation where the demand respect, power, and take on challenges are often attacked with a gender bia… https://t.co/HyJchQjedP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously need to stop pulling all-nighters for no reason other than to fuck myself over]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #PresidentsDay to the first 44 of them only. Don’t @ me until 45’s term is up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[President: @SadlyCatless  Vice President: @OhNoSheTwitnt  First Spouse: @CatFoodBreath  First Pet: @ellle_em  Chief… https://t.co/BBSPrtmoZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Blackhawks have a very meaningful game today. Important hockey has returned to the Madhouse. I'm happy. https://t.co/yRSFO5VwPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HornintheOzarks @RoyBlunt No. Something I read I thought Roy should read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EA_KRAELO any update on an update to fix the update? Any info would be great. Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These stupid idiots are being exploded by fuck news, but they do not care. These are just two stupid bitches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here reading Twilight Of The Gods while the wife meal plans and watches reruns of Roseanne...and up pops Bo… https://t.co/kvFjU4RGVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[100 career titles for @rogerfederer I’m amazed and honored to be living in the same age as the great one. #GOAT #KingFed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really hope this Antonio Brown deal falls through so I can watch buffalo yet again collapse]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys night in...! #newsupermariobrosudeluxe #videogames #pizzanight @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/IQG5HU3ZFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R_O_Donovan Also getting late in the day over there.  Doesn’t appear as if it’ll happen today.  Why wait?]]></document><document><![CDATA[bout to walk into oxidation and reduction in chem next week. Dear lord save me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flyers play great for all of February. Get beat by the best team in the NHL. Flyers fans instantly https://t.co/RNl8i63nRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AprilFools less than a month away got me:  @EvidenceRobot needs a Systematic Review of Systematic Reviews.  Also,… https://t.co/uMW7R4vznw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clarinetlaj @CPC_HQ @MaximeBernier @peoplespca @CivicJeremy @KellyRDay19 @BrunswickBeard you will be looking for that soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetin_yogirl @tommieclark094 @DannyJay3 We were like 20 tryna get lit off anything lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChildishAmbeeno Exhibit A: Sitting next to Joanna in the car after letting her get double shots all night post-breakup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdr9090 Only after Trump is impeached for destroying America and his obstruction of Justice. I don’t know how you… https://t.co/4yKpUESQN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter followers, I need your help. Our local school board is screwing over special needs kids, and I need you all… https://t.co/KLflVTGXBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Space friends Jean Wright, Julian Leek , Alicia Murphy posing with @ulalaunch CEO @torybruno at his talk "ULA's Tra… https://t.co/zpenaijuzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Dallas, TX? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Engineer Full St… https://t.co/bmuhw2y2o6]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it comes to sleep, I’m kinda thinkin’ “f*ck it”... anybody up for Waffel House? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sjrobin2014 @DanCrenshawTX Not only new gun purchases but inter family and friend transfers and loans as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BancadaRC_ @EcuavisaInforma @RTS_LaNoticia @24horasUIO @TelediarioEC @Gamanoticiasec @tctelevision @CanalUnoTv… https://t.co/LOUn9oFXjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soy inteligente lo sabe mi gente, que siempre me la he rifado, yo tengo mi ambiente y ya estaba enfadado, de llevarmela encerrado]]></document><document><![CDATA[Witness protection is going to do absolutely nothing to hide those stupid tattoos]]></document><document><![CDATA[#handmadesoap at #artboxlv #supportlocal   #lasvegaslocal @ Art Box Designs Fused Glass Art https://t.co/lPgzlDEVvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to see Sally, sad to miss Lucy's concert. But it will be fun. @ Edina Performing Arts Center https://t.co/Gto27DR0z2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really can’t take DT serious anymore, Cohen already stated that they didn’t take the election serious. He has to be trolling us now...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the @BAM_MS_Official  Symphonic Band on their unanimous Superior rating at Assessment this weeke… https://t.co/Ic2IZHRhTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emlaughsallot88 @rexglacer Liberal solutions are the major source of all our problems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaVey141 @CJOlanasty33 @jd_gregory1 @BcTheWrestler22 @dylanwisman @LaVey141 You got 3 out of the 4 State Champs that are in the picture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@98PXYRochester I do, but when I do I don’t mean to, if that makes sense. Or I start saying it and then I turn into… https://t.co/EQhADi0rPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliaDavisNews @soledadobrien Our allies are clearly communicating (or, in this case non-communicating) their displeasure with us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot sausage and turkey sandwich drizzled in bbq sauce and made with love!!  Excellent breakfast food!! #food #love… https://t.co/6k5ssd9rTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready for “pushing your Uber up an icey hill season” to be over with]]></document><document><![CDATA[To brighten your Monday morning! #GoDawgs #thispictureisreal https://t.co/xiMFYMrE5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Bron want Coach K to Coach the Lakers😂😂😂😂 that shid will neva happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys Being alone or with Someone that Enjoys some SILENCE! Is HEALTHY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_ankrom @LaunaSallai @gatewaypundit Shut up Booker and eat your lettuce!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valenciam07 Y todo lo que Peña nieto hizo al país, Porque ahí nunca criticaste nada. Lambe huevos. . . Porque no h… https://t.co/cKA7fQMQbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big night for @TheMeadowlands; handling over $3.6 Million last night. Hopefully momentum off the first purse increase continues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Cast thy burden upon the Lord, and he shall sustain thee: he shall never suffer the righteous to be moved.” Psalms 55:22 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Wow Factor by @EurekaHeights @ iPic Theaters — https://t.co/ChFfsBcyxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani @DunkelBier_Jay Hehehe @RudyGiuliani said “integrity”. hehehe https://t.co/dKQEtC3Fbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte @LabattBreweries @jamesonwhiskey @PAWineSpirits @ATT https://t.co/xBwXUmYgrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmhorp That’s a great article. Does this mean “Infrastructure Week” has finally arrived?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robin_ked @KAT40811334 @45HarisonHarold @Michaelcraddo16 @JSWDH1 @Trustedfriend2 @ParisTwatter @LadyChesapeake… https://t.co/R9bZDLRA2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiegoMB27 @ITF_Tennis To open up qualies draws yes and one ranking only]]></document><document><![CDATA[Completely didn't know Frank wasn't introduced until season 2. Either way I breezed through it and have been into s… https://t.co/dDTAE3rrMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkFreemanLaw Oh... And I loved the way you sucked up to Vladeck - "sir" - when he never bought your story either. LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“How you die at 30 something after gang banging all those years?” #RIPTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[“They will fight you, but they will fail. For I am with you, and I will take care of you. I, the Lord, have spoken!… https://t.co/JJ9paMtvtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought Woodley was all that, if I’m being honest. He relies way too much on his counter right hand and his… https://t.co/K96LK3j1Ym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CesarsamperioG @CartonCalderon Solo que seas narco. Por que la guerra fue contra los narcos, no contra los ciudada… https://t.co/kVA9i8QUiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is always so inspiring talking to Sean Cowper and Lacey Romero at Share the Love food pantry! They are jump-out-… https://t.co/WJZ1JEtg5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHBAmador Lately I’ve had a lot of book editing so I’ll have a large drip coffee and a large latte, so, um, I’m pr… https://t.co/PgyTtZcFFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[YESSS! Support of this screenplay will MAKE THE MOVIE HAPPEN! That's all 💯👍🏾🎯✔️🖌 That's our #1 goal now to buy, rea… https://t.co/8ysCjX5rrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[False grip is your friend!   A little bit of training before this weekend’s competition. 🤸🏻‍♂️… https://t.co/zz0msvuFUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Walking Dead #188 #thewalkingdead #walkingdead #backissues #swipe #swipeleft #twdfamily #twd #imagecomics… https://t.co/KzUuH6ikKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[High schooler: You’re a writer? How fast can you type.   Me: 300 – 500 words an hour.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mochamewz @Texas_Dexter @JosephBadal XD  SO CUTE!    *makes snow leopard sounds*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a great night with @saintdle - the recurring topic was the #vCommunity - there is so much value in it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErnestoHGII @KinelRyan I can’t even imagine being a grown man caring about someone blocking them on twitter. Serio… https://t.co/3aDlQ8XXV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[AC Filters 4 Less on #Google: https://t.co/QxFyEyRQLb https://t.co/cfCUfgBDwF Call Now 954-588-7774]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for a pleasant, fun-to-read film nerd thread with zero acrimony or stupidity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GopOf210 If she would have only been caught under @BarackObama !  He would have pardoned her and sent her back to… https://t.co/v6gZ46dFwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m good at leaving my mark! State to State💁🏾‍♀️ #BklynTyeWuzHere #February16th #2019 #PrinceWilliamCounty… https://t.co/y8WWxgeYvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @9_11_IsAnInside @AE911Truth @xrey1 @Boeing @BoeingAirplanes @FBI Is this an attack on Trump?...i believe… https://t.co/htHXodHUHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugas wins round 10. He’s up 96-94 on my scorecard .. #boxing #PorterUgas #PBConFOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cornpuddy @Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump Ryan what criminal registers the guns they use to commit crimes with? It… https://t.co/2emKTzQg8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usaf__vet @nytmike @maggieNYT @adamgoldmanNYT @anniekarni @RepMarkMeadows He can't stand up while he's on his knees servicing his Master.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilentUschi (((Ties slice of pizza to Booker and has him run with it))) that should get her up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- why is this so important? C- my head is annoyed by voices every waking moment.  Do you want life to be able to s… https://t.co/ioTpH2QNF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndrew_lawrence For now honestly knowing the facts and truth. Once the investigation is completed and revealed to t… https://t.co/GZE0VUoiIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cityatlas @rgunns @bentleyballan The tank thing wasn't a design issue so much as a decision to make a tank (the Sh… https://t.co/ASUVsqAn21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeySalads @AudacityOfHoops @zig314 @JonathanM0ral35 @AOC You are literally too stupid to insult. She's proposing… https://t.co/PpaozxIKJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patriots @Gillette “The video that we obtained -- it shows the act that took place,” he said. “On every gentlemen… https://t.co/vX6MKQpMIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MZHemingway Post now realizes the story was flawed. The defamation of a private citizen is a legal issue. The Post… https://t.co/cLMtOj3hsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer Folks should just accept that you’re not gonna go away unless a new younger, hotter country comes along...]]></document><document><![CDATA[We'll discuss how the #Rays look to deploy the opener, plus the zany ideas coming to the Atlantic League, the legac… https://t.co/Oq8q1FUQFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed anti socialist trope is strong in #GOP  And we know they call the cops or firemen at the drop of a hat and h… https://t.co/JVrsxIysuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Maryland I-95 North Welcome Center - @travelmd in Savage, MD https://t.co/AZap1IQb27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wine bags shouldn't exist because, I, personally, don't know how to act like a functioning human being.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus is the only way to get through any difficult situation! Our trails/difficulties in our lives are megaphones t… https://t.co/pnliCtdGm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NascarChuck336 Today's Cohen boondoggle was orchestrated by the Clintons and the Clinton's lawyer. This was Hillary's revenge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[brb about to throw up . I just sent off my first talent request for a client to walk the red carpet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/mLTs4jxhOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gravity-1  Tyler- 0  Bouldering with the boys is a great way to spend a Monday morning. #bouldering #climbing #fail… https://t.co/3ZFnjjZqo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then when i think of the team we had in 97 and 98... Omg were we stacked.  I want a time machine. I wanna relive th… https://t.co/K2a07aUPWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haynesworthiii @InsTech_af @apsu2045 @KayilanEsat @wyu50320 @RENAISSANCEUS @Dritt31 @monibhachu @KAMOGADERRICK6… https://t.co/4h5qiHdjzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day to this one! Love you very much xxxx ❤️ @ DeKalb County, Georgia https://t.co/iOnIz9u94V]]></document></documents></author>