<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[You know something is wrong with isiaha when he doesn’t bring his toy story gang with him to the dr 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leading High Quality &amp; Soft Leggings Manufacturers USA https://t.co/h68HpVOv03 #leggingdistributorscanada… https://t.co/QDp94LPy2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexWhittler “It came in clutch with the last minute purchases back in the day” aka for me that means last month and last week 😂😭🤷🏽‍♀️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewNadeau0 did you see? Did you see? I’m going to be a real educated lady. Not a pretend one anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sad and homesick and just saw a video on my snap chat memories where Malibu was wearing a collar and so I think… https://t.co/I6XZM03zml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marshall6218 wow thanks for being so generous as to posting the most flattering picture that has ever been documen… https://t.co/VclTqqesJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HHLifestyleTrav @Sostraveluk @poetixtrip @Adventuringgal @travelwithirine @sl2016_sl @JulesHalvy @Nicolette_O… https://t.co/iaoHqIDbuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinTweets4 I’d imagine! Gathering the specific info from your clients must have  been a huge effort.  Go Team!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaPutrelli @acidoviejo @adribilu @usembassyMVD Por supuesto que la gente arriesga la vida para escapar de países comunistas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCampo13 @TheRickWilson The problem with many Dems is they want it NOW. We have to know how to play the long game.… https://t.co/zEmqir07HM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SavannahBayBVI Im going to take a look at Jaime Harris who's running against Graham.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best book ever!!! Madeleine #McCann died in apartment 5A. Cadaver dogs alerted to her mother’s pants and wardro… https://t.co/x6v7LNIiyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oooooo_Donna @TheRickWilson @cristynes @DNC No one pays me to make these decisions but that second provision would… https://t.co/y9TmxjPM0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you really like a movie/show on @netflix so you look at the “more like this” and realize you have watched them… https://t.co/Zm7U8QHu9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[J'ai bien commencée ma journée en écoutant Joe Berridge, associé de Urban Strategies Inc., donner une présentation… https://t.co/ba4VDF8Czi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe. OH NO NO NO NO You aren't doing it to us again with TRUMP RALLY! CLICK CLICK CLICK YOU PROMISED NOT TO DO THIS AGAIN!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goingglocal some healthcare plans do offer full coverage of preventive care but it depends on the  insurance plan… https://t.co/9BRxg9XE1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoesURDogBite @DeepStateExpose @realDonaldTrump I'm still waiting for anyone from the Trump persuasion to explain… https://t.co/n3V952hVeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZFishFFish Or sitting in an office in the Breslin Center! https://t.co/233wSa8ZG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-cheer competition #FunFriday!! #ETCAllStars #Cheetahs #Panthers #AllStarCheer #Cheerleading @ Dunkin' Donuts https://t.co/6nDtmsS6cW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Word on the street you got hoes I disappear like El Chapo”  same same -@KALIUCHIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxorosette @Jimostenes @convoynetwork @korno @Radiohen @drabasa Hola, no worries! El #tristeturno va de 7 a 9 de la mañana ✌🏼😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GHMansfield It seems it's okay to discriminate against disabled people, look how people with serious health issues… https://t.co/OOXgIPnUzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awe I don’t know if she knows I can totally see her screen shotting my snaps ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[ultimate FOMO. this is why New York is the best (when it’s not being the worst).]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear i will NEVER put a good world in for anybody else to get a job under my name.. Shit even your closest frien… https://t.co/4MOZzrjuOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[She hit THE FUCK out her head 😭😭😭😭😭😭😭 istg if I woke up and seen my man did some shit like this I’m beating his ass… https://t.co/E0rsmjCey2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s safe to say everyone has been affected by cancer in one way or another. I’m selling “Hope” and “Love” boards t… https://t.co/Pc0Yp7eMqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those that would like to donate to Dustyn’s memorial fund here is a link to the GoFundMe: https://t.co/f3ImtCoeAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Errrrbody needs to watch this amazing show!!! Binge it. Tell your friends and familia. @everythingloria odaatnetfli… https://t.co/ZP7iqjxITc]]></document><document><![CDATA[BUSH TRIAL: Quick recap: In 2016, 2 groups of people were arguing at 4011 W. Virden Court over a belt. State’s atto… https://t.co/hLQhuWLK9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yaaasss haven’t seen gnmedley in ages and she looks INCREDIBLE, btw. #ZuluBall #ZuluSocialAidAndPleasureClub… https://t.co/izFNc9CfKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freeyourmindkid Because society does not judge men as harshly for their looks as they do women. But evil does age you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodijodijodi I wanted to say something but couldn't figure out how without it coming off as rude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Name just one thing you’ve done for our veterans? Besides not paying our Coast Guard during the ho… https://t.co/5hyc4w426Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qui mom li mouy lakk si français dou diam, mane dale dam ko fan rek. Kegn lay degg yi ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veryhip4u @LastStand2019 He said while crossing his fingers behind his back. Lawyers are by &amp; large professional liars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy happy happy birthday @Jacksonwynn54 !!!!🌟🎉🎉 https://t.co/q0ZXCiONAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am soo thankful today’s my day off, my back hurts soo bad, been laying down all day w the heating pad &amp; heating blanket]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost my art passion (honestly, lost other hopes and passions too) but I know I want to get back into it. Making cho… https://t.co/EWNhf9KJ2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_GNation1 He used to do a Valentine’s show here in Atlanta every year. Not sure if he still does, but I’ve been a couple times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retweeted Another judge bought off. Manifort did worse then the Congressmen who Judge Ellis threw the book at. By t… https://t.co/ZOClB05wr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenn_VanHorn @bushofficial @GavinRossdale @CT3GUITAR @coreybritz @robingoodridge @wilkesbarrePA You’re very welcom… https://t.co/ivDZzed80T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OkizemeDes I mean i understand that completely. I just don’t believe it’s that serious 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentines dinner is ready nachismo17 😏 @ Oakland, California https://t.co/VDOq1PpXwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 nights @TheGarden in the span of 4 days... Always a blast 💯 (Still not a @nyknicks fan, sorry!) https://t.co/LRhVlQu1MS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KnightlyMike (for Whitney) I know its hard but better that you get in to see someone that can help you sooner than later.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1956 Mark II, previously owned by Benson Ford.  #ameliaislandconcours2019 #NPD @ The Ritz-Carlton, Amelia Island https://t.co/gk4umMQUvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherLyWGRZ @MattGlynnBflo Ahh! You smart TV person, you! It was driving me crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarisInigoVFs @kapalmoks23 @NigoMar @AirahAquino8 @Mabelskie09 @maloumunar422 @JudaelB @CharmineBalles2 Who u ka daw lol  #POPSSSS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie is a professional LIAR! One of his spectacular works of fiction in real time and full color is detail… https://t.co/VEYaQIE8hg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok Greeley Fans ....this is why we need everyone’s support this Wed. If TZ fans were ejected at CC, they will surel… https://t.co/sFltwLIBBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rollwthepunches @thegymterdotnet @LaurenHopkins96 Exactly how I read that too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[╭ ◜◝ ͡ ◝ ͡◜◝  ╮ (     Thinking ) (             Of   )   (           You )    ╰     ͜      ╯                     O… https://t.co/6W8raoL18p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aldotcom @BamaProUpdates Bad list. You can say 100 greatest.. gotta be pro or college..Sullivan never made it as a… https://t.co/HjYcdvRltp]]></document><document><![CDATA[In other news... to the people call this gross, have you eaten ballpark food? 🤮🤮🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for american_grappling_federation   #jiujitsu #bjj #757bjjkids #jiujitsufamily @ Boo Williams Sportsplex https://t.co/VAtzg01Fvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[the great thing about getting your wisdom teeth removed is that your nose looks so cute and tiny compared to the rest of your swollen face]]></document><document><![CDATA[We took a break from all the theme parks during our holiday to take a ride on @iconorlando360. We even got a capsul… https://t.co/7C0vfCQ4K0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oprah once said, Breathe. Let go. And remind yourself that this very moment is the only one you know you have for… https://t.co/qJ1x0zZM0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, wondering why I never actually stop and explore LAX?¿ I think I’m due for a long weekend in my near future here]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Memoir:  Your Journey, an Inheritance https://t.co/DzyMe0zWuY via @wordpressdotcom                         @moonbridgebooks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buy a #NewHome in #California  If your #Negligent #Builder #Lennar screws you, trust me #Government cares none!… https://t.co/HRDR7Gvh49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OttNik I feel like I need to delete all his songs from my library. Ugh. Tainted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the Jonas Brothers coming back is a sign that summer 2019 is gonna be like summer 2008]]></document><document><![CDATA[The "buck" you make won't last as long as the difference you've made! 🤔😊 https://t.co/FtAjkyv1oH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throw back to last Sunday at The Total Mom Show where I had the opportunity to discuss work life balance on the sel… https://t.co/N2QQAI6KQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend is always trying to out do me with gifts. I got him 4 pairs of yeezy 500, and he gets me a LV bag. :’)]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my lil sisters friends dad is a bartender/server at Grand Lux and he’s totally cool with it bc he makes a shit ton of money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would Netflix get rid of Sons of anarchy??? I was on the 3rd season and stopped watching it for like 2 months and now it’s gone😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet @AmyTidd @HillaryClinton @StormResist @mcspocky @TheSWPrincess @DanaScottLO @drbashir2018… https://t.co/QKzsXhnUcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[hola guapos de monterrey soy nueva aqui quien me habla y salimos https://t.co/ujJT4oJaCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[ONE WEEK FROM TONIGHT! Come to LA's Premier Dance Experience! Class, with a bit of Sass. See everyone soon!  • •… https://t.co/WEh20vucZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP is scared of Mike Cohen.  All they can is do is trash Cohen.  People of America can see thru this #CohenCongressionalTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t goto another concert soon... I will literally listen to somebody grandma’s cover of wonderwall https://t.co/dRY4fjG4HF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The main reason veteran readers rarely fail spectacularly is that they’ve failed before.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski @DevinNunes This has to the moronic post I have ever seen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS is why I believe that Learning Walks are such a powerful tool/experience. ❤️💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beniboi21 @MammothLax @RocKnighthawks That is a big loss and really sad 😢😢😢😢😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pulled out one of your chairs with my backpack strap this morning @kait_butti]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is beyond stupid ,,, how are y’all just gon aim for this kind of audience. kids will do what ever they watch o… https://t.co/hnOUFFz8Ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was pulling out of the Starbucks Drive-thru and the guy said “ See you Latte” 🧐  I don’t know what to think!! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moms are the only people who know the true meaning of 24/7.  Yay for our... https://t.co/1SpCmxz58F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tee10202 @PrimeCreator2 @tine614 @JeremyRobards7 @2newearth777 @111DE111DE111 @markjohnt2 @FlaRhps @Amorpheus333… https://t.co/O8ifMnj07Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when I tried to go on a month cleanse? Yeah. Impossible, because put two girl who are down for anything to… https://t.co/Vf0mwcbpqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, when you speak on me and say that "she ain't put together," don't forget to mention I got my shit together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wretchedthings @mschelseareed Chelsea is a  Mean Ol’  Insidious  Sniveling  Trickster Perpetuating Everyone’s Eternal Nuisance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC you must be getting old since you can’t remember last year you said we don’t need the wall. That j… https://t.co/B0gGtBqwSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cckayd @hauntedmuseum It is nice to have no distractions for my own senses, but an EVP meter would have been nice… https://t.co/micavUksNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Colearning and #Valueadded are priorities when developing and  nurturing #researchrelationships as well as… https://t.co/2Vx0zir3no]]></document><document><![CDATA[My school is having a Step It Up! Fitness Fundraiser to raise money for programs we love. I'd be thrilled if you co… https://t.co/dposlxuk33]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roxiqt @orphaned_annie Although. I read a book called What Made Maddy Run about a very talented Ivy League student… https://t.co/S8lbDlJMF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skingfam @DanOHerrin @AnthemRespect I disagree. A change is not a given but neither is remaining the same. Remembe… https://t.co/V6saJwHfbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our first newbie is Kristin! A fellow runner and lover of a good time. She is ready for the long haul. https://t.co/pgFlyVMIjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss the beach so much! @ Fort Myers Beach, Florida https://t.co/9Poy1ADOpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fleissmeister is really out here trolling Kim K and teasing about Khloe being the next Bachelorette and it is prob… https://t.co/b7PsHrWgce]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here {born/raised in the south} trying to picture myself eating a roll like @BachelorABC is saying I’m supp… https://t.co/U5RIYA3KIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to be in the room with great elementary principals from across the state and represent @MASALeaders during… https://t.co/39tbuM0G1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @MaddowBlog Because the dog would get more attention than trump and he couldn't live with that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wownotever @danwolfgang_ I do not disagree with you. But I also do not see Venezuela as a good example of a hornet… https://t.co/NZFIOecx2k]]></document></documents></author>