<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[i've watched one episode of #UmbrellaAcademy and all the episodes of misfits, and props to robert sheehan for being… https://t.co/7HpvEBN3Aj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Democrats are happy about this because they have no use for law enforcement!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoIsLife @Andy No she's really not it's all fake phony it's all an act just so that she could stay on Housewive… https://t.co/nJdYPKNPvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So who forged your nomination for a Nobel Peace Prize? The FBI is on it! You’re the new low. Right… https://t.co/QUmuVXYsG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The analysis found that Roche Holding AG's Herceptin breast cancer drug, after rebates of roughly 15 percent, still… https://t.co/5jrOieP5g5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrashFlutist Ah, I can see how so much hinges on it. You don’t want to be hurtful but also don’t want to stoke any… https://t.co/XzeEzztYCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatWomanKL @maxbergmann Ryan has won the 'mob boss for a day' award. And of course he will forever be pushing gran… https://t.co/cyl50Y9mck]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My biggest fear is someone not being ready to get engaged at the end of all of this”. Cassie: I’m not ready I don’… https://t.co/BQ34up0lMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I worked Friday-Sunday, 3 12 hour shifts and on my day off today I woke up at 2:30 in the afternoon 😂 the life of a nurse]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out someone that I’ve known for a long time works at the same job as my mom and my mom told me she yel… https://t.co/WDDcuv0MxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at CVS Health? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and informa… https://t.co/dtDKfdigvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr And what is a child sitting in a classroom? And what is a weapon that can gun down mass amounts of IN… https://t.co/9jYHJWBodw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t sleep! I gotta go to work shortly myself!! I just wanna know if she’s in the studio or satellite interview!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excuse the ever loving fuck out of me. What the hell? @DrPsyBuffy I’m so over it all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence @KamalaHarris Oh yeah...we can expect more of this shit as we get closer to 2020! From the DUM DEM PARTY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyOstroy I wonder what god says when he hears these people say he put this guy in the WH !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrbanikMarysel @RedRiverReport @uniquedeehan1 @templar003 @rkline56 @kathyja74921323 @SongBird4Trump… https://t.co/hzX0jVtEpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyCrouppen @IanSohn I wrote a full script before speaking to Jon Kim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[La gente está cansada de tanto atropello y de tanto engaño; ya saben quién es quien.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikkywalks is so cool and elegant as Aaron Burr in @hamiltonmusical eventually building to the ferocious intensity… https://t.co/7YjYcsDzjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo que dejar de querer tanto a la gente porque lo único que saben aser es aprovecharse de uno y aserme sentir como mierda !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone that Needs #Promotions I have NEW packages!! HIT MY EMAIL: pbebianca@gmail.com (be sure to include details of what you need)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AyuntamientoCLN puras motos de empresas..   con una prepotencia los oficiales, se les pide de  buena manera la mot… https://t.co/sMefjxwBVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malnsol @fairoaksmall @GlasgowMS @AcevedoWrites This is on the top of my TBR pile!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for having @RepGainey @LeonFordSpeaks @LeonFordSpeaks  as well as myself @sloan_amber as special guest for t… https://t.co/4Ww2DciErY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all the women @LBECDC and @dcpublicschools who continue to invest time in our young female scholars. C… https://t.co/lxnUWwvLjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Best President Ever! He will never give up on us! He will fight for what is right and He will figh… https://t.co/taNPEDoGLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lanabtrull Dr. Fenton is literally the man. That dude knows everything. Need ya back cracked? Need to learn how to… https://t.co/c0UPhMYeNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just left my spoon in the fucking microwave with my soup..and turned the fucking thing on.. and it went for about… https://t.co/e1OlzLR2Uc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I know so many people who have died of an overdose in the past month it’s crazy. Get this shit off the streets.… https://t.co/egOA6J60YB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @WWENetwork @WWERomanReigns Great documentary.  Welcome back Big Dog.  Glad you are feeling better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo please do not have @KellyannePolls on your show. I have to turn it off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only good part about my current job. 170 lbs of goofball!!! He was SUCH a pain to wash. He barely fit in the tu… https://t.co/gGNIWaqVcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all the travel recently, I just now realized Mardi Gras is NEXT WEEK! And I've only had ONE King Cake! 😱 Lucki… https://t.co/OjyLkt2fdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[STOP SAYING CASSIE WANTS THE BACHELORETTE. Colton goes to get her and they end up together.. don’t worry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomTillis @SenatorCollins @RandPaul @lisamurkowski @JerryMoran @ChrisYoungNV @MittRomney @BenSasse @tedcruz… https://t.co/Zz7rqAyfmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wooooowww...all 10k+ of y’all need to hop off here and into a book. Immediately. That’s a damn shame. https://t.co/kbieEqpNMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign on the shower @ Courtyard by Marriott Tulsa Downtown https://t.co/O5H7e04S74]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been working on my City Council &amp; Mayoral Democratic Candidates getting elected; how about you🇺🇸🥊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate Women’s History Month &amp; Music in our Schools Month! #WomensHistoryMonth  #miosm #TeamSouthBend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for this cozy morning, @KidLitTV_NYC— I loved talking about Becket Branch for the 100th anniversary of… https://t.co/qY6eWu89NQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dominickpurnomo @KathleenSkeals @NorthColonieCSD @Djosephcorr Thank you Dom!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulmeza29 @NadineLabaki @alfonsocuaron I need to watch Roma. I’ve heard great things! #HTownRush]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spaul6414 Sure thing! Would love to connect and learn more about the work you do in the tech education arena]]></document><document><![CDATA[No lie , anytime I post something on my finista I swear I get one unfollow , y’all some woes 😤😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeelPoliceMedia People are complaining are those that never needs the amber alert .... the system works and the gi… https://t.co/mAziIh2Q8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudreyWeaver21 You get tornados and we get a whole lot of white crap.  Going to work later to crash for the night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casieriewerts Nope I just run the podcast business now. Which is so much more business rather than podcasting lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[First night with our new baby boy!😍😻#orangebaby #greeneyes #rescue #kittensofinstagram #alreadyinlove @ Irving, Tex… https://t.co/fjPN2IgMcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[New video up of @FabFitFun box opening and @BhadBhabie copycat new buy!!!! #copycat #fabfitfun https://t.co/0s0vAZpyKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want someone who is not an oil tycoon to explain to me why these are bad things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since no one is awake to beat me to it I get to be the first to say HAPPY 21ST BIRTHDAY to one of my very best frie… https://t.co/PyguVhZN0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉💥🔥Omg!!! This is bad azzzz!!! Congrats!!!! #Awesomeness #Goodguy #Hardwork]]></document><document><![CDATA[@staceymdunnigan I feel like I should know who ... But I don't. Who was the celebration for?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an unexpected, yet incredible, night with good laughs and great friends♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day thanks to Enterprise for the United Way Women’s Leadership lunch! Thank you Mercedes for the fun picture.… https://t.co/D11jZWmrro]]></document><document><![CDATA[HACER lo que realmente AMAS, lo que TE APASIONA, "DE ESO SE TRATA" La vida es demasiado corta como para NO HACER LO… https://t.co/zg9ZnXhdYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am usually v reticent to speak favorably of any corporation (as you all know too well) but I'm really bothered by… https://t.co/Sq6J7kAxuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes of course i believe in tipping but if you do not even try to give me good service you’re barley getting a tip a… https://t.co/I7LhZszIon]]></document><document><![CDATA[everything about @crusharizona_ was PERFECT. Happy two year rave anniversary to me😭 couldn’t have asked for a more… https://t.co/MXDcMu0NmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParhamLogan Malia should not have to live under a microscope; she deserves a private life. She is young and wants… https://t.co/EBXTLERdz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was gonna go to the gym, but I just got off work and have -25 motivation rn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart is fully for chyna , you did it girl ❤️ congratulations DX well well deserved. #HOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Date to @Dombresky this Sunday with @rikki_azulkrema I think yes! 🙏🏽😎❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SocialMedia #Design: 11 #Principles to Improve Your Social Media #Images [#Infographic] https://t.co/Mm4otpPspS vi… https://t.co/1kj3tRPGdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sean O'Brien 50mile,  February 2014. This year was a stacked field of men and women competing for a Western States… https://t.co/n4jd2SdiTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calminthechaos1 Writing from Ontario Canada and in complete tears because a few months ago we did experience a tra… https://t.co/Ud8ocxOtNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PKhakpour A therapist once told me to observe my family members like an anthropologist, or alien--I guess this is… https://t.co/dbdAhWXp9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate that I don’t have time for myself and that’s a bad thing 😖 I seriously get no breaks   #momlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating our building-level honorees at the SJSD Building  Excellence Luncheon today.  Thank you for making a di… https://t.co/Ka5YBymIo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi Why are children locked in rusty dog kennels? What demons are in The White house? What are you doing… https://t.co/eOmLd00pCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @ProtectCatsLDN @WhickyWuudler @mojo_and_scout @MrMeowington1 @Kitty_Cat_Momma @IngloriousCats @OneCopaceticCAT @catrapper]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is where it happened. How do I know? My sprint drive fell from the impact. (2/2) https://t.co/KibLK3QkQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cage, Black Keys, The National, Local Natives ... INDIE ROCK IS BACK BABY]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one in the world deserves the title of my best friend as much as my baby brother.  No one has ever been more wil… https://t.co/wyuXbdFqrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg my dog really just pissed me off bitch lucky she not homeless right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mommandem @alisoninsco @Boatoptional2 @cathyhadenough @canadiandaws83 @CunningSq16 @ShapesBlue @DoloresManley4… https://t.co/3N0JbflXNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/1Q480VQ8gb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone ever restore there lives after allegations or prosecutin ? Praying for all involved]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LeTourDevore4 has kicked off! Tonight we stop at a fav spot of mine, @drinkatwestend ... but first, we preparty wi… https://t.co/FuaHeHPq0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuhFreezePeach @YousefMunayyer @jonathanchait AIPAC does not donate money to political campaigns. So "it's not abo… https://t.co/JF8z9MQR0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is short! Surround yourself with beauty. And buy the damn roses!! https://t.co/GLNJ5Vrofx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caspiansmommy @rhydersmomma Cas always pulls my hair 😩 but it’s okay he makes up for it in cuteness 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never buy me expensive jewelry... I’ve lost my earrings again and these were 4th or 5th replacements already 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ticiamell @gibth I don't think Blake is big on traveling beyond like Canada and Mexico....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill I hope they've been arrested and the children have been taken to good homes. I simply cannot comprehend to… https://t.co/XAhfHeRQQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Sex with Dr. Jess | Blow Jobs, Crushes, Sex Education &amp; Cheating Clauses, let's play it! https://t.co/6X5At1JvwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meow_Ivy Girl, I text you all the time... you just don’t wanna come here lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly.  No double standsrds.  Listen to the song and Retweet it. @tictoc @MikeBloomberg @robreiner… https://t.co/XRS6h7JyUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cab driver put on a Madonna cd just for me... I didn’t ask. #Holiday #Madonna]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you seen my latest scene on @plumperpass   I got this text this morning from a fan who turned client who is no… https://t.co/TOMalDm1L3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The future is now and it's inspiring! @EastonLaChappel #Prosthetics #helpingothers #Robotics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know that February is #NationalBirdFeedingMonth? Go to this link to find out how this theme month came to… https://t.co/V8o6m8P3eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soy yo o los aderezos de Clemente Jacques son los más culeros que pueden existir?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelleismyna2 Wonder if she has anything in that pill bag that can fix SHIT STIRRING ASSHOLE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Quick Name Activities for Helping Kids Learn to Spell Their Names~And tips for how we... #comedy #laugh #smirk… https://t.co/4bXrLA2w7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been working on something for while. Should be available soon at #andyandmandylove #poeticaspirations1#whittierpoet… https://t.co/eiINdNUyFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#girlpower #cancersucks #friends4life @ Dacusville, South Carolina https://t.co/O4x5uSGkCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The French director and the wrangler  #meettheparents #family #visit #baby #stuff #beret #people #plaid #buttonup… https://t.co/H94FZHymGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bloomplanners I need and want this so bad!! So pretty!! Thank you!!💖💖💖]]></document></documents></author>