<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@OfcrMatt Then a. Warrant would have been issued for your arrest lol. How dumb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigCMen I’m confused, Jared just posted about a bag of Oz weed? Don’t get me wrong, to each his own, none of bee’s wax. Just curious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babyajules If it’s a girl next time @Sugar_Plumy11 Ima be like https://t.co/jLhxDahrWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Workin on the night shift baby. It’s been a wreck me week. On the night shift. Baby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy next to me on bart is listening to the six flags theme song on repeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @rodentpolitics No! Wait for a more factual explanation of what happened then report it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMars1978 @gervaise_al @JoeSmithTB Not saying the #Simmonds deal happens. The #Bolts have depth to stand pat. But… https://t.co/GE4UiRu434]]></document><document><![CDATA[@songberryfarm "experiences with microbes feeding crops"  Feeding in what way? They aren't talking about fixing N i… https://t.co/1zDuDAiReq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDougCollins It's sad how you have to go to such great lengths to defend Trump's "national emergency".]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @KaseyMillerxxx @tiffanyroussoxx @francescalexxx @xxxRiley @CassieBenderX @bethanyxxxbenz]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's too much pressure when your'e undefeated.   (credit @ioannaraptis) https://t.co/XkaTY0sMOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I used to jump off my couch with a bag over my head hoping I’d fly” @Alyssa_hall223]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey designers interested in playing w/ machine learning, here's @framer classic project for this model chaining dem… https://t.co/PdrZsNLig0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan You sound like an idiot. Maybe you should learn how to properly speak English before you try pushing a certa… https://t.co/8P4UH8dR5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pokerpami71 Thank you Pamela. That is a wise choice. Keep warm and have a beautiful day. ☕️😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[The aftermath of #chadwod brought to you by brickwallcrossfit and crossfitclayton and @511tactical. 60:39… https://t.co/zTdYQmLq64]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decent for a chain. - Drinking a Bass Pro Amber by Bass Pro Shop @ Uncle Buck's Fishbowl &amp; Grill  — https://t.co/tB7l6duq8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkyNews @sajidjavid Emotional Upheaval 101: There's a fine line between kindness and tolerance and a bridge from t… https://t.co/KUUAW6U3HZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WomenWhoInspire: “I’ll tell you what Freedom is to me: No fear.” - Nina Simone, singer, songwriter, pianist and ci… https://t.co/gJx82XMUjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOnlySweeney We are looking at doing the same thing.  Do the two dogs get along?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello folks and welcome to this new bi-weekly post on stuff I just hate. There is... #mirth #giggle #smirk… https://t.co/bRqu1918rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you notice, her words are a convoluted mess designed to sound intelligent when they are sctually contradictory,… https://t.co/wOHgaYmw35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lerg @usairforce Sure, lots of easter eggs for #avgeeks.  Not a single example on-screen of anyone portraying USAF… https://t.co/knKEPfkIlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump Since we’re into ratting on each other, I’d like a go at it? How many @GOP members condemned… https://t.co/pIqObf6MnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jj_mason Not many people remember when Jack Elam played Batman. https://t.co/S8sk65BP5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kerry Hezbollah drug run from Lawrence Massachusetts to Maine is today Cocaine heroin Major delay in madawaska and… https://t.co/YrdYHDaBDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samforus The RINO Republicans need to move their venue to the Democrap Party!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wizman_23 You in essence compared owning a gun to talking and tweeting which just because they are both on the con… https://t.co/QN6QGlEJHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fearless in faith.  Teamwork means active listening!  #listen #respect #ideas #brainstorm https://t.co/07F0ms0K7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[A week in Florida and then watching Captain Marvel Saturday night. Does life get better than this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@braden_sayers @FocusedOnNow @charliekirk11 @KellyannePolls @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker @ewarren @SenGillibrand… https://t.co/KDJgYLAo4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is a bad idea for the Free World to follow the Taliban's lead in misinforming or uninforming the rest of the wor… https://t.co/RNHcNnaJ9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inside of every woman is a #superhero and I was fortunate to see one in person @iampastore . #unkownsuperhero… https://t.co/lWMJ9C8XYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KYEducators Make sure you send someone to @MattBevin castle to read it to him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@czabe Here is one of Steven Wright’s best (and longest) jokes: https://t.co/hx72btuHz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GCTigerTracker as you sit soaking in the California rain just know there are two pathetic guys in much sadder shap… https://t.co/RnOCUxQFFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking hearing people talk about their bulllshit podcasts in “LBK” is a fucking joke! 🖕🏼go fuck your self! No one… https://t.co/7YTt5FyAc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[We win. Suck it Ole Piss. I’d be mad too if my mascot was a shark. Sharks are weak. Try a Bluetick Coonhound. That’s stout.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to win DP-12 Double Barrel Shotgun? I just entered to win and you can too. https://t.co/RX2KNv1tVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets Its hard to think of something major with the possible exception of the Interstate Highway system in… https://t.co/ykZcopHPB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice to see Harris playing well tonight. Showing off that speed, making some crisp passes, and of course knocking down some shots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s your daily reminder that @KeshaRose’s “Rainbow” was the best album of 2017. Thanks for listening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewartMcDonald Imagine Juncker was the PM of the UK.  Then you might have a point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CillizzaCNN Is that a poll of Democrats?  The polls told us Hillary was going to destroy Trump in 2016, but Hillar… https://t.co/kPrmIeoWvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StumpforTrump @richard_crouse 👍👍🇺🇸🇺🇸❤️❤️🙏🙏🤩🤩🍾🍾🎉🎉🎉🎈🎈🎈🎊🎊🎊🎶🎶🎵. 🚂🚃🚋🚃🚋🚃🚋🚋🚋🚋🚃🚃]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Qué los ha hecho estremecer hoy? Algunos huyen frente a los problemas, otros deciden quedarse. https://t.co/gmQsyRh8Rs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias a dios por los buenos y malos momentos, Por mi familia, Por mis amigos, Por ver mis errores y por todo lo q… https://t.co/iejVGZfwxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@femalestuds Ohhhhhhhhhhh Shiiiiiiiiiiiiiiit, those are big ass fucking titties!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[They had to make their own dog tags... and other cool things at the #WWI museum! https://t.co/19LBaajuhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billpeduto Problem is that once we law abiding citizens start giving up our rights, that's just the beginning.  Yo… https://t.co/tbrdjjhZnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnimalMemorial @gothamwhale @APCruises @WhaleGotham @RealSaltLife @nycfeelings @Sigma_Photo @OCEARCH @TMMC… https://t.co/eCJs53Yc4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the fuck is wrong with these ppl. MIND YOUR OWN FUCKING BUSINESS, &amp; LET others do SHIT THAT MAKE THEM HAPPY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyBrunoShow Said Adam to GOD? Bartleby  echoes that sentiment...so do I. Or at least I used to when I looked kin… https://t.co/0K98YW4vw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT. A. BURGER.   Or Pancakes.  Or Taquitos. Or Biscuits.  Or Patty Melts.  Or Chicken Strips.  Or Pies.  Or Shake… https://t.co/ylgkq6MFgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The people that's considering subscribing to Hulu in the future please don't do it. It's not even worth it, you goi… https://t.co/OjFPhKGZCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ImpeachTrumpAlready #RonBullStyle2013 #Bull2019 #TimeForTrueGrit #NoMoreWarGames #AintPreSchoolNEMore #Graduated… https://t.co/I22biIBhbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bm029444 @Trump_Regrets @realDonaldTrump Trollbot account.  Not that I've ever been a fan of The Orange One. But I… https://t.co/v56ZSV7JYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/z7mq9zsusC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @NRA @realDonaldTrump Most if not all crazy shooters are liberals who don’t legally own guns🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDice I guess the old fashioned ways of taking a knee just don’t cut it anymore. 😂 time to punch yourself in the face. 🤜]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep getting told Sasse sabotaged his own bill, but no one ever says what is so objectionable about the bill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who missed Boy’s Track signup meeting stop by Coach Hogya’s room (1056) during seminar for paperwork. #gopirates]]></document><document><![CDATA[The University of Michigan truly feels like home! June can’t come soon enough! Let’s make things happen. #GoBlue https://t.co/cRYmNSKdkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I rather not entertain that corny shit , I’m trying to live wit luxuries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeerJeet Clearly he is trying to say the complexity of US requires eminent domain to secure its borders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesCrowley20 @yugiohtas I think it will probably be AJ vs Kofi at Fastlane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[once that guy you thought was a cutie starts wearing tights under his gym shorts and hats to the gym it’s over leave him alone sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whats to review? Diverting money from the military is rxactly what Trumps Russian friends want. What the hell is wr… https://t.co/ijUsHgELel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpartyHawkCache @royalscharities @CYITML Gotcha I am following but was just RT the goodness my brother]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Demisfit2000 @TBoneWFNZ @macwfnz I was about 3% back in '98 LOL https://t.co/ucTHoetGL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FuctupMike @KatTheHammer1 Sorry about the snow, Mike. When it quits raining here, I am going to have to mow my lawn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[all fun and games till you’re in the wall against an alex morgan freekick and your baby gets nailed]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s cold, it’s rainy &amp; the allergies are in full effect. F-that! Get your ass out of bed &amp; run.… https://t.co/XFrQoybip8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rasbury22 Not sure. I would definitely be coming at them with different a perspective from 99.9% of all the other film critics, right? Ha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the first time in my life I want october to come back lets get  s p o o k y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j4r__ @Melz_1010 I used to always think Dios was straight and playing all of us.....and then i see things like thi… https://t.co/byx55t6XNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[In rural and urban areas of our nation it's hard - if not impossible - to find work in times of economic downturn.… https://t.co/hAuEoP27AG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike35033639 @davereaboi @DonaldJTrumpJr It's so funny that you don't understand any of the language you are using… https://t.co/Vpaz1rm7aK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent all damn night trying to get OoT rando co-op working with Vinny. Using the new randomizer website seems to be… https://t.co/hubsiSL9CQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manndmd But so does cerner…. ummmm we aren’t the juicy target on this op]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChetMason32 And that what’s it’s all about ! Good Job Coach . We see what your doing and we are proud of you putti… https://t.co/kZpB4jvFpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading To  SexyLand Wishing All My Friends Sweet Sexy Dreams Hugs And Special Kisses For All My Favorite Sweethear… https://t.co/ofNbrKUcgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickyCookMusic @rowdyraudy Are you and DLS going to be in NashVegas on 4/1/19 ???? I sure hope to see you fine you… https://t.co/n61ubAWBAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Civic Saturdays in Harris County, today happening at the new @BakerRipley East Aldine Campus with County Judge… https://t.co/7SdzlAit0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[If shit really gets real out here , a lot of you niggas will really struggle with picking sides . And that’s the sad part .]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing I love about the #XR industry is the diverse set of backgrounds.  No one I meet 'majored' in #AR or #VR.… https://t.co/Licw8fSHy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 14, 2018. #ashwednesday / #valentinesday , my wife Cherie @chereezyp and I started #planetfitness. She als… https://t.co/ys4DlJTyKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hckwilli @thehill This is a an argument I hear a lot from the right. You’re personal beliefs are yours and only yo… https://t.co/7vqRZuc2KK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Airbornex82nd @catherinekirby @POTUS What are we doing letting foreigners hold high office?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t remember the last time I worked on a Saturday and honestly this shit sucks lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my gosh please, friends, be kind and no #BachelorFinale spoilers! I’m on third shift tonight and can’t watch til I get home!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff @Google @facebook Thank you.  Nowadays we would wait in vain for @GOP "leaders" to do anything.  The… https://t.co/O9121RhMk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamTouchet Thanks for the tweet, my friend! Man, I really do miss Acadiana. #BOOMSAUCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADRheeSJSU @SJSU_EPICS @quakerengineer @roxsanarh One more https://t.co/D1qijVAKqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleFonzie920 @CarayJer @CNN Money buys the Propoganda machines (otherwise known as Bias Main Stream Media).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandallKraft @TjReasonz @Electrotek2 @McginnKeven @TonyMalone7 @WattzzD @Inge_Mausi @CraigChermside… https://t.co/PqdHgljCi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bionicanadian @VashtiQV @tinseymiller @Mhollstein @ClaudiaC @DianewasHR @echoicpoetry @juliet_cromwell… https://t.co/egFR6VdF4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CallofDuty I'm gonna need the season pass for the inconveniences of this whatever it is u fail to acknowledge nis… https://t.co/RPCNA0SIf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@01Starblazer Crowder was also a low key very nice move. We need Bell and Paradis (especially him)...]]></document><document><![CDATA[After singing on the #redsteps @ St. Paul's Episcopal Church - Mobile, Al https://t.co/WyT33ZwI1K]]></document></documents></author>