<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Man, I'm bored today. Bored to death. So bored I wish I had another job to go to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jewelsvalxxx love you so much and always will I will always be here for you you are so beautiful 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ssquishcatt have you played spiderman yet?  I love this game just beat it right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toniboyy @Philibertarian Reagan study found U.S. ed failure do to weakness in local control. Locally controlled ed… https://t.co/pNTONpdUZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[En 56 Días voy a andar a caballo en Mi Pueblo mágico bien pedo 😂 si ya saben como me pongo pa que me dejan ir]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys Basketball Marlboro over Chester 10-9 end of the 1st @HVSportsReport @GoMHSDukes @Marlboro_Mayhem @suptbrooks2015 @PJSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loathe Angeles 30x40 acrylic and spray paint  🎨 if interested in buying please do cause I need storage space… https://t.co/gJQvUs7cFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I finally lay down to sleep, listening to my boy @WAxelFoley on the @DVRPodcast recap his rewatch of… https://t.co/bc1NQxOhv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day of #amstud interviews. Great kids, going to have hard decisions next week. .🐲🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGingerMamba @clublanus Muerte, impuestos y el pepe sand clavando goles son reglas de la vida gambeta!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Murray robbing McDavid on that penalty shot might be my favorite thing about this hockey season unrelated to Tom Wi… https://t.co/uq3nD538ID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working hard is in these guys DNA. Give them them the workout and turn them loose.  Alternating Dumbbell Work:… https://t.co/gCHHyVBAHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[is this... karma??? @ToledoWalleye @FWKomets @CincyCyclones https://t.co/m1XmF0BA5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is a powerful motivation, so to is hate! Identify your enemy, Rocky had Apollo Creed.  #Identifyyourenemy]]></document><document><![CDATA[idgaf if your white, brown, Puerto Rican or hatian...  Let’s fucking get it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanna point out. The @Cubs have a better projected chance to win the World Series than the Brewers. Take that… https://t.co/J8CaV7t3B0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight in Nashville..  me: anyone guess where I’m from?  audience: Dublin? Brisbane? Sydney? Somewhere in Australi… https://t.co/wjma3LSTfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up early &amp; being still before the Lord is a beautiful thing !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast with this guy! @austinfunk94 @ Della Fattoria https://t.co/EUzgKgd30d]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ask and it will be given to you; seek and you will find; knock and the door will be open… https://t.co/8pGdPAEnxP https://t.co/YSds4Y2uc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradA53472906 @RacewayFreehold @nsurick22 I should’ve gone with my gut and keyed Surick and orange crush]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChagoSoto ALM, eso fue en la EFL Championship, que es la liga de ascenso a la Premier League y está penadísimo all… https://t.co/I7InSQ55Kk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellybr83939782 @RepMattGaetz @NRA At least one and several arrests that daddy made go away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennClarkRadio I think "Waiting" ages well. My sons and I still watch it and laugh our butts off at it. Watching… https://t.co/Is811JZ5lc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The future is now (1942 Arzens three-wheeled electric mini car). https://t.co/Fh6QccfWhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormOrnstein Can you imagine the Beschlosses and Brinkleys  of 2080 looking back at Trump's speeches and going: WTF?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChosenMert @LionelMedia Common Core counts all books read to include other required subjects that were previously not counted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched time go from 0159 to 0300. It’s an absolute crime and detrimental to health in regards to sleep loss. Hospi… https://t.co/gH0LPgmRS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reymysterio vs @BookerT5x  #FireProWrestlingWorld https://t.co/fWh3WfJDPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philippinesusa Please drop all charges against Maria Ressa and the online media outlet Rappler and end the harassment of journalists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayethatsnayy This is why you shouldn’t have kids until you’re married. Now he’s stuck with this girl forever. Sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clashcitybaz @eugenegu @realDonaldTrump All the others you mentioned were entrapped in process crimes. Until they… https://t.co/hYKCf34H2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancylee2016 @voxdotcom If this tall tale has the vaguest ring of credibility to you, we aren't reading the same s… https://t.co/DXIgnWgxwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Señor César Silva lo que pasa es que usted es un comunista y usted apoya a los asesinos como Raúl Castro el Cheguev… https://t.co/Vsaoo7NLIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1GunnaGunna album 🔥🔥🔥. #ATW   What u thinkin @J_Whitt3 @yaBoiJ92 @CoachPettyHSU @beautifal_  @iAmDrizzy__]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch @greta I would fund the expansion plans of the Alpha Omega Miracle Home in St Augustine Florida for young… https://t.co/nZooIiC14E]]></document><document><![CDATA[This might be the only real good takeaway. (If there’s such a thing) bc sports can shine a light on problems like t… https://t.co/6LZNv6snsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗣🎙 @lansingignite VP/GM @jeremysampson10 spoke to @YouthGuyCash about the upcoming season and more on @ytsspodcast… https://t.co/hlPPE4N008]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deepest thanks to @knightfdn and @SV_Creates for their support of @The_ExD #100BlockSJ as artists help beautify… https://t.co/OnDQZboQO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HELL4SL00TZ @HARPERMADI_ Can’t wait dude 💕 love and miss you &amp; @babysid69]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ya, GOOD LUCK with That BERNIE! But, They said you were to OLD the LAST Time you RAN? Did you Find… https://t.co/kEoi1iIa2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the way to location in Wolfeboro NH. #GreatFoodTruckRace Holiday Special.  @FoodNetwork @DiscoveryIncTV https://t.co/1iJJ3VUWkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Suburban_Dad @2Retort @jasoncfry They were all a part of the Jedi Order. Luke wasn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THE_mattjensen Can always count on Matthew to come through with a Farley reference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two new side projects in the works. It’s now official since they have a social presence 😂 https://t.co/QGCyFfzwAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my beautiful wife @ShellieRoss74 .  Your an amazing mother and we are thankful for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@actualitecd @LydieOmanga @fatshi13 Un produit @VitalKamerhe1 ... elle s'exprime bien en anglais .]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this talk about #LASnow and I’m just here in Ohio like .... meh https://t.co/rUTQFMTSBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mashable Knowing how public transit systems are perpetually short on operating capital I can just see these thing… https://t.co/2OlEEj8xkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching one of my favorites Brian Williams. It was hinted that Ivanka might be in some legal trouble. I’d love… https://t.co/MNmdYACUxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was ignoring someone who was trying to FaceTime me and I accidentally called back. He picked up... I hung up... n… https://t.co/pf1Uvz2lWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course they covered it, it’s a new story of interest. Just as they’re covering it now.  In both cases the media… https://t.co/E9icQrmDca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a great day for fights!!  The morning started with a bunch of great fighters you never heard of from… https://t.co/HuqOpteU5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/92qDM8wrwo So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew! One💚☯️☮️🤬! https://t.co/3ddeyj8GLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Are you suggesting that he should have randomly worn a wire to catch your daddy’s comments about wh… https://t.co/IQIApCsHJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChildersRadio Clearly they are delusional. I’ve had BBQ in NYC and it was average at best #LockhartsBBQ… https://t.co/fINgm2kIUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Happy Monday, have a great week, be awesome ❣ . . . #objects2desirestudio #awesome #happymonday… https://t.co/LPpb672sw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmartlive @ShawnFace Wow! Let me guess? Clay Gomer Pyle didn't think he was USC man?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kdotcom2 @forumbluegold I love Kuz but Ingram is a WAY better defender]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooh.Ineedtogetthatgoddamnsquirrel.thatsonofabitchchewedafatassholeinmymama'seve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's morally correct so your data facts are irrelevant to her Always Ocrazyo noCortex CASTING CALL CANDIDATE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TarekFatah @ezralevant She sounds like she is from the Philippines, honestly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy preparándome mentalmente para esos tequilasos y que me voy a meter el viernes 🤢🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meltedpotmama @ABCPolitics @GStephanopoulos so you support an investigation on Bill Clinton that resulted in nothi… https://t.co/WhjR4N4h1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@extrabaggs @GrantBrisbee @LOLKNBR Let me tell you something about that ball. I was shooting on the field down the… https://t.co/vMrRTbPmBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[New video is up, check it out.   F350 SEMA BUILD + KING RANCH F450. WE RAN INTO SALINAS PHOTOGRAPHY AT ES...… https://t.co/3SXhuKb7Qv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cam finally did the anti-move... you watching #Jibjab cc: @FiredogsHockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. Feeling a tad bit better today. Need to take it easy still…]]></document><document><![CDATA[None of these little worms better call out today I'm not doing any extra work on a Friday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch Manafort is struggling for his freedom over pretty much the same thing ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great win today as Maddy had a personal coming out party of her own !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Booz Allen Hamilton is hiring in Austin, TX! Read about our latest #BusinessMgmt job opening via the link in our bi… https://t.co/HQEvpWv97z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some guy caught his girl with another man at the gym and they out here fighting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keluarga mahasiswa perantau kayak kami sih hampir selalu dapat gratisan dikasih orang, terutama dari mahasiswa lain… https://t.co/oSTBg7Elzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joven relata cómo asesinaron a su bebé tras aborto fallido https://t.co/HDVqUGgR08 via @YouTube@taller2006]]></document><document><![CDATA[There ought to be a better way to search for all those exceptional tweetstorms out there when you need them]]></document><document><![CDATA[I engraved a plaque with a few plates for Oneida FD https://t.co/SwkWnOwMc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FXinsights +$539 TUESDAY TRADE #WednesdayWisdom #TradingViewTOOLKIT #tradingview #thinkorswim #tdameritrade #forex… https://t.co/4FrtuaXTYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill More than “totally insulting”. Racist. Congresswoman could not say that, I will. Disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Francision @THQNordic Yup. There was some uproar about it in the news circles and progressive circles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realized I wouldn’t even have been able to watch #TheWalkingDead last Sunday because of a power outage. Not like I was gonna watch it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hudsonwest  *Happy Tuesday* Hudson! #ActorBuddy 😎👍 https://t.co/aKZPBWv5kV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogueNotary I find that every outrage story has complications and mitigating factors that, if they don’t make the… https://t.co/REA4mYirmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yeah that ending song of #AttackOnTitan won best ending song at the anime awards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arturitob @JRHMonge @RicardoMonrealA @lovrega @Pemex Pero si, el tweet no me parece preciso. Saludos]]></document><document><![CDATA[that bottle of champagne is probably $400 and they just literally waste it like that - you KNOW they’re not buying… https://t.co/f5zNufoR9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPN_FDJ Mis 10 mejores de la historia:  1- Pele🏆 2- Maradona 3- Messi 4- Cruyff  5- Ronaldo Nazario ‘Fenómeno’ 6-… https://t.co/Pv9OqTCVeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbaOTpodcast @FTFonFS1 @getnickwright Making the right play resulted in championships for LBJ. I’m his losses with… https://t.co/oCFMwqptNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for @RobMSheehan to be the next Joker. Because he’d be a close second to Heath Ledger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of Game of Thrones is definitely the look all the loyal watchers give you when you tell them you don’t watch 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all drunk and partying on campus on this Thursday school night shame on y’all 😂😂 #nccu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricFidler Sounds like a good question for someone who has information at the department of for hire vehicles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephRickle @NateArnsby And then making it to conditioning at 6am the next morning when we barely got two hours of sleep 😅😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could get a bunch of people to start a video thread of them going “WOO” in order to celebrate @RicFlairNatrBoy ‘s birthday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDennisLynch @WhiteHouse @PressSec Maybe you should worry about your English before you start worrying about le… https://t.co/pxLmJj7pQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  Folks.. the wages for the cheerleaders is so Low.. that If robert Kraft had asked them nicely and paid them f… https://t.co/oAxHMSD78S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntonioParis You can’t drink all day if you don’t start in the morning. https://t.co/aFz8SQkWbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diamondblack37 @FallenSocietyGG @ElpyTFS @KalEl_TFS @TheFallingGames Lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[✔️CLASS REGISTRATION FORMS Students are reminded to turn in their registration forms for next year as soon as possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirtuallyYours6 @ActionCapNCrunc @baseballchickie Cairn Terrier is a non allergic dog. My buddy has one his wife also has allergies.]]></document></documents></author>