<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Ugh my fave recent Netflix series was Hill House, it was dark and written beautifully. I liked the new Sabrina seri… https://t.co/cr0T5wYjz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoyKeniaOs @maurg1 Que le pasa a este Señor de vdd insultar a mi bello puerto @MazatlanMex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Capedcr82210140 @RealJamesWoods Anyone supporting this crap that the libs are pushing is insane!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had so much fun at #kats30th last night! What a warm welcoming group of people to make me feel so accepted! 💜 @ S… https://t.co/IsXuRoNi1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legends. &amp; I got to be at the game which was special too 💙 #MFFL #DirkNowitzki]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: *keeps getting sick*  me: omg, body wtf, why won’t you heal yourself already???!  my body: perhaps a vegetable?… https://t.co/zpnWTrijtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mamie's fudge and Elizabeth's scones, now all we need is a nice cup of tea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@serenarenee_ can you text me back please it’s been 30 seconds since i sent the message]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciated the opportunity to represent the #XM Institute at #QualtricsX4 and share ideas to capitalize on the evo… https://t.co/k5c5IDEUoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[travis made chili last night and it was really good and all except that he forget to add the seasoning packet and i… https://t.co/Mke8d8QVDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardsJayS Felger is the biggest accuser of it and it’s hilarious. I’m kinda in that zone now where I’m constant… https://t.co/rqDYpEuo2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rahvil @MBoudet How dare you evoke mantzoukas, he would fucking hate Mike]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe .somewhere in the swirl of mud and rapids. I bawled for the remainder of the tour and left the site… https://t.co/ZGbsSvaXSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregR13 @DeathSquadAB15 @deandelray @ComedyStoreLJ so completely true. Brody started it all for me and brought so… https://t.co/qo7ONkqq2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnafranger @NASCAR @KyleBusch I feel the Denny win is fishy! Kyle comment got my attention he said he didn’t lik… https://t.co/Bg9igAW0gL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity She is an example of our failing education system in math, history, science, and, civics!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brigid_noreen @uan1105 Someone needs to watch the Gillette commercial!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the retweet, but I realize now I tagged the wrong Mark! Should be @MarkRPellegrino]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravesSupt I know!! ... Final score: 64-60. They played their HEARTS out! So proud to be a Brave today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My anxiety over tomorrow is thru the roof and if I don’t distract myself with other thoughts I will literally start… https://t.co/3rghfs0QlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Not deeply attractive. Not at all attractive. Physically revolting. Revolting to the core. Ugly soul… https://t.co/gYugvyNErF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does Nestor send his most difficultly named son to keep Telemachus company? Probably just to piss me off. #TheOdyssey #Peisisisistratos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes just hanging out in bed, at a hotel, watching movies is the best! https://t.co/V95krgh9a7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthemRespect This is the problem. A bunch of RINOSin office. A handful backing our President.  What happened to the backing your GOP S]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you read in 3 classrooms for #NVReadingWeek but didn’t take a photo, did it actually happen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d like to know when it became legal for a woman to tell her doctor to “ kill her live baby “? I can see an aborti… https://t.co/DUZNBQ8Jl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems that @SenateGOP and @HouseGOP neither honor nor respect the oath of office.  Why else would they shield th… https://t.co/5nq43s5ahk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s still #coatseason in L.A. #parisianchic  here’s to #selfiemirror #jennyandthecity to a new month new goals @ B… https://t.co/hhz29mtLob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor is so cute in my new premium @christiwchaos sports bra and leggings.🦇🖤🦇#Repost taylar.lee with make_repost ・… https://t.co/SiZFIcH6DE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why i agree to come in at 8am . I’m tired af 😩 13 hr shift today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CountyGibson Vectren has a complete monopoly in Evansville. It is awful. So expensive!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you guys jut appreciate how my girls and I all have a hair tie on our right wrist!! I mean most girls probably… https://t.co/4WwNNDwaXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also apologies for the onslaught of UNC tweets in 3-2-1... #LookAwayDukeFans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CelticTiger357 @misty4630 @Renevelation @Franklin_Graham “Without faith it is impossible to please God, because an… https://t.co/ApM4ENBUum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diego24fps @mina_bloom_ @BlockClubCHI May we quote you? Is Diego Lopez the correct spelling of your full name? Wha… https://t.co/ygcSELKTH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your professor asks how the semester is goin and then gets aggressively defensive when people voice their conc… https://t.co/HtTjBCZySm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManMadeMoon I'm thinking a snow globe.. and that this idea came from The World According to Garp.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffmanForNC @tenyearstoolate @senatemajldr @senatemajldr Mitch, you’ve been on this “The Democrats” rant for year… https://t.co/N3WwBhBlUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harvard University professor of constitutional law.  Separately, the focus of investigators on Trump family finance… https://t.co/AEHgE6vcSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorgeous FRYE boots. Sz 9, $80 @ Cherry Consignment West Seattle https://t.co/nkI81XqItr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnieMcCarren @Sd2Shah @ZoeTillman Watching the Republicans today, they don’t want to get to the bottom of anything. They ARE the bottom!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interpol @interpol at the Chigago Theatre @chicagotheatre was magical. They played most of Turn On The Bright Light… https://t.co/FHpXoAoJs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[At @LimmudNY today, join @romemu's Rabbi Mira Rivera, Tamara Fish, and myself, for a discussion “Reflections on the… https://t.co/qXYu71RMH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning’s #meditation  brought in the imagery of a #bear and reminded me of an old journal entry.  Great symbo… https://t.co/WVqfORxtBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_rantz @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Not a chance. Nice try, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker I was gonna say hose ‘em down, but he’s a grandpa now so just shut the cell door &amp; keep walking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmaogreen @TheAtlantic Are you withholding the full story https://t.co/8Gu8WVoP6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump how about the 5 Democrats that took a 3 day trip to South Africa and it cost the Am… https://t.co/RYjqa8NjEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am an only child. My late father was a 2 star General. TO THIS DAY I still have this stuck in my head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is definitely Dynesty, Emma @cassie_smith014 &amp;&amp; @JustineCarmen0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen It would be ironic if this was the 1st item to take Trump down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy St. Valentine’s Day!! I hope you fall in love with God’s greatest creation... YOU! Have a great day! I love y… https://t.co/BnSzNneMWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody fucks with me when I’m at my worst so I don’t want anybody talking to me when I get to my best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold your head high mr. President we are behind u! Build the war stop the crime! Democrats don’t care , they know i… https://t.co/TOAK5vWHcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The whisked whiners want their food apparently… &gt;^..^&lt; #woke (@ The Catz Den in Deerfield, NY)… https://t.co/Z8QgBeJDUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I died when she said “it taste just like a pineapple omg” like no shit 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueLivesNYC @JrzyJoePiscopo @bluelivesphoto @realDonaldTrump @NYPDONeill @TomiLahren @NYPDDCA @LisaTuozzolo… https://t.co/Ca0i1e7jia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brakes ✅ Coolant ✅ Tag lights ✅ I still need a new air filter but that can wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I’m being tested in almost every aspect of my life rn and I’m trying to keep it together 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stellucine @FrankFigliuzzi1 @MSNBC They tried to tell everyone but most ppl didn't listen, I did. I started listen… https://t.co/yrenUjLlo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!! It’s especially a problem with chronic conditions and multiple doctors. Join us! #hcldr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acabo de terminar  #TheUmbrellaAcademy y puedo decir, es la serie mas entretenida de Netflix desde el Season 1 de S… https://t.co/DvalOTSs35]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspiration for me. What is yours? #Fendi @ 800 N Michigan https://t.co/4a4s8qudu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yesnicksearcy @peterbakernyt Obama never called press enemy of the people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog @ParkeyJennifer I think Kushner and trump are  taking as much, if not more, than they're giving. Allowi… https://t.co/zh1CSL0Kdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradPaisley Both my babes!  Carter lives with congenital heart disease and was born with multiple heart defects an… https://t.co/RbPdvt71jU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy fuck! 317???  It’s February!!!  Get your shit together dumb asses! #uber has never been easier!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For many people, avoiding allergens and taking over-the-counter medications is enough to ease symptoms. If you have… https://t.co/bwSa99Px6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackiefairytale I lost 170 on my blog’s insta... I was like 750 away from 10k and now back to almost 1k away!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpacedOut_K @Wildfleur3 Lmaoooo sis finally caught up to us with the scissoring jokes 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stargaz98500427 @RealMAGASteve Exactly! It's rumored that she has ties to terrorist organizations. Frightening!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t surprise me that you won 😂😂 congrats !!! Years and years of hard work paid off 🎊🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miss_steele89 Really cute. Looks like y’all are ready for Mardi Gras 💜💚💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snifflesnack Glad you didnt use. Sobriety has lots of tough times. Music is wonderful for healing. Get yourself to… https://t.co/QTUNY4ay0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[made a lot of mistakes in my life, i wonder who i’d be if i never made them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBMAMMAN1 @osquare78 @NOIweala You all and being impressed by simplicity. Nigerians are so easily entertained 😩🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[“So is an egg considered meat if it came from a chicken?” -@warren_mullen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenJTrevor @piratefoxy @SallyAlbright Hey stupid educate yourself. The average job be paying $150,000 a year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcarlstromDR @MarkJWestpfahl Thanks guys! You both work just as hard as I do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandiSanders17 Certainly. This one is a female- her black "v" is much lighter in coulour compared to the males "v"… https://t.co/hB5e72lScD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WILLOWOOD2 @PrimeCreator2 @theColor13 @AboveTheBurgh @HeARTofGod99 @2newearth777 @davidsodell @tee10202… https://t.co/NhxQXxuoDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My adorable bf was just singing along to this after i put it on https://t.co/4IjoxA9CsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did a thing fam! #techsupport #roche @ Roche Diagnostics USA https://t.co/VDOSlOFQ6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone was excited!#burrito #bestmanever #bestburritos #yummy @ Andale Taqueria &amp; Mercado https://t.co/6lD5CF1Ewm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sideway Selfie 📸  . . . . . . . . #toronto #torontolife #torontogirl #toronto_insta #torontophoto #fluevog… https://t.co/uW94wXXt6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Margaret Sangerwould be happy especially if these babies were Black Babies. This Breaks my heart to think that the… https://t.co/LiOPUCDAEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAngryBlackWo @GMSarli @SecretarySonny @realDonaldTrump @POTUS https://t.co/0zsrbO01uE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rouquinne @PubTriviaFacts One of my students just wrote a technical definition paper on this, otherwise I’d have n… https://t.co/0vQad8NJZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the way my friends and I call each bitches but like in this powerful, endearing, loving way. These my bitches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tgabor0728 @2sick4u1 @DonaldJTrumpJr I'm not racist at all. Wasn't raised to be judgemental to anybody of  color o… https://t.co/f87w3MKbF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to formally apologize to all our neighbors for the excessive screaming from my me and my roommates abo… https://t.co/PnzCiTgPkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though I’ve lost 70 lbs, sometimes it is still difficult to see all the progress I’ve made in the mirror. You… https://t.co/Zd4D9Zz5de]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swipe left...  . . . . . #chinwaxing #brazilianwax #eyebrowsonfleek #chicagotattooartists #lipwaxing #burberry… https://t.co/98jy5CaKzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be morally courageous. Make revolution irresistible.  #Tinkerversary #SJW2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@citizenstewart If you’ve ever been a military family you’d know that the housing and education of our military fam… https://t.co/MyS0dcYUFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think spring! Can't you just hear its sweet song? #whitelineprints #teamNeary @KAVprincipal https://t.co/QYcievtuhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the worst headache all night. I look at my man and say “I’m sorry i dnt feel good on vday”  Him: “it’s on vday… https://t.co/R2ddC9XF5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when I start to read a bad and uninformed take on Solange: https://t.co/2o2xhkBEJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Holy Spirit will stir us up to serve, to give, and to pray. At FCC, we have a heart for the house! Tune in to t… https://t.co/sk1OVHaWGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcshaiman best of luck tonight.  Lacey's puppies are beautiful.  It was great watching them being born this morning]]></document></documents></author>