<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[LOCK HIM UP!!! YOU HAVE PROBABLE CAUSE ESTABLISH ALREADY, BY THE STATEMENTS OF THE TWO BROTHERS Robin Roberts says… https://t.co/4JWbxF0yIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I respect people that paved the way for me to speak my mind.  I think about this every single day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BasicallyIDoWrk @SimoneOlivia  Y'all see this?  😂🤣😂🤣 https://t.co/Tdxmi9B7cU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AyannaPressley @IlhanMN @robdelaney I worked in Somalia and have visited Dadaab "refugee camp" where 10,000's… https://t.co/HHWZsEl860]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @williamlegate Being rich also Shields you from the law it seems. I know if I would have done even one… https://t.co/h4davJQ00N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piedadcordoba Esperemos el decreto presidencial donde quede claro que los Uribistas o su inmaculada estirpe están… https://t.co/DjGcqlMB2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not much of a machine guy but, this is a CoryG daily challenge and we must embrace change and challenges so her… https://t.co/0SiMP8QkSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paul27560022 @JGalt_Dagny @JoesGuy @minniefirst @realDonaldTrump For Ana and any of the other Trump supporters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My current situation. Going to leave this right here. @ Delaware https://t.co/O2VL6HUyYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DraftTulsi @Hebahersi @RoKhanna @TuckerCarlson This is how they smear Tulsi, too. David Duke endorsement, "Assad t… https://t.co/jItjiFUHUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikkinacks @PowerFuck ROFL... I was taking a drink when I refreshed and saw this.  Almost spit my screwdriver all over my screen.  hahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING SHOCKING ARREST: New England Patriots owner Robert Kraft charged in Florida prostitution bust. https://t.co/eD3nQB3PJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshmccormack @BlakeGuidry_ Yup. And Blake now lives across the street.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am glad @JesseBrown called out Postmedia for promoting @SueAnnLevy School of political unthought and half-truths !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to this cutie. Thank you for making life full of adventure, fun, love, and laughter. Here’s t… https://t.co/lprj7TThAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Green New Deal Is Better Than Our Climate Nightmare https://t.co/akXWL4Tipp WELL WORTH READING! @ananavarro… https://t.co/YzLSSsUOYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KylePhillipsFUN @ccarrollbeard @StarMan_Studios I'll be in there with yall ready to learn and grow as an actor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh Oh! Latest Report From CWBChicago Indicates Nigerian MAGA-Bros Flipped On Jussie Smollett… https://t.co/8Yb94RSWQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias @LesterToledo por su extraordinaria disciplina y firmeza en cada frase que usa ! Estoy seguro que serás alg… https://t.co/fOQdt0Myaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you weren’t sure about my brand, see my bumper. https://t.co/MclVhXlFgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill ONE of the challenges is getting the everyday people including the press...to Appreciate the invention of… https://t.co/5mYoi8Rmmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertoRodNews Y el negro pendejo ese de donde cree que salieron los millones que le regaló Chávez ? Hey… https://t.co/A1rNVYdy9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ken and I found one of the three Banks arts that were in Park City. We thought that the second one was covered in s… https://t.co/jQG9H08gKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this photo for so many reasons. I really really like the way it was processed. It’s a great look.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VTVcanal8 @DrodriguezVen @NicolasMaduro @jorgerpsuv  @jguaido  "Bienaventurados los que tenéis hambre ahora, porqu… https://t.co/7xaC46OVaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahead of NICAR I cleaned up the command-line version of our FEC loader. Stream filings directly into newline-delimi… https://t.co/0n5BV0cZcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a bumper sticker yesterday with a javelina on it and it said “Javen’a good time” and I want it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nouveau:  .@JFLisee publiera un livre fin mars dans lequel il racontera ses 2 ans comme chef du PQ. Il mettra en lu… https://t.co/YZAfR7ZA5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirstTake It is still illegal in the eyes of the federal government. Until that changes, the rule has to be enforced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarrenShipley The truth is not what they are after. Hence the Tran bill. What it really does and what they want yo… https://t.co/Jy8HUTuDCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenBlumenthal I thought you liked secret dossiers.  Or was that Vietnam.  I can't remember which you liked more.… https://t.co/ribz52UIxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mysillyplanet @56blackcat @MaddieBarry8 Stay in your lane Jasper and mind your own business, jerk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anniii_L Doesn’t matter where he moves things, we all know a foof will end up in the middle of his room]]></document><document><![CDATA[We Be Trainin’! #rugbytour #vegasbaby #barrienorth #rockymountainhigh @ Westgate Hotel https://t.co/W764ZlWETX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GageTenebris @Mike_Grant603 @CHSommers @USATODAY Are you a comedy writer? You seem to have a knack for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rafaelsobis @TigresOficial Bien Sobis. Sabemos ke extrañas y Igual te extrañamos. Pronto se viene la Copa Libertad… https://t.co/7nZFjZ6An5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Graffiti will always have a pizza my heart ❤ Street art is my favourite source of inspiration and creativity. Stree… https://t.co/qgxRYTsuOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycfuture @NYATEP #AutomationNY. Visit https://t.co/ctLeFLfGpi to learn more about 50+ years of HSE prep, College… https://t.co/2DCK7RKynv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Can you add “Remove the Electoral College”? We need the popular vote to elect our Presidents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fk u @myspace give me my music back I put some hard work into that ish I just wanna jam out to my wasted Talent 😭😭😂… https://t.co/1nkGJXQ1Sq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JodieLirious @ChuckRossDC @DailyCaller @realDonaldTrump Better than Fake News CNN!!! https://t.co/iV1ewnOo45]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who just one flung up onto their 2nd floor balcony https://t.co/4Q3Uq0lFFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@State1Deep @8NewsNow I get what you are saying.  Trust me!  But again don’t fb and drive and cause a accident and… https://t.co/u5hdgzV9dq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TropicalJay97 Whats one real pressing matter that trump needs to address next?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC NOT practice what you preach? @benshapiro  Fox News: Ocasio-Cortez leaves parade in 17 mpg minivan — blocks fr… https://t.co/syMBVBMGdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pensjetsfan @DKPghSports But you player touched the puck therefore not offside and a good goal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to hanging out with the coolest of friends RYAN AND KELLY. Obviously for her birthday!!!! (@… https://t.co/lIrXMDx4x4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@classiclib3ral She's young. Let her alone.  Let her have fun in her young life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamccabe22 Haha, I love to chirp. No issues here. I've never argued for Simon over Blueger in a bottom six role, t… https://t.co/I0TRLlEmMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malaynarenee @NBCS49ers Actually ass hole I spent 8 and a half years in Army doing 3 tours over in Iraq and loosen… https://t.co/8ANOtfhkZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[2011 #chianticlassico continues to impress 👍 #granselezione #greveinchianti #primipiattimtl @TorracciaPresur… https://t.co/bWuaElmJPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avariciously greedy conservatives will violently strip everything above the firmament.]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's amusing. 10 Random Facts I Bet You Didn't Know About The Harry Potter Series #comedy #giggle #smirk… https://t.co/hbzuEBBXkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garypaljr Beyer Speed Figures are dynamic. Contrary to popular belief, they are not etched in stone. The figs are… https://t.co/yukKGPpjKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlatantMacaroon @MerlinPsychSage @jlegewie It notes that “[t]he disparities in police exposure do not necessarily… https://t.co/PlVMxZ7gYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisG1988 I ordered some @mike_Iaconelli mini flips and head bangers to try out this year! Got them in the mail Tuesday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex_wham @BernieSanders Btw.  Out of WHAT context? Tell me, ma'am.  I WHAT context would this statement be any le… https://t.co/pQNsZpfMYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[FB LIVE 12:30 pm EST - Against All Odds with Judy Hippensteel from Lancaster, PA !!! Don’t miss this amazing testim… https://t.co/hh5vDW8nvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasiaj777 That's the whole point .. it's an investigation. Why would they reveal everything before the finale?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @JarredRowe to post covers of 7 books that I love.  No explanations, no reviews. I'll challenge… https://t.co/HRLRO9N2zc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLParlays Stole a couple road games early like at Florida and played about par down the stretch .  Won tiebreaker with Auburn head to head]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanieInABotle7 @Acosta There are three doctors Includung the surgeon general are able to find this person DOESNT… https://t.co/Sxf9N4i4zY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorKimberley @MollyJongFast How long a shower does it have to be to get CPAC off you? Does that require turpent… https://t.co/bOXDa2DgA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollyejacobs Not that we’ve heard of yet Hollye, but this is far from over. Hoping for the best tonight. We’ll be… https://t.co/NTirYVLy9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of these two for giving amazing talks at #SBM2019 and being great representatives of @HPCSCUNY @CHESTNYC… https://t.co/jyywFZwKTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn’t get this groove out of my head! • • • Comment what you think, and let me know if you want stickings!  •… https://t.co/MA4mCOthe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMorgenroth Doodling helps me conceptualize concepts in my notes better than pretty much anything else. I doodle… https://t.co/0HvcSlhSPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[What should I do for my birthday!? It’s March 28th. &amp; yes, I’m an Aries! https://t.co/TYfjnOq2HH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RidgeOnSunday @SkyNewsPolitics Staying in is a demonstrably better deal. This man is another ignorant Tory.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People come and go oh well😆don’t need that negative shit in my life cause I’m living good🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CelineTerranova @scifilondon Speaking of flash fiction, did some few years ago for writing practice: someone posts… https://t.co/oYgYEPZTpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI, Friday Night Lights 2-22-19 Part Two @ErieBayHawks @ErieOtters @HurstMensHockey @HurstWHockey action… https://t.co/ecZW88OQRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last time I went to piano bar i left my truck at the Tap for 2 days. Do this. It’ll probably be fun. Or a shit show… https://t.co/0IdWuF5IYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the motion for judgement of acquittal that the Defense filed this morning. The judge denied it: https://t.co/iqmMMGtEkf @WPLGLocal10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClueHeywood She's also the supermarket checkout girl from Animal House]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Shipping and Receiving" at ResourceMFG, then look for people you might… https://t.co/LOdKG2x1em]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadLivengood @BRIANDDICKERSON “What are we going to do?”  “Fix the (damn) roads!”  “And who’s going to pay for it… https://t.co/dBTcKUrNhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of a Great night at Jakes- Melissa, Deb &amp; Kathleen @ Jake's Boathouse https://t.co/27Hl84cpZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was one of the first sports and baseball writers that I truly loved, respected and enjoyed reading. His baseball… https://t.co/gNqZTlEkat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tasty Tune of the Day ... With all the buzz for Greta Van Fleet, people still continue to pine for a Led Zep reunio… https://t.co/XYjcH9dV3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you see oppression of the poor, and violation of rights and justice in the realm, do not be astonished by the f… https://t.co/yJ3xbKglwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstroAmaro I have never written such a letter, but I’ve been on faculties that have received them (including yours… https://t.co/905iFE5CJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Wildflower Research Center #austinlife #traveltexas @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/FJX5eHEZrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@super7store I beg you to produce a #MacGyver figure and action Jeep please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshReed21 I mean he has 15 and 15 rebounds. One night after scoring 48 and 9 assists and 8 rebounds. I know he’s… https://t.co/fAb2QmVObE]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRX Plus Core class. #trxtraining #trxclass #trx #worldgym #flpt #abs #core💪 Who needs Orange Theory when u can hav… https://t.co/A3GVXsqEsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Plaza Casino - @plazalasvegas in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/yUmhYJBrNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James_Gross Wasn't clear if the uberx trips started and ended in the service area. I'd assume so but in that case,… https://t.co/MDlOmw91zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now that it is officially my birthday eve it hit me that I have no real plans for my birthday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity I love that fool she is the best thing that is ever happened to the Republican Party]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 48th Valentine’s Day together to my beautiful wife, Audrey. We both individually decided that there was no ca… https://t.co/Mamao6cNvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eliminate-Daylight Savings Time - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/B4jnFSCTNp via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @NBA all star game is worse than watching SanDiego Fleet of @TheAAF football!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ultimately it was decided that the state had no jurisdiction, since David's real mother had given consent, and prog… https://t.co/QesUknpAuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[CBS: What's going to be different about your campaign this time?  BERNIE SANDERS: "We're going to win." https://t.co/j8laXvTTtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Ella Dorado West Kill by West Kill Brewing @ Shindig — https://t.co/Uyd0RwaEcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drink a Aguila Tequila. I no longer use I recommend you try this Buttershots after you hit your tequila take abou… https://t.co/w8l6p3aQIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattyboygoblue I am 1000% stealing this adjective, Matt. Soupy. Love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always find team or program anthems entertaining... but a player/coach combo take it to another level!!   Those n… https://t.co/bfzNGdkG4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[These hookers be talking to me like I’m a custy.....babe I lived here before I’ll make you mess your bag up lmaoooo… https://t.co/HIOwbXlLvG]]></document></documents></author>