<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[pretty sad that offset can’t be proud and stunt with his girl without u crackheads having something negative to say… https://t.co/sGAqyIbkNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cherish the growth me and my girl friend have gone through separately and together. She’s the one, she always has… https://t.co/PvnJLCdR07]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoyed my job so much today that I worked nearly 12 hours and still have a HUGE smile on my face. #blessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best way for an indecisive person like me to choose a new phone is to go into the store 25 minutes before it closes. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We went for a walk and got some pictures. #OrangeLakeResort. @hiclubvacations @ Orange Lake Resort Orlando Poolside https://t.co/0tRy5ynS9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[No everyone must show ID!  Like finger print or retina scans!  Fake IDS  for illegal Aliens are given out like cand… https://t.co/ZkSaR7kpB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am very happy and lucky to have you, thank you for your love.💘💝❣️ en Palm Desert, California https://t.co/sgK8dO3O28]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: 7 just yelled, “mooooom is dinner almost ready?!”  Me, from my bed, no dinner started, “gettin there!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdawsey1 @EWErickson He’s moving the the campaign. This isn’t a huge deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Celebrity Tortoise Breakup That Rocked the World: @atlasobscura https://t.co/Upn81tYmKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to WIN a Taste of Paris with Your Own Box of Macarons and a Signed Copy of Paris Writers Circle #giveaway #win https://t.co/oliFI2iaHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once someone told me I looked like Lady Gaga and to this day it has been the best compliment I think that I will ev… https://t.co/sSNowGPMPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@f_obermaier @amazon @OpenTheGov Treason &amp;Tyranny with no transparency run our Government Courts  watch this… https://t.co/3MQP8cCWwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fml my head😭 yesterday was fun with my man so im good plus didnt drink much but i woke up every two hours concerned… https://t.co/K6jlYhHYtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump 🏌️‍♂️⛳️ Oh, great leader, protector of our borders: What shall we do about this national emergency… https://t.co/7vHeX3bpHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WhiteTrashNicole showed her trailer park colors by throwing a temper tantrum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5) I think they don’t always really support the idea of tech supporting learning. Sometimes it can feel like tech… https://t.co/gBZiTs9Vce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkedquilang chief of an all female surgery team @UCSF_EastBay !! #ILookLikeASurgeon #WomenSupportingWomen… https://t.co/KczqG0IrJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldBaronBradley thoughts? I can’t rewatch WH for the third time. Ooh, maybe I’ll go on a late night walk through t… https://t.co/02bERjBqIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally how inconsiderate. they should have picked the cows up w their hands. so lazy. and no funeral?? those cow… https://t.co/o1JB2lMFCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thank him in the hopes that will appease him as I speed away from him as fast as my wheelchair will take me. It's… https://t.co/HDQ99v9hp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#word #realfriends #cannabislatinanurseceo #cannabiscommunity #BUYMYBOOKABOUTOPIATESANDMEDICALCANNABIS #ebook… https://t.co/EhwEcE3BMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mary and Maddy just came to give me drunk and luv, I love them, when I say I legit don’t know what to do when I’m a… https://t.co/3Rqrq59ZgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessethechef 😂  How old are these people.  Act like they are single digits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Approximately 24 counts of felony against POTUS, I Say indict, it can't hurt !!!! Mitch,Lindsay      Graham.Russian… https://t.co/f5Y4Qq9PwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ Who gives a lovely damn? She should have dropped his lying azz in her THIRD TRIMESTER and why is this trending...🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see all y’all backing Cardi B. She’s a horrible person, do yourself a favor and drop her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are PUTIN's BITCH! We all know it. Putin's Puppet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are an utter embarrassment.  No class.  No intelligence.  Blatant personal agenda. 2020 cannot come soon enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what real food looks like! The taste is divine! Turmeric Sweet Potato Hash atop a green salad with plenty o… https://t.co/qUM8nSNISr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @TINAcious_D this guy glen should have answers for us .... @TheAcademy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debbie_regis @coachcarcich Thank you! Good luck to Justin and Sean! TOC bound🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg everyone let’s get him to his 1000 followers and someone win this coin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lux_beatrice I am actually Polish (my mom's side) but I don't speak or read any Polish 😢 I just felt very connecte… https://t.co/VwQFJbWd6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xfinity changed their automated system so that it wouldn’t let me talk to an agent about getting my ridiculously h… https://t.co/dnIISNxmn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[kids would fr play connect the dots on my arms and clown on me for my freckles i always wanted to get rid of them b… https://t.co/zikPYF3ZcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANYONE BESIDES ME THINK THAT KUSHNER LOOKS LIKE THE HARBINGER OF DEATH?  OR A MORTICIAN? JS! https://t.co/XgMrZ0SUK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mystikal_blue3 😂😂😂 He's a well known Gospel artist, writer &amp; producer. Has worked with a bunch of folks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlashbackFriday to when our dad won Best In Show at the 2018 Addy’s for creating 84 Lumber’s 2017 Super Bowl comme… https://t.co/iTQmLq8JKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smugrevolver Hey listen I want to say sorry I didn’t me to offend you in any way so please don’t be upset with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Done forget the fucking useless prayers to only make yourself feel better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KawaiiStephanie TinierMe was such good times! I'm so glad I was able to work with you a little!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready to experience the magic of Wildwood Grove? #Dollywood   https://t.co/iBhzYGJRFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who tf let my drunk ass climb in a bunk bed bc i just fell 5 feet off a ladder lmaoooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw this on the TL, I’m curious af! Lay it on me. https://t.co/HmapQ1nun6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stylezpromo @Harry_Styles #BestCoverSong #iHeartAwards #StillTheOne @Harry_Styles https://t.co/nKQNBdlcbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CREWcrew @SimondsDan The hypocrisy is strong with this man. https://t.co/VaMHRBJY4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muchas felicidades Diputado @jaimebuenoz ! Que vengan mas éxitos! #somosmaslosbuenos]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone has been trying to hack into my instagram for weeks and idk what to do anymore 😭 pls help @instagram]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badzoot7 @SueQuez @doritmi @BarbaraMcK42 @EmmaGPaley @boglethemind @Rosewind2007 @Zigmund_Fraud @Awithonelison… https://t.co/7zOzjzWOYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[i want to be cute and fit but absolutely hate working out. do u see the issue here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejordanariel Pulling an all-nighter tonight so I’ll come up with some content then lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty proud of this piece, I had started it a few years back and I finally felt confident enough to execute ex… https://t.co/upIJd4D8g1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when people put on there story “I’m gonna make a story who wants to be on it” and I get added anyways w/o saying anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[tell me why this girl been all over me all night but then her phone go off &amp; it says ‘baby’ 💀💀💀😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my brother and to watch him play the last 4 years. Gonna miss it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @Jordan2Gary to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations, no reviews – just th… https://t.co/G0Mfkfqf41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerry_bier @ProudResister I understand. I'm pro-scientific evidence and quantative analyses since adolescent. Taug… https://t.co/JINpmAqERi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of you, Sef! Can’t wait to see the noise y’all make in the tournament. @bball_forlife11 #SMACFamily… https://t.co/sUu2P1EQDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao! Hahha David just phishes me for crazy ass quotes lol 😂 I never fail to deliver!! Hahaha happy HUMP DAY!! @ Th… https://t.co/Wa0yDIvYGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[ur boyfriend ever pinch ur ass so hard it rips a hole in your leggings 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wenzforfreedom @TrevorGdchld @Serremmy @JSchwar68644942 @RN_JB7 @32Lar23 @jonz970 @Khalsaid @ctanner3 @frfldres12… https://t.co/Ttn5N4q8MF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vivi_lovesmusic I am so sorry.  Sending prayers and good wishes. 🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to high school in the same town as Olympic weight lifter Sarah Robles. Absolutely not gonna try her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OomphGroup Love the way you get right to the heart of it. Actually I've spoken to @MaximeBernier a number of times… https://t.co/ZxJ9WrTZHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕️☕️☕️ (@ Home Kitchen in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/S9lSrgGqbK https://t.co/PIXvKxop6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top IoT Trends to Rule in 2019 | IoT For All https://t.co/octMzftwgm via @iotforall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only is @OffsetYRN NEW ALBUM FIRE 🔥 but his album cover w his kids and him &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay let me get up and head back on campus. And then drive way back on LSU side lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomansDay is the perfect time to celebrate some of the remarkable women I know. Congratulations to… https://t.co/BQ8pDVsDfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing the community we live in, full of support. People are still good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chancetherapper can you please follow back?🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼 you guys look sooooooo beautiful together!!! Amazing!! Congratulations 🍾]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SheInspiresMe @ladygaga inspires me. She paved her way with  her unending talent. Also @Taylor Swift. The progress… https://t.co/dvfXZufoe7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald tem dois filhos brasileiros, paga impostos e entende mais do q acontece aqui q muitos mas pros bolsonar… https://t.co/EeAwnB4Rsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[So let me get this straight, 5 different girls warned Colton about Cassie, he still chooses her and is devastated w… https://t.co/LZTwjgMTsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really felt the slip off the couch &amp; the walk out cause I be helllla dramatic when I’m laughing 😂😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bag purgatory is the worst.  It’s been an hour and the lady at the bag desk said “ohhh it takes a longggg time.”  W… https://t.co/Zy72WkDgsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[31 days to opening day! Go Brewers! 👍🏻😁👏🏻🎉🙌🏻⚾️  "The game of life can be too short, so play with everything you've… https://t.co/6geJWSVre6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always great to have more @OneNoteEDU  #OneNoteAvengers @Flipgrid #flipgridfever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s So-Called "Emergency" Declaration Is Also Illegal !! https://t.co/9V39FDyfuK via @aclu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaBertrand Too little too late. Apology of the “I’m sorry I got caught” variety.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m way happier with this years winner of Celebrity Big Brother than last years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc if we got 1 inch or 10... I’m off from work with pay and that’s all I care about 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 Are we going by songs around birth year or teen years? I'm not sure whether to use this or Britney S… https://t.co/cVhZfTs59Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland So. Now we are headed to CONRAD MONTANA. I gotta see a man about a BIRTH CERTIFICATE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RecoveryCOA I just had an argument not quite 2 weeks ago with a rather young looking guy who claimed, “ It’s NOT a… https://t.co/jOydFZ4pWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those keeping track, @mrBobbyBones platform includes the following: - no construction in the day time - mandato… https://t.co/BmiUnpr9Kt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s way too early to be awake 😭#workingmom #workflow #WednesdayMotivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Concourse B - @atlanta_airport in Atlanta, GA https://t.co/qDC6pGHgAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimlockhartga @smolandsassy Now when you recommend books, please be sure to tell us if your heart is shredded. Som… https://t.co/5BLEmwb6iL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Jim Manderhine on MSNBC complimenting Pence,  telling us the good things he is doing in Venezuela and Aborti… https://t.co/puL7J6WtCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SpiritAirlines  you add insult to injury when the belt stops and it takes over half an hour to even address it. Gosh I hate this airline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bell_Support Good morning. Who do I contact if I need a new remote for my Fibe TV?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha I'm so corny I can't deal with myself 😂😂😂  Kai: I lost MVP by just a few votes  Me: not that it changes anyt… https://t.co/Iz3tP1oCch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArtbyAthena1 @AdventComics @zandook @LostLeanore @ODSTAc310 @Strafe_Rebel @L0B033 @ReganZupan @RicoReadsComics… https://t.co/aXwf60bKtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You were wonderful Mr President. Thank you for trying to make a deal with the Chairman. That’s mor… https://t.co/StYSmsTgeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always love hanging with you ❤️ @ Columbus, Ohio https://t.co/tvkAngviCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mine would be... thank you God, thanks mom, thank you to the @TheAcademy and @Twitter, I love you dad and Viva El P… https://t.co/9eENJCXDBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @swish41 so much! Please don’t ever retire! https://t.co/g6ydC5YgzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travitron1000 @RealSaavedra @Enrique_Acevedo Here is another "staged" report https://t.co/SEkvzNLgLy]]></document></documents></author>