<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This is what it takes for the important role of SAHM to get noticed, valued, and appreciated by culture. 👉👉👉 "While… https://t.co/JhqQaGWQf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Usually my neighbors incessant video gaming keeps me up at night but we’ve now moved on to them binging all of the… https://t.co/ebVrUB2RXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What is the purpose of life?”              “It’s to give!” 🤲🏽❤️🤲🏽💙🤲🏽💚🤲🏽🖤🤲🏽💛🤲🏽                          👇🏽 https://t.co/mQCmycyOEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo se que no hace falta, pero es que me gusta mucho como nos vemos y por eso lo hago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LachmanBenjamin @CoryBooker I am on the roads in MI everyday as an advocate for students w/disabilities. I have ne… https://t.co/I4JPjW5HJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonorsChoose Check out this awesome teacher’s project      https://t.co/j8Vgjtw9x8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier @fliflisky Trump is the only one getting anything done, while the left is using all their energy on… https://t.co/YXJ5NXRFJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry guys i got distracted so running late but my #DevilMayCry cout down to 5 will be starting shortly on https://t.co/mhuHrt4Dch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron_C5 @AstridStarxx @BenLewisAus @YorkshireSmash @Matthew669691 @CarsonGarrard_ @SamTanginoa @JillKassidyy… https://t.co/0EikBb4Sy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_wintergirl93 @Scully64 @AOC Amazing. We should order those for EVERYONE in the House of Representatives. Along with a pitchfork.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColbyDigsSoil Yes, precisely. Just me, my kids, and your free spirit students enjoying the sights. Peaceful. But h… https://t.co/f9envBZwmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I think I’m over it I actually realize how fucking not over it I am]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Expect to go to a new level of faith! (Rom. 1:17) @ifollowbfc  @bfcpastor #righteousexpectation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neal_katyal @nytimes A finale of no consequence other than more investigation would be a major fail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure I’m more excited for North Zulch prom w @kawrtt then I am for iola prom.🤩🤷🏻‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s interesting to see how states have so many measures but few measure post-secondary success. @NSHE @NevadaReady… https://t.co/99pXYv2aHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamcbest @realDonaldTrump Sir, You are distorting the truth, how have you drifted into this view?  Sad for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarbyXX @ShawnAbner @CODReTweeters @FlyRts @TwitchReTweets @FastestRts_ League play doesn’t get released until tomorrow morning for Xbox 🤔🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran into a lot Latina queens at this nightclub called Cielo... they kept telling me how pretty my kids are gonna be 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharon_schwan @rosemoczulski1 @CSonafelt @sannbs @72cricket @MrsSpuds @RidenerTina @BxglL @ACog1984 Aaargh, really… https://t.co/7mJwc5uqRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[we just had a fancy dinner and now were going to old town scottsdale 🥩🍾🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I'm google I declare war on this commie fuck. Manipulate search results, ban from services and hosting. Watch he… https://t.co/FeuRmjwd4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want classes to be cancelled tomorrow because every one gonna be laid up with their piece and ima be lonely… https://t.co/RRQTZzpJ8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never had a dog go missing before, this is the worst feeling in the world. Like mama are you ok? Why did you l… https://t.co/RIinbRJt5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[KEITHDWAYNE(@matheniakeith16) - Instagram photos and videos https://t.co/rFKJvVq8KO]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2 from MIT student: #ethics in every aspect@of@yhe curriculum, developing and ethics-centric mindset #macvicarday]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 years ago today I was at the Pens vs Flyers Stadium Series game in Pittsburgh..I would do anything to relive that day it was so amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an amazing time watching Shinedown, Asking Alexandria, and Paparoach at @93XRadio 's Brotherhood Beer anniversary show. ✊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repuvival Put some respect on Only You. Everyone forgets about that one]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you for supporting young hunger heros and for encouraging more kids to get involved!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Iccho Japanese Restaurant in Torrance, CA https://t.co/ii9OQdG19K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariyanatavakoli Lmao okay lil miss future WINGSTOP employee check urself b4 u rex urself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best speaker shirts ever!! Thanks @devnexus for the awesome baseball themed evening. ⚾️🤩 https://t.co/sHpFDwgKIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld Jussie should of announced he was going into a rehab immediately @mentalhealth , would have explained… https://t.co/EWiqKq3kSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @BlackWarriorRev for publishing this beautiful weird story!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the sun shall shine again!!!! Pretty beautiful both ways ;) @ Wear Valley, Tennessee https://t.co/OmX5DIZANL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pathetic..... lol 🤣 #pathetic @ Lincoln Park, New Jersey https://t.co/9FdgGvt2Ri]]></document><document><![CDATA[Semana de clásico regio es igual a semana de ponerme puras camisas de Tigres.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump Yes it was! My parents are from Puerto Rico and I was raised in Manhattan so he mos… https://t.co/8vHLgyCWx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4: We make time for one another. Most recently we took the Polar Plunge together!!! Laughing and living outside th… https://t.co/JJ5KbGLdUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at the questions in the ballots very well before you vote there are questions that you voted yes without knowi… https://t.co/QJAQXdD5HC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting to watch one of our 7th grade @HickoryHillsSPS students compete in gymnastics! Gus is amazingly talented!… https://t.co/gpRGxTwT3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingkingII How many times has Marcus put up less than 100 yards passing in a playoff game?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AC360 You tell them Phil Mud. Manafort needs to do his time where er he committed the crime]]></document><document><![CDATA[You all me!!!lol....#yummmmmmm #goodfood #goodcompany #gooddrinks #roosters @ Rooster's https://t.co/iCXUJmAWaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Skin #Rejuvenation #Treatment - Your Little Secret To Be Young Forever see more https://t.co/anLnh7srXx… https://t.co/r5O8JxUGor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a nap, but I can never fall asleep on time. I take me like 10 mins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GCHDutta @rpskataria @u_mirella @IamSunitha777 @nmehta4 @AnupmaMichael @fghdil @GsjpJyoti @greatairi… https://t.co/YGH0mgroFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#5 this is a time we went out for drinks in Fort Worth. We all had $0 by then https://t.co/cPPW6xN56D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lauren and Tyler I love your new show #WhiskeyCavalier 😁I miss you on #TheWalkingDead 🧟‍♂️🧟‍♀️@LaurenCohan @TylerJamesWill]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is searching for vaginal moisturizers on Etsy https://t.co/fgzbb0NO0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was really good. Tart cherry and dark fruit notes were excellent. @fridge_guys episode 10 - Drinking a Drumpf… https://t.co/uLHicuhrew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dhegertz1 @NateSilver538 They dont get an education  The top tier players are always practicing, getting training.… https://t.co/qCNuwH0Dcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fine line of showing enough interest and also not showing too much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These single digit mornings are a struggle....but it is a benchmark day at #OTFPortland today so bring it on! 💪… https://t.co/vrTOPnPLQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was born at the end of the Baby Boomer Years.. in my humble, voter opinion.. I do NOT want a President that is 5… https://t.co/LqK0dDrxom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chriskl70208387 @basedinfidel8 @fellspeaks @TH3R34LTRUTH @AlexWY18 @JayCory7 @SmackYeti @Americanthatguy @johnw299… https://t.co/yzaSWYUaYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake up in LA, and make plans in London and Paris for the weekend. It feels like a rap song but it’s my actual life. https://t.co/2elljejTA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we r filled up with HIS love we can truly love the unlovable. We can look at them the same way we look at ours… https://t.co/ds95AuznAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be performing and walking in the fashion show for those who may be interested. Hope to see ya there!… https://t.co/5pD0M14VH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patricia6227 @garway95 @kfisme @gneely17 @Gracieluf @Mooster22 @stripedbanana3 @trumpAngel45 @Priya4Trump… https://t.co/EolNAWMThp]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone saying “he made this a long time ago!” UM HE HE STILL KILLED HIS FRIENDS PERIOD LMAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SubKultureEnt I AM a Stay who DOES travel anywhere for Stray Kids. #STRAYKIDSinHOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at More Than A Teacher North Office in Austin, TX https://t.co/riqNbOiZPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My professor think I’m laughing at his lil jokes.  I’m really on twitter tho 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Omar must be removed from the House Foreign Affairs Committee for her blatant anti-Semitic comments wh… https://t.co/040yHU9t79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett you should be disgusted with yourself. Change the world?! Love?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@la_gata_negra17 @momness1 @cspanwj Now all of us know what ED means...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dossie1954 I assumed (never assume) that you're taller than my 4'11" self?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LACaldwellDC You stumbled a sec on 'if past...' and I expected you to say, 'What's past is prologue.']]></document><document><![CDATA[Since you trying to serve me all this attitude, you should've put all that in  that mood inside your spaghetti you made last night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markknoller @POTUS Because Kim is a pathological liar just like Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is a journey, not a stop we arrive at. Keep traveling. https://t.co/PA7FZD3nu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgustinOMG @Pajaropolitico @lopezobrador_ @GobiernoMX @ElFinanciero_Mx Aahh¡¡ y nunca me han encuestado... 🤔🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AprilDawnRaney @mandyeellis @kcarroll75 I love how as a school we have put some of her ideas into action. 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ivt_2020 @realDonaldTrump I feel so sorry for you. You're as idiotic as that piece of shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer We took care of our 18 month old great granddaughter for two and a half days. 💕🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been craving Everett &amp; jones for the longest but no one is ever down to go 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Azalias. So bright!  #fivepoints #spazhouse #bloggerstyle #riversideavondale #fivepoints #flowers #plants… https://t.co/cA9hoLbeIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMFanSupport is the mega ticket the only option for summer country concerts??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doodlemancy @SarahLerner So understand how you feel. Bet you’ve also gotten this one like I do, “How long will that last?” 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so stunned by the subtleties of what Cohen is saying about sex, or otherwise hush money, and the committee isn’t even biting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elusive hoodwinker sunfish washes ashore near Santa Barbara in first U.S. sighting - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/5gWKeUot6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Share your thoughts with Beto on the issues that are important to you: https://t.co/1eonOik3h9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanFred1903 @RedTRaccoon Puerto Rico doesn’t have oil reserves. It’s all about the Black gold that is steadily des… https://t.co/VgGppvLQc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alfonsocuaron Gracias por darnos tan bella obra de arte @ROMACuaron , esperamos volver a verlo en las redes social… https://t.co/fkV1jnAxsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should White Boys still be allowed to talk? Damn. Evil racist article published by the Dickinson college. The com… https://t.co/zhEA8K4qrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even follow baseball but man, I am sick of this Harper drama. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dropped Koda off at the groomers for the first time and I’m an emotional wreck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaSpillYT Weirdest video teaser I’ve ever seen. Not excited at all. No liquid lipstick is that magical, except… https://t.co/vG8tifwwZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sign says it all. 😉  #margaritas #happyhour #visitsd https://t.co/4jDENVqCzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D76developer Now, all of a sudden, Jason dies, and then comes back, and things are fine W/Jason and Sam with Sam b… https://t.co/NzoJ5t9oUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[But according to Maduro... this is just a show!!! People are dying, people are hungry, the people of Venezuela are… https://t.co/VvMOYOOAxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paranormom @chipcoffey Negative people are jealous and insecure of other people's accomplishments. That's why they… https://t.co/KVsYA1be8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am David Whitlow Jr., a junior an English and Secondary Education Major from the HISTORIC city of Montgomery, AL.… https://t.co/prfb8z15GW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know if I should be proud or ashamed that I still know every word and every dance to EVERY. SINGLE. High School Musical song (all 3)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R_A_Banks WELCOME TO TWITTER, my amazing, brilliant law student best pal!! ✨ I ADORE YOU! https://t.co/AuukDH5Vo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corbynbesson Can u ask the other guys there favorite color please and thank you 😀❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliseMenaker @IowaWBB @IowaOnBTN love the emotion...@IowaWBB ...champions!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's no snow yet and now they've changed our forecast from a foot to possibly 1-3 inches! I'm telling you, we sh… https://t.co/OadHHW3q9a]]></document></documents></author>