<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's to my beautiful wifey Jenn Jenn love you @ Long Beach, California https://t.co/LazLyCOgIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My main man Scrape a/k/a @ivanneville some #prince #littleredcorvette at the #loverocksnyc #afterparty #lifeisgood… https://t.co/KMwLeEUjYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m curious how the #Amazon healthcare initiative is handling diabetes management.  If anyone has some insight, it would be appreciated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perez_chrisss Lmao na gotta listen to this nigguh Russ tho it’s just straight facts .....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solo deseo que la igualdad de derechos, respeto y oportunidades, sea un logro algún día para tod@s... #8M #DíaDeLaMujer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveFarleyAZ It's not just #rape, abuse and McCarthism - all that's an excuse to take advantage of private famili… https://t.co/wemUkt9IB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachSamz @FootballScoop Great and it is time for retirement of others NFL pre game shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay so turns out BOTH my brothers got androids and they BOTH flex about them at random times]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sól loves to slide. #happychildhappylife #tirehimout @ Sprouts Growing Bodies &amp; Minds https://t.co/F03BvjlljR]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Listing! $649,000 #intracoastal #waterview #luxuryrealestate #realtor #realtorlife #southflorida #floidarealtor… https://t.co/8XfbGM9lcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Heat, #Magic, #Hornets, and #Pistons all won tonight. So Heat remain in 8th 1 up on Magic and Hornets. Nets in… https://t.co/3o31moybSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamBaldwin Trans women just have extra large clitoruses  without the fun stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally did it I got my Facebook account deleted. It took an act of God. I hate that site I don't see a use for i… https://t.co/jYF0fn610N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Port City was in da building at the Plies “drip for sale” Party #allstarweekend2019 @ Buffalo Wild Wings https://t.co/gBoIFxsIMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Uber driver just out on “Hit Em Up Style” by Blu Cantrell - 6 Stars! 🌟 🌟 🌟 🌟 🌟 🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald .@ABC @CBSNews @NBCNews @NewsHour @CNN @time @nytimes @newsweek @usatoday @washingtonpost… https://t.co/UOLccnmrIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROHLL5 @clovis1931 @Carolyn83694751 @yourn0tentitled @currie14_kelly @LisaSmith4680 @ReneeCarrollAZ… https://t.co/El98bm4EhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all see how his people made sure he remained untouched from the police?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[!!Oh,si me dieras bendición,y ensancharas mi territorio,y si tu mano estuviera conmigo,y me libraras de mal,para que no me dañe!1Cr4:10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra     This capricious foghorn is running for the presidency of the United States of America???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would ask you how life’s been but it’s clear it’s went to shit like you 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_HyPerion94 Don’t worry I had the same thought too, texted a friend to see what he thought and he responded wi… https://t.co/qunUNMLEN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apoyando y excelente demostración en circuito de adiestramiento en Club Hipico Monterrey https://t.co/3KP7a0OILO]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you want something different in life you have to stop accepting what your used to]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will likely not make much sense to most.  Here is what today’s leg day looked like. I’ve been recovering from… https://t.co/6mQ23z3bQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SInow @Rosenberg_Mike “Pigs get fat ....hogs get slaughtered” ....are you serious? How much is enough..batted .279 LTA....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshietheGod @blk2us Also, many African tribes recognized a third gender]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjohnson175 You would think that Raider fans would like him because he called out his coach and players , I don’t… https://t.co/iqLCEuQ2nj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep them immobile during Christmas break. | 38 Awesome Christmas Card Ideas You Should Steal #humor #laugh #smile… https://t.co/fwiB1Yn2HP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ItsMondayBaby!!!! Attack the day, attack your week. Let's get it. God bless #lscsports #lewissalgadoconsultants… https://t.co/uUmbS0yR5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[When frustration hits a all time high. #guncontrol #senflowers #thankyou @ Peachtree City, Georgia https://t.co/KJPfTVoPTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grabando lo nuevo de alianzaefectiva @RoyGTV1 frankguzmanjr 🔥💯😃🙌 @ Producciones JJN https://t.co/FScYWOT9Jl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @pkmartiniv and members of the senate education committee for supporting the work of @CS4GA !! @MAC_Policy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bien por @AlvaroMorata ... lo merecía mucho. Que sea el primero de muchos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Figured I would try to look more presentable 😁😁 #freshcut#kuttinzone#somethingnew @ Kuttin Zone Unisex Salon https://t.co/YuBaigPrXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcysutton Thanks for filing Spectacle issues as you find them! We have active maintainers, just a lot on our col… https://t.co/AejsA29FwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@INDCarSerious @thistallawkgirl You failed Libonics 101?  That's an accomplishment to fail something that does not… https://t.co/WVXmPmWqUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshlynnWarford I AM DYING THANK YOU FOR THIS. Like this is me. Even looks like the same place 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbcideas @DavidTreuer @tehaiaiake @torontolibrary What a perfect under-the-covers #sickday episode of Ideas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello tio gio I was trying to tag you but anyway good morning.. @ Tolleson, Arizona https://t.co/pMEcYGN0tK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump This comment is what you like to say Fake News]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kanye looks like the weather report from Miami with showers starting at 1pm all throughout the day with an overcast… https://t.co/069svF3PPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Financial literacy is such an important topic, #MeetThePeetes! 👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽 @hallmarkchannel]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had my first “I’m not ready to leave my college friends yet” moment today. First of many I assume? 😬😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom is learning English through an app on my sis iPad and it’s adorable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeRoy47186034 @tribelaw You mean like this genius? Or is it ok when republicans do it? https://t.co/NiIMlMB9lU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A church with a clear purpose, will have a far greater impacted in its city.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nanmckay Looking forward to my two sessions: one with @DnorthernSr on entrepreneurial housing authorities and the… https://t.co/C4M0AOSxFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@david_hanselman @AtomsksSanakan @MatthewHavicon @SteveSGoddard @InTimeLiving @MLBinWA @realPitBullDog @RoyPentland… https://t.co/ANvnAZy2HM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Corey_Feldman sometimes it’s best left in the past why can’t they just let it be?.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a reminder @IlhanMN supports BDSmovement a virulent Anti-Israel group whose leadership calls for the destruction… https://t.co/9D2OLPZbx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[By doing so I jump way ahead of other people because I was now considered professional actor and member of SAG .… https://t.co/UfHEh3DGRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 @DevinNunes  Stop tossing your paraphernalia after you snort cocaine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll always give Iron Maiden, the true brotherhood card, just because they went against the grain, when came down t… https://t.co/QqO6m7IcUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jamieson with a pickle back... @ Lockhart Smokehouse https://t.co/7XDv2jiA6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@supremepatty Lmfaoo this is stupid if you actually have a decent job that pays 2000 or more a month. But Dunkin’ w… https://t.co/QlPBOSMcFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Am I the only one who thinks Adam Lambert actually *singing* Queen 2ish hours before Rami wins the Oscar for lip-s… https://t.co/sGSc5EI5EI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in North Attleborough, MA? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/m7AWpKuoiL #Simon #Sales]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Robocall Nightmare May Be Coming to an End by @LanceUlanoff https://t.co/O2WDC0C3Dj]]></document><document><![CDATA[when I be loaded and bored asf I just be on the same 3 apps back to back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Played a team-high 48 minutes and was the Nets’ second-leading scorer tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone is happy to be home. Love that smile.  😁 https://t.co/lngSMyhwbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s just chalk up March 5, 2019 as the day that picture of the cat with the dirt circle first appeared and everyo… https://t.co/S5EBCtTMyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want a 4.0 this semester? Looking for a place to study? Join us tonight in Campbell South at 6pm as we prepare for… https://t.co/XvLfE9Gj7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Ivanka Trump create ‘millions’ of jobs?: President Trump bragged that his daughter has created millions of jobs… https://t.co/ydVmB40bO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broken sprinkler pipe repair, American Property Maintenance free estimates all work warrantied. #fl… https://t.co/5xLPbbktQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chafuen No, I'm looking for data. It's interesting because so many believe something (tattoos are attractive or in… https://t.co/Z9gmibm03B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are dashcams becoming the norm or are companies just running successful brand awareness campaigns? Does me question… https://t.co/buG5F6Z1N0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well goodnight....yoga and gym.tommowe Xoxo kunismilaonline @ Bedford, Massachusetts https://t.co/gdlEwtOL4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voters can now cast ballots anywhere in Harris County https://t.co/Lp3RsDpmhp via @ABC13Houston VOTER KNOWLEDGE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así o más divertidos al final de @noticias62tv #11pm junto a @TrejoPris y @alexs265 desde #losangeles #california… https://t.co/A2ciq5B0Vc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally getting my burgundy suit tailored. Awwww yeah! 🔥🔥🔥 . . . . #imronburgundy #gramoftheday #suitup… https://t.co/isPC8Eaiwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bdsfail #toofunny #israeltech #oops @RashidaTlaib it really is hard to avoid Israel and their tech https://t.co/VIPMYwOXSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickShielsPGA 3 hybrid TaylorMade M2, 4 hybrid Titleist 915F, 5 hybrid TaylorMade RBZ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a man cave isn’t fun when you aren’t married. Any room I walk into in my house is mf man cave]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw #HappyPresidentsDayObama trending and thought we had another Jussie Smollett prank. Close though.  How you do… https://t.co/vsmeCHXV4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow every day next week from Sunday on. Lovely 😳😩⛄️❄️⛄️🦘 @ Billings, Montana https://t.co/SVX2pGS1ZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Diego looks BEAUTIFUL at night! 😍😍 - - - #sandiego #freaks #freakscomeoutatnite #night #photography… https://t.co/H7T45xwpzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter @nbagleague I think my high school gym was bigger and had a larger capacity than this...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never wanted to watch American Idol until that Don’t Stop Me Now commercial]]></document><document><![CDATA[TARIFS ÉLECTRICITÉ. C'est vrai que les tarifs d'électricité sont ici les plus bas en Amérique du nord. Mais pour ch… https://t.co/0dtJsuXYfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[“So don’t discount the misfits on your team. Find out why they’re frustrated and invite them to solve the problems… https://t.co/QyAEGywrca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sylviaduckworth @Rob_Dimeo @AlishaZ143 @Cbustamante2222 @lgonzalezteach @mcoutts81 @alexstubenbort @AndyLeiser… https://t.co/2bWRk1j27P]]></document><document><![CDATA[jaclkoff`s lets go to war with iran  - god any moron who supports trump and these assholes deserves to eat dirt  oh… https://t.co/oWIlRe55rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[But really though Pocos pero locos and Midnight Magic used to go hard af]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulbrindis Raúl en Atolinga Zac un tío se dormía en el@jardin en una banca diario se tomaba una siesta y hasta la… https://t.co/4sen2HindO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshallCohen The UN Charter reads in article 2(4):"All members shall refrain in their international relations fro… https://t.co/fxdNutRGj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to listen to this! Steph is hilarious and in no way am I saying this out of fear!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[$800 for two Chinese visas... and we’re only there for one day! https://t.co/283e4QfsO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to get back to my first home, stay tuned.... #TheStage   📸: @zakkiblakk @ Long Branch, New Jersey https://t.co/aoGQENNa7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bigearl &amp; I have been huge Six Million Dollar Man fans since childhood. Check out his smdm tribute @TOYLANTA… https://t.co/DAhaXdoWc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalmartInc Last night at the store in Ooltewah, TN I experienced the WORST customer service I have ever seen. I ha… https://t.co/WVZwwROHkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody reads my Twitter anyway, so, you ever feel like killing yourself because you know you'll never be with the o… https://t.co/DV1XSahKRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottDochterman So referring to someone as King Kong is now racist?  Welcome to the world of being offended by eve… https://t.co/eETUFV8Lcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anonycraig @maladamus @siano2020 Honestly, even if DOJ indicted and convicted him, he’d still be president. The on… https://t.co/LzpZc37MZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day back after two weeks rest (@ New York Sports Clubs - @nysc in New York, NY w/ @miss_chachi1) https://t.co/YKj4IJCGJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PablogtzT47 @NYEmmyAwards @Telemundo47 Simplemente eres un ejemplo en tu profesión y te dedicas con humanidad y ti… https://t.co/i0D9wELUzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[OFF THE HOOK 🤣 martysmountaincycle rynopower_canada blackspire_components #goprohero7black #pov #bikebuddies… https://t.co/siKAcrHqId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorrie_e @JLo @joechapel3 @TatianaLuter @RachelAMullins @OlgaG921 @beachbabyyy13 @Alicia_Tarry @KarlLagerfeld… https://t.co/nnaudPtIqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squireloaf @Ch00ch Hahahaha!!!! Spoken like a true Cheatriot supporter]]></document></documents></author>