<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It was a pleasure learning at the National School Leadership Conference! TY @hatchingresults @TrishHatch for puttin… https://t.co/KsaMeiFQRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tina Turner - Come Together (1970) STUDIO VERSION https://t.co/3zlk3F9IjO via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[This poor, sweet girl...I just can’t. 😂😂 @ Disney's Magic Kingdom https://t.co/0Yq2R7RgLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lake Wally What? in Paupack, PA w/ @emilyaskedwhy https://t.co/AzgEor78st]]></document><document><![CDATA[Art Ties Us Together! Big Art Day 2019!! #SISDPVA https://t.co/x5LoVsLzmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Front end developer" at Robert Half Technology, then look for people y… https://t.co/FT0S862JUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[How’s my professor going to schedule an exam at 8pm on valentines day?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samquinones7 the antidote to heroin isn’t naloxone it’s community People not drugs need to solve #opioid crisis We… https://t.co/Icz7h6Zy59]]></document><document><![CDATA[So super sad. Like AF. ❤ @bmthofficial @olobersyko  #bringmethehorizon #untilYouComeBack #vegas #firstLove https://t.co/fzjJy8UlCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[China targeting US kindergartners in $158M pro-Communist propaganda campaign: https://t.co/c89ZqZiff6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told Zack we could start thinking about getting a dog. Came home from work to find him making a dog collar out of leather  🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's like the crazy old uncle who always shows up to Sunday dinner uninvited.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please me music video just made the song 10x better. I know offset triggered 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @FoxNews Every time she opens her mouth her brains fall out]]></document><document><![CDATA[i get paid tomorrow and i have to pay rent but ill still be going to the galleria bc im bilingual. i speak broke n boujie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sasha_Devaroe @halsey Yes hunty I will fly to wherever ur at just to watch u perform cuz I luv you two to pieces lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[So honoured to be part of #Brampton ‘s #IWD celebrations w my colleague and friend @citytammie . Thanks for having… https://t.co/tSJpoYlQNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markshampton Holding out for sweet sweet dance moves. 😁 Happy Birthday!! https://t.co/NYaIoi3VX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerizzza Ang hirap! Naka 3 weeks lang ako no rice. Ngayon once a week rice. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MerrillHoops off to a HUGE start in the sectional round of the playoffs! Blue jays up 11-1 on New London with 14 l… https://t.co/8jV8nHmH7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashaEats @RoarLoudTravel @Sostraveluk @GailBenzler @TouringTastebud @MattsRoadTrip @always5star @MyVirtualVaca… https://t.co/aGtO4SgRO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time Breyden got the cops called on us because he wanted to chase a opossum in the neighborhoods yard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jed got to feel Remi’s tiny little kick for the first time last night &amp; his face was the cutest thing ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoeEternal Yea! Wait until @bushofficial comes to @FMKirbyCenter hopefully this year...Sir @GavinRossdale gets… https://t.co/schQacucZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[We KNOW "PLANNED PARENTHOOD" SURE APPRECIATED THEIR CUT ! .....https://t.co/ThQ51eZXgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaceyRodas @heritagetoronto @cdnwomenfdn @PauletteSenior1 @seam_technic 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students need to experience positive relationships with the adults in their school. Healthy and caring relationship… https://t.co/Qe7KOzkmUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practicing double digit addition with a scavenger hunt! #teamgreen18 @MasonelemGP https://t.co/HcteRFUXyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rmilesvox I couldn't agree more. I loved @nkjemisin's trilogy and your narration made it even better. It transported me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @LPN510 just tagged me in this and said its so me 😭😭😭 https://t.co/PtdF2CcGgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello!No limitations with fluid art.Abstract Expressiont artist...on fire.16"×20" fluid acrylics on canvas by Prisc… https://t.co/HuVtlz2BcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a tragedy 😞Our prayers and condolences go to the families of the victims during this difficult time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Topic of Ann: This country has 2 strains... Putin and Netenyahu...@realDonaldTrump is with Putin...@AnnCoulter is n… https://t.co/UycsySmfVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to be in Mexico with @LA_lexiadams and having the time of our lives!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That time of the year again! #renfest2019 @ Quiet Waters Park https://t.co/tjWTZmbHX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never seen a more intense episode of the bachelor in my life. I think I was just as anxious as Colton was]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need to be riding around listening to music but instead i’m laying here bored]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a big fan of #socialist programs: #postal service, #education, #transportation, #healthcare, literally everythi… https://t.co/z5jw34PzcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allyracing @JimmieJohnson Jimmie has been my only driver since I started watching. He is a fair driver to other dr… https://t.co/LZ1reUDzsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He sent me a bitmoji that said will you be my valentine, so I sent him one back that said happy v-day with me sitt… https://t.co/5b9AMUtm5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badger_runner @UW_CreditUnion Aww yes! Thank you so much Jon :) @amfam and @culvers are huge parts of me! 💙❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Until #DaylightSavings is STOPPED the Monday after should be a holiday. Just for sleeping. Just Saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr_palazzolo @RepAOC Let us pray and agree that Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez be found by God Almighty and that her hea… https://t.co/HkwaGa1LEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I just watched @chrissyteigen Instagram story I think I had my first food orgasim ! #betterthansex the queen @chrissyteigen !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Takin' My Time by Little Feat on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/odWKYOaKsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nysteveo2AOLcom I drive around with not one, but two Hillary stickers, one ClintonKaine.  Yes, I will not remove t… https://t.co/K5YV0zGWda]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm feel so much better if knew these job training programs were for true, Actual American citizens. NOT also… https://t.co/TUliBqHLnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I said... @realjoeyfatone uh huh. Yep. Knew that voice. I even bowled in his lane at #CFTC in Chicago! @NSYNC 4eva #TheMaskedSinger]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my boss that I couldn’t work today, and he told me that he hopes the boogeyman gets me while I’m sleeping... oh ok 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is worrisome. But, I’m surprised there are phone calls... what are the odds that they’re robocalls and not hum… https://t.co/MYSaZ0u79a]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I put my trust in you &amp; you let me down??  You ain’t shit to me no more]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone is ready for area playoffs #rp4l @ Mount St. Mary High School https://t.co/IJ8YdlixJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope you too are having a Sunday Funday! #DelawareBlogger #ABlakeEnterprises #socialmediamarketing #branding… https://t.co/SjZ8NuI04A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LCNM99 @realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger I love it. You never sleep. That's commitment to the resistance. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awards from our afternoon meeting! #thankyouteam #goodtogreat #lowes #hicksville #ohana #allstoremeeting2019… https://t.co/vds52OP268]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday morning writing!  Our favorite ‘thing to do’  #dreambigger #livetgelifeyourdreamingof @Livingsonship… https://t.co/TOlRDl0Y0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😁😀😸"Compromising Photo of Ocasio-Cortez is Going Viral, and She Wants It Removed Immediately https://t.co/RikOWWN9Qc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PardesSeleh @AOC @JackPosobiec @OANN Taking one look at his tweets, both before and after he tweeted, tells you ev… https://t.co/Xpb9uhA7Rr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom The only time it's appropriate to sign a bible is if it's a gift and you write a note on the inside o… https://t.co/0InaHSsM4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh myyyyy - Drinking a Baba Yaga by @etherealbrewing at @barrelhousetap  — https://t.co/f2E2tfUOZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why we gotta fix him...shit we need fixing too! But yes I’ll have your back and help you if i know you’re sharing t… https://t.co/o6uvnOGR4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[outta all these niggas in the world, she choose tristan, khloes bd, her bffs in-law, im just 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook reminded me this was one year ago today - when @Oprah blessed my whole soul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hijadetumadrela Shop at Hija de tu Madre! ❤️ My fave Latina brand  https://t.co/hm9gapkfNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warriors hey Warriors great game tonight! I am a huge fan of yours! I was wondering if I could please get an autog… https://t.co/jUla83JB0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I went harder Pushed it  Broke that fkn meter  You got some follows.. cool You ain’t no fkn leader” 🔥🔥🔥… https://t.co/uznhICiUCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnfromnyc @fawfulfan @shellymaxwell @JohnCornyn @TarrantDems @SharonHirsch1 Or @Sharon4TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[taking up arms. In addition, many European Muslims are alienated from their governments and societies, believing th… https://t.co/C4qi8mx33r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDoctors @GoodDoctorABC @IamNickGonzalez Hi Dada awww too cute !! Beautiful family !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was walking in a field and I saw this little guy 😂❤️ https://t.co/p0kQzcAs0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!! @ChrisKTLA HAVE GREAT DAY!! Cheers🍻 https://t.co/jikuA6iy3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing hurts more than losing one of your girls you thought you'd anyways rock w 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was in the basement giving my inside rabbits a carrot. Victoria Grace is not very nice. She’s a little aggressive… https://t.co/2XcoTLNnTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Audreystanley@cuatc, Rachel Maddow did an amazing job tonight on why this president can be indicted. She has a fabu… https://t.co/C36l88lWTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tenemos #nuevosproductos de maquillaje de edición limitada, te gustan? Búscalos en https://t.co/WtCUfSoem6  #makeup… https://t.co/jHa4fYGzuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yet it is still super disconcerting to see that 40 some odd percent of people would even be in the pro-tRUMP/tr… https://t.co/HpsdqcnQSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamJBoston @johncardillo You are so right.  Human trafficking also at southern border.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D3_B0H All the horror that came to their family. All because she couldn’t love a motherless child. Smh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just heard that Barr said a sitting potus could not be indicted! Ok so as soon as he gets out indict him! What’s the fucking problem?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dirkduncum The first one was grammatically correct. I owe nothing to anyone. Or you could say i don’t owe anyone a… https://t.co/z4WAergFUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hw_chronicle I love that you’re all working together on The Chronicle! What a great group featured here. Well written, Sophie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what the inside of the mobile pet hyperbaric unit that was stolen in Houston looked like uggg!! However gre… https://t.co/ZAXUnddg7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[#globalvillage According To Netflix, We All Have 6 Shows In Common: Bird Box through Stranger Things... @forbes https://t.co/uWIsk2tNHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissagorga what was the lipstick color in #RHONJ that you were wearing? Awesome look!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, you have a point. I disagree with you on transitioning, but you have a point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to move because I just want to be a normal fucking couple who does normal things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is climate change. We can do some things, but we can't pay for or fix the whole world. To think otherwise is… https://t.co/UOX8s2fKOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bad thing about this hotel: I can hear the dude next door snoring. Good thing about this hotel: homemade cookies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec Wait, I thought we were finishing the wall and we had wall already being built.  What’s the emergency?  A… https://t.co/ySAjjbO5ij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoorWullie @olypaw A Space Car, something like the Jetson’s would drive, right 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning 😃 sharing how colorful and beautiful the Yuma garden department looks this morning...#402toYuma… https://t.co/72qpuRihwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[So blessed to have meant the friends I have. If anyone doubts moving somewhere without knowing anyone things will fall into place ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skrulnik @davematthewsbnd They don’t come in the mail til just before the show]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KentuckyBecky @kristyjmc Happy birthday Becky!! You don’t know me (but you will in a few days) but I’m still gonna… https://t.co/EditbuzkAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve is the best! @CafeMartorano #legendaryrestaurant #epicfood #goat @KissRoyBoy https://t.co/nMLjduoqVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Homecourtadvantage☘️Let’s Go Caseys Beat Squan        #underdogsarehungrydogs🧩#Autismhoops https://t.co/sZojlGWlP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smooth, tasty &amp; dry but not TOO dry. Yum! - Drinking a Vanilla Nitromare by @LTDBrewing at @ltdbrewing  — https://t.co/0ACQzKFf7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me rompería el corazón horrible si me llego a enterar que Jbalvin es uribista]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Muslim_Patrol @AmericanZabiha @banago Men who think it’s appropriate to repeatedly DM married women or any women w… https://t.co/vZ6wLyCxLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Comes Love… Then Comes Mortgage? Couples Lead the Way https://t.co/8N12x03HpA]]></document></documents></author>