<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[FREEDA FOREMAN 6/2000 @GeorgeForeman asked at start of five FIGHT BOXING career."Do you think my Daddy is PROUD of… https://t.co/HebadOfN3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Second arrest made after man’s body found in suitcase floating in SF Bay - San Francisco Chronicle… https://t.co/osYu8myUs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who take nappies on the commons room couches are true bravery...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManishChandSurg @UCLDivofSurgery @GemmaASiT @msukinhealth @HoloLens @AISChannel @BBCClick @beccacaddy @cnntech… https://t.co/FFuhAkT6pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndiBearCo @wyocoalroller Beautiful and can flank. What else could u ask for]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up running errands paying bills getting shit done early 6:16 am @ Stockton, California https://t.co/5zu2gmFHqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I would’ve gotten a pic but I swear on my life I just saw the Jurassic Park Jeep Wrangler driving around Kokomo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awe he got you flowers ? Oh that makes him the best ? He’s be the best for a 700+ credit score and paying off my st… https://t.co/r2j5ViddfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night’s Leafs performance in STL was poor all round, from the playmakers to the decision-makers.   We add our… https://t.co/tMYV5T7UJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the women's side I think the MEC also gets three in. Give me Glenville as the top seed, Charleston No. 6 and Wes… https://t.co/Elar2Dm5tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pt Maybe people are that dumb. Successful politicians are masters at understanding the people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reclaimed Vintage Wood Beams In Gorgeous Transitional Kitchen Design https://t.co/WBhl94sPlE https://t.co/HyooNPGxOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually, great words by Obama, but this should have been titled differently by Time. 🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, #TheAcademy saw this and internalized it. And I’m here for it. https://t.co/xXOXVYTyJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichLangdale I get this when I visit https://t.co/IYlh3OI02c on firefox:   "Your connection is not secure  The own… https://t.co/WG5ZXKvBny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Typically, mid to low 60s RPI rankings were where at large hopes went to die. If the NET is handled similarly, team… https://t.co/qNkGE1YkWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sims_jw We have a garage. But I'd use it so often it would hardly ever be idle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyshawn @LZGranderson @TravisRodgers @CMMSpectrum @RojGrobes @stephenasmith @VeniceMase @LAIreland @BergmanGreg… https://t.co/rr7PbMdFBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebreakofdays Amen Dawn! Hope you have a great evening. https://t.co/sWaZktYesB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ndinsanity I can’t take this debate seriously because he ran to GS... he made the finals with westbrook and harden… https://t.co/myT0UWInMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving is easy. It’s the obstacles that come with it that’s hard. Keep focused and work through it together for God… https://t.co/6ZM8mn5brX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CantankerousCMF @11amAirRaid @wwarfel71 It is. And so many amazing planes. We should stick trump on the AF1 they have there]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing more satisfying then seeing @KyleBusch spinning at @DISupdates #loveit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS Deslusional Donald thinks that getting rid of his Communications Director will improve his… https://t.co/kCcEgmZaD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFGillespie Binged it more than a week ago, and I still have it stuck in my head. Some great stuff in there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.#BREAKING: A mobile home caught fire around 4:30 a.m. in the 52 Mobile Home Estates neighborhood in West Lafayette… https://t.co/iRsFwRbaL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandiOnAir After Barr’s contribution to allowing the perpetrators of Iran/Contra to go free, I doubt this very mu… https://t.co/N1lX80gYXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBN_Wildcats_ I concur. Right now looks like Ole Miss wants it more...let's go Cat's!! 🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carolyncorneli8 @ctanner3 @Patriot988 @MaliCatz @WandaWomanHere @JulieReichwein1 @LUV_my_Country @my3monkees… https://t.co/AllTgnp8Rc]]></document><document><![CDATA[REPOST from @lgbt_history_ig “I’ll tell you what freedom is to me: No Fear! . ”I mean, really, no fear. If I could… https://t.co/rBAGBnbRn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruinsHONK @tomecurran @8fiveBibby Dwayne Allen just got cut dumb ass bitch Curran, come again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Why do Democrats feel compelled to tell me how I should live my life? Why do Democrats want to take away my freedom?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited to be at the 2019-2020 Season Announcement for @Indy_Symphony! https://t.co/2YeEZP8maC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Why in the world are the media still reporting on what Roseanne Barr says? We care, why? Does every wa… https://t.co/E4oziviSYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a warm welcome this morning in Sioux City, even with the snowy weather. And people at Pierce Street Coffee eve… https://t.co/CN4dGAHV79]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vanessa Pérez-Sauquillo   dime, si me frotabas  hasta romperme en hebras, por qué nunca pasaste los dedos a través.… https://t.co/Qr9qzaUu4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachKCH I make these students tell their parents how they are doing before I talk to the parents. #teachingtip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when I was starting to feel pretty good.. got wiped out by a kidney stone. Spending tonight in hospital...brut… https://t.co/Nmeaeo7z0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say it was delivered. So now either someone stole one package out of my mailbox or idk.🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shakeshack really disappointed with these Chick’n Bites.... chicken and breading wouldn’t stay together https://t.co/M2iC8qF6lO]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Paddy’s Day Tournament in Franklin - Gracey serving for TEV 17 Abigail. #volleyballdad @ Franklin, Tennessee https://t.co/O8u8SIUDgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Fostech Fighter Lite Rifle w/ Echo Trigger from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $1200!… https://t.co/QjgyC4kgjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MVP_nobody If the Cards do indeed try to trade him I'm sure the Giants will check in on the cost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Amen Dan B. because DST is an absolute joke and hoax perpetrated to save energy. In actual reality it cos… https://t.co/w0y7HPinP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanesFan311 @jsram311 I used to think this was a trippy video because of the strange camera motion during the chor… https://t.co/pDKtu3k3BM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joannperrone15 Traders that need to be jailed or ran out of this country permanently,]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do you people follow me just to watch me?  go rt my post &amp; support me, something man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you agree with the @STLWizard’s choices here? @Cardinals have lots of deserving HOF candidates on their ballot t… https://t.co/iD0wi9AwbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’d probably be more successful if we would stand a little further off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me waiting for taylor to post something with 4 things in it https://t.co/Cu51AlVgs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBA I miss these days, how about another 40 game lock out next season🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting on sunglasses is 99% based on mood and 1% based on if the sun is actually in my eyes..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiamCooper__ Truly honoured and humbled with those words w/almost 50 years of support!Your work rate, leadership,… https://t.co/JH3IywRTV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I remember from my dreams last night was somebody saying “do you want ketchup with that?”  Not surprised.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us for this #historic event featuring @EnonTab @VesselPraiseDance, @kapsi1911 , @NewConvenantChurch,… https://t.co/Ac6eBSPM1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do I insist that I'm fine and don't wanna talk about stuff whenever someone asks even though I'm not and I should]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the @Raiders land @AB84 we better call @KingCrab15 @derekcarrqb will have a nice 1, 2 punch again. #RaiderNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hampton House (University Village Building 2) in Norfolk, VA https://t.co/ZiqRCdowxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul How can you not see what's going on at the border. With the murder, rapes, sex trafficking, human traffic… https://t.co/ZMhsqh1EOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed my first visit to Eastbrook High School FCA yesterday afternoon! Great student-led lesson about owning out… https://t.co/Fs1R054XRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Lackawanna Wrestling (@falconssports) on your first ever All-American at the 2019 @NJCAAWrestling National… https://t.co/kYZhXwulCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the people who have most impacted me in the past couple years have been these amazing two: @Tiffanyoche and… https://t.co/rp0CD2PjGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Bills are a better situation than the Raiders. At least in terms of football.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Hartigan @Spotify @ApplePodcasts @Stitcher @TwitchPoker @VanessaKade @Stapes @JenniferTilly @normmacdonald Heck… https://t.co/bGEkkIOYZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expo 2019 celebrating #Smokey Bear’s #Birthday was a great success. 1,000 cupcakes for those attending.… https://t.co/Qnf47nTVUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciate all your follow up ... you became the night’s “master tweeter” so good on you!  Enjoyed chatting afterwa… https://t.co/qKEsEoXIgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is a national emergency and what isn’t - A short tweet.   Is:  Flint, Michigan  Gun Violence  Our aging infras… https://t.co/SO10GsgC7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bighomerfan or does ganassi do some work out of there now (not sure how much of DEI still exists from that merger)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesserodrigue23 @ckimbrell @DonaldJTrumpJr @TPUSA @charliekirk11 @bennyjohnson @DanCrenshawTX @kimguilfoyle You poor things sore loosers]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I don’t want to hear any of y’all bums saying “iF itS In A SOnG I WiLl sAY iT iDC” it is not hard at all to not… https://t.co/5WNzvIGbGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyCarlsonShow I'm the "most famous" one on Twitter. The more famous Ron Clements doesn't have a Twitter account.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahh I see the Russian bots have figured out how to attack @Twitter again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A victim focuses on outward pressures, while a victor focuses on inward confidence. Someone with a victim mentality… https://t.co/tvnHADGbef]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teodors Bluegers with Geno &amp; Phil? Lions, Tigers &amp; Bears, oh my.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After three quarters, Lexington trails Cornerstone 41-25 at Dwight Regional.🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lorain Public Library - Main Library - @lorainlibrary in Lorain, OH https://t.co/FCeuqoEMdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Son_mamadas @princhipesxa @Una_tal_Dian @DafneHDSM @lopezobrador_ Y sabes que estaba pensando? ALV hasta telepático nos saliste 😂😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday March 9 - The Washington Post Today's Headlines:    Trump budget to propose slashing domestic spending, bo… https://t.co/6OAxsgKRC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all really need to do yourself a favor and start listening to @CriticalRole]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pitcher vs. Greyhounds: WP-Daniel Garza 5.1 IP 5Ks 1BB 0ER 5Hits @RHbaseballFAITH @RHHS_Bobcats @RHISD_Athletics… https://t.co/snuqzsoA0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nolan Arenado, Rockies finalizing an eight-year, $260 million contract extension https://t.co/2ttM6lSwS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kenya_Simone17 Just miserable with himself. Don’t let him get to you. Stay positive and do you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter don’t wanna see you be great 😂😭 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19… https://t.co/th62BmVBL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do the facial expressions and body language from this punk from Newark always look like he’s about to burst and… https://t.co/QRaGab0P0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny how you call this assault. Let’s just not mention that these men returned from being bombed every day and loo… https://t.co/cIc3unCXtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDLHughley @kevdog How it go DL? "People go home and say some f**ked up s**t". Yea you were right my brother]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días... 1 Juan  4:4 Hijitos, vosotros sois de Dios, y los habéis vencido; porque el que en vosotros está, es… https://t.co/5fC7jGBkUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@powertoimpeach You are too dumb to know that what #Cohen Plead guilty to is not a crime. That is the FACT JACK!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SudburyHomebrew @WellingtonBrew @DrunkPolkaroo @Paul__G__ @david_buist @ottawahockey @heatherington84 @xBeannote… https://t.co/d3iC3YfTV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another example of greed and pharma taking unethical action which dictates a patients medical care:… https://t.co/3ZPzdk78Y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shocked that the #TheGifted probably wont be renewed for a season 3 on #Fox, this is one of my favourite superhero… https://t.co/tmIOmAyfJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[We both shared Tom Kosnik as a mentor in Palo Alto. #ENGR145  Princeton and @stanfordEng’s @bases co produced… https://t.co/bgCMNBsmgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaroncassio @Dylan22LeBlanc Come and see me if you want to buy a real truck! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anc227 @MongoGoesInsane @jodymacman Oh he'll be calling.....his calls to Jody are the best. But this one will top… https://t.co/tYpJcTXWMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crystalpandapwr *Looks up at the ceiling* *looks at the time*    *turns TV volume to a 9... no 10*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@creepybranson @FreddysMuse @creepychills2 @PromoteHorror @MFFHorrorCorner @horrorshorts666 @OddNMacabre… https://t.co/u0LnqpGbac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Foot and Ankle Center of Philadelphia https://t.co/cODWMoHxHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ochocinco putting in work at @fitspeedAP today. 20 MPH 🔥 https://t.co/bBzJOOHoEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelRapaport @_DrewWheeler @SportsBriggs Lmmmmaaaaaooooo!!  Why is it always ugly ass folks that do these poses that wanna talk shit!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m very thankful today. Recording sessions for the #hungupwet EP are in the can. I can’t say enough about… https://t.co/lec46oNWbk]]></document></documents></author>