<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I just want someone to play with my hair while I sleep ... is that too much to ask for ?! 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolezaleskii I stay jacking songs from kourtney and Kylie’s IG stories tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#crochetersofinstagram #crochet  @ Mississauga, Ontario https://t.co/t8ZEZJkWLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MonicaSRosen. Proud to be listed alongside these fierce female leaders! I would also like to add… https://t.co/lFIosqRzRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful thought from my prof this morning: By the time you finish your book, you will be a different person tha… https://t.co/0cVgyFLblM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt He"s a feral rescue. We're working on him. Looking good...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMartinSJ As a mother, this passage is extremely difficult. It’s like I’m seeking health care for my child and… https://t.co/v0jLmo0wPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backstage pep talks = the ultimate #MondayMotivation 💕 . . . . #backstage #dancelife #dancer #danceteacher… https://t.co/QcpmOLmzX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fill in the blank With whatever GOP candidate was there. Take a moment of silence for democracy in North Carolina.… https://t.co/HkRxQ8Hupd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The peer-to-peer learning model used throughout the MaRS Growth programming continues to inspire. Pushing boundarie… https://t.co/L9ealUXcrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicholas S. Zeppos: Vanderbilt: do right by BethAnn Mclaughlin - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/tem5Caf1mG via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrEarpLA I love this movie! Especially since we get to be a part of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating International Women’s Day with these amazing UPSers in the Central Plains District today! 💜#wld… https://t.co/dHbXkgxaka]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tweeps! What are ways you overcome writer’s block that does  not involve a seance to summon the will? #PhDChat… https://t.co/vruUzw2jsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump F off you are a real jerk.  Have some respect for the President and the people who voted for him....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael would stay with me on the couch I slept on when I was going through it and I lived in a living room with ha… https://t.co/k0pEjmRHJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stancehoops @ojhospitality97 @JenksTaziah Here’s the Queen of Stance Sock Louisville Ky @JenksTaziah she wants to… https://t.co/7IhHgINx9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[why is colin jost so wet for amazon ? he keeps defending it on weekend update]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our LaCreole Robotics Team took part in the state competition this weekend. Team Glitch took home the Spirit Award… https://t.co/4R7kHsIifl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matcha Green Tea &amp; Black Sesame Ice Cream @taiyakinyc #matcha #icecream #dessert #instadessert #desserts… https://t.co/h3WjbHxxi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[a dude ran into me at the airport and erik told me the guy was a porn star... that is all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealkevinTE @h8Wankmaggot45 I don’t because it will kill me...if my husband doesn’t first!  Not worth it...8 years on the 14th!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amm_lee @Sarcasticluther Totally! Both are just too much! I had a dear sweet friend who was the spitting image of… https://t.co/JZCJDTKhDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randy_silver @James_Mayes @destraynor @cagan @kennethn @ttorres @msjaneaustin @iamctodd @leahickman @joshelman Yaa… https://t.co/etU7ziqcEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BilldeBlasio @scdp Perhaps the biggest laugh @BilldeBlasio got today:  A woman says she wants to ask a question fo… https://t.co/8tIgbyp32S]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD continued: - Prohibit data transfer good and go further to address ownership of users data - there’s a reason… https://t.co/ICU0yzrpDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[How mad are the Real World kids from the 90’s that went on to be servers at Saddle Ranch, after 6 months of exposur… https://t.co/GATPe1jWJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EarnhardtKelley @sambassartist I loved his art work. He is really going to be missed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder if Star is Born % includes Gaga’s singing too. Especially the Ahh-aw-ahhh-aoww-aww-ah in shallow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariooRoca 1) Lavanda 2) Pan recién hecho 3) Coco  PD: ¡Hola, Mario! 😽😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ben__Hutchison I held them all in during the video - but they were definitely ringing in my head the entire time 😍🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Google Play Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below… https://t.co/EhQL0Wz9uP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of these students!  #healthcare #chronicillness #populationhealth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teacherirwin @kbere07 ❤️ this idea! Wow! They got so creative with them!! Great job!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guajira, estas más perdida que el Pan en Cuba. No has visto como el gordito rechoncho de Corea del Norte dejo de ju… https://t.co/oQc8OUuixe]]></document><document><![CDATA[And this Old South home is a wrap! Video reveal coming soon!#wannalivehere #contractor #realtor #moveitimproveit… https://t.co/Gal1YNnxMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger Complicit with probable acts of treason; criminal aiding and abetting]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember screaming at the television set during the presidential campaign when he lied and lied and lied]]></document><document><![CDATA[world peace formula theory?; learning not only about cultures besides your own BUT also mental health disorders! “s… https://t.co/BSVd17yIeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathdawg @netflix my super human talent is knowing who they will pick. Sarah’s roommate said she always went for “… https://t.co/GHW66Ejf39]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me-“ can you hand me a cough drop”  David- *as he is playing video games* Ugh come on I’m gonna die”  but when he i… https://t.co/1cWXflnHgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatsajellyfish @emilyrschmidt But what’s going on with the bloody hand on the left]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pte @jguaido aplique artículo 187 #11 de la Constitución Nacional. Intervención humanitaria Ya.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nate_bowling Looks delicious!!! Great choice! @2016NMTOY better be feeding you well! 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect place to spend a blustery February Sunday. With @womenwhowhiskey @ Colita https://t.co/328eXSQSdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[😰😰😰😰 nooo mm.... acabo de ver la noticia del tren que chocó en El Cairo, Egipto... que horror!!! 😰😰😥😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prizzillla The sad thing is a lot of us know people like that IRL as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if we hug and do that weird starfish dance thing just know you a real one fr fr💍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieWGME @WGME @AmandaWGME @LexieWGME @AaronWGME @Liztorrey2017 @WGMEReynolds @travisharsin @MovieQueenAri… https://t.co/RI83qtV0uU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will pay someone who has the flu to sneeze on me so I can lose 30lbs and be extra skinnty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of my mom asking how my trip is going she just texted me “Are you alive?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOTHING hits the spot better than an ice cold water after a night of drinking]]></document><document><![CDATA[@happysquirel75 @DuvallJulia @lynnv378 THANK YOU. I missed the center overlapping squares.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful are the lives of men and women who share His Gospel of Peace and Salvation!   Dr. And Mrs. Billy Graham w… https://t.co/eo3C1cBQCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Please don;t spread his lies without commenting they are lies.  Or do some research-how many work for her in U… https://t.co/oVZU7kFest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 @TuckerCarlson @maddow @NicolleDWallace @SRuhle @Lawrence @chrislhayes @HardballChris 🤣😂🤣 Madcow 🤣😂🤣😂 Tuc… https://t.co/If4xfOY1C1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hj foi o dia de apreciação de empregados na empresa e o diretor bancou café da manhã e almoço pra geral. Aí teve um… https://t.co/TXb3Os6Z1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NCMEA @MissAmerica @ncstatecapitol @NDHSChorus @NAfME @dcsnc So proud! As a Fifth grader at Friedberg Elementary S… https://t.co/eQXPikF1ST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColetteCarr @DoorDash That driver should be held responsible for delivering your food to probably the wrong place...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of drifts this morning. Top pic is in front of our shop...bottom pic is same area after shoveling.  Bill was b… https://t.co/69PRRpFrD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HonoredValor @giles_whitaker @CrucifiedMusic @SGCountySheriff @dparkbaer1230 @MocksvilleD @RocksForLEOs @FMedic921… https://t.co/KNSIbuUsa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Vitamins and Meds 💊💊💊 (@ Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA) https://t.co/wjbr7H2cd5 https://t.co/9mA7DkBFiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeWiafe When you look me in the eyes used to have my whole ass world shook 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Kingsway Community Life Centre https://t.co/XNOAPTa4OG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxBoot No they imagined him they didn't imagine a Republican Party that we have today https://t.co/XvPYgEviBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi comida mexicana fav en el mundo mundial y ya aprendí a hacerla. #Discada  😍 https://t.co/MnNfjPjUkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asma Khan’s episode of Chef’s Table slayed me. This show is 👌, and women are amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pro-@JayInslee super PAC, Act Now on Climate, launches this 7-figure ad buy to run in Iowa over the next 2 weeks (h… https://t.co/EE8HzLaajw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpikeUnderFire @RogueWolf2001 @AuntTre @Angelsgal02 @BostonBubbalooo @JSG_54 @esteckler2 @TheSarge11… https://t.co/IldhhzXfoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GymCastic @TheBBSituation @ncaagym Ahh ok, didnt know if there was some sort of block or deal at all :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philly_f_baby_ @YDMilik_1 @KeyshawnEvans1 @tinsley_william we're ready to see a nice Redbird win on your senior da… https://t.co/HNbNm6L9LR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Naples National for a great show! Today I found some inspiration on your beautiful beach! thenaplesartass… https://t.co/xCjoqXyb4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for stopping by @WingOnWoAndCo ladies! @maeveric @helenjunglee 💙💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BatmanGothamUSA @anelda24 @LinaCovfefe @Kimperiale @itbmeang @jonmtaggart @FeeAngel223 @ssl57 @clearimages… https://t.co/xrmBWYKBSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[i saw the finest man at tonight, someone help and if you have woman i’m sorry. yezzy #3 black jacket. hi thanks bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyJL I’d probably lose you there. I’m a huge fan of cream of wheat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cleveland OB team- anything being planned? @AmyOBG411  @monimchenrysvet  @beridgeway  @ReedVickiMD  @JayTrainNYC… https://t.co/4JqkJZOTzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenidraRWoods_ Thank you for sharing your life. And please take care! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[What will it take?? A REAL crisis at the Border.the crisis is the one trump made by separating families and putting… https://t.co/WtvszMbRUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Look up to the Heavens and make your request.  I stand in agreement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @vladimirpadrino NAH!!!!!!! #VLADI1000 @vladimirpadrino https://t.co/Dh3oNWqfvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[📷 larry84988  While I may be partial to CN and GTW, this is by far one of my fave locomotives as it honors my first… https://t.co/5E6SGPyNSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listed just last week and already in escrow! 🎉 So happy to be representing both sides for this beautiful Laguna Lak… https://t.co/5hloJTYyNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am ~okay~ with Bernie and as many others running in the democratic primary AS LONG AS candidates drop out in a ti… https://t.co/Ii7nWXnlA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls coffee, tea time! 💕☕️🥤#Starbucks @ Starbucks https://t.co/jSQjgQnJlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING DALLAS COWBOYS NATION. HAVE A BLESSED FRIDAY. HAVE A SAFE WEEKEND. @ Irving, Texas https://t.co/BD3RRYynf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#C89robandmegan #carride #bmofieldtoronto @ BMO Field https://t.co/lGCDmuKqcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can say from experience: Playing sports for a small town is tough - benches are rarely deep. You got this… https://t.co/g6DQ4qwIG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of Luck to Annelie Heine in today’s Miss Shamrock Pageant in Emmetsburg,Ia. So proud of the person you are, th… https://t.co/Y82k8nnEyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davebriggstv Well I was totally confused thinking it was Monday LOL...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nooo, what they want is misery and hunger. They called themselves progressive but they’re building a wall where lib… https://t.co/lMaEJNeMoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7evenSoFuego he ignored this tweet to support his own agenda and create a fake narrative.]]></document><document><![CDATA[all I want right now is cuddles, movies, and chicken nuggets. That too much to ask for??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noms (@ Beef 'O' Brady's in Bradenton, FL w/ @ghostwriterxx @james_arendt) https://t.co/XSOJA58D2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 HOUR PRO-TRUMP MEGA-BLAST! Donald Trump &amp; The Great Awakening - WWG1WGA! https://t.co/JyUqyXOIeG via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melinda, you've been on my mind all day. I woke up thinking I had missed your birthday. I thought it was yesterday… https://t.co/c24FDBCxDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thereal_truther @lawnatural @chrissy_goss @Boxmenot @TsuDhoNimh @Melissa62263619 @TakeThatCDC @EmmaGPaley… https://t.co/YB6laNC3j2]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 TEACH LLC is sending a team to work with @YCSD. Excited to support their #coteaching efforts! Here we are after a… https://t.co/pGqouUUpyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Are Wonderful Just As You Are 🐼!!!! @Horn_Dream_Big #AliefMission https://t.co/gg317e6yQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj I have a friend who sells knives, at Gun Shows, and I have witnessed so many weapons being bought without… https://t.co/Zm8tIZtxIH]]></document></documents></author>