<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Once again Ginger you didn't disappoint you should've won 1st in the dance contest. You   are a woman who is truly… https://t.co/huqmIpdYwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of our listing on 3118 First Avenue Avalon, NJ 08202 #Avalon #NJ  #realestate https://t.co/e1J1s52jSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[If me taking a piss feels better then you giving me some head🤔. The biatch yo head game is hella garbage🤬! Step ya head game up ladies!😑🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@predsmart This is just something I’ve been thinking of. If we want both that to me means losing Eeli, Kyle Turris,… https://t.co/0Wby2k3sI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanPatMusic Oh I agree, from the NFL side for sure. But one of the biggest issues the NFL deals with is the percep… https://t.co/ubn9njWksG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayorDanRoe @onejoey @RosevilleMN Thank you, Mayor Roe. I appreciate the feedback. I hope the city recognizes this… https://t.co/VsyK03enqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actor Jussie Smollett has turned himself in to face a charge of making a false police report. #LiveDesk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgitchell We call this a bias of familiarity. Human nature means that a lie repeated often enough starts to seem t… https://t.co/EccuGu3dBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGitsAliA Fortnite dosn’t care if people spend hundred of dollars on a phone or on a graphics card :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just registered for the planning event of the year! Join me and thousands of planners in San Francisco for #NPC19… https://t.co/iy9GIjhbHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katamac1967 If the MD’s want you to stop describing their behavior in an accurate way then perhaps they should cha… https://t.co/N1wbrN0WDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRMFFL531 It did and does. But I just posted an update. They contacted me via Messenger and apologized and asked f… https://t.co/WX7E3lZoO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanemwhitaker ❤❤❤❤❤❤ Take your time, man. We'll all be here when you're ready.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bit of funniness for you. #hilarity #chuckle #grin #funny https://t.co/seIWysXjNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8Wankmaggot45 Unfortunately, stupid asses get elected when a lazy electorate stays home on Election Day. What % o… https://t.co/gF3fWY8b5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro all girls got a side piece they run to the moment y’all aren’t together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp all the Bardstown city teams are out of the tourney after our loss today. County teams are rejoicing. That’s f… https://t.co/gC10Wt9GTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best Production Design Will win: Black Panther Should win: The Favourite https://t.co/ojCMH7Mf6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro I think she is maybe conflating being jobless with being a survivor of an abortion. The DNC is official… https://t.co/0s34IZVrnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryinz Art 001/365 Picture taken in my living room, drawn with 2h pencil on scrap sketch pad paper. Eff that car.. .… https://t.co/95WkpEBvn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to watch the @USPORTSca @USPORTS_Bball final 8 and you have to buy a subscription... Doesn’t seem like a goo… https://t.co/2WcXXNxfBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[light rain -&gt; few clouds temperature down 38°F -&gt; 31°F wind 5mph -&gt; 7mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cant beleive ive been driving for more than 6 months already. Time fliesss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realdawnsummers I believe people are inherently good. Praying they behave today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite all the prep— Valentine’s Day is crazy for a florist. 🌹👇🏽 https://t.co/i7tBcdLr4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 @ProudResister You and me both!! My husband says he can't wait for my blood pressure to be normal whe… https://t.co/WfMVHZNYFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give him life in Prison. I’m willing to pay the tax dollars to make sure he stays here in America to pay the Price!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealEvilGenius @DrKnockels That’s fair.  I have been messing with a everything but green hero deck as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[First. It’s team. Second. The manager role is basically a drum major role for marching band from what I’ve heard ab… https://t.co/XiluonuACb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Shawn Mendes CK photoshoot really just made this whole weekend. He’s such a beautiful human being]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, and just to make @rafaelmagu a little jealous, I'm going here for lunch tomorrow.   FRANKLIN BBQ   "Also known… https://t.co/yBeYbuhEDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nizio_h @amyklobuchar Everybody birthdays are not on the same day.  So you'd be celebrating every day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at NJT - Bus 119 - @nj_transit in Jersey City, NJ https://t.co/946XLOucEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 6 weeks AOC managed to cost her district at least 25,000 jobs and 27.5 billion dollars in tax revenue.  When ama… https://t.co/0SJcmw4ydR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost mscreamofthecrop ・・・ Today's was dope!!! Thank you @DonnieLynee_ for being today's featured guest Artist! 🤗… https://t.co/ZzpT6h5g4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was supposed to show my friends My City last night and was passed out after 1 drunk 😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t need a holiday to show how much I love this girl, but it is Valentine’s Day so why not? 🤔🥰🤪 #iloveyou #goals… https://t.co/8DLaqRrHBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unbelievable. Now, after paying for our flights with @AmericanAir, four tickets round-trip, we need to pay over $40… https://t.co/6kaGzS61h5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnaLutes @GoldenKnights Then your job is done, because I do not get!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay weather, I need u 2 hold off for a bit, we want to hit 2 services today!!!! #letsgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was a great eye opening positive presentation. Let’s change schools for better with  her knowledge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To get to the top you need to make some big things happen along the way - Congrats @Phillies - looking forward to t… https://t.co/uFBi9fivjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kkondik @PoliticsReid They need to put up some ballot initiatives in some states that will allow it. I know Michig… https://t.co/xSULHJVxpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Quake_Tracker4 I know where this is because I played #Risk. Hope there are no injuries or property damage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericswalwell @cnn @MSNBC Why are you misleading people?  Hey "news" networks, will you press him on this misleadin… https://t.co/iiqHcMZ3oL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wpcerber It's basically a function of Venus Pages not providing much resources at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 8 am I will have been awake for 48 hours. Don’t think I’ve done that since I was like 16 years old]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent the morning at the doctor’s office attending to a cough that has plagued me for weeks. Afterwards, I stoppe… https://t.co/F4VJkyvOlp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @sanuzis @realDonaldTrump @nickgillespie “Bravado, BS...” Kim, listen to yourself. This is the man you support with no shame?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormaLayon / @Noti_Texmelucan @HolaTexmelucan ... https://t.co/PmqJ1iCDeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UVMmhockey vs @TerrierHockey deadlocked at zeros after 2 stanzas. #gocatsgo #uvm #btv #hockeyeast]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been up for 24hrs straight and my alarm goes off in less than two hours I’m so upset]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really need @dcarterruff to give out his picks for the #UFC235 main card @circlingbackpod]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great idea from @MoDOT_KC  It is always better to #BePrepared and #HaveAPlan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Central_IL_GBB @AOCathletics @NoahNewmanWAND @1233McCain @ibcacoaches https://t.co/sV2HRZCtOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Route 422 at Trooper  Must be an acceident,,, ugh. Headed to Jenkintown for a day of work.  The most recent… https://t.co/zah4US2ejt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisarinna This makes me so angry. Our community (LGBTQ) has enough issues, now this! Smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacqueline_xo2 @ColeAnderson444 @ReyleeRodriquez I SAID!!!! FUCK DARLA sksksjakdjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EduardoCepedaV Dejate de triunfalismos que asi se llego al partido con Argentina y te recuerdo el resultado, ganó… https://t.co/kRQhWKPFc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nvcentralsports Old School Nevada! Back to the rurals.  I enjoyed both semi-final games....]]></document><document><![CDATA[1) Haven't done a trans rant in a while but here it goes: I'm finally at a place in my transition where I feel comf… https://t.co/XQTrUU0XDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patel_bole @ndtv If you think time is over than get ready to be destroyed by Pakistani TIGERS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being with the scouts last weekend made me realize how much I miss taking band photos. Can I please just do indoor somewhere?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starting9 If there were one guy that I could magically make a #Royals player, it would be Nolan Arenado.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJonSowl And conservatives don’t strive to control black people and all others.? If you believe that you truly a… https://t.co/WlcEy5t4ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bnau21 And Nebraska playing now with three guys who couldn't play in junior college.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amahnke You’ll just move to Los Angeles .. it’s going to be 15 by 2020 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crocokyle373 @YankeeNation14 You are a Bills and Rays fan ...   Nevermind , you have suffered enough   You get a pass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AccuracyInMedia @RyanAFournier TIME Magazine has been a damn joke since Obama took office. Totally bought and paid for....]]></document><document><![CDATA[She literally hitting the nigga fuck was he supposed to do when don’t wanna stop.. yallll SWEARRRR ya can put ya ha… https://t.co/YeQKRiUQdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Telluride leads Ignacio 31-29 with 2:44 left in the quarter. Ignacio has not led since the start of the second quar… https://t.co/xjGK4KAGR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This tweet caused me to make that sound Scooby-Doo makes when he’s confused?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jester_game Lol I didn’t even think about that reference.   Well played.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WATCH! Greg Gutfeld Explodes on Juan Williams on The Five (VIDEO) https://t.co/il9ggsuNPw via @realmattcouch #ripem]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @MrsLFeger to post the covers of 7 books that I ❤️. No explanations, no reviews. Day 1 is for T… https://t.co/T5cdArs6xP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight's halftime entertainment. #flyingcanines timberwolves @washwizards @ Target Center https://t.co/MahEiQLtsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It should be encouraging that even the heroes of the faith had their own misgivings about their abilities. Moses ce… https://t.co/8ejNEcRM5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That envy of the world??? They are either laughing at us or sitting in stony silence at the mention of your name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bryce Harper to Padres confirmed. I don’t know nothing about nothing, just want to be first to confirm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeMillChi @5pm @BillBellis @DawnHasbrouck @KristeNicoleFOX @coreymcpherrin @LouCanellis Hi Natalie !!❤ Are you go… https://t.co/d9fJrdnRFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[votto is so cool. one of the players i get sad i haven’t watched more of]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DinnettH @LindaSuhler @realDonaldTrump Still talking shit... oh to be a leftist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW WEBSITE!!! Some old images out. Some new images in.  Please check out. #paulsimonphotography… https://t.co/Y3Ca56RMfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcdonaldcomedy Wait. I thought Trump made it clear white people don't have to follow the rules no more. `\_( •_• )_/`]]></document><document><![CDATA[“By choosing to treat others with this gospel kindness, I choose obedience to Christ’s way that is never dictated b… https://t.co/kpFWPryqAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just remembered what the #oscars stage reminded me of... #ghostbusters2 https://t.co/Ulj8qItcyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wreck on the shoulder in #WakeCounty on I-40 WB approaching The 40 #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[People say “martial arts you need respect” but martial arts full of mother fuckers who just talk shit 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard work Pays off🙏🏾 no stopping from here still haven’t reached my goal]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so happy they didn’t charge me for my food bc this surf &amp; turf dry then a mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[When hate crimes are up “20%” doesn’t mean that it’s always conservatives doing them...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctmrjg @packattack2613 @coachbell_ewhs I hope they can keep this up. Playing some good ball right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tim is right @WinksThinks here’s my price breakdown for 2 tickets for each round. https://t.co/ImJGdDYbtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. President demands protection money from U.S. allies.  “Nice little country you got there; be a shame if someth… https://t.co/wKPLv08kHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Voorhees Township, New Jersey https://t.co/TGaVIbp3OT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drove 2 of the guys I work with to lunch today and they were all like, “Are you sure?? Don’t want to upset your man… https://t.co/KMI8OjqS5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heckling a batter hit by a pitch. Gotta say, that never occurred to me before. Leave it to Carolina fans...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachaeljean96 Girl, fix my Twitter. My heart spoke too loud tonight... Lol . #dontfireme 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tess_mx Buenos días Tess, que tengas un excelente martes 😀🌷🌹🌺. Abrazos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarah_Cubs @TacoAffcionado Idk what “snitch tagging” is...and learn more about baseball please]]></document></documents></author>