<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I got 99 problems but a bride ain't one Can't believe I get to call this beautiful woman my wife in 99 days.… https://t.co/dUe23uSlDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoodTravelist @MyVirtualVaca @SouthernerSays @Adventuringgal @SashaEats @RoadtripC @monstervoyage @always5star… https://t.co/0H19zKsJ3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakeballis @loomsboldly @Utbighair Hope y’all have 3 second pause button😳😳😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @cassiuswinston!  You’re an incredible leader, clutch player and class act.  So glad your a #Spartan… https://t.co/g1BnoecgGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Wow, and here we are 30 years later. What’s changed with the climate? Nothing!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @hfc7507 If the bible is taught in school it would be tied up in court. And Islam would have to be t… https://t.co/SqRcugg3Mu]]></document><document><![CDATA[After nearly nine minutes of scoreless lacrosse to start the game, Maryland put together their best half of the sea… https://t.co/HGd2Qlh2Lw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello! 👋🖖🤘✌️#newdo #haircut #filmmaker #director #writer #actor #lgbt #gay #gaydude #gaysofinstagram #hollywood @ H… https://t.co/kNbBTRpY9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[The little dicktator wants retribution against comedians. Maybe we need #NationalEmergency for this too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bridges2italy @_Raul_Perales @JustMyStyle579 @MSNBC And the US is the largest arms dealer in the world !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi You are dangerously close to enabling the reelection of Donald Trump by refusing to clearly condemn… https://t.co/ZKihMneo9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tarynuptx @WordsHq It’s why I stopped playing. The times show that you’re dealing with a lot of bots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@24kCrates It’s free and it is not, as we’ll discuss on today’s podcast #askitm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiaLiar1 The problem is in real life they're almost never the same age. The age difference usually suggests a diff… https://t.co/8C1TEzEMZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[They take freedoms away because We The Ppl let them time for citizens to take back America or you’ll lose it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 @voxdotcom He is insane and being a Jew I can say that. https://t.co/bBzkCOJoSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayWigmore @spencersRus @BloxelsEDU @BloxelsBuilder I use them with 5th and 6th. I have a smattering of students w… https://t.co/eufDuJvpZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VegasBorn: Gerard Gallant walks out of press conference after getting upset with media.   FINAL: #NHLBruins 3,… https://t.co/U6rVW71BI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @JonnyFairplay Enjoy your day and welcome to the age 45 club young sir!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Similar to the northern &amp; southern gamma-ray Fermi Bubbles caused by the black hole at our galaxy’s core?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up early at Grayhaven ,  wondering if the nice weather will stay because that’s a sign that @putney_sam will have h… https://t.co/AVL1rv1P6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Senior Statistical Programmer - https://t.co/KETDq6adwY #Actuarial #Buffalo, NY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember . . . #Kindness starts with YOU! #BeKind during this #RandomActsOfKindnessWeek and feel the #Joy !!! 😇… https://t.co/J4dDfBRmQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, incredible finish and such a tough way to see a season end for Sachse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dirtyfeet4you @AfterHoursCBS @ALawRadio Do Miami have a chance at the playoffs no....did the Warriors hang out all nite in Miami probably]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little kidney healthy food. For the transplant. Chicken that taste like Fried chicken. I prepared in the oven. Ma… https://t.co/ZDzJBpa3AR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nacholozano Yo me duermo ya que no sabes en qué momento terminara de decir una sola palabra, mejor me pongo a trab… https://t.co/nuZx4AFSvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TobinShort @realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner Phylonious is 10  Mimi is 12 And Ali is 5 We are very sorry to hear abo… https://t.co/YEojS5iRIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hsmiles @Rick700WLW @jemelehill Dark World for the win Alex!!   Definitely the worst one]]></document><document><![CDATA[My shrink is telling me I got crazy dreams, she’s also sayin I got low self esteem. She’s kinda hot tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Jeffery.... try to use a brain cell like all of the other idiot hat… https://t.co/qkIV5H01FV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LIKE TWITTER ITS SO FUN . PEOPLE LIKE TO JUDGE ME. HA HA WAIT TILL I ACTUALLY GET STARTED IM GOING TO BLAST YOUR… https://t.co/pa2hVC7gNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbyshmurdaf @YeBoyDyl And trolling got him locked up you sound stupid. It is evidence idiot look up the court records]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahAshe I want one it’s so cool you should open up a merch store online]]></document><document><![CDATA[Competition breeds excellence. The threat of blending in with everyone else's scores was one of my top motivators f… https://t.co/vA2rMXPD7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaneMayerNYer @kathcor Good luck with that, your messing with tRUMPS advisorers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC That saddens me beyond words. Growing up in the last years of a fascist dictatorship (Franco) people don’t kno… https://t.co/ob5WOYOEqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accurate. Universal rent stabilization and apartment ban abolition make each other stronger. Should be pursued toge… https://t.co/nkUpit6JqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Midterm sketch model of a modular shotgun house. That is all. @ Portland, Louisville https://t.co/lRrwKylOKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jojo_haack Interesting that you “hearted” the tweet about mocking.  What behaviors of his did you perceive as “moc… https://t.co/njPhLwNrvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lady Vols win a big one on the road, beating Missouri 62-60!  The win avenges Tennessee’s prior home loss to th… https://t.co/jts8ivzZwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliteElect1 Love the greengrocer’s apostrophe.   They actually revised the (American)NEC two code cycles ago to re… https://t.co/bsVmeeIU9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎂 Happy Birthday 👑 Princess Lola Every day in every way, we love you more and more. You are the most loving and kin… https://t.co/67NgITlquk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just under 16 minutes until Borgia and St. Charles West tip off at Troy High School in a Class 4 Sectional game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedlineJohn_ @escobedo_ricky I need me one like this https://t.co/WGbnFu7a7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a shame I was planning to apply for that position one day. I’m sure I wasn’t gonna get it but still. https://t.co/ghaNPgQBnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepSt that's good they catch them at the border trying to gain access look at all the other ones they miss where there is no border wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RDEMUSA You are correct in that: you are not my son. My son understands socialism and spell basic English words. I… https://t.co/HEEsXEQw3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cari_rickman @TPingitore @BBCWorld Cohen stated that they were returned to him. He now has them in storage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped at Maggie's Diner from the movie Wil Hogs on my ride last summer. No diner, just a gift shop now. https://t.co/Q05XFrXsPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, Johnny Cage is now one of my favorite fighters for #MK11. Hands down the best fatality ever haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Coatesville, Pennsylvania https://t.co/3VQvHWSJyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Awayjersey_24 if Coach Ham got the recruits Roy and Mike get he'd take them to the Natty every year! Look what he… https://t.co/QfImvUqqGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daddy daughter date on the golf course. It was cold, windy and a little bit of rain, but had a great time golfing w… https://t.co/MFfPRXCtU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Iaçá by @sswellsbrewing @ Southern Swells Brewing Co. — https://t.co/zKjeEcGfPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great crew working @workforcecenter Construction Job Fair! @investorstudent @SecretaryToland @Gschlickau… https://t.co/rI9S9hKsVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into some friends at breakfast this morning. #MNUFC #DCMN #WWMN https://t.co/GmDRqbtDs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhingingLefty @DesertCorps @TimbersFC @mobileminicup ...or always chant before, during, and after matches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Candy bags for every 6327 Associate! Thanks for all the hard work in 2018 and starting out 2019! Special thanks to… https://t.co/GGcdobrDcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Production Assembler - https://t.co/uOjJeZTwIu #Manufacturing #Chanhassen, MN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um, @IvieNathan I’m not happy about this. #HTTR https://t.co/TL6J0J0iyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the chance to write my experience at CAMP. It really does change lives!  https://t.co/13lSTri2tp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretStephensNYT @SenSanders Thanks for sharing, Brett. Did you hear about the eyewitness that caught Bernie pickin… https://t.co/zhPfm9kTZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@averybrewingco #StPatricksDay #10K #5K #Kids1K Sunday March 17th out at the #BoulderReservoir  Come out and run, h… https://t.co/n9PEMdf3L4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @RepAOC continue focusing on 45s splinter while having a tree in your eye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s called a salute to America, that means all Americans, can you read?]]></document><document><![CDATA[investing in this weekly pumped up market is like... https://t.co/1kAeATy0lo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kalvarado35 He deserves MVP after everything that happened, not tht whinny baby down in H town]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bizarrogoode Recuerdo me pasó de pequeño. Aunque no llegué a bañarme, pero es horrible sentirse desubicado]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MennoPastorAU @Physastronomy2 I know it I touch it I will throw up every thing I ate in the last 12hrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[almost went into a depressive breakdown tonight and matty saved the day ❤️ thank u for keeping me sane king https://t.co/YxD88Fx7qR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either the Revival or Ricochet and Aliester Black hopefully win as long as Roode or Gable are the ones pinned I'll… https://t.co/FejgSeDKyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trimet and @oregonmetro refuse to do this, because "bus" and "no money"  Imagine, for a piddly fraction of the $3… https://t.co/OXp8cmM7sC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s sky remind me when I was traveling across tornado county in the Midwest years back.  Somehow I found beauty… https://t.co/1Y2aXVFAMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CARLOSEES @EfrenGlez77 @elrenecito2 @luisaguilerahmo @levantamiento1 @Luperciote @ulisespena @arielvmachado… https://t.co/17N2mqibue]]></document><document><![CDATA[From yesterday morning, to this morning 🤦🏽‍♂️ that’s #Colorado for you smfh. https://t.co/i4LHKIvw9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sheet writers and furniture enthusiasts going wild upon @JANELABABY ‘s confession about fucking a chair last night.  #TheySaid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazon drops plan to build headquarters in New York City.  https://t.co/o2P1YIm4XX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MST3K_UK @EmmaOfTheImpact @mst3kmotivation Correct me if I’m wrong, but 2 pm EST is 7 pm your time, right?  That’s… https://t.co/u5dcMqe3PC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BERNIEBURNIN @owillis Impeachment will be dead in the Senate. This will be read and spun as "the President is not guilty".]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @NickMudd8 @realDonaldTrump @ICEgov As popular with intelligent voters as the republican belief that th… https://t.co/rQfEz7pnx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntiDemoCat1 I’ve also lived in the US and UK and worked for a variety of businesses including Time Out, BBC, Yaho… https://t.co/fiSgrn4k4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump MR ; President You might want to include all Educational system's in your Executive Order. High Sc… https://t.co/4wWFnOY3MO]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Comes Love… Then Comes Mortgage? Couples Lead the Way https://t.co/8HIlcELfpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astros grab the W over the @marlins at the FITTEAM Ballpark! @fitteamglobal @FITTEAMBallpark 🤩⚾️ #FITTEAM… https://t.co/F4LMkRXit7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop For education the forward but for responsibility the next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Austin: haze, 73°F 73% humidity, wind 11mph, pressure 1017mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobeyRockets 3rd graders created their own tally chart and line plot based on a question they were curious about a… https://t.co/HawXV4jUUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[move forward together  heed the call of our #Master move forward #together serving our neighbors those out in the w… https://t.co/rTrjCmRnaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como cuando me dicen que en la oficina de seguro solo hablamos de electrónica y software. Pero no también hablamos… https://t.co/hecK7BCUq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging at dental office with my cousin’s son. @ Santa Ana, California https://t.co/2a047t0OQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still here at Art in the Bend, selling books, surrounded by some incredible artisans!  We'll be here until 3pm. @ A… https://t.co/5mibbKtiFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started my new job at a pizza place today and I just want to say: TO ALL OF YOU THAT WALKED IN REQUESTING BROCCOLI… https://t.co/wwaF3ox4lT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rock Bridge out to an early 8-0 lead over Belton https://t.co/idwJRXTSzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmitT82 @D_Mitch23 His plus/minus isnt that bad. Rando has the worst +/- on the team IIRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allthingscomedy The motivational speaker sketch. Where he lived in van, down by the river!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coolkev1701 @vicious696 It is great to see new experiences deliver. Anthem rocks. But it never hurts to have throwback fun too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gg you guys!! Gg. Also, many thanks to @HyperXESALV for putting this on.🙂🙂 #SuperMarioParty]]></document><document><![CDATA[They tried to trade for Khalil Mack - the Raiders wouldn’t.   I asked this question a week ago, who is everyone ups… https://t.co/XsQO0naMxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Active faith and prayer work!!! #AsaalamuAlaikumWahRahmantuillah #Alhamduillah #Allah #AllahUAkbar #ProphetMuhammad… https://t.co/PfVEW3jwVv]]></document></documents></author>