<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MDiederichNL AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA YOU'RE WELCOME! I took you down with me! 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT @KattyKayBBC His lawyer and pr people thought this a good idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vient de publier une photo à New York, New York https://t.co/n7rmMjNCrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michel me trajo a un restaurante nuevo y pedimos un menu tres tiempos. Estando en pleno postre se queda callado y m… https://t.co/ggFzr5PxEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Weeknd’s baby pics on his story is about the cutest shit I’ve seen today]]></document><document><![CDATA[now i’m working 50 plus hours a week, managing, and a lot of times customers won’t come in if my vehicle isn’t out front 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yadi4President @FrankConniff Ditto. I immediately made the rest of my family watch it cuz my god. My brother and I… https://t.co/zUaApG0srN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a great idea for the friend you want to help but don’t know how.  I made a similar jar for my dad one year… https://t.co/l3eYfAPfAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Books available @bonniemacart #embroideries https://t.co/YnLVOuhwdz https://t.co/AFq1EewGvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[For there will be no future for the evil man; The lamp of the wicked will be put out. https://t.co/0PxOknhcQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[damn my sister crazy laced this blunt so it was nice knowing y’all guys cause I’m gonna die from this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrawfordMichael I Greatly &amp; Humbly Appreciate You As A Beautiful Human Being Michael!! Leila xoxox]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to hang out with this beautiful soul this morning. Sauna and outdoor pool in Peterborough. #PTBO @holidayinn @… https://t.co/H75ghkiJEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I was only in elementary school, but I did not appreciate @madeleine enough in the 90s. I see you, girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZoeyDollaz That’s true and  even when you show support they flick you off like you’re some type of fly , that’s wh… https://t.co/szg0iuyLVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[in a Trump Moscow tower project from 2016.  The letter follows an announcement by Oversight chair Rep. Elijah Cummi… https://t.co/DbDr3pr9ck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes 🎥 Finger prints &amp; background checks! Story coming soon... https://t.co/EKJ29TDTAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiyakiko @GirumTweets @Ethiopialiveupd @PMEthiopia We fight tplf (666) for @PMEthiopia to become PM any questions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeatSauce1 😂😂😂 Genius! #TrailerParkBoys @SWEARNET https://t.co/qTO1AVlpU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[i cant stop thinking about those comments saying i look like woah vicky...... thoughts ??? 🤧🤧 https://t.co/P3gCgbKHdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubyRedTwitch @kodofwar I am so bothered that this was even asked. LUL its obviously cray-on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USAmbIsrael @realDonaldTrump @LindseyGrahamSC None of you have any business in public service.   The Netanyahu reg… https://t.co/GShVP4mW0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@JohnCornyn  .@tedcruz  .@RepRWilliams  FACTS MATTER! THE TRUTH ABOUT THE GOP’S LAST TWO YEARS IN POWER.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I make everyone better and they don't want to stick around PREACH! @BachelorABC #BachelorFinale]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hope the ap at my hs is happy i sold 90% of my tube tops on mercari hahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is this Judge Ellis anyway? I think as citizens we were a little too complacent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i jus been letting my phone die and i don’t even give a fuck about charging it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanetRWojcikPhD Makes sense &amp; something like spin 🚴🏼‍♀️ is slightly glycogen depleting. Slightly💦💦💦lol! #QualityWorkout]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HC_Richardson I actually busted it out during the depths of dissertation process and left it visible on the shelf!… https://t.co/BasxqfbeFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel so bad bc my mom bought me leggings and had them shipped here but they’re so ugly. I had to tell her I didn’… https://t.co/F8yYv57by7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adambonin @SenToomey is a pathetic sell out. Yesterday his staff said he is against the declaration. And today, he… https://t.co/tDiex68X6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODAY FUCKING SUCKED BUT AT LEAST I LOOKED CUTE https://t.co/ulc8mkl8gr]]></document><document><![CDATA[About last night!! 😁 I truly missed the South and glad I'm back. There is nothing like Southern hospitality and my… https://t.co/bkKqTkBgot]]></document><document><![CDATA[So lucky to be working w a talented dedicated group of ladies on #pand2019ame @lbmartich @HarperPat @rustnutrition… https://t.co/eRwdp28F5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkiesDeLimit Fr fr when you’re young and don’t know no better you put up wit shit you don’t know no better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erogers8877 @psychdr100 And if things keep going the way they are, everything will!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pissing on the fire calling in the dogs and time to go to bed and getting fuck up tomorrow - wise words of JONAH BROWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s day 2 of the trimester and I’m already up to my neck with assignments😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidkrell @NJTRANSIT Nope. Nothings wrong with the weather. @NJTRANSIT is disfunctional rain or shine. Yet they h… https://t.co/IoAX8zswVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelle Malkin speaks at CPAC 2019: full speech https://t.co/a8SrboBUhT via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carmen Aristegui @AristeguiOnline es la que explica todo lo que está pasando en este gobierno, las mañaneras, etcét… https://t.co/SUSuZ3iup3]]></document><document><![CDATA[And without faith it is impossible to please him, for whoever would draw near to God must believe t…… https://t.co/ThhJGXJAuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chloe_trautman Yes! OMG he would be SO miserable every single day of his life if it were me. @khloekardashian  is… https://t.co/Av4X0UgNt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKubota @VisitSanya @RickGriffin @Adventuringgal @SpaTravelGal @MadHattersNYC @MyVirtualVaca @SouthernerSays… https://t.co/qzfzhEoW8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all going too hard for shorty cause if they kardashians took her back she’d be right there happy with them lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Use your digital footprint to get noticed...pay attention to your own SEO...#careeradvice  #jobs #seo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo también tango un hijo con discapacidad intelectual,  ya cumplió 30 años, cuando estaba cursando el 6° grado, en… https://t.co/ZWFE6Pgrd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Wyn1745 If the DEMs worked as hard doing their jobs as they have trying to get something on Trump, wouldn’t that be great?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This St. Patrick’s Day, I’m giving back by supporting @GuinnessUS and #StacheForCharity. Are you in? Learn more her… https://t.co/03psjYys3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FGNYFW @FGNYFW #NYFW @NYFW Makeup by makeupforever Nails by polished Team Lead: @KelliJ_ #NewYork #StylistLife… https://t.co/Ouf8252IkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, @kellybarnhill just sucked me down a towel Twitter thread rabbit hole. I just spent a solid 20 minutes reading them all and laughing 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls that try to hit on men that are taken are biggest kinds of sluts that this world has to offer. And let me say… https://t.co/zGoeInymZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulgarofalo11 @CBCKatie @CrazyCanuck53 She did, idiot. Read her tweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sticking with the pet portrait theme, here is a watercolor of Black Jack, the gentleman canine.. . This is the very… https://t.co/AXTgYBv1t3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch is ready for @SDPBCProfDev! Tuna salad with crackers or mixed greens! @SuptFennoy @561Sdpbc @gonzalo_lacava… https://t.co/2rmfWGp5Q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's Coming! This Man Is On Fire! Watch Out Democracts, He Will Chew You Up And Spit You Out! The Man That Devours… https://t.co/SVDwJwyBGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had such an amazing experience in Atlanta the funny thing is I’ve been to London before I’ve been to a Atlanta On… https://t.co/DCjOjXJSwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The Democratic National Committee announced today that Milwaukee, WI, will host the Democratic National Convention… https://t.co/RFRtk3uaqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@figueiracesar1 @mariagraciagm @lacoriana @vicmars72 @dcabellor @ConElMazoDando Y ahora como quedan las pensiones?… https://t.co/nCgDQuywRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chickens are unconscionably tortured for meat and eggs by the food industry in all countries. Fortunately, we need… https://t.co/kMVQsTTOb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh some hilarity. #hilarity #laugh #smile #cute https://t.co/iZ5oX00ZE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love listening to viking era inspired music and it's all just *mysterious instruments* and *ÖÖÖÖööööÖÖÖÖÖÖÖÖööÖÖ*]]></document><document><![CDATA[No #HR1044, dont try this CON on USA workers. We have known this all along. Bc we work with #INDIA visas. @POTUS No… https://t.co/tXFeHdWf5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cold is fucking UNREAL man I carried groceries in and my lungs were literally hurting from breathing freezing… https://t.co/TNMWzPGB0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOkieWind does Okie tornado have a Twitter? Asking for a friend #dorothygale 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suspect in the fatal shooting of deputy sheriff in Illinois arrested after standoff  https://t.co/uMrGIlyTRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gonzothegreate1 @GmtzEmilia @Se_szol PiS uważa, że nauka jest gorsza od pedofilii! Zauważyłam, że ci, którzy prote… https://t.co/3JJ3A2kCfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a class full of meteorologists observing the slight breeze today. https://t.co/FQ3MfriKjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are at the scene and will bring you the latest developments throughout the morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to my calendar (which I forgot to take down), I was booking my flights to the US exactly a year ago today… https://t.co/HixKf79Wx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[No sabía que por modelar en ropa interior y ser un chico ya eres gay, aunque realmente no debería ser un insulto de… https://t.co/MswoUb6kFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenRickScott @senatemajldr You trashed Florida and now DeSantis has to try and save it. I think you should keep yo… https://t.co/8uzX9M2X2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget consistency between “X Corp., LLC” and “X Corp. L.L.C.”, and the use of the Oxford Comma 🥰 #lawtwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorbanU_Coach @CorbanAthletics @joel_johnson1 @Aubrey__15 @mikeseng23 @theDenisKirich @jaxonhughes22 @seth_kessi15… https://t.co/YfkX6TUXns]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putin felt Calvey's arrest was justified.   Vladimir Putin defended the detention of Michael Calvey and other execu… https://t.co/gJhEq1Y2Hh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought a cast iron pan today and it was the best decision I have made in a very long time 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raising four strong, intelligent, resourceful and independent women is, by far, the most important role I will ever… https://t.co/5VsNH07Dhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thehairtiki #sebastianflorida #nofilter  #blonde #shadowrootblonde #shadowroot @ The HAIR TIKI https://t.co/Ktq0ecJGrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kimber420_xoxo @MannyMua733 @carversl0ane People are really reaching w my one word response. So, like chill. Like you said. 🌻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seashelltweet I’m so happy for you, I thought of you the minute I saw the announcement 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be listening to the @jonasbrothers all day today, don’t judge me]]></document><document><![CDATA[We preach every day how bullying is so horrible and wrong but yet it’s witnessed every day with the news coming fro… https://t.co/YxE20ylkjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladytron 💕This song came out when I was 17. Seventeen year old me would be so jealous of now me. 🎹 🌈 https://t.co/FrbeWcAKkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler Ryan crossed 20K. Time 01:48:26, pace 08:39 min/mile, est. finish 10:51 am https://t.co/kc03qVEAIw #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tressiemcphd Why does this keep happening? There was a similar *field trip* reported last year with no parent detailed notification]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is 26 too old to start getting into Dungeons and Dragons? I really want to hop on a campaign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjturlington @TheEllenShow I feel like we’ve all made that mistake....😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordankilner @PacificResThtr I've got family and friends in all cities will spread the word. Thrilled for you and proud of you Jordan!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya votaron??? 😏 #OurFirstLoveYoongi  #HAPPYSUGADAY  @BTS_twt https://t.co/U4hPZbRguz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExtractionEngr @CNN @nischelleturner @smerconish Mmmm no not really, the major news media is just milking this bec… https://t.co/DBUxrbdtUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inquisitordj Primero una cooperación para que le hagan una lobotomía 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Stockton #CA  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/bpeCGDt1Rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby   #portraitphotography #ToddlerGirl #CutenessOverload https://t.co/C6aDJPicX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mueller asks judge to throw the book at Manafort https://t.co/E6NVMBbNjO via @MotherJones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davekeuning Explain to  me please what album related to Beatles/Paul McCartney is coming out in May and dropped a… https://t.co/iU1Tfj3AYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittneytambeau Better yet who the fuck allows us to attend state champs shows together still]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TenderGreens corporate and *Emma* reached out about my unusual less than great experience. She was a pro and appre… https://t.co/0GlAp5am7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvmrsl @cardamonelaur What a mess! Dave schedules our appointment and I just want it over with. I have heard so many negative things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is being used by my classmates in mnemonics to study for our exam. https://t.co/qdshbRqipS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirstLadyNJ talking about Nurture NJ to reduce maternal and infant death. Black mothers and babies are at risk. https://t.co/3bPZ6oe4XW]]></document></documents></author>