<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AdamWeinstein YES. Yes yes yes. This is THE TRUE THING. You've said it. Please continue saying this https://t.co/Lg5fSfPM0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queen Bey ­ЪўЇ­ЪљЮ­ЪЇІ #Beyonce #madametussauds #tussaudsla @ Madame Tussauos Wax Museum Hollywood https://t.co/M0iYxz6h2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEAD UP @Forever_Jordann !  ItРђЎs a long season!!! @OregonSB Learn from it and get the next team!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewHannis I canРђЎt imagine the excitement and relief youРђЎre going through right now. First thing I thought of after seeing it was you lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #article this week is on the history of my place of work, @HolbrookAuto. Check it out]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHEEL OF FORTUNE: Sajak always seems punchy in the Friday episodes.  Maybe they film 5 of these a day and heРђЎs readРђд https://t.co/gxfzzHoe6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skipr619 Awesome!! Chris is one of my favorites...mostly because of his authenticity...heРђЎs definitely missed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This hoe used to stay playing with me and ricky ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ always had our fingers crossed on certain games]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger And he knows this how? The propaganda channel says your clean, well I hate to tell yРђд https://t.co/ITs38YB4Sw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ff_jvp @F3Pod @BMaaaaac @DynastyOuthouse @DynastyRobot @TheDynastyDudes @SuperFlexerFF @FFTraderJoe @DynastyRonРђд https://t.co/3znra2ffcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Everyone needs to have some skin in the game, free is not a good idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr YesterdayРђЎs news Junior. Is that all youРђЎve got? Oh, did Avenatti steal your schtick of hiding millРђд https://t.co/rCQqFLEhCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[In out latest installment of socialists are morons, we discuss totalitarian governments &amp; who supports them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBeurling Maybe our money was spent to fill up EhabРђЎs yacht. Because he certainly hasnРђЎt done any work on new contРђд https://t.co/7aKZNhebTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drive all the way from Toronto and we get stuck in traffic at Watford https://t.co/jegwiuECir]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback Saturday night . .. ! . . #michaeljackson #kingofpop #mj #music #moonwalker #s #jackson #thriller #loveРђд https://t.co/eNYkhXbfJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[IРђЎm in the waiting room at the doctor with the entire trump base. YouРђЎd have to be here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebigm @ESPNNewYork In other words, our team sucks.  Do not come to watch them ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deactivated my Facebook cause mfkas starting to think they truly know me now days!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turfgrass is covered in a heavy 6-7 inches of snow but the course is beautiful this morning. @ Iron Lakes Country CРђд https://t.co/Vwswy5JNjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradley Cooper and Lady Gaga. Amazing performance. #Oscars2019 #Shallow #gaga #BradleyCooper]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the volunteer awarding you your medal is your mom! #PrincessHalf https://t.co/isNohFIgyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[GAME DAY!  LETTSSSSSSS GOOOOOOOO!!!!!! #lccbaseball #lccreddevils @ David Story Field https://t.co/Eqyhsys7OF]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you develop a new method in lab to improve the efficiency of an experiment and your lab mates are unimpressed :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooohhhppp sent a # RISKY message to the group chat because my BPD brain doesnРђЎt let me rest until IРђЎve put in my two cents]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Miami! We are sad to be home, but glad to be home at the same time. Beautiful day @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/Bgvs8pXT4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorldBoxingNews If Big Baby wins it will shake up the heavyweight division and complicate AJРђЎs РђюAРђЮ side claims. #Boxing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@overtime @niccolomannion That first dunk had me like... https://t.co/pl8L60lIXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonAnthony7 @Riopedre31 @Beantowndougish @TaggartRehnn @FrankBenXXXOOO @MynameisMok @KingPeachDP @JoeMomma833Рђд https://t.co/FhlJlZNSry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking I'd like to start an educational institute for people who want to learn to think better. #philosophy #thinking]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fncischen amazing. What powers the voice recognition? I love the song it sings haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night of baseball, awesome pitching, defense, and bats woke up late and backed up Isaac. CanРђЎt wait to get afРђд https://t.co/vQnQiUQpQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 @debilu2 Rachel Maddow said he valued one house at $290 million. Not sure about crime but it WOULD getРђд https://t.co/9xqUIJraeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 8th &amp; Corinth Station (DART Rail) - @dartmedia in Dallas, TX https://t.co/sD9ga2rlo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prranch Haha we will definitely be doing a lot of both, good sir. I'm looking forward to the trip. I've never beenРђд https://t.co/2OjZZFxZed]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you wake up in the morning do you say:  "Good morning Lord!"  Or do you say:  "Good Lord it's morning!" ­ЪўЋ  TodРђд https://t.co/R508GrHORj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen I have never seen so many spineless coward Republicans in my life. Almost all of them are politics beforРђд https://t.co/ixxIRuAG5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@backt0nature Whats really cool is if you look closely he is sitting in a chair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok @Bharper3407, one at-bat will more than pay off all my student debt. Seems like a good deal. https://t.co/aDMS8u32Dx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericwobser @ohiocitytweets @cityofsandusky Also true. ItРђЎs complicated. But I think weРђЎre on a trajectory to proviРђд https://t.co/pA6ayY1dS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdcoley3 Um, IРђЎm now terrified of those things.... https://t.co/W3iAng62q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfaoooo I told my mom I was getting a tattoo and she literally pulled the Рђюya basta de estupidesesРђЮ ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ all I can tРђд https://t.co/qUYoLMP2Vt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Nope, however, they are helping him get reelected with today's circus]]></document><document><![CDATA[I realize that IРђЎm very, very, very, very late to the party but #theheartofman is only on @netflix for 2 more days.Рђд https://t.co/1xc7YHIC8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dan Glass of Fine Tuning Guitars jamming in  Junior Jr. One Year Bandaversary &amp; birthday showРђд https://t.co/swsksvF17b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SatMeteorology7 ThatРђЎs really interesting to watch the plume move against the grain. No word on cause yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[CONSTITUTIONAL. THEN ALL THE LIE ABSOLUTE CRIMINAL STATE JURSDICTION JUDGES HAVE TO DO. IS PROVE BEYOND SHADOW OF DРђд https://t.co/CMSzApXSUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure to follow lafamiliatattoostudioav heptictatz and make your next tattoo appointment, quality work!! Also,Рђд https://t.co/hoHwpl0Xif]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nightline Are they going to fake an Alabama tornado ­Ъїф https://t.co/XPVvuZe6Tb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YodaECP @craigwylie @1SecondLater @FatalMoves @TeamAusEms @buzz_para @FatamboGary @David_Lehr @NYCEMSwatchРђд https://t.co/VqdllwgqU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mnoslrac Maybe you should do some studying before watching (not like I ever do anyway, my success rate is probably the same as yours).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck toxic ass men who drag women through dirt when they can't control them. It's pretty fucking pathetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re: #CohenGonnaTestify One of the most indispensable weapons in the struggle against criminals and terrorists is inРђд https://t.co/thtLBC4jls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goofballgeorge @JapuntichKim @JBird9394 @JCTSOTW1 @JDenmire @Jeff_Morris_TX @Jerriannjaz @jesusoneformeРђд https://t.co/GsSBvrd6ko]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Everyday Things I #see in #newyorkcity #upperwestside #uws #tvwriting #screenwriting #amediting #amwritingРђд https://t.co/DTkrdPiFD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandadeibert I have a unique perspective: when IРђЎm writing, my work is far better when I wait until the last minuРђд https://t.co/Kje2fRdgod]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because each active scene is kept afloat by a small number of people who are overworked and underpaid, Рђюselling-outРђд https://t.co/4Q300JKEVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miina_Ottawa Good morning Miina and happy Sunday from my alternative music station ­Ъўў­Ъўў­Ъњќ­ЪњЋ­ЪњЋ­ЪњЋ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zehicle @kubernetesio Today we're exclusively multi-tenant, but looking to allow dedicated clusters for large-scalРђд https://t.co/9exmR6gzql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@True_Canuck1 Discount the opinions and deluded beliefs of demonstrated, self proclaimed bigots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jrdns ah gotcha, yeah they resisted operation sea lion (invasion of britain) which would have drawn out the war wРђд https://t.co/WFL2AbU9Fb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chores are done. Time to ride with #lucile2 ! #livetoride #ridetolive #yamahawarrior1700 @ North Heights, Bixby, OkРђд https://t.co/NVpyyMBiSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuseoArcheoCa @paoloigna1 @bite4309 @maatiside @TerraDiPalma @GPiziarte @CittadinidiTwtt @VistanetCAРђд https://t.co/b0ze2BxPuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Invisible Man: Reclaiming the Image of the Black Father #reclaimingtheimage #blackfamilies #blackdadsРђд https://t.co/3CBnKOxpu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToluseO @FaceTheNation @margbrennan @davidfrum @sbg1 @GeraldFSeib you tried to correct how @margbrennan said yourРђд https://t.co/fafbspGweQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alien arcade machine at TNT Amusements! @ TNT Amusements Inc. https://t.co/XQUaf3tY88]]></document><document><![CDATA[To-do list: 1. laissez les bon temps rouler.   2. And then head to work.  #fattuesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this time, I thought the Mad King and Rhaegar Targaryen were the same person. Now I can Google everything aboutРђд https://t.co/YR3zR6F2kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_josieflowers itРђЎs even more amazing when you realize we pay them ­Ъци­ЪЈ╗РђЇРЎѓ№ИЈ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hidden Canyon &amp; M&amp;M: 21.6 mi, 1 hr 54 min, 11 mph https://t.co/LCpuWDBmQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theodramatist at Yale &amp; VTS; @MalcolmFrench at Princeton; Episcopal Twitter will be even more skewed than usual]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austin_weaver18 ThatРђЎs exactly how IРђЎd want to die. In a high speed boat crash coked out with John Daly and TigerРђд https://t.co/5Pl7H8AJxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[IРђЎm smarter than he thinks. Now heРђЎs not really on Twitter. Absolutely makes mine look bay shit crazy but boys canРђЎРђд https://t.co/IhNNA4KmcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClubXXX21 @Abella_Danger @BangBrosDotCom U have not seen any thing yet tell u see mine and u will be sceam and moang alot loader]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wawa I declare a petition to get wawa to Dauphin County,  PA!! :) I miss you guys. &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast with Steve and Amber (at @George_Webb Restaurants in Greenfield, WI) https://t.co/JTuhsLh9Mu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arzE strong Sister Golden Hair vibes on Big Blue. Love it, canРђЎt wait for the record.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baptisms are a huge production in a portable church. So thankful for these guys who make it happen every time.Рђд https://t.co/P6zwcVVnFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI my column for https://t.co/Oe0RP7mx6o Harpers contract doesnРђЎt change market concerns for players  https://t.co/xb01tavxB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei What I really want to know about George Conway is what he is going to do, concretely, out on the histiРђд https://t.co/hsdya52oPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOD is good. And always will be good. NO MATTER WHAT the circumstances of each day brings you. Thanks for the memorРђд https://t.co/B2CAfBTesC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieMcClintock i finished watching warehouse 13. IРђЎm lot afraid to admit that during the last episode I had tearsРђд https://t.co/vj5JAgCLJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a superstar to me is actually about being comfortable with : ppl wanting the old you  but  they donРђЎt even kno u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connections through Civic discourse to SEL, Math, Science, ELA, the Arts, etc. with a focus on equity... itРђЎs going to be ­ЪћЦ­ЪћЦ­ЪћЦ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichWilsonP361 I know they arenРђЎt responsible for it but thatРђЎs SO Mets-like ­Ъўѓ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachSaxton Def is my guy!! ­Ъўѓ one of the best movie series ever made. Inspirational.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ngl tho if i was LSU IРђЎd have finished this season with my middle fingers in the air]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-game warmups under way at Garfield Hts. HS for the OHSAA Div.3 District Semifinal between #4 seedРђд https://t.co/dxjHAkRZyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed are they that keep his testimonies, and that seek him with the whole heart. Psalms 119:2 KJVРђд https://t.co/xrcY6rrXfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Almaden Valley 2018 Stats: ­ЪЈъAvg Sale Price: $1,716,237 ­ЪЈАMonths of Inventory: 1.2Months РЈ░Days on Market: 1Рђд https://t.co/PWaA2LxMto]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is good imo.  PV gets a lot of credit for player identification and making these great deals for the club, wheРђд https://t.co/8f7BOcdo2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zach Collins could be my least favorite basketball player in the association. Durant and steph Just laughed at him last night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PFF_Eric @Marcus_Mosher @EzekielElliott Is he worth locking in long term? Dunno...is the price right? But to discoРђд https://t.co/4omfI9IJJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюThis is what the Sovereign Lord says: Woe to you shepherds of Israel who only take care of yourselves! Should notРђд https://t.co/6cLuqehBdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[At @UMassBeacons supporting @PHACharter Girl's Basketball in the @MCSAOrg State Championship! Followed by the EMK vРђд https://t.co/8ZhEvgIDeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsCharlotteWWE my girlfriend wants to know if you you only have one outfit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5ugarcane @PapaB3ar1787 @TexasTribune Agreed. My comment was directed at the backhanded diss on the publication. TРђд https://t.co/HAGVhlms0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Queens BLVD &amp; 45th Avenue in Woodside, NY https://t.co/poZXOLmH8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@6pintsofkramer @joshdub_ Longtime fans are sure to relish the opportunity, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fascinating read. It hits close to home. My stepson was diagnosed when he was 5. WeРђЎre still learning, and weРђЎveРђд https://t.co/X5TIR7QlmX]]></document></documents></author>