<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Help if you don’t mind? Please see the link in my bio to vote for my image in the Overland Expo Best Shot 2019. Thi… https://t.co/61izhKyHT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3c3p3d Thanks Chris. I know of one owned by a Cincinnati Family..? I went to the PGA Bay Hill, only 18 miles from my house. Thanks again..!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WxJase Yea, our morning TAFs had more of an easterly component to the wind for this eve, but weak secondary low mo… https://t.co/kklB4OeYkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenHaring27 Look at Pujols stats from 2003-2009 and compare to trouts and lmk what you think again]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Raise your hand if you are a BEAST at wrestling” @YCpierce https://t.co/EXWGZ45FEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActorAaronBooth living in Baltimore and having lived in St. Paul, MN, this makes me laugh.  I have seen things in… https://t.co/iyuYm762H7]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the loop... #ThisIsWhatISee #aNGles @ Cleveland, Ohio https://t.co/iab4jPOdNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[So good!Can’t wait to hear how they sound with ICS Vortex now taking over vocals for @BorknagarHQ. @ Greensboro, No… https://t.co/Uwu4EfKFCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you all seen my newest @FalconStudiosPR scene #GETWET with @SkyyKnox !? It’s 🔥 here’s a link… https://t.co/Lqs57KE17t]]></document><document><![CDATA[FLASH SALE PRONG CUBAN CHAIN $1,850 PRONG CUBAN BRACELET $1,150 ! TODAY ONLY SERIOUS INQUIRIES ONLY TAKES 3-4 WEEKS… https://t.co/1uwRvuP8Sz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmileSimplify @NASASpaceflight @austinbarnard45 @ClementFavaron @CowboyDanPaasch @DOfaquarius @Hein_The_Sayer… https://t.co/P5hCWa4Lry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justmyreading If youve never listened to ‘Infected’, do so. One of my top 3 albums of all time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adolescent Boys With Disengaged Parents May Be More Likely To Carry Guns https://t.co/5NTTkjLaS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We pay taxes for the congress,military,muller and others,to protect the country,when they stop doi… https://t.co/yeWOBFE6Qe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steak, potatoes, and salad.... Sometimes I just gotta make a basic meal.  The good ole American steak and potatoes.… https://t.co/zVM1aTjBAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[And, in contrast to past work, differences in judgments about whether someone was the ‘same person’ were not a func… https://t.co/4Yhzhi7YdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamGotimer @TracksideMikeN @andyserling Heard the days I’m at Spa they’ll get 40k for the week😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge stretch of games coming before we start conference play. (#25 Illinois, Wake Forest 2x *previously ranked 20*… https://t.co/mNsMWtClUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Last 3 RTs Were Direct Refutation 😳f L🙈ME G💀P/TR🐷MP F🔥Nzzz Who Critique STEELE Dossier  They REPE💩T “NO PR👀F !”… https://t.co/utoxiwMBCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Genejr18 @sianoresist @CrazedIndianW Interesting article on the subject and more. https://t.co/0b4ZbgBytE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GouletPens As a lefty with a love for pens, it is a great sorrow in my life that I cannot find a fountain pen suit… https://t.co/0ekaTU7gBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[CBS’s Scott Pelley said McCabe discussed DOJ meetings shortly after Comey’s firing in which Deputy A https://t.co/l8OgsnWWTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only #TheMagisterium left now. Babylon is here. Apostate Rome. SS. Peter and Paul, Ora Pro Nobis. ➕ #CatholicTwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 53: Easy pace after a long night. #noexcuses #blackmenrunatlanta #ahealthybrotherhood #atlantatrackclub @ Hartf… https://t.co/TcQMvYhw6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMUAthletics vs. @JessupAthletics tomorrow at Horton Court, for the GSAC Championship game at 6pm! https://t.co/I6ImozbkCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cum show us boy some love on our birthdays meet us @TheAbbeyWeHo tomorrow at 7pm!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realBenShapero @Ilhan @mcbyrne I still want answers why it's ok for Trump to hide and lie about his taxes till after the election.  🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acosta Trump would magically gain 100 pounds if he was weighed on a scale in front of you or I.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ok_isla @funder People are wayyyy too serious and judgmental on here. C'mon, it's Twitter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ethanlamesday Even worse is having something the next day you’re not looking forward to, which is every waking day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPrescott94 Regular cycling, like commuting or running errands, does need a helmet. You really only need one if yo… https://t.co/bGv8ndeNGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This seems like a much better intervention than telling people to wear long pants and check for #ticks.  #Lyme #LymeDisease #SundayThoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[What has hate ever gotten anybody? What positive thing has hate ever done for anyone? When you go to church...do yo… https://t.co/A5IF5van4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytmike @maggieNYT @adamgoldmanNYT @anniekarni #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner… https://t.co/SXNpU9uz72]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @maggieNYT is not the enemy. She is a brilliant journalist and America is so lucky to have her and… https://t.co/MuGoI13coo]]></document><document><![CDATA[i stan bts but they deadass have mad accomplishments and are too huge for y’all to be making stats up out of thin a… https://t.co/Rp1B3Hy551]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedrunkpenguin Zion is tanking for the Cavs because he knows the Cavs will drop to the 7 pick. ✊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DustinFox37 Crybaby! When things don’t go his way, he pouts #playoffmode]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JVATALARO @kelseybolar @HeatherChilders @realDonaldTrump @Acosta https://t.co/9zgqrPZNsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a #nofilter by @hookerbeer @ TAP Sports Bar — https://t.co/7UfEWn6hpV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buurds @RainiEldorado It’s DO SOMETHING PRODUCTIVE, please and thanks. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEGraves hey a piece of advice it doesn't at ALL looking shady when you tell your ex "stop talking about me being… https://t.co/QXqIuIaDXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lachter @sandysternshein @HowardSol It does. Wait for the family characters to develop and I promise it’ll be one… https://t.co/Uty7msdkLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OTRSCentral is fucking clown shoes at this point. I’m going to bed. Please explain to me why @TheJeffSchlegel  is… https://t.co/JhRRZawZeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@profgalloway Would it make sense for Amazon to buy AirBnB? Zillions residences, ordering n getting delivered food… https://t.co/bASoxTihcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I had the carburetor, baby, cleaned &amp; checked.   #FaveFirstLine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcunited Ready to watch the match from Scranton, PA #DCU #Vamos https://t.co/TQdxpTtpHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColdBucksOnly Yeah but bro cap space don't mean SHIT if nobody wanna come play for the team cuz they're garbage lm… https://t.co/ZwfSwqcGFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro. People move out of their hometowns all the fucking time. I live across the country now. Holy shit. You can’t a… https://t.co/gZmDvttBT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iTweetTurf @APinv @Starbucks @NikonUSA @KyleWeloth @GCSAA @penn_state @PSUTurf @PSUPlantScience @agsciences https://t.co/xZXP1FCJvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or "what are you doing?" And ten minutes later "what are you doing now?" 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bwats21 @BryceHRper @SnAgholor13 @WentzTheGoat Because the entire defense was no longer hurt, what are you missing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's assume the issue at hand is the same root cause of the Lion Air crash. That the anti stall program/design tha… https://t.co/PcMFvN2YG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Like it or not Rand, you know the Presidency has this power...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioDawson Knowing Washington, Colt McCoy will probably be starting anyway by week 8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Rays taking batting practice before today’s Grapefruit League game against the #Orioles in Sarasota.… https://t.co/nDRDabdQcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A man who dares to waste one hour of time has not discovered the value of life.” - Charles Darwin  Well, we did lo… https://t.co/FVnSY7eRx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pommconnect @WFTV Apparently this device is included with some packages. It may not be included with all. As yet I… https://t.co/zdbMfQmKwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angel Oak #trees #nature #charleston #parks #beauty #instagood #mood #feels #Angel #energy #flow @ Angel Oak https://t.co/28OivurDUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sesamestreetlive with the #lilgorgeousness @ The Force is Strong Here https://t.co/LwdXSe0IK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Sunday at SVA NYC .. Come experience the art of competition. This clinic leads into a tournament in late April… https://t.co/3t6CA9R1ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForTheRuleOfLaw @BillKristol @justinamash @RepBrianFitz @RepGallagher @HerreraBeutler @HurdOnTheHill @DustyJohnson… https://t.co/os7Ddg1bYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F1John @Hinchtown @Ericsson_Marcus @IndyCar @SPMIndyCar Doesn't matter, Marcus is playing in this League now Man..… https://t.co/dDrDNQHJuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump should be the last one commenting on killing babies.  He removes grown children from their b… https://t.co/l1OOX7epXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@linkiowa Fluer is scheduled for major reconstruction this year and next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why men go to bars to meet women? Go to target. The female to male ratio is 10 to 1 and they’re already looking… https://t.co/UMnhJINtWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breequigs It doesn’t matter who it is, if I do not want to tip or if I can’t tip I am not going too. Until it is the law it is not required]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #DontStopTeaching on @TheTylt. Kids need their teachers; striking isn't the answer. https://t.co/gWNPptT1dm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kurtbardella @SHO_Billions @AsiaKateDillon Axe is going to crush her this season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScalaTenore @rigoletto111 @operamarseille @MacerataOpera @lauditori @LaMonnaieDeMunt @Codalario @odbopera… https://t.co/RcIZ3bIjQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really excited about this partnership  I know we are about to do some   ***Big Things***]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Daytonasupercross @ Daytona International Speedway https://t.co/Tf5jnNvW7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GPKMom @FoodNetwork Not just duff but the birthdayguy and sharri yar too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlangianGaetano I still cannot understand how many #IMFC fans continued to hold this guy in such high regard. Afte… https://t.co/CwqOiPVjM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update the vocal performance major and I now work at the same subway so I’m just gonna claim this as a victory]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like the tax scam, this all Reagan era retro tact.  Reagan administration said we don’t vegetables for lunch just b… https://t.co/QgQClI5Ohw]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you and Scheer, if he gets elected are going to git er done. Of course like you he never explains how. Guess the… https://t.co/uUVzmZjelE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been sick all week... super not-cool. Might be a little quiet for a bit, but not for long! Xx… https://t.co/HaRTJcnzY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[EDC LV 2019 😘💕 can’t wait to be inside of you!!   Who am I gonna see there? https://t.co/nZTTTkM1Tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bubinater Dude , how'd ya know ? With a Cane each step so I don't walk in circles. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RailPassengers @oregonlive @Amtrak @Oregonian Typical of Amtrak employees.  We had a conductor on the City for a w… https://t.co/ILdMIoJY7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is too much fake leadership leading   the people down the wrong path for unrightousness?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth @KatrinaPierson @NoahPollak This genius is a reflection of the people that voted for her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalkingDead_AMC @YNB That's awsome - it's cool to c u together now!!! Wish u were back, miss y'all]]></document><document><![CDATA[The National Anthem before the contest between ⁦@RutgersMBB⁩ and ⁦@IndianaMBB⁩ .  #RHoops #GardenStatement https://t.co/2g3BWxWPVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SellsSSB Musicals you say?? Well id recommend, falsettos, be more chill, heathers, dear evan hansen, waitress, bri… https://t.co/7rPYIQnX9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Future of Learning Top Reads for week of Mar 4 2019  https://t.co/RFhDbQDPlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙏🙏 Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Tr… https://t.co/OIh09Uk5xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two down(Trent Brown) (Antonio Brown) Next up (Le Veon Bell) (Landon Collins) Then defense, defense, defense in the… https://t.co/RNMVVS1KSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA When he was inaugurated, he solemnly swore to uphold and defend the constitution]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollyinstpete @Killernato @aaronbergcomedy @InHotWatershow We get it!  You live in Florida!]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you balling and rapping in the morning but got choir practice later]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeMillChi @5pm @MarkStrehlWx @KristeNicoleFOX @RaferWeigel @shaepeppler Hey Kristen, Rafer, Mark! Happy to see you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Now you sound like trump.. first amendment, you of all people should know that. Toughen up mike]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noah Thomasson (George Ranch) has received an offer from Houston Baptist!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hungover and i have a dodgeball tournament all day today. Let’s see how this goes. https://t.co/CkIdDkAQA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Immigration is a lazy and ignorant leader's attempt to stimulate the economy when in fact it creates social unrest… https://t.co/xbruZAZgCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dave Rose on with Greg Wrubell just now: It isn’t really an excuse, but the conference has got to do something to l… https://t.co/crPifNEBfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it’s possible for Blacksbear to improve 300% from last year, he’s done it! #BeatDuke #Hokies]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@sebsf⁩ ⁦@SebFromont⁩ ⁦@CappGarden⁩ Where did this come from Safety Cat? You alone have my credentials, so I’ll be… https://t.co/XIScLsk851]]></document></documents></author>