<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[... coming from the pregnant 🤰 lady “ they don’t need to worry about the needles 💉”😳🤯😡 #livepd]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re of legal age, then let’s all be adults here... and look at some art. 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO excited for this episode of @BFWorldPodcast from @OIEAHC and @FairUseWeek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome first @Lakers game tonight! BIG Congrats to @KingJames on an incredible accomplishment 👏🏾 👑 https://t.co/VohA1Zdzwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone would like to donate to help benefit my remaining $2,000 Southwind tuition, or money toward my personal c… https://t.co/3XWSIbjJCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joylross @ShaftMovie I know right and that was the first shaft I love they got him in it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The city girls got y’all thinking y’all can just pop out wit girl groups and drop a hit, I’m here to tell y’all that is false.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babby_kr Dogs are always be loyal friends and never betray us.♥️💖❣️💕💜💗❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnie5155 @DeepStateExpose @RepMarkMeadows @realDonaldTrump @the_USO @CoastGuardFound Your war? Started by a repu… https://t.co/OudzW0NPc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is a car really innovative if it doesn't come equipped with a popcorn popper?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@playboibayboi I’d smoke you out, but you don’t even have time for me 🙄😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @MaddowBlog Oh MY GOD. This is just too much. Stop being unfaithful that is what your wife deserves… https://t.co/0BvlRNRPVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary #loveit https://t.co/xYGTVEW8Zr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had such a wonderful night with these amazing people I'm lucky enough to call friends...well family ❤️ We laughed… https://t.co/FrnmaE4ryU]]></document><document><![CDATA[alright universe im not sure what kind of sick joke you’re playing or what your goal is here but if u could just li… https://t.co/J4j6FEbVou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyAmelotti @H50_Writers @Joancollinsdbe Yes exactly..the scene in the limo..I was just doubled over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhruby2 @selectedwisdom Wait what? Pamela Anderson? Did I miss a joke?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Alot of anti dictator tweeting #45.  When you are the biggest 'DICK'-tator wanna be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenyakai_ Hey. Hey. Only one of us is allowed to get sick at a time. Wait your turn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennyDupuis @trump2triumph @RealJack @realDonaldTrump Our President is for the people and usually  says "We do thi… https://t.co/iMaBoGpknv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren I don't mind being schooled about economics. We need to know about the basics. Faux News doesn't believe i… https://t.co/0eZy8gdQeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vandersonauthor @Hezzah My cat THiNKS IT'S FLAT and he's really trying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad just surprised me with VIP tickets to the Mad Hatter Beer Festival in San Diego on April 5th!!! So I’m fucking excited!!! 😭😭❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelylewilliam @RepJeffries @SarahKSilverman And we the people get to pay for it.  The whole thing is beyond ignorant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you FCHC &amp; Sauder’s got coming out today &amp; speaking with our students #tradescareersandmore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone else reading this reminded of a proof? Like the ones we had to learn in geometry?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wish my husband would give @PFChangs one more chance because I miss it]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9hgkSxPtpd @ The Redbury South Beach https://t.co/6OiyQE0G6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna know if @KylieJenner is taking any applications for a new best friend 🤷🏻‍♀️🙋🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered for a chance to go to the Rock &amp; Roll Hall of Fame 2019 Induction Ceremony! https://t.co/9oVLkKPGe1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now, brothers and sisters, I have applied these things to myself and Apollos for your benefit, so that you may lear… https://t.co/XkClWxdFHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LPsoldier4ever @AmirSaysNothing Happy Birthday Amir!!! Hope you have the best day ever , today you get… https://t.co/VYyLIaaGyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Johtajatar @Mathias_Nygard Was informing of said minor detail. It's been one issue or another getting the package… https://t.co/8wsyb65xBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of people reselling their tickets...why buy them in the first place? #BlackpinkInNorthAmerica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @voguemagazine @IvankaTrump Hey CO, why don’t you let the Leftists know their gods, The Kennedy’s, ma… https://t.co/a8hN84n3Pc]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #StevePerryArt by #angelactroutt Created with Photo Lab app #photolab @StevePerryMusic https://t.co/rPlpjfbinB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone has opinions about celebs and their relationships. I hope all of you judgy bitches were perfect in every s… https://t.co/XAtL8mXAnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[☺️🎉💖🖤👭My Mom With Her Sister Chrissy For Her 44th Birthday!!!👭🖤💖🎉☺️  🖤March 3, 2019🖤 https://t.co/SH4sHzfVLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a bad spot to take a knee... @ Crystal Mountain Resort https://t.co/9zdgx4gdSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hawkeyeinmd @THEJeepMafia @KrawlAmerica @toxicoffroad @JeepShawty @SethVoss @Legendary1941 @7026saki… https://t.co/Y7I1cIMS1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sravenkamp Mom was flying the drone. Dad was busy fixing something on the other planter lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 weeks ago when Raw was in Phoenix we WERE loud. It was like Raw after Mania! Tonight's crowd was just 😴👎🏼 and ton… https://t.co/miCxRMNZ6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ghostnjabronis @silly702 I mean when you feel like shit all the time being on all that maybe you just don’t feel a difference who knows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC It seems your job lately has been to cover up for your racist #trash colleague. Maybe one day you’ll realize y… https://t.co/NqTwraB18W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PosziMC2 @BringTheBeatIn I normally agree but 7 seasons of The Good Wife was NOT ENOUGH!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Board of Education : Cameras in classrooms - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/tYAQ7kwCeV via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDramRob Although it's more than bloggers, it's instagrammers, Youtubers,  and the like. Brands know it. It's w… https://t.co/3J1fldY2XI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing is scarier than Socialism! Ride &amp; RT to fight! #PatriotsUnited #Trump2020  @cindys_2cents @donnadwt4444… https://t.co/Vana1lxbjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveCook62 @Bgiant1Bob @MSNBC There’s just too much open and to choose from..  Make my mind up for me..You choose… https://t.co/yhb8vsgfqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johndelizondo @SAHoustonFB @SAISDAthletics @SAISDHoustonHS @bralyn01 @MoneyMakinWolf Great story John! Congrats to… https://t.co/C9nkkwV93U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobW521 Thanks Rob, you’re right. I don’t why I make my job get to me so much. I think I’ve been there way too long]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3912Drake i’m going home and having a nap for dinner, no shame about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[how cool. I love hearing about the things people do that you normally wouldn’t think about]]></document><document><![CDATA[#loveafterlockup Scott....you have a penis....you have a son. Why? I would love you...what's wrong?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the hell is impeachment for if not to remove a Russian asset? Impeach him. Indict him. Remove him. Let him fac… https://t.co/yWbd86kfZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @realDonaldTrump Well, the $11 billion wasted on a pointless govt shutdown seems to be okay somehow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup honey ain’t nothing wrong being a single mom shoot I am to with two boys. @khloekardashian @KimKardashian she c… https://t.co/YgL4X6BSuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great evening @whiskeycakedfw #Tampa - congrats friends on a great new spots!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilibethstar i’m wondering the same myself 😡 and it’s not me but @LuigiM94 who has to get up at 5AM every day for… https://t.co/iNNILmUjlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow day.  #okwx #ihatecoldweather #coldweather #oklahomaweather #snow #snowday #governmentspringspark #enidok… https://t.co/Ugt8daRJyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wyatt and Jack meet at Dartmouth and live the outdoors. They decide to take a long camping/canoe trip without any c… https://t.co/5EOwL4mM0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[In retrospect, Funny the got served a subpoena on his was out for not handing over electronic docs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏👏👏 #womeninfilmandtv #womeninfilm #femalefilmmakers  #Repost @johnsonmediaco with @get_repost ・・・ Mother of a Sacr… https://t.co/jCN2HfDJom]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing quite like seeing this view upon landing 💙 There’s  no place like home. #NewYork #NewJersey… https://t.co/RmUjrUAl3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[A customer came in that told me I lost so much weight and that people would pay to have the type of body I have, ev… https://t.co/0s0SiKImL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're headed from North Carolina into Tennessee, you'll need to take I-240 West to Exit 4A and get on I-26 West… https://t.co/RmbQGNLKuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fishpencilcase @wyomingpd Also, just so you know, I have nothing against anyone. Race, gender, sexual orientation.… https://t.co/OSY1oIHwyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes @MaddowBlog Apparently, for some Republicans must surrender brain cells for seats....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: having a lot of friends cause too many problems, keep your circle small bc a lot of these ppl not really yo friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #Karma #Baby @livekarmalife #live #lauva #killeen #TX #greenhair #yellowhair #ombre #sneakerheels #gold… https://t.co/IIcrwTfQ29]]></document><document><![CDATA[thx u ~ whose in the house today for #healthcareunions Ontario-o-o-o-O #HouseofLabour #CLC #OFL #CUPE #OPSEU #OCHU… https://t.co/63MdJXbX2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out in the parking lot. Days are getting longer. Fabulous winter #sunsets. @ Mercer County Community College https://t.co/iazQazqDhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone has to do something to stop her. This behavior is disgusting and humiliating to other people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamilahLemieux Just left a NJ Cheesecake Factory w my aunt instead of getting on the train back to the city.... #timewellspent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's rejoice that it's Friday and begin the weekend with a little LOL.  We all need to laugh; it's good for what a… https://t.co/YwJNFlqGfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st Birthday @t8barney !!! 🎂💃🏼🧁😂🙌🏼🎉😘🥳🙏🏼 Can’t believe I’ve been able to deal with you for this long!!! https://t.co/ss8yu8LOVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que bonito vivir en un mundo donde en alguna parte existe el papa de Dua Lipa https://t.co/r4ADQHDr8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[this little boy at work kept staring at me so naturally I smiled at him, he then proceeded to scream and say “ew get away from me”🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait to play over in Forest City, NC!  If you're nearby, come on out for this free show!  It's going to be a… https://t.co/tjSXHLlUEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The artwork created by Okemos Public Schools students decorating the halls of OHS brings me joy! ♥️ https://t.co/4GM22DDkCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 @ABHcosmetics PLEASE add me to your PR list!!! I’m beyond obsessed with ABH products! My IG is… https://t.co/5GscdAXnvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump News flash: Trump is president of ALL Americans not just the ones who ‘love’ him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[De Blasio in Des Moines: “If we talk about [Donald Trump] and not the people, that is the best way for him to be re-elected”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greenhousenyt @realDonaldTrump And the deficit was not the highest ever like it is with trump Clinton actually bro… https://t.co/txUX4CyxQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent the last two days covering teens killed in horrific car and motorcycle crashes. Various circumstances, variou… https://t.co/QAkm9p4Ibs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SideOverride @TIME Imagine being that guy that acts as if people who want justice, equal rights, and to not be rap… https://t.co/u0Xuy6A5Rt]]></document><document><![CDATA[What kind of people assault children and old people...I have one word for them....Cowards]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in, I’m in! See you on May 5th @IBXRun10 🏃🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/fCAMrgnUo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eeeekkkk 🎉🎉🎉🎉 @jen_shafer , it’s safe to say I could NOT wait 😱😱 ordered to try @SquarePandaEdu out ‼️‼️ I am looki… https://t.co/3kJi6vE1f7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathieLGifford Whom have I on earth beside thee?  Whom in heaven but thee? #passmenot]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Graders spread kindness by sharing valentines! Thanks for stopping by our classroom Mrs.Fanshaw! #we❤️RFES!@m… https://t.co/hsndAk6SIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOURTH video on VERBAL DE-ESCALATION is out!!!  Subscribe to my YouTube channel : https://t.co/ixh6GJHJMU… https://t.co/0wambLcTZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[👨‍⚕️ appointment this #MondayMorning at @OrthoMaryland 🤞🏽 good news with my X-rays]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 @WokeWomenResist 4 IN 10 VOTERS DO NOT HAVE ACCESS TO MENTAL HEALTH CARE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[21 years old and I’ve always been able to tell if a guy was interested or not. This ones got me perplexed outta my miiiiiind 🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only good thing about 8 am’s; they get canceled when there’s snow❤️ #College https://t.co/iFmxt9GUxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremarketer My friend saw it and said it was “awesome, a little over the top but not as cheesy as aquaman.” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Love Day! #HappyValentinesDay ♥️@BonePoolRadio @wildsteveradio @WFMU @RitaHoustonWFUV @CygnusRadio… https://t.co/aoq4nvsozK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday visit. We heard another great message from Pastor Don and then spent the day at the Ranch. Horse shoes and D… https://t.co/KRPcRnty8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[New shoes - we need them! Click to find out more! We’ll celebrate totals at the #2019CFFSummit https://t.co/KvNqLFnY3b]]></document></documents></author>