<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DolfDietrich @JonGaltXXX @sfarrell_leathr Had an agent for my 23 years in TV news. They are worthless. No one can… https://t.co/5Dd0ixngUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pammerhockey tough one?!.  Anderson should  not be playing.  we are rebuilding?  get the old man man to Belleville… https://t.co/e9xJ3Ughya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClayTravis Since Vandy not even in the tourney I would not bet on them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/3 of the league has now felt the wrath of the #stlblues during this streak. Who’s next!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[u stopped me from crying over dumb boys by liking my tweet thank u @awsten]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TGowdySC Hey Trey - the next time you see Trump, why don’t you just get down on your knees and kiss his fat, Orange ass!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews so what did the guy do to make this happen???? remember 2 sides to every story]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise The only person that tweets more than you is the President and both of you are hypocrites and patholo… https://t.co/qyoNb1I5C1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PupDigger @RCandDigger @JakeNicolaX @AlexandeKristov @adamrussoxxx Cool 😎👊🏼👍🏼😉❤️🌈❤️ https://t.co/MgXv1lSRgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now the rest of Florida needs to catch up. Sunshine state after all; we should be the biggest producer of solar pow… https://t.co/0C78qXtIUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[❣️🏖❣️Remove far from me vanity and lies: give me neither poverty nor riches; feed me with food convenient for me: Proverbs 30:8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Your proposed wall will do little to prevent this. Most drugs and contraband find their way into the Un… https://t.co/0hqYmoD5WE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABabip @RoundRockTim @Aarcraft9 @CraigHarmann @klkdave @MDeskaTTU @AstrosOptimism2 @KingBobbyWdlnds I don’t see ki… https://t.co/ZPmcahmRDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ummmkaay If u speak in tongues and say it’s my time and my turn!! We will come running asking what must I do...]]></document><document><![CDATA[SEBASTIAN CHALBAUD 2017 https://t.co/DwJNy1GEtC via @YouTube @FCBarcelona @FCBarcelona_es]]></document><document><![CDATA[The future of the game is now 🔵🔵 @jumpman23 and @nikebasketball showcased their new technology this weekend. Adapt… https://t.co/XjFAqXPr76]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ All Star Tattoos &amp; Body Piercing https://t.co/gKQG9vI8Nt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular Opinion: College Teachers are overpaid   • TA’s do most of the work  • Students only attend class for att… https://t.co/u0sFYRo2gy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. So Drinkitz was right, he really was running scared the whole time he was at state]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheldonAYS @footwork_king1 @_WiFi_Ty_ @Ravens @AhmadThomas13 @Colts @jmon_moore @packers @DelfonteDiamond… https://t.co/RiB2TZBKdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardfromla @CharlesPPierce Did you not see the fear in every one? Stalin wasn't some master orater,he was exact… https://t.co/SeQZycTljy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems pretty accurate 🧐🤷🏽‍♂️ @suckerfreewes @ Privé Bar &amp; Lounge https://t.co/x0N0JxXsgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening today:  @realDonaldTrump will arrive in Vietnam for a Summit.  Here’s why: https://t.co/afv8cIjccG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MakeMyDayBetterBy  Watching  a  Simon  Pegg  Movie https://t.co/CAfKsYGwVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#teamgoals❤️ #graphite14 #nextball #weareelite #beelite @NCEliteVB @triangledq https://t.co/iO0TFkspAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams @Happy2BMom1 The only one who can't accept defeat in this scenario after saying its bad for our De… https://t.co/KG5trR8VD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT is the LAST night to see Urinetown! If you still haven’t seen it yet, this is your final chance ❗️  Luckily… https://t.co/XWh47zuNac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep this fucking bullshit out of the one place I go to get away from this fucking bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The heart is a muscle. You have to exhaust it to make it grow. My heart is growing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suekhi @JoeBarri @SenWarren It would be wonderful to have a perfect candidate. That is not possible. If an indepen… https://t.co/DuPKVK3QWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is probably one of the weirdest shuffle I've seen on Spotify https://t.co/8NNbudE5LR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great week on the West Coast with pgatoursuperstore team and @callawaygolf - Thanks @Amanda_Balionis for adding to… https://t.co/9FKMyE0GiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morethanmySLE @debilu2 Please keep up the good fight. Get better soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are a few things I don’t like. Cheaters and hypocrites are number one and two though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vincepaz1230 @PGATOUR It’s not about the tree. It’s about the stance. I completely agree with you though. They bot… https://t.co/aVARVD3K5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live NOW on @WRHI FM 100.1 📻 the @SCHSL 4A Upper State Championship as @SouthPointeWBB takes on @whsredhawks Join m… https://t.co/pfB6PY0U05]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriJo848 @RedMakuzawa Well you have more than enough time. Sorry about the animé list by the way. Been helping my girl's Mom out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burner_hinkies @WalkWithLyle @dmay706 He didn't play the full season so wrong. Plus if a backup QB can come in and… https://t.co/XS2P3fh3m9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russbengtson Most humbling day of basketball in my life was playing a Lady Volunteer alum. She. Did. Not. Miss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Englewood, CO, check out this #BusinessMgmt job via the link in our bio: Contract Sp… https://t.co/YnZ4bU1erl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to be invited to try out for the US national team! Thanks for the opportunity @USNFT https://t.co/UkvRYh7MYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Mitchell South Dakota.  Prime told my friend to F off and then he headed out to the freeway with his f… https://t.co/gdxGkt4dB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[whodatxvli fades Khudobin in a head to head on showdown like a moron and gets a kopitar goal instantly. Lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank goodness I’m one of the first ppl in the office in the morning, because my dancing while I wait for my coffee… https://t.co/4HqRSC4o6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports @NBCNews And in related news, 🇰🇵 announces they will not sign an extradition treaty with the 🇺🇸, a… https://t.co/lKoTM8JTak]]></document><document><![CDATA[😬 yesterday was terrible, but i kinda saw a lot i like today.. https://t.co/e7neXxFwj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas, dear Texas ! From tyrant grip now free, Shines forth in splendor, your star of destiny!  #TexasIndependenceDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[So great to see my buddy Jeff Ostroski play with the @stacymitchhart band tonight. I kinda love Nashville.… https://t.co/GnPkGXqDEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hay gente que no debería reproducirse. Caso puntual es Jorge Rodríguez, el secuestrador. En este caso los hijos sup… https://t.co/cx0Pj52AlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viewpoint: Why Trump may win his legal fight over border wall https://t.co/N4IK3FOIVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although it was a  rainy day in Washington, and gusts of rain blew over Roosevelt as he spoke, he delivered a  spee… https://t.co/VlhcVR0o09]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm watching Game Night for a second time and I'm very drunk but I'm finding this film really well written and made.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it wrong that I don’t regret a lot of the bad things I’ve done? It’s not that I don’t feel bad for doing them, b… https://t.co/wyYc25FZUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwiesner331 Good effort!  The free throw line tripped you up but we were cheering for you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveOceanAir @DullesDistrict Seemed I spent hours manually tuning in all the DFW market stations on my VCR. The UH… https://t.co/CLvjizZh11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattSchultz13 @SenCoryGardner And yes, get rid of PACs, and lobbying, they are essentially buying and running the country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bravo means Brave as well. In the context of Spanish word. But it also denotes "Hooah"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hispanics don’t identify as black but y’all be quick to claim them 😌...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "National… https://t.co/o7krbXuY6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome  Thank you for all you and your staff has done for state of Nd hockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaraGay @jbouie What a stupid statement. We have a Republic not a Democracy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntonioReaper @LVPesLoL @LVPibai @ernesbarbeq solo se fedeeo el renekton y el kayn y de repente un resplandor y booom]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @bernardbergan with get_repost ・・・ Jason Wilson (@MrJasonOWilson) has spent more than twenty years working… https://t.co/Z5ZcHyFPTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been so damn secluded by myself ion know to go bout interacting with people smh I need to get out more]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llegando a mi casa y me encuentro con este regalito de parte de mi vecino/entrenador para que no me enrede con el c… https://t.co/xAbJsy97T1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCCogan @RaySr1946 @seanhannity Religion can make fairly nice people do horrible things. #Evangelicals]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether you agree or not, @POTUS isn’t the first to declare a national emergency to get what he feels is best for A… https://t.co/aTMgvGTo07]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bguarnery @Millz2BeMade Tupac’s music isn’t for me I didn’t grow up with a crackhead mom and never was slangin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett indicted by grand jury on 16 felony counts #BuzzVideo https://t.co/XoSu0fbE98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkuodkuo The exact reason why I went last year, wanted to get to an Evo atleast once]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bigdoggpinc  Just sayin Bigdoggpinc on Pinterest to see more... @ Woodside, West Covina https://t.co/NdRPwxrC7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkink @SeanMcElwee Mike Doyle plays baseball with the Republicans.  Literally.  That is about all he does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crisp and delicious! - Drinking a Soul Eater by @hardywood @ Hardywood West Creek  — https://t.co/yIB1V1HuI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[2:12 4th  Portsmouth 51  Adena 50  My'Quel McKinley hits two huge free throws. Portsmouth keeps the lead!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate ordered me this from fucking AUSTRAILIA, I’m done she gets me ok @trixiemattel https://t.co/0rM48x0yCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morasee Is he showing up to the soft opening of some restaurant and getting smashed, crying in the corner mentioni… https://t.co/EC46VHBgSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennethrpreston @KyleKashuv That is a mass murder in the making. Keep a close eye on that kid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Corrupt republicans propaganda again! Hey why are there so many compromised corrupt republicans? And wh… https://t.co/jMFTWgBEtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tobymuse I am describing the general climate among the populace, not referring to your description, my bad, should… https://t.co/q72zEsTqgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have the radio or the internet machine on today, @TaylorStoermer and I will be on "Connections" with… https://t.co/JRI6zVSdx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReevesMatheson @vinman905 @Jhope1923 Montreal held their own vs Tampa for 2 periods last Saturday.  It was Drouin'… https://t.co/V5573xYpeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GCAHoops 62, Whale Branch 40 (Final). Tommy Bruner with 23 points and Jahlil Robinson with 9 and Khalil Robibson with 8 for War Eagles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I refuse to stress or overthink, over people and their decisions when it comes to me being in their life. If you do… https://t.co/K8eY7lATjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr When you can spell investigators, maybe we will.  What a moron...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IllinoisStateU @skhunt2 @mmlinbloom After all, we are #RedbirdsForever, @IllinoisStateU @ISUSOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @POTUS What do you possibly know about facts this is nothing but a politically motivated attack on someone… https://t.co/HAkeJFP1tP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomas_tmcdwgh @bruceeien @thecoachvogt @FBDevCoach @SpreadOffense @CoachDanCasey @CoachKGrabowski @SpaceCoyoteBDS… https://t.co/fqUsGlwo8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joining @stlouligans for a tailgate before @saintlouisfc plays wearetulsafc in a @USL preseason match.… https://t.co/GxrDZxhrf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like the Hampton Inn is a 9 on the Enneagram. https://t.co/X53z039Cbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Messenger_smiles !! @ Newport Beach, California https://t.co/QX6dFDWqc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never thought I’d get a car with a heated steering wheel. So glad I did. It’s a huge blessing on cold mornings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchillerIndyrok @SixStringSurfer @roses97730379 @thecocoscott @stevebikoartist @MassimoSongs @basantonan… https://t.co/5N8Z21Wa5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is false. 48 percent or so of American voters couldn’t care less about this stuff, which was evident in 2016.… https://t.co/kmhgVT7rMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to our @947_QDR February #GoldStarTeacheroftheMonth Ms. Nunez of Bryan Road Elementary in Garner! Nominate… https://t.co/z3DbyLXL90]]></document><document><![CDATA[There must be a special place in heaven for people that put together these types of resources. Thank you… https://t.co/rgDEB7T81t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if @marshmellomusic requests a bag of marshmellos in his hospitality rider...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy anniversary babe @jessyjeyc  I love you so much,  we will celebrate it proper next month after surgery! @ Chu… https://t.co/HQZFgopcGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMAjunkie @TheNotoriousMMA has an issue with getting #KTFO or having to tap like a bitch by @Cowboycerrone is the entire issue 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great WARRIOR event at Bethel! #bChurch https://t.co/vBDS0vsjMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic interjection here. At some point, you do realize you’re not going to win and you don’t want injuries ...… https://t.co/tDZ30mIi0z]]></document></documents></author>