<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @MisterHudelson  to post covers of seven books I love: no explanations, no reviews.… https://t.co/wbBFU49R98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GB_Sports_Talk @Truth_spreader @tedlieu @realDonaldTrump @nbcsnl I call BS: SNL aired lots of satires of Obama. Go… https://t.co/JKbIoj5Ml3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yates_Doug @FordPerformance @roushyates @NASCAR @joeylogano @Team_Penske @Mastercam #Pennzoil400 @CMANGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s so not funny that it’s funny i’ve been dying for five minutes... i’ve had this picture for months now every timeeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SweetlySmiles @UNDEADANGEL6 @Carreenv1 @JonnyRotten1714 @james_bong13 @rustman_the @laurajax1 @KaRaRacn75… https://t.co/OxJmReHosD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StansburyShow @HeavyseT330 Dumb take. His WR coach from LSU and NYG is there in addition to Landry. Receivers with… https://t.co/0NgGGtqCpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[When running a race, you may get tired but whatever you do, DO NOT QUIT! Remember why you started and continue to press forward! 💪🏽💪🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[And at 2 o’clock in the morning, she realized suddenly that she was not prepared for a natural disaster...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UntilRevelation @childofpromise3 @GKCdaily Hopefully you see that the decisions of which books belong in the Canon… https://t.co/SHQUv76Jd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrFreddyColon @realDonaldTrump She who actually apologized should go while the lying con man is good with you lol?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all Tayshia showing up post break up looking more flawless than ever 🔥#TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[The calm before the storm. #WinterStormWayne is expected to dump 4-8 inches of snow across most of #CT tonight into… https://t.co/sXoKOLGoxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobplain @RIDeptEd @egreenwichnews @kmkwagner @DanYorkeShow gasped when I told him and we had a robust debate abou… https://t.co/PZ8w14ZOMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[At CROI in Seattle. See news on patient with possible cure at https://t.co/ebWisTAujQ search Gupta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bishubish @Isgoco Creo que se refiere al Maximus por su mala ortografía. 🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[How has it been almost TWO years since we've seen each other? I'm so happy I got to see you while you were in town!… https://t.co/uKZlhTi6wp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adie_Genz1 @wildfiresingers @facingwestmusic @evacampbell_ @FrankiLoveMusic @MarvinP_COR @destineelynnfgm… https://t.co/zOMeKQaeJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKels50 @DrCBenge @ShelbyHolloway9 @MorrisAlana @spateslady @FordAskills https://t.co/iWFQVJQoVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what I’m sick of? THE KARDASHIANS. I would love if I never heard any of their names again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching 90s tv from angry beavers to are you afraid of the dark. What happened to... https://t.co/nBmTGyJMBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayaerskine @annakonk @SamuelOnionman thank youuuuuu for creating the show. I didnt know I needed it so much 😭🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[So blessed to have Prof Anderson as my psych instructor this quarter. She’s amazing. I was so stressed out this mor… https://t.co/DRoSWE64XF]]></document><document><![CDATA[OPEN HOUSE THIS SATURDAY MARCH 16th 11:00am - 2:00pm | Refreshments will be provided! https://t.co/HSWCuRSSwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s  a good morning when your favorite song comes on the radio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keeping everyone in suspense!  What will our new all school book club selection be??! Stay tuned!  #WeAre44… https://t.co/dlsgw4yR73]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I love getting off work late, haven’t ate dinner yet, and still have to prepare for a presentation at 11 am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 I hate to say this but I disagree. White, old and rich. The GOP will protect him to the end! https://t.co/RlG4ANvtbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Best news I have seen all day! Thank God! @FLOTUS @washingtonpost @POTUS #TrumpTrain2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 Pffft. If they don’t arrest him, all bets are off and there is no rule of law in America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi it's time to clean house and get all your racist's people to resign now. Or your party is over! We t… https://t.co/W3eXtMNQzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I thank God for President Trump. He has done more 4 our country that all others combined. When I t… https://t.co/JfITlzKqbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m obsessed w/them   (@briannabilliard cause she can’t be tagged) https://t.co/T8CLq9X7s3]]></document><document><![CDATA[But when they say “ No, maybe this time” I stop and say I was you and I’m gonna sit here and let you make those mis… https://t.co/I1WsfJnKeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Norman Reedus Shares Old Pic of ‘Badass’ Diane Kruger’s Baby Bump https://t.co/YuyUlf4B1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhowlz @TwoUnitedFans "They must know the pain of loss to better appreciate their victories."]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously can’t believe that these dna testing kits are really airing out a lot of old family secrets for people lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[The opponent is me to my brother whenenever we play a game he's just too good 🤦🏻‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#love #followback #instagramers #socialenvy #tweegram #photooftheday #20likes #amazing #smile #follow4follow… https://t.co/uKzEVYKHrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I SHOULD be getting out of bed to walk my dog and go to work but  🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 3 tickets for sale for the Gymnastics Meet on Saturday vs UCLA, they are in SEC F Row 29.  Selling for exact… https://t.co/3lEuucmH8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/db90RoeNKT  @lisheyjohnson  https://t.co/ZrqrsOxUjQ TEXT CHECK TO 644-33  What happens in Vegas stays… https://t.co/p7xffu43Wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @shellsburt18 for coming to support Clara today! https://t.co/uYsrCHrMVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you get better this morning?  @BallStateFB did. #OneAtATime https://t.co/R3f7PEsKoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quando_rondo @KodakBlack1k @ Pompano Beach, Florida https://t.co/Ho6DPyCKNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noah_scout Okay. When I’m back in LA next, I NEED you to do my new round of headshots. You SLAY behind the lens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The aftermath. So sad. @ Capri's Pizza of South Chicago https://t.co/b5KBSIcB7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peraltaprjct BRUH A MANGU ARTIST OPENS A FOOD TRUCK AND I’D ACTUALLY STAND ON LINE FOR THAT. I never stand on lines! 🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green Fluorite Sphere 2 inch, 164 grams. ✨ Green Fluorite adds growth and nature energies to the properties of Fluo… https://t.co/mQn3qe51GP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarnivalEnt hey, what if you haven’t necessarily hosted events but have been part of the planning team and cast of… https://t.co/PkXJFzdIVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Humor Heals - So Laugh Often - FB!  #LisaDCTComedy #MinuteToSpitIt https://t.co/JpOSWJ9l3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Michael Cohen was Trump fixer, his right and left hand attorney. Now Trump trying to down play it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charming little carriage house I visited this weekend. I love those green accents that brighten up the look.… https://t.co/LvcqCLuaMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[all my baby wants is to be held today, so that’s what this perfect little boy is getting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super incredible hike today!  So neat to see snow right at the coastline. Too many photos taken so I just put a sam… https://t.co/ikapiYlh3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DKPghSports @dlolley_pgh @CarterCritiques @HunterAHomistek @Dejan_Kovacevic @btsteelcurtain @SteelersBrazil… https://t.co/ZL6gaElgz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want a slow burn, hot with desire, baby hold up, don’t blow out the fire]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sad how rare it is to find something good with someone and it lasts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entra ano, sai ano, e a Thais NUNCA supera a treta dela com a Carol e o Bruno kkkkkkkkkkkkkk fica querendo desenter… https://t.co/snzGRecExl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found a radio station called relaxing favorites which is basically oldies and lifehouse 😂😂 I’m officially that old person #Old #Almost31]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to eat a nice ass breakfast but it ain’t happening till after noon]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dear brothers and sisters, take note of this: Everyone should be quick to listen, slow to speak…… https://t.co/vzek3uYYSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bars in Boston unironically play “Shipping Up to Boston,” and I know I will probably get tired of it but for the moment I am HERE for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@official_sitm got verified on @Spotify today.  Congrats guys! Proud #SomewhereMom https://t.co/OI4DCuvLTR https://t.co/QBIpfXko52]]></document><document><![CDATA[No picture captures your soul more than nature. #roadtrip #arizona #CanyonDiabloCrater @ Barringer Crater https://t.co/RYhtAaIngr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS please do these things. We’ve had enough of the Dems lying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colbertlateshow @StephenAtHome I think they will throw the Iron Throne in the smelter. There won’t be one ruler. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arianaishigh wow ily thank u so much but tony went and got wipes thank god!!!!! 💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I attended the @TheBYAsOttawa Finalist Cocktail evening, supported by @BMO and PWL Capital. One of my take-… https://t.co/ZZgtfZIa6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was a lot of talk about stephenking on my post yesterday and obviously that made me super duper happy!😊 So le… https://t.co/i4eXKPW5ZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im slowly realizing that so many guys and girls i have met in college struggle w mental health and literally none o… https://t.co/On3hV82tc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeyfanBrendan @jkfecke @byelin Have a look at the whole video. https://t.co/Wzm1Q5i8vj … It makes a big difference… https://t.co/al7TLuHsaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Holland, MI, check out this job: https://t.co/u3On8Nlb31 #Restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leanajoy_ omg omg I almost missed it ! HAPPY BIRTHDAY BEAUTIFUL !!!! I love and miss you SO MUCH 💕❤️😘☺️ https://t.co/LWGWhMT4hT]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @t_wells13 hope you have the best day! love and miss you sm!!! 💛💛💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got the key! (@ Chicago Police 16th District Jefferson Park in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/TVkT0VyKgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class D-2: Falls City SH leads Johnson-Brock 34-31 with 1:24 left in the third. The Irish have been without leading… https://t.co/IJ7Nl9RlFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ironalexiscardona #alexiscardona #alexiscardonachallenge  #raindropproductions #boxingtraining #malemodel #jimrohn… https://t.co/FMoS4gkqMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and les playing Harry Potter LEGO for an hour before bed. Marriage done right 😂 #lovehim]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtf is wrong with my dog? I was sent a video of her tearing up my moms cushions to her sitting area outside.   My m… https://t.co/WPs0yYYs96]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this #dog that wants to be with his human as the human is being taken away by #EMS #DogsAreBetterThanPeople… https://t.co/74pPoFPmov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mar 23 2019 Photo: Jay Saucier @ Huntsville Strings Shop https://t.co/1XaLNDtPTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nunca me imagine hace unos meses que iba a estar un miercoles en la tarde de compras en SoHo New York]]></document><document><![CDATA[my sister: so do you still need that swim mom shirt cause i have it  me: are you kidding me]]></document><document><![CDATA[WV: if you care about your Constitutional rights, say farewell to the nays in 2020. #wvlegis #wvpol #2A #campuscarry https://t.co/EUO29Ukcrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Saturday...I love the weekends, even though almost every day feels like a weekend in Las Vegas!!   I’m availab… https://t.co/kPZwA1Wgof]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am #APPALLED!  Barr #Confirmation a “Great Big Valentine” for Trump  https://t.co/xmXNBF2uCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay, the weekend is almost here!!   I’m available right now!! 🥰😍  Text me if you are in Las Vegas and want to see m… https://t.co/t5Q3XLbFtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdhorton23 @The_RealDYL Give him any 94 x 50. And he’ll produce consistently. Kids gonna be GOOD GOOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am drinking me some coffee so it will keep me awake and i hope it does. It never does when i drunk one cup of cof… https://t.co/SgUBDQHARL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m having MAJOR writers block, can someone please send hugs, chocolate, cookie dough, and a clue my way please? Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boss texted me saying there's no work tonight and I almost had half a mind to tell him "I wouldn't have come in… https://t.co/OO9uqPzw05]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poll: What's Your Favorite KISS Album From The 70s? #KISSARMY #KISS @genesimmons @moneybagsoda @KISSOnline… https://t.co/GRofcu9krs]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 sets of 10 #backsquats with greg.stamper 🏋🏼‍♀️  my squat was not great tonight but I got it done 💁🏻‍♀️ @ White Ta… https://t.co/IagcAHuXYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bunch of losers. This country is in danger if these, idiots are our future leaders. The coach should be fired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all folks who wish comedians on twitter would stick to jokes: all comedians wish you would stick to laughs! Stop… https://t.co/FUijQnQ5Wa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I congratulate everyone at T-Mobile for their leadership and commitment to ethical standards – within the telecommu… https://t.co/EOFEsS8yC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[so i have an exam tonight but they didn’t even send out the study guide until yesterday. But that’s okay, everythin… https://t.co/SyEZMmPICu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenStanaszek @kaenic_ @itsjameskennedy Jen, I agree. Alcohol makes some people really mean. It did with my mom. God Rest her Soul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hchopg @ashtonlfowler @mikalafarrell she got drunk and left a whole carton of melted ice cream on my counter and t… https://t.co/EkfrwIkMwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaJamesRye68 @danabrams @JakeKanoSquad @LivePdBlueLine @CraigmylesMob @TeamGwinnettFan @IndependenceGr1… https://t.co/bRbgKaMtQc]]></document></documents></author>