<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto @BillH_ITGuy There’s only ONE SIDE. That’s the damn truth. Not what you spew lady.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby g made a new twitter bc hers got deleted for inactivity. Go follow her @Kammmwatts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordynwoods you better get started on your own businesses I’m buying EVERYTHING of yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And prob true for histoplasma as well. I guess good news is we can add this paper to ours when we respond to review😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OllieBSighting #Charleston #SavannahBeeCompany . . I don’t know what a meet-and-greet is but I love hanging out at… https://t.co/W1Q4afnkhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm excited for the sun to come out so that I can gain some motivation but I'm scared for the summer heat waves ugh 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Night is a Good Night when Znation is ON !!  #ZnationS6 #netfixznation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @Bradynyland64 for pushing me to be better than I was yesterday. #heath #fitness #goals https://t.co/hoDGhdQgm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peabody: While others...were stuffing their face with candy, I diligently pursued an angle...that I believe might b… https://t.co/Fd2nPWsZmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaleneybobeney I ain’t got time for the best job in the world. That’ll be my retirement job that completes my fina… https://t.co/sJKLIAwncr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yrdsb_skills @YRDSB @caseydaleman @c_g_tucker What a great activity #buildinglifeskills]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/v1PC01mYfr —— new video up on my channel. Check it out 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been trying to come up with a tweet that accurately summarizes my feelings about this but the only thing I can… https://t.co/Yu3GIXcfiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLo @jecoggins Congrats On #Engagement to #Marry AROD so happy for you. #Beautiful Couple. He'll be great #Hubby #Daddy love #Jennifer #JLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms. Henderson sharing with the group some of her data-driven decisions to advance her 8th grade students.… https://t.co/XYG5KmzAKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since Beauty and the Beast is my all time favorite movie and I actually think Beast is hot, even while a beast, I m… https://t.co/Scy8ZJgCAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyAg72 @RobertDRoseJr1 Lol, yup;). I got a kick out of it too!   Mostly just happy I could help out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergioNovelli @MiminaVera El cable submarino está hirviendo. @jguaido manda a cortar ese cable!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QDStores @MarilynMassoud @cookiegigan @Chrissyann12345 @catlovertamjo @mov46 @FlossieShelley @ghenderson1013… https://t.co/Oai9PMSpkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impossible to choose, but in the running: blues harmonica legend James Cotton (1996); Otha Turner (2000); Guided by… https://t.co/E6tWLBGOJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think I’m finna pay my car note &amp; then some to get my car? Nope. Just give me the shit that’s in it. Keep the car.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sandraxf @AndrewWMarlowe @TerriEdda I so need to get the last 2 DVD'S of this show. I miss #Castle so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Black Hawk chopper leads Border Patrol to illegal immigrants in Arizona desert https://t.co/KMmNJhcPzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CountryKSC @architectjill @gbabyflex22 @wffleballhelmet @IAMBARNINGHARD Your absolutely right.....hide your laptop Cams back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of amazing new music was announced yesterday. This being one of them. Congratulations to my little sister and… https://t.co/a3FTxxfErP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GertHanekom @fighterpics I asked him he said it was P 51 Mustang’s… My father flew them I know the sound of the engine. 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casual. ☺️ Pair distressed jeans with a simple tank and sandals, throw on some hoop earrings, and go have FUN! 💃🏻 .… https://t.co/yO2hxJ4VB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so excited to go to Montana when I got my new job, but now I don’t know if I want to move to Montana and I’m freaking out a lot lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sterling_NJ @LoebVernon @TheAtlantic @PeterWSJ @elainaplott When he is dead!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu Illegal immigration is against our values. Time to build the wall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have one puppy left and she needs a loving home to go to https://t.co/9Ybwb7mS2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KmCarolan In this case the money is his second priority.  What he really wants is a Nobel Peace Prize.  It’s all about his ego.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ollie's first hike 🤗 she was not a fan of the rain but was quite the trooper. https://t.co/xQdbWR29dY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is where she goes off the rails for me. This is NOT the government’s job Ms. Trump. It just simply is not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sucks. Thank had the pleasure of meeting Luke Perry many times through friends. He was a genuine, good dude. D… https://t.co/PRgHzopfJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT Good that you cleared that up!  Us democrats believe in being humanitarians]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which is why it's so important  to #SaySomething- Say Something for yourself, for a friend, and especially when som… https://t.co/DWqL1OrfCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[All right I’m trying to figure out how to put on muscles with a plant-based diet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChantaCombs @KA_Carlton @KatieRich850 @DKGlobalInc @cbi777 @waycooljen @greenwisemarket @Greg_Tish @sweeteabourbon… https://t.co/ONlGgebwyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait. She called the police on him for a taking a Coke. Did I hear that right?  #FixMyLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking home today I saw this Jeep. I actually turned around and went back to look at it a second time. Am I crazy… https://t.co/OiXXO0A1c3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBaier We need history classes at all levels updated to include the horrors of socialism.  Instead of washing t… https://t.co/WHoWmkSIAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark to Mark: "why do you keep getting blacked out Mark?" Mark to Mark again: "i dont know Mark, why do we keep bla… https://t.co/Fs5YwuBHwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@its_Ku @mohafez01 @premekarim @crippilingfears @toomuchmonclers @gothbirds @24kgoldheart @kadenktnk @IPAguy_12… https://t.co/N3oXke9CYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kim con esos zapatos de plástico se le ven los dedos ultra apretados le van a salir vejigas https://t.co/CHf2FtOnxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald do you realize space X is not part of NASA?? Did you ever go to school is that why you’re hiding and telling… https://t.co/637Sy37PzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you guys follow my IG? @Kimberlyrenee___? Spam my pics &amp; I’ll return the love ❤️ 🤗 new content coming soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am fairly certain this is the first time I have ever succesfully changed all my clocks on the same day… https://t.co/0cGqteSScI]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SusanSarandon &amp; @Emma4Change join parents of #ParklandSchoolShooting victim #JoaquinOliver in #Midtown today.… https://t.co/LGInKA48zm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure Lydia is using my ribs as a jungle gym this morning. 😳  #ouch]]></document><document><![CDATA[I crashed with the baby at 7:30 because I didn’t feel well. Now I’m up at 2AM not feeling well. Quite well rested,… https://t.co/ticxShMrji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Market is almost here🌻🌞🏡                    Agents;  spring market is just  around the corner. Are you ready… https://t.co/GHAll1Wu4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[She was part dash hound mix with terrier .....R.I.P. MY SASSY GIRL...MAMA MISS YOU LOTS 🐶😇🙏🙏💔😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time i take a nap, i don’t even want to wake up so my naps usually turns into sleep till the next day 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WestWingReport Lies he’s talking to people and working . That’s what he said and I believe him 🤥🤥🤥]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like my uber driver rly ~gets me~ when we don’t speak one word to each other the whole ride 👽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynneasmitherzz also does he realize the risk of TSS.. like even if u don’t bleed through a tampon you shouldn’t h… https://t.co/eB1GZMp5l5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@estalinemarie @kaylenward5 @kaylaabigail11 You must be hella pressed if you have to unblock me and continue adding to it😂🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are going to work? Lol. That would mean you would have to close your mouth and open your mind… https://t.co/0Qagf29kJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[so sorry to anyone i haven’t answered in the past 5 hours because i was helping a 5th grader write a paper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngryBlackLady He was found not guilty on EVERY count and several have admitted they lied . Nobody gives a rats as… https://t.co/FGuV3OoHd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Of note: he's a trumpuglican. They have no bottom!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Are you sure???   We cant believe your lies or the truth.  How are suppose to know when your telli… https://t.co/q7xGy7FKuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think my heart just broke for @mattdracing 😫😫 I was really rooting for the underdog in this thing, but wow amazin… https://t.co/5YRY0oZy2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Polaroid Stories shows this weekend dudes! February 28th, March 1st, and March 2nd at 8 pm! Find us at Crites Hall… https://t.co/tCpUdFtrdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LoveLike_JESUS Romans 8:38-39 For I am convinced that neither death nor life, nor angels, demons, neither the pre… https://t.co/KodkslQX4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I give up Humans... it’s takes a sick person to do this and they are able to do to an animal what makes… https://t.co/acTe2JphXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our       Princess Eugenia ..  So Stunning .. So Gorgeous and Elegant!         Gives Her ..     ' All For People Ar… https://t.co/hOve3mehGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaClinton @IlhanMN Chelsea, none of those accusations are true. That’s part of the Fake information circling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelRCaputo @ScottAdamsSays https://t.co/d3EiqbyNf9 And they have the nerve to investigate for collusion with f… https://t.co/QUPrKeQ9VF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealSonyaEd @henryrollins Love him!  Saw him speak in the 90’s, and love his poetry!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yyarden03 @sxsw Thanks for sharing this, Yuval, and for your passion in helping to #AmplifyPhilly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lower Body / Core Workout.  Let’s Do It!! @ Onelife Fitness - Rockville https://t.co/KvT7vx7m0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Megan almost always says “Bye beautiful” before she hangs up the phone and it gets me all feely 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kryan92185384 @PrimeCreator2 @JarrodAdam1 @HeARTofGod99 @AboveTheBurgh @theColor13 @2newearth777 @davidsodell… https://t.co/JwPJv9SSdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fridapharres not in the racist aspect but i feel for this girl HARDCORE. i was the sounding board but i had to all… https://t.co/AHsku2hmG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeredthSalenger @Twitter Tell them the next time that they were all people of color affiliated with Qnon and watch… https://t.co/pF9rNJJPum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oscarpaz__ @DLPZ_Omar this is deadass preston bruh “40 minute drive to the town? bet i can make it in 20” @preston0347]]></document><document><![CDATA[To save yourself from stress and excruciating pain , pls don’t use @sprintcare @sprint . They will frustrate the li… https://t.co/jJX1pHOyRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarahloulisgar1 Let's all retweet and make Sophie to hot to handle. Sending her family supportive prayers for a speedy return!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrylterryjr @CNN It’s not about the war or the peoolw@whonlost their lives or those who fought in it. It’s about… https://t.co/87Jpl5SgnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNDERCOVER: Late-Term Abortion Clinics Exposed! https://t.co/DxDGlZM7WO via @YouTube GOD HELP US!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamie_Foxworthy @PalmerReport McConnell must be counting on the Russians to keep their agent IQ45, him, and his co… https://t.co/uOvFIeYC1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m thinking my mom needs this!2019 New Double Layer Cat Litter Mat - Silver Ion Antimicrobial Protection https://t.co/5Fskhp1eIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m that gf that will pay half on everything.. you bought breakfast? I’ll buy lunch. We both have jobs, we both can pay for things...]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; obviously siblings don't have to look alike but he was just trying to be funny and it wasn't. Go do your job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Às vezes a única razão da nossa tristeza é tambem a única da nossa felicidade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😭😭❤️❤️- Kitbull | Pixar SparkShorts https://t.co/GU0gOiCFF1 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never measure the height of a mountain until you reach the top. Then you will see how low it was. https://t.co/csTBGivXke]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm hoping so its written to pray for Asia and I do think it's a big part of our peacemakers responsibility to do s… https://t.co/SIIQQAqzr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colorstarboy ok. I  will ask my project manager Mr.Shankar Masilamani to contact you via whatsapp to discuss your… https://t.co/QmNM6NbfKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fav thing is when ya friends don’t invite ya places and exclude ya from things &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stewpotfan @KimKawata @dinogcole @mcclellandglass @CalimityF @Sharksbait5300 @62Greenmachine My thinking!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st Ellary, Hope you have an amazing day. Come see me soon. Thank you for being you.💗💗 https://t.co/rONBD1BHYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SirHenryofColchester enjoys the finer things in life: walks, sniffs, snacks, and naps 🐶 Mostly naps 😴💖… https://t.co/5Gqtfp8AYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came with 300+ of my closest friends in the Olmsted Falls Marching Band to Universal Studios to perform in a para… https://t.co/l5Jyl3Vh0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelEveStein Aw. Framing seems not great. Why not commit to try to work with the city to extract as much afforda… https://t.co/D661o1umY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesAALongman @GGthinking @ABCWorldNews Sorry you can stay in refugee camp once a TERRORIST always a TERRORIST 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[TEXAS SOUTHERN UNIVERSITY IS AN FANTASTIC UNIVERSITY but is has it problems like any other universities But shall o… https://t.co/DNW0XTjr8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenMJeff @ChatByCC The last I checked, Trump's support was decreasing. And after Mueller's legal docs are rele… https://t.co/WMOCMQG5Uj]]></document></documents></author>