<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[AZ Atheist Lawmaker Gives Invocation, Then Gets Mocked by Christian Colleague. https://t.co/cJvO1YJQ2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch out for the Sacramento Kings even tho they lost they still solid team for future]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HervGOTTI Lmfao like FOH 😂 of course im still going to eat it 🤷🏽‍♀️ https://t.co/6icSk8MYsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tony_Rotundo @espn @trfoley Minor details. We all love the India wrestling site. I’m all for investing in it. More… https://t.co/WheWPzADZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaeveReston you call yourself a journalist..your fawning over kamala lala shopping has shown the world your bias!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__x1r Thanks it took a little getting used to the ortholinear for typing but after a few hours it feels natural. A… https://t.co/OXurNmGJev]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKInfinity_VVS @steveaustinBSR @SCOTTHALLNWO @FightOwensFight @DickTubs Man if i could see @steveaustinBSR… https://t.co/3c9OdpAQID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey it’s 2:40 am and I’m still pissed about how some idiot got our server transfer function taken away at work. This is a very niche tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anuaryeme @Tonyar27 @carlosyeme Traer a zidane sin Cristiano es como si los Bulls hubieran llevado a Phil Jackson… https://t.co/3oHeXTRNSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicStafford_ @KingJames @carmeloanthony 😆😆😆 you’ve never seen melo not rotate or make slow rotations screwing up t… https://t.co/M6ry0HxIeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three will be inducted into the Little 500 Hall of Fame   ➡️ https://t.co/lt6oRsrAfU https://t.co/oPVCjUpa3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alcoholic me just finished an entire bottle of wine. By myself. In my room. Alone 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shot and edited today. I can’t get over these! 💥🙏🏼 https://t.co/LUlzaZLv57]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Princess_BianK @Gamavisionecu Gracias. Viendo Ecuavisa ahora .. un abrazo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some new Nip and old skool Luda for this AM 💪🏾 workout https://t.co/I51iJU80NK]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Europe and other parts of the world speak several languages and that’s celebrated. In the U.S., people scream “s… https://t.co/92IEiqwf1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Jim_Jordan didn't seem worried about the rules when he was lying to coverup for his friend for sexually assaultin… https://t.co/0LwOnsKvU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Sally Ride nameplate for #uswnt. That is brilliance. What an idea tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wrekonize @ITSBERNZ @NonMS305 Between South and This gotta say great job. One more question that show in Philly ne… https://t.co/1QsPYqLhtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Texas Blonde by @wildacrebrewing at @bigfishgvine — https://t.co/fPJAHOnqeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite moments from last night.  We prayed together over all of Greater Nashville.  Unprecedented reviv… https://t.co/ihCJruB5Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GbengaGOLD @AdeBanqie @OUKtweets This is a great result when you consider Buhari got 13,394 in the whole of Abia in 2015]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨Parents, today is the mid-point of Quarter 3. You may want to check your students’ grades on PowerSchool.  Parent… https://t.co/5LG3TAffAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DKPghSports @penguins @Dejan_Kovacevic @mattsunday @PghBradford @HunterAHomistek @Kennedy4848]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maximizing your fitness doesn’t only come down to what type of exercises your workout program consists of but also… https://t.co/nFzlMTCKwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five points by @BaroniJayden gives @_Hawk_Hoops 11-2 lead on @SonoraHigh . @LodiSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is my sincere hope, that each of you, takes one step toward your dream today. 💯 https://t.co/vm6O15W4F8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, this is awful. My sympathy to his family, friends, colleagues and bandmates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took him to watch “How To Train Your Dragon The Hidden World” https://t.co/O6zJXlCZKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gianluxx18 @BlackYellow I didn't make it🤣.  It is his fault he went to our little sister team and couldn't win a CL 🤷‍♂️.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Melaleuca @lawrencewasden @FLVanderSloot @WellsFargo @AdvancingWithUs @DeptVetAffairs @FTC @SEC_Enforcement In an… https://t.co/qLFUqCoefk]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/x30dLQb5kf   770-361-7864  anxiety_free@att.net  #stressfree #stressmanagement #stress #anxiety… https://t.co/YUKNFpG8aD]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Miss If I | fatherfuneral 🔥🔥🔥song is fire #dancer #editing #ididitall #animation #trash #ihadfun #latenight… https://t.co/TNi0jaAvls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mickakers They did a @LevisStadium for the first two seasons and cancelled the service after that who knows why]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIVE NOW: @paschutz interviews @ToniPreckwinkle about her progressive vision for Chicago on @WTTW's #ChicagoTonight… https://t.co/4GiJe9cHcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my opinion, this is a top 5 in game dunk. @HenryJWilliams @mrpaulperry]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @tristencitrine: “you have to come see this? You won’t believe this unless you see it.” *walks over* Me: “How the… https://t.co/Avls4YWeUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karen_surman Heartbreaking for Botcher. Almost curled perfect game and still lost.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is not against immigration. He simply wants what we all want and that is to control immigration, keep our fam… https://t.co/13zedFKmR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[These white girls in la stay dressing  Like they got an indoor outdoor ball  In their tote bag  Shorties come throu… https://t.co/RysBDECAY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish dey would rob my track I would rob dey whole family. Don’t even play with me like dat haaa 😂😂 day kno]]></document><document><![CDATA[If those fans had half a brain they’d know that was a great charge call]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goals for this year🙏🏼 Learn to play guitar🤘🏼, master jujitsu💪🏼, go to therapy🧠, learn how to swim🏊🏼‍♂️, and get a new dishwasher🤤 - uwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Centerpiece at dinner tonight...just sayin... #florists @ Macon Marriott City Center https://t.co/pps467F7e0]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXTENDED!!!!! While you are out planning your appointments consider one of the most affordable tax rates communitie… https://t.co/RPiA2zyGPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBA All-Star break was a wake up call that the big dogs weren't coming to the Lakers. They proceeded to tank, convince me otherwise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone. Don't wait for something to happen make something happen! Work on a goal, a project, or your dreams!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Agreed.  How the heck can Mueller’s investigation be complete?  Is this Barr effectively firing Mueller wi… https://t.co/gkZAIc2Em6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#btsedits Behind the scenes #video shot by @odalager_j.  Setting up shot and rehearsing our Bellevue scene from "AS… https://t.co/6Uh74YNJw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taemloops HARPER'S BA-ZAA-R A-Lways A need for TWO Americas: ONE inside And ONE OUTSIDE Why Consulates And Embassy… https://t.co/XJGkVqxmi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The president’s sons entrusted their private hunting retreat to a caretaker. He was working in the country illegall… https://t.co/Fb8tWybqBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelivhaynes We're gonna give you a viking funeral, Liv. God willing, in about 80 or more years. But, still...(...… https://t.co/SX58Wvhlxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate waking up middle of the night tired as hell but can’t go back to sleep.... this literally on happens when I’m off the best day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennis_p @Teslatunity @Tesla @teslaownersSV Big time downer. Talked to a guy 3(?) weeks ago at SC and he said his… https://t.co/EUsBg4hk12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelaveryy @MiLB @AviatorsLV @sportslogosnet @LasVegasLocally @RJ_Sports @DICKS It could be worth $100 some day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mantia Crazy idea here: maybe they should’ve figured this out before posting those half-assed mockups.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a good run, with a nice comeback after a slow start. Sad to see the end of an era— and what could be the las… https://t.co/rgRImplAD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if @VinceMcMahon fired that guy in the truck for letting the F word go during Champion by Chipmunk and Chris Brown]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's never been an actor more ready to main event WrestleMania than Jason Momoa. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[TFW you see @chrisdepizzo is STILL talking about how he ONLY lost 22%. https://t.co/c9CdAosqlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bendevall9 @mjcoelho480 Yea they really did give Louisville the shaft here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Royvin Get ready to drop another $10.99/month for the Disney streaming service. I hope they bring back Luke Cage as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very cool find! Thank you #picozzi for this awesome box set! Can’t wait to bust this open later! #1029thewhale… https://t.co/uvehugqW1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevilleRay @SamsungMobileUS Service for T-Mobile 👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👊👊👊👊👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👊👎👊👎👎👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Seajay603 @kneadinghands @Observer2541 @Mel_the_geek @Elinor27652146 @deelane @YeshuaLover1970 @TheFinalDuke… https://t.co/wpY8S9WHao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennkirschner2 ALL lawbreakers must be held responsible. https://t.co/aqS1jN0YoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s day! Here’s a feel good story that’ll be sure to make you smile 🐶 ...and check out the byline 😎  https://t.co/vRtMlAI1R5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeDan1024 @RaychelTania @EamesJared @rstefens @AOC Go away. Maybe find a new hobby. What you're doing...it's bad.… https://t.co/QJJlEF3qjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[young Silicon Valley employees are some of the most destructive American workers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bettyjoanblack2 @gemshoppinglive It’s The Opal Hunter tonight. Guaranteed fum]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch me tomorrow on the Bearkat Sports Network YouTube with @G_Myers33 on the call for a love stream of… https://t.co/8kIBZKpoXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Waymo “has been seeking #financing from outside #investors, such as European automakers like @VW…the efforts sugg… https://t.co/XsRgCNP1sJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deut 8:17-18 17. And thou say in thine heart, My power and the might of mine hand hath gotten me this wealth. 18. B… https://t.co/G80OA4Aquz]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 of the more productive WR prospects in the country is Parker Washington 5‘11“ 190 Richmond Travis HS. Good hands-… https://t.co/5I8qhG0IuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3coltshandicap @GoldenKnight89 @GGFracing Btw Matt, I hit the pk5 which paid $109.45!]]></document><document><![CDATA[God been answering a lot of my prayers lately Beat the odds and remain humbled 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlyWood7 i absolutely write the script first, though the most important part of script-writing is outlining. i… https://t.co/ysLq8qdy5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know we’ve got a great beer and soccer culture in the Lou, but this (pic in comments) sure seemed like a “natural… https://t.co/9zA33TUja2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking back my space. Just have 2 more band posters to frame and hang. @ Lansing, Michigan https://t.co/Wf5th1dFQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the great things about having @SIRIUSXM in my truck is being able to hear college broadcasts from around the… https://t.co/GjnjuT30jt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redidbull @AndreaWBZ True. The lowest i can remember is 27.9 cents a gallon. I lived in New Rochelle NY back then.… https://t.co/nD4U4BcEEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, @chrislhayes, is there a formula for skipping Thing 1 and Thing 2, or is it just when you feel like disappointing me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow this reminds me of Scalia's mysterious death just before obozo was about to leave office. Wonder why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Infanticide the final solution by the left would be a twinkle in Adolfs eye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomStoup @gregmparks Then they build a new stadium to start the 2012 season and sign a whole bunch of talent in th… https://t.co/mw9eqIk4Rr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I recently learned about the @BeMyEyes application. This is incredible. Check it out :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venezuelan crab meat, anyone? 😋🦀  #SamRustSeafood #VenezuelanCrabMeat #ChefTalk #ChefLife #Seafood @ Sam Rust Seafo… https://t.co/xcc1OoTdjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[These guys do a great job with fitting and club reviews https://t.co/hDWGagtGc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes the best reporters are local but they bring in CBS, NBC, ABC, and etc. For national!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ @AOC If you think Elizabeth Warren is Native American than I got some Ocean Front Property to sell you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patdrinks Many Disney restaurants require a credit card to make the reservation strictly for this purpose. But tha… https://t.co/U4FV6py4RZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a very dope thought but honestly i stole a good portion of it from  @DaniellaLira_  I]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Trump still cannot handle a comedic sketch... Furthers the notation that he is completely #unfit for anything.… https://t.co/QXPMt8yIh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[That should've been a major on Shaw... cross checked Harrington in the face #CBJ Shaw's garbage 🚮🚮🚮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @ChatByCC @AOC She may not realize it but we’re all gonna die, I’m ready, ARE YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love and relationships come in all different shapes and sizes and all of them deserve to be celebrated. However you… https://t.co/YTZDhQUFRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report: Some within organization believe Anthony Davis has played last game for Pelicans https://t.co/uXYaMYbt58]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drpatfarrell “Michael, there’s no business in Russia, there’s no business in Russia.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Trump_Train McCabe is a sad little bureaucrat that has a messianic complex and made a conscious decision to pu… https://t.co/O4mV4x9lxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast is the most important meal of the day. What did you eat? https://t.co/6gFr7ZXslM]]></document></documents></author>