<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Don't you fucking dare pull that anti semetism bullshit on me. It's not anti semetic to point out that Bernie admit… https://t.co/rWoGEHGrE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow blocked on instagram by CR stylist okay — TERRIBLE looking shoot https://t.co/v9THmYot05]]></document><document><![CDATA[It don’t matter what city I’m in, I’m smoking the best flavors and that’s facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Shantel_Ro Me! There's a difference between spanking and beating. I had my fair share of spankings growing up. I… https://t.co/Z13hhPASrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone see how Lebron only cares about himself? He’ll still always be #3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Team_Penske @smclaughlin93 @FabianCoulthard @DJRTeamPenske @adelaide500 Looks like you guys got the mustang right on all fronts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilNobileJr @RachelTrue Rachel true is beautiful and my favorite member of the craft.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Whitneyhouston &amp; #LelaRochon in #WaitingToExhale ❤👅 https://t.co/nb1CV4a8sE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my new skateboard art by @evil_rob (IG) He showcased some of my favorite characters like Spider-Man, the Gre… https://t.co/nLllxqLKif]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter Sandman, done in a bluegrass style. It really is very good (and I don’t care much for bluegrass) https://t.co/qeld9vQwQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lastly, and probably most importantly, McCollum said that out of everyone on the NW Men’s media team, he thought I… https://t.co/zleLNMZxnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Improving mental performance and attending to mental health concerns are both needed in the lives of athletes today… https://t.co/eCgw8fjuFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleBrandt I am willing to be a kidney donation if I can please let the player know who's story I saw on ESPN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alivitali @Hickenlooper LOL - Hick said he wanted to have a beer with McConnell]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all think I’m gonna be successful, wait til you see what my brother is about to accomplish #justwaitonit]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know D heard me say “ow i cant wait to take this shower” when we we’re in the car for him to bring his ugly ass i… https://t.co/n3AXgMTLnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“No one has the right to waste a day in the life of a child.”   -Unknown Principal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbauerAP @wispolitics @SpeakerVos @GovEvers @wispolitics1 I suggest that a political reporter ask Vos if he not on… https://t.co/i3oL9jsNzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neurons ready to fire for #sculpture class crit session yesterday with mattboonstra . Tentative title: "reality is… https://t.co/btNsY4uMkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t be more happy for this kid.  We watch him daily work HARD on his game and it’s awesome to watch it pay off… https://t.co/ptkenuySLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes Sarcasm or irony or whatever it is is definitely not one of your strong points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why don’t most NYC retail buildings install a plexiglass covering on many of their exterior windows?  A simple larg… https://t.co/Wn8OuG5e8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t know who @MichaelCohen212 is, then what rock do you live under. He is a GOAT. Thanks for releasing what we knew what true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBRacingStable I figured since ya wasn't in the winners circle , you had to be at home . If I were you I would get… https://t.co/OL4qlKGOo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smi5504 @NitwitTV @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump They don’t bring crime. That’s the whole point. Native born Amer… https://t.co/pYSwQ1qQ96]]></document><document><![CDATA[‼️also wanna follow this up with I know now that nicki minaj is a part of the GROUP young money IM SORRY‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martanchristian @MoorheadOrch @spudspeech Just trying to figure out how you forgot a 3’ x 4’ carrying case and easel?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShonHarris9 @dmataconis @dana_deree @JimKaten @smerconish @CNN Then why did this bust happen in Florida and not Ne… https://t.co/n4gNK8pWrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kahneman on “availability cascades” and “availability entrepreneurs” - Beware: https://t.co/ZVxKH1AySc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilia_suze Losers have a tendency if finding each other's causes.These three are huge visibility problems for the… https://t.co/m01L1WzlGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natebuckwell @sevenaces11 Did Chucky Wucky and Nancy Wancy go to Tijuana to advise the mayor on the invasion? Does Chucky have a pet ducky?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Ba'al by @newanthembeer at @wesley137 — https://t.co/K4mTPx7Dg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished day 358 of the @YouVersion plan 'Bible In One Year'. Check it out here: https://t.co/QTKC3gyZVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidrlurie @DavidCornDC losing his senate seat is the least of his worries IMO humiliation and prison are more likely the immediate worry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fire vs Crew. #CCC19 @ChicagoFire @Chas_Battery https://t.co/AHVYxr9dD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling you get when the cars and clouds part and you get the parkerpalmsprings entry to yourself! . .… https://t.co/lFrc3jUoGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Tuesday! Currently, its 19° under Partly Cloudy skies.  Sunrise: 6:40am, Sunrise: 5:28pm.  "Do not love the w… https://t.co/OSFrY2f0yT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @FoxNews  Really? Even @Jim_Jordan and then @PamBondi ? When you ask your guests a question, shut th… https://t.co/t871e5Gf1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world today has become one of entitlement. We have lost the art of being grateful and appreciative!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madflavor Great set tonight Uncle Joey! They didn't know who they were dealing with! Thanks for the laughs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piovoso_1025 Winter time forces people inside and seeking comfort and for people without a significant other they… https://t.co/l0TkBkrtHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The strongest people tend to smile even during their toughest times. Smiling is a psychological symbol of strength. Keep Smiling :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I prefer March basketball to March soccer! @ Basking Ridge, New Jersey https://t.co/2TxhiRpByw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be with someone who’s constantly just going to put you down and make you feel like shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PowerFuck I invented pineapple pesto pizza, you should try that shit yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[AI Interprets What Rodents are Saying | Psychology Today https://t.co/aIZCpGffe5 #DeepSqueek #AI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamWriting_ What was he doing!? Lol I don’t have empathy for stupidity😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the song SuperWall it says nock it off!! Your best friend Oasis https://t.co/jP2T2PyerP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HardyOHara @KCKennedy93 Agreed, and the 10C always seems to struggle a little at Northern C.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@konjak Silly question. Can you create a folder on C:\ first and then save to it? Are you trying to save to an existing path?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatZingano @ufc I've gone twice in 13 days, they didn't give me anything 🤣😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidESmithJr2 @SenatorDurbin You apparently don’t realize that Constitutionally there are some powers that Congre… https://t.co/HWFxbpKN6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who gonn meet me out in the quarters and drunk ride a bike w me 👀😂😂 i got the drinkss 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Possibly our only defense against icy @ottawacity sidewalks. #imgonnaneedabiggerpocket @ Ottawa, Ontario https://t.co/DNPmtTliHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t decide which is more of a perfect example how dumb @sxsw has become, hosting Billy McFarland - Fyre Festiva… https://t.co/kqRxSTBGUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NC5 " Don't want to Go into Why The Ladies Don't Like Me "....!!!! https://t.co/CmCTSpzYKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found, Trevor's long lost sister. #trevorlawrence #thenorthstarsf #separatedatbirth #sanfrancisco #clemsontigers… https://t.co/WCiNhTHilM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure, more investigations into crimes that did not happen, spending millions of taxpayer dollars to find NOTHING!]]></document><document><![CDATA[just watched a vid of a woman who dives w sharks and after she took a fishing hook out of ones mouth, a bunch of ot… https://t.co/jUoA7i1JaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very nice! - Drinking a LOUD! Hazy DIPA by @AlmanacBeer @ The Bat Cave  — https://t.co/2AiafTmfqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Per CIF, the recommended minimum seating gym for Open Regional final is listed between 1,800-2,000. Clovis West’s g… https://t.co/bwlOh4TAIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEnigmaMachi1 @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Yes. It’s appalling. It’s like these people are proud to be criminals… https://t.co/bNNIsb4cAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched a scene from Dinner with Schmucks live.  Trump’s “special relationship” with North Korea’s murderous t… https://t.co/FhB8JYAMIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Louisking_29 thanks for finding and following me sir I am going to follow you too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/TIWGv6VCDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cioppino at the oldest restaurant in San Francisco. 😋 https://t.co/u9wUdNRFTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllyLuna99 @RayadoenDiDi @OOHMyGOS Si pero en realidad que técnico es mejor Alonso o Mojamed ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pixelpreaching He basically made "The Green Berets" because wanted to show support for the war in Vietnam and thou… https://t.co/xVRcslaSro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out with this guy. @ Greensboro, North Carolina https://t.co/vnVBycTj38]]></document><document><![CDATA[@srmanuq Para mi hasta verde algo se podra hacer, un zapallito en almibar capaz? @rosbergmartin algún pedacito de s… https://t.co/a7o6uwRtyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWERollins Should have any merchandise to promote the #OneLastTime reunion of #TheShield.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bornabrit1 @ellievan65 Putin ;prince of Saudi ; Un ;@realDonaldTrump believes them all over our own CIA , FBI, Sec… https://t.co/W8UzPF7h5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defamation of character you can be slapped with for false accusations.  Boom Moron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giannis won the popular vote. #NotMyMVP  Trump could build his wall with all bricks Curry and Westbrook put up in t… https://t.co/JzNgcdUzvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Explaining Harry Potter to our Creative Director and he goes ‘Wait is this real history?’ 😂😂😂 he genuinely thought it was real and I love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 18/84 of the Cut The CRAP Challenge!!  Carbonated Beverages  Refined Sugars Artificial Anything Processed Foods… https://t.co/sJcZM4ApY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Machado loves Miami. Difference here is that all his friends and family probably didn’t ask when he was going to be… https://t.co/VKWhXnumoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wife tried it on me last week. Very hard to make it look graceful..]]></document><document><![CDATA[You've got to know when to hold 'em Know when to fold 'em Know when to walk away And know when to run You never eat… https://t.co/LtzXFsgXWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@El_Universal_Mx Felicidades al gobernador independiente de nuevo León....don @JaimeRdzNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sillykid9iclou1 @QAnon_Report Right, the 80% of American Jews who vote Democratic are too naive to understand thei… https://t.co/rOlpV96t2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpsperspective I would love that but nothing from our past 5 years says that's possible. They weren't joking?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leftists want to do away with Capitalism. They don't care that when  Socialism and confiscatory taxes arrive, the w… https://t.co/2ZvQ4fpzpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heARTISTatWORK @valerietilton @cvarsalona @thewrightleader @ValentinaESL @VNixon1988 @drlizavarvogli @heffrey… https://t.co/2OvyISGVK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CincinnatiPhil I 100 percent believe this. I've had multiple similar experiences.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha that would low key be a small 10 min break for me when I worked at ihop😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @krassenstein fighting with his brother over Donnie America https://t.co/yNb1qfUn25]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matthew 13:35:  [35] That it might be fulfilled which was spoken by the prophet, saying, I will open my mouth in pa… https://t.co/ZcJS4H67am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olgaNYC1211 The key figure in funneling money from Russia through the NRA to all Republicans in Congress - A giant… https://t.co/qc68OvqR1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[442.450MHz https://t.co/zPl92Udizi DMR TAC310 (@ CHKD Health Center at Oakbrooke in Chesapeake, VA) https://t.co/JRdiYivuoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zigmanfreud @johncardillo More irony. Smollett hires The same attorney that represents Michael Cohen. Michael Cohe… https://t.co/dxaSNqHCd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fleshandbrand @saknussemmocean He “Tirelessly” campaigned for? What planet do you live on? his supporters did noth… https://t.co/dy4dKv8LT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WAxelFoley People walk into my library playing music off their phone all the time, or talking on speaker phone, and it’s not just kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[- Thank you guys again; dj_seinfeld , @ypset  @kindasuperdisco , @thedivehtx - It’s Swedish. 48x36 Acrylic, pencil,… https://t.co/EQgcd8t2Ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlibonne @Melanch10844904 May I have your attention, please? Will the real Hillary please stand up? I repeat, wi… https://t.co/BZjlg1tcuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaileHolly @realDonaldTrump So you voted for a person who has demonstrated throughout his entire life that he only… https://t.co/7cOPcnMtT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776Stonewall The Democrats may have something there when it comes to their voters...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rockets getting healthy at the right time. We need @imanshumpert @KennethFaried35 to be healthy and may need to res… https://t.co/g8rPHjlILE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bryce Harper arriving in Clearwater. Will be re-evaluated in 6-8 weeks https://t.co/jQrtIuPnxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I root against any school that hires a coach away from another school where he was HC for just one year]]></document></documents></author>