<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Abdomac1 @AnnaCAAlves17 @SarahJazz17 @jill_magnussen Very thoughtful of you...  for a friend armchair, flower, sta… https://t.co/CyvcZNOGUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ummmm what??? This guy is new and I have no idea where he came from @TeraBriteGames https://t.co/4uemo3goo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mleitten @ej315 @CharlesEsten @B_Libby @BethLHancock24 @amygeurden @algallo5 @Allyallpgh @KeepinItChereal @Beils33… https://t.co/1s4JG9GPo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beverlyfelix3 @jlshine5 @DorisZelaya5 @RevLDReed @elliesangelwing @JOEYKNOWSTOO @JUBILEE_7DOUBLE @endtimeslife… https://t.co/6LpuuVNwKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[A St. George Police Department lieutenant and another man have been arrested in an undercover human trafficking inv… https://t.co/dhQjh3qdnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 10pm and the roomba at the airbnb we’re staying at just smashed into our bedroom door and I almost died right… https://t.co/tTdxmiGUJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so tired from work that I can’t even get motivation to walk into my house]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beer Me! 🍻 #Denver #CoorsTour #travel #DestinationWedding #BeerMe https://t.co/dFfqzaH3cU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call your representatives and urge them to vote yes on #HR1112 ! Close the Charleston Loophole! @MomsDemand]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve never been to the midwest in my life but i say “ope” like 6 thousand times a day for literally every single th… https://t.co/3i4gTfUzsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DellaMendenhall @GillespiesPearl @gillespiefloris I think it’ll work for Lil Dot too. She’s bigger around than she… https://t.co/Xv2jJ1QU5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump cares about Trump.  He gave the tax cut to his wealthy friends so that they would spend more money at his bus… https://t.co/VESb4lEtRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @sarahkliff, are there any urgent care billing projects  where I can submit this fun new bill I received?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s your favorite #country song of the moment?   #countrymusic #favorites]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish you well and we will hold you to that contract!! Fuck cancer!! 😒 It took my mother! 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good afternoon to all God’s Twitters spreading The Word https://t.co/y2lCA3ckxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m too cheap to be in a sorority I don’t want to spend money on dumb things like a sticker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kenny Goins finishes with 24. Matt McQuaid puts up 22. Aaron Henry adds 15. MSU tops Nebraska 91-76 to improve to 15-4 in the Big Ten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was a few weeks ago, but we saw our little friends do the same thing today!!  So precious!! 🤗🤗😍😍🦆🦆🦆   We LOVE… https://t.co/waXYWJytc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t wanna miss today in Canton Ohio at 10!! 🙌 @FaithFamilyOH or streamed live online. 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yes he is building the wall he keeps his promises all of them not like other presidents before him like Obama buzz off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepStevenSmith This is crazy... Comey is rotten to the core. I'm glad he has a nice bank account, he'll need it wh… https://t.co/RBjX4Mpfc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 4:30 AM Me to Uber driver: I didn’t sleep well last night. Uber Driver: Neither did I Me: https://t.co/zWqm7ROf99]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RbrtL1981 That sounds like something right up mine and my sister’s alley! :) Have fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol i fell back to sleep now i’m gonna be late to my math class oh well]]></document><document><![CDATA[where ever my future boyfriend at, i just want him to know he’s lucky 🥵 https://t.co/dSFlz2BmOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ethan and Burton having way too much fun doing an intro to #BLAZINGSADDLES @ Alamo Drafthouse San Antonio https://t.co/pQZ35X3I78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another thing I have learned: Given the lower income rental options for seniors (which are still pretty nice places… https://t.co/pYGesZOgzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @tolag Did you think that up while playing virtual golf? Boy that executive time is productive!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Brexit was the practice run for stealing the 2016 election in the US. I remember watching in horror as it unfolded… https://t.co/45Whnr6ZcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔷🔸CASTING CALL🔸🔷 Send your Resume, Headshot and 1-2 min Video Monologue to freedperformingarts@gmail.com… https://t.co/1L9XIWhDfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanilsonNE A @PMERJ estava lá é deu fim nos arruaceiros. Não iria em carnaval na rua do Brasil,hoje em dia não dá.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So nice to finally meet you in person @CorrineRahman !  Thank you for being so involved.  ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump @VP @SenMajLdr the NATIONAL EMERGENCY is you 3 leading our country down the toilet...… https://t.co/5fJAh1A8b2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a little bit of anxiety realizing I’ll be in my forties once Bryce Harper’s new contract is up. #Phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Marissa  I was born in a new place  My age is still a little bit more than I thought it was I like to th… https://t.co/EjthCx9eIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can @BernieSanders stop using that one photo of himself getting arrested fifty million years ago and go get arrested for POC *today*??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waylon is our Kindness Kid this week! He’s helpful, a good friend and uses kind words with others. What a great exa… https://t.co/mHabGsVpkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMQuotes_Videos That would NOT.....  BE A LIBERAL.... JUST SAYING.... 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dairy Free Cinnamon Rolls Check out this awesome post just shared from @MakeItDairyFree https://t.co/Z4gB8GBU9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t let who you are detract from who I am going to be. @msrachelhollis #SXSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Saturday Lady Drive Nation Louisiana will be hosting “6th Grade Only” workouts/tryouts @ East Ascension High S… https://t.co/GvgkXAZAeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can this guy say it any plainer. Hungarian F Minister is saying back off bitch we will run our Country the way we w… https://t.co/Lc9SnQh8Fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn it... now I gotta throw my Vans tomorrow at work to see if Twitter is right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prepare yourselves this thread is gonna be amazing https://t.co/VHavZra2Fd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxvol @SwainEvent @benmckee14 @neylandmafia @volstorm00 This is the best thing I have seen all day!! I freaking love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FHS_Swim_Dive 200 Medley Relay finishes in 13th place. #keeprollin’ 🏊‍♂️💙💦 https://t.co/1HFv2dH99I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta say I have the best Valentine 🤷🏼‍♀️🥰 lol says the girl who just bashed it 😂 #ValentineDay https://t.co/PJi22wT3Ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noxime @PatrickDenis20 @ethier_frank @coucou2225 @OBaillargeon Je suis de la Rive-Nord mais je peux me déplacer !]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m being honest, this why we friends lol OH AND we think alike a lot and it’s just funny hehe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have man respect for everyone still in school. This adulting shit ain’t easy. You keep going and you do that shit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re looking for some entertainment this weekend watch @phhaas @AubreyPeacock @SwimJules @jkhowen stories beca… https://t.co/5bLjIlSroa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just can’t get over the cuteness.. omg omg omg https://t.co/oOuUUnixWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the owner of my favorite #ShelterIsland eatery!  https://t.co/upfRVluqQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes @SethAbramson Cohen's written testimony here https://t.co/cELgkc9EdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[every day’s just another flight, every flight’s almost over @andrewmcmahon #islandradio @ Newport Music Hall https://t.co/6iDNXcETg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me how someone just called me and said that I’m the only person they know good at acting so he asked me to cal… https://t.co/sgXSly4jH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL I agree! I lost my sweet sweet Bailey to Lymphoma last week and it has crushed my soul. I don’t kn… https://t.co/CFcgXQAg7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyShowLive Omg THANKS!👏What a blast to wake up and see! https://t.co/0atZZTFKoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a flipping disgrace you are 🤔you should have called for the president’s resignation after all his racist bulls… https://t.co/dZDcuBWmJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[having genuine people who only want the best for you in your corner &gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did this in my office like it was a movie theater. I saw it coming and said “oh no don’t do it” out loud right as he went in to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A convicted perjurer's hearing is scheduled same day as @POTUS historic meeting with North Korea! Coincidence? I th… https://t.co/FhdIUxtYch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So tell me Toxic 45, what exactly have you done ??? Because all you did the last time was waste th… https://t.co/xTlbfnp3VM]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re lucky to have places like @tavolodotave so close to us. Amazing food, warm and wonderful staff 💕 @ Tavolo Ris… https://t.co/0vmqsYJE2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a helpful thread reminding us all what intersectionality actually means. Thanks @kat_blaque !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boyvirgoo @bluemotelroom @RealRicardoDiaz No.... people were going against her saying she was a SELF-MADE billionaire.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport Its amazing how disgusting these guys are willing to be for their Trump votes!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This could've been her "Be Without You" moment.  Like how #MJB did it with the Breakthrough album. ♥  But I agree t… https://t.co/yfolOWs525]]></document><document><![CDATA[#protectivestyles #naturalhairgoals #naturalhairjunkie #naturallyshedope #hair #updo #twostrandtwist #braids… https://t.co/Jrogew2vQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoveTheWorldUS Bite their arm, not the stick that keeps poking you, the arm holding the stick!😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[emotional maturity is getting halfway through a book and accepting that you’re not going to finish it because you r… https://t.co/eY7dO4uyrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDjArtist @OfficialSP7 @Vickypham52 @DogMomUSA @NatStrawn @ElyseWillems @_rufhaus @TheSamiJoShow @loholmes963 Th… https://t.co/T9unIcWbdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[she’s playing the same venue for her first headlining show in sf i’m crying]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at MTA Subway - Sutphin Blvd/Archer Ave/JFK (E/J/Z) - @nyctsubway in Jamaica, NY https://t.co/RIVuznwaLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@la_patilla Usted no tiene la mas minima idea de lo que en Venezuela pasa!!! Se acuerda de las torturas en la epoca de Pinochet???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebStrickland65 @StricklandJess @VincentRule @Type1Liz @shuds16 This is good, right? Lol https://t.co/0Ipn7okpzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trust and believe #40daysofstrength Day 37 ✅ #yogaeverydamnday #lovelife #yoga #yogi #loveoneanother #yogaworks… https://t.co/W6YdkLEpF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KarineGiboulo: la part d'ombre de la barbe à papa https://t.co/C3ThbEHRQI via @lp_lapresse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClonyDungyXL1 We finally have a fairly healthy team ...now to get a good D- line and we should be OK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out the new @earthfare today and saw someone else wearing a lillebaby from behind. Surprise, surprise it w… https://t.co/0IZ73XBmRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the mountains to the beach all in one afternoon. Great family day.  . Did you know hiking, is a great choice o… https://t.co/YEixP4xHjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dltav @DemFromCT @chucktodd The show is a disaster now thanks to Todd. Really sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tjlevi32766 Good Morning Happy Tuesday Hope you have a fabulous day 😊😀😁😆🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh dear Sarcasm.... #mommiediaries #lovemykids #lovemyfamily   #Repost @auntyaciduk (get_repost) ・・・ #auntyacid… https://t.co/QxE1p5m4Zu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just discovered that @YogurtPark has a twitter announcing the daily flavors. About to be spending a lot more time in Berkeley... #yopo]]></document><document><![CDATA[my skin is so gross right now and I didn’t pack any of my skincare stuff🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are you doing on Valentine’s Day eve? Me? Oh I just took the single most uncomfortable freaking bra off and th… https://t.co/i7ajL4Y39Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is in the air! Get ready for spring at gallery andrea! #luxuryhomes #scottsdaleartgalleries #interiordesign… https://t.co/g7visQivvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Turtleturtleptv happy birthday yay were 21 💕❤️ we can go out and drink 🍸🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[5:00 left in the 1st quarter 16-14 for @raptors905 @ Raptors905 https://t.co/oPR8wVMbzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Period because the law system is getting out of control and it’s crazy that we don’t have to just look out for thos… https://t.co/cTX2obCFyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMFlint And such a successful vehicle for enacting legislation. Who can forget his naming of post offices? Or his… https://t.co/hINlSUKZfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LFHSHoops @DannyARam22 @Rickyaltamiran8 @jordankurbina @GerryMa08308545 @c4r103 @proudgdad @alarconbert1120… https://t.co/LFYkiFiczc]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @shanedawson here’s some answers from people that used to work there, nobody knows!!! https://t.co/sPI1RGVANL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This coming from the guy, that had no elected PWR, demanded and harassed the Barack Obama incessan… https://t.co/hWsmBSF1VY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby Love. #nailsbytashalynn #nailsbyamericans #youshouldbehere #polishroomfl #orlando #downtownorlando #sodo… https://t.co/thAFpVVvbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Evelyn for such a fun photo shoot #dancefriendsarethebestfriends #petitedancers @ Veterans Park https://t.co/8LoXetX8Mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh! We should’ve been there cheering! But been in traffic since 4am!! We are coming for you @PhilMickelson - we do… https://t.co/LCfEaAtRul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchfromOhio @SunBrigadeSC I think we played like crap for the most part (lots of chuckling and groaning amongst… https://t.co/ggK4AahwKJ]]></document></documents></author>