<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[As I continue to grow myself, my brand, my dream, know I appreciate every single person who's been part of my journ… https://t.co/M0DGwapTdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s so many famous people in Austin rn that makes me actually want to go out. But at the same time there’s just… https://t.co/IxokHelIzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only dude I need in my life this Valentine’s Day ❤️ #puppylove #nash #adoptdontshop https://t.co/Ei1nBTIM2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hiddenvllyrach Lmfao I guess there’s probably a legit reason why they aren’t but then I’m like what girl doesn’t l… https://t.co/wOlzvweSuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My starbucks app works perfectly every day until the morning im running late]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will go to the self-checkout lane even if the line is longer.  Probably says something about me on a different le… https://t.co/CAXnaXCXMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is not past, no future; everything flows in an eternal present. - James Joyce . . Life is all about determi… https://t.co/fWQiXolD3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillieGeist @JennaBushHager @KathieLGifford @hodakotb @TODAYshow 👏👏👏 I will start watching now! ❤️ @jennaBushHager]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftwardSwing @brooklynnygirl Agreed. One reason I want to keep educating myself about socialism is because the sy… https://t.co/Gb2XoPRmBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityofKissimmee @kissimmeepolice @KissimmeeFire @StBaldricks Way to go supporting a great cause!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hear you ppl in charge of the Oscars. After a while you’re just like “fuck it I’ll do it myself.”  #Oscar2019 #Oscars #OscarRedCarpet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot tub time after our hike. Yess. @ Amara Resort &amp; Spa https://t.co/k1Yj5ZFRxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[SAVE THE DATE for our 11th Annual Benefit Bash!  Join Pittsburgh’s doers, makers, movers and shakers for a dance-fu… https://t.co/48HYnzAinK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sing1out1Louise @JacobAWohl Maybe we all made it happen? We can keep up the pressure. That’s the great thing about… https://t.co/c4VobXaAJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TristenWhite97 @ZackSohn_ @jpdavis1982 @splinter_news https://t.co/xNLtKtRF5w Nurse at abortion clinic tells it li… https://t.co/kxsfHNmqMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snowellet @internet_niche the matching fits.....im gay i love this shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramsey2108 Girl I feel that on a personal level.... just landed back in Detroit😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XSteamBunnyX Republicans are Pathetic!!!!!!! They are so transparent. They know Trump is a criminal. Cohen is tryi… https://t.co/pEKVrB2QIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@david_smarty Congrats on a fantastic season and win! Best of luck to the girls and you at State!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christineestima Happy birthday! 🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knew that the CEO of Goldman Sachs moonlights as a DJ? Investment banker by day- DJ by night. He was so good! D… https://t.co/ZsdMYSIdUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boo for us but yay for you. All the best to this great pillar of our community. Can’t wait to see what you do next!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unfortunately this is not an unusual incidental finding on a coronary artery CT report.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 years ago @Kimzolciak retweeted me. AKA, it was the day we became BFF.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My future cell mate is @IvyMangram   ......... Ivy what did you do to get us in trouble?? I know this one wasn’t on… https://t.co/Vbbafly4HA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VincitOmniaVer2 @imillhiser @SeanTrende Because there is nothing that is not Corrupt in his policies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to our staff members who were chosen for this weeks PBIS recognition! @mariz176 @GiulianaJ_Lewis… https://t.co/RNMyO5yiaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeez what a shootout, bummer that Boston didn’t win that one but they’ve had an awesome trip #NHLBruins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugeniocarpinte @PedroFerriz Desgraciadamente muchos funcionarios y otros empresarios están beneficiando de los re… https://t.co/akoksiTMC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’ve lost about 20 pounds since January 1st. This is the longest I’ve stuck to getting healthy and I feel great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FansMLBSpain Gracias @FansMLBSpain 🙏🏼⚾️ os mando un saludo enorme y vamos a seguir haciendo grande la pelota en España! 🇪🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[People living along the Clarks River in McCracken/Graves Co are starting to feel the impacts of rising flood waters… https://t.co/xH5aPSLBoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1SteveBurton Good afternoon sweetie hope you’re having a wonderful day love your scenes with @GenieFrancis yesterd… https://t.co/aTTiDK1eBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t put shit past anybody these days, always stay prepared for a mfr to switch up 👌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr If he lied he should be held accountable just like you Jr and trump senior.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaithNaff This thread is a cesspit of cishet white men proving you right. https://t.co/uuKcjPvSb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[LET US GIVE A STANDING OVATION and APPLAUSE 👏 to @POTUS for Regulations Afforded to Title X  #PraiseBetoJesus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kid: My sock got wet! Me: How? Kid: I accidentally stepped in the toilet.   #MondayMood]]></document><document><![CDATA[me every morning...except..if you know me...you know i can’t fight/could never, so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash They said they had credible evidence that Brett Kavanaugh created a crime too and we all know how that turned out...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reveling in the gorgeous off-green lighting that resides only on an airplane 🤢✈️  As the song goes “on the road aga… https://t.co/Wa87WfNCcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so glad my eyebrows don’t look like they’re scared of each other anymore since i stopped tweezing them. i used… https://t.co/vCu4qnraXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @shihtzzu If the Dumacrats had won their underwear would be below their knees!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm in so much pain. I'm sick of PCOS and cysts...I'm crying myself to be sleep. Pain from my ovaries to my knees. Fml]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was just an earthquake I didn't feel it tho.. (@ The Meadows in Culver City, CA) https://t.co/GmK8pXVF8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdTechAmber @TheTechRabbi @art_heard @cinehead @tishrich @Artguy76 @burgessdave @GrundlerArt @TaraMartinEDU… https://t.co/tT80RI6omO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mog7546 @Katriana74 No Mikey, he paid off the porn star SO HIS WIFE WOULD NOT FIND OUT. Just how stupid are you Mike Round?]]></document><document><![CDATA[CAT FOOD ALERT. We found these two black foreign pieces in Rawz canned cat food. They claim it’s actual pieces of c… https://t.co/CHnSxdWHcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the messenger update, the dark mode, and also, Twitter night mode. I'll never back to the regular.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganSimerly @PaitonChambers @Tony_Corley @GraceSauer1623 @djbrab74 FORREAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's give her a reason to apply for asylum in a different country. It's on now...who is with me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be the change you want to see in the world orrrrrrr stop bitching about everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌻🎀Washed my lil bug, she doesn’t look great but she looks a lil cleaner🎀🌻.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We won't fall when we're under the gun!!  #music #quotes  Never again.  No matter what they say, we're not the ones… https://t.co/GT4o9uDxmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s ok @bradrossTO because a co that I worked at for yrs would terminate on a verbal complaint from #TTC is not go… https://t.co/QI6PSQKVYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KendallRogers @HailStateBB But will they host. That is all that matters, rights?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tammybrownnc Thank you for coming in and reading with my class today. They loved your visit and their treats. Love you sweet lady!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you’re telling me Dwight yoakam doesn’t sing “bears, beers, battlestar Galactica”   We’re leaving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of humans need a dog &amp; alot of dogs needs a human. Ur mine 😇 https://t.co/cHr020U8ps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@earpforlife @MelanieScrofano @itssphillips @emtothea You take the prize lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m ever in a room with @BillFletcherJr then I know I am on the right side of history! This man is a gangsta thr… https://t.co/Vxb8Wc5rhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KapeKarl @disarmingfilms Sarah could have made Serial in her fucking basement. I even believe part of it was made… https://t.co/BnvNuuILib]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would not wish the flu on my worst enemy. Going on day 7....#needsleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy sábado “éxitos de todos los tiempos” en tilica barrio y micropolis! 🎤❤️🎧 en Tilica https://t.co/BVhHl3zUMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting on @celtics and @HoustonRockets game today! Should be a great game! 💞🏀💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Otra Noche en Miami 🌴 @ Ocean Drive, South Beach https://t.co/7qRYx2tPSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It IS a toupee or else there would be long hair to wrap around and flip back. I’m so happy - what’s wrong with ME?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today sunrise was at 7:26 but there was a layer of clouds that keep the sun from popping up. Just after arriving at… https://t.co/n2NkH4CKk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacLeodLisa Get a wet towel, I hear burning in hell so awful. #ResignLisaMacleod #AutismDoesntEndatFORD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#parents #recherche #cannabis❓ @rclalq @FRAPRU #cannabis #logement @francoislegault  @CarmantLionel  @SJB_CAQ… https://t.co/jTNLu3BBoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop the toxins! Tell the @NYSDEC to deny permits for the Williams NESE fracked gas pipeline because construction o… https://t.co/MT42nT2hsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The school board doesn't broadcast the livestream of the public comment period, but so far speakers have been large… https://t.co/m5oflIMV5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachDiliegro @kualoaha1 @Truman_Tigers @PLTWorg I was very excited to hear this morning how many of the students… https://t.co/8Jr5iH3tEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Get used to it .... when you crap in your own hand it gets full.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Heart Of North Philly ! : ) https://t.co/n6n85fg8oy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My namesake is going well. I think I can grab some coffee ☕️. Next year I’ll bring it home 🏡 I have to go pick y’al… https://t.co/QlALCULLkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queen          Elizabeth     Such A ' Darling ' ..          England is Ever So Proud! https://t.co/gdhRY6bw84]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when ya’ll say “suggests”. It sounds like you’re acussing her of making an outrageous inference and not just… https://t.co/YxsrUdYnex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travisyost Is there anything he can’t do broadcast wise?  Really knowledgeable too, clearly a master of his craft!… https://t.co/EGmAM4Wdol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nino728 @nadiachaudhury Thanks for this! Wine ‘zine will live on and I will help with it remotely. Weds blinds wil… https://t.co/e5mhZFmfd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the Arlington Hockey Team for supporting our 🏑 girls tonight at Winter League! ⚓️ https://t.co/a27OTnbX1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjpasek @BenSPLATT “Love is Love is Love is Love is Love is Love is..........”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lamzelok Alguna vez leíste sobre el sitio de Berlín? Durante la guerra el espacio era pequeño para aterrizar y des… https://t.co/9neAhCrkV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure why one man would be whistling at another man in a sexual kinda way #unless #questionable #interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl! ❤️ Today she turns 17! 🎉 She is precious to me like diamonds are to most.  ❤️ I can NOT explain it. But.… https://t.co/Duyvb3nWlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for letting me birthday with you this weekend, brooksmuller. #latergram @ Compass Rose Bar &amp; Kitchen https://t.co/LMSOO4jEd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post your business link here!!!! 🔻👇🔻👇🔻 Someone may be looking for an opportunity.  🔻👇🔻👇🔻 https://t.co/DuBQFLDpvJ  .]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAY 3: I have accepted a challenge from @jkeister to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews. Ea… https://t.co/HkFSEhokvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTalkCBS GAME OVER: Chicago Police Reportedly Believe Jussie Smollett Paid Brothers To Beat Him Up… https://t.co/uOXfZY6UsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone thinks being a reporter is glamorous...here’s a photo for you. This was my “dressing room” today. I was d… https://t.co/BDHjADvml3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been on Twitter for quite a few years and have NEVER gotten one reply or one tweet.  I feel forgotten and invisible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kpavonescooter @HillaryClinton Maybe on your dime, not mine, and I’m not an evangelist!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to do homework and I get distracted by a frickin SLINKY FOR 30 MINUTES    NO BODY TALK TO ME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maaaaaan I cannot wait til Sunday, to see @chaseelliott and @Hendrick9Team take the checkered. #DAYTONA500]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gilhova Yeah, this is also a great point. I see fascinating, catchy themes that I just want to dive into, and then… https://t.co/mat6HOd1DM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kzfin HAHAHAHAHHAAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHHA AND BUTTON MY BODY SUIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently me seeing everyone talking about a relationship that has nothing to do with themselves 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[As of now there are just under 3,000 people in the dark. About 600 are here in Amherst.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's been a HandBagsULike sighting via 1 of My Favorite TWINS Dr. Dedra Evans pharmadoc96 in the Fuchsia Pink Tw… https://t.co/hugJahIH4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[never thought I would say this but game of thrones is actually sick as fuck]]></document></documents></author>