<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@obyezeks at @AU_SIS today said she would not serve in @MBuhari cabinet. Why? Politicians make implementation by th… https://t.co/vWv1ZHZl4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sucks when you strike up this awesome conversation with someone about life, business, etc...only to find out the… https://t.co/INL2QxMZde]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wish bad upon nobody,but u will reap what you sow In life ,,, you don’t treat people like shit and live a happy life.💯💯✌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Collsmakers experiementing with their own #opticalillusions #collsedu https://t.co/W3GbiAvVu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarryEarthling @WhiteHouse You could be never so wrong, Obama. Hillary, Biden, Bernie there everything you mentioned.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennyaschnabl jlbrew3 @TwoHalves45 eating_healthy_thermostyle mrtravellingman blakesolly @ssfcrabbitohs granmabunn… https://t.co/UwyuKSDh1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@normmacdonald @billburr @BrianReganComic Actually Norm you are the GOAT. And John Mulaney sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morbid obesity by tomorrow. ✔️#Vegan @ Cinnaholic https://t.co/HnpDCR0vuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport Not only sucks at being a delivery man, but sucks at basketball too. Should be perfect for the Lakers LMAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 He did he gave you a place to play but you yes you made it evil. Go already. Go destroy another town.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ADO26Nao criminaliza a palavra de Deus... criminaliza os cristãos... criminaliza os evangélicos... criminaliza os… https://t.co/ovVoR5fxmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to #adoptlove? @PetSmart National Adoption Weekend is less than a week away! Can’t adopt? Post a pic of an ad… https://t.co/VRXJ77K2ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get ready, Dallas - it’s #NCAnationals weekend at the @KBHCCDallas! Let’s show these athletes our Texas hospitality… https://t.co/wWK9pgBvWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[IHSAA basketball sectional scores https://t.co/ZqViJHnMqg via @courierpress]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come flying up on me like you got a problem? Hope you got good brakes 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFCBarstool @KayceSmith @Jared_Carrabis probably a lot of tiny wiener talk on RocketSpace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alfred_twu @tmccormick My concern is that housing development is already too costly, but perhaps less of that woul… https://t.co/8GQaS8WilE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave_Matter @anne__rogers @stltoday Brian Smith.  Best Mizzou coach in last 10 years?  IMO, yes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachDouglas21 I’m 3hrs from New Orleans too my birthday is about to be bananas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumbullSteve @jvcderby @IMWHorvitz You probably got an email from Low Carb Denver with instructions. I watched last year that way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEPTA_SOCIAL @SEPTA For the record I don't blame the conductors at all they have to deal with all of the mess. If… https://t.co/n4kkiXcHFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__TonTon____ happy birthday ton! Have a good one pal. I’ll give u some buckets for your special day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charlie_Kansas @ArrowheadPride Im not arguing that. I don’t want him long term because he’s already close to 30. B… https://t.co/nF6gd5hbv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OL_CoachBolis It’s gonna be a big day! Serious coaching, serious knowledge, 4 SERIOUS Players! Big Potential May T… https://t.co/5q2h48uqRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsSimplist @SneakerNews I just checked the current times around the world. It’s 5am in Greenland and 8am in Icela… https://t.co/NZTYNwFsnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a rematch of the 145 Region 1 final Wyatt McCarthy beat Stefano Sgambellone of St. Joe’s for the second time to… https://t.co/ziXxkNfQrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticusSarah Our legal system is a joke if your wealthy, and a disaster if your poor.  That's a sentence a black… https://t.co/JdLW70Ik3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RIPBiggie #BigPoppa #RIPBigPoppa #BiggieSmalls https://t.co/Zek54Pfpf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a James x Troye x Jacob collab. Send tweet  @jamescharles @troyesivan @gwynethpaltbro @mamamellet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Americans are only concerned about ourselves. Has anybody stopped to think about poor Chairman Kim?  No. I bet he's… https://t.co/pPgHTEkNXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next on stage our @UoB_Engineering PhD student Joe Gregory to present our work on MBSE at IEEE #Aerospace Conferenc… https://t.co/Qzh0B8DxoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CongMikeSimpson @GrandTetonNPS @GrandCanyonNPS @Interior *except for the areas the oil and coal lobbyists who now… https://t.co/0ueSEEig4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlebenthal Thanks. Appreciate the feedback. Have a great rest of your day. Peter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @MrBennett_RHS having classwide discussion refelcting on a text. Student-led but with form and substance.… https://t.co/5shcCCF851]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fitbits are just Tomagotchis, except the stupid animal you’re trying to keep alive is you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @BramptonJrA products are looking good so far. Teat with 1 goal and Patterson with 2 goals and 1 assist through the first quarter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alysa2004 @CheerFessions1 @cheerUPDATES @ProdigyMidnight @prodigyallstars @CheerTheory Alyssa, you know i care and… https://t.co/zwtDl1bTdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy at the Vegan Hot Dog stand was like "this is the best taco I've ever had", kept going on about how good it… https://t.co/vxz2tBADf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our beautiful friend from #Canada DIED from PAINFUL complications from #surgicalmesh #pelvicmesh #60minutes… https://t.co/BuouBfbiIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hawkinsdotbiz The administration that already has more criminal indictments than every  post-Nixon administration combined?]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a busy weekend with @WJTV Nothing beats a day-off walking the campus of @JacksonStateU listening to music, th… https://t.co/jQPi8jdLjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guesses on the OL Administrative Grouping Tomorrow?  LT: Leatherwood LG: Ekiyor/D Brown C: Owens RG: Womack RT: Wills]]></document><document><![CDATA[@popularspup I get that way with Captn Crunch or Ben &amp; Jerry's. And I'm 60 years old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queerthoughts @BeautifulRed7 @Puglaas For those getting all excited and prematurely horny over SNC it isn't  that… https://t.co/gbBw4V5nID]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flapjacks62 @CBSThisMorning @GayleKing That same day Azriel left her job  went to r kelly hotel room ,her mother f… https://t.co/cND2AfyhY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shallowbrigade @nberlat This last sentence really gets to the crux of things. #burnbook https://t.co/7ISnzjMJpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoffeeIsLife06 @Watsonsw611 @Brandonmartine @jlaws007 @Starrbryte67631 @jafah2012 @curly_lovitt @ZombieH89527152… https://t.co/4GsIP5nn9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[We officially reached 74,000 meals in our first four years. A small idea has created positive change. Do you have a… https://t.co/r9TII4j6Gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch me and a bunch of other folks talking about some of the best Game Boy games ever made! Thanks to @MrNobre for… https://t.co/FaI92Pvc7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s International Women’s Day! I’m thankful for the strong, capable, loving, nurturing, intelligent, and talented… https://t.co/DYBWXFO1DD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moxxx7 said to me if you can’t figure out what u wanna eat order something different, so u at least serve a future purpose. the hit me hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DominicJGM Can’t wait for the 1at story/episode. Waiting with bated breath!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshaTempleton @DrDonKAnderson @IndianMotoFans @indianmotocycle @mattanderson88 It’s not good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @AOC What about every Congress man and woman’s bank account and tax returns. Some have become millionaires while in office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enroute to Ottawa 🧳 later today for this and a few other things. Looking forward to it! ⬇️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BracketForecast @boettger_eli You can watch it through the @Stadium app]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys, we are off tonight but we are getting tagged in boys scores.   Please tag @hoopinsider for your boys scores!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RydelLynch wow I love the nails 😱😍😍 I have to redo my nails too I do shalage https://t.co/spnVLmrWhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaolaVintimilla @MazapantaPaola @CarlosErnestoT https://t.co/OZ2n6ELPOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChicagoBears Look at that Gostkowski Available. 🤔 Doesn’t hurt to talk to him does it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s saying something considering he’s coached: Ty Lawson, Raymond Felton, Kendall Marshall, Marcus Paige and Joe… https://t.co/V0vgB0zPut]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve never been to a funeral for someone named beth before, but i assume they’re idiots for not saying “the lord gi… https://t.co/SL4WaocSYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is sin (with a capital S") if I can use a Christian category on corporate media tonight."--Cornell West disc… https://t.co/Eu7OuBZEFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity the msnbc reporters are on laughing and giggling about the ending manafort sentencing.. They are sicko..the msnbc network Sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating the Slovenian holiday at the Hofbrauhuas this weekend !! @ Hofbrauhaus Cleveland https://t.co/PoLRsQ2fi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[MATANZA: Behold New Mexico’s ultimate pork fiesta https://t.co/t6tO0AqSvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fuckjavierr @Dougie6196 @vanielmage @chris_grasu @ABCNetwork I mean compared to Aqua man and whatever else came ou… https://t.co/fMvug7mRCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC There should be research on alterative ways to fuel cars and planes.  I support solar energy, a free fuel sour… https://t.co/wtBG1EA8rA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @LampApparel for the care package! 👁❤️💡 https://t.co/3W2Eu32FsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mmmm...Salisbury steak and peaches for lunch today with this great kid! Highlight of my week, as always. @ Barfield… https://t.co/IpCQB6DQyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[K-State looks out of sorts right now. The Wildcats might be ripe for picking tonight if WVU can make some shots]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathyTuttle @seattledot @SeattlePD Ah, that was a @SeattleParks employee and not @SeattleDOT which said that SPD h… https://t.co/M2OWs5ZIKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[UFC and WWE are two totally different orginazations. CM Punk tried and failed. Brook will try UFC, but fail. The wi… https://t.co/Zm4iZZQHmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LovelyJay4U @CMP_4U @CBwebcams @camstraLCom @HornyDutchy @CamOfChaturbate @nosoloporno69 @iHotCams @maxdefretes693… https://t.co/8NjDjEeUhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kassyvianey I literally ate that today :( hahaha make it for me next time I’m in San Marcos 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/f9vzv4ZP4l everyone go comment I’m following people back and liking everyone’s pictures who comment on… https://t.co/HUBRYD2Te0]]></document><document><![CDATA[On trip visiting family in El Paso, I had the honor of meeting the legendary coach of the “Might Miners,” Don Haski… https://t.co/e7CnwSDZsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Targeting VEGF has may important immunologic implications #ImmunoOnc19 https://t.co/zcIL7iaE6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJudyChu False!  Teachers work barely 8 months a year, off work at 4p and earn a pension with benefits for life.… https://t.co/CgmPti0MBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#justsayin #realestateagentissues #comeonpeople #besmart #realtorsdoitbetter #realtorsofourcommunity #respect… https://t.co/CR11CJJ2b8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Artspiration @USDUpdates @SCCOE Thanks! So proud of our students, staff, and community!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever seen a conservative girl just looking real nice, funny and hot? Or does she just care too much that G… https://t.co/hNT0STAMm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking people's money to give it to lazy and unproductive people is socialism take a class in economics or better y… https://t.co/FFatiBAElV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant even let this bother me. Too many other things that require my thought and attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennypoupou89 Non c'était un deal entre Cora et Sale... Il laissait Price partir à sa place mais si les Sox étaien… https://t.co/Si3sbFqFvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Democrats are over the top with investigations and most people are fed up. I want to know when the Republicans… https://t.co/ZNoEw4XHRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eye_tee @Twitamtrak are you guys behind that or ahead of it?   Ugh either way. Second train/vehicle incident natio… https://t.co/gxfR3rW2gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[No filters no apps no fraud= Tru #TruDarkGuap01 #callenegro #MidnightPaPi7 https://t.co/MlRrpdMxB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Great show tonight . General Jack Keane is a great guest . I watch your show every week . You’ve had… https://t.co/OSQ97iZ9OR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This stinks. I know folks that share the progressive view that DONT think like this at all. Do they realize that Af… https://t.co/E8IGLnHJYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[We watched Black Klansman last night. It made me think how Do The Right Thing was not only relevant at the time, bu… https://t.co/dFymDcLQcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WitmerCarl @cleared37Joseph @AMike4761 @ThomasPKennedy3 @r98121261 @IsraelUSAforevr @godrockin @moekamerow… https://t.co/XxNgiOiMyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Randy Moraitis, MA, CIP, BCPC https://t.co/ItE2SbTeYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veejangl @nytimes Your sniveling because Trump doesn’t get enough bad press? Someone else gets a little bit of bad… https://t.co/Bozsqi8x21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dannars19 @trish_regan @AOC And yet it has a socialist core! Do not we ever forget that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DubyaArrJay Inbounding the ball is like watching a child running around with scissors.  The offense is horrendous. So lost. So scared.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarianGoodman Interlacement (simploce/complexio) 1 https://t.co/1vmgVLkmzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurgerMondays @carlruiz #ruizing at it’s best. Brined, deep fried, then BBQ’d. You fly, I buy https://t.co/HXWmhuFHNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disappointed that the Chair is not enforcing the dress code that members must wear jackets on the dais.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Thank you Mr. Kissinger, now just go away. You’re simply a nuisance here. You whine and… https://t.co/RpawHxCmAf]]></document></documents></author>