<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Tax reform: NJ taxpayers find returns don't quite fit on a postcard https://t.co/urahbfQRRA via @asburyparkpress @NJCPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crimson3Pointer Here’s how I see it: he was patient in making his decision. Seems like Duke anticipates an extra p… https://t.co/2i59cl6IfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidcying We could have solved the transit access problem for the lower half of Hells Kitchen and taken strain of… https://t.co/MBEHl7GXvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fourmonkeypress @NebraskaReads Thanks for being such a “good sport!”  ;0)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshrogin @JonathanLanday @Manuel_Rapalo The spirit of J. Edgar lives on! Never forget it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un placer saber de nuevo sobre ti, no eres la excepción y aquí andas entre mis oraciones👀🙋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@topo_tron @BigBallerRob02 @ggonzalez6894 @SupaSmashMode @edsexy_13 Just bought my boot]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the pizza is not from Southwest Side of Chicago,  thin crust. You are on your own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tg_412 So what’re you’re saying is... Nina won’t see it with me and now you won’t either. What if I bought your six dollar ticket hahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RizziMyers has a beautiful, powerful voice with great, soulful modulation.  I had to push my button for her on #VoicePremiere @NBCTheVoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayorSchieve @DevonReese1 @CityofReno @OscarDelgadoNV @NeomaJardon @BonnieWeber @JennyBrekhus @NaomiDuerr I see a… https://t.co/JkmpPSlMMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@P94atHome @AlmightyRay @GeekToMeRadio @UpToTASK @CBNostalgia @GeekVibesNation @WriterStreamer @BrianLeeOkert… https://t.co/GvpahIeaYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MUNQITHDAGHER انت تعرف جيدا أستاذ منقذ، وقد تكون أكثر مني.. ان كل قوى العالم المؤثرة كانت مع العراق بعد 2003 لكن ه… https://t.co/5Jh59uUX4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vasocialflight The Broad! You can email them about coming in for the week, the website is https://t.co/fBN4WcclWX!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mitchell_Mumma @chaseelliott Man you a couple weeks late for a vacation in florida buddy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder sometimes what would happen if the music that plays before each of these punk gigs was decided by a 311 fan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even the team and #BBN were grieving the loss of the Donkeys and Llamas 🦙 #bambamfarpower!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would pay $25.99 a month for a version of the internet where this doesn’t exist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beverly Hills BMW 5070 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036 (877) 794-4678 https://t.co/bP3aRGQh45]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will be replacing at least 3 of my smoke/carbon monoxide detectors in the house with the Nest Protect. @ San Luis O… https://t.co/7vF9oyY8ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBHenderson @BloodyRedBaron @BRYANMAGNAYE1 @Dixonverse @BrettRSmith76 @CautionaryComic Love that cross hatching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hamm's Premium by @MillerCoors at @LiveWirebar — https://t.co/TuZYnT0G6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acosta Wish they had at least mentioned Trumps names. Maybe after his latest really BS tweets. He loved Otto? Did… https://t.co/VqIoVTejTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Jambo House - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/rgljywGMpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_reymenn @GASMASK115 Umbreon is only relevant when shiny sir, I'm sorry.  That said, fucking T A N K https://t.co/yxwqxRL0a4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Institute's Catherine Taylor, conference organizer extraordinaire, is presenting research about ancient imagery… https://t.co/5giz8uGnp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sabientje Yes! But it gets better quickly.   Throwing out all that garbage we think we know creates more space to… https://t.co/oAVKm0SuOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetBlue app glitch cost me $50 and choosing my seat when I was assured I’d be fine by customer service. Great way to start the week 👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredEisenberger can you see if something can be done about my previous tweet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judemgreen @GOP @realDonaldTrump I can only assume when Mueller says there is nothing there with Russia, you'll ap… https://t.co/Q3YQvjgbi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could meet Emilia Clarke at the Game of Thrones final season premiere—all because I supported a great cause. Than… https://t.co/HXhDDV7PeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMelina and @MickieJames don't even get credited for putting women's falls count anywhere matches on the WWE ma… https://t.co/vdcsgGPRKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[BIG HAPPY BIRTHDAY S/O TO MY WIFE  " THE LOVELY VAL " 💖💖💖💖💖👍 https://t.co/vqpQPnHJxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2Z5LL5R0aA Anyone else ever had either a small leak or a complete blowout?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brad Lea's Sales &amp; Closing Masterclass ... Launching Soon  https://t.co/ngKDC95P9c #BradLea #Sales #Closing… https://t.co/uFWGMIr1u3]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your a girl without a job don’t hit me up I’m looking for girls with checks not free loaders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aradwanski Trudeau has 24/7 access to the media. If we don't know his side of the story it's only because @gmbutts… https://t.co/8YOdmRtgKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mwen te nan Philo Collège St Pierre à l’époque. Champions league final MU vs Bayern Munich. M tap gade match sa nan… https://t.co/5uwGKJ32F1]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to start 👏🏼 ❤️ 🏃 🚴  🏊‍♂️  #pasadenatriathlon @ Pasadena Triathlon https://t.co/zkHjCBm19y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenBB81 @ingress This is 1 unique hack from anyone in the faction. So tell your rural areas to work on sending… https://t.co/onUDnjzoal]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I seem a little sluggish today it's because I hit over the head a dozen or so times yesterday by the 90s Nostalg… https://t.co/4ppQdvZyLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CICsal @policiasaltillo  @CFE_GolfoNte  poste de luz callendose sobre la calle vialidad cerrada]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hammondpolitics Pretty successful morning for the #schk12. Hammond - Culver Academy for the regional title tonight in South Bend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This picture is responsible for my weird ass sense of humor https://t.co/b9CCSv5VdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Espero y aguanten, lo pierden 1-0 con el global 4-1 a su favor. #CCLFever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnni CNN IGNORES BOMBSHELL UNDERCOVER REPORT PROVING FACEBOOK CENSORSHIP OF CONSERVATIVES!! https://t.co/pkYh1VNnA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inclusionist As I said, I’d support most policies that raises wages even only for near poor. But, I tried all thos… https://t.co/qzCFHvp4Tb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Day 61: View from Capitol Hill. #365photochallenge #365daysofphotos #k5winter #seattle  #sunset #spaceneedle… https://t.co/iCOj8VGntx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smh broke ass’   That one girl “my date, my check” is not garbage she’s a queen]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn't cry to Viva La Vida at some point in your childhood...smfh🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ssunderlands Children’s toys from the past are terrifying, it’s like the makers hated kids]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Chronic and illmatic are the greatest alubums of all time dont @ me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrates to all girls and boys associated with the New York pride either with training or playing on the teamsLots… https://t.co/9HuZCesMiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days I think about writing. Other days, I think: Maybe I should write? Then, I begin a load of laundry or vacuum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to Moriah House with a car load of food donated by the Hope Kitchen Ministry! Thank you for your constant s… https://t.co/nYo4uubN2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GordonRamsay @TheWoodyShow @breadstkitchen @heddonstkitchen Just looking at it gave me  Diabetes https://t.co/kcbbFxV5jK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important thread. Papa Ostler is right. This teaching nearly caused me to take my life a few years ago. It is not d… https://t.co/Ex2EflrQxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning and Happy Fucking Friday @woodbrid5 Woody has a head start on most of us but make the day great 🥃🍺🍻🍹🍷 https://t.co/wAJWJ6WkEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Debt cancelation has been around for thousands of years, used even in ancient economies and has been cited in the B… https://t.co/fJpEy1VeTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nora_kelly We'll see what he might have to say at the state party dinner on March 16...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParkerMolloy I’m furious about Billy Porter. It’s just not fair that I could never pull that off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HogsnK @EricSully1037 Hm, interesting. I’d also be listening for the contact of Kelvin Sampson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great event. Ran into so many good people last night. Needed another 2 hrs to catch up with everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @GeorgesMusic in Springfield, PA https://t.co/XiIahqVce3 https://t.co/2TaLhogfti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattMackowiak @AOC If she's so uneducated why you feel the need to comment on her so often?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSCameraGuys Y’all need to sign mini sale now before your agent Scott boras signs him.... 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alliebeemac I have no wisdom because I’m not a girl but have fun at Disney!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guys for the next few years ⚔️ #ChargeOn @gabriel101310 https://t.co/EAYy0COO9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cajunsmiley  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist 🏳️‍🌈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Waukesha, WI? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/yjQyzN5LxM #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlacalle_IA No worries, your English is better than most native speakers and certainly better than my Russian, Kurdish, &amp; French.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dam I go soooo harddd I ain’t know this was even possible foreal I just tried my pushing myself to the max]]></document><document><![CDATA[*me coughing myself to death* My mom: you sure do make a lot of noise  Thanks mom. It’s not like I’m dying or anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WhenIOverthink @BrianCOHalloran I always watch a @ThatKevinSmith movie.. Clerks, Clerks2, Mallrats, Dogma, etc. I… https://t.co/RiPQxHWqXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to watch the Wizard of Oz with the Pink Floyd album playing. It supposedly matches up? Excited to see now tha… https://t.co/O7tTPS2LcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zackfisch You know @expomick was right on @OldBarnHockey today.  Leafs are too soft.  We got no grit.  Simmonds wo… https://t.co/YQnDW68S4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrayInFaith Amen waiting on the restoration I gave my life to lord and I asked him to pick me up one more time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whataboutism has poisoned y’alls ability to think like both scenarios are an injustice based on lying????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@e_swan93 @Wolf359Radio Makes me think I need to re-listen to Wolf359 next]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NPRKelly @LindseyGrahamSC If the President succeeds in moving congressional designated appropriations from departm… https://t.co/lhS8yvg2EZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to work (at @CTA - Wilson in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/CmgtEQAuHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UniversalORL Is there a way to sign up to ride a Mardi Gras float if you’re not a passholder?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's game day @FH_Rangers District 6Playoffs start tonight. Come out and support @FHLadyRangers and @FHHSBasketball girls at 6 boys at 7:30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senneca_stone @MartinellisCo Let’s do it @MartinellisCo https://t.co/7rLmkbsXn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Notes and Observations: Looking into #USC's 2nd spring practice of 2019 - Pace of practice unlike anything we've se… https://t.co/rqLkd3EcGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sylviaduckworth @MandiTolenEDU @mospillman @HeckAwesome @SteveSilbert @Rob_Dimeo @AlishaZ143 @Cbustamante2222… https://t.co/ILJo7mysap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Round 2! #southbeachmiami #chillinwithwifey #life @ Pelican Restaurant https://t.co/4ur3Kx4QVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyBigTweetr @heeldaddy1 @LuckyHaus @ARlAVENTlS @miriamhowlter @mrimcool26 @SamMobiles Ye that's some facts I'll give you that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisredmayne @thugjitsumaster @OstynCade @DustinPoirier @ProFightLeague As much as I'd love to see @DustinPoirier… https://t.co/cbECF6hQG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinKeneely1 @NLEastChampions Ricketts has plenty of money. Don’t let him fool you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseGranger_ @RyanHockeyGuy @prestoncaldwell yes, yes it is. #suckitGranger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceBartlett And during the Munich Security Conference, which would seem like the perfect place to meet with alli… https://t.co/hd22oK0Qzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donald_j_putin Every thing is Coming out !! I always thought American People are Scandalous !! Not our Government… https://t.co/KVS3vvkaEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cash is not king here. We will see more venues going cashless. Mercedes-Benz Stadium going cashless, changing conce… https://t.co/i2qCkvABll]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao yo you gotta hand it to her for dedication, Been like over week she still tryn 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because they are cheap and the team isn’t even in Tampa! This will haunt them all season! @RaysBaseball #paytheman]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @WWE are those “Cleveland is Awesome” shirts only available at the arena? Need them online. Huge @Browns here an… https://t.co/uLBc1QNGkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pakman888 @billyjoel @SCSU_hockey_pbp @deanthibodeau @Solontdubb Billy Joel sucks ass.  Nothing good after Glass Houses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I get a text from my Postmates.... I have a few questions... but mainly wtf could a frowning winking face mean... https://t.co/RMyW8nbj6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@W00DZ he instigates and then when someone fires back he cries like a little bitch 😖]]></document></documents></author>