<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MLE_Online @RueNahcMohr I'm pretty sure a lot of these are 30 years old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp @CPAC @RepMarkMeadows @Jim_Jordan The Democrats are losing it with Elijah Cummings disrespecting POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry, @SpiritAirlines, your pilots are late and so my 2-year-old niece will scream until further notice. 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe freedom is something is feeling that happens once and can never be replicated]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been wrapping my dog up in a blanket at night and also called her a burrito.  Maybe egg roll is more accurate… https://t.co/5ydxblIBLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaNicholes @HarmanKardon I have these in white and they are better than my Beats or any other headphones. The… https://t.co/1loNVcUuKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍ohhhlala the NDHS assessment board is up and running, countdown starting soon 😉 #NDEagles #mcap #parcc #misa #hsa… https://t.co/X4C6PLpvlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Media I am sick of the words “his core base” someone should ask GOP when did having a “core base” absolve some… https://t.co/4RiVunZ6G5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol So then, we can be highly critical of the policies of certain predominantly Muslim states, without bei… https://t.co/0unLxHXMYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtracey Half empty or half full? They are not vanishing...they are appearing and it's a beautiful thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kuckuck Sculpture by askanier (Germany) | Artmajeur https://t.co/CnSWnOK1kA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impressive turnout for @Mvilleschooled #EdLeadership doctoral program info session. #MvilleLeads… https://t.co/OvpKw6pFtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redhead6258 @Tourrep @SamsonEffect @marknali1 @stb71 @dwellman21 @Underculture1 @AOC Having intimate knowledge of… https://t.co/NSAdmWwRMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaulSeguraB @jusnajab1 @zcanosa1 @JuliaCarabias @jjschmittersoto @Dimartzs @ElenaBuylla @VLBarradas @victormtoledo… https://t.co/I9qMoDOZwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_isDonaldTrump @agargmd There is superb research on cannabis from Israel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattieScutella @IndianTrailES @UCPS_MonroeNC Girl....a session w/ @lesliefisher = tech lottery! Looking forward to… https://t.co/QzgpMZPRiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump He said he would build an unnecessary, wall AND that Mexico would pay for it🖕🏼🖕🏼🖕🏼🖕🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I logged on to @normmme MyCoyote today because my computer has her login information memorized for some reason... a… https://t.co/MNnHQXpSpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsiaTater @Heywood98 @Freedom2713 @KevinMFerrara @hoppinmama5 @AmericanYvonne @grannyanon1969 @CensoredSammi… https://t.co/Zgy1oEczCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw the boys! Can’t wait for the concert tonight! #RallyCryTour https://t.co/3WhupM3X6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s hard to look sexy for your man when you ain’t have shit to wear 🤦🏽‍♀️ #needtogoshopping #hotmess]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. Let's get this work week over with so I can go on spring break 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[After listening to her for an hour, you can see the difference with @amyklobuchar, striking a more moderate path th… https://t.co/ktKpUHp1Nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cathy is a great organizer and talent- making us all proud and teaching us well. #BlackHistory]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are secret Human Trafficking processes - which are facilitated by way of PERJURED TESTIMONY gladly offered to… https://t.co/qxyBPWE17Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad/ this video sent me into full mental breakdown mode everything from move era gives me anxiety bc it was really… https://t.co/QnuaW7R7WD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just started listening to @ThePropheC new album and I’m already crying😭❤️BRUH IF YOU HAVEN’T LISTEN TO THE ALBUM YET YOU’RE MISSING OUT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would say, “Go get active.” But it’s freezing outside... so “Go force yourself to get active.” 🤣💪🏼❄️ . . . .… https://t.co/kGoJv0zBYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The name came from a passage in the book “Naked Lunch” by William S. Burroughs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashhneth I’d love a copy of the sheet! I’ve recently begun using podcasts with my J/I students.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got flowers twice today! One from my boyfriend and one from my bestfriend! Thank you Collin and @ChristineeLongg… https://t.co/uvD51LJTnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scenes from today’s Virginia Craft Spirits Roadshow in Alexandria (Tweet 3 of 3) https://t.co/slP0LTAtc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise Perhaps you should shut your mouth and do more reading, you are making a fool out of yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need eyewitness reports! ⚡️Dennis Smith Jr. thinks the dunk competition is still happening  https://t.co/FHICmEVVFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethmachlan I guess it just goes to show that it should be a "middle of the road" "common sense" position]]></document><document><![CDATA[People, I need you to chime in: what’s one of your favorite ways to celebrate Women’s History Month? Read books by… https://t.co/uk5TMOrN6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWisemanSaid2 @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump If you can't realize this meeting in Vietnam was scheduled long… https://t.co/sSawHL8Nbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its not a good thing to cheat on your loved ones .. Good luck to you guys  #Kylie  #TMZBestInShow  #Khloe… https://t.co/rO3mropYrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crites_es Because the universe is made of stories, not atoms. (I stole that from Muriel Rukeyser.) Among many real… https://t.co/Uq8PTArjpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[If they DO NOT support our Constitution and they to swore to uphold it, their lies  are a crime against our laws. T… https://t.co/6prAG5vVY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLo You killed it! Loved the moves you brought with you! You were the only one that shook the show the way Elvis d… https://t.co/0AYHkLOh2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @tacobell, this local bistro owner arrived home in the Toledo, Ohio,  tonight area after a month detained in So… https://t.co/bmyf7YzUFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BB_Swann @TreyStoneAuthor @EvieDrae @Nadine_Little_ @Dana_MuChick @authorecfarrell @tammy_oja @WillieHandler… https://t.co/wuNC4lZSVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Certified and earn CECs in Chicago NEXT WEEKEND! Lakeshore Sport and Fitness is hosting a 3-Day Club Convention… https://t.co/z6mzQNCxse]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a proud mama moment! My super talented son has been invited to play in the Perfect Game Tournament along wit… https://t.co/RiWD5NG90K]]></document><document><![CDATA[And holy cow I’m thrilled that Max Mittelman got the dub for the chimera ant king! All I could think about while wa… https://t.co/6h3stFiKFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@profgalloway walking into #Pivot studio today with @karaswisher today...  (sorry @LaurenGoode ) https://t.co/UwLILSZS8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd Annual SEPAG Community Fair.  Our very own treasure, Mrs. Richardson, spending her time with TOPS Sports! https://t.co/pgyvRKsr07]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things are just funny. Beth and Catbug from Bravest Warriors #hilarity #tee-hee #smirk #amusing https://t.co/HeJel6YvBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, if you say you want the world’s wildlife to survive and then try to pose in selfies with them or set up pretty… https://t.co/Zucvnr6nvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Ways to Feed Your Family Organic on a Budget  - https://t.co/fsBnTwOD0k #organic #healthyfamily #realmomsrealhealth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating the music, composers and songwriters of the Oscars with the fantastic annual _the_scl Oscar gala. I lov… https://t.co/QQNZkKqbbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is just around the corner gottayogamooresville! Fresh tank tops and homemade soaps with all natural ingredie… https://t.co/kZcGj63Ok4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Closing Day for 201 Notchleaf means peace of mind for my seller a thousand miles away! Happy for a new family to lo… https://t.co/flyy1m66DX]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that, it’s #mardigras2019 in #galveston ! @ Galveston, Texas https://t.co/7NEIyLAXzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@avahflavah But then again I still listen to acid rap like it just dropped]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nights like this a romantic interest would come in handy https://t.co/bH6GrCZcaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pollak: Trump Can Build ‘Wall’ Now, Despite States’ Lawsuit https://t.co/ZJ6xTJZXgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[if it werent' for mirth . . .  dog animal coat hanger stuck head no idea what doing funny pics pictures pic picture… https://t.co/gtgRNvKoCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup! Don’t wait until you Have to get loose weight or get healthy!!! We were only sent to this plane of existence w… https://t.co/eITacuarap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KECS13 @baseballcrank @SethAMandel Is it? Well, this wouldn’t be the first pop culture reference I’m unaware of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My [insane] little sister ran a damn marathon today! So happy we could be there to see you finish! 26.2 ✔️ @ Washin… https://t.co/PGFmk1TObK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ God's Divine Intervention https://t.co/QrqLKDJ8Oz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going to be reading: https://t.co/dNxfCLb0Nh https://t.co/ERWDv9nazx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate that airport delays means copious amounts of fried food for me. WHY have I no self control RIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neeratanden @BernieSanders I will say it for you!  I do not want to see that narcissistic old coot again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unless it’s Gerald himself.. you accept the drink and throw it in his face.  (-:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGoldberg Seems like journalists care about their own safety, but not the safety of their fellow citizens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sommerrae @kimmy12575 @johnjayandrich Has this been fixed for anyone? Mine is still playing the Incorrect podcast for 2/15 :(((]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanetJackson @parkmgm Bought my tickets. A work trip caused me to miss your last concert with my bestie but I’ll b… https://t.co/Z9Rht2tED1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Fit in 30 Studio Battle Creek, LLC in Battle Creek, MI https://t.co/7UeVlmywTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIDEO: Ilhan Omar attacks Elliott Abrams during testimony, refuses to let him respond | Herman Cain… https://t.co/yZKdMZtvsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queen and Adam Lambert Will Rock the Oscars with Bohemian Rhapsody Up for Awards https://t.co/mKrm5HSFsn via @people]]></document><document><![CDATA[So ready to be done with this babyshower. Lowkey feel like slapping everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billbarnettjr @Bharper3407 @Phillies They made it part of the press conference!  So amazing!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our cast is FAMILY our cast is EARPERS @SYFY @IDWPublishing Put #WynonnaEarp back on our screen! #FightForWynonna]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are in the Denton location and looking for a new furry friend, please hurry over to Denton Animal Shelter. T… https://t.co/YcRVQB8cmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@precociouspenny That’s a huge responsibility to take on! Yeah...I can’t imagine an **agent** not being able to exp… https://t.co/0sxxL5Evjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankWWebbJr @TwitterMoments @washingtonpost So true... https://t.co/RIQQAtyZi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LivingAboveAustin....Private Listing....Come By Feb 21st 10am to 1pm...6603 West Courtyard dr and catch this view.… https://t.co/Pvd8QQC44b]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fight! It’s been a pleasure to work with you @CallMe_Poodah (my svu girl) and @KarlisKelly - Wishing the bes… https://t.co/Y0g7uiXwZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to know how he isn't in jail anyway, special treatment for the rich!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it bad that when they started talking about the year 1989 in #CaptainMarvel, I just thought “oooo Taylor Swift!”… https://t.co/rNi2MCSS7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iowa  has the boxes in the news.  Long time ago a family named Warnox ....  they baby sat that way.   We could call… https://t.co/YSHBFQ1bG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember you are WATER: Cry. Cleanse. Flow. Let Go.  Remember you are FIRE: Burn. Tame. Adapt. Ignite.  Remember yo… https://t.co/zzKvuaOkdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvelynMae11 @edstetzer @POTUS I think it is best to listen to his own words, what he says about himself and his be… https://t.co/4Mikub9rlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @colton do you have to be 21 to buy your wine ?¿ asking for a friend lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rottzillasgirl @JoyfulBathCo @4judyblue @Pixxydoodle @McGuireSuzette @NrsgJBHCtwmn1 @CupCakeLady1313… https://t.co/IjMR5e49oG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eric and Jamie Talk Heathen. Every Sunday. Check them out. Call in.   https://t.co/I6Lfrxd89Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Google suddenly getting lots of spam and inappropriate g-chats. I know I can block each person but is there anyth… https://t.co/fBJCW2fX4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[No joke! #Alpha &amp; #Beta make Governor &amp; Negan look like day care workers!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corkchopk @auroravrosas @Ernest___Perez @cmelissa1024 @RogerCruces Yay Roger!! Hope your first day went well!! 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[RU Wrestling recruit needs your help to win Wrestler of the Year!! Please vote!!! https://t.co/GX1F2TESGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[In after school , having fun with the Custodian 🙃 @BocaRatonMiddle https://t.co/u5nT0aIhBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[76 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19… https://t.co/5nu9OlpyL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darthclaudiaa I wouldn’t be surprised, our Dr. is making us make appointments for routine prescription refills now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monitorLATINO Voto X #CuandoTeAmé de @julionalvarez para 1° lugar en el #TopNorte @SAPSGrupero @ChulasDeJA @EEnrique_F 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tech_Buddha @SangeraSubaru So cute!!! Anyone that I know with a Subaru, loves it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me being excited about advocating for students w/ @RiseFreeOrg https://t.co/BYCxvHoFFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Envidio a todos que están con sus tenisitos bien cómodos en este momento.]]></document></documents></author>