<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman She got debate answers ahead of time, she ran the DNC so Bernie had no chance of winning ( don't care… https://t.co/lLkmi09s1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why waste your time on someone that won’t give you the same treatment back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The chargers need a free safety badly because they ran an all pro guy out of town. Now he’s on the open market and… https://t.co/ELrjohuLIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's the same in Boston as long as the #rupefangirls don't wear heels.  But that also applies to surviving a 4th of… https://t.co/U4sdgpLkBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaPagina Un dilema eterno para los paises perifericos. Que tanto es sumisión y que tanto es independencia? La clav… https://t.co/g4lbX5RlIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/s5KBaGRi8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamonaHolloway So proud to work with you and your team! @mattharris1079 @KaryDegrassi @BrentHarlan1079]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Olgalexandra1 Tan triste y trágico. Es una lección para todos nosotros. La democracia es frágil y siempre debe ser… https://t.co/wQJeGS8zbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning TakeOff 🛫 https://t.co/yDyH7cofbM @foxracingshox @Bontrager @AMPLIFIGear @bellbikehelmets… https://t.co/CDXjSgutxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[DC - TONIGHT WE RIGHT BACK AT IT.... “INDUSTRY MONDAYS”....ALL NEW MOVE FOR MONDAY NIGHTS.  thelivingroomdc 1008 VE… https://t.co/J6YN79hmij]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Waiting for a black toenail to fall off”,  probably the only thing runners and diabetes have in common.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our new ambassador to Canada explaining her belief in “both sides” of climate science.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham You mistake religious freedom with the right to be a dick to people you don’t like.  Jesus would n… https://t.co/aGLQ2wmqWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with my bestie in New York @ New York, New York https://t.co/cKFb1370Y8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know this is super basic and cliche but I have to give a shout-out to gavin.gruwell for this beauty. Even has a h… https://t.co/Q1ZaFU6Axw]]></document><document><![CDATA[SZA’s leaked EP under Sister Solana is still on SoundCloud.....you’re welcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[El NarcoRegimen permite con esto se Viole la Ley del Ejercicio de la Medicina, así como permitió la entrega de nues… https://t.co/VcnkoBI7UV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan Strome has 23 points in 49 games with the Rangers this season. He had 36 in 100 games with the Oilers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaDGilbert G❄️❄️d Morning Jess! Have an amazing day my friend. ☕️☕️💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABXXNA @daniellastagram Until death do us apart !!! I’ll marry you 🌹💋🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[There can be a large range in the digestibility of different feeds, you may think that you are feeding a ration con… https://t.co/Mt04XrrOvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeOfABruin @TheArmoTrader @brosales12 Especially for us, who have Lebron locked up for the foreseeable future (win now mode)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jon_greenberg #hottakes Florida hates baseball and what is up with Philly’s fans? The Padres have better attendance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And you don't lie without the approval of Putin and Russia. And you lie everyday. So what's you point, pee pee boy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can build the wall AND have El Chapo pay for it... @tedcruz's #ELCHAPOAct is how. Stand with Ted Cruz and add yo… https://t.co/bgiOT5jm5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsQueen_5 Hell yeah they are. Then are overdue for some of that main show love 🤘🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember the first time you realized Mondays were created so you could set the pace for the rest of the week]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm choosing Scorbunny to join me on my adventure through the Galar region in #PokemonSwordShield!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennovative @Josh_Moon You have to be able to perform simple math to understand this. Reporters are not known for their math skills.]]></document><document><![CDATA[CNC Cutting a Gatorfoam Board - Grateful Dead Sign on Router https://t.co/Hy9LHkBVye via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrcrom1 @smittygrrl All the slaves have died. There will never be reparations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCouchAR @WinnieWrightTV @FOX13Memphis What is your advice to low wage earners who now are seeing day care cos… https://t.co/FF536nI3yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning I am so thankful for the opportunity to work with families and students in @HaywoodSchools! Seeing the… https://t.co/vFT1aM4YFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArgRayados La verdad.. No se nota que les faltan jugadores... Todavía hay cambios excelentes!!!... Vamos por todo!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaiaArzilli @lrblondon @Qadre @Pavegen @MayorofLondon Thanks! What’s the video? I didn’t make the event!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One down and Mitch McConnell a Russian Asset now like Trump must be voted out of office. With the rest of the repub… https://t.co/MAw8X3ARoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathan_borody @NHLbyMatty He hasn’t scored in two months. Party over.  And we don’t have a 97 for him to play with😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HernandezTony @thecjpearson @phxwardog @realDonaldTrump So when Odumbo Obama did it, it was ok with you? Hypocrite!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t expect me to have respect for you if you can’t even keep your word .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think my hate - love relationship for NYC is because I’ve outgrown it. It’s like I either am here for a quick sec… https://t.co/6A4H3ifqmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesssss. Yet another @espn needless split screen of a coach standing with arms crossed taking up 1/4 of the screen. #BBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@508gloryFelix @BrerBradshaw We will see the constitution stretched and beaten by the sick fucks Trump and the GOP served up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iarkintsharpe When I first read this I thought it sad bad bod and I was like ooooh do they not know who’s mans this is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffwhelpley Try doing rush immunotherapy.   I did it and it really works.   https://t.co/GLKrxgRQQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good “red sauce” joint. (@ Colombo's Italian Steakhouse and Jazz Club in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/9Qa51GhSkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Women_Of_Christ Who is jesus,,,,now,,,before we forgotten it,,,, https://t.co/oXtdjl3E1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrionPax_TA @AliEhsassi @DianeMariePosts @AndrewScheer I’m assuming you said the same for Adam Vaughan, and this i… https://t.co/CIQhO2uQJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a lot to learn from SERPs, and they are out in the open, and free to see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColinSimmons53 Dude it’s lit. As close to mainlining coffee as you can get haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriciaMazzei 30 minutes on a good day, an hour due to weather and traffic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badbuddah @AdamSchefter Kraft wasn't the biggest name, just the biggest name to the football world]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jaishan Norris finds Darius Parham in transition to extend the Bishop Ready leads to 32-26 early in the second half]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Weezer and #Pixies Concert was awesome!!  #kfcyumcenter @ KFC Yum! Center https://t.co/Ua9pV9I2Ng]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still don't like the CG art style. I realize my opinion is becoming unpopular, but it just weirds me out.   For m… https://t.co/FwF8VcgMhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanHicklestein VHS would you like to co-conduct the 2019 Alex Reyes hype train]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously doubt Tiger is caught up in this.  His ex taught him a lesson  or three.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toney_Mo I was really upset after john warner gave that speech about respecting how we spend our hard earned money… https://t.co/bxefNGaTGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielH56533386 @juryverdicts @GoodmanHoops No. He’s talking about if they (the players) are deemed “unprofessiona… https://t.co/aQfpeGVUdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't even care about the time, I'm feeling pretty dang proud of mysellf. Thanks to @KGDowdWTOP and @sarahbethhens… https://t.co/uvrn3JbLbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It's like a new pair of underwear: At first, it's constrictive, but after awhile it becomes a part of you.”… https://t.co/r2cbNHU36b]]></document><document><![CDATA[the non-Democrat Sen. Sanders has officially joined the race so he’ll be in the next poll as he again seeks the nom… https://t.co/ZcgZMyvNpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tremendo putter para salvar un maravilloso Par 🔥🔥 @joaconiemann @ Bay Hill, Florida https://t.co/4FrGf6buFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[2018 CHEVROLET MALIBU 1LS - Used Car For Sale - Hudson, WI https://t.co/dQ3uDY0TI9 via @YouTube #LutherHudsonChevGMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Smash_Adams Not arguing, but who who the other better teams in the league and the west? I think that’s relevant to these comparisons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please don't tell @AOC but I just ate beef at breakfast and I'm thinking about a juicy burger for lunch! #MAGA… https://t.co/Dbw9Va2YTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruckerDesiree @realDonaldTrump Caused the current problems by not enforcing the laws ! And the Congress is also r… https://t.co/17F0Vuyw2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rico_3MINDZ #puertoricansinhouston  #houstonrican  estamos trabajando estoy aquí todavía 28por8 oírte @ Greenway -… https://t.co/KQgIVR5HU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCAR @KyleBusch @LVMotorSpeedway Oh waaaaaaahhhhh. Cry baby! Go back to your mommy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icychey @JhineseSharee Some men know how to keep it in there pants until marriege🤡. We're not all freaks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Near campus? Stop by and pick up a sticker! #UCADayofGiving https://t.co/Vhf7IE7rr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Americans fetishizing African beauty a thing yet?  Text me when it does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andyhicken @RhetoricPJ That's what will make it all the more stunning. It's like the Spanish Inquisition. No one will suspect it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredZembo @Kimmeebabe @eagle5119 @GOPChairwoman Like everything Trump does? No explanation? No plan? Remember how… https://t.co/qoSD6KhoLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poppcorp Good morning and happy hump day my friend! Have a great one! ☀️👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougPlagens @LindsayBHockey @ChrisWittyngham @MannyC_894 @goldieonice @DenisCPotvin @HeyRedDeer @CraigMinervini… https://t.co/jmFTfbEirE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @AOC still wanted to raise taxes it’s an attempt to avoid the collapse of civilization as we know it. Who’s goin… https://t.co/CjbdYRuX27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tpeck2 @USATODAY I'm not saying he's not on shaky legal ground.  I'm questioning if a state has standing to sue wh… https://t.co/oM1rMFER7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DynastyOuthouse @DFFMemphis @DFF_sjonathan02 @FFHurcules @DTC_IzzyE I’m in season 4 right now it’s been amazing thus far]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericfisher It’s on the news every storm and it never stops.  Tractor trailers need to be cited as well!  They thro… https://t.co/yvjFtsz5Cl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now imagine you are a #chronicpatient without insurance bc @POTUS took preexisting conditions away. At minimum is a… https://t.co/3Ksf2bUMfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders And you own how many homes?   How did you make all that $??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@digitalteeeej @cultfilmfan @SarahKSilverman Don’t forget trump was the one who made Obama produce his birth certif… https://t.co/MwAuwpUqhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyHeyItsConrad @PrichardShow Wrestlemania XX Wrestlemania 21 Creation of the WWE US Title Backlash 2004]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because it doesn’t show up on your electric bill BUT yes i will freeze every night I’m there with a smile on 🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frank_Melgarejo @AH__Athletics @larryblustein @psurtain23 @AF_Football Good job Frank Im proud!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This pre-work out fucked me up tonight. I can’t sleep. https://t.co/7EGI43cFMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s Transform Education in Michigan with ArcGIS and Geospatial Technologies. Every K-12 School has Free software,… https://t.co/JZU0X3LRgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beckhams Z Tam dominates; Tetrick wins five at Big M https://t.co/pjXLaoSjzb via @ustrotting #PlayBigM @eedoogie… https://t.co/lls10S6uw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelockhart @WaterMusic3 Jim Jordan is just a pervert protector like is just as QUILTY of it .]]></document><document><![CDATA[#new #nj #nyc #park #dress #art #artshelp #photography #model #mua #work #life #yolo #travel #shoes #portfolio… https://t.co/kk5Ml0FOLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can move into this one as is and enjoy, or utilize a renovation program making it your dream home. Contact Kris… https://t.co/8QZPnDdPIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why isn't there an option to see quoted responses to other people's tweets?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonassiegel What a way to twist a bunch of bullshit. That had zero to do with Love]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 100th Day of School from George L. Cooke Elementary School! https://t.co/jM1MaWemdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylakaye @2earsandaheart @dcpl @TheMorningNews @Urrealism Tayla’s the only one I know who reads all the books each year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#deadlydetention is just the amount of corniness i need! I’m legit laughing out loud! https://t.co/f9egur4AcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance Trump certainly can be indicted. Part of the leverage over Pence is that they can have him remove… https://t.co/W3rATqsqll]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no amount of evidence you could present to a conservative to get them to care about this corrupt foreign agent in the White House.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just participated in a fantasy draft for the final season of #GameOfThrones and that may be the nerdiest thing I’ve ever written.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do nottt “like” eating pussy tbh. I mean I like getting girls off tho 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document></documents></author>