<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[No worries @NicoletHoops, Port is not allowed to host their own sectional game.  Stay tuned for location updates.… https://t.co/BpsZ02Bq7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had some fun with some long exposure photography and my led mask! #sonyalpha #longexposure #NightPhotography… https://t.co/lUObnmxiQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JAGVIEW: Great final night cadillachotelmiamibeach. Couldn’t leave without visiting my little #CadillacHotel sanct… https://t.co/5ZKyr29XkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[During a parent-teacher (probably 1st or 2nd grade), my teacher told my parents they were concerned because I spent… https://t.co/eaHSclEovS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s birthday girl is the ageless @sharonstone. https://t.co/OgfxgdVZ1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsideCarolina UNC seniors 39 points, 32 rebounds, 11 assists.  Dook seniors 0, 0, 0.   How is that one &amp; done working out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerseymike711 @PamBoling1 @slack2thefuture @AlanDersh The only fascist things I've seen so far are the fake news p… https://t.co/BtHN2TOVkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ticiaverveer “Neuroscience gives a clue” - uh, most likely it does not. This is like looking through the exhaust p… https://t.co/0OweT2Jp1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you listened to #SantaMonicaWave Podcast Episode 2 yet??   Message @SigCMoney or myself for access!   Ain’t no… https://t.co/cd7BK6lO66]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like the love between father and sons. ❤️  Thank you for your service @JoshuaJeffries_]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gave me nightmares through elementary school after my brothers made me watch it lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnsatiatedBlood @Alyssa_Milano How is trump ruining the county ? Because he actually does what he says.  And he’s… https://t.co/WTYbxovIkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[stardust_tinyfeet has developed a taste for human flesh. #kittylicks #catsofgoldenhill #catsofinstagram #stardust @… https://t.co/IBYjt12jf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tripel B by @adelbertsbeer @ Big Hops Shaenfield — https://t.co/p5LIxzatU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition So are smuggled girls in cages attached to heroin drips for several years before they’re let off t… https://t.co/yKNegKr2ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want a Different Minka 5 Days a Week? I sure do. https://t.co/BcInnLBSKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[When in Rome, drink IPAs. - Drinking a Flagstaff IPA by @Lumberyardbrew at @elchorroaz  — https://t.co/COmCRfQEnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Bait and switch is nobodies forte least of all yourself. You just had a tweet recently that put yourself at so… https://t.co/ahOgSWWCF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bagatellenyc what the f%*k! Is Bagatelle? 🤔🤫🕶 ——————————————————————————— 🅲🆈🆁🆄🆂 🆇 🔈🔉🔊¸¸.•*¨*•♫ ★ ⭐️ #bagatellenyc… https://t.co/6tuiwQJpdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shallow15 If you mean let it rest for a while that would probably be for the best. But Hollywood can’t seem to hel… https://t.co/7yxpOTnyRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsAmerica @jorgeramosnews @Univision @NicolasMaduro That's what he gets , por metiche, le gusta poner palabras… https://t.co/yypeln8GJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manijade26 Nope this is no joke. This love story needs to come to light. Fuck Marshall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being an authentic Christian is about progress, not perfection. When have you preferred pretending over living?… https://t.co/kTxndn8H9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InEgoVeritas Here you go.  I had her send me the file. https://t.co/V6EzZ6VLiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter @Patrick_Reusse Another first rounder allowed to walk away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanDFischer AND HE GOT A FREAKIN STANDING OVATION! What kind of craziness was that!  I thought it was just me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those disappointed by today's storm, I'm tracking not one, not two, but possibly THREE chances for some measura… https://t.co/FuwC609KkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephMcMahon it would mean so much to the whole entire universe for Bailey and Sasha to become tagteam champions t… https://t.co/zMGUk3RTVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see @JesseItzler @10XGrowthCon #10xgrowthcon2019 #miami #10x a great speech it was! https://t.co/CKWMLIJYQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you've reached a certain point in adulthood when you are thrilled to find your local grocery store has "bu… https://t.co/pNEjzIUMMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealFrankC_ Maybe change to Clark Francois 😀 Then those hits on the QB will be more “gentle”]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is almost funny: my Dr gave me a new prescription today. I looked it up: ‘Drugs like this one have raised the ch… https://t.co/VJxBQWAaG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchalisaCole Thanks for Following! Like a good spy thriller novel or know someone who does? Please check my author… https://t.co/MODIAKzGp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wheelieWednesday from beautiful Bellingham! #shotonrylo #transvision #nature #bikedork @ Larrabee State Park https://t.co/XfPPzIbK6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DunlapSports How 'bout we just go back to a wide field with three attempts and they take your best two scores?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter and The Starcatcher 3/14-3/23. FREE Preview 3/13 at 8pm! sienacreativearts  noracoll bomonic alyssa_bergman79… https://t.co/1OtzXKVBjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mviser @NickMerrill “Stacey Abrams should be governor,” says the woman who should be president.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegitEricRobles nothing says you are appreciated mire than a steak dinner! Thx2 @philrynda we are OG #GlitchTechs… https://t.co/RkKs8X39RZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t want to pay for hotels man, I’m barely ever in them... I fly out see what I gotta see then I dip, but… https://t.co/XXGpsKIbZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalKathy The answer is No.  Jesus was Divine was on a mission. That mission was to be the final and most pur… https://t.co/pSbdipcKYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Conservative183 If you gave me a choice if I could trade my Lyme disease for cancer I’d take the cancer any day. L… https://t.co/wgA9wtZizn]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you think of this 5 bds • 5 ba • 5,546 sqft home I found on Zillow? https://t.co/rZGxX60Q96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kristencrowley3 As long as you can remember how you got there, you’re ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @BustedOpenRadio while I wait for the boy to get out of school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to all the Arkansas High School Boys and Girls teams in State Tournament this week! Make the most of ever… https://t.co/OkIgE3ygya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacieJayGaming Are you taking “meta” of all players or top ranked players? There’s a massive difference in operator efficiency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SÓLO GANAMOS CON PAPÁ, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/6rvGJSO9Nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMW to my first rehearsal for THE GRELLE DUVALL SHOW THREE @hideoutchicago. (Like I did for the first two, I’m chor… https://t.co/yLKeianwee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylevy They should be made public so the assholes know when they're in a time-out. #thenaughtychair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zovatto55 Mi punto es que America del Sur no resuelve nada actuando como don Otto botando el sillón, ( y comprándo… https://t.co/0h0Z82vxQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evesdadisbest Your now laying into the ROCK side of music and it sounds great when you sing it .]]></document><document><![CDATA[This beautiful lady got married to her soulmate last night. The man who never once camouflaged his love for her and… https://t.co/AgACZ2ICQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeschlossDC Did they ever catch that train to Clarksville?  Where is their Clarksville?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmccreary OMG.  I hope you are ok.  Pretty amazing “little” surprise there.  Thanks for coming to the show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It Took Two Months and Nearly a Million Dollars to Save an Unvaccinated 6-Year-Old From Tetanus  https://t.co/Uwkd3JHqYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nofilter_Senior @TravisAllen02 BTW, my wife has an 8 lb. Yorkie Terrier that totally dominates him in the house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shared this last year, but my grandmother is worth a thousand reshares. She’s one of many women in my life I’ve b… https://t.co/xvYkbSVEbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG! What is wrong with you? HE LIED! PUTIN LIED!MOHAMMAD BIN SALMAN LIED! THEY ARE MURDERERS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eli when he doesn’t take terrible shots  Carey could use more minutes Braswell ain’t bad with minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remeber me lmao  Here’s a song for you… Reefer Man by Cypress Hill https://t.co/paN1v6x4gh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vickiringer @Bakari_Sellers Yes I did miss something, thanks for bringing that to my attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone has known he was involved with Riussian collusion since the beginning. The only thing shocking is how much… https://t.co/emgHrqvkVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[eliroscoe @Esoto2011 @roscoecouture @kbainc1 #classicmenswear #international @ Studio B Chicago https://t.co/jIGJzioO2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill @RyanHillMI @AOC @AyannaPressley @RepPressley @RashidaTlaib   🔥...WE COMIN FOR YA...🔥 https://t.co/D3ELqXgsqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Antrob8 @BreeVandy @ChatByCC For sure mitt. Don’t know how that wimp got elected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the DJ in Vegas plays a medley of @britneyspears for you. Thank you @DJRicoche]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the 2019 NFL Scouting Combine! @ Lucas Oil Stadium https://t.co/qO5RsqcFS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is me with my #Toscar @thetoscars I #WON #bestsupportingactor #britsinla #brits #british #britishoscars https://t.co/ZHPIGOED9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are one sick individual. I am going to encourage WHITE PEOPLE to move to your district and throw your ass out o… https://t.co/MIbDOmUCGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why I’m breaking out, never did as a teen. Any Recommendations to get rid of this ish #savemyface… https://t.co/UXPr37bygA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frankiesamba I saw your tweet earlier and was just thinking of making a Kazuma Kaneko thread because I love love l… https://t.co/6U43GsM3if]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sadlerimages Your vision was on point with this one thank you!  @sadlerimages]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone told me I was too negative.  Someone else asked if that bothered me.  Me "Horsesh*t, I'm always positive that I'm pretty." idky 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvolvingWild Yes, because scoring goals is the new all end all of an all around defenseman. https://t.co/j71UIAcdHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@faouziaofficial Mon sicatriste My apologies for the potential misspelling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FernaUSA1 @WalshFreedom not on everything but Glenn was wrong on something about trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GentleBrookSpo Meda dad who has two kids playing baseball. Heard Steve about 10 years ago and said he is one of th… https://t.co/D9duXdnqyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so thankful for my great session interns, Paige and James, whose hard work and dedication was immensely helpful… https://t.co/YvMNUordmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLBruges @SecPompeo @Maripuerta @usembassyve Qué van es con todo pa dentro mijo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraBookerTN Is there a site where we can track our district progress for @HaywoodSchools? Just checking. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck They forgot about Sponge Bob in the memorial https://t.co/lOke52YM8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gouxforever Could’ve had the Cal DB Coach and Strength Coach, but SC is being cheap. That’s not on Helton.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Follow the Money. Never truer words for the  Trump Grifting Organization, a family that grifts in pl… https://t.co/7vgpfo0g95]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @grantjmcd for the opportunity to share my thoughts on Leading With Courage in Government #PSNSmartCities]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conorsen I get the impression a lot of these guys are like robots and we tell them to loosen up but then it’s “no… https://t.co/u8wQfJzkPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mustafeabdulah7 Aaaamin aaamin  Allah give his grant janatulfardawsa insha allah]]></document><document><![CDATA[DJ’s second at bat as a Yankee a little more fruitful. https://t.co/se4clOO8TO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha never a dole moment with julie told her to give me directions to nearest  highway yet found ourselves half way to Bakersfield. . Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever just wanna be invited to somethin?  Like you wouldn’t GO but you just want to know that the option would have been there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittRideau Hostiles National Treasure Ghostbusters  The Dark Night  Wind River Spectral All the Indiana Jones mov… https://t.co/F9DUfMK9wI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC I PERSONALLY  FEEL FOR ALL WAR VETS ,, WHO HAVE SURVIVED THE HORRORS OF WAR AND LOST FRIENDS FROM THAT WAR ,,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enséñanos a hacer como tú. Escribir para los paganos. https://t.co/2eHkWTfVGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[He didn’t tackle him. He grabbed him. Happens all the time in the NBA. Get over it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@29Duke17 @HWaiver I would always encourage a player to stay but it is absolutely your right to transfer per new NCAA rules.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@absalon78 @JoelGro6 Lo veo (lo veía) seguido en el penal 😒, hay mucha novela aún por contar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanMarrazza I got “might move countries and languages at 4 am” and “on a ferry”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HJPreller @leisurefriar @MiserableSDFan @madfriarskevin @DSmithShow @woedoctor @rich_roberts [scratches out Bay Ho Boy Toy]]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:48.6°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raymysterio305 Would be able to tell the difference? Probably not👎🏻😂🦄💨😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great game from @TheTraeYoung and @jcollins20_ !!! 🗣📞My team came out with the dub]]></document></documents></author>