<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@my_new_garden @NickCannon @MaskedSingerFOX Yes!!!!  I’m so in love with #PeacockMask  @donnyosmond is my favorite!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump .@realDonaldTrump There really already is a celebration of July 4th in Washington. And you are not… https://t.co/ABzMUSAuVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APSVaSchoolBd Support @APSKenmore at @DogfishFC Seven Corners, 2moro, Tues, Feb 26, 11:30 am - 11 pm. @DogfishFC w… https://t.co/y8CAfsOkzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RueNahcMohr @wackyvorlon I wonder what you could do with an acoustic coupler in this day and age.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahMarais IT IS MY NEW FAVORITE. YOUR ACTING IS INCREDIBLE AND IT JUST A MASTERPIECE. I LOVE YOU SO SO SO MUCH #COLDINLAVIDEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like BART is having a terrible, horrible, no good, very bad day #yikes https://t.co/dzhwPOVlFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got: 11/12 Enjoy the spotlight! https://t.co/k6DULYn3EX via @playbuzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KnorrMelvin @MaidsMarathon @SidneyPowell1 @60Minutes @JusticeOIG @CreepsOnAMissio I agree. Not convinced with Barr. Can only hope]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cultofpedagogy Take a Breath after @SXSWEDU w/ your new idea/ don't have a half baked plan and present it to your… https://t.co/ji8VK1fxHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[T minus 14 days until working 2 jobs 7 days a week finally starts to pay off! moving into my first apartment here i… https://t.co/UwyfiMlXUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow Dang it @TheEllenShow I can't get into my EllenTube on my cell phone. Getting Very Frustrated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this picture that was captured from our game last night! These boys worked last night! #committed  #hearts… https://t.co/X2JKFOjBYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends picking me up for @BrettYoungMusic tomorrow night at @starlandNJ 💃 https://t.co/N3RKOUbOVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally saw the BSB elevators (after all these years). Mission: accomplished for this trip. 🤓😂 https://t.co/L8NnIa2xf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3lillE @mad_liberals @realDonaldTrump @CarpeDonktum I took a long break after some major medical issues back in 20… https://t.co/MumVcgzi59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter She’s back!   (After a moment of clarity calling Trump an idiot!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanLeandre55 You’ll need a few pairs brother they’re nice to wear they go with everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timothy_gumm @IamGMJohnson @Alyssa_Milano It’s not about “seeing color”. When you say “I AM” you are taking on the… https://t.co/GgJpqREMHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBigBazzaVD @ScottBaio @MisterSchlatter We taught Shane and Owen; when you owe someone money, you pay them back… https://t.co/WkzmZXAEyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeenVogue oh look it's Teen Vogue the newest fake news seriously Beto O'Rourke had more people,? You're lying to t… https://t.co/v3jZAMxPmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano She's scared of her own shadow. She's a #Liar for the anti-American left. We know the truth. https://t.co/g6BdjESFPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[This looks like a cool #coding activity!  This was done at my friend’s @sureeset school in Henrico Co. (Achievable… https://t.co/LVaS8jkAMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenkent @BBBSEasternNL @bbbsc @w_m_c Walking down memory lane this week - I love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at eckford and calyer street in Brooklyn, NY https://t.co/KxWbhAiXls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConservativePTZ Is she a French Bulldog? Love the b rindle, she is beautiful!!❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanedawson hey Shane, I’ve got an assignment for school where we have to do a presentation about someone who insp… https://t.co/1J5aRcyCqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who gets up at 4:30 am on a rainy Sunday morning to go to New York City again ?  Me !  Tune in to W104.3 to listen… https://t.co/iGcMLB8jcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendships that are timeless ❤️  . . . . . #birthday #celebrations 💕🥂#friendships #priceless #family  #goodvibes… https://t.co/O1O6mquVsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Why don't YOU do more with less money because it starts from the top you know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord,THANK YOU for your DAILY guidance,protection and being the KEEPER OF MY SOUL!!!! I will ALWAYS bless your holy… https://t.co/tWNBJXWrB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimonAcePursall @MattNelson02 @TaylorFan01313 @NicolaC51255305 @Lampi_NRW @HarcourtDoug @Wendyglitters @raehering… https://t.co/DNUFQVih5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_emilayyx0 I don’t even know when it happened 😂 I JUST noticedz super random but whTever]]></document><document><![CDATA[clearly some of y’all have not seen the butter cow at the iowa state fair]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new business mantra...doing right and proving it  https://t.co/H4uqnv1rpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to move for May 1st or earlier in #Toronto if any of you know of places to rent message me! If you wanna he… https://t.co/znyibPW1u4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madanboukman Importing rice into Haiti. Doesn’t that sound like pure 💩?   Keeping Haiti dependent and despondent is so a WIN/WIN for many.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dtofig @lolonghi @paulinapineda22 @breeburkitt I don't know if that would fly. Oh gosh, can I say fly?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time with #family today at the @ctcharlottenc 💜💜💜 These two kids are pretty awesome! #children #theater… https://t.co/Ry55fdBjyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sister:I'm just talking to myself  Me:Welcome to my world  Sis:Only I don't answer myself  Me:Thanks for making me… https://t.co/zlegmoBDf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @thedailybeast All this nationalism and Brexit is a fucking joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryelder @realDonaldTrump Handcuffs for this race baiter . Anybody that had any common sense knew it was a HOAX!!!!!🐍🐍🐍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommamia1217 I'm much more afraid of 50 something and 60 something Republicans voting. 16 year olds are smarter an… https://t.co/xKSNgiFySg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope GaGa is on early because  I don't  want to watch much of the Oscars😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickyDavila Watch @Lawrence for his take on why McConnell is supporting Trump declaring a national emergency. I… https://t.co/eckjhdwNI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[1800 registered Walkers joined us for our Walk for the Animals today! What an amazing way to celebrate the pets we… https://t.co/4lyNPl3iZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because pictures are memories❤️ #losamo #carnival  #boyfriend  #brownsville #fridaynight @ Brownsville, Texas https://t.co/n4IxzAb508]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer It was a voter initiative &amp; our Mayor, whose a Dem was against it cause he knew this would happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriotGamer77 @maxschachter @AndrewPollackFL And add Obama to your list!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MSNBC IT IS NOT ABOUT SATANYAHU. THIS IS ABOUT BABIES BURNED BY USA BOMBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes,I also play shooter games...and I made a YouTube account on this game called "pixel strike." You could get this… https://t.co/UNofsvYoFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I tell you I do not recall watching Stefania's interview....shit I might not have watched it at all 😬😬😬 whoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll sleep for a few hours and then I’m up for a few hours... my body thinks I’m taking a nap 🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[there are people who start their day without coffee &amp; that baffles me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN To be honest, I will never be able to listen to MJ in the way I was before. It’s just not possible for me to s… https://t.co/dMR6W2J6xx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GustavoArellano @hragv @cmonstah @Saber @LoudenStudio @CastleMetals Taco y cerveza siempre @millerhighlife… https://t.co/Feu8oUZb5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[be sure to listen closely, for @MitchMarchand is on the writing team for the Academy Awards, y’all! #oscars 🏆🏆🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesQuinteroTX @chuckazooloo @WhistleForTxEd @MrDCav As a military family member, I was particularly unimpressed… https://t.co/dAGhzERCNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 10 year old cousin in Honduras asked me to teach her English 😭💕 I will be an English teacher on Friday afternoons 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/CzL1wbilHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The earth is reading your life but heaven has already finished your story.  John-Gray]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeysIrishPower @joeymcintyre @WaitressMusical @NKOTB @GMA Have fun! Miss you too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up and wasn’t in a bad mood. Decided to take a snow day and go back to sleep - only to wake up to someone repe… https://t.co/UdFbbbkJFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Much like Isaac Newton, I have gotten way further in life because I stand on the shoulders of some really gorgeous,… https://t.co/JN91gGx9Hz]]></document><document><![CDATA[before men to attract their notice; by doing this you will lose all reward from your Father in heaven.” The three p… https://t.co/W1zNx69eC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was in Hawaii I’m our Catamaran cruise some girls did this and it’s honestly soooo nice. I didn’t even ask 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job is now open at HMSHost in #Lawn, PA. Follow us and turn on mobile alerts to hear about jobs like these as… https://t.co/uBLfcxEFgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods watching you and @RobertDowneyJr in True Believer.  Loved you then and love you now! Thanks for hav… https://t.co/IeMSMzZzUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sometimesHg ok I Stan the minimal makeup she wears for her deposition too. Hair pulled back, no dark eye shadow, c… https://t.co/TU5ou2kqEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjauthor ?  What was contempt of court?  Nothing happened to him did it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all remember her from zoey 101? I used to hate this annoying Bitch, always crying for no reason. Now I am her 😐 https://t.co/8w3ftL1JE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how busy I am or what I am doing,  when this comes on...I have to watch!  #DNA will always hold such a sp… https://t.co/xEDN482BW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marylangbein @MelodyThomasSco Go to https://t.co/7rlEOgvu0j you cDNA watch it there!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHordenchuk @jimknight99 @ChaptersInt @zurichfan @bobbidc10 @Stef_Chisholm @RichardsEricJ @miss_topophilia… https://t.co/UvOO5bwW2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody loves Gossip Girl as much as I do and their wardrobe 💜💘 #itsovernow @ La Verne, California https://t.co/Vm1dZNiB56]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last weekend was a great weekend being with family and cheering carter_kucera on at state wrestling. Hard to believ… https://t.co/xWbQ9xaIQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[A major scandal for the Liberals the year of the federal election.. count me in!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta mentally prep for her cutting seasons...Gotta get some patience!!! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[He knows where that record of "Achievement" is.  Go get it. Release it. Be a hero for America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do carnivores drink Kombucha? “Asking for a friend.” D’oh! @siobhan_huggins @KetoAurelius @CarnivoreKeto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods That whole thing was sick to watch, she’s lying and you can see it all over her face… https://t.co/Uqof10Hd9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVLCraig @robreiner Never because Trump is doing a great job! Pelosi has lost control.....the dems are divided. Fi… https://t.co/qxD3YNHAsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@komondors @krassenstein Fortunately the wall building will be tied up in litigation for years and likely never get… https://t.co/at7DinQv9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[187 de la Constitución Venezolana numeral 11 : sin atribuciones de la AN pedir la intervención de un ejército extra… https://t.co/6CUYjNv4cf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always thankful to learn from and work alongside smart, strong and fantastic women at @WBTWNews13! ❤️ #IWD2019… https://t.co/rXwlowmmCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[how u gon boast abt how much u love ur gf and then constantly talk abt what guy hit on u out in public today or wha… https://t.co/q6Xf8H2M9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY IS THIS SO FUCKING FUNNY OML a true commodity   Rrreeeee @VolocoApp https://t.co/xflRL02eaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚚 Like our photos...Follow our IG 🚛  These photos were taken by me! Photography by: Connie Wheeler @WheelerConnie… https://t.co/blb7QJQVu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solo finalists at the Showtime competition for @MHSBelles are Macy Self, Ede Rogers, Emily Cook, and the SOLO CHAMP… https://t.co/6S0ZGdyn5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pink_About_it I still do not know where Obama got this money and did the Democratic Congress approve the transfer? I smell a rat!!!😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleDanielle97 I just have to go to class tonight and my roommates car just got stuck in the drive 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @NTMCounseling to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations-just covers. Each t… https://t.co/0wfk4coHNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I was heading to an event at #sxsw and I ran into @joelcomm  . So what you may not know, is that I have known J… https://t.co/1SSEkFQkyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twist up, light it, get ready for natural healing. ❤️💛💚 #cannabissavedmylife #freetheweed #plantsoverpills https://t.co/Esv0t6Imcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlynne32 Colton just doesn't randomly go to the gym with Cassie's sister's boyfriend Gregg Sulkin. Colton is with… https://t.co/mUoMLy8ykA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mads_Waller1 For the sale on his website he used this subject line for the last push email: “ValenTIME’s almost up… https://t.co/GkextALw7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big part of our problem is that we define intelligence within someone as them having opinions that coincide with… https://t.co/RheMkY20GN]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @youtheremehere nods at you approvingly in a review meeting. https://t.co/zg8j6FoWTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracías a los @CaballerosYDamas Qué me felicitaron por el día International de la mujer!!!!👏👏👏👏👍👍👍👍  Para todos ell… https://t.co/4n57HfJbPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acejordan23 @Americareform especially when he had no problem slapping handcuffs on SHARON who he supposedly loves!… https://t.co/X6u2EzAB35]]></document><document><![CDATA[i still can’t believe that people will repost pics on insta with the caption “accidentally deleted this” like sis t… https://t.co/mUzeOdBGCM]]></document></documents></author>