<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WasatchSnow I’m really disappointed in ol man weather this week. I’m finally coming out to shred @Snowbird and the… https://t.co/zJrtvLPwL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Cryo-hydrus by @TwoTidesBrewing @ Two Tides Brewing Co. — https://t.co/YQ5ynqMMex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrAnneCarpenter I like saline gel and for longer flights I use a fabric mask of some sort (since I seem to become… https://t.co/RYd0If6LKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[(3) Refs put the ball in play. No one noticed or said anything. Keep an eye on this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #CBJ will NOT make the playoffs and should be absolutely ashamed that they’re just not getting beat but getting… https://t.co/NSTKQsb5HI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time hanging out with @lwcmobile Pastors @sullivan_brad and themarysullivan @ Dawes, Alabama https://t.co/6YBwNNiLRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someday I just love the internet and how it’s allowed me to meet so many awesome people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamYouTube @BallingerMom @YouTube @YTCreators @PhillyD I've got a question, @teamyoutube, did advertisers complai… https://t.co/GCL9Lng2Su]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaomiKritzer @FOLIVER4U  Like many, I despise Andrew Cuomo but I fear he’s right about this, and that going full t… https://t.co/PmukE330Lb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutOfRegister @Rparisee @ShawnG927 @KimberlyMrsRR1 @RedWingGrips @CajunChick25 @Maggieb1B @SiddonsDan @GeanineC… https://t.co/lQyXDvjlf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dian5  "What's THIS? People are discovering that abortion really is murder after all?" https://t.co/m1rhwt2wjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[As well they should be they are they to report what happens not make comments or protest!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanSkreens @AllenKessler Yeah, that's bad.  Didn't look at the picture.  Thought the way he said it meant he had won the hand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most #inspirational thing i've seen today. @ Neutral Zone https://t.co/Io1BC5vwjA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Media371 @NiagaraMedics @Ornge @NiagRegPolice You forgot the multiple punches to the face, kicks and butt end of a rifle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyBlestLNP @LancasterOnline It is difficult to compare apples to apples since each municipality records the e… https://t.co/KZvINKet8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Wish Mfers Would Tell Me Whats On Their Mind Instead Of Playing The Guessung Game 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskThePatrick @ThomasHall17 Senators have never been resourced for that kind of work and do not maintain offices i… https://t.co/R703YgjJGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye, @Stu_Mundel, always such a pleasure to tell people we’re on the same team.  Great work as usual. https://t.co/MgaULqfvEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zo_EP2 @zo_ep @AbbottCardio Great. Will give it a go! Maybe we can turn this into standard practise in our lab for… https://t.co/3mDFaRLroM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beantowndougish @tianjin1980 @JonAnthony7 @MynameisMok @woodywood1999 @someone_1958 @wolflayla420 @KingPeachDP… https://t.co/3X82XwxHiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trend Vision 2020 - Best of Trend Vision 2020 | Watch the full episode here: https://t.co/BJ4wCXQvDF https://t.co/jjwsmpBbBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still haven’t taken off. Some engine issue. Going back to the gate so it can be looked at.  Lol  Jesus fuck  Awesome job @SpiritAirlines]]></document><document><![CDATA[True that, however, Steph still turns ball over too much, makes undisciplined passes more than player with his expe… https://t.co/Rq1ROj1JGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 301 East 2ND Street #LeafRiver #IL  #realestate https://t.co/IYWbTjWqMN  RE/MAX of Rock Valley]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drkristinek Think: who is number one? You, Why? You have opportunity to create a tease, firt, &amp; anticipation in any subject.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wrestlerweekly @OldWrestlingPic @OxBakerJR @tappedoutpod @bobbynorton9115 @OfficialPWI @Wrestlingwclass @JZ_Flair… https://t.co/89r0SyWR4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@butr0s Still in search of the right word. “Meatbags” feels a little aggressive to me 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remembering Nitro Drag Racing Legend Frank Rupert https://t.co/Ig2is0m8uY @hotrodmagazine https://t.co/iw55k43X6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamfnaughton @trippier2 He’s had as many shots on target as do Chelski.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSkipBayless Skip, this is such a dumb post. We get it, you’re playing a character, but sometimes you need to relax.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kikoescamilla @revistaetcetera @SergioMayerb Como cualquier mexicano bien nacido.]]></document><document><![CDATA[just ate a whole can of diced peaches .... only meant to take a few bites .... whoooops 🤣🤣 lmfaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EatSleepTrain_ Thought we all needed some sarcasm ! Keep up the outstanding work, Coach !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acevonjohnson time for a winter BBQ -16 outside https://t.co/RiEIRRSbEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PGAdfsmikelara @lullekbh @seraphicpetal @EmmyStar79 @megan_thescript @What_A_Dame_42 https://t.co/LtmSK2wqRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 30th bday @ajRAFAEL ! Thank you for everything you've done and being a big inspiration to myself and many oth… https://t.co/sDo81IU2dq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep Wasserman Schultz is asking if Ivanka, Don Jr, and Jared Kushner has knowledge of Wikileak emails prior to release #MichaelCohen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shadow7591 i (unironically) blame forces. mania had so much hype, it was one of the best sonic games since sonic 3… https://t.co/AXvFwIJiih]]></document><document><![CDATA[El problema de dar subsidio a desempleo. Nadie quiere trabajar. @vanesavallejo3 @cmbustamante @LuchyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt feeling the love in Oakland... 🤘🏼 . .  #muse #muser #simulationtheory #simulationtheoryworldtour #oakland @ Or… https://t.co/9GxTtMoZvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SgtBuzzkillmsp @kirk1778 @GMA @Disney @RobertIger @starwars @Disneyland @WaltDisneyWorld I have no plans, I'm just… https://t.co/Utzn6uHPOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOtherMarioC @red_stylo @kickstarter You know if you’re in it I’m all about it!! 👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kokoroco25 @goodenough_fu That’s my Dream Queen Girl Friend, I sure like this beautiful woman ⭐️❤️💯😍💖⭐️❤️💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall its 2019 can we not just stand around as a guy gets mad disrespectful just because he got rejected every dude… https://t.co/bkVbTs4mFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaySteeleRTV6 I do miss Indy😁😁. I’ll remember these comments when you make it to upper management lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[List of singers who attended #LimpBizkit’s “Three Dollar Show Y’all” (besides @freddurst):  -@marilynmanson -@Billy… https://t.co/Vi5SwjK8u3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope he wasn’t being called out for a bad drop or his caddie standing in a bad spot on his approach shot into #18… https://t.co/7QmCyk0zmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@JoshConstine asks crowd to hiss if they hate the Instagram algorithm.  #Entire room hisses  .@Kevin “Thanks”   #sxsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big sky country... It ate my car and now I'm flying out. Thanks, Montana you're beautiful but I'm glad to be leavin… https://t.co/vjjBEs8vzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Tia just did a limpia on our house &amp; it feels so calm &amp; serene in here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cancel the Uber. Next stop, the boardroom 🔋#Houston #REI @ Midtown, Houston https://t.co/Kb6031twt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@townhallcom WTH is wrong with the #Democrats ?!? @DNC  How can you buy a gun if you are #IllegalAliens ?… https://t.co/ssC9qymsxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@middlebrooks That goes for every day life. Love your family and friends because you never know. 2nd chances are hard to come by.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bust of a woman, pastel on paper, 2019. https://t.co/P8xKvvmRGp  #art #artistauruguayo #artecontemporaneouruguayo… https://t.co/KIU9XShjsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Queen and the King of the Seven Seas!! Helen Mirren and Jason Momoa!! #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcJSpearsESPN @DetroitPistons @Raptors Marc lol you are the 1st to recognize DETROITBASKETBALL on the National s… https://t.co/iPGJVsv6re]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigMikeY3587 @Donald_Wood @BGNY3 @RingRustRadio Never... Danny Briere &gt; Antonio Brown]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at San Francisco North / Petaluma KOA - @sanfranciscokoa in Petaluma, CA https://t.co/6SNKNg3JMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@polishprincessh @Digidiva2018 She is a narcissist who lies like she breathes, lacking the basic tools needed to re… https://t.co/uBMifxy4OH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianMarlatt @DonMartinCTV @Puglaas @cforcese @PCParty1867 Wonderful, but I hope that you don’t equate party affil… https://t.co/0Xg3GsIqBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisSeelbach @Enquirer You are a disrespectful politician and should resign. Horrible example of a leader. You la… https://t.co/t07pZ1Pn5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of the first quarter, Wilson and Pine-Richland tied 24-24 #berksgameday #PIAABasketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wear them like 5/7 days of the week trust me u need them. Also I’m borderline a midget and they aren’t super fucking long on me!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz Hey, Goober, resign and delete your entire Twitter, you fucking colossal embarrassment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just looked at the forecast. Got a little excited when I saw some yellow peaking out on Wednesday...It was a lightning bolt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @dunkindonuts guy. When I ordered a soy latte and your response was: “sorry we don’t have soy milk, but we have… https://t.co/7b0fItDvj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you forgot what your first sip of hot chocolate tasted like!!! #hotchocolate #milkchocolate #hotcocoa… https://t.co/nlEqv5EToZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PittNarduzzi Yes of course. And I keep shouting ‘Karen!!!!’ For no apparent reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VasBlackwood @EditinKing That KO was Fierce Kangaroo Style! Casket ready!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that is one way to protect your head only just riding a bike not motor on it. 🤔🚴‍♂️ @ Southpark Meadows https://t.co/ufffPp9Uwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnitersCentrist It is not a nonsensical question. A good number of retirees would see their income significantly c… https://t.co/7x1pY7O3K3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSOLogan @eedwards226 That’s exactly why. That gym requires you use rubber plates in that room. That’s 315. Not ba… https://t.co/mE2lstig13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually getting a decent tax return this year. Now I gotta decide if I put it in savings, or pay off some debt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 3am and I haven’t changed out of my work clothes yet @ Georgetown, Texas https://t.co/iEWGz8l9Ds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lasagna and making a new constitution hell of a good day. https://t.co/MfLuolWne1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NedBreslin There are so many children who go to school every day hungry. Free lunch is the only meal they get. The… https://t.co/WNBoIVJOdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity I absolutely think he should declared an emergency. Most people don't realize, we already have 30 Nati… https://t.co/H9ozNcfpGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to Hamilton County Dispatch, about 6 streets remain closed due to flooding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Pro Football League Headed By Ed McCaffrey Just Might Work via @forbes https://t.co/WPS8j9e2En]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because no Va Tech players qualified?  Nothing against Red Panda - was grateful it wasn’t a player. 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joy_Villa Look 👀 at his veggie eyes 👀 “ I got to figure out how to stop 🛑 Americans from eating Hamburger 🍔 “ yikes NOOOOOOOOOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing that I didn’t get to Fuck shit up at Crush because I got too drunk.... @BeyondWland I’m coming for you full… https://t.co/W26f8qtMIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've wanted this bottle since it was announced. Johnny Walker Black is what I recommend to beginning Scotch drinker… https://t.co/X4B5d70y1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wrote an essay in primary school which was a complete rip off of the Tomb Raider II story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reesetapher @TwitchPluto (Dan) Echoing Reese on this one, we're glad you're proactive and reasonable in talking to… https://t.co/P3FTtcTYZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck today @WakeTechMBB. I’ll be cheering you on from 38,000 feet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One 💛! ☯️🌎👁️☮️😎💣!    https://t.co/92qDM8wrwo https://t.co/Vyc0Ayb72M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@we_r_Psymese @DdVoyeur @VAGirlsmom @machalo0712 @806_sharon @ColbaltGooGal @Seahawksgal81 @naughty1loveb… https://t.co/G4v5pAuzzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beating up the Monday scaries like 🥊🙌🏻 Go check out our website at the link in our bio. • • • • • #boxing… https://t.co/WfeGQ8fJ37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DynoDangle @palffynyi16 @Dynamo6719 @CarverHighCBS Possession means nothing if you don't do anything about it. Whe… https://t.co/3jgUA9QRxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aside from the great front page headlines and photos this is another reason why you should read the @nypost.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Phora said “ I pray for you, she said I love you but I need to stay away from you” I felt that..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asking for easing of 180 day rule, reasonable cause exception, time to become an active business, 12 months safe ha… https://t.co/N9kHx6aXhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Training Monday Nights realpremiercombatcenter Foundations Boxing and nlbjja CAP BJJ 🥊🥋 "Building People into Bette… https://t.co/l60XwMBoig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music class every Saturday! Be sharp. We start at 10am first come first serve...bring your #instrument if you have… https://t.co/Rk7vYeH2Jy]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Kentucky can pass a law where you don’t have to have a license to carry a gun with no problem but have to think… https://t.co/Ddeoy6shJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do it now, sometimes tomorrow never comes. Take the first step towards your goal, achieve those great accomplishmen… https://t.co/yLls0l8iAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“All of us have greatness within. Some of us become so envious on what others have we lose sight of ourselves. Inst… https://t.co/tMW3BM91mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIRD ROUND GIRLS   Luella Lady Lions appear to be putting this one away - start third qtr in a 7-0 run - their hei… https://t.co/z6S308iDYY]]></document></documents></author>