<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jdbarker It’s that Leap Frog puppy’s fault! It whispers to them when you are not looking]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Boston's Tyler Caldwell and South Webster's Shiloah Blevins have been awesome all game. All game. Both playing… https://t.co/WqAlR7ELlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_in_DC Absolutely. I think they could be go in individually too, but glad at least this is happening now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Unrefined (Batch 10)  by @voodoobrewery at @voodoobrewery — https://t.co/lw1KnkfH69]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spokesman for @NYGovCuomo says he’s been a “tireless champion for immigrant communities,” but last week he pretende… https://t.co/msc3ATSl8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Washington Gov Jay Inslee ever give us here in NH a decent response to this? https://t.co/1GCmF6irw7  #FITN #nhpolitics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JT_Bangkadang Love you bro. Keep your head held high. Hit me up if you ever need anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterKash Steven Avery is 1000 % cant wait for him to be the 18th person freed because of @ZellnerLaw #faccts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryenarussillo Vendetta officiating is bullshit. I can’t stand the Warrior bitching, especially Green. But Jesus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings @morningmika This guy doesn’t do anything but holler Racist! Bad as Mad Max. You guys are in shambles.… https://t.co/YawZwWnN8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tayy_bayy22 Hey, no worries, time to start another one! Tomorrow is a new day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomselliott @ElizabethJudy2 Get this clown 🤡 out of here. He’s be playing the victim for years. He dislikes white… https://t.co/bm31KBjL6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very heavy Greenway crowd inside the X. No Cathedral band makes this music lite affair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoucBigalow @Prince_Dartez that mean u would have to stay in the car or go to miami moon😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[on-the-go snack.. . . . #me #nyc #live #now #lchf #post #keto #ketoaf #meal #snack #vibes #butter #ketolife… https://t.co/BvZi6XJ7nI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKarem @realDonaldTrump @PressSec makes you wonder who else he has ordered them to be issued to without process]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiesgamecrner @StrongholdGames @MarkGerrits Welcome To from @DeepWaterGames and Railroad Ink from… https://t.co/nwyGj6FQMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will people understand that I do not care what others think because I know how I feel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFExplosion The northwest is awesome danger.  Hope your enjoying my neck of the woods]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was one of the best moments in my college career!  Blew the roof off CHA!  💨 @TomBrandsHAWK told us before tha… https://t.co/rA8ZVqQEPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Briefing by a Sentinel from the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier at @ArlingtonNatl for the middle school I am guiding th… https://t.co/bO8Wt8ljKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckinzie_sharon @IAmTreyDrama @WhiteHouse Why wasn’t he patriotic when it was his time to serve? He was a draft dodger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember seeing one of these a few years back in Montreal...glad we don’t need that today! https://t.co/0p5RyeYdBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onetermcongress @kippaxcity73 @realDonaldTrump have enormous numbers of illegal voting and also have enormous numb… https://t.co/DSmO07zRxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it me or many goals are scored against us  when Mete is defending? #Habs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ms_Mayfield @_Trappucino Unpopular opinion: I don’t think humans are meant to have one mate for life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mental Renewal: #1-  We can not move ahead in our spiritual life until truly we admit where we are.  Psalm 51:2-4 #Slamism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump the definition of “corrupt” is NOT “someone who disagrees with you”]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it's time for action against women slavery in Saudi Arabia Mr Pence or the killer.   Pence says 'it's time' for… https://t.co/x7W8lElybj]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Orlando: few clouds, 69°F 56% humidity, wind 17mph, pressure 1026mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KASDad Remember the Bawl Street Journal that came  out on April Fools Day?  They had fake tombstone ads for Murder… https://t.co/M1KzUCvGsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetimes That beef is way to raw to be English. Needs 3-4 more hours of cooking]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar @RepMarkMeadows So yesterday really was just playing to the cameras as a run up to this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anna_bokus Articles are easy to write when you're working with amazing people. He was truly a gift to work with an… https://t.co/zV0oSRSEtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#possibility #mindset #positivity #wisdom #truth #jeffreybyron   Aroma! ❤️ @ Century City, Los Angeles https://t.co/XdCB2RPMPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just took off my clothes, I'm nude now. I will be fully nude until Sunday night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreeSunshinee_ ...😐... Oh... Hmm... I'm Detective Beasley👮. I guess I'm happy for you but... Where's he from...? .… https://t.co/PD3Rc6nREg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sburt3365 That’s not accurate. MLB trade rumored projected Machado to get 13 years and $390. Harper is there for t… https://t.co/aensBJozIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsmarymi @h3h3productions His story of manipulating the family to get access, the way they describe the grooming,… https://t.co/gZ2mHQ9seO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Client: AHC+hospitality / JW Marriott #ilovethejw @ JW Marriott Grand Rapids https://t.co/HucqtdGFxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BerthaLila3 Muchas gracias Bertha e igualmente para ti pero hoy toca mariscos , jajaja cuídate mucho saludos cordiales,!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courtside at Portland Expo for Class A South girls basketball quarterfinal between No. 3 @mhshawks (14-4) and No. 6… https://t.co/Gva0Umw16A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner (@ Jack in the Box - @jackbox in San Diego, CA) https://t.co/lBTdoOAsGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh I dont think anyone has toits clear that he is mentally incapable of carrying out the duties of @POTUS.… https://t.co/N3uZg6eXw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Randall Shreve during the finale of his tribute to Freddie Mercury last weekend.  . . @randallshreve #randallshreve… https://t.co/kjRo2WzSN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonlk For sure.  2019 was the first time the Quality of Venue fit the Quality of Content.  My 4th year. And the… https://t.co/IHR7PFulxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided to watch a magnetometer when a WMATA 7000 series train accelerated. https://t.co/VBfPmpu2Yz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinLudden @MichaelAvenatti Or a child out of wedlock! Could you imagine if the child is a brown person!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of y’all clearly didn’t keep your birthday wishes to yourselves and it shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryantDenny_UA Me either. @JalenHurts bringing that Beast Mode to OU.  Hope he wins em all.  Except vs #Bama… https://t.co/Vn1bNU9abz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP good time for it, he is hoping for hoping for new news to happen in the next 8 hours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cookie dough eaten last night was not good enough to outweigh today’s repercussions.  #liveandlearn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little clip from today. Track was mint! @ Tomahawk MX Park https://t.co/ZIdK8Iu2Ww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattNBCBoston Good ❄️snowy❄️morning Matt! Stoneham has received 2.0" of snow so far as of 5am. Temp: 27; DP: 27; W… https://t.co/3hLu26zo7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing with #Regis staff and teachers for their retreat today. #Prayerswelcome @ Fr. Bernard Youth Center https://t.co/KnJ3Xth0PZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Bible is gods word and is instructions for humanity, why do you need another human to interpret it for you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alien_rogue @MPaulkovich @_MrsAtheist_ Cuz you have all seen all the facts. No? Hpw do you know they are facts?… https://t.co/ysDUDxkBOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure why Honey is all tuckered out. She didn’t drive to Tucson and back.  Need a nap, those solo trips get tiri… https://t.co/EJaDwOsZuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomsims @EdwardJDale I'm stuck at a rest stop. @APompliano  has liked me wanting to do a documentary w/Medium. Now… https://t.co/jNO7Vw1Una]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Ja Morant did not get more recruitment letters? I will never know. This dude is a bucket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As Luis mentioned, Jose Ureña, Miami’s Opening Day starter March 28, will get the nod today against Tampa Bay. Firs… https://t.co/Ka8qjqKG9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turned on game &amp; #Duke were losing by 20 with about 6 mins left. Unreal comeback !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess it's easier to admit people are stupid than to coach them up. Another bad look for NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[💀💀💀 @cwrobinson92 @UpAtHalftimeBy3 @jinx0511 @ThinLineRemix @rayrock3000 #ATW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obianuju There is no BILL OF RIGHTS, i .e.  Freedom of Speech, anyplace place on the planet. The UK does not tolerate free speech.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wore a Spice Girls shirt to school in 2nd grade and, after i got relentlessly teased, I cried and made my mom bri… https://t.co/hur4Es8Dwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zermatt_tourism E guete Tag und es schön's kommend's Wuchenendi us sonnenscheini #SouthernCalifornia. Swiss women… https://t.co/DipqacgEkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSandusky_TCC @BoozyBadger Boy howdy that’s true. There is definitely no such thing as too much ammo in West Virgi… https://t.co/GmdjEMLDPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@collegeftbfan @JimbruhF Y'all LOSERS thumped your chests for months on end about being ahead on Rivals, then when… https://t.co/x1Ex6bxCQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarryWBZ @wpbf_sandra @MichaelPageWx @PeteNBCBoston @Met_CindyFitz @ShiriSpear @JackieLayerOn7 @sarahwroblewski… https://t.co/uDKJ29zQ7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never get ready anymore, so when I do I post selfies 🤷‍♀️ https://t.co/333Lkq3C3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack We revolt against the dumbest collection of numnuts to ever hold office in our congress]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump I think you would be more suited for Moscow. However there is an ocean you will have… https://t.co/KOK0oqnT2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texans upbeat about Will Fuller's recovery from torn ACL https://t.co/KORsC7OJ4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@jwestMSHSAA High School State Wrestling Championship is underway here  @KOMUsports https://t.co/wm1lsEZHF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @marthamaccallum we didn't have a serious problem with race relations in America until  President Obama .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Memories please. #faithful #RIP #cedricHardman @NBCS49ers @49ers @instant49ers]]></document><document><![CDATA[to get inside to search for the hot spot source of fire, it was necessary to make a hole on the roof to ventilation… https://t.co/f8nn0JQT6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodUnitPoll @sportsfanTaos Mans game on FS1.  Guys are getting after it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost POPE FRANCIS THiS.        .NoTE       FRAmericARF   A-FRAMEHouSAE       LeGA-LTende/R NOTNAMINGNAME… https://t.co/qkkTk6XtKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[You wish. You’re not any funnier, Batman. You’re just happier and at peace with yourself.  And you’ve always been s… https://t.co/FwNwLjulhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[America is not a Mob rule democracy but a republic where minorities are protected from the will of the majority]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appropriate glare on these pictures of #ctastatecouncil educators meeting with Assemblymember @QuirkSilva2018 about… https://t.co/YTE6pkJ3Ly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a sad and sorry picture.  However,  this is what America represents. "This is America "!  #ADOS101.com]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsungSupport can I get back my old camera? S9 update removed portrait editing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Wilcock: Stunning NEW Antarctic SSP Insiders! LIVE (2/23, 4PM PT!) https://t.co/S89FlCGlAv via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Whitney had a great time at Station Square and South Hills Village today. #pittsburgh #stationsquare… https://t.co/0qBxxWIbZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huh, this is the first incompatibility I’ve heard of, are there others?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The boy in the striped pajamas is on Netflix, but I dont know if I can put myself thru that movie ever again. 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 years of links to my Instagram posts 👌🏼 #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/kelILZGUKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photo Twitter: So worth following @elodiemailliet.  The work she is doing at @catchlight_io is helping transform th… https://t.co/bNpUxivmV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[How callous do you have to be to complain about an Amber Alert?  What a world whe we are more worried about inconve… https://t.co/Q7V5cL4t45]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just screamed “Period” soo loud I woke up my 5th grade English teacher]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KKluver @tony_chapman76 Class A model wouldn’t work for class B because of travel distances between schools. Or so we are told.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZephyrsFootball @barkley_33 Damn he dont even look that big that's good]]></document><document><![CDATA[reckon they have bowed down and fallen, but we have risen and stand upright, the source has given him the desire of… https://t.co/9hESp5Nv6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pcornell2 @canesvoice The betting line in Vegas was moving around quite a bit it ended up closing out Miami favored by 5 1/2]]></document><document><![CDATA[And PS- if you’re ever stuck...you’re screwed. No tow, no sheriffs, no nothing. Thankfully a random neighbor with a… https://t.co/r88sDnBnyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[PBR at Capitol, a vegan bar in PDX! @ Capitol Bar https://t.co/JSVxUrta2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REALNEWMACINC @JohnnyMac52199 Getting back at him over the fight he had with the 2 somebody’s?]]></document></documents></author>