<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@joshwolfcomedy @BrodyismeFriend @TheComedyStore Thanks josh, I remembered after the fact. #stonermoment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so annoyed, bored and uncomfortable that I just chewed off most of my nails on my right hand. 😳😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup, surprise! I'm on a TV show episode (@24HoursFOX) with @GordonRamsay so that means I'm too famous now. 😉😋  Also… https://t.co/dI3NJn64WJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve gotten so many dirty looks bc of my camo crocs but fuuugggggiiitttt, i’m in vegas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never too late to get a few more dubs. #fortniteFridays  Road to 100 wins - [21/100] https://t.co/pTrxXFmTtY via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok I’m gonna need miss swift to slow down bc I’m still paying off my pit ticket igngbkhbjhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pam_houston at @FactFictionBook!! I first saw this woman read when Mia was only a few months old, and I remember a… https://t.co/J2HrZSO27u]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was today years old when i figured out that a shock is called a shock bc when you get shocked by something it shocks you (scares you lol)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ppl Funny Bro 😂🤦🏾‍♂️ This Camera Shit is not a Hobby it my occupation my hustle whatever you wanna call it so yes i… https://t.co/XRvKnhszCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of ya’ll posting vacation pictures can suck my ass. About to block every single one of you bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffDuncan_ @GawnPecawn Not to be ~that~ person, but I wrote about it on Monday.   https://t.co/wM5P7e6lMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus, like the pay isn’t terrible and it’s a guaranteed 40 hours a week]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at this charming waterfront seaside home in Old Greenwich.  This is one of the last original waterfront homes… https://t.co/rW1nHCzXWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE seeing athletes progress through their rehab from their ACL surgeries 👏🏼😭 Keep pushing y’all! You’re doing great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JarrodWiggins Campaign estimates were 800 for Warren and 1,000 for Harris, though both may have been slightly smal… https://t.co/4fnealoy6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping for a miracle win. Lady Raiders need a perfect game to pull off the win but they have enough heart and momen… https://t.co/Ifn41IFkgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inside the Bates Mill in Lewiston, you'll find @baxterbrewing, which kept a lot of original mill features in its sp… https://t.co/1kw0Plqopz]]></document><document><![CDATA[LeBron came to the Lakers to 'build his brand' not win titles. But he hasn't handled the struggles well and he cert… https://t.co/i0coizduJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derrick_daKidD People already doing that. All over organization because they think he won . The best wide receiver… https://t.co/dpcTlGumua]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a new gallery coming to town! District Arts Gallery opens in historic Frederick, MD. Grand opening event is… https://t.co/0xTrsOroES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day! And just remember you should be sweet to those you care about every day not just one day a ye… https://t.co/BLY4tmCM7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… My Blood by Twenty One Pilots https://t.co/Ey5ZqE74tb]]></document><document><![CDATA[These little digital microscopes are so fun they make me forget I’m the teacher! Today my 5th graders took pictures… https://t.co/FASGHkwfFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally am not exaggerating at how hard I’m crying at shameless right now. the letter, the plane, are u fucking kidding me?!!!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Double Bastard Ale by @ArrogantBastard @ Stone Company Store — https://t.co/eb3JMIoE20]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why don’t #proteins have their own Twitter accounts? I’d totally follow Notch and p53 to see what they’re up to...… https://t.co/gSofLBpY1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[These leadership training initiatives whose goal is to ensure our organizations have many diverse voices at the tab… https://t.co/i1VGliG5lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first step in getting what you want, is having the courage to get rid of what you don’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just can’t get it wrapped around my head how some females can just talk to someone’s man knowing 🗣 he is someone’s man 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rottzillasgirl @CodyShaneWare @KodakPlus @RickWareRacing @Kodak @amsupdates Your welcome Rebekka 🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man hopped on the subway tracks to rescue my cell phone. It was a blackberry pearl and I was wearing these amazin… https://t.co/wgajc89wJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ziah reminded me how crazy i was tonight...   she remembered...  #realitycheck #mentalhealth #bipolardisorder… https://t.co/tUopalzlqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're stupid drumpy jr. Aww.. everyone. Come look at lil drumpy jr. Getting the attention he craves. Aww.. getting… https://t.co/MbhNiz0yzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity You realy are a low life ,attacking the very peaple that protect you. What does trump have on you. It must be good .]]></document><document><![CDATA[summoning circle, hope this works                          🕯               🕯              🕯         🕯            It… https://t.co/jN0qxK5xy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Will this start impacting the Athletic scholarships for WOMEN? Nobody recruits losers. Does that me… https://t.co/wk7RmYnWk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askmrsmartinez Maybe some paper folding to see equivalence? https://t.co/HxR07u0Dm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting my workout in. Getting ready for the spring/summer season #bballlife Coach Q.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemSellouts @RepShalala @SenSanders @jguaido Bring called an idiot by a Russian troll is so 2016.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The systems that serve young LGBTQ people are broken in every city. These young people need their basic needs ley f… https://t.co/cXJW95pnoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You get overwhelmed when its a whole bunch of shows on @hulu you have to catch up on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodreads I would be sitting inside my home reflecting over my life  #ThroughTheValley written by @Write4Jesus1 https://t.co/2ggcXgzOEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ. It was a fucking back pass. My 10 year old club team doesn’t even do that shit. Man. Not impressive. #USAvENG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got a dog camera so I can spy on the doggos while I’m not home 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumaneSociety I love elephants. I keep asking my husband to get me one, but still no elephant. I wonder why he's s… https://t.co/hun99Yrkrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter What's wrong with you Ann!?  We the people want that WALL. Pelosi is ridiculously insane!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My album Ether Fever by @evillainmusic, originally released in 2016, is finally out on all platforms! Guests includ… https://t.co/GzcfFUv9a5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so f’d up! On the eve of the day I’ve become obsessed with going to Istanbul!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC The Trumpeter is one good teller of tales... No collusion? What would you call it Mr. Trumpster?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fist look like i fucked a bitch up last night but i don’t think i fought... 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Icryduringsex Dude go to the hospital. There is such thing as walking pneumonia. You’ve been saying you’ve sick for a min. Go bro go]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you live at an island you get a little tan when you live in New England you have to pay for the tan,  a few ye… https://t.co/w4CSuxQFBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to hold Wilder last night! He never woke up!! Melts my heart!! 💙💙💙🤗🤗 #love #grandbaby #cutenessoverload… https://t.co/d6TugqitKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cabaret Night   #menschoir #fatherlydutieswithcris @ Hacienda Heights, California https://t.co/EXg4YC53xW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet Mayor, Sima Kumasi Chhetri from #Nepal! Sima noted that her greatest challenge is to meet expectations with li… https://t.co/zRX6vHV9q1]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I'm sitting in the overflow section for media and the vendor behind us is making chorizo with veggies. Is it halftime, yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home filled with drugs, guns discovered during arrest of three people: https://t.co/ctGwoTrfQW https://t.co/AGJaewKN0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should spend all the money we have raised for this stupid wall on somthing like a massive ocean clean up. Becaus… https://t.co/OVPtNfyG7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[So awesome to read another great review of Doom Patrol, especially Matt Bomer’s portrayal of Larry Trainor.… https://t.co/zgiUGn3BjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go check out my old army buddy dudes funny and talks more shit than my wife #streamer #TwitchAffilate #PCGamer]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Joe Biden he has the experience we need to fix the disaster trumptard has created]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gubich76 @LiveAtFirefly @ToriGeiger Even better, she about to win every one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rexthetvterrier Don't worry Rex all the Kool people are Democrats.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Itsbriiiiiiii See y’all all kinda backwards 😂 I showered when I got home and THEN lounged around]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to take these twists down bc my hair is dirty, but idk how I want my hair next...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaChepely @gevinella @Alyssa_Milano @TuckerCarlson I read your “somewhat morbid” bio. Lol. I’m a writer. My poet… https://t.co/1Ik4rj32Ot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alicecaviglia @FLOTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse https://t.co/6xZW4w2kJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonBJanney @AnnaKFaris watching the latest episode of Mom! Omg this one makes me laugh and cry at the same tim… https://t.co/6M1TlV1kEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duh_adriana Cut back on caffeine / alcohol. Notice what triggers it and try to avoid and develop ways to slowly ease it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN I don’t know why people think this guy is going to give away what has been passed down from his grandfather to… https://t.co/dV25pijgVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesPPierce Argh. I put him in same category as Howard Schultz. Please go away already. If Biden doesn't get th… https://t.co/zEoOsbnkGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your administration has committed crimes against humanity by kidnapping children from their parents.  RETURN THE CH… https://t.co/Z2e7tVnR2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[11:30 PM hair looks perfect. But tomorrow it’ll look crazy #LifeProblems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonRedeker A1 my classroom is eclectic- so I may have to say the a movie representation of my room  is a mix betwe… https://t.co/n0YXZgxocM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gay pastors kid. He’s got a spot in heaven I think. As long as he believes Jesus did come and died on the cross… https://t.co/Zo1JTKHlft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBruceTrp773 @BreitbartNews Right ...misunderstood question...sure you did😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[#enjoylife❤️ #withmysweetie #spendmylifeliving #walkabout @ Tolomato Cemetery https://t.co/guqNY3iNP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyberadam26 Sorry i went back to my room; arthritis/fibro needed a rest. I've got lots left, though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KISDHlthSvc nurses across the State recognized for their service to the Lone Star State! #schoolnurses]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine The problem is when u dealing with Idiots always going to be idiots]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living in Florida makes me appreciate the snow so much more! I love it here but I can’t wait to be back in 80+ degr… https://t.co/RlFbyzGH6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews @realDonaldTrump is our 21st Century MANCHURIAN PRESIDENT, handled by PUPPET MASTER Putin!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harsher sentences for animal cruelty! - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/0or6PyKSrW via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next they're taking away our toothpicks! Ahhhhh!!! Don't even suggest the mints dish at the hostess's counter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegreghansen He’s speaking in philly in March or April on a random weekday and tix are still available.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@voomvoomk  I have to write now here, because I don't want that he find anything. Let's go on: I wrote him: you rea… https://t.co/LJLmC9gKQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandmother just saw this on the news and let me tell you... I have never seen my 92 year old gramma so disguste… https://t.co/5i70YYxihu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess we just skipped over all the black people on campus but alright UT 👍🏽 great work]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe I think too much in love which is why i don’t have a love interest or maybe I’m just not as stupid a bitch as I seem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lulekapitaj me after seeing the waiter tonight he was albo and mad fuckin cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[FREE TO GOOD HOME! 4 tickets to @bobmouldmusic at @MetroChicago tonight.   Don’t let these go to waste!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @IAmSophiaNelson Praying for her daughter and the rest of her family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jazzteamstore @vivintarena @utahjazz Send me some tickets and we will come. 😀😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the first time in a really long time I want a real relationship again but idk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou Talk about blasphemous. Guess he's taking credit for the good book too?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TartarugaTanya @SamHeughan @MyPeakChallenge @peakersrus You look fantastic Tanya😘 good for you #peaker 💪👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a few hours late. But March 1st, 2018 changed my life forever. It’s the day I started dating my best friend. Wh… https://t.co/zVidJubVaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m staying the night in Forks so plz only refer to me as Bella Swan from here on out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_baliad @glenwalkerktla @LuParker @weatherkaj @KTLA Hope you have an awesome weekend, Fred!!! 😜❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TLara4 @RandyMoss His accuser deserves to be behind bars. Lying about something like this means they filed a false… https://t.co/3rjFR13ZNQ]]></document></documents></author>