<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @dilruba_lees @DLees28 @CynthiaMark14 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best @cheryllyndunn @TBGTNT @reeves5150 G… https://t.co/dDtdQF5dBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have to fund the home their Going to while our aging parents get A reverse home loan ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A long season all comes down to this. NAC championship today! Let’s go Terriers! #everydayguys https://t.co/TPp0Jfr5Cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast for dinner is always a good thing. #FAT #nomnomnom 🍳😎 https://t.co/dVmfMFvVDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jokoy basically made my whole family’s night tonight. #breakthemoldtour https://t.co/8ZB9q3AbKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LesleyMillercyp What a mess Lesley what a mess!!!!...Britain needs a strong leader that will topple May big time.… https://t.co/DeNmYXtdgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RefinedBogan @Wishes_She_Was Twitter is so halareouse https://t.co/JslEUA8liE]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇯🇲 Coffee companies devising industry plan to court US market. #coffee #specialtycoffee #Jamaica https://t.co/zVxiLY499o via @jamaicagleaner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwendyaustin I'm sure some sort of psychopath will be mentioned somwhere. Of course, you're the doctor, not me. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my under shirt tucked into my under britches, I’m ready to whoop today and get all up into this three day weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sick as hell but still about to go grind it out all week and get this money 💵]]></document><document><![CDATA[AUTHORITY. JEWISH WAY CRIMINAL WAY. WOMANKIND SECURITY SYSTEM. INJUSTICE JURISDICTION AUTHORITY.  MR AMERICA TRUTH… https://t.co/onXPeK6vh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSeattleWeather yep.  I happened upon the best place for convergence zone snow by chance because it was only place… https://t.co/djAwO5EyaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaunceyGardner They lie for money. That alone should repulse every person on the planet from supporting them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHSPirate65 my tongue enjoys spicy foods but the rest of my body doesn’t 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandma called me to wish me a happy Valentine's Day. She ended the conversation with "treat yo self"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Country Music Hall of Fame and Museum https://t.co/z3F09Voz7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter So  the media's job is to be "shocked" every time he makes a crazy statement? If your wife made a 1,0… https://t.co/iLdBhDh2fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlotteflairq   We won. The first game.   The score for the first game  was. 36-10. And the second score was 41-… https://t.co/XMaEpvYBRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a little wine and tried to say "George R R Martin" and it came out "gerbil merfkin"]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Then came Peter to him, and said, Lord, how oft shall my brother sin against me, and I forgive him?till seven time… https://t.co/HD95ODW7rA]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/xdUShQAU7i  He wants a free ride. And 50% tax for the ‘privledge of US being there’  JFC. This is Amer… https://t.co/HS590wRcEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kareemhunt7 nothing but love for you here bro I am happy to see you back. You dont remember me but yall stayed beh… https://t.co/NgMSlbnnNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleMorrill I’ve been w/ my own co. for 11 years, so I can relate to what a transition this would be.  I would… https://t.co/BSZPZ1dNEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celtics +22 with Al Horford on the floor tonight....-16 with him out.  #ChocolateMilk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wegottoner @VegasRebs For sure. The rivalry is fun and all but we come together when needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenAtHome @robreiner  @julianzelizer Congress needs to hire anger management professionals for the Republican… https://t.co/nJk4emnIZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good point by Jeremy Weinstein: there’s whiplash in this conversation, nobody knows which institutions to trust #stanfordtechethics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chillin' &amp; Watchin' Creed." 🎥 @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/O9V0gfEr5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico How about everyone’s personal right to not get infected by a non-vaxxer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 There is something we can do to keep Schultz from playing the spoiler role and syphoning votes from the… https://t.co/4AzKEjKHMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImNotABot17 @AndrewGillum Nice spelling.  Maybe Trump can help make spelling great again too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mickey is the best much too late but well deserved. Trigger is a national treasure and the sound of Mickeys harmoni… https://t.co/uaMG2zKRXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Of course.  They do not want to be called on lies.  But the GOP will not cut our CNN and MSNBC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBlountSports any good BBQ on the peninsula you found? Have you tried the BBQ2U in gig harbor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HRMRobertBruce @KyleClark @Rossputin Oh... now you're all about "false complaints" when you also condone "deport a… https://t.co/mcH8rK4Q4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@legalissue @DavidAFrench Uh, no. What capitalism does is move money through many hands as it seeks its most productive use.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Passport2Dreams Or even a willingness to admit that there are things you don’t know. Even if you don’t care to lea… https://t.co/Z25teteWHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez responds after report accuses her of 'Green New Deal' hypocrisy: 'I also fly &amp; use A/C'… https://t.co/4ZzzIPyFmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[On exactly what do you base that assessment of our President besides dem and msm lies and propaganda? Think for you… https://t.co/qYdisE9xWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IFTVofficial I think Balotelli needs to earn his place. He’s 28. He’s past the stage of having potential. Either h… https://t.co/efYbGxCS8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[My student: Mr. Lubin! I really want to take my instrument home over the weekend so I can practice.   Me https://t.co/jRa2pFp3M7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rick_Sanchezez @mikeag96 Take a lap. Deadspin acts like a moral authority, it’s their “writing” is for people who… https://t.co/9XixYFxydw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Again Mr. Paul , the president can use title 8 , code 1182 and close down the entire border without havin… https://t.co/SHWL9Yoofi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s do it @PennStateMBB   Beat the mitten! #ClimbWithUs   Finish strong!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone loves his new bed that he got @petfoodexpress. Oslo loves the staff at the local Stevens Creek Pet Food Exp… https://t.co/vQrsEQGrVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nanisimo No, they don't own exhibitors and wouldn't be excluding anyone's ability to see films]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealroseanne Truth ??? You support trump. The bigest psychopathic liar who ever walked this earth.  A man who b… https://t.co/LtMfMwieAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Disney Princess Half Marathon @runDisney with the @APS_Finance crew!!  #princesshalf https://t.co/nygZwaRyG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_keyakelly_ I said that years ago when I walked away from a music scholarship all I had to do is sing before years… https://t.co/7lpisdJj34]]></document><document><![CDATA[@profevanbennett That episode might be helpful. The research the students did was on the emergence of the urban met… https://t.co/7jMdXLtDpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TechZilla_ @mikebrewer But see in america, that was the high school thing for us to do back in the early 80's drag… https://t.co/gDnpEf7Lx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d like to extend a formal apology to all those affected by my previous tweet. If I had known then what I know now… https://t.co/udhA4jNgaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KISSINGSAILOR - WWII veteran captured in iconic photo dies at 95  https://t.co/cyPxa9M1B3]]></document><document><![CDATA[As ye have therefore received Christ Jesus the Lord, so walk ye in him: Colossians 2:6 KJV https://t.co/rRL13SM23f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird flex, but I’m low key hoping for the Tetris block colored track suit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TOSubways @Tonyyjabroni @MPCelina @Puglaas Again.  Focus.  Sunny ways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/ksyz2hM2qs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Gencarelli's Bakery - @gencarellisbake in Bloomfield, NJ https://t.co/xaC6gYBY7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cannabis Red velvet cake mix brownies/ cannabis coconut 🤯il 😎 And the ingredients if you would like to go make it… https://t.co/8ZpuCuUgRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oranicuhh Profound wisdom from a profound wordsmith.  Praying for you and your peace of mind.  🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottieBeam Nah just don’t be so quick to believe anything. Period.  And your situation is a prime example of that… https://t.co/CDUQvkEcQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now is the time to buy or sell! Check out the local market stats for the area and call me at 540-845-8711 to get st… https://t.co/t0Wa0uuc9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just enjoyed an inspirational message by @Broncos great @BMarshh at the Black Male Initiative Summit at Community… https://t.co/rFAhDUSBRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ride 7: Kilimanjaro Safaris. Using fastpass #1 at 8:13 AM #EveryRideWDW @RideEvery Please donate to Give Kids the W… https://t.co/KlqW9sZdk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseReevesFF Yesh just made me less excited to take him as a top 3 wr. Easier to have AJ brown, metcalf and butle… https://t.co/IN11Ocib4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarielosUca A ti,siempre quiero estar cerca de ti,llenarte de alegría y,felicidad,porque eso será para mi dicha y,… https://t.co/8L6B1I6l9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristina_wong If I had any doubts they have all been cleared for sure!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ganesha 🐘 BWI #ganesha #bizarre #random #bwi #killingtime #rivets #chrome #selfportrait @ BWI Thurgood Marshall Air… https://t.co/t7R7CnaQ1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmatye7 Yeah definitely, vs “The Great” Buffon, a guy old enough to be his dad. Huge especially with all the injur… https://t.co/bqX8kESJ4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debbymiller52 @dani_gooner @dbongino @EddieZipperer Judge Amy Berman Jackson threw out former Trump campaign manag… https://t.co/Izcd7yJ3vB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ignore the insanse glare from my glasses.  9 years ago I had my first date with @rebdcampbell and here we are 9 yea… https://t.co/pUY5wAybcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Campaign took Russians money. Only a traitor would ever vote for anyone who takes Russians money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarlicCorgi @Volceltaire Those who have experienced the empire from the outside. I like it. You've convinced me 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitneyCummings Do you know of an accurate and convenient way to find AZA accreditation status?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliotShorrParks I see it as Howie was like: “yo, we want Brown. Brown/Agent: okay, well I/we want this.” Howie: https://t.co/bqQYD5aHFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jump son, jump. #porygon #like #follobackforfolloback #likeforlike #PresidentsDay https://t.co/fioMD522EX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Glad the truth finally comes out! This is how you find racism in America - you manufacture it? @seanhannity… https://t.co/mYYb9bnGAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahnpbowman @stephen_m_w @bpickbpick @waddell_adam The notion that we shouldn't strive for the best possible ch… https://t.co/zfNdDCE3Km]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3rinbluluna I have a lot of strong feelings and almost all of them are negative]]></document><document><![CDATA[live gooney die Saint RIP steve #dffs @ New York, New York https://t.co/3hRNZt93Nt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Maxon Shooter's Supplies &amp; Indoor Range in Des Plaines, IL https://t.co/tutrCPr4TQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrandBlancHoops defeats Carmen by one point in the first round of districts!! #BobcatNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you cannot #write well, you cannot think well; if you cannot think well, others will do your thinking for you.… https://t.co/c0njyRjdUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Similarities ???                                1974 - 2019                        Nixon  -  Trump… https://t.co/Nr8preLfqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red velvet cake mix brownies/coconut 🤯il 😎 #redvelvetcake #redvelvetbrownies #brownies  #dnzm9e #bxnzm9e #bnzm9e #🤯… https://t.co/lop7QZxKh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyvillarreal98 Alligator isn’t to blame...the guys who set this dog up ate the ones that need to be shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Pathetic. Worst POTUS of my lifetime. Zero class. International joke. You really have defiled the office. Please go away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was craving a college tennis match. 75 minute drive down the road? Easy. UGA looking to "upset" #45 FAU https://t.co/Icw1Krfnz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@n0ahkats @BleacherReport What should have happened... https://t.co/UvWM4qf01l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrashCanDanpt3 @jimjoneskoolai2 @cinema_strikes @realTomCody @ElGaucho56 @puritythrufire @stagescreen60 @KZvonaric… https://t.co/QNQ8TDv8GA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler Scum of scums. He’s worst live was ever deciding to run for President. It won’t end well !! @BetteMidler]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willy04 @YaAuntAtTheSpot So you mean the Cartoon Network Midnight Run (which lasted until 5 a.m. at the latest) or… https://t.co/hgDcXY39F4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeMathMoney What you miss is most tradesmen are contractors which means they have started a business. @EdLatimore]]></document><document><![CDATA[james blake did what he had to do on “I’ll come too” https://t.co/kIXopT2P6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Groundbreaking with RimaAnn Nelson Director of #Phoenix VA Medical Center for a brand new VA medical clinic… https://t.co/Zyw6N4pNbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tlemieux72 Winter is Co.......eh it’s already here https://t.co/FJ4TjWScG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why it’s so hard just to help customers, it’s not like that’s what you’re paid to do 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff @RepSwalwell @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows @RepJerryNadler @JoeNBC @GStephanopoulos @FaceTheNation… https://t.co/wBF3dngqek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making a Difference for our Real Estate industry! #worktogether #loveyouabq #luxuryhomes #luxuryrealestate… https://t.co/msKscNBciL]]></document></documents></author>