<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ObvslySherlock @astudyinsnoggy @bottomjohns @youkeepmeright @consultingdr221 My question is, where do you draw tha… https://t.co/rIVqgQVMiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t even tell you where we’re at. middle of nowhere basically. and my legs need to be stretched.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever dozed off in your seat on an airplane and jolted awake with the realization you were starting to snore? Me neither...]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOYCOTT ROMA THE "FILM" GLORIFIED TV MOVIE EVEN STEVEN SPIELBERG SPOKE OUT AGAINST SHOULD BE MADE TO RETURN YOUR IL… https://t.co/sbVEn9aawm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainy night in smashville brings the Carilona Hurricanes to town #Smashville https://t.co/qOVol5witA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOfficerTatum Thank you for that. If I said what you did about BO, I would be labeled a racist. He was in the po… https://t.co/NpefZFmPiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Tee-Versations Apparel &amp; Gifts https://t.co/histZEpiZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[More on their team operating for real estate theft here with the cocaine men from early on. "I was told to play unt… https://t.co/iTQyKN9HLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andrew124_ @DaveWeasel @DonaldJTrumpJr He has a hat on. Why does everyone suspect fraud]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have to hear from everyone you know that what you’re doing is right, maybe consider those opinions are biase… https://t.co/tCQDxNZrNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[White people need to look at their leader Trump he is the most racist person on this Earth but everybody has someth… https://t.co/ZI63R6CIH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bailey Kleespies with a great at-bat. 10 pitches, just kept fouling off pitches until she got one to drive for doub… https://t.co/apdlE00h15]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #granddaughter being all #teenagerish @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/vgRHaGDE9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger Please dont let terrorists take over our country! As Democrats! Nancy Pelosi is givi… https://t.co/giKb5GZapE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ballingercuties This is the best tweet I’ve seen all day oh my gosh yes yes yes😃😃😃 ps I just followed you😃😃😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 am thoughts: My graduation sucked ASS. I didn’t want to go but I forced myself to so my mom could see me receive… https://t.co/ILRz19YOgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr I still think he made a deal with HRC when she stole the DNC. He just rolled over—-no spine Bernie.… https://t.co/8BrD0GxzOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandiceAiston Microsoft did not have the best office automation apps. WordPerfect was better than Word, Lotus 1-2-… https://t.co/JCiosSNHOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go hard or Go Home! - Drinking a Head Banger by @strathconabeer @ Scarborough, Ontario  — https://t.co/NuyHHvuqYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dears, Powerful &amp; In short sentence tweeting, make retweeting easy to get more voting 4 only #TWBDimash  #WorldsBest @dimash_official]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rlthresh Wow, cool! Not sure I can access it? Do I need a subscription for that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddeanjohnson @ABC7GMW @jessob_reisbeck @VAratifyERA So, I and 37 other states disagree with you.  Plus numerous ot… https://t.co/MUBsMYmXcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This comes after a new video surfaced of the singer allegedly having sex with a 14-year-old. #RKelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RSTP_ca @PAznavehzadeh @CCSNewcomers Please help me understand the reference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The TIME’S UP Legal Defense Fund has raised over $25M since Jan. 2018 #AtlanticInclusion https://t.co/zZHCrX2F1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[💗My friend Kendra @SheIsKendra is looking for 10 more people who would love to switch out their regular coffee for… https://t.co/nJ25oyYhjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing I wouldn’t do for my friends, they ARE MY FAMILY. Woke up to a phone call from Nick to tow the K10… https://t.co/aAFu0uyD7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my friends @KoellingChiro on your 20 year anniversary! Dr. Bryce, his wife, Zoe and the ENTIRE s… https://t.co/NHX35pQ5J6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the Gents of Lancaster’s latest post on some of their favorite local bottle shops!… https://t.co/PFzXzhEkR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me why @Netflix_CA has The Flash and Supergirl but not Arrow? It makes it really hard to keep track of the man… https://t.co/0hWuOI1soQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday everyone! Have a great day &amp; weekend! @MckeeveMichelle @Vacek2Vickie @sfw1515 @MysteryOffice… https://t.co/Y7BlCk7XhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been focusing on myself lately and it’s the best feeling in the world 💕✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full house for the @TMDistrict29   #Toastmaster Leadership Institute https://t.co/DK0OGiAUE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This why i duck off on mfs. Ion be having time for the petty childish shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calendar of Events March | Eventos de Calendario Marzo #marchwithhope #imhopefamily @ Hope Family Health Center https://t.co/GKeHQdbp9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarfieldsLasgna @KingNeptune767 @History_FlightV @Libertad_350 @NewVillage717 https://t.co/kDnnETWOh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theverbalthing @FatventureMag Seriously, this is perfect. Thank you so much for drawing my attention to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJenGunter @drphiliplee1 The busiest chunk of highway in all Canada, pity those who live in Hamilton but work in TO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accepting applications for a new boyfriend after what Kody just said to me 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day I wake up proud that @JulianCastro is running for President. From the west side to the White House.  As a… https://t.co/cyazxnv5Cn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SXSW19 is happening in austin this weekend so now would be the best time to hangout outside the airport and celeb… https://t.co/r8DYuOic28]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful Carbonara for Friday Night Date night with my honey at a local restaurant called Le Mista that we just tr… https://t.co/gP9weADqZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevDrBarber Exactly. I watched the @Morning_Joe panel normalize how him serving fast food to football players is h… https://t.co/FsoHXr5rKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting excited for #AAASmtg to start today as I enjoy this beautiful DC sunrise! https://t.co/jWEIsZJT8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLissing wonderful of you dad. wish him happy birthday and many more. hope going well for you. keep smiling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sour Pitch Suds by @mikkellernyc @ Old Man's Boatyard — https://t.co/DCpNtVvNlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neilhimself Your daughters will always love you ... cool or not.  But AOC? A bit on the dumb side don’t you think?… https://t.co/IYaLJrf6kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventures of Hayley Trying to Cook Hard Boiled Eggs Part 17:   Was told if I left eggs out at room temp that they… https://t.co/tzMo0SbEyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IowaHoops there is no "I" in team @iamtc25. Bad start...please utilize the 4 other team members on the court!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I didn’t eat like a 6 year old. Always end up with these crumbs in my bed🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was fun!! Be sure to check it out! There are new #Doomtown cards spoiled here!!  #SavageWorlds #deadlands #rpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone please stop me before I fight my dumb ass roommate for “forgetting” to pay rent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanKunze1 @__alex_h_ @JoeSalmon85 @GillesnFio @MaximeBernier First that does not exist. Stop repeating clichés you… https://t.co/DOtKta7mjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[9.6 on floor today! Go D @ NEXT DIMENSION GYMNASTICS, LLC https://t.co/nFWdB2OmgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of CTMS cheer tryout clinics!!! Go Bulldogs! @CTMSBulldog @mroswurmct https://t.co/rcG656U83u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cunningbro them bitches are gonna die. should’ve bought 250 cheeseburgs off the dollar menu champ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been having a rough week dealing with depression (long month if we’re being honest), and one of the few things… https://t.co/5baPuYTXkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dar_kal_ien Alright then. Thank you for clarifying buy too would be surprised how many hold those beliefs,  even y… https://t.co/os9U0wesql]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just relax and watching tv I love my daddy and mama so much @ Holopaw, Florida https://t.co/2DLWZXHzjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Catholic Church cardinals implicated in sex abuse, cover-ups  We had a molester priest at my parish. I told Momma… https://t.co/40NpUb7YkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Rabasco I know, so sucks he did this! He has so much money he could’ve had anything he wanted in the privacy of his home!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There is one friend in the life of each of us who seems not a separate person, however dear and beloved, but an ex… https://t.co/cuTQCAot6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LincolnDuncan8 @Ellahbie @SenSanders He is not supporting regime change. He has said that time and time again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my 3-year @mozilla work anniversary! I’ve 🧠 Learned a ton and continue to learn everyday 🌎 Feel proud of t… https://t.co/ZMze0re1dI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The President of the USA  does business with the owner/operator Day Spa's specializing in happy endings. In fact, C… https://t.co/RbM8PCCyiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are a hateful racist and a has-been actor who's frustration has turned to pathetic bigotry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright sailors: let’s show the world 🗺 chesapeake bay when Tatiana drives on the bridge 🌉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matrix119911 1/2 Haiii!!👋 What I can say is if u buy for the long term (if u believe $btc will fly back to $19K+),… https://t.co/W7Jkhydwoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump GOD BLESSED US WITH AN AWESOME 👏 PRESIDENT! Love you and our BEAUTIFUL @FLOTUS WE ARE TRULY BLESSE… https://t.co/PiGztqAi4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What if I paid your flight? Would you come?” Shiiiiiiit you ain’t gotta tell me twice I’ll disappear lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Krisssycakes3 this thread will be ongoing so maybe we can do a study on it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cudlitz @RealJamesWoods @TheWalkingDead Well said. Thank you. I will never understand why some people are so mean spirited.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dork won Monopoly last night and took me out to breakfast with his winnings.  Also, Papa's on 42nd is so good. https://t.co/ur34dH2Lea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryelder @JoeFreedomLove @realDonaldTrump And Schiff,  yeah say that!  That will surely keep him from getting re… https://t.co/oP1VK7ifbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg @NKOTB @GMA 30 years later and they still have our hearts❤️🔥❤️🔥🔥🔥#HangingTough30 #NKOTBonGMA #BHLove https://t.co/d5pOiPnc5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chuwenjie Whoever nabs you in August will be a lucky studio! 💪 Your work is 💯👌✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle Not one thing, he is part of the Democrats dog and pony show!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent croissant 🥐 sandwich and yummy treats in Truckee! #truckee #Tahoe #bakery #Sierras @ Cornerstone Bakery https://t.co/lz9jR9KkTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomKochABC13  @Esther188rod  THANKS TOM FOR READING AND LIKINGS MY TWEET HOPE YOU HAD FUN 🎗️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy for you @venezia_megan! Well deserved! Thank you for working so hard for our school and making a big diffe… https://t.co/Hna64mnh3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Unlike the WH.. Muller doesn’t have leakers! I’m sure it must bug the wanna be Prez… https://t.co/4lCvIbWt07]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBridge2RC Got yourself some space invaders there! ❤️🐾❤️ Double the love!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found this video on Dailymotion... https://t.co/VTiARU90Wl #YouTube #ViralVideos #DonaldTrump #DACA #BorderWall]]></document><document><![CDATA[All i ever want to eat is ground pork with rice but I can't cook so i just cook the pork with soy sauce, sesame oil… https://t.co/wGtaTXZEjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[maybe it’s just my opinion/experiences but i feel like restaurants w automatic gratuity, always have v trash service and mediocre food]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1SteveBurton @BfordAnderson Patiently waiting 4 May dates &amp; hoping one is in Toronto, Canada or close...😘🇨🇦… https://t.co/UkzhfdJ97i]]></document><document><![CDATA[the best thing about the washer and dryer being in my bathroom is that when I’m cold, I can throw my blankets in th… https://t.co/kBVc7dwGAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HCSDSELDirector @HenkelWarren @VickyClark1 @jessrardon @Ms_Hueter @EKDooley @SammyAlthouse @KatiLMiller… https://t.co/sXrcrvWoSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tariq Nasheed: Who Else Is Involved in the Jussie Smollett Hoax? https://t.co/UraD4012uH via @YouTube. 👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾💯💯💯💯💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HassanShibly @realDonaldTrump Don’t even try to pull the Latino population in to this by stoking fear of citizensh… https://t.co/iA7VOwpNo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBC Did u seriously think a spynet that collects billions of bits of data on every person in #US would tell you it's spying?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have always been a true friend with best interests at heart. Sometimes, I just need to step away for a little bit… https://t.co/vz05VLOhU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trespotatoes @davidaxelrod @PeteButtigieg @CNN ^^^Good for him and pat yourself on the back! Good Mom right up here^^^]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDaveeg @Thomas1774Paine Saw that one coming a long time ago!!!  Hey where is Hillary btw??? 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was struggling on my history exam and this girl in my class airdropped me her scantron 😫😫...GOD is good !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louizahoward @marvinsapp @DonPUMPhrey T H I S YEAR!!! I AM GOING TO FLY❤🎶🎵🎊🎉🎁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love audiobooks! There are some wonderful tips in here about how to get into them! 🎧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: needs all the cute spring clothes and shoes   my wallet: https://t.co/UHBqknhplZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbMcQuade @neal_katyal @Lawrence @MSNBC @nytimes @NatashaBertrand Never, Barb! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not really looking forward on working at 8am but at least I’ll have my day off on Sunday.]]></document></documents></author>