<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#2 Presidente @lopezobrador_ apoyamos su estrategia anticorrupción   en beneficio del país pero el compromiso que h… https://t.co/u8P7QfyWnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[no post last friday because of midterms and an unexpected trip to urgent care. honestly one of the most emotional w… https://t.co/wsfCKY8AC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[El Dr. @LeonelFernandez conecta con el pueblo que recibe de su pueblo gratitud y para el país es la esperanza.… https://t.co/HEBevu1P8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trash !!!!!         #filmmaking #horror #spokenword #trash #users #abusers #drugaddicts #scumbags #psychicvampires… https://t.co/ih3SSzm7jQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMarinaTimes @BigadShaban @MrCleanSF @sfpublicworks Someone is getting paid on the backend of the contracted dea… https://t.co/BQJJAfiHIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[My blood's journey is complete &amp; ready to help someone. Donate blood &amp; help to save up to 3 lives with the… https://t.co/6Xmvg54CKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know we are good friends if I constantly tag you in Instagram post to try and win a giveaway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mah_abdellatif @mmamas1973 @escardio Probably doesn't have anything to do with the pushups other than a marker of strength and fitness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DUNK OF THE YEAR. Sha’den Clanton throws down the and-one. The gym is up for grabs. East up 60-54, 1:50 to go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @WhiteZinWench  you free Wednesday at 730pm to chat nyrb with @soundersduff and I on @Yellowcardpod]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does #Reeses and #Bourbon have in common? Me!! Which is basically my #Friday night. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisJZullo @realDonaldTrump .                             #DitchMitch  .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton is selecting her wording very carefully when talking about American citizens being refused in the e… https://t.co/HChfuTZWqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya cambió , la que ya cambió fué tu abuela , una cosa es ser candidato , y otra es ejecutar el poder , ???? Cuántos… https://t.co/s6IeD1HYYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgiaLogCabin First, this was a joke. No wonder 24 republicans voted no. Also, Pelosi, water down and put in so… https://t.co/CsqjKs8K3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Wild leaves Monday on a two week, six-game road trip starting with four in California. The next home game is 7… https://t.co/jUWIaxcts3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fat_guy_outdoor @WassmannBill @stephen_richter @JenniPrickett @XStreamFisher @mike_Iaconelli @SuchockiJason… https://t.co/I2k0iLipBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨Payback Is A Must On Tuesday @TSUMensHoops. This Just Got Real In Tigerland! @TrayvonReed5 @TheySleep_55… https://t.co/fahvjA7PRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auntievinh When you’re out of something, you could say it’s “Sai Gone.” There’s plenty of fun wordplay to be had.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I predict that real patriots will hold counter events on every Main Street in America that day, complete with firew… https://t.co/SCsWt4fb2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting to hear pundits representing @CPC_HQ unanimously recommend bankrupting #SNCLavalin -- is this official policy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[IN FT WORTH... @ Meadowbrook First Baptist Church https://t.co/Bgu7rfrqbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOHMaster Video games is a lack of productivity issue more than not working, unless of course you get paid for playing 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WitmerCarl @ThomasPKennedy3 @cleared37Joseph @AMike4761 @r98121261 @IsraelUSAforevr @godrockin @moekamerow… https://t.co/rpTP2Z1YYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[USA Softball: Week 4 https://t.co/MwzPugLpDi Softball Collegiate Top 25 Poll #Fastball @USASoftball… https://t.co/iPhTjjhNje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epigmenioibarra @cafevega Cual es el punto de "exhibir" si no haces nada al respecto. Digo zapatero a tus zapatos… https://t.co/5PMTt3NhVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren I think you are ridiculous I’m a minority Mexican born,you have no appeal and you try way to hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[can someone explain how a “faithful good Christian person” is allowed to beat random people’s ass and make others f… https://t.co/E6IStKv0fY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cagewm @MacLethal just saw the Juggalo cypher. Super dope to see y’all on that. Both of y’all killed it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @therealroseanne @prageru Can we make it 3 Jews? Don’t forget about me. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynnWilson111 @williamlegate @realDonaldTrump Glad to see how many demrats crawling around looking for shit to eat… https://t.co/LsyO9Xcm6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PardesSeleh We live in hope. Talk about Trump dismantling someone in public...OW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neilworms I walked by as part of @bockfest yesterday and apparently I missed out on the final result by just one day...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido fuera de Venezuela No tiene ningún valor para que caiga Nicolas Maduro, el costo del cambio tiene sacrific… https://t.co/K5Z936eZOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milivojorlev @DaireFeeney @AnnaSemlyen1 @Alyssa_Milano My point exactly . There are tools for hunting and tools ju… https://t.co/pFBTRNveIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This how I busted through my ex’s window when she stopped texting me at 7:30 PM and said she was “going to sleep” https://t.co/jbwJVqq63K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coca-Cola earnings for Q4:   Sparkling soft drinks: ⬇️ 1% Juice, dairy and plant-based beverages ⬇️ 2% Water, enhan… https://t.co/c7vT6JmuQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahfayboston @narrative_io @TechCrunch @nick_jordan @GlasswingVC Great group of investors joining a great company 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just stay focused and keep God first in your life Lil brudda and it’s all gon come together❗️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to see Zach LaVine in the dunk contest next year! Has to in Chicago. #BullsNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AxelChldofDstny @GoldenDicePod You’ve prob seen the TC ones.  His are based on the same idea.  Just solid metal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samfordbaseball @bdc_28 making out like a 777 dropping some destructive ordinance in last night. https://t.co/6q0jIv3X5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spot me in the mirror at Jones on Santa Monica blvd. #california #westhollywood @ Jones https://t.co/ykB8wiX3Xs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePsycholitics @Deplorable_Man And were the violent ones supposedly. https://t.co/bP7TbXRiBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lancaster chamber board meeting @ SpringHill Suites by Marriott Buffalo Airport https://t.co/LFBe1MArNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my permanent response for any accusation made against me in 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are puzzled by what this means, I recommend doing a little bit of reading into World War II bomber’s over Na… https://t.co/52Tnpc74CJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the boondoggle that COAST and its allies should be raging over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tfrint Tell us what you’re doing to help and we can use your life as a model]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HandsomeRandall @FightfulWrestle His feud with Savage over the title literally helped create the #MegaPowers and j… https://t.co/GiG8yEhJoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ngfreshh @CorruptedPOD @CountdownEnded @RealAdamHuish @RealBluEEaZY its being said that harper was the more talent… https://t.co/nXritEAaOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do any of y’alls families separate the trash from whites and colors or is that only mine?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crisp with hoppy IPA ish flavor but more subdued.  Refreshing. - Drinking a Necessary Evil by @mpbeerco @ Growler U… https://t.co/r4E4szePsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody send @SillyCee good morning tweets. She is very chipper this morning! https://t.co/83lsK869vE]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the #FakeNationalEmergency rally ended at Federal Plaza, everyone marched to Trump International Hotel and To… https://t.co/mchFnHR0BG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photos from one of my personal favorite moments as a singer. Surrounded by the lights. Thanks again to everyone who… https://t.co/l7nNgvDB48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_Schmitt1 @Dr_BLyons @maegschmitt Do we need to convene?.... tomorrow night is 👀 https://t.co/rk2qijBXX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day #1: Savannah, Georgia 🚎🚎🚎  Highlights:   1) The Day we’ve Dreamed About... 2) Partner Dinner in Bluffton, SC 3)… https://t.co/99NIyC84nF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lisac02 @qanon76 Ran across what?  No sources, no evidence, no attribution. Just accusations and speculations that… https://t.co/SbXyacDaAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grattongirl It doesn't look like the Jetsons car though!  :-P https://t.co/9cYeNYvIVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseMnlRC @jmanuelfigueroa El partido mas facil que ha tenido en años chivas. Esto es del entrenador y de nadie ma… https://t.co/NPT1PKlTTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseKellyDC GMA is not interested in African Hatred of 'American's they call Whites'! I know your anger. It is Na… https://t.co/v8UAhg5MnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[You made sense till the meme. Knowing what it is does not automatically mean you will recognize it when it happens.… https://t.co/aHvV9heu5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liiiii_Liiiii It’s okay. Missing someone hurts, but it confirms your capacity to love. Stay strong, boo. It’ll get better with time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeopleOfUK i work for myself, on a youtube show. it's a blessing and a curse...but mostly the curse part. ah, but i kid. i love what i do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleWBZ4 Morning Danielle.. 3.5" for North Weymouth..Its on the Box PNS rpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder: “Show them what crazy dreams can do!!!” -Nike 👊 #HappyMonday☀️ #GoGetIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar I want him to run so bad.  He did so much stupid illegal shit for his daddy.  How much better will it be w… https://t.co/CuU2KMA6KF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vivianne this will be a great meeting. Looking forward to the pro con opioid debate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSL5TV @DaveMcCannKSL @TomCantHackett Sorry, got to stick up for Bronco. He is a good man. He rolls differently bu… https://t.co/lNTvU0UiIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NetBase On Tour happening today in Atlanta, the customer success team is presenting how to best leverage their ser… https://t.co/3cj2L8LDtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: REVIEW: As @AndrewMcMahon pursues new sounds at @themetphilly, crowd still loves songs from his past. Read… https://t.co/t8shRtzFFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SupportNHHS Will there be nazi beer pong at this event? If so, I don’t think I’ll be able to make it… https://t.co/AseYShLObh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #Springfield, MA? https://t.co/BVMy46NGOG #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForeverIamLady I’ll kill everybody for that weather. The weather here suck https://t.co/oFZJakWn3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know this story real well! But don't worry, my lips are SEALED! 🤐#secretsofthemorgue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both Kelly and McGahn documented their objections in memos, the Times reports, with McGahn’s memos outlining concer… https://t.co/7YfRkv9KZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesliedgonzales @brehmc Well if you wanna zoom one day to see how to develop some of these types of slides, let me know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wolfy1328 Had to get my good bull done for the week. https://t.co/b0zLFzfHTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelseahandler You know! Squidward Calamari!  “Grazi!” https://t.co/RclyLXL8sE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a CR Double IPA by @crbrewingcompany @ H &amp; M's — https://t.co/TlstiXZcgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although I’ve seen others do the same. Roll out is nice. John Legend displays his genuine love for music and playlists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cancunbound2022 @cowboys20041 @Black_is_back5 @My57ChevyBelAir @Mharris888H @AbrahamAlyzah @bushie200 @schjoe1… https://t.co/oD7dN7Ycxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspiration basketball story from teenage girl with big heart.  #baskeball  https://t.co/4m4II432Lw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing this video because it's very heartwarming https://t.co/05d17uclH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HerbShields Ha! I admit I couldn't go full suit. I opted for the easier-to-bike-in "cardigan over a shirt and tie" twist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you really want to die without establishing a legacy? I know plenty of people just waiting. Pondering. Sitting a… https://t.co/dvWksEW6IK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very cool seeing 2 former Voyagers at first base together! Proud of you guys!! Keep grinding 💪🏻 @gfvoyagers   2014… https://t.co/VIKDYPHRQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KBrown412 @julian__little @_JGreene_2 @z_gray11 @BenThomasPreps @Coach_Lud @Coach__Archer @BrandonTate2015 @CoachTBarr ‼️‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[phillip wilson on Twitter: "Listen to Philly2000 on any music service 🎶🎧 https://t.co/j8sjXzilU0 #ListenAnywhere… https://t.co/qEQ0dtWp74]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if unveiling your wife is as beautiful as taking the foil off of your Chipotle burrito]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud moment tonight. My last year of coaching at Waseca HS in 2016, I moved up a freshman basketball player to my… https://t.co/o7mWvVHtnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/GQrjDcR3BU @1037KISSFM i think u should probably just add this to ur playlist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nathan984612221 happy birthday young man watching you grow up has been quite a charm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulianG922 @EricTrump Our President always cares about the real Americans! Not those limp wristers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHRAReinhart 🙏🏼 Been a fan from Dad and Son says days congratulations o Momma for putting up with you Little Pig P… https://t.co/E3aacMP3kE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_becks22 Well he needs to stay out of it. This is poised to give more ammunition to the opposition than help our side]]></document><document><![CDATA[The president thinks part of the constitution is unconstitutional.   Stew on that whopper...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stashes of ACC/AOC gold:. #yorktown #FlintWaterCrisis #CapeTown #SINemaSundays #brightwaternewzealand… https://t.co/VAXIICZ6Yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PureStorage @teestarnes @storagemagician @TheChrisHorn Thanks for the welcome and the RT too. :)]]></document></documents></author>