<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[You can find this delicious sorbet at @WaltDisneyWorld  at Disney’s Contemporary Resort. https://t.co/gqYst6dcAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hcyang0115 @29rain Have patience  and  hope or it will get getting  we cant always  me living for u ur  a man try… https://t.co/e04oC2kQ8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STL_UVA @kylejguy5 Thank you Jack Salt for being a quality player and a quality person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get your hair done and feel like a brand new person 😂 I had this homeless look going for a while tryna gro… https://t.co/WwbTvTNCF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[planning my vow renewal for 3 years from now for an island I’ve never even been on is the hardest thing I’ve ever d… https://t.co/5jOwZ2t47o]]></document><document><![CDATA[One was physically and verbally abusive, the other was mentally and emotionally abusive, Both niggaz taught me that… https://t.co/VHI09O5lhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertIrwin @russellcrowe Love this family!!  One of only 2x I watched Dancing With The Stars  was bcz @BindiIrwin… https://t.co/62NFQ4b9Ww]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, my youngest sibling was dancing they were so excited about the #JonasBrothers news and they rolled their ank… https://t.co/C7i7GQTedx]]></document><document><![CDATA[More technology to move us away from fossil fuel powered vehicles. All these technological advancements will help d… https://t.co/72kHoKFCW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RHONJ Jennifer is so tacky, her CHANEL jewelry that she wears, her brother makes. Cheap tacky swapmeet garbage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So lucky to have you 😻 #luckynumber13 #valentinesday2019 @ Oakleaf Plantation, Florida https://t.co/Jfj2yo1JMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrytynP @jonasbrothers I’m so happy they’re back for jayce to experience what a blessing]]></document><document><![CDATA[its #LoveYourPetsDay and I miss my dog soooo much I love you Kilo :’( https://t.co/8Qrt044KlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Likewise we live to die.   #traitortrump #EnoughIsEnough #Mar-a-sh*thole]]></document><document><![CDATA[we’re all like a guys sleep voice &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; but it’s really their drunk laugh 🤧🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@docdhj @SU68399458 @Lrihendry @tracybeanz @thelastrefuge They tried to gain the whole world but will lose their ow… https://t.co/W7JiQRlU4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something I’ve learned is just because you have a child together doesn’t mean you HAVE to be together..❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCleavinger @OPSUAthletics @NewsChannel10 You earned it girl, congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it with the therockersball squad tommorrow night @boardners in Hollywood! Festival style lineup, 5 bands, m… https://t.co/Obxho34B3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying this #internationalwomensday by reminding you all that I’m badass enough to eat ice cream in the dead of w… https://t.co/2YCxiknzhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raise you hand if you feel personally victimized by daylight saving time. 🙋🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatdudeshrop Honestly. A good friend would encourage them to keep practicing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joejoehasfun Have you considered marketing that dumb bitch juice you're always drinking?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤩when your juice is always sweet b/c you’re diabetic and can’t eat sweet things &gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calitruecrime @thehauntedheart @DomesticPodcast @NRWMpodcast @MensReaPod @killerjobspod @talesof2citiesp… https://t.co/goGnyb6N1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[The strength of each member is the team. #calvarychristianhighschool #calvarychristianhigh… https://t.co/l1RFeTzNGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry You are proof positive of how the Republican strategy of dumbing down its base for the last 30 years has… https://t.co/wRDpE26c4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much fun at #miamiboatshow2019 @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/3wL04aNtM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[was gonna play club penguin tonight until they banned me, so what does one do now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petition: 26,000 Scientists Oppose 5G Roll Out https://t.co/IUacik4boE via @john0sullivanp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Card Woelki has responded to what he calls a “factional dispute” in Germany raised by the clergy sexual abuse scand… https://t.co/jA6sp2Vlyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[More rolling trays coming soon! #420 #420life #420girls #gingershippieshack @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/sFVamXpGv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felling fab AF 🔥 and I had Tito’s and pita bread the night before those after shots were taken 😏 . For 6 weeks I sh… https://t.co/8NdQBlw7Vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[La bicho dice que Poly estaba drogada pero no para violarla, entonces Poly se drogo sola? #ElValorDeLaVerdad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkooterMcGaven @NJDevils Garbage. At least give me free tickets to a game given how bad they are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y solo son 2 años de diferencia. Mi bebé ya creció ☹️🔞😭 https://t.co/lSt9tFxqa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 months away from being in that same pool, partying my life away. I’m so mentally ready for @SplashHousePS already… https://t.co/W2O7dDQgZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking from the tongue of an experienced simpleton who obviously would rather be an emasculated, infantile complain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CommittoVote @ProudResister @JeffBezos Just what the Mayor said in his op ed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It means I'd like the government on a short leash while I beat it into submission.  "Is that what they mean by anarcho fascist?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[#itsatotething #joinmyteam #itsnotajobitsacalling #thirtyone #bossbabe #allin31 #31why #misssells31 #31shenanigans… https://t.co/Sxfh2T2ARs]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don’t deserve @Lin_Manuel in the world of #DonaldTrump in @BarackObama we did, but not now. We are just grateful he still talks to us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Souriswingette Panther is a versatile word that can refer to different leopards, jaguars, or mountain lions. A bla… https://t.co/95ucTKXKVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @mattreevesLA I still think @jaredkeeso should be on your shortlist to play #TheBatman ..I mean LOOK at that ja… https://t.co/ah6JZuUxPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile @SamsungMobileUS I want to win the new Galaxy S10e as a gift to my cousin. #TMobileTuesdays + #contest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday morning showings! #realtorlife #adayinthelifeofcarynblack #kurfisssothebysinternationalrealty #sothebys… https://t.co/jDOzGGklw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a great time at the Guild of Music Supervisors Awards! #gmsawards #redcarpet #christiandior #tiffanys… https://t.co/x3TCnwjof2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left a bar early to work on this fun (&amp; very tedious) DIY project 🌸🌵🌿 https://t.co/4dzhLWpFcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StealYaFavHoe Lmao no i actually had my licenses physically with me i got 2 tickets one for running the red light… https://t.co/8bAGpnv3ZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although not likely, it would certainly not hurt these scientists to consider contact through meditation while they… https://t.co/Bp4x6ZFPex]]></document><document><![CDATA[So when @MarkMeadows said "My nieces and nephews are people of color. Not many people know that." And why is that,… https://t.co/lkpPYaBUzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[White shirt n grey shorts?? WRONG. It’s bout that suit n tie 🥵 got me HOT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard a dude I met a few times in passing tells my friends he’s mad that I post photos of my body loooooool I’… https://t.co/5yzpsU49xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[tAnother amazing morning speaking at the State ADR conference. Important theme "Promoting Relationships and Equity… https://t.co/Q9pDQNyK0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[It still is because he can’t read your mind . He can’t just know you want something without you telling him 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickyd6865 Be proud you have enough smarts and awareness to realize how we are getting screwed!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 @AMErikaNGIRL07 What a wonderful demonstration of compassion for humanity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJay_01 @joncoopertweets Trump if you cure cancer...come to St.Jude Children's hospital in Memphis, TN. And pro… https://t.co/EMAbAXf1Nm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best part about dating is getting to go to all the movies. Seriously I’ve been to the movies more in the past 6… https://t.co/KPK8jge7ur]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have now put my event tweet in my pinned tweet. Just read it and I am here for inspirational messages for most of the day.  🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simple reframing of a question changes everything: "you have missed class, how can I help you?" Ss react positively… https://t.co/S3tDcYeD8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthanObama He's dead and they still are!  The Jackson movie attacks someone who can't defend himself😭🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[You all need to check you privilege advocate for people that RELY on local bus service too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@descuderoq talking physics and #HoloLens2 @MSFTReactor #ARLife @MicrosoftSV https://t.co/oALNqFE0S8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IJefTomI She did the best she could. Despite unspeakable forces from every side, and still cleaned his clock in th… https://t.co/ZO9GmS56l6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sound of color guard equipment being caught is one of my favorite sounds. Oh man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pixxydoodle Wow I was reading it and it went poof.. then u tagged me.. thanks. It’s very good. It made me think I… https://t.co/dsT73ywEw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandyTolbert9 @CampbellCSI @CSIpto @Cre8ingArtNC14 @carlsontweets now this is the kind of cheering we want out our assemblies ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[pittsburgh has finally started to feel like home @swissarmymusic ❤️❤️❤️ @ Mr. Smalls Theatre https://t.co/PO8xZJIzED]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever want to know what it’s like to fire my hammies. 🙄🙄😳😳 And that’s when they feel like firing.… https://t.co/LkC4YV8nLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter the #BestinRescue At Home Contest on Hallmark https://t.co/aq00Dk7riT and you could win $1,000! https://t.co/vzvTODa6tU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to sweat stretch and center myself 🧘🏻‍♀️🕉💖💦 #sunday #yoga #hotyoga #sweattherapy #recenteryourself #meditate… https://t.co/wKOeK5QVhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duke had a seizure last night and hasn’t been right since. Currently waiting it out at the vet. Anyone who knows me… https://t.co/BrjsYMhzR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slicksmoovee @scotttony10 @ZskyYyY @LeahLuneke 😂😂😭 well damn what females y'all fucking with that's gone have y'all catching charges]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacqui is honestly the most genuine person I have ever met. So many in the community are excited about this new add… https://t.co/9CbADhVzsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking... Justice Kennedy &gt;his son &gt; Deutsche Bank &gt; tRump 👀🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome job to our T3307 team! 11 Mycheckouts, beat our Redcard goal, and received a guest compliment card!… https://t.co/gFGLBG31pJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hillarybloze , classy twitter name 😹. I guess you weren’t  happy with the question AOC asked MC last week. I thoug… https://t.co/9CpajFRo1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[IDC if you out with friends 💁🏻‍♀️ but if you seriously think it’s okay to not text back within the second I text yo… https://t.co/1troStl3BY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christina_gungl Right next to the playground. There was also a beer can around the corner.  True. Could have been something worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emt4godgranmma1 @lacroixwater @njfarmerwife @4judyblue Thanks so much Carla! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGoddesss_ the good thing was that it stayed in the cup until I took the pen out 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jijmpel @PeterAskin1 @Change Omg.  Whoever did that deserves the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby, it's getting personal ALREADY out here!  But @BernieSanders supporters KNEW this was coming.  I cannot believ… https://t.co/GttcmujxKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read a meme that said “I havent felt myself in months and nobody noticed” I felt that shit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/03/2019 • #Art • hungry #Cardinals 🐦 🐦 in the cold rain 🌧 in #Conway #Arkansas 🙏🏻 #blessed @ Conway, Arkansas https://t.co/HfFSOFmdPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[You may think my solo #valentinesday lunch of Pizza Hut from @Target in the dark (the power’s out) is sad, but I li… https://t.co/M1xDcdOx07]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YolandaAdams Oh no, love C U as an artist, but they ruined a beautiful song snd performance of the King’s back in… https://t.co/LKWytyfyKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you seriously think your job was created so that you could manipulate what the American people get to vote on?… https://t.co/Dy4z0N9urX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need the media to move back to truth telling.   Stop trying to bolster up the left.  Speak the TRUTH!!   Give th… https://t.co/ALATD7pIbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetNorvena @SourceRobert @AlliCamAllison @Danielle21A @OncerHardy @frostgirl11 @hjhollis93 @NGDAverk… https://t.co/h33YpbQXoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisspangle @hale_razor Definitely agree with that! The only one that seems to be a real emergency off that list was 9/11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday fun with friends with margaritas and tacos! @ Barrio Tacos https://t.co/WTk67gGrtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[few clouds -&gt; clear sky temperature down -4°F -&gt; -10°F humidity up 53% -&gt; 83% wind 17mph -&gt; 5mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldivory @JustJaneinWA That is amazing! I think now a days more women are getting into programming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So is there a dry eye in the Dean Dome during Luke’s speech? Wow. #goheels]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delsasolorzano Cuídate Hija @delsasolorzano Te Necesitamos Bendiciones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol Haha thank the lord because it would be more women like to wear those cottonballs for ears too 😢😢😢😭😭😭😭😭😢😢fake t… https://t.co/Fa3qukquEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[People noticing my little weight loss got me like https://t.co/XLGwGQ1o6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BDSEL @SenateGOP @AOC Well you better address CHINA then because they are number 1 when it comes to pollutio. It a… https://t.co/sJDBy1ahgP]]></document></documents></author>