<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@yidwithlid @TamikaDMallory @IlhanMN And listen to one of yours https://t.co/K8J4WXxPjq   And this was said by a Je… https://t.co/BgWFuOdVfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom told me she noticed I’m actually happy now &amp; not “masking” everything like how I was for the past couple months 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at CROSSMARK? We're hiring in #Charlotte, NC! Click the link in our bio for details on this job and mo… https://t.co/hvTwcrqHqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferDuray1 I’m gonna give the big guy a special ro@antic rubdown this weekend. Cause I love him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarisInigoVFs Tinatawag na kayo. Haha  @kapalmoks23 @NigoMar @AirahAquino8 @Mabelskie09 @maloumunar422 @JudaelB… https://t.co/SjiCq4cFdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stranger: I’m an immigrant just like you, I know the struggles we have to go through in America   Me: Really? Where… https://t.co/rFOQKZE04g]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a kindergartner brings you a unicorn cupcake. https://t.co/eeVk8HAopx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope #PolkCounty is paying attention tomorrow. @kellistargel will be letting us know if she listens to profession… https://t.co/GQR6ld7WEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dog definitely has a whole obstacle course planned out in his head]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilihernandezb @seanhannity @jorgeramosnews I saw Ramos very fake during the interview! He is looking for his own p… https://t.co/pwmclH4QeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real jealous of anyone lucky enough to still have their grandparents in their lives]]></document><document><![CDATA[#jamesblake #olympiamontreal à Olympia de Montréal https://t.co/aJVhaHZ9oM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wildbirdfund @JerryBasford Ha! I have a teenage boy so I can attest to the unformed brain. You guys are so great g… https://t.co/vhcYogbaVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbuseChat Yes! Many times by both men and women. Recently someone told me I deserved the abuse I endured. #abusetalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[She knows what she’s getting 🐶❤️🐾 #pupachino #starbucks @ Dallas, Texas https://t.co/8SiCYgMGKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lashes for daaaays 😍 I absolutely love having eye lash extensions and just had mine refilled at chezannsalon right… https://t.co/XJoyZu7v6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenKamalaHarris @SenFeinstein interesting that the people working on the border would say such things! What do you… https://t.co/tUEiyQg533]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_Legend1976 @BronzeMars I’m sorry #UmbrellaAcademy, are you talking to me? https://t.co/JWenfzyosH]]></document><document><![CDATA[dia dos namorados, todas as mesas do restaurante são casais. Menos a nossa que sao 9 pessoas kakakak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday everyone. It’s no secret that I love talking (yelling) about women’s empowerment and… https://t.co/E3NHu8P3EK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah the vaping isn’t cool but do y’all se the dude in the fucking ball cap and sweater in his wedding picture]]></document><document><![CDATA[The life of motherhood + being a PhD student! A great example of the need for extending a dialogue about the import… https://t.co/xv5A8HKfMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty dang lucky to get to spend eternity with this guy. I have the best time with him no matter what we’re do… https://t.co/wO2L1E8JVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeaneJudy @ParkerTeacher13 @kdice29 @SandalwoodSS208 @PeelSchools @Irish_Neill @KathyRi28306738 @ERFPeel… https://t.co/sJ84wAYBjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was watching greys anatomy and this couple was going to get marry but she ended up in a coma and he waited for he… https://t.co/Y2inUKsprn]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the market: Homes on the (brrr!) water, from a vast villa to lofty penthouses and cozy condos. How do they stay… https://t.co/u8VDLbGR9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManUGBCole Well, I've got my lucky mug this time (forgot it last game 😞)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also got two DMs just now from two ladies trying to warn me about how “vindictive” she is and how she outed someo… https://t.co/a46FVFT3mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/x5QSJnCKeq @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews @RepCummings UKRAINE CONNECTIONS....MAY HAVE TIES W/RUSSIA...COHEN IS CULPRIT😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[But Trump does manage to make them so. Notebthat it is Fox also protesting the move.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, if a man who is uncircumcised keeps the precepts of the law, will not his uncircumcision be regarded as circumc… https://t.co/vRB3MYyu53]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for having me! 🙏🏻❤️I thoroughly enjoyed it. So meaningful. #DaytimeEmmys #ChrisVanEtten… https://t.co/8KE9f9E5sC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@News_8 Take a field trip to border and find out for yourself what’s going on down there and don’t rely on the #HateTrumpMedia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hair2makeupgirl @mbutton47 @RyanAFournier Sweetheart it’s not a lie it’s a fact. Jimmy Carter froze Iraq’s assets… https://t.co/6jFoUZFWvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay I just cried looking at @ciaoobelllaxo wedding photos. 1) because I’m so happy one of my favorite youtubers is… https://t.co/EqUgcC8pab]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wished for this got it and I’m back...I slightly regret taking the chance to come back..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stocat1 @tomspolitics That is utter BS in this case. There was no appropriate answer other than, 'that simply is u… https://t.co/EiWUjU9aKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join us in congratulating ELLEN on joining the 10 pound club!   Now, losing 10 pounds may not seem like an a… https://t.co/qqGpGhTeJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[You would think a company would realize there is a problem when your workers are committing suicide in your establi… https://t.co/c3rCnhd8hO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eorden  Can you help my NYC elementary public school students with Virtual Reality kits on DonorsChoose?  We will… https://t.co/xESi0I3hSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Dougherty County, Georgia https://t.co/gytROcL3tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyver45 @SpryGuy @albyselkie They are Russians feeding you shit and you believe it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I chose a shower over stopping for coffee this morning. I am very much regretting this decision.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@connorrambles 😂 that would have been a fast one! No, just my puppy baby rn. 🐶👶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cap916 @RepAdamSchiff Another delusional Trumpkin! Go Stick your head back in the sand! You just can't cure stupid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I order a case from Wish 1 time and it came 2 months later never again .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smiliey_Kylie I can’t it would be a lie...I sorry😔   Only saying sorry to you @Smiliey_Kylie but everyone else.....ehhh don’t care lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cry in the car  Clean the apartment  Do some martial arts  Cuddle with your friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I made this I AM ALL WOMAN CHARM BRACELET'S for my Aunt Diane and her wife. I made it before Valentine's Day. Wa… https://t.co/vQv2z2SQkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elias_julie @Hazel_River12 @dokta_foth @jeannefisher17 @DanielBRichard @cinbashaw @akach5 @ecclesias… https://t.co/vjuYF4c0b5]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was drowning you were supposed to pull me out, not push me further under. Little do you know I still have a lot of fight left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I see where she’s been busy but like a message pushing it back would be nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @kimguilfoyle Keep talkin! Just gonna get worse for you.   Shocking that NO ONE in your world has t… https://t.co/j7lW7HqOPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ginger_Kliffin I don’t care how big of a lead we have, the Big 12 refs are hot garbage. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@douglascountyks @TheKLC Good morning Jasmine M! Always great to see familiar faces #leadershipisanactivity]]></document><document><![CDATA[people who brag about how mfs gon miss them when they leave be really the ones missing the mfs the dubbing lmaoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many times are people going to make the Bowser joke for our new God?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know those infomercials where white people struggle with easy tasks? Yup, your watching them reenact my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this talk comparing Bryce Harper and @profastpitch and I just emailed to get season tickets for the… https://t.co/HSHSdMbRgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had such a blast meeting these ladies. Women empowerment, am I right?!  Keep blazing the trail 👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well Payton’s mri was good. They still can’t figure out what’s going on with her bowels and it’s not affecting her… https://t.co/W0Ej5q6aIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Britt_Thomason Tim Long sent this article to me this morning so I thought it would throw it in the conversation https://t.co/tGvZjhN3oT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bedevilme666 @billy4ever9 @SpriteJ11 @redmartagons @Patti_Sc60 @SealeyGerald @kevin_ponton @jonz970 @tweets4poppy… https://t.co/ZWEXmyhQJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xoCanadianAngel @trishapaytas Omg thank you sweet angel!! For sure getting the bra!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can't believe ive had a laptop for two months now and i haven't downloaded the sims yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steelersdepot What, he sits on IG and watches the next posts that pops up about him? Sick!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No puedes evitar que te mientan, pero si puedes evitar creerles 😉 #filosofandoconwhiskeyenmano]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highly recommend Super Dark Times on Netflix. It’s a twisted coming of age film and it’s absolutely fantastic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s great driving home from the night shift in the snow, basically no one is out and you can’t even tell what your… https://t.co/RLVpRlVGmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I can’t be the only one that thinks it’s inappropriate to set up a hidden camera in someone’s bathroom]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔🤔🤔🤔 oh uh ok then whatever you say @RondaRousey for speaking your mind but I'm still a fan of yours]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si une firme d'ingénieurs albertains avaient fait des magouilles avec le gouvernent, vous seriez les premiers à chi… https://t.co/rQi6oM2W9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to go to HomeGoods today, but I don’t wanna go to Destin again 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love me some #Starbucks but when you have happy hour it should not be just for the people who drinks coffee!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING SWAT team here for TWO barricaded suspects believed to have firearms. ONE is now in custody.   ▪️Double s… https://t.co/054XYgdwHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WOSfanatic Y seguirá pasando mientras no señor demandados. Yo los demando y quito acreditaciones. Que cubran los p… https://t.co/thHBU9pWtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryLBauer And they’ll immediately invoke the nuclear option in the Senate - as soon as they have 50 votes.  There… https://t.co/iI5GdGaSBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hate text messaging. I feel like I sound so robotic when I am certainly not. I am anything but that. What a weird world we live in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of you let to much drama in your life and that’s why I don’t talk to none of you bitchessss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcshmltn @DonladyWorld Chill. I do need to apologize to my boyfriend though 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeseahern It’s cheetah and says night night in pink cursive. It’s Gucci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alternateDT You think  like an airhead.  Globalists want you to reject Patriotism, Nationalism, morality and God.… https://t.co/VxgwcJt6jW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always tell Seth I don’t want the material things.. it’s the thought that counts. I told him if he picked me a fl… https://t.co/KaFi8RDf4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[The official @Bharper3407 To @Dodgers press conference would be Friday at @camelbackranch and the announcement woul… https://t.co/MEb4XmQVsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes we’re destroying the planet but can people stop sharing inaccurate/false photos to bring light to the issue tha… https://t.co/ARYe0jtpBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah yes. Invite the bachelor that didn’t work out with who he picked and still can’t move on to give Coco advice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joselui15920574 @jm_aguilera_a Ahora, ya no habrá ceremonias cívicas en las escuelas, por el mal ejemplo de López y esposa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codeofvets It will prove to be a disaster just like affirmative action,  those who don’t pass the test get hired a… https://t.co/EViMcbZvXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s she doing as a congresswoman?? And why is she even here in the USA?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indoor cycle! 🚲 I woke up in #beastmode (@ Central Park Recreation Center in Denver, CO) https://t.co/irg3VCJ7ra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamCiaraAndBen @lizzie20114 For some reason I love this twist!  This is really going to be good.  I just pray tha… https://t.co/FPPsPGqSVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dual screen in action for the boys, my type of sunday #suckersunday 🍭 #JonasBrothers https://t.co/NlqXisXQzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends bullying me into not drinking anymore porque borré cassette last party https://t.co/E61Svq2rSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @EricTrump Got that right!!!! We’re not idiots!!! #FISHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prepare to see &amp; hear a whole lot more of @DonaldJTrumpJr, because he makes the case for his father,… https://t.co/ZuWJ1k4EdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker Nothing. Because she is dead inside and it would make absolutely no difference to her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What you deserve is not always what you get sadly though! #NeverSettle #UnconditionalLove #Boundaries… https://t.co/eg1JXmayXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I only could make a deal with God &amp; get him to swap our places @PLACEBOWORLD @KateBushMusic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You sir are an idiot. You go after mothers and kids instead of "real" criminals. Spend time here i… https://t.co/2sBedERT4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well if he’d have kept his legs closed, this wouldn’t be an issue. I mean, what a slut he is, having unprotected se… https://t.co/ZJ9HASlKds]]></document></documents></author>