<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[highlight of the day was definitely seeing this guy drop by for a quick visit.  Spent a couple days with us earlier… https://t.co/UW7WEjpOcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My Intention in #FindingYourRoots is to break down barriers between all of us.” What a commendable mission and vis… https://t.co/jqTmqRfQUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo, what are you doing?!?! Click on the link for the new episode of thenoneofourbusinesspodcast!! Get with it! List… https://t.co/44HM9v3Uuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz día del amor y la amistad #happyvalentinesday para las personas que hacen felices mis días en amor y amistad… https://t.co/j8BTpf659x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robincarlin @SSalisburyShow @SportsTalk790 @SeanUnfiltered Thanks. Miss you to!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see you @FSU_Swimming @coachstudd #lulastchance https://t.co/h563q6RHKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I judge a chicken place by: 1. Is the chicken good? 2. The sweet tea]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Walt Disney World Dolphin Hotel - @swandolphin in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/3U2RilhZJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #fightingwithmyfamily movie about @realpaigewwe @ AMC Classic Galesburg 8 https://t.co/2olJcRMlAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever look back when you were a baby when you got a bath in the kitchen sink and look at it realize how dirty it is… https://t.co/kQLowljTwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morales_mini6 @yudi_gmorales Y’all ready to take an L that weekend or? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WriterMera It is exactly the opposite of what they are trying to mislead the public with. A driver with little pai… https://t.co/AJnm8p6VLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K__Ritchey @GdoubleThree Yeah don't do it. I remember the day I said those exact words.. I've been buying cigs for 4 years now. Don't do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTestyTarheel @ReneeCarrollAZ Ilhan OMAR👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎U S A NO NEED YOU! GET OUT HERE!!! GO HOME 👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sultanparalysis Unless I got to I'll do what I got to  https://t.co/pzJaEkdCzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn we are going to get wasted tomorrow cheering on EPFC! @eplocomotivefc @8thNotchEP Time to March! Oh when the..… https://t.co/01uCUUyOQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Camilla Harris's is praying for Jessie's quick recovery how long does it take to recover from being a liar LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimHill1075 @WilGunter excited for opening day! My mom texted me yesterday and told me she had got two tickets and… https://t.co/0tFlJT7zPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndrew_lawrence It’s just proof of how stupid they really think/know/both their audience is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You belong in prison.  You alone are the biggest threat to America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessyjams10 Time to turn up make sure you hit me up when you get here ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another cold run through Houston @ Museum District https://t.co/w9R7WXPKZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ThEy NoT tHaT gOoD” 😂 @jmartinjr15 @SirFlynnAlot @BLVYNE @BonoNikolic https://t.co/ssbnqo47uf]]></document><document><![CDATA[After two years with this router, Brystle let me change the name. https://t.co/wQ3VuZ34AF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davealevine @roseyx8 I bet if it were Instagram instead of Amazon, she wouldn't be celebrating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@polisands @DennisTharp5 @peterdaou @IlhanMN @AOC CPS is an agency that is filled employees. Employees aren't infal… https://t.co/hQYMhHfRZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMAjunkie @TimBoetsch Hope that wasn't the last we see of the Barbarian in the cage, but either way, thanks for ev… https://t.co/NyP8EAKDU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FreeRealityWinner #FreeRealityWinner #FreeRealityWinner #FreeRealityWinner #FreeRealityWinner #FreeRealityWinner… https://t.co/dbntaBK4e3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zeb01cah @goldenjet64 @dwnign @AnnCoulter @MSNBC @CNN https://t.co/JQDYKyPHlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need immediate enforcement truck illegally unloading on sidewalk Palomar Hotel 2121 P St NW. @311DCgov @dcpd… https://t.co/hAmF55dOhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimRobbins1 @ikebarinholtz Then you and your other wealthy celebrity cronies go to Venezuela and do something. Rea… https://t.co/W8ZA7QDfTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny thing is I didn’t even realize a Hawks PR account existed until a couple months ago. Now I lowkey want that j… https://t.co/WXynI4uSOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess if you're gonna steal a cut of beef, the tenderloin is a good choice😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @SeatGiant ordered tickets off your site for the first time a couple weeks ago and was just curious if it was c… https://t.co/YoNctDtfvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss Wegmans too! And love Patagonia, third on the list. I visit every Patagonia store I can though rarely buy an… https://t.co/nRHJuC3MPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chelsea Clinton just walked by me on the upper west side.  NYC.  No one else noticed.  Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the sad thing about facebook (besides the data privacy and genocide abetting stuff) is that just using the core pro… https://t.co/kw3oAMCgal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Withthewin2 @Brandon_Nocaute I believe it was 30% a tragic knee failure, 70% and powerful uppercut landing right o… https://t.co/dFGjL9h8kO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to send a shout-out to my Loving Parents Today, who deal with my weirdness and non-sense everyday.  Wishing… https://t.co/IR9DNvxJL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Hey Mitch, what kind of #Republican Party are we dealing with? Why did the #GOP stab the #President i… https://t.co/03LybvGgsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[“As we grow up, we realize it becomes less important to have a ton of friends, and more important to have real ones… https://t.co/0fGcj9ZyQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EParkwayMcDs It took y’all this long to realize that if you put bacon on a Quarter Pounder it will work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolee2002 @DennisLaffin *Happy Monday* Flash! Had my Flu Shot! 😎👍 https://t.co/3LSGlh95dC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las Vegas is a wild place. A lot of niggaz out here with fake designer weed, belts, and bitches truth be told 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steve_holt Yeah...*wiping sweat from brow with shaking hand* me neither...]]></document><document><![CDATA[52 years ago today I gave the Mumps to my first grade class! Happy Valentines Day!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericfisher Johnson City , Tennessee where I live is still beating Boston which i don't think has ever happened bef… https://t.co/6wm41jSR5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fotografía Oficial. Tribunal Superior de Justicia del Estado de Coahuila de Zaragoza. https://t.co/RsvJMfUyXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[An observation: While there are certainly downsides to a zombie apocalypse, it would make carbon emission targets c… https://t.co/lXjiW8YLnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwardGeretyIII @MadisonGerety My all time favorite RomCom musical scene, Thanks for the prayers 🙏 and an old memory]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 I wear my Trump stuff all the time. Have since 6/16/15.  I dare anyone to make me stop. And hope hat… https://t.co/zcSxOUpzbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilippBayer Ahhh the days of SGE where I couldn't just throw more nodes into the kubernetes cluster to run my wor… https://t.co/Xt1zjHUS2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsambleaEcuador @ElizCabezas @Hora25Ec @teleamazonasec https://t.co/a2DvJsoKxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkZuckerman Unfortunately health is a major part of people's career successes. If he can't even be healthy after… https://t.co/yHYjSXX9e9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austinfish Freedom = #Innovation Coercion = Repression Litmus Tests Suck #Diversity]]></document><document><![CDATA[The question is, what will they do next time? Because you know there will be a next time. https://t.co/IvS14eJwKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Brooklyn99 embodies the same magic that a lot of shows I watched as a child had where they’re able to be funny and… https://t.co/qoLzYYsNSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise Up, a song by PhillyBlunt2000 on Spotify https://t.co/Y8TG6bZpQZ @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Believe It" https://t.co/NEizB29Ocw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DTVTotal @fpetrocelli Que manera de vivir del pasado, se fue y listo, con cr7 Juventus está afuera de copa de Ital… https://t.co/V8Rsh6Vb5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve Clouse exemplifies what a true leader should be. He is one of several who comprise our Wiregrass delegation..… https://t.co/WlrIzh94r6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Todd_McFarlane I see you’re making a Doom Slayer figure. Lemmie know ASAP when you can show off anything at all, I need it in my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487 @EMluvsPibbles… https://t.co/Lhh8eIsHA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JRHall Yes, that office did. My mug being in there rather marred its overall appearance. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is NOT going to suck.... #SNKRBall2019 #Poison #BelBivDevoe #Nike #SwooshLife @ Portland State University https://t.co/ZE0ubWsFRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YorubaMontana Dear tall people can you guys look ahead and see if the future is bright for our country we have part to play🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jajaja pero qué no sea yalizta aparicio por qué nos tachan de racistas .. por cierto que aburrido esta roma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great idea- maybe this will catch on and we can celebrate America every year on the 4th of July...🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is almost here!  Come paint your next decor item!  We’ll help you paint anything you can imagine!… https://t.co/kALpHcONwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I should start binge watching Arrested Development in preparation for the new season, right @iDeKay?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently Watching/Binging: #TheUmbrellaAcademy https://t.co/M494jJzZ3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two Milestones in Distance Learning  https://t.co/aVDf6yNMid  #ham #hamr #amateurr #amateurradio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SolFGC @defyNW @3irishboyz @406Yeti @ProWrestlingPST @swerveconfident It was very emotional!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beartooth meet &amp; greet. I blame a coworker. (@ BrewDog Franklinton - @brewdogfton in Columbus, OH) https://t.co/0Z5tiS6SVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcstephenson1 @Young23Charlie @janthonylong To be fair Tom, you did say you wanted to watch the internet burn haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thenickviveiros Get in touch if you need an ear. I’m deaf but I’ll nod a lot and smile😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hudd07 Niners fan doing his best to influence the draft on Twitter.  LOL.  Heart is in the right place tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylor_janicek Put my dating site profiles in, not, I repeat, _not_ in an effort to clone myself, just the only "p… https://t.co/GgNZwlE7hH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get that they're on the tail ends of their careers but this seems like SUUUUUCCCHHHH a bad call, especially with… https://t.co/XEpOHr7chQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1974Baseball @70sBaseball @Dbacks One of my favorites too. I’ll never forget that collision at home plate. One of… https://t.co/h03urf2C1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NuggalistParty @SenFeinstein @NASA @intheMatrixxx @StormIsUponUs I’ll look this afternoon. Interesting. Bookmarked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women ain't shit and never will be. Y'all bitches find a damn good guy a piss it away and wonder why y'all are alon… https://t.co/Gdis5eQVCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatholicNewsSvc @peterisely In God we trust.  All others bring data. https://t.co/45F6LD2OW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re either dying because of the cuteness or because you need sleep. #NationalNappingDay https://t.co/WDdPWMozbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast yesterday #homecooking @ Norwich, Connecticut https://t.co/eX4WQQoU2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattSerweKETV @JenJoy I think I told you this before, but I mentioned on air that I'd be hanging out in the beer t… https://t.co/oJtEnYF9Dk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelsNav @WrestlingPastor @JMHCCC @mrshillow @Reid_Hebert @davidworcester Yes, definitely John Worcester.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traffic is crawling in #OrangeCounty on I 85 EB between US-70 Connector and I-40, wreck in the beginning of the b... https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hughhewitt Say 90% of the drugs from MEXICO came thru a Port of Entry....X-RAY Equipment since only currently only… https://t.co/Qy3D1DjQn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop falling straight into the old Republican dreams of splintering Democrats.  The enemy is Trump and his minions.… https://t.co/99X2ARmU60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win tickets for 4th Annual Jack  https://t.co/ymGXgmetgk #SXSW #SXSWParties]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakemangum15 I think it’s either Dani or Jon and the other one will die. I hope they both live tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Coors Light by @MolsonCoors at @schoonerspg — https://t.co/h6mQaB7DC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn’t imagine not having Meltzer blocked so his drivel doesn’t appear on my timeline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOR NANCY PELOSI CONGRESS=JOYFUL MYSTERIES 1.THE ANNUNCIATION 2, THE VISITATION 3. THE NATIVITY 4. THE PRESENTATION… https://t.co/SzIwn7HT2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeDicenNoli @eselpirer @totalrunning La exoneración digital en Mexico aún no es válida legalmente]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethJonesBand I subscribed. Question: will you exclusively be filming in portrait mode?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at SR 436 &amp; Hunt Club Blvd in Apopka, FL https://t.co/Xk1lh7uQQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConsulArborists Excited to have our @SavATree Consulting Group colleague Brock Eastlund attending this year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praising you this morning Lord for the gift of this day, your day, this life, your life, this path, your path and t… https://t.co/hC7lTzCg7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronjgamez @thepstall @cincyplanner @JeffBruder @TomPelissero @nflnetwork @NFL_DougFarrar So now it’s a team game… https://t.co/6uedCMbJW0]]></document></documents></author>