<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Missing my favorite little pal today. 💕 can always use a puppy hug. https://t.co/yWUW1ImRwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sequencer16 @Serremmy @tdpga @sc08960854 @tweets4poppy @Lwsres1 @CaliRN619 @sgrishka @Briteeye777 @mymynags… https://t.co/5eqWMKxu1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am listening to my first baseball game of the year on the radio. I am incredibly happy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's a lie! I had to call 5 different doctors offices to schedule appointments. Turned away. Finally found one th… https://t.co/8kYXwPfN2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mountain Jam by @SouthboundBrews @ Moss &amp; Oak — https://t.co/gm1yCk9h6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinstrasser My deepest condolences to you and your family. Take all the time you need.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maden_marjorie Good night Marjorie. Made it to and from Mass without a problem. Roads all clear. Wishing you a pea… https://t.co/IRZo5V8ykK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LunaLuvgood2020 So sorry and I know from having been there that you have lost a piece of your heart but I like to… https://t.co/pGsDD4wBAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have so much to say and owe so many thank yous, but for now this pretty much sums it up. Let's get to work (after… https://t.co/nUmYy3ajEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wishing every clock in my home could reset itself to #Daylightsavingstime like my #iPhone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayeAnna88 I dont owe anyone...dont bother with my account  balance...lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/nrjGo8gU6j It’s the little things U do that get me super excited 😆 @GavinRossdale @CT3GUITAR… https://t.co/n5VnKBTDWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPDONeill GOOD MORNING COMMISSIONER. IT IS WITH URGENCY THAT I SEND YOU THIS MESSAGE. PLEASE RUN A BACKGROUND CHE… https://t.co/lgXyW6voVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derek_mafs @JReynolds43 I work in Health Care, I've met people who work hard and it's not enough to pay for medica… https://t.co/JZK21SSXvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren This system went wrong in 2003 under Bush and it continues to be ignored. When I enrolled in college 2004… https://t.co/Bhl5L3019J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porter Robinson’s Multiverse Festival: Register for Exclusive Presale Access + the chance to win FREE VIP TICKETS!: https://t.co/KyS3UqF1Ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[We Up One April 5th 🔥🔥  #FredoBangLive In Tyler Tx 🌹  Calling All ETX College Students + All Surrounding Areas ‼️‼️… https://t.co/pLJM7T4rTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Mr. Jordan are you under oath...I think you are the one testifying?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeattleWolf @DeAnnaLeeDance I mean...always my concert bestie @catsiena!! #entourage #soyougo https://t.co/dKlk3M3JAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday - be #empowered, be #respected be #successful #believeinyourself @ladyrensbb @ Byron's Sout… https://t.co/EQbfVCC3nw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Sigma Chi is tonight and if you don’t go, you’re an L7 weenie https://t.co/FGXuEGqJrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathystokes123 @Nickslive I did, they were all 40 and I came from Canada for the show so I didn’t wanna NOT get one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland The petrodollar system originated in the early 1970s in the wake of the Bretton Woodscollapse. Preside… https://t.co/SOXTiYNhlp]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna kick senior years ass and make it the best year of your life! even though i saw u like 45 min ago i miss u al… https://t.co/L8moV3MReI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notbuyingthat54 No need; the damage is done - signed an angry black woman]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would honestly be the best thing ever. Such a simple gesture can go huge lengths]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariecountryman @lilith2u @bunkybun @haloefekti @Communista2 @buell003 @ajamubaraka @AOC @IlhanMN Thank God for Vermont!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleScullion @SheWrestlesTest @parrostroika @AOC The dog and his owner are regulars in the neighborhood and know Alex well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Braxten: Hey Brantley look at that dolphin 🐬 Brantley: I want banana 🍌   Brantley loves bananas. Life should be thi… https://t.co/SyqCZGyBSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Pharmacist job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Staff Pharmacist P… https://t.co/Nu3wG8O5qm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last one from this look I swear! 🌟 🌟 Now booking for prom. 🌟 🌟 •Prep: Urban Decay Cosmetics Optical Illusion Comple… https://t.co/ZVawfCpeac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family day skating is starting now! #sctskatingevent https://t.co/QLQsDBL0lD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family portrait!! Me, Tina &amp; Guillermo (big guy) @ Indian Hill, Ohio https://t.co/jvOHdovBwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This corporate welfare has got to end. Amazon will pay $0 in federal taxes on $11.2 billion profits... for the seco… https://t.co/po7SRBIC4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greendarkknight I thought it was already started but I got banned.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[My big kid is learning how to push fear aside, stand up and speak out #mysuperhero ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ownit  not playing my self this year  @iiipoints . #dexterityfaby #fabiolapierre #festival @ Mana Wynwood https://t.co/XFtwtKDoTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[you put the boom-boom into my heart 💗🤟🏻 // for the past few days the notion of Galentine's Day has struck a chord i… https://t.co/ynPoAtFmK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AzorcanGlobal Agreed. Don’t know why it gets such a bad rap for being crowded and dirty. It is spectacular!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumanNatureLive I recall very well the second time. Justine had that beautiful glow of a new mother and the gorgeo… https://t.co/WOGtkcKwkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[To say that this is a glaring violation of the Second Amendment is an understatement. It won’t keep guns from crimi… https://t.co/5uVZjmh1hk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out here in these #skreets #jiujitsu #hooligan #heelhookhooligan #nogi #eddiebravo @eddiebravo @10pTucson… https://t.co/M08rmj4XZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And then Teddy Roosevelt had to swoop down on his bald eagle and mediate the whole thing”]]></document><document><![CDATA[SNOW REPORT: Snow is starting to coat roads, decks in Lincoln, MO! ❄️📸: Christie Ross #mowx #kolr10wx… https://t.co/V9FDw57fVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kleib323 @drkivela @LivingFamilyCO @chrisvanderveen @SurgeryCenterOK For my type of facility, Texas has its own ve… https://t.co/syJUknKyXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MDHCommMalcolm “Firearms are not only the most lethal but the most common method of suicide in Minnesota....suicid… https://t.co/DsHt285JSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MassimoFaggioli Are you familiar w the Morse mysteries, set in Oxford?  There were advantages to being in a small,… https://t.co/oyS1OGTDt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My people will again live under my shade. They will flourish like grain and blossom like grapevines. They will be a… https://t.co/cDcLS7wB9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberArod20 @slaymarra @serennaaaa___ See gotta tag Izzy too cause she put up with us that whole summer @Izzy_Albrecht2 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EscoBlades The makeup skills in that meme were so admirably next fucking level.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnKimbleSL Should be in jail for HATE CRIME. Just like the poor boys who were protesting abortion and some loser… https://t.co/VtJA7QLuoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[dance gavin dance is always good no matter what and if u disagree ur just wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔊 ON!  ♨️🎶♨️ 🅱️eep 🅱️eep  🎶🎶🎶 Toot toot  ♨️♨️♨️ Bad Girl 👧  Please help me show some love to Lady dazzachic ❤️  For… https://t.co/WYgm369zZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauriesmcintosh @Flipgrid @dbc_inc @burgessdave @burgess_shelley @tishrich @tamaraletter @TaraMartinEDU… https://t.co/9El4VKfcac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take delight in the Lord, and he will grant you your heart’s requests. Ps 37:4 #wordstoliveby @ Syracuse, New York https://t.co/6ShYqd4a2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone else: Happy Valentines Day!   Me: MY CAT HAD HER BABIES TODAY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had a choice between a guy from The Bachelor or Taye Diggs, no contest! Taye all the way! #TotalBellas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu Except that doesn’t explain the look of horror on @MarkWarner face after his private testimony today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's office: the Musical Instrument Museum performing arias and ensembles with azopera! 💃🏻🎶 . . . #opera… https://t.co/xniCYarlFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love The O.C so much damn you caty for giving me a brand new addiction]]></document><document><![CDATA[We wrote some lyrics, encountered a    creeper, had some mediocre donuts, and discovered some gnarly shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jonatha37024189 Um not for me I ain’t have one of these in like 2 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s actually an accomplishment to not take a nap during the day  i nap ALL the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthnicVillian Because if she sat with useful for 80 minutes we need at least 20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckellogs I use a lumbar/Cox’s cushion for my degenerative disc disease.  I can take them with me then to use with any seat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting to notice that people you’ve know the least got your back more than people you’ve known your whole lofe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending this AM crying to Chris Bell like a totally normal person. Yay Monday! https://t.co/ceZeNp3ilB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande my nigga.... why you snapped like that? The streets wanna know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering why I have been so stressed/anxious lately, and I really think it’s because I stopped watching soap cutting videos]]></document><document><![CDATA[What. What ??? Democrats preserve the Constitution ? When ??? why after they twist it, and change it. They never fo… https://t.co/2iO8RdkHcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pictures of me being naughty in Area 51! I also got pictures inside a hanger bay inside. Calling all UFO / Alien lo… https://t.co/UoDSCkv9ou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@everythingloria Same for me back in the day, when people would ask me to bartend at a party bc that was my job then 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clayphillips27 @BradWoodis I don’t see VU doing that now.  I think he gets another year.  I’m as discouraged and p… https://t.co/N4G6ltQUxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biaginger My heart broke a little when I saw that news.  Such a great guy and all he wants is to play ball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyEmrick @ChloeTallent Drunk History but it's explaining music history and/or the plot of operas]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wrote this super sleep deprived and now I’m regretting the way I worded it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrIncio2 @brendalipereira @fmaier50 @Al_jazeeraT Neste caso em específico não, pois a senhora estava se preparando para descer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending Amazon Web Services Women’s Technology Panel! (@ Amazon Web Services in Atlanta, GA) https://t.co/3RFOM1H1je]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcarlson1964 @DonaldJTrumpJr You spelled conservative wrong three separate times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s face it CNN is owned by a corporation. They’re in business to make money. Bringing on Republicans and causing… https://t.co/djd2HMr0Ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyBirthday to my loving son! Life has been an amazing adventure with you and I look forward to what’s ahead 🎉🎂🕺… https://t.co/IDDJzcGgAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost madisonlimelife with get_repost ・・・ Mixing and matching until Ruby Chocolate is back in stock! Drop a 🍫 bel… https://t.co/wFt34HlCSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish your mother loved you like I could’ve that way you would know how to love a woman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kaytlincheyenne Listen to me when I tell y’all.... ALL MY B*TCHES BAD‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great idea for student newspaper fundraising - a competition between rivals. https://t.co/CSGsNvaSA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will pay someone a million dollars to come up with a gluten free hibachi chain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @newsbusters Wonder what he would@have done if two white guys would have been arrested for the crim… https://t.co/N2nWUYETt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyPresidentsDay Mr President‼️ and that’s to Fitzgerald Thomas Grant III aka @tonygoldwyn NOT you Donald Trump… https://t.co/rNij2HSnRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the Venus Concept family, erickasomabelmedspa !!❤️… https://t.co/GZR4L9LvFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went back to high school today. Enjoyed chatting with these future broadcasters! @LSAPioneers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valentinifrank @josh_swickard @donnellturner1 @GeneralHospital Very slowly. Chase’s bulb is pretty dim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a lifelong Christian, I have NEVER seen someone autograph a Bible! That’s just weird. 😳 #DumpTrump #TrumpCult]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay World of Color is back @Disneyland!! .....boooo my shift ends before I get to see it! WHHHHYYY!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Lauren_Alaina for a great concert @TheFieldhouse https://t.co/VBQ7Me1YNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Supervisory Airway Transportation Systems Specialist, SSC Manager -… https://t.co/VQ5a6CxoHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have called Hunter 7 times today and I have NO shame whatsoever @StebbinsHunter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hyaluronic Acid is a large molecule that can’t penetrate into the skin. Scientists at Forlle’d managed to reduce th… https://t.co/5ujW9YRckH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@literallyguess rightfully so and we would be listening to one direction]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being in recovery I think I’ve done more then when I’m on normal life 😳 ... can’t wait though to wear makeup bend a… https://t.co/m3cp4Rx5lR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAtlantic @amandamull Hilarious! My mom always had to separate a portion of the family dinner salad just to appe… https://t.co/Wv6NSAbsDh]]></document></documents></author>