<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If this @starwars trailer edit doesn't blow you away... something is wrong with you! Wow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimTebow is so tight. What a guy. He even made that haircut and shirt look cool on Fallon tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[✈️ ¡A volar con @Aeromexico &amp; @clubpremier_mx! 🤙 Inicia la aventura... 🇳🇿🇨🇳🇺🇸 @skyteam https://t.co/3EgRfbILfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebastianComedy Hey bro I think you're going to need some of that Gorilla snot gel, if your gonna roll w/ the sunr… https://t.co/QcM3CwaHOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[so i hope bakersfield is ready for dev when her payday comes through cause i’m bursting through that town &amp; fucking shit up]]></document><document><![CDATA[vc chega nos estado unidos é mt doido pq as criancinha e os mendigo td fala em ingles eu sou um merda mermao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have fucking chills. Sarah, May you Rest In Peace, you will get justice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMPBS Can we boost the signal on this and reunite this boy Chaco with his missing best friend, #pony Baby Blessing… https://t.co/TU9UExGhrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepCummings What did Ohio State do to make you accountable? Nothing!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TassosMorfis @rushkoff @justinhendrix @pilhofer @jayrosen_nyu @profcarroll @emilybell Abhorrent. The ruin of the n… https://t.co/S08klCDnqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan Binnington has 5 shutouts in his first 18 NHL starts.   You can’t draw it up better than that.   #stlblues]]></document><document><![CDATA[Layover time - Drinking an Anti-Hero by @revbrewchicago @ Berghoff Cafe  — https://t.co/xk1tItnggh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan comical you condemning Cohen for tax avoidance...when can we see @realDonaldTrump’s tax returns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottsantens @JohnCornyn Medicare for All has not even been defined! What polls are you citing because everyone I… https://t.co/NpjulyyFE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManLarrea @MiguelCarbonell La actriz una mujer muy guapa...😍 Gracias por recordar esa buena película, hermano.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in bed with my dogs and honestly, this is why I want to stay single because this kind do love is always]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Blue Screen of Death still exists. Just with a better font.  #neverforget https://t.co/nUiunFfHqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaaaaaannnnd just like that the chances of Trump being elected again goes up exponentially. Should split the vote o… https://t.co/kCT6B4ilFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPAC_TV Conservative Leader Andrew Scheer responds to the prime minister's statement on SNC-Lavalin: "What I'm hea… https://t.co/Z7qAZexCfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaussyBaybeh She’s the ugliest hot chick. Dude get off Twitter. You’re done]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's all I hear on the news ; INVESTAGATIONS !! We the people are paying these congresspeople $176,000.00 + yr. a… https://t.co/4OEwSy5QcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who even ARE these people in D'Amato's mentions still supporting IP in any form?  It seems the Pirate Party may hav… https://t.co/gjmUzVhPz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Good freakin question. Hey @marceelias, we have a question for ya over here....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando la gran mayoria se de cuenta que ¨DEMOCRACIA Y LIBERTAD¨ tienen el significado OPUESTO a la de los poderosos… https://t.co/23DlJX6E9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[.       #PreguntaTonta Las felicitaciones del Gobierno a las mujeres en su día internacional también incluye a #MiriamGermán  ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PollsBraves @DonaldsonsJosh @AlbiesHelmet @dansby_s @culberson_hair @OzziesChainz I can easily lose a poll in Marc… https://t.co/8ErxLxeV4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga  --  great moments are meant for those that share their gift with others. Congrats #Osacrs #Shallow #cooper]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m very much down to earth. Just not this earth.” - @KarlLagerfeld #KarlLagerfeld #RIP #Quoteoftheday… https://t.co/zqOvoj2rwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  Folks.. It should not Take a former Brain surgeon. @RealBenCarson  to Know that IF a Kid already knows there… https://t.co/avL2cG8mOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: Never invest anything into Merrill Lynch. They are mischievous and incompetent. Worst investment firm by far.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haldorson now with a 3-pointer for Corvallis is C.Falls lead is just 4, 51-47, with 6 to play #mtscores]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Craigsa02926817 @RealJamesWoods Agreed. The feds need something to save face. Hopefully this racist is the example?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PatriotsUnite #PatriotsAwakened #WWG1WGA #GreatAwakening #MAGA #Q #QANON #WEARETHENEWS #FAKENationalEmergency… https://t.co/2ssJbWYZpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance @CyndyStachowiak He is scary but the A-Holes going wild in back of him even more so!]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Report: Suspended Oakland priest fled country after accusations of sexual misconduct with a minor… https://t.co/Rv1a4LUnbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is President so let’s investigate his company, Not one charge of Russia collusion with any associate of Trump… https://t.co/5uY7xMAwsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[First thoughts when viewing this IGERS❓🎬 #TrillionCutPolished #GoSeeFRED 🥇🔌 (PRODUCT TAGGED IN THE VIDEO) @ Seattle… https://t.co/geDsuPgNIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTKNet I think this woman will not last long as a politician in this country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders is 77 and @JoeBiden is 76...does America really need an 80 yo President?!!!? Love you Biden but it’s a NO From me. 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellyrigg Nicely put. Or as Gramsci said in a different context, "Pessimism of the spirit, optimism of the will."]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter said the the @NBAAllStar skill contest intros look like a cheap @WWE knock-off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My New Next Door Neighbor In The Upper Peninsula Of Michigan - Thing Is, He's Beeter Than So Many People I Meet, An… https://t.co/kjzMo8ptlb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pens have lost 11 of 14 draws so far, including all 6 on special teams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celso Fortoul es un ícono de la ingeniería, un maestro de maestros en el área de Estructuras; la UCV venció sombras… https://t.co/QyYwd3ZRkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UConnFanDotCom @EricCHenry_ @FTUknights78 I agree with this. @CollinSherwin has told me they do great job of hosti… https://t.co/CvtUgbRWBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidlagreca1 @bullyray5150 @BustedOpenRadio I think many years down the road when @WWE induct @BeckyLynchWWE into… https://t.co/5RFtF32QqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonCorneliano2 ...será “al lado” de esas enormes panzas a punto de explotar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Show us how it’s done Ali girl.   Sugar•Cream Blonde  COLORMELT™️ @ChadKenyon using @Olaplex @Framarint redken Hair… https://t.co/T6BLmvrh8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not even kidding I can’t go one day without spending money I don’t have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Machines and Me | SMA News Today https://t.co/PnSbAqvd0s via @SMANewsToday]]></document><document><![CDATA[For YEARS I’ve been wondering what Scary Movie was making fun of in the basketball scene and I’ve finally found it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kinsanity1 @EJF_215 @BenSimmons25 @Bharper3407 Bro your literally making up hypothetical situations to say Ben is… https://t.co/It2ZYm4JHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sabientje Amazing when you understand that's a representation of infinite energy and it resides in us. I could look at that all day! 🙏😇🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day! Enjoy a PBJ&amp;B with the one you love! There is nothing like it @GHGraceland  . .… https://t.co/zcms5yPU1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiraffeNeckMarc @Mariners @Topsheff42 Justus is saying, "Is this the same dude who embarrasses himself playing MLB the Show on YouTube?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SultanOfShame I am so glad the Reds didn’t trade for him. Real piece of work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizabeethbayy You didn’t even know Today was international women’s day 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roller skating last night!!! What’s great Birthday Party!!! @ Scooter's Roller Palace https://t.co/zqYiKxR7Tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charlie_Z When I was there on Saturday saw a young boy looking at the statue in awe and asking his Dad all sorts o… https://t.co/OIaDwGbtiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cardinalsgifs @DannyMacTV I love watching Cardinals baseball from Oregon. It's like watching it with friends now.… https://t.co/eQBJH9zWjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdflynn Art by practicing Catholics, not Catholic art  Whether in writing, music, or images, it's focused on the o… https://t.co/glTGF0bUgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s @UDaytonAlumni in the House.   We are....not used to crowds!  #chicago #daytonflyers #LOWD https://t.co/szKJ0JNsty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never give up 🙏🙏 Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young Trae Young… https://t.co/Iw1K5kpJ8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaveWeAllGoneM1 @smfehir Just got there floew by the reporters mumbling something!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom They'll all be dead when their children are paying for it. They only care about themselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoorDash_Help I never got my order. I cannot "connect" with an agent. Just @Venmo me my $37.44 back and we're good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austin Dillon led them off of pit road taking no tires. Second through seventh took two tires while Kyle Busch took… https://t.co/QBeCAQ3z0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter (on the left) after dancing in the St Patrick's day parade. Glad I was able to be there to watch her (o… https://t.co/kk7LHwget2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealWayneRoot @sjlnlgl5451 Let’s sent her there for a month then ask what she have to say]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miles Davis - Miles Ahead, the first collaboration with arranger Gil Evans • • • • #nowplaying #nowspinning #vinyl… https://t.co/35AeFYLEJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhioStateOO1 @JoffreyRasul @bptx27 @charlesrandallP @tammigaw @nick_pants Don’t remember anyone forcing him to go… https://t.co/LW8C4713qY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acdlite @sebmarkbage @dan_abramov @pomber Hmm that’s tricky because this hook could be composed with many others a… https://t.co/3uNXHfqvoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought a used book and it used to be in the Drake Newman Parish library at @DrakeUGriff's college! https://t.co/FP0PoyUf0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes @jennydeluxe WANT TNAW WANNTTNNAW WAshiNgTon dot com     ANNUiT CONSTIUTUTION TH iS SPARKLER FOR JULY 4'TH… https://t.co/8VjZA58v4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you say something really offensive, repeating it immediately to the same person makes it less offensive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throw home-court advantage out the window as fan favourite  @DeMar_DeRozan returns to Toronto. https://t.co/aRY8cqtngi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway Q/b (F) train #9553 conductor car. (Numerous) Homeless client(s) sprawled across several entire section… https://t.co/BBj27ar2BT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I once won a free throw shooting contest at my school by hitting 86 of 100 shots then went to the regional tourname… https://t.co/dTeg8ahwJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USAO_LosAngeles PSA:SOME OF THEIR MEMBERS STAGED CAR ACCIDENTS 10 TIMES A MONTH. REST OF USA HAVE 1 ACCIDENTS PER… https://t.co/hTAT8Q2LmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Point High School exhibition team twirling some weapons. #impressive #jrotc #drillcompetition @ North Point H… https://t.co/9f6m4OH7xE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBR_Basketball 36 @BLAZE_HOOPS 30 Things are getting tight. Page with 12 for Blaze Wood with 12 for Blue Raiders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BayonetDivision @DeebsFLA This entire sad story has put a deep gash in press credibility. Will they trim their sails in the future?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goals are getting closer @CSUEBBasketball! Keep chasing! #BeastBay #LetsGoPioneers #BuildTheBridge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus if you are single enjoy it I sure do you don’t have to answer to anyone plus don’t get in a relationship just… https://t.co/yfY4sdPOTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[You really think I'm going to like you just because you smoke weed?   Guess again put head...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, I just read everything that happens in #THEBACHELOR #BachelorNation finale and it's so disappointing]]></document><document><![CDATA[First dive in a month - whoops! @ New Braunfels, Texas https://t.co/7JkRVWV3GB]]></document><document><![CDATA[State Formally Apologizes for Atrocities at Dozier School for Boys https://t.co/L2OuBniwep via @mikevasilinda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or the online shitshow during the Dem convention, fighting over the street protests and the RFK tribute. Ugh. The t… https://t.co/cKvLkyiQdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@connor_m30 loved your passion and driving to the hoop tonight! Respect]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandallMoore26 @SimonDingleyCBC I had liver. With fava beans. And a nice Chianti.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Twittter! As you go about your Friday, please remember the 30 million Americans with the primary chron… https://t.co/dGvE0O01FX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m frfr waiting for the big time rush reunion now like come onnnnnnn https://t.co/diHQheVtWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheUnvirgin Go get more shots, cause you ain't building any "real" immunity to it. Don't be surprised if your memo… https://t.co/mcbapYIUZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_daniellenunes_ @DelanceyStarkes Delaney took to long to respond...I had to steal his thunder!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[WBB: Halftime. @Miles_wbb 20, @KYSUWBB 17. Mya Millner 5pts, @sakinaaa20 4pts, 5reb. @TheSIAC @MilesCollege… https://t.co/q8xTvik06Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@28delayslater @Teslatunity Honestly... I'm pulling a hard Fred. I still call 🐂💩 on the door handles hahaha but....… https://t.co/sLaNH3oArh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TakamasaKashima @XSLasvegas_Ken What’s so boring about Elon Musk’s company?  Seems pretty interesting to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heathermlister @Raspberry_Pi @DesignMakeTeach @nathan_stevens @jigar_patel @thenerdyteacher How’d it work? Haven’t… https://t.co/46fX1PR0te]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravelBugsWorld @LGSomewhereMcK @ggjourneys @OrganicRoadMap @Fit_life360 @poetixtrip @ExploreThePrime… https://t.co/tLZMKyHQIH]]></document></documents></author>