<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to @Empress54681342  we love you! Hope you enjoy your special day! https://t.co/B5m7t3swOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIVE REPORT ON CHANNEL 11 MORNING NEWS--Police are on the lookout for a Jeep Wrangler that damaged parked cars in a… https://t.co/SwMHXQ4k3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope that the B.Smith reality show   does not see the light of day. He won't survive TV if he can't stand the hea… https://t.co/s1RwSS0urd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tradition. dbneal2208 rileyparks17 @ Glazed &amp; Amused Paint Your Own Pottery https://t.co/yusurSkDnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will start Arts in OUR Schools Month right now! Shout out to this amazing student photographer Erica from DuVal H… https://t.co/EHNw6Z4pmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSUbrent @DamonICT79 @tylerjcrow @ParsonJeffrey Awww but I cant hate on Pooh!! Adorable]]></document><document><![CDATA[lost a lot of things and a lot of people on the way to figuring out who I am, but now I know that I don’t need anyo… https://t.co/ULs7xipU7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Press conference is about to begin to update triple homicide of Six Nations victims. https://t.co/dhFDJJWZCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SXSW2019 has taken over the city. And it’s gorgeous ❤️ https://t.co/2t8vuKpQ47]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suckermouth catfish https://t.co/tSWkKVPhtf  We had a couple of these. One was named Plucostamus Bob, for the band… https://t.co/GdKrVyLIsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TWPundit @StoneColdRoger Crisis management can not help because your going to jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[82% sure my 82 year old Dad is @StephenAtHome’s #1 fan. He NEVER misses his show and does this👇🏽 throughout. https://t.co/zDzyjRuNlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“... all of it is growing you for the person you’re becoming, for a future you can’t even imagine.” -… https://t.co/FL2hJaXOin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiest when I’m with you 💗 Screenshot this pic to get shoppable product details with the https://t.co/yUIqtP5sen… https://t.co/O42bMusUdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianFDCollins @tinderdistrict @LucyGoesDating @TheSerialDatist @UnluckiestDater (2/2) one of the sweetest kids.… https://t.co/pEAVJGz4Q7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered this @ChaseRiceMusic #sweepstakes on #tunespeak.  Follow the link to enter and help me earn entries. https://t.co/pWaWhwlHI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence @dartmouth @DineshDSouza The Democrats are now the party of intolerance, hate, and racism. They only wa… https://t.co/PZb0sXtqK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LacedUpBreezy I low key love my cave when we get a house set me up with a room in the basement so I can escape🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind many Public Information Officers is an Army. ❤️🚔💙  This is my immediate Army.  I could not have made it thro… https://t.co/wuxCpFmByi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parc National de la Jacques Cartier 🇨🇦 #quebec #landscape #park https://t.co/Ns3wL8DIsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s weird when you meet a guest at your hotel in AZ who knows your pediatrician from 20 years ago from a small town of 8,000 people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my boyfriend have matching blankets and I love it.❤️ https://t.co/O9PW5Qao17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omizzle13 @ahl @AHLBruins Yes, AHLTV will still being broadcasting the game, just with no audio]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the 112,578th thing that makes me miss #teaching English! Have you read Updike’s Gertrude and Claudius? It’… https://t.co/N0aoEQsuRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[ladies, let me hear yall make some noise for lactose free coffee creamer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You truly are stupid. Those are America tax dollars. You are no hero to the working people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[on a scale of 1-dumb bitch, how dumb of a bitch would I be to revisit my splenda daddy days?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aileenlee @ArlanWasHere @imchristiepitts @sarahkunst @pjux @meghalexander @suzywillow @pocketysun @nakisnakis… https://t.co/qwMG5s9ne7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@King_Ignant I cut my back while I was shaving it. You can’t read or something???]]></document><document><![CDATA[#misspryor #misspryor2019 @ Avra Performing Arts Center https://t.co/qHVt3LzObI]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realdonaldtrump, health care shouldn’t be just for people who can afford it. Blocking care at Planned Parenthood… https://t.co/77PRM3Y2ki]]></document><document><![CDATA[The views from my new listing at Marquis Residences in Downtown Miami. Gorgeous two story 1/2 + den with 1,675 sf… https://t.co/mYXfb78WE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen!! Behavior charts are humiliating. Never understood why some think they were a good idea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The teacher I work with walks into our classroom and goes “here, I went shopping at Zara this weekend and got you a sweater” SO NICE 😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally my school was the only school that said screw President’s Day, screw a three day weekend!🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cinnatweets @AsianEd @storyofthedoor I once lived there a year and a half. Best public transit, friendly people, a… https://t.co/AIO5cAau7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t ask people for much, ever. But when I do, I’m somehow asking for too much...so I’m not asking anyone for an… https://t.co/AlZ0P1FiaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl Citation?   You're an attorney???  GMAFB!  Assert without evidence, reject without evidence.  Dumbass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my newest listing in #OrmondBeach! Tell me what you think!  #realestate https://t.co/1Dad62ZdEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My princess had a ball at Disney fr hbd🎂🍧🍨🍡🎁🎈🎊🎉🥰😍😘 https://t.co/PVRqFMWg5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why On Earth Is Ivanka Trump even entertaining the Idea of Marketing VOTING MACHINES- NO FREAKIN WAY!!!!! 😱😰😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickFriedell @CodyWesterlund @chicagobulls a coach that relates to his players]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I overhear kids say at Skyline: A thread (not sure why I haven’t done this yet but here’s the start of it)]]></document><document><![CDATA[No mention of two of his grandkids in his obit because of divorce? Petty. Soooo petty. Dont know why I expected bet… https://t.co/hARSRTYUzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGrimes2 @EdKrassen And there are going to be increasingly whackadoo judges out there now that McConnell has Trump… https://t.co/DzBikgIGcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasCru2019 Congress cannot indict or impanel a grand jury to hear evidence.  From what can now be inferred from… https://t.co/7dn3elrmWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Femalewelder @rocko611 @rcale1776 @realDonaldTrump @POTUS I heard that before....]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat is meowing because the door is closed. So my dad is meowing back at him so my cat feels heard. 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my gyno is really gonna do me so right, and then just walk out? K 😔💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just passed a billboard that said have a super mar10... IT SAID HAVE A SUPER MARIO...... MARCH 10 SAYS MARIO.......… https://t.co/0M7MehkOf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds like a scam. I hope someone (or committee) will be doing oversight on this "fund" so @IvankaTrump doesn't fu… https://t.co/pymu2XssXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rex_rexchapman Wow. Somehow, I don’t think their insurance company knows they do this. 😳😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always the highlight of serving on the @TriCedu Foundation Board- hearing first hand from our extraordinary student… https://t.co/MOwPjXCCU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our students look up to every adult in the building!   “I want to be Jacob Pitts, because he comes in our class, fi… https://t.co/rMqgxbE4d4]]></document><document><![CDATA[REPORT: Democrat congress members took $60,000 trip to attend Beyonce concert in South Africa… https://t.co/3LXIZcLhO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #StAugustine #FL  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/w8cmg2yw4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm all for higher taxes if it means destroying capitalism if we're being honest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does Instagram show you the persons name you DO NOT want to see liked a persons photo? Like um show me one of t… https://t.co/h9bYeZ9C0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find me at AA E10 at @LBComicExpo all weekend! And join @womenondarkside at 2:30 today in room 104A. Mention this t… https://t.co/bZKfSDEgjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my students for sharing their tech skills with seniors today! #hightechtrojans @scms_trojans… https://t.co/gnxyWne7eS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last daddy daughter dance for the Holzrichter House. Bittersweet. ri.chip101 @ Kohler, Wisconsin https://t.co/Hkq0Neu1lB]]></document><document><![CDATA[La santidad hace que el oído de Dios esté atento y su bendición a mi favor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llego por la Payola al depa y se me conecta el wifi desde el carro. En mi casa no llega ni a la sala no mamsss]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/4ths of the team that made today's campus tour happen. Great job Greg, Gerald, Eric &amp; Daniel (not pictured)!… https://t.co/H2AiRcIKsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol anytime something bad happens or Ella gets hurt all she says is “ no daddy!!” Even if he’s not in the room😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet @JackPosobiec We literally wouldn’t do that to a dog!!! 🤯🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queens 👸🏽 are born in March!! Waiting on my Birthday!! @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/JeTnLCseTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings Mr Cohen just lied again to congress, there are many witnesses that can collaborate this, will you cal… https://t.co/Un7A5vf85t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrs3Marotto @Lafayette_25 There is a great mystery doug about the heart!  Email/text me if interested.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating one of my favorite ladies birthday!!! Love you, my friend!!! @ Hank's Fine Steaks And Martinis https://t.co/BMVzHOVU4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally was genuinely happy today and I haven’t felt like this for about a week straight. It’s feels amazing an… https://t.co/Z4qGz1JpP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FeedYourFandomEntry https://t.co/477gVsjIGs ❤️🧡💛💚💙💜💘💘💘 Ends 7/31/19 ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLDandMe @protoword @s_redmondUofU When she is medicated for her ADHD, then we can better target her language skil… https://t.co/n7Vbx68DfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump His manuscript wasn't written under oath. You really do not know how laws work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaauOlalla_9 @Onepiece_Frases @MechanicalJapan @NoePrieto119 Jajajajaja friki, mucha suerte 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[At work counting the safe when i heard “Nobody that works 40 hours a week should live in poverty” 😭👏🏾 PREACH 🗣‼️ ca… https://t.co/nEdijYkWtI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #24hBlueMTN online auction is open &amp; I'm bidding to win a tandem skydive courtesy of @SkydiveToronto &amp;… https://t.co/wO3q1HMkVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBethPhoenix I made this for you ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/Rjn16f98PH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WEAU13News our dog Benny might be small but he's certainly enjoying the extra snow! https://t.co/rbezs8PMyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dailystem @atkauffman @Makerspaces_com @jsnhubbard @DianaLRendina @gravescolleen @LFlemingEDU @3rdGrade_STEAM… https://t.co/L786W9AVCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sad Truth!   I hope and pray for your success in all matters!   You cannot let these obstructionis… https://t.co/Nh4ZNhpY2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toaster charger- phones pop up when fully charged. I. Want. One. https://t.co/ngDnxVVea8]]></document><document><![CDATA[as a human i’m generally a VERY sleepy person... but concussed me is even SLEEPIER which i did not know was physically possible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaVS49 I’m a redhead I would be so so pissed off and still be pissed over it lol. I’ll do the jump, but I ain’t kissing ya lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyond disturbing. Trump once again defending murderers of American citizens. https://t.co/Zi0DhzTbyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gil_Brandt Gil, but doesn't that valuation include the stadium, which he paid for?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When this deal with North Korea is over it will obviously be VERY historic. We patriots should immediately begin ca… https://t.co/oMX3fEJped]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Everything should always be velvet.” Just making sure y’all know the tea!! https://t.co/oBHZ6UN054]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still Life With Porch. #butterflydown #muddyshoes #mixedmedia on #wood $1,3737 #im me @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/ciz9KNuJAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #WWcruise is heading to all new destinations including Italy, France,Spain!Are you ready for an adventure?  Sav… https://t.co/VDMbwqxTra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze For generations people have wondered if they should bring a child into this world full of problems. This is not a new thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KinderKelly69 @Burtonsuper2018 @ibpyp @BurtonSchools @lombardibears @badwolfpress @mrsgamblesclass Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who in the HECK would vote this crap? This is the same governor of wa. State crying he needs help gov. Wa. State,sp… https://t.co/RFGNKBlwCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Installing solar is great on every property. Grow Solar - California! #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarEnergy$]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChefChristinaW thrilled to see ya tonight at Gordon’s burgers! We’d be honored to by you a drink if you are out and about tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffinOhioGov Not enough to conceal school.putting our kids at risk! Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KariLakeFox10 @FOX10Phoenix Praying for him, family and friends in this dark hour!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing Q1. @AudreyDesisto  #CyberMindsChat #RuhGlobal #InternationalWomensDay2019 #Cybersecurity #womenInCyber… https://t.co/GXhjoFiKjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @steph93065 If its heads up I keep it. They say its pennies from someone in heaven saying hello. If its h… https://t.co/SNoDkXsqY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I love the color blu so much? Well, it may be because when I was. Kid, mother doused me in a pink room. I me… https://t.co/pD49tOj6kz]]></document></documents></author>