<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@yashar First the towels, now this? Add a jersey tomato to a burger in July &amp; it’s heaven.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So does anyone know if they are renewing #Manifest? I want to know what happens! #RenewManifest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnjames75 @RunnersLifePTB Ahhh! I'm jealous. I didn't make it down there this year. Good luck and enjoy the after party 🥣🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeptofDefense I believe we sell those at our Walmart’s in Florida, bring your ID though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emmetcahill Morning my time!Hope you’re having a blessed Sunday!!......xoxo........ https://t.co/aFLDq3Ro9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Fellow Readers, I accepted a challenge from @jensweda @mckenrickreads and  @terpteach to post 7 favorite books… https://t.co/noSKacNgdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariagalanis @MrBillySpicer @iTeacherLauren @jg_jgarrett @JennyLehotsky @ice_il I left too soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Schleuse @dylanbo it is insane but it is heavy and wet, not our beautiful Colorado champagne powder]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @PattyeLJ @realDonaldTrump @Varneyco It’s too bad that’s happening in Venezuela but nicely enough, our… https://t.co/ZTRvYbXGVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[all excited, but we don't know why. maybe it's 'cause we're all gonna die.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is baffling. If you hate kids and don’t have the patience why are you working with them???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@46_still @NO1GifQueen @michelleismyna2 @linablue @LJLanham Not fair girl we be here for you xo 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[The teachers @frps_Talbot love their public schools #FundOurFuture https://t.co/dv3Kmj2BVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[D25 ELA teachers keep the magic alive with a strong emphasis on independent reading!  Proud of these teachers!… https://t.co/VtWOsRuDG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you. I love you. I love you Kylie 💕💕💕💕 @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/xeYuMvXDgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix WE LOVE OUR SHOW #WynonnaEarp #FightForWynonna @SYFY @IDWPublishing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dream big! 💯 #robbiegmindset #robbieg #success #wealth #money #cashmoney #business #sales #marketing #amazonsales… https://t.co/2PnuGFw8gB]]></document><document><![CDATA[im ashamed that I’m almost 22 years old and still can’t put eye drops in myself 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdils @wpmodder I heard a story once about a dead man who was told by a hearing person that they could hear farts… https://t.co/z2qpO2qSuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@William79304674 @norwegian76 She be usin' too much Wite-Out, not surprising really.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only one way out! Remove her from Congress and all committees! She doesn’t represent any true American!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren Your point or concerns would have been better received if it was done with less whiny shitty comments.… https://t.co/S7parQdCgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow @JEEPREISENDE He should be charged with a hate crime. If he succeeded, how many Trump supporters would be in danger?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miltonlaura @kinsellawarren @sunlorrie Statements from 33 ministers shortly after JTs fiasco of a stump speech? Th… https://t.co/W9uh6XiWMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win Tickets To See Shawn Mendes on August 23rd! https://t.co/gl0XU9qWiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[CONCEPT: Drunk History, but instead of comedians, it’s professors/PhDs/experts who are just very excited about their topics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csjennings Interesting.. had to google what you are talking about.. sounds like another college cover up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasmined_brown Y’all ain’t ready for all that. Vegas about to be another level 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Renewed the season tickets and got tickets for Miami today.  Is it football season yet??🐊🏈😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[So if you ever fall you  You know that I’ll be there  I know how to put my ego aside :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycsebi Omfg never forgetting that weekend. That weekend is what made us best friends 😭🤣❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bernieadufe @Knockadoo @TarynDeVere @beannfatale @Lady_FMP @SAFEIreland We’ve reason to be hopeful for this change… https://t.co/93x5JxubQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[... Hyde/Market/Grove, that middle finger was at, ne?  Don’t know why but it was one of the more interesting Versio… https://t.co/8ZzIBeQGJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bon_vivant007 @RikRankin @Star54iwas @RRankinFans Damn girl. 😂😂😂 Finish off that bottle!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@get4208 @CoryBooker another false Flag and you keep peddling pond scum Booker it was staged and lynching is a crim… https://t.co/lAWDYr3Snl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Odessa_Baseball @odessar7_stuco #1 You let someone sit in my seat at lunch yesterday. #2 You weren’t even at school!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevincorke Thanks!!!  I need glasses or a bigger computer screen.  Thought the clocks were lemons and didn't see the chocolate chips 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay but why didn’t the guy who was recording do something??? “hitting her more”🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M44582166 @heroldbarton @Edward733 @BeverleyGlazer @exprezoe1 @vallouard @jeancla01685290 @AAvallones… https://t.co/YFILkP6juu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me:  Medicaid lady at work: MEDICAID IS THE SECOND COMING OF JESUS. WHY WORK WHEN YOU GET HEALTHCARE FOR FREEEE. EV… https://t.co/XvrffQptkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day @jujfilo  you make life bearable. You make me smile when nothing else can. I love you so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[embroiled in Russian money laundering scandals and whose loans to Trump are coming under intensifying scrutiny.  Co… https://t.co/e1PMoco2kX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Eweee. Who thinks about the my pillow guy. https://t.co/l0GAQIMI9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kitosan Can science also make this a real thing? https://t.co/66neHzoCjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prableeeenkaur When a peer cuts me off (btw this has only happened with male classmates), I clear my throat and ma… https://t.co/gOmnH1Z1jS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Life Time Athletic - Syosset https://t.co/FxPs1qpG5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asm @IanCalderon and @fionama countered that the AB211 deduction would be worthwhile to motivate middle-class famil… https://t.co/XPkoXh5rqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorththeWar @LewisHa77 @marshallmyers53 @growth_channel @Judy_Cockerton @SobAlert @scamp246 @Gerizentime @p_ganzel… https://t.co/dalKapCK4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #IWD2019⁠ ⁠ and I am proud of the great influence of women in the workplace.  #walkthetalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que risa cuando mi yo de 10 años realmente pensaba que se iba a casar con Nick Jonas. 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trishsumerlin @JordanUhl @CheriJacobus too far left for me,  and he had the opportunity to bring us all closer tog… https://t.co/wTogaBe33M]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's your type of medication you like to hear? #reggae #Dancehall #rocknroll #RnB #country #classicrock… https://t.co/k2NndXmIDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@transitrunner Wondering what “zone improvements”  really means. This is my neighborhood they are talking about. 🙌🏻🚎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Apple @Tim_Cook #investors  #investments #investing #stocks #StockMarket @NYSE @Samsung #innovation @SEC_News… https://t.co/diLf8ssmet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #25thAmendment #25thAmendmentNow #25thAmendment #25thAmendmentNow #25thAmendment #25thAmendmentNow… https://t.co/PYIg31vC5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC He doesn’t have the stamina to do so it’s written all over him 😲]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump You have no moral high ground. This Presidency is one of the most corrupt in hist… https://t.co/NlyBNypgCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Together let’s turn potential to possible.” It was a great ‘Night of Soul’ Fundraiser for a meaningful cause yeste… https://t.co/HgTSQBCrFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rogerasalways To me he made our flag dirty.. like dropping it on the ground. No respect,, no decorum ,, no diploma… https://t.co/cEdU68Z0hT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like how is this even real. You said he was a victim then said he was lying and now there is evidence that he was t… https://t.co/epmd2mai9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers to a fabulous #ITKWM yesterday! #Saturday https://t.co/Hq5wbHwDko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of telling us we won’t believe what happens next- JUST LET US WATCH what happens next!! #BachelorFinale #bachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @SEPHORA in New York, NY https://t.co/4CGYa3jpUD https://t.co/9MMHkDOoxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillboard FWIW I thought your lesbian canon tweet was the most hilarious of the night and now I follow you. People need to chill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like if someone in your life brings you joy, you should definitely tell them and tell them often. Life is to… https://t.co/dWoRMeyjqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confront me first if you feel like I've wronged you, especially if we cool. Don't hold shit in that's going to make you sour towards me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure you head over to my friends page and support head over to FB  #Kira N Kasan Variety, was busy yesterday b… https://t.co/di95qspgaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: I wanna go to Ireland  Will: arrrgh matey me: ....what? that has nothing to do with Ireland. 😂😂😂 this dude]]></document><document><![CDATA[White people think of the first black person they know and try to compare you to them like it ain’t racist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Just wow. The view from my front porch. #iawx #Blizzard https://t.co/s6nYn802qA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son is upset that Kofi didnt win at #wwechamber I say he is main eventing #Wrestlemania If not, then I will have… https://t.co/tOyQdDUM0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[The type of programs Sanders wants to implement if he's elected are far worse for our country imho than how Klobuchar treats her staff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeSilverman7 or even were instead of we're.... since I was an English Major]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffpitto @4everNeverTrump @realDonaldTrump The Texas Land Owners are suing him because his wall is cutting direct… https://t.co/jbXYZghYYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrAndyNgo @Woodshedder Chicago Poluce Department released a statement rejecting this hoax angle. Y’all look crazy as hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Betsy contains multitudes and she will sit anywhere she wishes. I think she looks especially lovely atop that blue… https://t.co/JlUHIEpA9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@husky_superman Yeah, I haven't done any of the month long ones in a while. Just too busy with other things over the past couple months.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexaanaliz @ICEDOUTFLAMES @StillDrippedd Pls cuz u running up my minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two different papers on Rhinoceros in the age of Trump. I love absurdism. And learning about Ionesco. #matc19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @kle317 There is a reason libtard is a real word in the dictionary]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to wake up at 8:30 tomorrow but im setting my alarm for 6:30 just so i can press snooze and fall back asleep cuz im a sadist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VDOOZER loved the live Fb chat, thank you! I'm dying for some new yet old to you #undateable gear or anything you'… https://t.co/rIsacq7Nt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I now fight with the Night King! I just entered for a chance to attend the #GameofThrones S8 premiere. How do you p… https://t.co/uaJefQn1Hs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway the app isn’t working. What are the upcoming times for the downtown R train from 63rd- Rego Park??]]></document><document><![CDATA[A  rare #sunny day in February ☀️ ☔️ @ Costa Mesa, California https://t.co/Lilnx1HBzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else notice how #TheBachelor nails the table runner at every meal? I, for one, appreciate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Concert - P!NK  ... amazing show and super happy to share it with this sweet pea. #pink #firstconcert crazycu… https://t.co/O5TalrlEU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@librarian_tiff I know you rocked it!!! You prepared such an amazing keynote! 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jasmine is sweet. It reminds Us of Beauty regardless of #FakeNews and True Purpose In light of true reality this da… https://t.co/SaLf6bMVqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this special moment benteen @zgfisch and her mom getting ready. Getting ready moments are a special because… https://t.co/3QIWx0KBxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss being skinny I’m tired of hating myself again it really is like I’m reliving sophomore year with these damn… https://t.co/3cV8lt0mXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caitopotatox I was drinking one or two red bulls daily. I’m two weeks redbull free! At first I was literally vomit… https://t.co/6wca3WCcyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime I also believe he has ties with Russia Kelly ann has a problem with truth when it comes to trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sugars from the sweetest little booga ❤️ Thann you for letting me be your mommy! #peytonelza #Nashville… https://t.co/Fymm9XKuMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been sharing it w/ faculty in synchronous professional development sessions. I love your work on emotions and… https://t.co/GItFhxJZMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so happy to be home and I have no travel plans for sooooooooo long 🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenaFriedman Ummm, @JenaFriedman - Usually you’re right on point, but it is hack spin to take that essay out of co… https://t.co/3WyuRvsrze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFAaction @IlhanMN @AyannaPressley @RashidaTlaib @AOC Unless @IlhanMN stops the racist tropes I will NOT support her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the Vice Admiral Norman shoe is yet to drop. That could be even worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_Brick Ugh it's tough going on main roads - shoulders are either full of water or slush.  Be careful!]]></document></documents></author>