<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Coach_WisemanJ @LHSFball He looks like no freshman I’ve ever.  Just ask the defenses that tried to stop. He is special.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thx for having the courage to continue fighting for the rest of us Congressman. @ABC hacks are so arrogant and bias… https://t.co/yLRqd5KJ6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[And Then They Came for Me. Remembering the World of Anne Frank @LexArts was an exceptional performance! I wish came… https://t.co/UqCKxcRKDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters Please Maxine,  you and the swamp should be impeached.  Not wasting our tax dollars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is he smoking crack? Someone shake that guy. He needs Jesus and some serious rehab.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Long Island City, NY in Long Island City, NY https://t.co/gUMrxozVqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I just remembered I’m seeing @MariahCarey in one week!!! https://t.co/axWnM3tNX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY BOYS are in town to go cruisin' with me! #Miami #BahamasBound @ Port of Miami - Norwegian Sky https://t.co/qvJXHGuLEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerperry Happy birthday Queen R.I.H. yes Tyler were. I am henry County we had tornado watch from 1:30 to 2:00pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frickindannie Take a case of beer to Home Depot and leave it on the back dock. The guys might be willing to have s… https://t.co/Szub8j1FEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamiehop27 @Yo_Geertz @NYYSportsTalk I think the Phils are banking on the DH coming to the NL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[and so it begins! Opening Day 14u Banditos Georgia! @BanditosGeorgia @BanditoBaseball @Banditos_FL2017… https://t.co/6WVwFyMfRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FFBehavior Done by delivering great leadership program with measurability! Extreme Leadership @FDIC @BobbyHalton https://t.co/jh2qIl65zM]]></document><document><![CDATA[One year go. Did I really know what awaited me? No i didn't. I didn't know anyone in Jacksonville. It was a new lea… https://t.co/3L9qJam71r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terisa_clothier @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump ...and his approval rating has steadily gone down sinse he took office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Political operative in tainted North Carolina House race indicted: The political operative at the center of the ele… https://t.co/l7xwGx7Js0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oscxrvm Se resuelve dejando una tarjeta de crédito, tienen buenas coberturas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@showupforthis Charles Manson and Neil Young, and we are going to transform our old telecasters into weapons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEPFuller Brutal dataset to collect. You either need access to unaired C-SPAN camera angles, illegal video taken f… https://t.co/sFTQXyFxGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shittt it’s time to throw that shit the fuck back this Thursday and Friday. Last night of black history month is LI… https://t.co/1BeKrtQcRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[sleep really hits different when you are laid up with that special person your your life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter @espn @JeffPassan Wow congrats if you have any extra I could use 50,000 if you have it lol if you don… https://t.co/GKQQDRnznZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great first day with @SenBlumenthal. Proud to join this fantastic team! I will be based in Hartford serving as th… https://t.co/6fnFtppmu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT My old home.  I used to sleep on the #LAMetro every night until the trains stopped running at 12AM, and then s… https://t.co/ppQJWuXGma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BloodwingBX @CheerfulWarthog @pattonoswalt @jack For us, sure.   There is a large population of very, very dumb people on this platform.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelFails I also cringe when I’m about to go into a meeting and I hear “ok let’s gather the troops”]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are going to see #TheLEGOMovie2 lads, we are sitting in the funny smelling theater right now waiting on the preshow junk!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Apalladino8912 @ArcticPanther86 @Orfeu_Negro_ @marxistfilm I could support that. Just think D Will is as good as a… https://t.co/eOnZt9pEvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby’s All Right’s Baby’s Neon Sign #babysallrightbk #babysallright #williamsburgbrooklynnyc #williamsburg… https://t.co/i4ulJp09tm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saying I wouldn’t have been mad if Russ threw the ball out of bounds “accidentally” and hit that annoying ass kid 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyday I find a new song from astroworld that I like... maybe I have been missing out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lakers won and Kings and Clippers both lost. Now that’s more like it. 👀👌🏽😏 #LakeShow]]></document><document><![CDATA[They, just like the rest of us, want to see them do better. It was just handled in a way that didn’t explicitly mak… https://t.co/DJi5qsyOtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm only interested in free agents that can actually help the @Chiefs. 🏈🏈🏈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drjjdyck Democrats, imo, won't win on "(white) nostalgia" or "policy." They need energy.  No Dem since 1964 has wo… https://t.co/E8u8bz3I53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BilldeBlasio @Chirlane @RedSox Every day that goes by, you’re lucky we can’t recall you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hastin I’m not. It’s a weird mesh of like 90s, with some mid 2000s thrown in, topped off with an 80s icon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PUBG PRO LEAGUE LAUNCHES WITH A NEW LOOK  From SCCG Management Esports Director Anthony Marquez:   “The 2019 Season… https://t.co/WobTmlUFyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 6th grade team decided to take a picture with the fish that most represented us in the aquarium. @DeJongEWA moo… https://t.co/8SxJ2dCAmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the opportunity, along with Councilwoman DignaCabral, to welcome @DrJabalUffelman, CEO of @RejuvChip, to the… https://t.co/TcveIRk1F6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Henastynasty @supermanebony Haha Rico ain’t got shit on me I see , I lost my virginity to this nigga and I ain’t d… https://t.co/tMzrbXpLAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday February 22 - Grabien News:     Maxine Waters Not Ready to Believe Police in Jussie Smollett Case;     Fox N… https://t.co/ICDxWLfv6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Korea rebuilding long-range rocket site, photos show https://t.co/Umkvl63fwa via @nbcnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSource Haha what a clown! 🤡 their music blows and rap HAS been mainstream since long before his shitty group]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElMoscanoche @MarkHumes_Art Oh I do fine at client work. I just suck at closing the inbound leads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crsmik1 @jimmykimmel @realDonaldTrump Maybe same reason it wasn’t a big deal when it came on tv 🤷🏽‍♂️... but love… https://t.co/PkXtERQIY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash stand up to Trump? why doesn't she sit down and work with him for us citizens.            Which she do… https://t.co/dVA8lEtpwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los nietos de Maria Chavarría extrañan caminar con la abuelita, sus cuidados y sus comidas. Han pasado dos semanas… https://t.co/9pYw5zhcLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting trend here @Sportsnet @RogersMediaPR. Shoutout to @SNCaroline though. #wherearethewomen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLBRandomStats NL East: Jacob deGrom and Michael Conforto I'm not biased at all shut up]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only cruise I’m trying to go on 🍻@PostMalone @rriproarin https://t.co/SzZIWq4JDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sawyer appreciation post!  I am so proud of this kid. He has more energy than anyone I’ve ever met, and he can’t ho… https://t.co/NqNezdcX3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SmallWorld. Sitting next to John, who was @TONY22BISHOP JUCO coach at Richland. #AllTimer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KARISSAPUKAS Depends on the location. The Midwest it’s more common due to severe weather.]]></document><document><![CDATA[RAs really woke me up at 2am banging on door bc they said they could smell weed. Took all my shit then made me show… https://t.co/FISfh2K1ce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YWorkFT @justinsuntron Read more. You know very little. Tron was built on a Google based platform and not an ETH c… https://t.co/ql5sritkJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanneByers111 Yep. We'll have the game on WBUT 1050 AM, WLER 97.7 FM or you can stream it on https://t.co/AC9MwIVF53]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Pirelli’s Isola unfazed over graining issues seen in first week of #F1 testing  https://t.co/y2BgaUbwe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are united with all life that is in nature. Man can no longer live his life for himself alone.  -Albert Schweitz… https://t.co/eyVUZmjtCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Jim_Jordan #FactsMatter In Any Investigation. Biased Ideology Does Not Work In Any Investigation And In Fact, You… https://t.co/PTtxWIVLFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruBisonPride @BisonBoysHockey @Spud_Hockey @BHSBison @BisonSuperfans @BYHA_Bison @Joe_McNamara10 @nathan2932 No l… https://t.co/EPk7NPJZx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieslysz Morning! Have to check , i know it’s over half a foot here in Stamford.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No se enoje, nadie de @Rayados quiere que hablen bien del equipo, nadamás que no desvíen las transas de mis Tiiigue… https://t.co/muiPsraZ24]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xenette_ See I’m not following this logic cleaning is boring and tedious and everything shitty in life I just dist… https://t.co/LzuPPmiGxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolute state of this 🤣 (Policies are saaaad, the old way of politics)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Titan IPA by @greatdividebrew at @minturnsaloon — https://t.co/g3MpdcskHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Her Name Was Trinidad”©️By Kevin Quinn #art #ArtistOnTwitter #artcollector #arte #artgallery #artist #artists… https://t.co/mu3I08B2n3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cj225devs Wellll, the fans certainly were clear in their feelings about him. About what I expected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanXtina I am sentencing you to the electric chair https://t.co/fyakC9jiJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cwietz1 @bruce_arthur @Justin_Ling Worse, the industry has been destroyed by a digital medium (we're on it now) th… https://t.co/LXENmP7J1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna make four grandchildren happy? Take them to #disneyworld and stay at a #waterpark hotel. #family #lifeisgood… https://t.co/uMGSKd0Gm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Every time you open your mouth your mind spews our venomous assault on on your fellow beings. How… https://t.co/vw7l0zwWDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those who stand the tallest have the farthest to fall . . . . #detroitgrammers #detroit #landscapes #architecture… https://t.co/BgYSsJA0dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Lindsey Graham Went From Trump Skeptic to Trump Sidekick https://t.co/Wfex2cauS9 // Transactional and a callous… https://t.co/Vr5yYlCAj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charles Schulz’s version of Leonardo da Vinci’s “The Last (Birthday) Supper (of my 20s)” 🥳🎂🎁🎉 #ItsMyBirthday… https://t.co/Uhso1NXEMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember what it was like to be a kid? . Or do you have to suck it up, be responsible, and take care of your… https://t.co/FC4UGd55rB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealboeheim I imagine you won’t be coming out for the coach’s show this evening.  Life can happen so fast, some… https://t.co/mcOVQTl055]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellisrogers_  with the catch .. nothing like playing in a national tournament .. #Pylon #GrindSquad #GarlandFB #20… https://t.co/srxfCkCyax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caleb_Brentley @NBCManifest I watch it every week. I get that. Worst turbulence I’ve ever had too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[L.A. fugitive on FBI's Ten Most Wanted list is killed in North Carolina: A man who was placed on the FBI’s Ten Most… https://t.co/0KKJob0mvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngeloCataldi 249 hitter last yr.  I have booed much better players who wanted to be here!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes... thank you Twitter.. this is exactly the time I wanted to receive this notification of news I saw a million t… https://t.co/f9RglZRRR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So this paper is ok when they agree with you?!  So weird!]]></document><document><![CDATA[netflix is trash. how you gonna take off one tree hill THEN GREASE?! honestly it’s just funny at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AWilliams951 My tax pro... I was missing some paperwork from the previous years so I didn’t file. But I did the la… https://t.co/4AVXJRN0Z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: POLITICO Playbook PM: Shine leaving the White House, heading to re-elect: And the House passes a m… https://t.co/Nt7b8RUkAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bkobz Finals are in Escondido March 15-17.  His team is #3 of four, so they’ll play the #2 team in their first game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MallyCat_28 Bro I had to do a double take... I thought that was our dawg Curtis!😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rennyson8 @EddieTrunk @siriusxmvolume @HardRockHolly I hope The Monkees are receiving the critical recognition and… https://t.co/ai5ROsjJPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SagesAthletics @SAGEHSPrincipal @sagestats @MonticelloCUSD @GoSagesPepClub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskAnNFLAgent @JBennett13 @AlfieBCC And I’m guessing the Steelers were able to get permission from the league? If… https://t.co/f9rE0NMUow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Changing the means always alters the ends. As we transition from one technology to another, we never arrive at exac… https://t.co/sUHuuvHE5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calma, respira fundo e vamos ligar os fatos para entender o que aconteceu ontem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeptofDefense About 1 in 5 teachers have to get a second job to live now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People forget on this day two years ago it was warm enough to barbecue, darty and light 1333 on fire]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the day I met you, I knew that I would love you until the day I die.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Janiaapaula4 @RepSusanWild @RepRoKhanna @SecPompeo Yes, this problem is only with corrupt judiciary sentencing. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great take on @realDonaldTrump from across the pond. https://t.co/FAD8wZZpvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me on 90.1 FM, Philadelphia's Classical and Jazz source! There are many frequencies of which to connect. Liste… https://t.co/wJgfbKNd5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bassmaster #basslive hey guys I think every Major lake in the state of Missouri has Kentucky/spotted bass. Stockto… https://t.co/4YLB0YpxMD]]></document></documents></author>