<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Having a blast at #MonsterJam for Juniors 9th Birthday! https://t.co/UG3NmTMdHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerminalLance The Corps was simultaneously one of the worst and best experiences I have ever had in my life. I’m n… https://t.co/1gpXl0cJY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaKierra10 @lexipeterson_ @taybaybay07 @c_reukauf @drewdixon_ @TrevorTerp https://t.co/rt8wBcx0Ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is endemic in clinical trials publication and troubling how journals responded. @bengoldacre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewScheer What's the plan Andrew ? You keep saying you got a plan but no explanation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKinzinger Mr. life saver, your district isn't far from Aurora. The 2nd aurora to be the site of a mass shooting… https://t.co/xZRhWR9dJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One 💛! ☯️🌎👁️☮️😎💣!    https://t.co/92qDM8wrwo https://t.co/Tmc6gQf9KL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiLLy_NS @defothebunt @Marcoelizondo16 @HighIightReeIs No ? Everyone and their brother knows  he was out on that… https://t.co/cnBBPK60uf]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇦🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss kirsty_lee__ The White RACE Australian BLONDES👑🇦🇺 Women Are The MOST Beau… https://t.co/1uecBUKlC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McDonaldsCanada It was the Strandherd location in Ottawa.  It was Friday night just before midnight.  Hopefully it's up and running now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t look all that bad, but I’m hard pressed to care about any of these characters especially Jean since we j… https://t.co/dd8Wt8BDsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders How about going after the drug/pharmacy companies to charge reasonable and true rates]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Orioles lost 11-5 on account of that pesky 10-run 8th and a rain storm. But Chris Davis hit a home run. They are 2-2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guzdial #SIGCSE2019 computing is a causal specification of process that can be automated #yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmersenLee @sw1a0aa Bad weather bad food and bad teeth???? Oh and soccer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSimpsons    I got 11 out of 12! How do you measure up?  Can You Recognize These Simpsons Characters By Their Si… https://t.co/CnXOf6SBjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful moment on my plane ride today: I sat beside a couple who gushed about their teachers after we introduced… https://t.co/8Edg1Wxtot]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASUNTO DE TIEMPO, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/vSqsdDwnoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing a rewatch of Schitt’s Creek and I must declare: I will be whelmed with emotion every time the family dances t… https://t.co/5GOH4eDmj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chenteydrach Mi día de vacaciones crucero lista #1 https://t.co/iVkldW6Fsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm Not The Type Of Artist Who Act's Like A Pompous About The Success, I'm Not The Type To Sneak Diss Or Discourage… https://t.co/sKQCRJ1d5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[It be slick tonight, be safe. Our driveway was salted a bit, then my boy woke up..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaShanneStokes @realDonaldTrump WHY DOESN'T PRESIDENT TRUMP DOUBLE DOWN ON HIS BIRTHER BS??  Obama's Kenyan Brothe… https://t.co/fiIT95GYzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH BABY THIS TASTES FIRE I DONT EVEN COOK IM BOUTA MAKE MY GIRLFRIEND AND HER FAMILY BREAKFAST EVERY MORNING]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing these faces and one other....#chchchchchanges  #foundation @ Kennesaw, Georgia https://t.co/pTJnIgt3Q8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OvercastFM  I’m having a consistent error where the Apple Watch fast forward/backwards buttons disappear and the w… https://t.co/WjSVeNKJ3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelaril2 @StaceyPrussman Awesome! send me a link of your work/portfolio; you never know when the right job might… https://t.co/FgJw5gPdwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls ,your bf or fiancee is courting you, and beats you for the first time says sorry, does it again and apologise… https://t.co/8IAGINEVW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hay un vato que va a la cantina vaquero y se ve machín, se quiere cotorrear pero yo presiento y estoy casi seguro que me gusta la v..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesPPierce We do. He who "knows more than The General" (Shaq's friend, the lil insurance guy) is sitting in the Oval.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaannostaShines @kablamoko @GingerHotDish @Holy_Elle @photogal519 @cheryl_marlin @KLBChicken @softly_sighing2… https://t.co/921zIT3y3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khyatt2876 @NWS @weather_talk Kris.. Jeff will put that on his gift list for his wife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scotttmiller Sounds like SHE took the purple pill (a fantastic ZzzQuil™️!!! Thanks ZzzQuil™️!)  #ad #sponsored]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better than talking the talk is walking the walk... https://t.co/ytvEAF9rgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Columbus: clear sky, 7°F 71% humidity, wind 10mph, pressure 1020mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another weekend and the @DFS_Squid Squad has a full golf roster. Let’s make some money https://t.co/WGxup9NXIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those Central Texas spring sunsets 👌🏽 @ China Springs, Texas https://t.co/GAIIe0Xs2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, bought a couple of books on the history of Clan Campbell. They both try to tie this clan back to King Arthur. S… https://t.co/AytiMd1zap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppleSupport It’s 3 AM and iCloud just deleted all my photos off of my iPhone. 🙄🗣 I’m sickaaa y’all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! So beautiful! I drove up the valley today from Fresno to Manteca, and the visibility was great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn't think of a better song for our next SmackDown women's Champion and tough enough graduate @WWE_MandyRose… https://t.co/9KS1gCPgMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #BuildTheWall #MAGA #JobsNotMobs https://t.co/Omnm3cfIiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say Their Names Joaquin Oliver, 17 Alaina Petty, 14 Meadow Pollack, 18 Helena Ramsay, 17 Alexander Schachter, 14  T… https://t.co/aJ5j3GDcSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#drainspotting Worcester Massachusetts USA   Excited to spend the day with my new teammates at Vortex Turnkey our b… https://t.co/c0HnpaGUR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mixedstardusts @Minimekee For real! Some of the stuff y’all be saying got me over here dyin!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a novel concept. Instead of singling women out one day a year, why don’t we focus on gender equality daily?… https://t.co/71DDHRbVGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKrittibas @SenSanders The homicide arrest rate for native-born Americans was about 5.4 per 100,000 natives, abou… https://t.co/1clI51cPcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PRSJournal— Read the March 2019 PRS #PlasticSurgery article, “Therapeutic Role of #FatInjection in the Treatment o… https://t.co/7DYfZYV6Ji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry if it's too much.... I'm sick and tired of catering sexy photos to men that would rape me]]></document><document><![CDATA[#resisters, do you now understand #MuellerTime is not coming, and it never was. Trump Trump Jr Kushner Flynn Gates… https://t.co/nrW7od3Quh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uncle_Ray2 I don’t care what @B_Ken63 says about you man. You’re an innovator. Best idea I’ve seen yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got home drunk at 11:15 last night, and got up at 3:30 this morning for a flight to Boston. That calls for a mimosa… https://t.co/fiaeOxg22F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewBerryTMR Between you and @cwotd @PatrickMahomes is having some awkward moments with men older then him]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say God Damn!!!!  Good call Jared - Drinking a My Black Parade  (2016) by @lostabbey @ Perry Street Cellar  — https://t.co/70v9Y75GD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[SIX STAR FROG SPLASH!!!! WILLIE MACK AND TOMMY DREAMER GETS THE WIN OVER OvE #IMPACT]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/xNFn4v4CQV Orthodox Judaic Rabbis, who are against, Rothschild Zionist Mossad Israeli "murderous" Gove… https://t.co/7LQvjPH3hQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are great things happening with DRMA and in our manufacturing community. Your investment in this membership i… https://t.co/q1pGOYs3LN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer Yeah the millions of illegals that voted forvHilary in liberal States]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just love how someone in the beginning yells DISCO CUUUBE and everyone goes WOOOO #arcticmonkeys #tbhc #tbt https://t.co/96e7rRwYl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s stoked for a few days home? This guy 🙋🏻‍♂️  📷: @nemphotography @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/vJRZVgDMAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just asking!!  @krassenstein @ananavarro @BillKristol @NancySinatra @ChrisCuomo @peterbakernyt @tribelaw @MiaFarrow… https://t.co/T5A4RBs3XP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukestamps Yah I get it the SBC has some rednecks not buying the Renwal project. But...Carl Henry was a borgie New… https://t.co/svTF1e5qpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillipColby @seanhannity @jsolomonReports @SaraCarterDC I have never seen Sean's   program. I'm too poor to affor… https://t.co/9jwz2VqHm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This might be a stretch but this may be the best wintertime picture I’ve ever take cause wow...  Shout out to my mo… https://t.co/l1icZzjbGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pictures from my visit to Apple Park. @ Apple Park Cupertino https://t.co/gG2yPaVTDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just imagine how the world would react if we found out Drake wasn’t American...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knock, Knock. Who's there? Winter. Winter who? I'm back! @ North Haven, Connecticut https://t.co/HbRIeEXqve]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how many other customers pay for air shipping but their package is really shipped via ground? @ups and… https://t.co/fQ0XjPbPAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our 2109 @KHS_BoysSoccer journey begins tomorrow. Every year is unique, every year is special. This is year #20 for… https://t.co/zdJ93c1ww9]]></document><document><![CDATA[You fucknut, we already have something like that; it’s called “A Capitol Fourth” on PBS!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StantonGreame @uncuttool8 @aussietrbl @jockboy1113 @purelygayporn @Hockeyguy13 @Unsucchiacazzi @GayFinDom… https://t.co/FKpQnbZHzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @EdRollins @realDonaldTrump Amash Fitzpatrick  Gallagher Herrera Beutler Hurd Johnson Massie McMorris Rog… https://t.co/CqUkWkG6t8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beinlibertarian @AOC yet we want gov in charge of more in our life? dems are weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CGRTeams @704NASCARHeat @KyleLarsonRacin @KurtBusch @MonsterEnergy @gearwrench #eNASCARHeat @CGRTeams]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheamus2famous @Autism_updates @MiracleLeagueFL @FriendshipCir @shakealegmiami @DanMarinoFdtn @DLCAVA @apenelas… https://t.co/JX4ZBOi04U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feb. 15th 2019 Day 2970: 30 min LISS Cardio with Shoulder Work with My Brother and Mentor Sagi 👊🏼💚💪🏼 • • • • •… https://t.co/wJWmFqzNUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t solve the cultural problems by itself, but downvotes/moderation can serve as a disincentive. It’d be int… https://t.co/k2UjSNbw1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @DIM_Oficial a pesar de su mala campaña cumplió un año sin perder de local por @LigaAguila… https://t.co/L1AQ9xpW8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a risk; open the door to opportunity and adventure. #leadership #quote #HR https://t.co/iqVBQcQ3Ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hulu @hulu_support when you gonna put the rest of the Dubbed episodes for Naruto Shippuden???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamAllen_1 @realDonaldTrump Yesterday was about getting trumps taxes and more names fore future hearings. All e… https://t.co/SXnMDbnOIi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrfomby @Marvyross @ogDupree As you see they can’t stop young guards because their best on ball passing lane defen… https://t.co/bSGf7wJa1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CountOnVic I'm gonna trade in my salary so I can say horrible things to humans and get away with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[doug shows has been ITCHIN to get back to a bama game and i do not like it at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who would’ve thought in 2019, Lady Gaga and The Jonas Brothers would still be topping the charts? I feel like I’m 9… https://t.co/AalSsfs6PB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonMHamm Almost like one individual involved has been the same person he is now that he has his current job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks everybody for the Happy Birthdsy FB posts, tweets, IG posts &amp; texts yesterday! 2️⃣7️⃣🎂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dealing craps at Mercedes Bwnz Stadium, Atlanta. Two weeks after Superbowl LIII.  Delta Sky Club. #actorslife… https://t.co/KxFbvrEOw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtbrowning67 @RepAndyVargas @RepPressley @Vote16MA @Vote16USA Teenagers have a much greater stake in our future th… https://t.co/QsLUGBx4Bp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawnfleek @andersem @balcom_holly @rachelamonahan I think the error here is misunderstanding the scale of geograp… https://t.co/QEjVXe7xic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chargeorge @OwenTheBell @Hengde It’s also a lot of smaller companies have only 1 or 2 developer on the project so… https://t.co/po4JxjICyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's Hermione. Because she was awesome.  #HarryandRonwerewanks https://t.co/vwkufAB3Lf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doranimated @DineshDSouza @BernieSanders That’s it, his new name is Bozo Bernie!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@build_bham @BhamFoodie Is this good.  Haven't had a chance yet, but love a good cheesesteak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guzman_rober4 @CDeportivoFAS Mi pregunta es a que hora te vas a meter ahora??]]></document><document><![CDATA[These kids do the workouts they see in certain magazines and have no idea about this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What can we learn from David’s response to King Saul? David made every attempt to maintain his integrity #Ps140]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yankees @MAndujarPapa Happy Birthday Miggy!🌈✝️❤️ https://t.co/mosQmj1hj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cameron_Gray @RealJamesWoods Were they in democratic states.  Washington.  California.  New York?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra In her defense, she thinks laundering money is forgetting to take her tip money, from the bar, out of… https://t.co/710sxkx4g4]]></document></documents></author>