<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[post, express yourself. But don’t cross the line. Use your own judgment. Social media should be no issue during hiring process. Tatiana]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 No, he would probably throw the family dog outside while watching old footage of his heroes: Hitler, Stalin, etc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamolestina Es correcto, en el area de #NYC hay un montón de cuencanos. Si lo sabré yo que tengo 21 años casada co… https://t.co/l0kPgR8k4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump At least he could pronounce words. Our president can’t. He also can’t spell. Now what school did you go to?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see all the Oscar tweets.  Who ended up hosting? I really don’t know. Let me google it lol 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gary_ARSC @JoeBiden @ElectBiden @BidenforPOTUS I like how you think. I was hoping for a Biden/Harris to run together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please share #KylieKulyk  @TheEllenShow  Kylie Kulyk spending her childhood coping with pain most can't imagine. It… https://t.co/lQQIZBJk41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner American have invested over 250 years into work by way of sweat equity in labor, tax investments into th… https://t.co/WI5if98LZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[FACTS Pop of Canada is 37,169,882 as of 3/1/2019. Avg WAIT TIMES IN WKS Plastic  26, OB/GYN 19, Ophthalmology 28.5,… https://t.co/VHZwHxm4Kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS Keep up the great work Melania. Keep up the good fight. Continue to help innocent children. God bless you a… https://t.co/zWVh7JwqC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amstefano988 Isn’t that even more perfect!?! Like if you asked me over a glass of wine after a day baking in the s… https://t.co/uvjaVJeeqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PremierLacrosse  Is there a date you can put into the atmosphere for Ticket Sale for Gillette?… https://t.co/ri0Y22b4kd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biggest mission ever to watch #FindingNeverland. 1. Borrow an🇺🇸 credit card for free HBO trail (🇿🇦 doesn’t work) 2.… https://t.co/r2LClewJEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Engagement on @Instagram has been total shit lately. Worse than it’s ever been. What gives, @instagram?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenryLouisGates obsessed with #FindingYourRoots how is this season 5 and I just started watching? better yet, how… https://t.co/45hgFJbxE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[But has anyone ever curled up in a ball and laid in the shower and just had the water hit you? Magical.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @jessicacline23 (get_repost) ・・・ My BFFL made this for me thanks @harleyannquinnn @ Warren, Ohio https://t.co/LXSb3EjycT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I much prefer doing the interviewing than being interviewed! This is a really interesting study about math instruct… https://t.co/jA8nUXDa2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😬 Dieser Moment, wenn dein amerikanischer Mitbewohner in LA in dein Zimmer gelaufen kommt und sagt, dass Deutschla… https://t.co/EEhQFGZkcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlminer That was their loss. Times have really changed in the past 40 years and here in the States, people with di… https://t.co/iSOwKPUtQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chesterfield native and 2x #Daytona500 Champ @dennyhamlin is joining us on @8NEWS #8sports 😁.  #DoItForJD #FedEx11… https://t.co/hJKBXHIH9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyboughner It’s Petite Peru’s specialty, delicious - and they make several varieties.  Casa Mexico also has it on… https://t.co/VCfE2JgXDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dear friend’s son is in ICU and may not make it. He’s met the same fate as my late husband and at the very same… https://t.co/6zyfeFF7Ez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind every successful woman there is another one! Celebrate all the women in your life today and everyday!… https://t.co/ILJ4ibCEfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My American Sign Language prof asked what i liked and i said i like liquor 🤪😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryssaAlbert Probably shouldn’t have kids if you can’t accept the 50/50 chance of a girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElvChap0 @melissaeaster9 If u can’t see the war that’s going on WITHIN OUR COUNTRY currently then you really are brainwashed as a MF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrNashington What the hell is zucced, normie and reee even mean Ok I get Zucced]]></document><document><![CDATA[The matter of Kavanaugh was basically swept under the carpet having non bias judge sitting on out Supreme Court is… https://t.co/MY61DQr7kS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You have set a precedent for a divide bigger than Dems Verses Republicans; demonizing media is wha… https://t.co/9co1ZEuOX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shalinhnaik Geez how many times did you end up going in for an MRI?!  #askthedoctor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just pulled $38 out of my jacket pocket that I haven’t worn in in forever and man it’s the little things like this lmaoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers have covered a lot of songs, with permission by the way. Sucker is an original. If they would’ve… https://t.co/WsOduQhgBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooo... im feeling like @vanillaice I’m done done done duh duh done done]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom still inspires me even thought she’s been gone for more of my life than she was here. #sheinspiresme… https://t.co/zf0IlD10NG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobCaton That would be awesome, but doesn’t “He” have a no trade clause?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WanderlushVibes @CNN Our job is to see that it no longer exists in America. That's why it is important to stop hum… https://t.co/mkdArVGOdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg. #CharlesBarkley is hilarious. I'm deaded. 😂🤣 https://t.co/auZBswKGV8 @TSN_Sports #JussieSmollett]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colgraphics @JohnCornyn @politico Taking babies and young children from their mothers is wrong. That’s my point. W… https://t.co/QCysgl6DZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏡 JUST LISTED 🏡  🔑 5069 Burgundy Lane, Yorba Linda, CA 92886 🔑 More info: 🙋‍♀️ Allison Van Wig 🎗 CA BRE# 00985700… https://t.co/gbAXxg0cfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markmm3608 What can I say? I’m a child of the 70’s and a young adult of the the 80’s! But, I’ve read the court doc… https://t.co/TtlFJpNEW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ostranderlinds I’m about to leave this class as soon as the attendance sheet gets to me 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[People really aren’t about it until they realize what they lost. Then it’s too late😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mother_of_Macaw Hey, I think my son and I are in your photo! 😂 Since there were so few art lovers outside yesterda… https://t.co/Y42yQnOs1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[My birthday is on international day of happiness...coincidence I think not]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capecodlibrary @joliboucher @roroshells @masscue awww thank you Kim! My heart is singing I'm having so much fun with this class AND y'all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holdenkarau Jean being a more a feminine first name in the US, I regularly get mail with Mrs. or people sounding v… https://t.co/wfnp642vk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JENNRAES23 hey have tickets already gone on sale for fan club for chateau st Michelle in woodenville?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@serbarica Damn what will we do when I finally get the chance leave there?😂 just kidding]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ganesha on a tiny forearm. Ganesha is usually male, but the client decided her Ganesha is female and named her Rosi… https://t.co/zC6PtXjfD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just think about it..in a couple of years maybe less, we will celebrate "The Great Awakening" as another national h… https://t.co/xKG7KfC8VY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buckiebathplug @YouTube @HackettOfficial WITHIN 5 SECONDS..and I'm  IN LOVE WITH THIS TRACK.. Thank you @HackettOfficial]]></document><document><![CDATA[Albanians are funny...my grandma had no problem with my ripped jeans before and then we go to another Albanians’ ho… https://t.co/z3ECYkDa1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok... for days they said it was going to snow and I pretty sure it still will... but where is the snow... cause all I see is rain. ☔️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beingfreeman @AWAKEOKC1 I really enjoyed it! I imagine with more and more people being interested they may expand their class offerings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tammy73619415 @kathygriffin @JussieSmollett The second chance hardly ever works with kids and people who hate othe… https://t.co/j8nzeiMSCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump 2020.  🇱🇷 true Americans are supporting our President for re-election.  Pelosi should do the country a favor… https://t.co/L1n0knFTUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manhattan friends who would be willing for me n 2-3 friends to stay at their place for fake patty’s! We will help with food n alc!🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JadenDavenport4 It was my first eco friendly straw(had it last night) at Beef a Roo🤔👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherBarmore Coconut stuff helped me through this tragedy (I can’t eat dairy, alcohol, gluten, most sugars) you got this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColumbiaSIPA Alumnus @mayorofsmile Creating Smiles Worldwide with @UnspokenSmiles  . . . @ColumbiaAlumniA… https://t.co/HDu4LeHk6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AxaltaRacing dinner tonight, what an amazing way to kick off the @NASCAR season!  #axaltaracing #Axalta24 #Axalta… https://t.co/n7obmTMXJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClickitH Get out of bed, shuffle to the kitchen, step on fresh hairball. Barefoot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is not cute at all and I don't accept his ass I don't want his damn apology. Kick rocks]]></document><document><![CDATA[What people with blue eyes actually look like when they look into the sun lol https://t.co/48psKxeIx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TeamGOT7 #TwitterBestFandom #SoompiAwards @GOT7Official  #갓세븐 https://t.co/mJO60waDs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reminds me of dumb videos me and @KaitlynKellem would make at her old house I’m SCREAMING]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1 since Day 1!! Don't let the beat faces fool y'all! #weslay @ Mulberry, Florida https://t.co/DhIlB1yjIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irenerio_ I used to like shrimp but I threw up and gained an aversion to it ok stop being so judgy miss roach eater!!! Bye!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg! She pulled the “I love you! But I’m not in love with you” card! #TheBatchelor What a shocker! #Colton dude find a woman away from tv!]]></document><document><![CDATA[💯💯.@CFPB embodying the BEST of all possible #UX communications practices! This email (1) acknowledges my issue (2)… https://t.co/Ikf3s9veO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 Ordered the @ABHcosmetics PR bundle! I don’t think I’ve ever ordered something so fast in my life lol. https://t.co/HZVNRoKEmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG don't watch TVW right now, you will cry. Hearings on #wrongfuldeath very sad!! My heart goes out to these peopl… https://t.co/CLUmieV59E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Dress + Red Lip ~ very out of character for me but it is almost Valentine’s Day so I’m feeling it 💋 Wearing d… https://t.co/cDYlZUzygI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@instagram magically unfollowed about 300 people I follow 🤔🤔 what is happening]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mexicandynasties on @BravoTV is a MUSTTTTTTT WATCHHHH @Daniellestuff @caseyrosewilson @LeRayBlanding]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this place!Love this city! #citybarrel @ City Barrel https://t.co/dY7XBXfgJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYGovCuomo Kinda sucks for you that Amazon backed out of having a headquarters in NY, eh? Karma, baby😗]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest Charlotte, NC job and click to apply: Quality Inspector III - https://t.co/sIH2hbUWkn #KellyJobs #KellyServices]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha!  Well, not a superhero but still a star!  Kedi is a beautiful cat.  Thanks for the entertaining tweets!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha. I live in California. It’s been the heart of democratic lying. How do you think they got all those taxes pass… https://t.co/z4rX9PvHKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReelQuinn @cmclymer And after seeing trump with his own child, they need to spend time with kids. And the elderly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SWA has $29 inter-island fares..... Hawaiian Airlines is going to get run out of business. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MakerBlock I don't think I'm entertaining when I'm drunk. I actually don't ever believe I'm entertaining.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber @craigmelvin You just made the "Melrahi" bond even closer...#Melrahi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristinaSaidSo @PR3SIDENT I should have booked mine in the morning! Deffo not booking an afternoon one EVER AGAIN!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm seeing Howie Mandel at River City Casino &amp; Hotel, St Louis, MO on Thursday, May 2nd. Who's Joining? https://t.co/Er68WSObDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of them posted about never having a valentine but still being optimistic and super happy for others. I’m like g… https://t.co/vIFjhlyCml]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tired of all the hate towards MJ victims and outrage about “they’re looking for money”... if they are good, they sh… https://t.co/8Rz5jeR2dv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I'll try. Im.about 200 less followers than ppl I patrioticslly followed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Yes, he’s going to mess up here and there but if he’s trying to be a better man for you, love that man, keep that… https://t.co/Po696ZUKZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[TV news showing @PeteButtigieg some love for V-Day: He'll be on Morning Joe, New Day, and Colbert tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oscars2019Live_ Such #chemistry....these two #GagaBradley #Shallow #StarisBorn #AwesomeDuet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrookeDivirgil3 i know babe. thank you ❤️ sometimes i just let my thoughts get the best of me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julianahatfield The ones who have done wrong should be scared. #IBelieveYou #SupportSurvivors #metoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @jguaido Thank you Senator Rubio for keeping us up to date.  Prayers for Venezuela!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now why would anyone sign up for  @BachelorABC if they aren’t ready for marriage?? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWordPeople https://t.co/nGLBj388sI Seeking new Technical Writing/Technical Editing opportunity! Will relocate f… https://t.co/jfH18n31xJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#girlstrip #JustinTimberlake #broughtsexyback #needtoseehimagain https://t.co/rbd0Q51chd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods He’s an imbecile. Dems in Congress cuz they can’t get real jobs!]]></document></documents></author>