<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[You sound like a person who doesn’t live in a border state. It’s very selfish and inconsiderate to those of us who… https://t.co/DwlWAiQ10P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MW_GoJoeBruin @garlic_chicken_ @4thGenBruin Only factors keeping me as a UCLA fan are my diploma &amp; friend who owns a liquor store 🥃🥃🥃🥃🥃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackHammerxxxx @wetboy27 Should never be alone 🌸🆗 https://t.co/UkzEKZHm0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NagusCook @theme_park Did two people just disagree on #distwitter, and yet remain able to see each other’s tweets… https://t.co/8VNuZJsX7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCuppRadio @AJ_Athletics @WpubRadio There isn’t a price tag you can put on connections to a community thru local radio. Good stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IsBetterThanUsingPlastics Micro Filaments. These will be refined when nano tech is revealed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At #AAASmtg? Want to talk about your research? Find me! I'm like, ridiculously tall (and curious)! https://t.co/XiZDosuXwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I guess in all fairness one of the coast guard guys did have his gf leave him for another women the day before we went clubbing. #Burn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watchin porn at this family gathering cause this shit boring https://t.co/xPo28gNH7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBC @CNBCMakeIt Having strong morning rituals can total transform you day.  String enough @MiracleMorning techniq… https://t.co/DZ9bh8Jrco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PepperellEddie @TigerWoods Well at least you’re not playing for second anymore!! Find the positive]]></document><document><![CDATA[On official Piaget business today in CT. Just me and my @subaru_usa . I have hit a new level of… https://t.co/jxWRblbZif]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good evening from Stanton, Tennessee and News Channel 3 viewer Jiffy Spencer. https://t.co/9EF53Jq3fD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can the grownups all agree to stop using the term "haters?" Anyone over twenty-five who uses the word deserves to h… https://t.co/m0cbRfqQS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The facts don’t add up.  You are not honest. It is just a campaign pledge that you screwed up and… https://t.co/jRcE9vbUfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks like people go to church these days just to take snaps and socialize. “We too we go the church some.” If y… https://t.co/ANDFkPyDzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bob_ranum I'd delete that picture pretty quick before the scammers lift the number, my friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feckless #Pelosi cannot even corrall her #Democrat herd of cats  to pass a resolution condemning #Antisemetic speec… https://t.co/oXBEsmeu2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio @AfterHoursCBS Hurting. He would be a big risk to put on your team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Blaine made the castle vanish @ Disneyland - Theme Park https://t.co/kwsJInpcRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my #godson got me this sweet #piano #tie and YES it does actually play #music 😎🎹👔 @ Safety Harbor, Florida https://t.co/ZH6KdiSZqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelysaxon I mean I am coming to London so could be fun but also sounds like I might end up dead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theScore @justinboone Nothing better than looking over the Fantasy Content on a road trip https://t.co/I3m5dwh8XT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hulu_support Well your policy needs revisiting. Last time I lost my DVR content I switched providers. A “hey we co… https://t.co/JCM3JHdWWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter your race, religious views or political views you can’t sit here and say that this isn’t right. Imagine h… https://t.co/8DGJ4H1peI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing the mayor and Ms. Ezzie (@ Broadway Place in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/WL5Etwyapc]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is such an opening for DJ Qualls to do a John Leguizamo style show where he plays every single young reaction… https://t.co/rr56ZMp2mQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gamer_lady I7 8700k 1080 ddr4 32gb ssds and m.2 so not lacking as far as I can tell. It does have some weird glitc… https://t.co/XxSfgLtRQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[whenever I see anybody with a tattoo, I think wow I’d rather own 1/500th of a home than that eyesore😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @msmorgan1968 @EMluvsPibbles @Jr3597 @ChaliceGarden… https://t.co/h7F4kCpuuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickFondacaro @newsbusters @CNN @brianstelter a 250 million dollar suit for lazy journalism will do that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iloveanime9999 This is just a wild claim of mine due to the amount of presence the franchise had at the poll. Adul… https://t.co/lLSMKKH0Kj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NerdPyle @SteveSyfuhs @blowdart @aiddya @TashasEv Yeah and you need to know your place.  Serf.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cypress @olubaseball tomorrow night at 7:00 @CypCentBaseball  For those of you wanting to get out to the ball park… https://t.co/K63P4yujo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to the contamination in the water, people are forced to buy bottled water. Contaminated water is detrimental to… https://t.co/VNeRQakMDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevecourtney79 @AFizgig @bonkersasscin @flixology101 @LillithKain @HallowsHaunts @stagescreen60 @Deadlightsmag Th… https://t.co/XLSWMxiE2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fitzer_patti  @Rebecca41453975  @MuchowTara  @Betsy_CravenLPS @PatrickMies @munday_mrs @Garfield_c_s @DubayRick… https://t.co/Flb4bohg4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this mod! You can finally play as @FFCFoxes in a video game. #SomosZorros]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PauseListnCount @TrueFactsStated If he kills people while driving drunk, that's just getting what he deserves. I d… https://t.co/5ElMpJFPQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[. https://t.co/nXdmot727S Trump's racist big mouth cause the NFL owners 2 blackball Colin Kaepernick and they have… https://t.co/iPrmhDeEFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Troubled by how many people I see caping for DiFi here. Yeah, I saw the full video - in fact, that was what I saw f… https://t.co/CxPxEFXmCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterwurster13 @nwohiotars @GovBillWeld @GOP My friend, once the general election comes around it is between me an… https://t.co/rXmSQdIGeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HobackSara @tonyposnanski Lindsey Graham’s motive is to keep that photo of a Russian oligarch and Lindsay on a lea… https://t.co/g3W8XorbKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard to believe it's been 8 years since @AWardSports convinced us to go to a random boxing match in Vegas that turn… https://t.co/2RtANrY0vh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkilAugustine you need to have a better handle on #TheHangout than telling people time-out give them all a chance… https://t.co/hNluW7q5m5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Regal Cinemas Bridgeport Village 18 &amp; IMAX - @regalmovies in Tigard, OR https://t.co/neWjXCSBcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[the worst part about all this is that it's made me kind of hate big time dog people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarafahmmy @RTarabic حاجه فعلا غريبه جدا ، بس هو نفس سحنه أصدقائه العكرة حتي بتوع الجماعة اياهم نفس السماجه]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost The only rehab that’ll work for this guy is a permanent jail cell]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wcw @graceeventide @candyvalentina_ @VanityyFox @Ally_Auer ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/exXAp7Jvqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you can run up on people (Celebrities), stick a phone in their face rudely ,probably when I am out with my famil… https://t.co/z6JBD39hoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Eastern State Penitentiary https://t.co/Tw5M7k1MZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twestytwesty @bov_chris @canisvex629 @TeaPartyOne1 @MAGAJesusJTrump @Carfield76 @realDonaldTrump @MostBiglyMaga… https://t.co/gT0N1N46iK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisVernonShow Do you have a funny/memorable story about the 08 Celtics team that people probably haven’t heard before?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont know why I feel horrible late at night. I wish I knew the reason but I hate this feeling everytime it comes.… https://t.co/uM8QSppm2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grannyanon1969 @John_R_Berna @jmbenson1491 @American2b @debit_mullins @mickelodoole @fortressfin @jonz970… https://t.co/oy6ZieAOnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolfersJournal This past year at my home course, Par 3, 188 yard 8th hole. Hit 6 iron that landed just short of th… https://t.co/fRa1jsCFzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan You could not answer the question posed by @MarthaRaddatz on @ThisWeekABC as to when a President has ev… https://t.co/DZD0yOTaeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and shine, friends and education justice warriors. Another day to fight for what’s right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many players NFL or NHL stay there. It’s a great place to live. The people that are negative about it, well, hav… https://t.co/CZTDNSPdfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m feeling super nice tonight. Congrats @gordonhayward! Way to keep your head up thru a really tough season. Who am I right now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to saltymotorworks for always doing an incredible job. Go follow him and hit him up for any tint or wrap j… https://t.co/hhCUUQI0Y6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SingaporeSling at #MrCoco!  - - - #palms #cocktails #luxury #tiki #thegoldentiki #vegas #usbglv #hospitalityfirst… https://t.co/BjBUq53Idt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not dead, but under threat - and America is ready for a conversation about what role government will have to ensure… https://t.co/mcp7U2jwmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@margaretcox2299 @AlexWY18 @fellspeaks @basedinfidel8 @JayCory7 @Chriskl70208387 @SmackYeti @Americanthatguy… https://t.co/GlPGyIflNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pookah72450 @mikebrannon_ @AOC Blatant stupidity is believing it is possible to have a different outcome from soci… https://t.co/XAb3k8mYDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE @WWE I know they’ve had a Gorilla Monsoon but @BeckyLynchWWE has become the Money Monsoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FatherHarry1 @DrakeBulldogsMB @ValleyHoops Too bad (Redbird fan here) hate to see injuries, but especially not right before the tourney.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liquor Industry News/Links 02-18-19 Trends, New Products, Education And More #wine #beer #liquor… https://t.co/pAYpWYqHW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Im not hearing anything per say (Pelinka job security) I think Magic really likes Rob and Magic and Rob are togeth… https://t.co/RSgxgEaN4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jbrackets1 Iowa looks like garbage too, but they won enough early that they'll get a bid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just spitballing here, but don't the Russians already target US command centers?  Like maybe before now they were a… https://t.co/q2cZVotRiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super puppy! #dogsofinstagram #cosplay #cosplayer @ Huntington Convention Center of Cleveland https://t.co/xBPPs7HMfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trish_regan @VPPressSec @VP @IvanDuque @jguaido go to Venezuela not Colombia, Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oziah Deloatch with the first FG for @TZeeAthletics then Adian Cunney adds a FG and its 38-36 @sports_pioneer 5:11… https://t.co/sZoXYurPUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown's move to the Raiders is more Jerry Rice than Randy Moss https://t.co/Irg7pEP8sw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some dude at this bar walked in and plugged in a crock pot. I have many questions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckRocha Good Morning! Nice seeing you on @foxandfriends w/ @kilmeade Great job on @FoxNews Prayers you and your… https://t.co/byRNIYRDBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonLionFineArt @aliciakeys Amazing Art -- both in process and product.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to my own Spanish feelings playlist got me sad asf 😔especially cuz of Camila and Chayanne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson His base won’t be able to afford the trip the way his Tax scam has most working class folks having to… https://t.co/Qr8hUQzY48]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do we New Yorkers explain to our childeren why infanticide is legal and no more important than abortion,marijua… https://t.co/pmzlpIqzqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doug Shows watch pending for Fayette County until 3:45 ET today. Warning could be pending as the front develops...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Straboye Even IF they didn't do it in the Press Tours, they STILL TWEET political shit on Social Media so that's a… https://t.co/7wp26pPiJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read my first piece for @SportsFungo (where I will be writing about #MLB and the #NHL) about how the big spending… https://t.co/upqPAii9A9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Latinas 🇲🇽 INTERRACIALS PORN At https://t.co/SivopTtTos || 🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian BLONDES👑🇷🇺Women Are The… https://t.co/Bza2CGz62T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mzimmaro @mfsfox Thanks Mark.  It was great to see you today.  Glad u were a part of this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stand Christmas music throughout the year but I can never skip Fall Out Boys, “Yule shoot your eye out.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffmorgen One of my favorite moments in Kermit Lynch’s book “Adventures on the Wine Trail” is the anecdote about… https://t.co/nnF7omgZ2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SushioGoto @LKGGlass @makuake_ca I liked this tweet even though I don’t understand japanese]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enimsaJasmine21 I'm gonna be 24 next month and still haven't either lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our team is growing! We welcome Angel Young to The Moving Experience! Angel has a wonderful wealth of knowledge wit… https://t.co/NZdYvJcyWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/EkL8G1X3aQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[y Boca aburre y juega mal @anellogaby @TyCSports @EstudioFutbol @radiolared]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of our listing on 225 33rd Street Avalon, NJ 08202 #Avalon #NJ  #realestate https://t.co/Y7tUFIzNS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[btw i just RT’ed one bc someone decided to RT on my TL and I ain’t taking no chances https://t.co/cLBNQ0JkKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DartDClark @NBCNews This perfectly encapsulates a mood: https://t.co/bMgChkohD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsnetBen @Aportzline  Has Jarmo or Davidson ever been Behind a Bench (ala Lou), when they Fire Tort's after Last Nights StuPiditY?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissNyetTrump @openpodbaydoor_ We need to stop calling them evangelists.. they have become the opposite of the def… https://t.co/7f6hXQXjA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wirecrats Sorry to hear this sad news James. Condolences to you and your family.]]></document></documents></author>