<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[A credible news source posted a graphic, nearly minute-long video of a woman writhing in pain, bleeding, following… https://t.co/cW8Op3cCqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picked up some dessert for tonight. 🤤 @clownshoesbeer  #yummy #CraftBeer  #beeroclock #beerlover 😋🍻 https://t.co/VLpjX9C9jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living next to a lighthouse doesn’t suck #KeyBiscayne #SouthFlorida #Miami #OldestStandingStructureInMiami #History… https://t.co/q7BROs7uQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danny_delaware @the_tacofreak Your diet is horrifying and I hope you know that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rlipstein @EdSkipper @CNNPolitics @mattgaetz This is who Floridians vote for, what a disappointment!  Matt Gaetz i… https://t.co/VPX9aEXAeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MenMedikamanAn #throwback  Great Track  @VICE2K  @ReynaldoVice  #Vice2k all day/all night https://t.co/GNKFQK6Lsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working in media is great until you are over analyzing focus, white balance, and if they used a tripod or not in ev… https://t.co/W3xw9euAkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve #justdonated to Jacki's CureSearch Hike campaign. Donate on @justgiving and support this great cause https://t.co/yUl7uTeqdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I quit cold Turkey in 1976. The Secret to success was to stay out of the bars because everybody smoked then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give good and get good in return.. #dontbeameanperson #bekind https://t.co/FcCKStAFNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent job Emily Gibson, James Masters and Kameelah Belgrave!! #ATsSaveLives. @OCPSnews has always been a leader… https://t.co/WHpjF3OHgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[it makes me so deeply upset that motion sickness is about ry*n *d*ms like phoebe girl I love u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every single one of them should lawyer up cuz this is a witch Hunt at the expense of the public the Democratic libe… https://t.co/GOZowr0ztG]]></document><document><![CDATA[REGIONAL GAMEDAY Tiger Nation!! Last one out of Alexandria turn out the lights!! Good luck to @AlexBoysBBall as the… https://t.co/Jo4kOwgzVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[For some reason I’m pretty sure @realBradStaggs and @RantsOfIzzoare used to getting looks of shame from women and c… https://t.co/amkH3tFtdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will answer any poll on instagram or Twitter no matter what it’s about]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would we be spending our time on this earth wiser if we knew our expiration dates? #life #lifeonearth… https://t.co/wbBsrSZPzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys idk why this made me laugh so hard last night. Giraffes Fighting https://t.co/zyTPyLEYt4 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zapmom @mechelew @thearinbear @mirandalambert Does that mean they use Miranda's income when calculating child supp… https://t.co/80AhK5ay1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for more brushes, scrapes and neon paints! Final weekend of rides through Hell begins tonight!… https://t.co/7MRfBIzYTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darthcrowley @nomaspri2 @Cuervomk @elenavilla18 @lopezobrador_ Aún así, no justifico, lo que hizo el macuspano.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 Keep your hands on 10 &amp; 2 o’clock position on the wheel at all times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ta mas chido que le avienten el queso a los perros que a los bebés; los bebés no valen vword.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will my professors post grades before midterms?  Stay tuned to another episode of absolutely the frick not https://t.co/mJUcXr7OSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m looking forward to seeing this man go down. Roger Stone the biggest crook of all. And the man that gave us Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good reminder for me on #nationalwomensday @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/sq833Z8Ueo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ciarasteward And look at the women you turned out to be! You’re resilient, you lead, and who doesn’t love a good g… https://t.co/aedy3nyGEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND ANOTHER ONE'S GONE!  AND ANOTHER ONE'S GONE!  ANOTHER ONE BITES THE DUST! HEY! HEY! I'M GONNA MAKE IT THROUGH,… https://t.co/8VSIOj3N74]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT EXERCISE DO I NEED TO DO TO GET THE ELEGANT HANDS THAT I SO DESPERATELY DESIRE!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg! Love the eye roll on this female reporter 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤪🤪🤪🤪🤪🤪🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soychicka @dalco1020 @WorldofRobert @maddow This is so incredibly important to see, read and listen to. Thank you… https://t.co/cXTRePTM8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theNICEbus second morning in a row my n24 bus had no heat!! This morning my bus number was 1903 and departed Jamai… https://t.co/veIEWudZUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The original OG!! #notoriousrbg @ Castro Valley, California https://t.co/duCZ4rnx3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know how the #atxcouncil is considering allowing density bonus affordable housing throughout the city? Not sure… https://t.co/6nK1cdHE59]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody knows Jamaicans are the most prideful so just don’t argue with us. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewWolfff @StormResist @DebbieDoesTwitt @laureldavilacpa @brycetache @AdamaEsq @ManInTheHoody @SnowBiAuthor… https://t.co/OFMJI63HkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kempyV1410 @JoDresbach @fabiola_pizana @RobeEmpire_1 @lunalover25 @rockromanfan @kaikaisonic @diamond_shonna… https://t.co/UjmIyzvXRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was among a panel of fabulous black women speaking to students @MCPHSBoston about healthcare careers. Ho… https://t.co/2xNlEFwO7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually made all this faces this morning at my desk when I saw the news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT trump, your brains are sparse and getting sparser every time you open your mouth and stupidity falls out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deshowne Really Bothers Me When He Comes To Social Media Instead Of Asking Me Wtf 😒 He Know We Don’t Count Favors S… https://t.co/MgSe24qV29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kamm_lester I can't believe they would launch this.  So embarrassing and disgusting. 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CourseCharted @thethirstytales @AmeliesBakery @Adventuringgal @KaraDiDomizio @MattsRoadTrip @Sostraveluk… https://t.co/IP5CvTSmlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReginahHope @FREEBetsyB @nhiscare57 @notjudgin @KittyLovesGod @beverlyfelix3 @elliesangelwing @GabrielleMary55… https://t.co/6TFzmvQrYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE PIANIST AT MARIANOS JUST STARTED PLAYING MY WAY AND NOW IM ACTUALLY SOBBING NEXT TO THE GRAPEFRUIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryelder @AOC Huh?  And AOC is an economics major in college?  She needs to get refund of her college tuition.… https://t.co/aJIeegQ9vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaseEmory Yes, I wanted to go to the first (LA) Seulgi’s bday (Dallas) and last show/Wendy’s bday (Vancouver). Bu… https://t.co/xTAUCGG9AU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ordered some EarPods. Since  apple decided to put part of my refund for trading my old iPhone in on a Apple st… https://t.co/dM0X147HRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems as if there’s no greater distraction than being “fully engaged” in nuclear talks in two time zones at once… https://t.co/ji752yorqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big thank you to Newport Beach for the photo feature on Instagram! 🙏 https://t.co/5BioeSH3ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[* graphic courtesy of the wonderful @VickyCBooks  (sorry I forgot to attribute in the haze of OMG I AM A DAY LATE)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sprinkles played a ukelele cover of What Dreams Are Made Of and THEN they played Metamorphosis. Their @HilaryDuff playlist game is strong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andresegura @natimontelongo @ceciliaballi Sorry, Andre. Houston no trae nada. Matamoros/Brownsville tacos are THE BEST.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffBezos Honey, Pardon my language but screw Cuomo &amp; AOC and COME TO VA, you won’t regret it Jeff‼️🌹😘🙏🏻🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[#shop @aanyalinen1 for the #best light blue comforter set. #homedecoration #interiordesign #interior #homemade… https://t.co/7dyEQOLFPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna go on a road trip soon. I wanna drive and drive and drive (I hate driving tho)]]></document><document><![CDATA[My newest @CreativeGIndy sign from tonight! @ Indianapolis, Indiana https://t.co/4f60OxoCQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ginger_Zee I developed this too! Repetitive sounds drive me crazy! It’s nice to hear someone else talk about it. W… https://t.co/MMetZhEGgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mte_detroiter Oh no...  I need the tomato....  😁👍Bread has more calories 🤣😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RrBXXbM6dC  Our Amazon Phone Number is there to help you 24/7 1-855-431-5111    #amazonphonenumber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson just heard your interview if you can call it that. Rutger Bredman he made you look like a lost puppy… https://t.co/V3vNsavfKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[A part of me was hoping to watch #OscarRedCarpet by myself + a part of me is glad that P can see me doing something… https://t.co/UK1QQUBXGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir Traveling to Orlando to see the Wizarding World of Harry Potter would make me SO happy! ⚡️🦉🔮#iFlyAlaska #AlaskaHappyHour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_foreignBee Blackjack isn’t in Starkville proper. It belongs to the county. Sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the perks to living in a c.1880 home....preheating yo coats, etc. when it’s 20 degrees in #Philly.🧤🧣🌬☃️ https://t.co/jEB59LPWI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[In any event, energy is what powers us through. I haven't said this in awhile but this is one of my mottos:  "We ar… https://t.co/qQQEOe925F]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT has some great products.  If you decide to get anything, use my name as a referral.  It's Sandi VoPava]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Never to young to start a empire” this boy has a dream ! Way to inspire him CEO Alan Joyce !  #Qantas… https://t.co/WxbYx7Pzy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaeljknowles @realJeffreyLord @KurtSchlichter           Projection.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TShinkarenko @susanWV309 @happy02013guy @Jonatha97947998 @robtropper @PattiBrookd @sherrig108 @reeves5150… https://t.co/DJPXiaIjaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soul_of_Nowhere So you haven’t started it yet, and I should add it to my list?    Is that a correct interpretation of your reply??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey y’all come see us this weekend duesouthtattooexpo in Biloxi, MS. We have sweetshrimp7 , @brandonlbf2000 , justi… https://t.co/kPykqQTTdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot believe @justinbieber turned 25 yesterday....Sometimes I wish I could go back to my crazy JB fangirl days.… https://t.co/rssMbRMFwc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird You are a bit, literally or mentally, either way, you’re a bot]]></document><document><![CDATA[The synopsis of #FearTWD season 5 sounds just as generic as ever.   I'm still very excited. https://t.co/ooHm6rRj0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work hard ➡️ play hard 😁💁🏻‍♀️  I love working with my friends! We have too much fun 😋 Can’t wait for more ladies to… https://t.co/UR96lhJV1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@townofstmarys Children's colouring contest for drawing your Family on Family Day, don't forget the pets! Download… https://t.co/yDHZ84vQb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DaylightSavingsTime sucks this time of year... I miss feeling like I gained an hour of sleep...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goose the cat inspired a Photoshop trend in Korea that's now gone international  https://t.co/2spc7c75uF]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you're wondering how my day has started off, I slept 2 hours last night and got teary on the train during "… https://t.co/RS6AnNlbpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday hoop session 🏀⛹️‍♀️ #basketballneverstops #basketball #basketballshoes #ballplayer #hoopstar4life #hooper… https://t.co/xAkEv7wUd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunterMw @PeteButtigieg Glad to see you covering, Mayor Pete! He's really great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ih8evrybdy @MJtheProphet @Phil_Nourse @ElPatriotaA1776 @sharrond62 Your points are so poorly considered. You shoul… https://t.co/1MbAWAbCJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTalesTV Wow, the news is on here nh thet just mentioned this. Jussie has been accused of orchestrating and paying for his own attack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[would it be rude if I woke him up and told him I wanna go get some food...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacFinn44 @stonecold2050 I hate these scum that go out and kill mother and baby elephant. They are sick psychos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance @SpeakerPelosi To do impeachment that would make Pence President.  may be worse than 45. she may not… https://t.co/jOgLxkmlOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mantis Cop would like to inform you of your right to purchase #AncestralNight in the UK as of today!  (Art by… https://t.co/RpstQKVvM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to be dramatic but if Colton doesn’t jump the fence tonight, I might. @BachelorABC #BachelorNation #Bachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday crazy girl💗 thanks for being bffs with me for 5 years. Idk what I would do without ur goofy self. Lo… https://t.co/maNbzWjf5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like ma’am it has been 3 years how are you still blind siding me with Hamilton tickets also how did I not suspect a… https://t.co/7oixVg87Qo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein i have no real hopes in Mueller. i hope that report spurs house to connect the dots and impeach, rather see jail.&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngrierWHStaff @dpharalson Mine, too. Imagine how much better he could've done if the @gop was working in the Peop… https://t.co/zwjMvj3Eps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another self-taught musician at our site who plays in a band. #arts #talent It's a beautiful day when you can walk… https://t.co/DTpaMxxFNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who just tried to use an old navy gift card at target by mistake?? That’s right. This guy 🙄 https://t.co/3iz4t5eTlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prosecutor Ellis tells jurors it was 3:15 a.m. , #CoreyJones was just sitting there waiting for a tow. "When it's t… https://t.co/Lfukk4YN2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachael_______ @kanebrown @Country1025WKLB Seriously please hook it up 🙏🏻 we’ve been calling every single day, eve… https://t.co/eROKuQRtcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did a thing. Word: plumage. #noob #scrawlrchallenge #amigoodyet @ Brush, Colorado https://t.co/hAOoaCjpLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlberdianoArg Te recomiendo que sigas a @phylogenomics tiene unas fotos de aves increíbles!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Julie Julie Julie, There is none. It was ALL fabricated by Crooked Hillary because she did collude. Get it.Prez was… https://t.co/KAjKRGdtJ5]]></document></documents></author>