<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Listen Schiff tell everyone how bad of a job they did and that he's going to do better?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sydneegarcia What a day to celebrate such a beautiful soul 🥰 Happy birthday bby! I hope you feel as special as you are today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CondeNast I have always wanted New Yorker...I received the bag...but there was no qualification of 119.99 after th… https://t.co/vp9oaybnkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish @Apple would let me decide the threshold for “Optimize for Device.” Always getting the storage full p… https://t.co/3HT0GPbHsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great advice. Something I would add for those hoping to get into data science: focus on learning about expe… https://t.co/aS8hK19k8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got my tax refund so it looks like I no longer need a sugar daddy/sugar momma. Thanks to all who applied. Chec… https://t.co/2sJiYTeXVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bishop/Apostle J. D. Dearman preaching Jesus Will Do It Again! If you're not here, you're missing out! @ Holy Templ… https://t.co/aIfDm3DAjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy my man @Bin_Hamin loved the @eaglerarelife I sent him. Convert! @rdowieATX @ItsSwamp @CnsprcyHrsmn @Bin_Hamin… https://t.co/1Hny4mv3Xy]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's going on in the playground or on the schoolyard?  What are your kids talking about?  It's likely that they'r… https://t.co/FPlQLZDmVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Within You Without You makes way more sense after an intense psychedelic experience #SgtPeppers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeantownBop Yeah it’s not good. Worse is that they hijacked the Executive Branch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might be able to watch Duke play by 2nd half because of CBS is always on time with their games and what not 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the selection of awesome @GhostGirlGrtngs merch at @MonsterManiaCon]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pledge my sword to the realm! I just entered for a chance to attend the official #GameofThrones S8 premiere. How… https://t.co/zk8oKl1Mtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trendmood @givenchy How does this get past ur quality control team? Do you not see other brands launch ridiculous… https://t.co/fcIxPomFTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinylMePlease I don’t think @OfficialMeshell ‘s “Bitter” ever came out on Vinyl - if it did though .... 💔💔💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ol’ pass to yourself for the lay in vs the zone. Attack the middle and good things happen #trickplays ⚡️🏀😎 https://t.co/HM6ag6p0On]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmassengale @fightingtraffic I very much like what you said at Seaside, and would amend it slightly to say that th… https://t.co/Ze9AHIXJ8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@js26783_joe @CREWcrew @Witchypoo43 Did you say the same thing when Obama put kids in cages and separated  them fro… https://t.co/6gks0j7vxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ask_WellsFargo lol-  great prank---i saw  a guy taping over wells fargo  atm`s signs with out of order   - IT WAS… https://t.co/4irwOJfPoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacticalDave44 @s_finch9 Thanks @TacticalDave44 Hope to see you in Winnipeg!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ltmjason @rileym4a @DaveyMuise @AtTheBarr Brother - thank YOU for your endless support and INSANELY good vibes. HMU, we’ll see you soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Drip. What you wear doesn't make you a better person. What you do for others does. I hope my character speak… https://t.co/SBWO2ai63J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkCurnutt @seanthurmond @CliffBruntAP @OfficialHacksaw I’m pretty the Farmers Market]]></document><document><![CDATA[「 k e y ² 」• Montreal, 2019 •  . . New process. Testing new tools and grading. • . . with: key_anne_  . thank you:… https://t.co/Cp33BG0bv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bradley61688984 @_Elz00 It still doesn't help that his challenge was completely reckless. He wasn't even looking at the ball]]></document><document><![CDATA[In less than 2 years, @tnyscm has become the largest, most active, and fastest growing community on @meetup that fo… https://t.co/8cf88zSTT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulHelmke I really enjoyed your Bicentennial Magazine article on the student fee hike protest of ‘69. A bit befor… https://t.co/t6Hgeg1sQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna be able to record and do my own graphic then be like man, I’m finna be this B out lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[For man looks at the outward appearance, but the Lord looks at the heart. 1 Sam 16:7]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the theatre for the first time together! Should be fun watching Dragons! @ Century Theaters https://t.co/td2Wkf5OxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hawryluk_Hive @patriotfal_1 we're a look but not kind of crew for good reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn't sleep so decided to get a workout in before work. Gotta be ARMed for the day. @ Fit Nation Bossier CIty https://t.co/9YsdUWIxX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaxjin Nice.  Brotherly wrestling match.  #competitionisgoodforthesoul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que mal primer tiempo, ninguna llegada clara, no han resultado los cambios, El enano inexistente... #vamoscatolica #LosCruzados]]></document><document><![CDATA[loving to play basketball it's a Hope Street YMCA and 4th and hope in the city of Los Angeles #love the court#justdoit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms Brown’s 6th science room door decorated in celebration of Black History Month.  Past, Present, and Future.… https://t.co/zfwSb6MCl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people tell how long ago something happened based on the Netflix show they were watching at the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 minute of your time gets you a free share of stock. That’s always a good investment! Join @RobinhoodApp and we'll… https://t.co/2sxHdx2Ovv]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Colossus Festival: Portraits: The Other End #newcolossusfestival #portraitphotography #portraits… https://t.co/OJv8I84tRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re a waste of a woman. Scared of some fat wigger who thinks he’ll be famous on twitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregorMLB Players play...they don’t set the corporate agenda. The Blue Jays are clearly in a rebuild mode, and whi… https://t.co/nUcdfEeLz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 is shaping up to be a great year for concerts for me. @Metallica @JimBreuer - March 9th @Slayer @lambofgod… https://t.co/O5CqHr3jND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PadawanDani Yup nothing like home sweet home. Plus the weeknd on loud 🤟]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't want to make a time change tweet, but here is one: it feels strange to get to work in the dark. Feels like… https://t.co/lSe165iRmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nckhui @CumberlandCoSch @fayobserver @CCSSuptConnelly @WCPSS Praying for you and your recovery. #LeadershipMatters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robey (Almost finished…)  Finally: even if it got zero riders, DPX still made a certain sense to BART because it f… https://t.co/Wu0HHCyW7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson It’s a new Cult based on cheating and lying and has been embraced by the TV Tycoon Evangelicals!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BamaOutdoors That's just so wrong. Now you need two little people dressed as Bo and Luke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bubba_March He’s still with you!! Angel guiding and watching over us all 🙏🏾❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Design phase vs. Real deal! Not too shabby.   https://t.co/IpfqFLQbKR  #Design #Homedesign #HouseandHome #Archicad… https://t.co/oxUdnpRHDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mizz_sgonzalez When I try and convince the kids I am the weirdest teacher at Walker... https://t.co/7ipFJzUjrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KekeKodeine Yea that’s just part of the game , he said on his next album it’s gone have nothing but trilogy vibes… https://t.co/ytHNrudaoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelamilz @workingrem Totally agree with this! I love the trust and flexibility to get my work done without being micromanaged.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out for dinner at one of the best Asian restaurants in Grand Rapids. You do have to ask for the Korean menu too. Ve… https://t.co/EgRLTLRLfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yuri_Bigouy @Neoavatara @SpeakerPelosi @IlhanMN She is from Minnesota - please. Hiding behind "culture" is a ridic… https://t.co/QfHdLoKC5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[When work finished early 2 mornings  in a row, now morning 3 and we can’t go home for nothing ain’t this some shit!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjforsythe New rule, you can only post photos of food you make if you have enough for all of us too. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connect with me on LinkedIn!  #wisepowerwashing iwashhouses@gmail.com https://t.co/p0QQDJaapR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GBrott The wheels were right about to hit the runway and he took the plane back up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of the book challenge by @ConnectedTruth. I challenge @CoachGeorgeCC to post a favorite book for 7 days and t… https://t.co/zd2bT3bgSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Undiano dice que Messi  Se ha tirado, venga pues  Y reguilon diciéndole a (Suárez)  Tú si que eres feo 🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill I will vote in the Republican Primaries against Trump if he’s still in office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardConnector Autos and GU. $2 each. Follow me and check out the other cheap stuff I have listed. https://t.co/oKMLRzDJV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllisterDen I'm with you #homegirl! ❤ Your arguments are rational and coherent in an irrational and incoherent world...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Follow813News Tipoff from today's @USFWBB game! #BullSpeedAhead #USF #LetsGoBulls https://t.co/iNVQLZoLpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your national sack monster is in the combine today - let’s go DL50 @suttonsmith5‼️#BeGreat https://t.co/3bFJVpfSQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlourishOrDie What time will we be able to draft our teams? Any idea..?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmay789 Maybe. Two wars would be even better to distract us from his treason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your slice of knowledge for the day: this is a “Rafter” of turkeys, not a flock. #themoreyouknow @ Oakland, Califor… https://t.co/60WJiUxqOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LinksGems @TimGavrich @RichardZokol @Back9Ben @AnthonyPioppi @TPCSawgrass @PGATOUR Nice! Did you read The Agony an… https://t.co/loIpKEiyXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TabernacleATL soooooooo y’all just weren’t going to announce that the @YG concert is postponed tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@bstockus introduced @GraceKelemanik &amp; @AmyLucenta at @MathLeaders with @janetdnuzzie @mbader32 @sondra_cano… https://t.co/eRIi5wBQv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[MIN1, WPG1, WSH1, And CAR1 all miserable tonight but Ducks hog wild lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new Samsung Galaxy S10 Plus comes with 8 cores, 12GB RAM, and 1TB flash storage. I have worked with databases servers with less specs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of you @Jojoo_Paris @Saldana_AJ @derekdiaz_15 ! As we talked about prior to the Alvarez game ! You guys we… https://t.co/qpJWBw6ZkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ethiopian Airlines has been such a big part of our family's adoption journey. We stand by you today and our heat br… https://t.co/UH0TkRSUMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody ever stops drinking once they out people may drink at slower rates or end up going home before others but no… https://t.co/90iupGKBSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better than videos of Trump throwing paper towels, eating taco bowls or pushing other governments’ officials out of… https://t.co/VggPAjCiEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrentOster @jacquicollins_ Dog year city, I age 7 days for each day I’m there. Not to mention 3 pack a day habit in 2nd hand smoke!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing but heart, fight, and creativity. I'm ready to go. I want this more than anybody and I've wanted it for a l… https://t.co/wIaxd8AaAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChronicHoosier @ChronicHoosier @AssemblyCall Kermit Davis.....PAGING KERMIT DAVIS!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheVikingAge Idk if he solves our LT issues enough to move Reiff inside. I’d rather we draft someone like Dillard.… https://t.co/wwdCOloFD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChacaoToday AMLO resucita al Foro de Sao Paulo en México. Ya ofreció el abreboca del guión: una nueva constitucion… https://t.co/eD6yiolLVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 22 #Hokies have a chance to get back on track at home tonight against Georgia Tech in a game where offense may… https://t.co/cuyQ9ZLzLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_AllenSZN @spectrorect it's so perfect, I just don't know how these clowns fall asleep watching it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFlyManly Lol I be loving it too they don’t get back till damn near February]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomPerez Look forward to you all screaming at the sky on election night again in 2020. You never learn. You just get worse. Fascinating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌟 “It Doesn't Matter Where You Came From, All That Matters Is Where You Are Going."  🌟 #TheBucketList… https://t.co/2fVh0Kycq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kingbuzzard1 @RepMaxineWaters Awww i have kids between 30 years young and 15.. sounds like something my 15yo would… https://t.co/ZFI2mjtOcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy MAR10 Day! 👏🏻 Um dos meus personagens favoritos dos games tem um dia só pra ele, dia 10 de Março ou #Mar10. P… https://t.co/0KEjcoM8YD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool to see @brett_wittchow Grandpa cutting down the net!  Congrats, Titans!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @rolandsmartin Young and dumb....brainwashed traitor to your race! Stop cooning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[RBIs from Will Blocker, Jake Justiss and Dylan Turner give Tallassee its first lead of the season. Tigers ahead of… https://t.co/Acel4S55zM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NavasAlbani For real, let me tell you , for me you have been the greatest proof that God is with me. I lov u 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janesports You should have each student do one paragraph each, divvy it up, then write a parody paragraph and then… https://t.co/s77ZA8pEeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGoJen When I see pictures of Tito,it reminds me of my brothers dog Sami. 😔 We had good times, when she was alive. https://t.co/T4gMpiGLNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gameday!!! #prideandjoy #23 #jayden @ Fayetteville, North Carolina https://t.co/5vgGWHmrmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrBlockbird @mbalvenie28 @Kherman112 Typical but I’d guess your not the one😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@porterguy1969 @dilemmv What’s he supposed to do? Vote against it and then be labeled a sexist misogynist?]]></document></documents></author>