<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Tiger Industries #PLTWSummit Delegation dressed to impress for tonight's Banquet. @PLTWorg @Mary_Murphy17… https://t.co/wWu8h2Pwwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbiedoll0087 I enjoy hiking through that area with camera ready. It must have been a hard life in the 1800s, mos… https://t.co/cetN3QNLwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 MY DAWGS 🐕 PROD. BY KID OCEAN 🌊  New cartoon music video dropping tomorrow 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, I think we need to stick with retaining and recruiting the best teachers we can and let them do their thi… https://t.co/sSzKXgU6dA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spades Night on Saturday Night starting @ 6pm @ The Lowe Escape https://t.co/DPBZ5uvAXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLozanoA Eso se llama negligencia, quizás debería investigar la palabra no le vendría mal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MegaPhilX @RE_Games Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/onfy8W8yYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[How she waiting to be praised? Looks like she's doing something for the kids to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoRepEvans @elijahhaahr Stop it Jean! You know how hard Peter fought for this for the past couple years. Even had… https://t.co/wWdrzXbayA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @GovKemp Is Kemp the Gov who ran a campaign ad with him sitting on a porch in a chair threatening the… https://t.co/97GTtXdOZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got tagged 5 fav horror + 5 tags  1- The shining  2- Alien 3- Halloween  4- Scream  5- 28 days later… https://t.co/fV80bLBDEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been looking forward to this for some time. I’m in need of a break. Can’t think of a better place to go and th… https://t.co/J9qPGys83s]]></document><document><![CDATA[PXG Gen2 X is Legit ! #pxgtroops #mitsubishichemical #pxg @ Doral Resort and Country Club, Doral, Florida https://t.co/74lakZnNrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhh well that explains a lot. 😂💯 Assuming the worst, creating problems and narratives is unhealthy and total 💩.… https://t.co/u5PckERQOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[To cover all those car payments I missed. Really pissed at the unemployment office, since I haven't received it in… https://t.co/4Pwbs8L6Zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot schedule a @AskLyft for tomorrow morning to MCI. I’m also having trouble contacting #CustomerService. 🤔🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel so very ashamed to that I’m RT-ing this, but I can’t stop laughing. So, in case this has the same effect for… https://t.co/NvFWYFxnBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiichaelStevens It’s a cross we must bear for the rest of our lives I guess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericfisher After such a quiet year last year too - and a fairly quiet few years in the Deep South. We need to be p… https://t.co/i1bIbJGz7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coopercooperco @chrisdole86 i'm going and it'll be a fine end to my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still needs more official confirmation, but here's the translated article claiming the 737 MAX has been grounded in… https://t.co/bVvEX5iwhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennishegstad @eugenewei Proud of what we accomplished but will never get over feeling like it could have been way bigger]]></document><document><![CDATA[My version of a Lite Lunch 😋 @ Hanami Sushi &amp; Grill https://t.co/fZ7OZljBLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Memes #memesdaily #progressive #dank #dankmemesdaily #dankmeme #crossovermedia #tampa #miami #orlando #capecoral… https://t.co/H2gJe8bnZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[People like her will always take advantage of the system. The system where our government encourages you to go into… https://t.co/tx1yYSY1kN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Lone Star Beer by @pabstblueribbon @ Stubb's Indoors — https://t.co/Oc1gfrM3i1]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Christ is the only way to be! #livethestory #dailyverse #livingwordgalena @ Living Word Lutheran Church - Galena… https://t.co/J0dT79Rvxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dukes PLAYERS are pulling in a minimum of 3K per ticket and people still think they shouldn’t get paid..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight to everyone except those who stand on stage with the DJ at the club.... you're not cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice start to the trip! I love bass fishing! @ Fin &amp; Feather Lodge &amp; Marina https://t.co/LdWxsptjbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[nakEdtruth - Starving Artist (Official Music Video) https://t.co/mwwpJ2cwy4 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m never buying @Breyers ever again!! My fave ice cream, hadn’t bought it in a while, something was different w/ c… https://t.co/CJ13us5uPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 4:29 AM CST, Meade [Meade Co, KS] LAW ENFORCEMENT reports SNOW of 1.50 INCH. A RANGE OF ONE TO TWO INCHES WAS RE… https://t.co/Gg2xnXFEFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/O the Homie @marktheMFshark on becoming a 3x All-American &amp; placing 3rd in the Nation. 💪🏽💯🤼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganOrtagus @WhipClyburn Apparently due to the growing number of anti Semite religious groups ,they feel their v… https://t.co/37JL3F2wRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Laguardia getting ready to head to SXSW. Can't wait to connect, politic, ditto... #headedtosxsw @ LaGuardia Airp… https://t.co/BLFW8FWtES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, it's been a good run, but my 2015 Razer Blade is officially dead.  R.I.P. to my first gaming laptop and the d… https://t.co/cdtWY3J8Ag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilybaldwin220 @realDonaldTrump I don’t joke about that. Politics, yes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AprilDRyan @realDonaldTrump @CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNEWS @FOXNEWS  #Oscars #Oscar   **BREAKI… https://t.co/LjuylmYHeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I treat my body like I get a new one every day” oh wow this is gonna be a fantastic Friday pod @ColeyMick]]></document><document><![CDATA[first day back to class and i’m already doing a discussion board. yeah i quit already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marianegan @Xanthippus1 @dvorakoelling @realDonaldTrump Just saw the colab was posted by Fox.. lol.. Doesnt matter… https://t.co/OQokJQ1H5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillPascrell You’re a damn idiot and fool there is going to be a wall one way or the other...!!!! So do what your… https://t.co/Df5JyaO7Hq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capgemini_aust Brava @capgemini_aust @salesforce @SalesforceEQ @Capgemini @CapgeminiInvent @CapgeminiASE… https://t.co/QcPdHLD4c6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SundayThoughts #SundayMotivation #SundayMorning  @OlgaPer65487606 @FelixNater @unclerayscrazy @WendyKathrynOwe… https://t.co/QGvt0vA2ab]]></document><document><![CDATA[Da la casualidad que siempre me encuentro cosas en algún lugar, hoy encontré una chamarra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drinkslinger321 @Ben_M_Berry @LarsenBee @laurenpgiles @GrandFundo I rode around Taipei in monsoons when I was 20,… https://t.co/xqHqJPR9iX]]></document><document><![CDATA[And thank you #choosingwisely hero’s @DrSimpsonHSR @FutureDocs @ReshmaGuptaMD @SL_Wallingford @KellyRand4… https://t.co/V4rk1aG8It]]></document><document><![CDATA[@demeatloaf I have a 14 month old and a 3yr old MOST nights they sleep through now. My daughter finally started aro… https://t.co/L8ZMytLnfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFranken21 @ChaseOliver10 @officialcvallas Top 5 human to ever exist. Right up there with Abe Lincoln]]></document><document><![CDATA[blakes birthday is tomorrow &amp; then it will be one month until mine 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewamiller @EricHolder So you are saying the Republicans didn't play politics with their vote...]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s only 7am &amp; I’m already getting good vibes. It will be a good day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been legit contemplating buying a Nintendo Switch for the past 6 months. Will I do it soon? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jperricelli_ Why not? We are the 2nd oldest franchise in NFL history behind the bears and Geno Smith was the 1st b… https://t.co/5KnAoUdENR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susan_chilton THANK 👏YOU👏 tired of hearing about all these sneaky mountain tops!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stillman_sean Nope, this was illustrated before the new First Order stormtrooper design was finalized. So Imperial… https://t.co/2Yz1qCiK8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swilli0521 @heady_chris You are exactly right. So many wasted opportunities earlier in the year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday morning jamz purchased last week at @folkartsrarerec in #sandiego #flyingburritobrothers #gramparsons… https://t.co/s6NtvVSMxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[+4% extra GDP +1% new business +1% consumer confidence = 6% GDP that doubles in 12 years to 5.2 trillion GDP. Debt… https://t.co/qupr4zn1n9]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:30 PM: Yet another system is moving into West Michigan tomorrow... I have a brief rundown and a first look at sch… https://t.co/YT3rCB0FNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeGoldFool @Dame_Lillard Damian Lillard, Steph Curry, Victor Oladipo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#writersofinstagram #poetsofinstagram #teachersofinstagram #tutorsofinstagram #poetry #poems #writing #freelance… https://t.co/aAL82isC3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants it AZ?  @Cehsfootball already has @MaterDeiHS on the schedule, so which one of our other top programs wil… https://t.co/akOi0dRyLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMcLachlan60 @NonGMOToronto @stuartsmyth66 @flutemanrich @albertafarmlife @biotechaction @GovCanHealth @CFIA_Food… https://t.co/baYZC01Tv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino It’s crooked @HillaryClinton’s game. DEFLECT. DEFLECT. DEFLECT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started my day off at sacredmandalastudio with this super cool piece on @crossfitdurham. It’s Hebrew for “it’s not… https://t.co/iuol5udAwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/3LOIbgKEs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buffer Your potential solution on the Status page worked for me, and I am eager for a solution that feels less… intense. Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeeWii_Herman @FortniteGame Meant to say bot lol. You wouldn’t know because you play to much Apex 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[True Blue - https://t.co/CX6htT1qgU #booklover #writing @ Chesapeake and Maine https://t.co/0FWQtZjD5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Circa Remember he’s speaking to to E Cummings one of biggest Uncle Toms there is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robobskis @j2502ackie @Peteonone @ScotNational Which bulls hit claims would they be? That Sturgeon is Head if State?  Oh...wait...]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Bernie wants to run on the Democratic Ticket, become a Democrat. What a novel idea. Don't expect the political m… https://t.co/655wIlXfe7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the shout out @julianbotta! I’m trying to convince my #EMPharmacyTeam to embrace Twitter - hopefully nex… https://t.co/ggbjfz6mrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this @muse night is off to an interesting night, where we’re taking Simulation Theory to its literal limit https://t.co/SdcawB2IIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to wish a very happy 25th birthday to justinbieber hope it was special I think it's cool that you are… https://t.co/PicHxOipCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems coincidental that the parents of poor #NickSandmann decided to sue the Washington Post and Jeff Bezos who… https://t.co/jQz0qwuagc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Invention of Humanity: Equality and Cultural Difference in World History https://t.co/KVEGttWXH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are upgrading this protest: moving inside the Capitol rotunda now! Join us for a warm protest against a fake nat… https://t.co/hfl0crbupF]]></document><document><![CDATA[First package from @Scramble_ can’t wait to rock that sweet gi at my next practice #grabbingsleeves #jiujitsu… https://t.co/G78LRFY4Eq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mannifresh25 The joys of being an adult. While we watch athletes bitch and moan about getting paid millions upon millions of dollars 👎🏻👎🏻👎🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep, it's hard to watch. The hustle would look a lot different if they could make basic shots...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Ponte Vedra Beach, Florida https://t.co/wiXfzLFT5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Devastated to learn that my filing deadline doesn’t care I have the sniffles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoannaConn3lly An extreme example is like if they add a 10 minute 7th inning stretch show for ratings but cut the… https://t.co/Nrwgl5FoCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBaier I would love to see a breakdown of the cost of social security  retirement payments  Survivor child benefits  Disability]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a good boy. Always look into masters eyes!! I lets him know that you are his and that you want to see him in… https://t.co/GKgWcUFtx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the Lakers need to go ahead and sit everyone and get the highest draft pick chances they can get. It's.  Over. https://t.co/JzlnlhDRr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @ROCtheFuture Chairman says “Not asking a state or mayor take over. But asking the State to support a community e… https://t.co/Bhsj2gIZ0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kick his ass Dave can’t stand hunter always holding ppl back an still have that pervert Corey graves still there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come visit me at the #EdTech Showcase sponsored by @MyPowerSchool and @Microsoft while you are at #PSEDGE https://t.co/QkqD71sszo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some meetings give more than they take. Grateful for the conversation about ‘indigenous UofT’ with colleagues Jonat… https://t.co/eBEPYhlY0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XXX_CockLover Salty.  I have blow guys who’s cum was sweet but most are salty.  Never had the ‘pineapple’ cum.  I… https://t.co/uBE9ZXnibj]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you choose A: You can only follow Joy Behar  If you choose B: You have to hide your best friend’s dog in Mexico.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Look! I stand at the door and knock. If you hear my voice and open the door, I will come in, and we will share a m… https://t.co/uvn3VfE9RR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassandraSeven @ProudResister Hmmm I’m incorrect. There was a partially effective vaccine for the plague.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guindage @ClayTravis a) 5 is what you’re looking for 👍🏻 watched it live and instantly saw his hand hit the rim and… https://t.co/LFGKwzzYcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iron_lombardi @Mel_the_geek @HillaryWarnedUs @HillaryClinton In reality we simply want the middle class to get jus… https://t.co/1csQcaV6UU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We spent today at @tthc2019 with @JudgeHidalgo talking about #publichealth #emergency preparedness and response. We… https://t.co/u1gUXbtBew]]></document></documents></author>