<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@drjoy77 Hi everyone, it’s me Sheila Wilson, 5th grade teacher from fabulous Seatack Elementary in Virginia Beach.… https://t.co/RSBz2cX8N4]]></document><document><![CDATA[A terrifying look at the consequences of climate change - The end of normal https://t.co/cyvR8PDmup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wxxdlxndwxlkxr @Anni_Bruno @naiibianchick @DonCheadle Be sure not to show an ankle ladies! You don’t want to tempt… https://t.co/1LDlm0Xbrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first ship?  I guess with a ship name it was Troyella from #HSM.  Number of other couples w/out ship names come… https://t.co/o1qQN5kXQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know.... I downloaded the soundtrack. I was so happy to see that both if those songs were included... kinda wish… https://t.co/herd0sqE31]]></document><document><![CDATA[This never ever woulda happened at ridge especially if it’s was Mrs Drone]]></document><document><![CDATA[i really wanna go somewhere warm for spring break, ya girl is craving the sun ☀️😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damon_thayer @PrattforKY I hope you vote for the legalization of marijuana in Kentucky!!! I endorse it to help tho… https://t.co/VxFAUBJw1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michigan_king1 Are you looking for a baby mama? Cause I can supply one or two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I already know one of my biggest issue in playing the mom role is I currently can waste countless time watching stu… https://t.co/jWenyS7PDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered the @Chick-fil-A survey, so that I can win a @FreeChick-fil-ASandwich!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my mom that yesterday and she said *I* think you're adorable. Which would be the thing to say in like, 1982.… https://t.co/gyjFO0TVL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Put your hand on a hot stove for a minute, and it seems like an hour. Sit with a pretty girl for an hour, and it s… https://t.co/S3jRFwu9U1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aahunter29 @fmreeves2001 Tone and Felix — two of my faves — ahhhhh yeah — Can’t wait to see how this team comes to… https://t.co/VYSh15zZuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This first grader built ABC repeating color patterns in #steam today 👏🏻 @wresWildcats @scienceCCPS https://t.co/WmnQ91sXju]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diagnosis Murder way ahead of its time. Lol #mainstreammedia @ East Sandwich, Massachusetts https://t.co/YelfCQR1Bb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maureen_B5 @GoodDoctorABC @BANNERSMUSIC I totally agree. Between the song, Shaun and Clair I could not stop crying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m not looking forward to working a double on friday but i’m looking forward to my plans after work. i’m conflicted]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday week to the two best human beings I know 💕💕 Also, S/O to the Q for taking all my money this weekend… https://t.co/0j8p3GuiT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emsque Change is rarely worth keeping- I geocache so use them for trading. For bills, an old wallet works surprisingly well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFL @DoubleBlueBlog @robertgreeley22 I have been a STH for over 25 Years with the @TorontoArgos but attended a few… https://t.co/dB7wKlETeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been 8 years since Minnesota had a First Lady. Coming up at 11 @MPRnews I’ll talk live with Gwen Walz, the wif… https://t.co/EgXzq5MP28]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a TA for an advanced course, how do you handle doing more than asked ("it will take you 2 hours" - took 15 hours… https://t.co/kyidYdj8pM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there a polite way to ask someone to stop talking to you? I mean none of the things I’m thinking are nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[White coat ceremony, on the road to becoming a nurse 💪🏼 https://t.co/0Zu2MFQmt0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Should have Capitalised the word God. It's enough that God's own name was removed in over 7k places in the… https://t.co/nvNMYK93aW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frjohnhollowell Father Mike Schmidt said in an Ascension Presents video, he was called a Child Molestor in an airp… https://t.co/JmjZqnYWZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mydoggyruss @BodhisattvaKat @CindisPLace @reese_malmgren @zingazingzing @Tam_Resist @mom_ceo_dj @Vickivbreezy… https://t.co/GXEjTryA9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lock me in on @z1077 right now, STL! Your next keyword to win a trip to Los Angeles for our #iHeartAwards is coming… https://t.co/Xf4hLFeuoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DissonantSubLT I like the usage of “dope” it’s really an underused word these days lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueDestiny92 @mirandalambert I agree !!!!!!  You are truly a.  #QueenofCountry  #QueenofCountry  #QueenofCountry… https://t.co/UHx0GBE9Ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrazyHaifisch @Billie_Jean00 #WhileYouWereSnoring I held your nostrils closed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday, I ate my Oreo pudding while sitting on the toilet. And just last week, I ate McDonald’s and drank a frap… https://t.co/Ad3HdGcTPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dad has apparently written 2 (TWO) letters to THE POPE and if that aint cute idk what is @Pontifex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethMacFarlane My heart breaks for that young boy who had to go through that kind of trauma because his parents ar… https://t.co/ZOkOS66PbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Macie is so obsessed with my brother Zach. 😭 any time she likes something she involves Zach with it. “Ohhh these ar… https://t.co/TowQ4Hi3ff]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I Refuse to Refer to Pro Choice People as Anything Other Than Murderers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I reflect on the last few years, I am so grateful for all of my friends, family, and customers for loving and en… https://t.co/Vsk0Ny8GhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FixGovernment @jimdwrench @cspanwj @realDonaldTrump @RepAdamSchiff @JerryNadler Are you sure....? My unnamed sourc… https://t.co/rYsntiyWQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drive by the ocean every day going to and from work and it’s one of the greatest blessings]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved reading all 3 of these back to back! Haven't checked out the playlists yet though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover When I'm Sixty-Four by The Beatles. https://t.co/91Rp22UqZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rogue_Leia_ @Sean_C_Larkin @Rogue_Leia_ good 👁 and the standard peanut M&amp;M’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[What? Fracking causes earthquakes? I wonder if anyone here in Oklahoma has thought about that. We are known for our… https://t.co/itL5zsMazE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should not have to justify myself when I tell a guy I’m not interested. It’s 2019, no means no. https://t.co/GtrOMk8Db7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realjoshgentry @WilliamDStevens @ViVicz93 @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@top2012kek @718project @joerogan Lol dude he literally said the father of the girl he lost his vrignity to tried t… https://t.co/yOjj0LcnBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seguimos en la Planeación y organización de actividades del PRI Saltillo, sin duda contamos con gente talentosa y c… https://t.co/KESrs8BrV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[:( sometimes I get sad about how I let certain people hurt me so bad emotionally and mentally]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Admin Apparently Still Pursuing Saudi Deal to Turn Over Banned Sensitive Nuclear Info, that Could Lead to Bom… https://t.co/mGtWCWcuko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillKourkoutis @stateofSATE I am so sad. I got the timing wrong and missed everything but the last song! https://t.co/hS74W736pL]]></document><document><![CDATA[when i walk around campus i probably look mad or mean but the truth is, my eyes are just sensitive and the sun is really bright]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RPJ1317 13/f/OH and someone replies 25/m/OH you instantly leave https://t.co/bzrmT6PYpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gif just accurately represents my mood 10000000% of the time https://t.co/068bfuvkg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein God is doing all this for a real... we shall see the outcome but I bet it’s to judge and put us to te… https://t.co/SxH5w7QZfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things that are wrong: 1. Pickle and Peanut Butter Sandwiches  2. Kim Jong-un  3. Crocs 4. The temperature in Fort… https://t.co/CocWXi6fvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mind over matter, right?  Tonight’s training was 103mins/10miles/1200calories. I didn’t quite finish with the run i… https://t.co/JASGQCHmUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one will care about climate change if Pakistan and India get into a nuclear war.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TFredYFred @FMSTrojanPride @mathmom2016 @Mrs_T77 @e12_nicole @MrThompson3 There’s another great section on onboard… https://t.co/U064xeN7lF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/3BhT7j3yvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasongay And I see the game includes my beloved @Bucks. Please pick me...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished walking 1.81 miles in 38m:32s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/UMLNNg2fHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tayshia’s dad is breaking it down. #TheBachelor https://t.co/qmvPoB0hVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS44 I totally believe in you President Barack Obama but I don't know if I believe in America anymore. You were… https://t.co/SAB53HW1le]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/22/2019 • #Art • #PizzaRanch 🍕 🍗 🥗 🍦 ☕️ for #lunch 😋 in #Conway #Arkansas 🙏🏻 #blessed @ Pizza Ranch https://t.co/7ima0pU7i9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voting for Miss Jetset 2019 has begun! Click the link in my bio and feel free to share and vote everyday! Much love… https://t.co/Bd4feYW4Y3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who continues to support this person rather than asking him to apologize to the CPD (and pay for the cost of… https://t.co/rahUqIs4qN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing we aren’t used to. Been through many #CardiacCard moments in my 33 years of being a Louisville fan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And why being lost - maybe a menace to others sharing the road with you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you and your hubs wake up from a nap ready to demolish the gym but it closes at 8... so you go to Buc-ees instead 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[JC has a very solid grasp of the reality of life and eternity .  "Every knee shall bow and every tongue confess tha… https://t.co/xhkUVJuObE]]></document><document><![CDATA[A 'first kiss' conversation between a teacher and his students leaves parents stunned: https://t.co/byPaXs2RGm https://t.co/pemXDMByZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nursekelsey mnemonic for cranial nerves.prils and tans for drugs,and many more. Same concept]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudienceNetwork @KipMooreMusic @AudienceMusic Wish I was still in Cali!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ron_fournier @TheRickWilson @realDonaldTrump I have always respected the AMERICAN flag. This is abuse. Unwarranted undesired affection.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmAlanWalker went hardstyle with “Lost Control”! Haha. Loved it!🤘🏼😍💯✌🏼️🤗🔥💛❣🎵🔊🎉💙🙌🏼💫 #AlanWalker #love #DJ #EDM… https://t.co/kfZcgfwgq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@georgiagirl581 @dtdstable Congratulations!🏇🏇🏇I was just at MHV on Saturday🏇🏇🏇I enjoy going there😊🏇🏇🏇😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the #POCUS people involved in the manifestation of @TIMESUPHC #TimesUpHealthcare - @ultrasoundREL… https://t.co/qPbNwsdwE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dabo Swinney’s first order of Clemson spring practice business: find new leaders https://t.co/PJcc01Z448 via @postandcourier]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should’ve started studying for this anatomy test a week ago, but nope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘I have taken and will continue to take many lessons from this.’ - @JustinTrudeau #SNCLavalin #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrScottEddy @WindstarCruises @JohnDelaneyWSC @Ceebz_Gerard @5foottraveler @EatSleepCruise @PortholeCruise Can’t wa… https://t.co/vEszO7iMIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox News really the first STATE NEWS CHANNEL EVER.  PROPAGANDA SHOVED DOWN YOUR THROAT WORSE THAN A BAD PORNO...… https://t.co/SlbDOMXkGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning and Happy Friday! #MyrtleBeach #FridayFeeling @EdPiotrowski @MyMyrtleBeach https://t.co/2zdxoJXZIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent so much time seeking peace in others that it felt foreign when it came from within #honestyhour]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved your scenes today @1SteveBurton @GenieFrancis @thejonlindstrom @MauraWest! Totally fabulous! 👏🏻👏🏻 #EdgeofSeat… https://t.co/1odd5tEJQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[What goes through my head when I’m falling asleep...  Gnerder reveal parties but for what types of fires you get that day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quebec Winter Carnival, with more than 100yrs history, and has been the annual event in the city since 1954. These’… https://t.co/IOc6fhtaJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @TexasTechMBB, that was fun, wasn’t it?! 👀🔥🙌🏻 #WreckEm #4To1 https://t.co/gT3Xb5rEWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 years ago today, I started working @DTWeetin! Accepting the position of Volunteer Supervisor was one of the best… https://t.co/TKqWcUfRh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[A swastika was found scrawled in the boys bathroom at an elementary school in Bethesda, MD. https://t.co/r3AO8ghbRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Va a ser una semana interesante: mi hermana llega el martes, me operan el jueves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Years from now, I will have to explain to my children who Space Jesus was and why I dressed like this to go see him… https://t.co/F1dkXA6uWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vickivbreezy @ivyjofreeman @doctoralexa @ElleWibble @FredMertzReal @JuliaKozuschnik @Grabsback2 @rdnk_grl @efocuss… https://t.co/vEOjtxKBoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/ndZw2yhi6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marvel Villains getting it done in 19.1 #thriveopen19 @ Thrive Fit https://t.co/eios7FZtyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @shorsleyteach to share 7 covers of books I love without explanation/reviews. Each day I post m… https://t.co/4gC6hmzIDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am an acrylic fluid artist and a fellow artist I follow on YouTube introduced me to this concept. Fascinating stu… https://t.co/H6zfV9anDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dang. I really need to work on not getting taken advantage of.  I always make too many excuses for people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya está disponible @MiLibroHispano en su #segundaedicion en @issuu. Ideal para #leer#compartir #participar. Enlace… https://t.co/UyMdyTAVdY]]></document></documents></author>