<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheDemocrats Democrats have already made it clear that they are not concerned about safety in our communities. See… https://t.co/1cJYzimzk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i don’t get prompt A on my exam i’m gonna kms bc thats the only one i can write about in depth /:]]></document><document><![CDATA[I especially appreciate that the grad students / postdocs taking me to lunch and happy hour were provided a credit… https://t.co/HTTLFRcdVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m TIREDT of y’all putting ccsds snow day tweet on your stories rn like we don’t know already]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to thank @GVVikingFB  for the invite feeling very humble for the invited ready to compete https://t.co/Z28B7Ln65u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mattkadian @Samuraihonor I just got it. But it’s only good for long distances.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marccrosas @UnivisionSports Tengo 25 años mirando Univisión y se van por lo que vende, no por la realidad. León no… https://t.co/4vnrtJHFom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColinASteph Faksa’s head was down around his hip since he hunched over and Mika hit him in shoulder blade- they wa… https://t.co/IeT1MEgFUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shari2112 @LindseyGrahamSC For some reason it bothers me. Have never understood why but I get agitated at the peop… https://t.co/Msp91Jywz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[popular opinion: most people who agree with that statement are white. interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaliforniaPanda @CNN @MichaelCohen212 PATH;O: LOG A 5 dollar note            i-c: A-L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social approval is a poor substitute for a clear conscience. #social #socialite #society #approval #popularity… https://t.co/oPYWmhRP2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeattleURedSea @mid_madness I was at CKMS during 6th grade, for me that was like 1997? Something like that. I was A 2004 HS grad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaundraSmoss @ByreLisa @RyanAFournier The catholic catechism is mans opinion, albeit it does align with the Bible… https://t.co/rGDZkZer4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carsemanic Brahh, shit like this make you really think how nature will Seriously fucked us up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ol_TimeFootball Nice trivia on this game John reaves eagles qb started during the strike in 87 after being out of the league for 6 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One 💛! ☯️🌎👁️☮️😎💣!    https://t.co/92qDM8wrwo https://t.co/yBZgFlUHyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoogieMontana15 @ECastro_12 Lmfaoo don’t do datttt 😭me and E spitting Facts rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevdogwhite @AdventComics @ff1221082 @thefootballgirl @Cianaf Yes. Some people dont know the game so they think he was good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can honestly say this is the best in flight beer I have ever had. - Drinking a Hop Peak IPA by @BreckBrew @ United… https://t.co/sRQgT5jkhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me:  “1989 was a great year for the @GratefulDead - crisp sounds, bigger jams, and Jerry was lucid and creative. Th… https://t.co/3mmyq88uFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think he has at least one pass and I have one catch left.  Joe Willie Namath!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nichohinojosaof Y es tanta la que nuestro México nos ofrece que a pesar de tantos gobiernos tan malos, México sigu… https://t.co/Jjcm2vwOOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LJ_GhostLife_12 @bradb38 @thekingnathan @FantasyFlurry @FlurrySports Thats not it chief 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't miss comic great Michael Blackson @michaelblackson and the Boss Rick Ross  @rickyrozay #charlotte #clt… https://t.co/AnzvNBrNov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would have been better if Capricorn didnt survive either Leonardo DiCapricorn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBALakersNation @X_DOM8 You want her streams too wow you probably seen me play carrying the team sometimes when I'm on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@opiate99 @DonaldJTrumpJr No you’re right.  He left out the part that his basis for doing so was a salacious politi… https://t.co/UZCspuZhNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's sleazier about @TuckerCarlson: -the awful things he said about women, -the fact that he's completely unrepen… https://t.co/h0OoO5BjH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to my Ravenwood boys. Take care of business at Vanderbilt today! #OpeningDay #RTTR @wcsRHSbaseball]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's crazy how the time changing by 1 hour can throw you off so much. I was 30 minutes late to work today lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well the Spurs are starting to make a run, but this one might be out of reach already. Can't start playing with onl… https://t.co/GZSm5pzEWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always be super hard at this time of day I’m trying not to touch myself lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Gronkowski87 #NEPatriots #SuperBowl53 Sounds like a                   Great plan to me Gronk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nachos were not as cheesy as I would have liked. Use only 1/4 to 2/4 a can of milk, reduce to 1/2.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lies. MFS be owing me smh @ Inglewood, California https://t.co/NAgdlSGyUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s astonishing that people care about the fallout of a celebrity relationship…don’t you guys have anything better to focus on?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah bitch, where tf this lil shits permit???? Shut that shit down. FUCK THEM KIDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just arrived in Milwaukee. New text sez venue has no heat! I gets paid but no gig. Trying to fly out on the next pl… https://t.co/zCFp5Z8ZC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonights Bolin Alley Live at 9:05 edt you will get the lowdown and the final straw in me dealing with Jim Cornette'… https://t.co/YJAKS2qBZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ochsner Health are a bunch of deceitful, crooked bastards. I hope to never have to deal with them again. This is a… https://t.co/bWq4598eCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like one of your lines senior year..... @DSchlieben @brucewittman30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drlnlopez85 @Rdc5520 How Do With Nothing But Respect For All ... https://t.co/YipNJJEWLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[As of today, I’m no longer a customer if you do not accept a #reusable mug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein God never intended for Sarah to be a bold face liar.  Rationalize that Sarah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClubSantosFem Por que de ellas no hay foto? Ni en eso se quiere invertir??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plug: man I wish we had some different gas around here   Friend in Mexico:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Co-Pastor Dr. Cheri Dearman bringing a powerful word this morning at Holy Temple Deliverance Church this morning. @… https://t.co/hbdARA7Rgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking Mom to the E.R with some supplies in case I get bored in the waiting room 💻📘✏️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler_casper They usually require no more than a short, uncomplicated answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is a lie and you know it! The Special Counsel was convened because of foreign meddling into A… https://t.co/p2xn1NlwNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @jonz970 @joe_nuzz @g1a2e3r4 @DRH1959 @frostfeet21 @tjlevi32766 @fishman092 @IvansGarage @ZigZag_1970… https://t.co/bGsAh47f1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[SmackDown LIVE preview, Feb. 19, 2019: Daniel Bryan’s WWE Fastlane opponent to be revealed https://t.co/eQOnyk2iX6… https://t.co/QLetjteOE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@candlebox last night in Grand Rapids (20 Monroe Live) on their 25th anniversary tour. #candlebox #grandrapids… https://t.co/mlfdWt2J7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫12 Études, Op. 10: No. 12 in C Minor "Revolutionary" by Maurizio Pol… https://t.co/f5Ydgoy9Gv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just recently discovered @ChannelAwesome on YouTube. Love the Man in the Glasses! https://t.co/Bficx59gzV… https://t.co/lnQhKShOnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManeatGrass @lagaviota521 @obrienmaggie17 @pppdreams @DUPONTBLUES @LuckycharmMw @helen19242686 @JenniferMlott… https://t.co/qPRHAZpVqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[La mejor inversión 🏠!!!#KWHectorDiaz #kwnext #bienesraices #Hermosillo #SONORA https://t.co/bbGZdJlAG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough loss for Bone and Williams today... 52-51 to Kentucky. Really thought they had it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Next Level Living Word Ministries "The Kingdom Church" https://t.co/1JUeqMmfrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump what kind of human and president are you if this is your do I wish u not less than the worse to your life .… https://t.co/jeV3TvTmCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keenancjpapi @WashMeDoIt @TwentyER Truly appreciate you big bro! In gods hands !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to get a job at a porn theater just so I can tell patrons as they exit, Thank You, Come Again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courage is a funny thing it is not a thing that is required when faced with doing good versus evil saving a person… https://t.co/p1vSaOfO0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought #knicks fan Spike Lee would be an a Zion jersey. https://t.co/VqMinxCl1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly in Memphis that High School Basketball was different when yo hood ass public school was ranked #1 nation L… https://t.co/1mHU0opTQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beckyspadea @JoeSpadea Have you discussed your cast iron skillet needs with the world's foremost authority on ever… https://t.co/GDGoI8ogZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nobody18038 I'm a conservative Republican. I've got my hands full explaining to my own side how they've destroyed… https://t.co/oPHjC5vxID]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never hated packing for a trip as much as I do this one. https://t.co/hWvBRifaLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlimThick2313 Exactly, but if you forget someone ...like I did they give you hell 🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find our schedule and menu on @goodfynd! 📅 Fri, Mar 8 🕚 11a - 2p 📍 Union station 🍽 https://t.co/tupvUSbn0c… https://t.co/t8Z1Ec6ljk]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite verses but do what an eagle 🦅 does when it faces a storm. I found out and this verse went to ano… https://t.co/KT7YDfrsL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say you should never say goodbye but I wish the homie coljitsu the best of luck and prayers on all your endeav… https://t.co/egCCz1n7BN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JEHutton @SEALofHonor @OVVeterans @GQCOP45 @MediaKristina @millerlawmd @dennisobaker1 @sugarbearfdn… https://t.co/BL1v4xVKJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @JoeNBC Trump's dealings with the leaders of both America's adversaries and allies is a total disaster!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only NEW information in this Cohen testimony is that he finally admits there was NO RUSSIAN COLLUSION.  The res… https://t.co/GJJrYZZwB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that the last game Zion plays in a Duke uniform? #EmbraceDebate @BarstoolBigCat @PFTCommenter]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hello guys this is @BBAARBBZZ signing back in” 😂😂 #ApexLegends @thisaintdisco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PimpinVanSmack @JeffPassan It is an independent league. Very few players move from there to the majors. You will h… https://t.co/xmruyoawXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Sofrito by Mongo Santamaria. https://t.co/6INT7ay9GJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UKTBL Kinda funny that I don’t know you and you’re butting in. Lived in the south for 6 years. Summer sucks hth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[C’est vraiment #larelache 🤮🤮🤮😂 à Knowlton, Quebec https://t.co/TzdjQ3eTpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @jdemling for Chase Taulbee write up on @247recruiting!! Go @UofLFootball !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC I’m coming to play at show to Celebrate st Patrick’s day! Come down!! #loveislove #Ireland #StPatricksDay #NYC… https://t.co/XQtqgqtXix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four new Team #Kanban Practitioners from the @Nationwide Mad Hatters line commit to managing flow and limiting WIP. https://t.co/nRKheEK4N9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 It is also for the GOP...look at Trump his kick backs and Emolument violation. Most politician of ei… https://t.co/xTljWdCdAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kieronturner95 @7dogsandadog Or at least a great deal less, enough that they are applicable outside of thy beauteous world of the Anglos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffpearlman Just finished Football for a Buck. One quote stood out. Sam Bowers "Decency isn't easily forgotten". Great read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorbidEmperor @kedward @BillSimmons Ok so you give up half your roster you're in the same spot, plus who knows how… https://t.co/HdwD9zNZL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a few photos of Adam Driver that I don't remember seeing before in Pinterest tonight, so I thought I would sh… https://t.co/VQpTXAsatU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greatest climber in the world repping IB in Free Solo. I see u @AlexHonnold]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling @ETFOPeel teachers to join us for what will become a regular commitment to keep pressure on the @fordnation… https://t.co/PpeLndr3wt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LantagneS C’est une belle madame 😉 sui à veille d’avoir autant de cheveux blancs qu’elle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colts host IceDogs tonight. Tyler Tucker comes into tonight riding a 4 game point streak. 3 goals and 5 assists in those games. #OHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/X7Q0EnYo7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕️🔬 Hi, can you or @NeilTyson or any physicist explain how @starbucks food/drinks are able to be served as hot as t… https://t.co/Nhcz14W05i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_NeeldsHD I simply asked a question...You have a youthful exuberance that will never be matched!  You’re the best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_G_1_2_ is a #SpartanLegend Love his story, endless hardwork and ability to raise to the challenge #Izzo gives hi… https://t.co/kzGdf7snUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BKarbowski @FUNimation I feel like the butt jiggle gang is secretly everyone’s favorite but no one wants to admit it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baranda61 @KenWo4LiFe @bullcity2018 @jonderickcook @whitesox Boring summer for you.]]></document></documents></author>