<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Annoyed at everybody for gate crowding and being rude to the gate agents??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tim_Embleton @TheRightMelissa @Michael2Turner @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson I think they are too and blocked them both!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @JakeMillerTech @mr_johansson is there a workaround for using @Google Drawings on an iPad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PMSchlesinger You’re the third persona with this suggestion! Guess I’ll give it a try]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hella long line for dirty bingo! Worth it! #wscruise #wscruise2019 #walkerstalkercruise #dirtybingo @ Norwegian Pea… https://t.co/BsiBUIjSix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 84 of #backgroundtobestfriend  I'm feeling way better today. I've been coming up with creative ideas and I'm re… https://t.co/VZ7SRQbjC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in adulthood...laundry, taxes and bill paying...send thin mints stat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pick up a quick bite with my scholarly06 💗💚 #IMARRIEDWELL  #LIFEOFADUCHESS @ Celestia's Coastal Cuisine https://t.co/VK7eHbkhJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[last night i had my first ever panic attack and for those who have them all the time: i’m so sorry you have to go t… https://t.co/uXoEEwf1g5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to thank those who stood on UNF’s green to make sure that no student is harassed by the anti abortion… https://t.co/C8NcSZbw47]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @jhtmusic sweettheshow 👏🏼 👏🏼👏🏼Great TV show!  . , . . . . . #sweettheshow #nicosweetofficial… https://t.co/EAWO3MgNWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a relationship dm me #singletwitter https://t.co/vTw1mvXmPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mostly dyeing my hair because blondes die first in movies and I don’t need to live with that kind of stress]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is their no limit to the treason coming out of this administration?  @GOP - this is okay with you?  House Dems Prob… https://t.co/PbmHx0MIXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[that look when the cancer doctor say you good #KeepPounding https://t.co/PjhVvhktGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[People talking about we’re losing so much football IQ. But that football IQ isn’t stopping you from getting beat in… https://t.co/2qmrzLDyYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @cleveland19news and again realizing  I miss the old crew @brianduffy19 @SamRobertsWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys really like this weather!?!  DRY LIPS!  DRY SKIN!!  FRIZZY HAIR!!!  SNAILS GETTING STEPPED ON ALL THE DAMN… https://t.co/DsaZLaoD1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Olympia Heights FL Mon Feb 18th AM Forecast: TODAY Chance Of Showers Hi 85 TONIGHT Chance Of Showers Lo 71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Like your inauguration. 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣. Hopefully you’ll be in prison by then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you bake with your family? One of the times that I feel strongest, the most in-the-flow. Macarons are HARD but e… https://t.co/BWUyTvXDP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talk about recreating something already great, this is amazing.  @StevenCurtis rickyskaggs can’t wait for full rele… https://t.co/b1I1LKFqy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@truckerfling @yoshioterada @chomado @kellyshalk @MegMallin @rallat @KingCaven @wyamazak @kazup_bot @tuttiq So much… https://t.co/R6qJXjXqhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimbrown1964 @CaroleGilman @PubliusNV @babylon_cat @siftyboones @Victoriaokane @sparkey909w @MTWTwoPoint0… https://t.co/WXi2PnDPJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter for a chance to win a free #eyelinertattoo   How to enter:  1. Follow @jenniferbassi on Instagram. 2. Like th… https://t.co/zBD236b3l6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epidemiology  👀🤔👀🤔👀 📚 #LA #museum #lacma #books #artsy @ LACMA Los Angeles County Museum of Art https://t.co/yqUN9V6Qbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanJones68 Have to give credit where credit is due. Kudos for your remarks at cpac.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much have you taken from El Chapo @SpeakerPelosi ?  We are going to find out. I just thought I would give you t… https://t.co/CQ4mMVl1pG]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Mental health signs is real, I am a therapist who sees a therapist. Who checks your mental health? #noshame… https://t.co/qGGyxYrupf]]></document><document><![CDATA['Green Book' Subject Don Shirley's Heir Speaks Out for First Time https://t.co/lSHV378pha via @thr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mucha risa viendo el video de ayuwoki en la tarde, ah pero ahorita con todas las luces prendidas. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelcburgess NOT NECESSARILY. IF YOU ARE PAYING TAXES BECAUSE YOU SNUCK IN ILLEGALLY AND GOT A JOB THAT SHOULD… https://t.co/AaeEb4rlGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @DrLeanaWen, @PPFA, @NARAL and ALL advocates for women’s reproductive rights. Abolishing or restricting a… https://t.co/fNFr4F9Njm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Did you fly on an airplane instead of riding your bicycle? Hypocrite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SageNatural do you have an email address I can contact you at? If so, message me! Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chortletown I RT and shared in hopes this poor pup gets ADOPTED/RESCUED/Real soon please people she only has one m… https://t.co/NucvpqzkSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindaholmes @RonBrownstein Via a family friend I got autographed photo that read: “Dear Dawn, I’m glad you like th… https://t.co/OGCSNXI1m7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well if there is another strike I am done as a fan of this league. The owners are always crying poor but the ink av… https://t.co/CPMepM8tbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristianafarias @KatCapps For me this is the scariest fallout from Prez Cray Cray winning; a Putin judiciary who i… https://t.co/ixbHIWXsOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza God bless you, and stay strong! The haters are ignorant and perverse pond scum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I found an artifact (orientation sign-in sheet) from when the @UofLSugarMamas met for the first time! 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyhersheyy @_kasumiii bebigerl are you aware that this is how you make kwento??? 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Self portraits with my new backdrop. It also took me about 100 shots to get a few decent ones LOL. https://t.co/Q7vv0xW5ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[First girls party 🎉 #hello #girlpower #bffs #oldfriends #newborn #baby #aunties #bubbles #sundayfunday @ Michigan https://t.co/hrKOPUmhQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The irony how I allowed you to think it’s just me but yet my conscious is clear on you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great way for an all time #TUWBB to end her home career thank you @_imliyah #TEMPLEtuff #TempleMade]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @DCCC please come up with a line to describe #Trump and stick to it. Repeat it 100 times daily. He needs to be… https://t.co/lM4YwmpeoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewportBeachPD @nojoak Here's a good story for you.. Scary part is she lived 8 blocks fr/ me in CdM.  I was 5 at t… https://t.co/pbCVSUcFoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@propjoesays When you say Howdy without an exclamation mark then you sound like someone died.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Disaster For Trump As 64% Of Voters Say He Committed Crimes  https://t.co/xYfqWgsdkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Yeah.  Doncha really mean THE BLACKMAIL ATTEMPT? Because I keep watching a video of David Letterman co… https://t.co/30XXHpSHdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein Every 11 minutes someone in the USA dies from Fentanyl Drug overdose.  And the Democrats don’t see an… https://t.co/DODqVWjjyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoingRight1 @Aug1405 @galacticaactual @familyfirstcorp @OHIW14 @JulieReichwein1 @QmagaMike @PaulieD55 @Patti_Sc60… https://t.co/AWEFEK2U3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[HUD Will Steer New York's Vast Public Housing Agency https://t.co/JkUWRRFvpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first thing that the keynote speaker of Human Trafficking Awareness Day did (Erik L. Bauer) during his speech w… https://t.co/eZKCtc5AWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what lunch looks like in the last semester of your PhD ... Heading to a neighbour city campus in a snow sto… https://t.co/xgapO5Ncz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun day with a few of my favorites! ❤️#Family #Brother #Niece #Nephew #CFA @ Chick-fil-A Lavonia https://t.co/0kIYszoZQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can thank white people for that. A parent of color who refuses to vaccinate their kids would be arrested and ja… https://t.co/wIgfUDTy4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @joneill55 @Cbp8Cindy @jflorez @SideHustleWino @SashaEats @DivaVinophile @GailBenzler… https://t.co/KlRn6lEAYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@showupforthis Mine would be Sigourney Weaver! We wouldnt just survive... we'd own it!  💯 #RipleyInMyCorner https://t.co/pi69vyevEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo mejor de las adversidades es la oportunidad que tienes de reinventarte!!!  #CristinaCastillo #frases… https://t.co/za3Y22OnHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing up I had four brothers, I’m down to too. I’ve had to cut off aunts uncles, my mom, my dad, grandparents. Bu… https://t.co/AsJfEiwq9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annvandersteel @Chrismc44 can you interview him.  His story sounds fascinating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find someone who loves you...  the way county schools love 2-hr delays.   Happy Valentines Day ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting complemented from a girl means so much more than being complemented from a boy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to say, I hardly did anything this weekend &amp; it was BEYOND FRIED. 🙃🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4’s love goes to Everyday Beaut, Dé-al Salon, Liquid Sun Spray, Lather Nashville, Nails by Pat Myers, Kimberly… https://t.co/8rFG3eVITH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett MAGA excorting out a youth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s (nice, but still) #catcall: “I hope you have a good day at work! I love your colors!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[These niggas literally talk so much shit and their girlfriends have the nerve to look worse than what they’re talki… https://t.co/RcrzieAPbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me what you have done in this situation if you were my friend here]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little Tech Diva and I are having so much fun at the #WonderPark world premiere party! #SheCanSTEM… https://t.co/KZ8h9mnJUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skyline_owlette Hello, If you need assistance with finding a rental or purchasing a home in Southern Maryland, let… https://t.co/FM5rpN3aZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[People always tell me I came up in their conversation and I’m always too afraid to ask what it was every time 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jgoss1971 @clintshane @mrs_hippiequeen @TexasChance I never knew you were such the problem solver. Two birds, one stone, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kebsten None of us have any idea what we’re doing. Some just are better at faking it (I would not be one of those… https://t.co/CVyk9sAngA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jen_l_espinoza I absolutely love this! Great idea to post. You are a fun grandma!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most beautiful things you can say to someone beyond I love you is...thank you for being in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting mad about all the obstacles preventing me from making coffee is the most on point dream I have ever had.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@letgolifeflows @LagranShane @gerrinnesmac @ChristiWalling @BabyGo2014 @jill_magnussen @DansoyGomez @kalimullah2… https://t.co/kE4u1owDNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I felt Colton’s pain through that entire moment. I can honestly say I’ve never related more... 😕 #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher This pathetic man just keeps over https://t.co/kTNfPQRNpi would think repubs in Congress would stop him.COWARDS!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juiceboxjulez My foam roller is my best friend tbh lol, but some days the aches are deeper than that :/ I had spin… https://t.co/kh8cbpa65I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish my dogs had a sense of time, so when I come home at 3am they don’t greet me like raging bulls 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[#movingforward #life #motivation #selflove #quotes #inspiration #happiness #loveyourself #positivevibes #goals… https://t.co/jpMwhfYP8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeForeman I’m so sorry for your loss.  wishing you &amp; your family peace and comfort. Sending an abundance of good wishes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right at the beginning, the main character is asked, "When was the last time you went outside that wasn't for work?… https://t.co/HsECzkPqmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[There has never been a more influential album in my life than Harmony by Never Shout Never ....try to change my mind 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrStevenCree I wood never think of using any sort of 🏴󠁧󠁢󠁳󠁣󠁴󠁿slang around U!! Because I have NO idea of what any co… https://t.co/dik8pGGK80]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahilkapur @JoeNBC Nice job toddler in chief. It just keeps getting worse by the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsabellPalushaj @maddiernst @TheChloeth REMEBER WE WOULD SKYPE AND WATCH! And the train would go by so loudly]]></document><document><![CDATA[you're going to giggle. funniest pictures 2012 #laughter #laugh #smile #amusing https://t.co/HreZTRcDpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The important story here isn’t that a rich old man bought sex, it’s that the “trafficking” victims here will likely… https://t.co/kI7lrp4dU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomItForward A5 I make most of my recipes with avocado not in guac form or eat them plain honestly. So Guac is not… https://t.co/XN8AJtf7Y3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me leaving work in 5 minutes to go get some margs https://t.co/ca3yH1xES1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamDamoff @TwitterCanada @PamDamoff I’m so sorry you have to deal with this. This is disgusting.  How is this even allowed? @TwitterCanada]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had a date planned for this weekend but it has come to my attention that my date plays in a band unironically cal… https://t.co/fQTkKdXgT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Give Too Many Females The Benefit Of The Doubt Of Actually Being Smart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleCooperMD @JimGMelton @westleyohman @blakepparsons Likewise. Great case and stellar job! https://t.co/gUSjfhv0y1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so sad and could have been avoided but this is the living reality of what happens without vaccination]]></document></documents></author>