<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ComedyRealz They offered a third-round pick last year. #Eagles sent a fifth to #Seahawks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grand stand in the sand Ilhan Omar’s Attempt to Shame  Politico  Reporter Over Obama Quotes Backfires. Bigly. https://t.co/dwD7aFKDQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachClarkTF I’m not dissing high volume sets but you got a train at 70-85% for your heavy work. Can’t be done with 12-15 rep pump sets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeWCTheFirst @SDHatGuy I think #Padres twitter needs a new place to post articles. There are many talent and passionate writes man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duped again. Went to bed expecting 6-12” of snow. Wake up and we’re back to 3”. #Mawx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out with Doug, Mike, Wayne while they are signing autographs here at @Mac_Tools job fair https://t.co/4BJUAO1uZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar @seanhannity @RepCummings Didn’t Rudy tell Hannity during an interview months back that trump repaid Cohen… https://t.co/LBP3k0P6E5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mekiell_kay @McDonalds @BurgerKing it has its moments where it can be tasty but unsatisfying ya dig?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Hipismo #Championshipmeet #7JustWhistle con gran atropellada liquida la 7ma de #GulfstreamPark , yunta… https://t.co/MbJUeeDZlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Mardi Gras! Zydefunk’s annual King Cake Party Friday night northsidetavern! @ Northside Tavern https://t.co/UEgg0KSRxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yoyorx3_ Yea didn’t taste good as well. It’s like the mashed up tomatoe paste and hot sauce for the salsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also here is rascal @SimonSaysMoo and @karnasoar he makes a fart sound lmao https://t.co/1rwgcQ4J58]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sscheer5 @icd_nyc Thank you for drawing attention to this! Your talk was so well composed, delivered, and received… https://t.co/PIKMzp1Nug]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought my merch from the saxomophone player and didn’t even know it! He was amazing. riversofnihil #riversofnihil… https://t.co/Pp9aZm6TJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read what Wussie Smalls said about Americans reluctance to believe his story because the alleged perpetrators being… https://t.co/6yzXJ58Lcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Kings Go! #lakings #nhl  WE CAUGHT A PUCK!!!! southbay_mexican_dude @icanla @ Staples Center https://t.co/9Ro0dVjzyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for @MariahCarey - #WITHYOU on Radio 103.9 ! Vote at https://t.co/xnIJ73sZco false]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RightWingWatch This is disturbing.  From the clown on the stage to the enablers in the wings and the applauding ra… https://t.co/T1rFeLLslH]]></document><document><![CDATA[VISITA MIS DOS CANALES: 👇🏻 • YouTube🔥 Channel: https://t.co/HF2s2OgRct • YouTube 💥Canal: https://t.co/oWfjqWNSm5 •… https://t.co/BMdCHZhT4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every app on my phone dry. If I don’t get a text, DM, mention, or FT call by time I wake up, I’m sliding on niggas blocks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDiscipulus @M_feeney Sounds more like FBI was discussing the possibility of 25th amend. being used and preparin… https://t.co/pLyCtBzJ72]]></document><document><![CDATA[Theirs alot of people chatting about some smoke in the City.  Damn I hope this shit isn't true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaceMullen Sort of like “textbook” symptoms being found only in a textbook...]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is arguing that if a baby is born alive—outside of the womb—the mother should be able to tell the doctor to let… https://t.co/Vkye8zHvol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to thank my longtime friend/business associate for taking the time out of his busy schedule to come ha… https://t.co/y1pQayZUCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: A big step was just taken to make Trump — and any future nominee — disclose his tax returns: To th… https://t.co/nn8BcuL1vT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Exhale Atlanta - @exhalespa in Atlanta, GA https://t.co/xB1kbVhsFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr happy president’s day!! https://t.co/bMgtWcIJU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The future isn’t people sitting at desks and at traditional offices. The foldable phone concept, if executed correc… https://t.co/KZeXzpUraq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Separate women seatings side during church service, Brooklyn 2017 @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/fvEplqyVzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @netflix time to get w/ @KingJames to develop a comedy special about “playoff mode activated” 🤣🤣🤣#Lakers… https://t.co/FVuDO0DRqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salmos 18:1-2  Nova Versão Internacional    Salmo 18  Para o mestre de música. De Davi, servo do Senhor. Ele cantou… https://t.co/m0WpHMApUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit, this looks really, really fucking good!! Graphics look absolutely amazing, love where the story is going… https://t.co/OIMP4LEfUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PennLive I'm confused, is this for all public higher ed in pa? Just passhe? Just non preferreds?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WRBolen I’ll just leave this here for you to do with what you’d like   https://t.co/Htj2tvGnBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbym886 @NavalInstitute @USNIBooks I do think there was a miscue in not saying boat in reference to us sub. And… https://t.co/OwlfefUH8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: I still don’t have a valentine so if anyone wants to change that hit a girl up. Totally up to you tho, no pres… https://t.co/OgFJov2Xtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the coach really said that to the Nevada players he should lose his job. There’s no place for that in College hoops.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya lo gana  @LaSelecta_SLV al min 2' #OscarCerén marca el 1-0 #Guatemala]]></document><document><![CDATA[That cardinals staff could be so so scary if mikalas continues to be great (i don’t think he will) and Alex Reyes c… https://t.co/vhnZklnblB]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much food.....great eats @ Harmony of the Seas https://t.co/LaA5xkJkyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Humans can survive climate change. God gives us the ability to adapt and survive. Government control… https://t.co/diEY25zzLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Take the money for the wall out of the Senate and Congress Pension funds!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recap of Class D: Simants, White punch tickets to title match  Read story here: https://t.co/3OL9Av8ATf  #NebPreps… https://t.co/bstQ4WEW2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonkneen @Liz_Wheeler The most loving, honest people I've ever met, that's what to expect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see me at the @houseofcomedyaz tomorrow - Sunday as I host for London Brown @reallondonbrown get tix at… https://t.co/awgv4E5J7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyCalidonia keep up the magic posts. Here’s tae us, wha’s like us? Damn few, and they’re a deid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyClarkson @JWJBowden @thegrandtour As a Brit on the US. I look forward to visiting any other country to get d… https://t.co/3HbR1Gb1V1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrMojays That wasnt your point so calling it a negligent action is wreckless. Just say what you wanted to say whic… https://t.co/p3rXACDRuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImWithHer33 @onnlucky @TheAtheistPig First don't gaslight us with "fair and just to their servants" lies.  Hebrew… https://t.co/2mDX7saywe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camreddish has turned it up 10 levels since acc games started. Dude is a special talent. Cam fam cam fam. Cant sto… https://t.co/fcz8JoDZ4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buffett showes imyself to more irrelevant every time he or Munger open their mouths https://t.co/nSTiU2FC4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthonRaptor @brjma @wehauler @DieterFrikadell @VaughnBeethoven @SteveSGoddard @rln_nelson @PAlterBoy1… https://t.co/gkqeGk33IJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CabanForQueens will end Sunday Scaries for good https://t.co/31jnERiibr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikRGamborg @BigE_71 @NFL @RamsNFL @UniWatch @PhilHecken @HelmetAddict @kengfunk @addicted2helmet Ok.. so I just… https://t.co/uE1tv6S4mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I justed wanted to say how proud I am of LHS in embracing the #gobeyondlampasas activity. It is awesome to see the… https://t.co/iVTg77Z7kH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully Ladd can provide a spark when he gets back into the lineup tomorrow night on Barzal’s wing]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When you believe in a thing, believe in it all the way, implicitly and unquestionable.” -Walt Disney #disneyworld… https://t.co/Ts2SiKUliO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ltsSaulGoodman Actress who plays Kim Wexler is a great actress! I’m going to make sure I know who she is and what… https://t.co/rm2Qq2gy0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fred02961487 @GarySharp1620 I'm aware of that, but I took it that you meant NU wouldn't have an NCAA level hockey team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @andrew52220582 Get'er done Trump MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laneflorsheim This article tarnishes your newspaper and makes me ashamed to be a subscriber. Publishing uncritical… https://t.co/DJ1IFWc4dh]]></document><document><![CDATA[just ordered $300 worth of tacos to be delivered to the bar I’m at and expensed it; how’s your evening going?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson That won’t happen! He stood at CPAC and called out anyone in Congress who’s an immigrant ffs! What d… https://t.co/owmXTcei2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to THEE Boracho Bill himself!! Hope you had a great day 💪 https://t.co/SJApmZI72R]]></document><document><![CDATA[New spokeswoman for Bernie Sanders won't be able to vote for him in 2020 -- she's an illegal immigrant https://t.co/WBJuxDh5ir #FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephrey4 @batman23476 @BeckyLynchWWE @Ericeezz @mrozz1978 @badlands66 @slicked9778 @ToyaSkip @mal056 @thelocabat… https://t.co/yaDV7HUJVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinceSamperio It’s only going to get worse. So many kids are playing way too much baseball. They are not resting e… https://t.co/hog0EIeiqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caring Into The Void season two starts today. @hottestsingles and I kick off the new run with special guest author… https://t.co/NUmyn8Qkcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt The homie stevenhuie_flyrite sent this to me the other day.   Bringing it back #NYHC my first bass I ever owne… https://t.co/mEx0io2flY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Stickee Monkee (2016) by @FirestoneWalker @ The Common Table — https://t.co/rWJRnF9S4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayy5ive Competition is sad young dude. We started that fasho. Coach wise Coach Wright started that too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cachepdc Pues veías tu novela y está bien, ambas están bien, le dieron visibilidad a la homosexualidad, y otros co… https://t.co/Trzd9uly1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrote in my dad for 2016. Kavanaugh hearings made me team Trump 2020 purely out of spite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días... Juan  4:14 Mas el que bebiere del agua que yo le daré, para siempre no tendrá sed: mas el agua que y… https://t.co/nUC61lYVs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afireinside35 @yummybacon77 @SurfinjJoel Dude..... Imagine if we get both disgruntled Steelers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your welcome teachs and principal the truth sucks at least you can still be a payed hero to people who struggle lik… https://t.co/gsMQmM7ra4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanikaBrass Good morning Danika and happy Tuesday from my alternative music station 😘😘💖💖💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Change @SenBooker @SenKamalaHarris @SenatorTimScott How cannot it already be?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You may have to shake the machine a little for that first option. https://t.co/JYRNXohBjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP to Luke Perry! He did a great job in 8 seconds as basically Lane Frost’s look a like. He died today at the young age of 52.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@littlekaylie69 @TheHardDepot @WomenOfMFC @bouncytits1 @LuciferPromo @evilbros34 @Redhat_Babes @CMP_4U @PornAtHome… https://t.co/Eko6VAqgBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proudly displaying the latest @BrockBadgers National Championship banners #wrestling #dynasty https://t.co/CHAYPVqK05]]></document><document><![CDATA[But seriously @brielarson amazing job on #CaptainMavel love love love!! Everyone go see it💛 ps. I work at the theat… https://t.co/G7zrt5lYoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kwips3 It’s the same result as when we had Kevin love quips big numbers no wins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ephoustonbill @DENTONCBC @badhopper @JonMontag @JohanBBT @zappafaye @OkiTimes @Paul_TheBeerGuy @wolv54b1… https://t.co/qvS5zdylFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate this addiction with social media, the need to stimulate my mind is getting weak at this point]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can't Americans #sue the makers of #vaccines?  Why is #Congress protecting #BigPharma?  And from what?  🤔  https://t.co/gEbegreHHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MylesLGarrett The same weight,as if the sand was the sky ,and the sky was the sand. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@W OK Joe. now it's time to explain to me what president never lied grab a set of balls and sit there and tell me which president never lied]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Longshoe heard you in the radio twice from the conversation with @DukesandBell929; thank you for simplifying every… https://t.co/kdxyjttxBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gracebettenga You should be glad I didn’t text you and try to help you https://t.co/1uwo33XyLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCITLFrAphorism Knowing who she is and what she is about, why isn’t she #excommunicated from any #Catholic #Church… https://t.co/rmuIqa3TPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jelynchjr please discuss with bob bob why the sixers would have interest in Andrew Bogut?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andresleonar @HassNassar @ghitis 3. Si se hubieran acabado realmente Las Farc, nadie estaría objetando el acuerdo.… https://t.co/fwBRkEo4QL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ravi Tekchandani started the Austin Half Marathon! https://t.co/90xvFvLxZS #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTimMcGraw I love you music and your a great person in general I have a go fund me page for my husband that is a… https://t.co/ghdpCxjejs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mundaneken I’m fine with deciding - but I feel as if I didn’t have a choice. That’s what irks me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @vpotus The FBI and DOJ were and are still today in a Conspiratorial way trying to… https://t.co/YO4Dnm1wAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenaine77 @Cakedaddy4ever @bhueypdx @chrislongview @chrisdameanor19 @nkem @pleasetryharder @MrDane1982 Oh? https://t.co/HBuRmZNSHN]]></document></documents></author>