<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Stop fucking trying to get me to be a fan of the league @mls. I don’t give a fuck about any league, only teams]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGameMKE @BobBrainerd @ArmenSaryan @DrewOlsonMKE @OnAirKB @DrewandKB https://t.co/KD9IVlOHIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LumpyLouish @ArmedfceSndwich @BuniculaTv @AnnieLinskey @washingtonpost How about #WaPooZon]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MustWatch: @rcbregman’s epic takedown of @TuckerCarlson. As usual, Tuck can’t handle people that call him out and… https://t.co/k9RcnLqQEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman Alas, you’re not also a racist taking millions from the networks to go away... @megynkelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s Your Favorite Color? 😉 #melanin @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/lsj1VlHizz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LandisImages @dallasnews @dallasnewsphoto @marciaallert Congrats!! You rock]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuffaloBlueBear @DanteFlorence Seems dodgy. Here’s the link. https://t.co/28KvOFtgmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former top FBI lawyer: 2 Trump Cabinet officials were ‘ready to support’ 25th Amendment effort https://t.co/59sfNQRWMQ #FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GardnerKatyg8 @FarmChicJodi @IHboog @AtlantaAgCurt @HedrickJessica @hkerkhofs @HaesenAnita @scoopermomma… https://t.co/z39t0t1TDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to start working out, which means Siri suggesting a lower move goal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long been a Chitale bandhu supporter but there's no question Gujju bakarwadi &gt;&gt;&gt; Marathi bakarwadi  Not even close]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UMassHockey vs @UConnMHOC 7:05 faceoff on @WHMP &amp; the @UMassSportsNet. https://t.co/G1vRC0NSil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodikyman @GOP @realDonaldTrump It's a witch hunt!  They should all climb on their brooms and ride off to the setting moon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Hindman #KnottCounty #KY #Appalachia #photos #authors @ Appalachian Artisan Center https://t.co/TMuC76lwEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DolarToday perfecto y solo iran a miraflores para ver el castillo de la Cenicienta ya verán]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so sick of all of these #SpamBot people and lonely single ladies trying to follow me on here and also on… https://t.co/MQ0FzUXj0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow both Jerry Palm of CBS and Joe Lunardi of ESPN have Bama STILL in their latest bracketology. How?? I really… https://t.co/L4OplTyCpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @BretBaier What a treat! Such a decisive woman in charge of her party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheoVon how are you feeling after your @firstwefeast interview?  #GangGang]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creo que si no la solicita la AN y el como presidente de esta y Presidente encargado. Pusiera considérese una invas… https://t.co/e5ktutdtwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenAmell I have never been more dedicated to one show or one actor in my life. I knew Arrow would have to end… https://t.co/NOmmwKcLAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mediaite He joins the Trump crowd for lying to authorities and creating “fake news”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i used to hate the jonas brothers bc my sister was obsessed w them and i wanted to be that annoying little brother… https://t.co/xS88LG8TB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made some doodles of @SWMRS songs bc I’m bored as hell. They’re shitty but I definitely want to get some tatted one… https://t.co/EIKKWmRqBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amazon is taking over the world. I can’t think of another company that can execute on such a high level. Our dream… https://t.co/SQHhr5obES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan I bet so,the never Trumpers !!!! Some politicians just can’t get over the fact that he’s not establishment Republican!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dude really got up in front of the class for an anti-abortion and said fully grown adults are the same as unborn fetuses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vigocarpathian @_waleedshahid @hmcghee @sunrisemvmt @AOC @SenMarkey No one is talking about getting rid of her: wh… https://t.co/StM17ajXfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comcast set mobile pins to “0000,” helping attackers steal phone numbers https://t.co/WIah4zzRHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasCRicketts are you suggesting he be named personally as a defendant  ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @MariaBartiromo @SundayFutures @FoxNews Can you talk to them about taking care of our first respon… https://t.co/eppNxeDOrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Among the very cool speakers showcased by #LAIEvents today: Superman (It’s Not Easy) singer Five for Fighting John… https://t.co/t3Wk6aEyxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patscap with only 18.1 mil in cap space can they sign Brown and Flowers deserving contracts and field a team]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's two types of artists. There's the trial and error guy. And then there's the guy who meets other artists to… https://t.co/YrOnF8DC2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shellylynnefl09 @ewarren like your hero were too good to go; when his college deferments ran out, he suddenly deve… https://t.co/mCZwv6ARd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IncredibleCulk You have to wonder what madman thought up a pickle. Or the nightmare workshop that created bologna.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Essa história do @zehdeabreu é engraçada no meio dessa maluquice toda. O problema é que o maluco presidente atual c… https://t.co/gE2NFygP0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only difference between now and then is that they get more time more opportunities because unlike then… https://t.co/a1T19Besy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waOZschoonover @plumplumcurse @Simon_Berman Door building is on that table!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueSea1964 @KatTheHammer1 All liberal presidential candidates demand moral -&gt; oxymoron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of laughter in the studio today. Recorded something special feat. yours truly this afternoon. #DatingAdvice… https://t.co/xnqWYG9VwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Somecallmejon Chaos Cordial Angel Island Iced Tea Fuzzy Knuckle Sazerobotnik Miles “CockTails” Prower Gin and Sonic Pink Hedgehog]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for creating this illustration piece of my wife and I Emma Callender for #BlackHistoryMonth .… https://t.co/sKBltRPqd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this weather. @ Sally's Fish House &amp; Bar https://t.co/KRF5RyDozm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chengesbaugh1 @RamblersTFXC WASTED. @FloTrack #MVC https://t.co/HcjLMpqI07]]></document><document><![CDATA[way back in the bygone era of 2002, @IGN thought this was a good analogy to put in their tony hawk 4 review… https://t.co/aaFXRRxhAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFBHome So amazing and the odds. Worth a retweet even though im a Sooner and i remember how sick and stunned I was.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guardian @maggieNYT That would be rich. Get him on the Pats before they go to the WH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm...are we talking the #ThornBirds? Look em up...lol They might #Sing you a #Song...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect Neighbor Award🥇 goes to Larry of Norwood on Walnut Street. He cleared his neighbors driveways of snow and o… https://t.co/XtB2i4184I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy Lunes regresan Las Señoritas Treviño.  Cómo las querían ver Muertas.... pero de risa!!! Teatro Versalles 8.30 D… https://t.co/oe3h9KWUB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh I’m so in love with the peeps @RespectClub One Love. Happy Valentine’s Day fam!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[THEY CANT BE HUMAN WHICH MAKES THEEM LOW CLASS WITH JUST MONEY HO WILL BE HOES NOW IF ONE DOES TALK THE TIME A REAL PRINCESS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @POTUS Wherein the president acts like he hates socialism but is BFF’s with worst socialists of our tim… https://t.co/TKkVjaWDni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lordcumslut @_melvel_ @tameimpala Only like a small hand full of pepple got them the rest went to coachella ticket… https://t.co/nyTXCvuTeP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom @DavidAFrench @Knocksious @J4Years @xan_desanctis @MollyJongFast @EricaGrieder @SohrabAhmari… https://t.co/CQFtlKVHXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bikeski2Jeff @TheOfficerTatum I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quinc… https://t.co/XFNn3pRGM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great deal on an amazing game. (I wrote a small chapter in it, echoing James’s stunning work.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Auburn losing to Kentucky felt like the football loss to LSU. This loss tonight against Ole Miss feels like the los… https://t.co/rY5Q4R6qMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly think with all three expansions that StarCraft 2 is one of the best games out there]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will play this every day for the rest of my life. https://t.co/3yPG1Uoexo]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Parent Leadership Month! We love our ES PTA president, Amanda Wells! #livefromtheschoolboard https://t.co/AKz1lkXjKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:23.2°F WchillLow:15.2°F Wind:2 mph Dir:NNW Baro:Rising slowly Rain2day:0.00in Hum:73% UV:0.0 @ 10:00 02/26/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely loved covering #NBAAllStar events the past two days — another dream come true. Sometimes, hard to believ… https://t.co/QJte21Os5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TedNesi Millea u r chicken shit weak matty hack.   Maybe u will grow a pair a vote no on all of lyin Gina’s tax in… https://t.co/Eoguxyc99Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Friday everyone habe a blessed one, already thinking of what to do after work. Why am i like this smh lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come Party With Me At Perignons For $5 Karaoke... Let's Have Some Fun, Because It Will Be Going Down... @ Perignons… https://t.co/8h0Qq6EPNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good night guys! It’s Monday! New week filled with blessings and opportunities!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sawicki_kyle would love for you to post them in the discord! https://t.co/ytxoGAEtXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#501C3 are we trusting in God or are we trusting in #governments? The reason why the #pulpits of America are so… https://t.co/cHCKR4iYiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hulu_support 😎😎😎I Know You &amp; @netflix  Can. https://t.co/euG6YU4An1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you all remember when @paramore put out that straight banger that was “Monster,” which also served as song punch… https://t.co/NeIlIlc4rx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lakeshowsoaring @ChuckShots I would definitely say mediocre. It’s the worst Lebron team since maybe his first Clev… https://t.co/8sdwQdLGJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you seen it on the new billboard sign from I-5? It’s electronic so you can catch them  day or night. 🛣👁‍🗨📣🤩… https://t.co/t3pfmLtkx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyFarnell dude what’s up with the alerts? I’m in Sarnia and it’s a light wind even lighter snow. It’s winter… https://t.co/RsG9p3CLI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr I hope to watch @realDonaldTrump veto that horrible spending bill that will be put on his desk this morning!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom It’s really bad when there’s a laundry list. But that’s how he rolls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yankeeslibero7 @angelsteve89 Only way things change is if Tulo doesn’t break camp with the team.. other option is… https://t.co/kkBz4v6Naj]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk how these 35+ year old rappers deal with having a 14-17 year old audience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great project launch today with the City of Lake Forest- working on the Welcome Home campaign to create social co… https://t.co/NrAG1xQOO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to hear @ryansatin and @TheRochaSays talk about how The Usos are one of the most interesting promos in the g… https://t.co/ieDBJsLaqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m starting to like the person I’m becoming! @coquettekouture @ Inglewood, California https://t.co/171nbKLomT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pottsgrove trying to stay in this. 63-48 Sun Valley with 2:50 left. Was once a 28-point game this quarter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanPanicNow Prosecutor here. I actually enjoy our small defense bar. The defense attys I enjoy the most are pragma… https://t.co/fYMDua3Hg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[No scoring yet in 4th Q, East Side 33, Hunterdon Central 27 w 5:57 left in North 2, Group 4 semi. #NJhoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best last day of a Birthday weekend! Chelsea and I had a BLAST! Amazing show and superb acting! #hamilton #chicago… https://t.co/Mo8rHwcHDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[From “It’s not a mullet. It’s a mudflap!” shirt to the victory worm, I have no idea what my favorite part of this v… https://t.co/56qO0PeuxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to get food forgot my wallet dude gave it to me got free... shows when you do good to others goof comes to you...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SummerCampFest Seeing the elephants crawl out of the lights at Primus and Pretty lights a few years back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to March in Williamsburg... #snow #williamsburg @ Domino Park https://t.co/KBPKSMZCob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben, Brown, and Le'Veon have all had issues. The difference with Ben is he hasn't let it affect his play or miss ga… https://t.co/E7bmaqlUq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill tRump isn’t most people. He’s a pathological liar, cheat and harbors the belief that he is above the law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Standards___ Hahaha okay I’ll let you know when we’re done we’re in studio city grabbing dessert. Where y’all at?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bags2285 @phillypaws @dodo @BJWTC Thank you so much - happy #ValentinesDay to you!  🐶😺💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alwaysaliberal @GeorgePaschall @MattersTyme @PoliticalShort @DonaldJTrumpJr Comedy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGiant @ThePattyB @PamKeithFL Speaker of house = not the same thing as finger on the button flying all over the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump implies that Democrats are trying to bring socialism to our country.  Question. Is Trump trying to bring fasc… https://t.co/ptd7ohPzoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate @StaceyRoedel @m2geek I'm too old to get riled up....I'll wait for a bit!  BUT...Bernie was then...N… https://t.co/MxWR4on5hj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Reggie for everything you’ve done for the company for a really long time, his replacement isn’t even that… https://t.co/oIUgfbkCGb]]></document></documents></author>