<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday GOAT! Love you fam... @WWEBigE #newdayrocks https://t.co/l4RJhgnBx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Can't believe you said that.  Trump is a destroyer, and he was responsible for GM closing.  He lied t… https://t.co/aZLpW1qXQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another thing I am enjoying at SXSW.  Discovering all of the new hotels that opened while I was gone.… https://t.co/Wb8DywdmqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nephew introduces his baby brother as “this is baby Luke, he just moved in” and I can’t deal with the cuteness 😂😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got up &amp; I’m already thinking about the nap I’m taking after work  🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezi this is so beautiful. I love your version of take my breath away https://t.co/ZEh5Uncxyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first one I want to talk to every morning. Start mornings right. https://t.co/roMP4hRgwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Week: Only one game but it’s a biggie on the road in FLA! #RiseWithUs https://t.co/oAcjmpcW8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my favorite website on earth lol #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/1w4QxCHb93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Keep human trafficking within your own administration. https://t.co/nWEo3chjJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear friends who have/will all be messaging me about buying tickets from them for @CJPAC Toronto #ACTION19... I alr… https://t.co/ttXiaKAa3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coco, an American Pit Bull Terrier in DC, needs a home now! See her on https://t.co/JVtEQUPiwS https://t.co/OvwlvRsOA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world is dazzling, I alone am dull. Others strive for achievement, I follow a lonely path. #TAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[February Bunco was soooooo fun! I love these girls and every month we’re together it’s a blast. Lots of wine, snack… https://t.co/Y3ZJkoPZeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley @NGAofSC @SCNationalGuard Thank you for your service.  Thank you Niki Haley for all you have done]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: okay I’ll take another shot at 11:15  Gabby: noooooo 11 https://t.co/eQnGefSpry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGilby12 @PamKeithFL @Iamdevinnsmart Now watch  this https://t.co/CU6vwVd0oH   We are all slaves, Trump is trying,… https://t.co/esQJaQpleL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super dope ladies doing the damn thangggggg! Yaaassss! @ellamai https://t.co/aquUDb2tLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are some things or experiences that you enjoy that bring you true happiness, joy and love? #TranquilTuesday… https://t.co/Nfj8uNMEeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy @UtahDWR mentioned the waterfalls at #gunlockstatepark Beautiful! With @tbbehunin https://t.co/yCvzoxmnvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #son is with me ... like true #lovers 💕 last week i was taking care of him in the #hospital  now he’s taking car… https://t.co/tsIufTv110]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday.  Lulu would like to remind you it is 5 o'clock somewhere. #blackcat #irish #friday @ Minneapolis, Min… https://t.co/Qb58UtBEvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alleged U.S. Air Force defector walked into Iranian spy recruiting ground. https://t.co/WjkvJ0mHmo https://t.co/cdF1FCUHx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikaelahelane The 2 men in video are black actors and friends of Jussie. Hmmm....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sungypsy_ @m_madilyn @starrynarelly @sydneyyy_x @alyssajeter47 @ohbabyc @dee_hoops_ @mollydrew_ LMAO DES we are al… https://t.co/nuajbTtbdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeonardiNeil @RealJamesWoods @1classact1979 Exactly .she loves socialism so much. let her go down there and live]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dhegley this is really good - I’m sharing with @ClevelandArt executive team -]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllaraTravel1 @softlikewater @TomSteyer @Jim_Jordan I see your sway and raise you it still makes absolutely no sen… https://t.co/2lixclJ7gE]]></document><document><![CDATA[No appt neccessary! Walk Ins are welcome with our #MUA  Makeup Lashes Brows by brows_by_keisha  Tues/Thurs-Sat 1-7p… https://t.co/MVzBHCAnu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I struggled my whole life with my gender identity to the point where I was extremely depressed and felt out of plac… https://t.co/9e43DWN47t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump @PressSec If it is a national emergency why has it taken you so long to declare it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WATCHJUNEEAT My dad loves Indian food, so for Valentine’s Day dantransform and I took my parents to one of our fav… https://t.co/Rtqo2B8CK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So for the longest time I wasn’t getting Twitter DM notifications and figured it was just my phone being buggy or w… https://t.co/Sfmw3pCKL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie @BulwarkOnline Power. Power of the "Protestant club". They are pushing towards a "war" between the Ch… https://t.co/TWLoj3s2sD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@varepall These ppl are stupid. If they put this much energy into trying to make our country better we’d all be bet… https://t.co/5XlrHScxP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SachseSheri @russellcrowe Nice to be in a tweet w/Russell!!! Thanks for posting Sheri!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freiterh @matthew_arend Yes!!!!!!!!! We have this conversation often!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LATAMforTRUMP @realDonaldTrump @AmbJohnBolton @SecPompeo @WHAAsstSecty @SebGorka @Lrihendry @RedNationRising… https://t.co/dc8glafdCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also add peanut butter? Like the man literally turned down nutter butters. WHO DOES THAT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DArtagnanFoods @crowdcowusa Ok - so why not lower that “thank you” amount to $75? To go in conjunction with the “f… https://t.co/6yanWYt2RV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers to the freaking weekend 🍻 #shotsshotsshots @ El Centro Classic Mexican Food &amp; Drink https://t.co/4fqhd0FE96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @TheLigerLivesOn @realDonaldTrump Suppose he'll put ketchup on his omelette?   Looks like he hasn't had hi… https://t.co/hjeWyNXegl]]></document><document><![CDATA[CIRCLE Foundation celebrates “A Perfect 10” recognizing a decade of work in Chicago and with Innovations High Schoo… https://t.co/DzHbEMREzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rodledwards @blckriflecoffee @SuperPupKandie How fun!!!  Thanks for sharing!!!  🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻🇱🇷🇱🇷🇱🇷👏👏🐶🐩🐕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vet50Army @TMZ Hopefully enough nonsense that qualifies for a prison stay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetroChicago do you reserve a handful of tickets to sell at the door for a sold out show? Asking for a friend..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EB00717082 @Roger__Barnes @ABC @RobinRoberts @GMA Actually honey, they found the guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never in a million years did I think ilovekickboxing will be apart of my workout rout. But alas it is thanks to a 6… https://t.co/BJVIAuOU7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waltwalters Haven’t left my bed yet, electric blanket on 10, being lazy af 🤘🏼😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[girls sliding in my DM’s always gets me way more hype than guys sliding in my DM’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Northface coat from when I was 16 is lake home coat. Longer days! 🌅 @ Brownton, Minnesota https://t.co/KLyWfejxSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bobbymccs @Seawolves_Rugby I saw your flag today but didn't wanna creep and take a pic! You got the Westside, we g… https://t.co/sNeBJBDAjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grantscruggs @kellyholmin @_jasminezeng HAHA i was dyyyying at this tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep on forgetting I have a Twitter lol, anyways I hope everyone’s valentines was as loving as mine. ♥️ #Nomakeup… https://t.co/dcssU0I4cH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SternSaid I think this is why the conversation struck a nerve with me since a good portion of my budget is salarie… https://t.co/kS64QdEKgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[take time to smirk. #hilarity #laugh #grin #laughable https://t.co/dDCojv4RgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaGuayTV Yes! I can't wait to watch it. Your stories are always awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien iT wAS DaRk. ThEY hAD oN bLAcK cLoTH3s. ShE DiDnT SpEEd https://t.co/hkEk4zsNOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjasonw @marceelias Current view of Mark Harris https://t.co/6P2vWh4VtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ILVOLOMIAMI Me too cuz I’m listening to Más Que Amor this morning❤️ https://t.co/YFg0gANT88]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌸🌸🌸 Spring in NYC, 2013. #cherryblossoms #spring @ Union Square, Manhattan https://t.co/ZLJQy36X4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMeltlingMan1 @pattonoswalt Very true, especially if people see you as the "strong"one.  People with Depression… https://t.co/FmxCLosueQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like photography is a powerful medium. I want to do something meaningful so what would you like to see/be apart of!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Cat in the Hat Day!! #DrSeuss #ReadAcrossAmerica #jhaleyreads @KJ_Kinder https://t.co/0r73RiYFqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting to think that the WH is like the Greek house no one wants to pledge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CRHSRedWolves @CRIBDP IB Biology collecting data for their practical on breathing rates https://t.co/sdCg9F0lXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronjmate @billmaher That's no surprise especially since @billmaher is Islamaphobic. I think it's time for the st… https://t.co/BL1JkVlrle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delavegalaw I can't believe threatening a Federal Judge doesn't put him under the jail. These guys are so dumb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Papaed15 Look! If you're in NYC, you can visit the headquarters like you wanted!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myserenity69 " I'm gonna wash that man right outta my hair, and send him on his way..."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarap na sana ng gising ko pero bat my nga ganitong tao talaga sa mundo? Sige sabhin nating fans ang gumawa pero it… https://t.co/2Ihdk7Itjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @realDonaldTrump What are you doing telling Maduro that he's starving his people when you're doing the same thi… https://t.co/TpggpBNbZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActuallyNPH  Hi, My daughter is a huge fan (I am too 🤗).  She would LOVE it if you would share her Girl Scout Gold… https://t.co/v47h2SEKpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonetPalomino70 Legit, one of my favorite songs. I get teary every time. It tells a story of my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[McConnell preps new nuclear option to speed Trump judges https://t.co/nUSKHzw2oC via @politico]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, it's obviously not a perfect Magic Kingdom day for me until I go see Rapunzel's tower, right? 💜☀️… https://t.co/42NUbAjd4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alfonsocuaron mentioning his favorite foreign films had me jajaja-ing. Felicidades a #Mexico #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[A gorgeous Destination Wedding at Loft .84  - Rory + Magdalena  https://t.co/9c6ydT7YnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MtnMD @rigel2020 I guess that's the best we can hope for right now. Mueller, sweetheart please take these clowns o… https://t.co/oQw5ydTLvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cumberland River and Nissan Stadium In Nashville @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/t3RfPG4xZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would Smollett do that and do we attack victims now???Are we going to question “me too” victims too.  I’m trust… https://t.co/bd5CmD1laf]]></document><document><![CDATA[But we also don’t make laws based on individuals. When “the Commissioner” is referenced in the bill, it isn’t Jeff… https://t.co/flSY92BKxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BionicOrgans @cnnbrk @SenateGOP_ Great roadways?! GTFO! We’re one of the worst states for traffic in the NATION! A… https://t.co/5uLP29Htqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por más que trato de olvidarte, eh, Aún se nota que me muero por ti...❤  #soloyo @ Bakersfield, California https://t.co/CznfBDTc27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrimeJunkiePod alright I need a list of all the podcasts you’d recommend because I’m all caught up and needing a fix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the lizard vibe these leggings rock.  #day1 #marchchallenge #disneybound #tangled #pascal https://t.co/sYnJJxlVJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@staggerlee422 @typhenicie @kdrose0718 @PrimeCreator2 @tee10202 @GABrecken @2newearth777 @AboveTheBurgh… https://t.co/8ssAJPAfuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidhogg111 Word, David! (Especially, true, if when you're #NativeAmerican? I gotta sit here, while "very fine",… https://t.co/I5D25GaiBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, in Oswego County... @FriendsTV #nopower #winterstorm https://t.co/HRYRLyffHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spencer_Brown has such a beautiful and unique sound. Amazing set rn at @AudioSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day! 💃🏾 Tonight I have the honor and privilege of performing at @modistbrewing for the… https://t.co/yBy3IRhNcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #EastLansing, MI? https://t.co/UlFtCrSkZm #CustomerService]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ingrahamsays @WarbyParker Omg. I can’t even see out of mine.  My prescription in the ones I have is so old lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetgeorge48 @liz_kesson Hey, I thought that I was your #1 groupie! Hmmm, ....I guess, I can yield to the Old Dud… https://t.co/9S0mufpVm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg @NKOTB way way cool;! damn awesome this looks so fun way cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolineocon19 That Should read                          he has a lot to be proud of 😊💜🥅🏒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@31biancax AND I WITNESSED IT BUT THEY DIDNT LET US STOP TO RECORD HIM !!! 😫 #proudgf ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch Colin Kaepernick agrees to settle collusion case against the NFL Free Online https://t.co/OVwqNnfVQs #YahooView]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got my wisdom teeth out. 🐿Drop your netflix reccomendations please 👇🏻👇🏻👇🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheetalHardikar @ASPrevOnc @saira82khan @huntsmancancer Great job with the session!]]></document></documents></author>