<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Having students decorate the classroom, instead of the teacher gives them ownership of the class. #outsourcing #RTMK12 @gcouros]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s heart break ending to think they’re people in our nation /world that would torture/abuse these loving/loyal pe… https://t.co/wmPnuzARLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now Playing: Ozzy Osbourne- Blizzard Of Ozz 1981 #IDontKnow #CrazyTrain #GoodbyeToRomance #Dee #SuicideSolution… https://t.co/lMHWTLPs2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! A super #sunrise in #murrellsinlet. Have a terrific Tuesday. #southcarolina #nofilter #blessed @ Murr… https://t.co/MYvASadZaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[GO NEW YORK!! GO NEW YORK!! GO!! @ State Farm Arena https://t.co/Pb4gveWXQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also! This totally highlights the performative aspect of casual racism, i.e., mocking and claiming to “not get” som… https://t.co/SoCeclgko7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going live with @fundstrat Tom Lee on Facebook in moments! Live from @TradersExpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family of American student rebuke Trump after his defense of Kim Jong Un - ABC News https://t.co/6wusaAiCzU (via @ABC)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrojanDominati1 @orthereaboot To be clear , I don’t think Tesla can afford to price the M-3 at 35K and make money.… https://t.co/gVpj73k5Je]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3U8bXBoZHZ  WOMAN ASKED BY OFFICER TO HELP AT CRIME SCENE ENDED UP IN HANDCUFFS  @WTHRcom @IMPDnews  @WizIndy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karen21093 To be fair, he's not Paul McCartney, he's just a guy who remembers Beatles songs when no one else does lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliLake I think it’s fair to wonder whether fundamentalist Islam is compatible with the Constitution]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilie66207965 a painting i did in high school of a raccoon drinking gatorade https://t.co/TCyVtFxCDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard announcer Lance Renaud say Jada Williams was his player of the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police: Attempted dine-and-dash in which suspect slapped Grotto Pizza employee on the butt results in standoff, arr… https://t.co/TXu8hLtxSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolCorp @drewmagary I’d say that’s a pretty sweet gif that I’d be proud of. Nice try on the burn though]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Amarillo #TX  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/Ph8CSeVD0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senate Bill 100 is moving in the Kentucky House too. To oppose this by sending a message to selected legislators or… https://t.co/8b2EHtouqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry, Lindsey, your attorney skills seem to have atrophied. But that's not the real reason you're in Trump's back… https://t.co/P1VZTfNYzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont forget to have fun ! When you find your drive, your motivation,  you tend to get wrapped up in it. You forget… https://t.co/FU9p5RQvI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Real!5-Million-Strong Wave of Illegals Plans to Storm the Border This Year https://t.co/8lb7Oox4jQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @chucktodd @Liz_Cheney Your interview was horrific. Lame that u failed to challenge Cheney”s bizzare hate. #fail]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MazdaUSA Please reach out to your AOR and have them work on frequency capping your OTT placements for your Mazda 3… https://t.co/ujBZjsupoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[💨THIS FRIDAY💨  FEB. 22ND ******************************************** "LIFESTYLE POP-UP PREVIEW" TEXT FUSION TO 545… https://t.co/tjmpMZF71f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al Horford had 1 rebound in 26 minutes. The back-up 2 rebounds each in 9 minutes each. Morris 2 rebounds in 26 minu… https://t.co/i0ctUbzvCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @RescueReality1 @JusticeForOlive @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/DCHKEIrL2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s walk in Savannah, GA.  #tour #walk #healthylifestyle @ Savannah, Georgia https://t.co/xJPJJnQTpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait for a Democratic President to use the grounds of a National Emergency to tackle real issues facing the… https://t.co/br4iK8KnD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahSajohnson @Seguin_B @PrincipalJ Apruary is not a word...and if our students think it is on the test it will b… https://t.co/Ikj8kb5jn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newark Catholic girls lead Northside Christian 63-5 at halftime @NewarkCatholic #nahss @NCWAVEPOOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now available and #InMyShop! #Vintage Framed #AbdurRahmanChughtai #Art Prints!  Want it? Then head on over to The 8… https://t.co/h0HsvnpNnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Few folks talking about how it’s our neighbors and us who are not driving carefully enough. I totally agree with th… https://t.co/HIhNb9qVIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Mueller has buckets of evidence investigating this crime committed by Trump outlined in the FISA warr… https://t.co/KSYHicgip9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t let them the strangely lit obligatory departmental seminar photo of @sheeldodani of @UTDallasChemBio be the j… https://t.co/ijisECrMLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiquidChap When you don’t convince anyone one to say CODE CHAP in the item shop lmao https://t.co/QktzDEfrUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter this #giveaway for your chance to win a a $1,100 entry into a MSPT Tournament near you along with a PokerCoac… https://t.co/XOACgqzdrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s weird how times change. My parents used to take me to the doctor. Lately I’ve been taking my parents...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impresionante edificio. Obra de S. Calatrava. #oculusnyc #nyc #loveanna en The Oculus at the World Trade Center https://t.co/XAPYDV4abX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Battey is getting the ball at the high post with no one within three feet and he has two failed possessions in a ro… https://t.co/slDGkfQ5jP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @HandleyJudges we are on a 2 hour delay this morning...as always please be careful and we will see you… https://t.co/gkVYshHp9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilyYog83 @HeidiStea @JenaC2 @Estrella51Ahora @peetahuja @JeanetteEliz @ladevita12 @SuzanneLepage1 @nieuwemarlean… https://t.co/dI1bH9d88f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticusSarah I'm asking for the emancipation of the infant. You gave to the helpless slave now give it your all… https://t.co/HwyF5e7bSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoe concept is fire...one time for the 1.  M F R I Z E #mifrize #union #unionlosangeles #jumpman #jordan1 #shoes… https://t.co/PfnRsmqNYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theeec annual conference is coming up! Save BIG on registration by becoming a #EEC member.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished walking 2.01 miles in 20m:54s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/l9KzyrMbHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should @GovMLG provide buses?  @RepTorresSmall, @BretBaier, @marthamaccallum we  need help with this crisis. Flood… https://t.co/lJMux0lRRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morgan Wirtz skipping Black Soul 2 in the RORC Caribbean 600 race https://t.co/85fEYVnA8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s short term fear of losing his base outweighs any long term concerns from congressional Republicans re prece… https://t.co/yVuqp1fxXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sex is good for your health. Don’t shame people for being healthy. Lol  Be safe &amp; mature. Y’all fuck good in this weather.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MommaUnfiltered When he’s finished could you have him email us the instructions?  - every husband everywhere!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham Today would be a good day for @Franklin_Graham to Repent his Sins and accept Jesus Christ as his s… https://t.co/BjwapI2izZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh I see how this game is going to go...only call penalties when the guys wearing all black have something happen to them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old guy on the bike next to me at the gym asleep who looks exactly like Dick Cheney gonna punch him out just to be safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsAllBollocks My Grandmother's answer to everything: It coulda been gas Breathe Glad you did well. We are all on… https://t.co/wdoFaofMhb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@overtflow Go bro! Hang with myself, and the bro @PanduhhXx is going too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carson was busy "chipping away" at his yummy snacks after a busy time tubing at Horseshoe Valley resort. 👍… https://t.co/9m9zdpYTwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Just come here legally.  Is that so much to ask ?   Crossing the border in a paid / organized caravan and stor… https://t.co/TPlM1BtRZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColleenDerkatch @CindyWilkey @TorontosMayor Same for #Cabbagetown the last 10 feet from the Uber to my (carefully… https://t.co/0XBVXhDcJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoundMonster @JDaniel2033 Still a clear release point.  Next to his left ear.   Hitters will figure that out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VerityNorth And if it did mean that you were no longer a writer - tell me what a writer who is taking a break look… https://t.co/OyRrFbCjUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Time Portal by @KansasTerritory at @marfieldsirishp — https://t.co/XyWF8PTBgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NervyBastard @LindseyGrahamSC @60Minutes “Peak Trump Crazy” by William B. Turner https://t.co/GY0VL31dji]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to. Just a 4 oz though. - Drinking an Acheron by @martinhousebrew at @cbc_dallas  — https://t.co/VwApKUB5Nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walter Johnson Single Signed University League Baseball PSA/DNA JSA https://t.co/HvCgrhgQkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing event with some incredible speakers and vendors from all over the world. We wanted to continue to g… https://t.co/dl3BPRE2eg]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the smartest guy in the room I could never get anything done. It was only when I became the dumbest that I found my groove]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTrolleyWalk @andrew_dunn Streetcar will be nice after this next upgrade and extension]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going through a time of loss? Our God is a restoring God. In scripture God speaks of receiving a double portion, re… https://t.co/9Vkm4SN8yR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crisp-shirted ad guy loud-talking hands-free on phone just said the client is “emotionally stoked.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[when girls listen to kehlani they reach an existential form of themselves in which all bull shit is deflected and not received]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence @casetwin Stay in the hospital no one has really missed your long speeches and your you all sense of humor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clarencehilljr sorry but this is 2019 and this is a movie, its ridiculous that a black actor now is expected to ma… https://t.co/OAZb0aKPr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesusRCuevas @lopezobrador_ @GobiernoMX Los reporteros de grupos consolidados de televisión, radio y periódicos, c… https://t.co/YsWdpDeUZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[thankful for the few people who never turned their backs on me, the couple friends, &amp; little family I still have left]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JC_Bryan1 @Glorify_thyName "Beware of the false prophets, who come to you in sheep’s clothing, but inwardly are ra… https://t.co/4UbG2HKyQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcosSanzVFX Top five Cowboys offensive players. Zeke wasn’t one. Assuming it was a mistake 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2019 when will y’all realize THE FEMALE OWES YOU NO LOYALTY. YOUR MAN DOES.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To Accomplish Anything worth While in this Life - Stay Hungry my Friends. Make Wednesday Great Again.… https://t.co/s3YgxbtFy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love it when local OKC, ⚽️ and general #sportsbiz talk all collides in a singular thread.  #myfavoritethings all in… https://t.co/yoOnN5IVJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Carolina smacking Duke in Cameron Indoor is impressive. Duke has 2 other top-5 projected draft picks on the c… https://t.co/gcD5nxa2Vl]]></document><document><![CDATA[and there’s people that hate and say he’s not even a top 5 PG in the league... 🙄 #StephBetter and its not even close]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bengeu2 @ChrisBentonGA @sisp101 Thanks for the wonderful follows.  Have a great weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And another. This is pretty much the only way real austinites talk yall. #SXSW19 https://t.co/PCaMY2abep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girl_IKYL @OH_CuzSheSaid I’m not gonna get caught up in any negativity here. Y’all have a nice day. #WhoDat]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TalkinReal is back on #KMYU @KUTV2News tomorrow night at 10.30pm MT alongside @DavidDJJames - @realsaltlake #RSL a… https://t.co/cWbbFW8iAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥👀🦅🏆😍 #Mpire18 #MoneyTeam18 #MT18 #TurnMeUp #GotPaid #MbracedTheDream #WeRunThisState #StateChamps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrassrootsSpeak I wouldn’t be surprised if they declared a national emergency and cancelled the election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliciasalinasg @Rayados Dejalos que la canten, en serio que tienen que estar bien pendejos para celebrar esas cosa… https://t.co/OEhY9VpWRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing is more persistent than your fire alarm telling you it’s low on battery]]></document><document><![CDATA[How come no one told me that Star Trek: Discovery was good. Also, why don’t any of the Klingons have hair? Am I dumb (probably)]]></document><document><![CDATA[My prayer is that people would experience Jesus when they encounter me. Lord in your mercy hear our prayers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join #mschat tonight 8 pm ET to discuss observations with @ezigbo_ and @LaurieBarron #miched #colchat https://t.co/R42sPKlq0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me want a cookie too. But, me on an 8-week challenge and can’t. Me sad. #F45Challenge #F45Training #F45ArtsDistrict… https://t.co/8aBKvI6J0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanieviola I just came to retweet this tweet but found out I already did so I undid it and just now retweeted it… https://t.co/tteKalQI46]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheLLbeLL_xo Oh say does that star-spangled banner  yet stir O'er the land of the cheat and the lousy bone-spur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renemyrand @VGaudreau Nos ouvriers, architectes et ingénieurs québécois sont mondialement reconnus en construction… https://t.co/Belf0daGRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be live on air with @patkiernan in 5 minutes! Tune in on @NY1 now! https://t.co/VnK8rdKWW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@775Reeves @THEMrsWindfeldt @NevadaWolfPack @Fadeaway_J24 @EricPMusselman To the P5. A job will open and he'll be g… https://t.co/39WaLRRylj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing better than beating the fuskies on their senior night. At least they had a documentary about their most fam… https://t.co/noFBKq1hXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayer is the key to guide you to the blessing and faith unlocks unbelievable closed doors. * * #church #leadership… https://t.co/sO5ndp8hRo]]></document></documents></author>