<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So this is a great game and everything, but these may be the BEST and most passionate student sections I’ve ever se… https://t.co/MMVkrq3oF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChannonRose Yes you did the sweetest and best human being ever made channon will you be my Valentine Channon😃😃😃❤️❤️❤️💖💖💖💗💗💗💓💓💓💞💞💞💝💝💝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barracuda_Bella @ReneeCarrollAZ Wow #CapitolHill is nuts today.  I feel bad for the ones who stand for truth… https://t.co/BVjwoSLw9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda inconsiderate that Josh won’t listen to me talk about Kardashian drama 😒  I’m just trying to laugh at the… https://t.co/36jt2DXCrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IrisWil82188689 Hey cuz where was @DLHughleyRadio appeared at in Florence, SC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shamrock Four Leaf clover Brooch  #fourleafcloverbrooch #luckoftheirish #kissmeimirish #broochlover #etsyshop… https://t.co/vRa14MHw42]]></document><document><![CDATA[100sUnit!!!!! We had a blast at the 2019 Black Joy Parade!!!! #BlackJoyParade #100sUnit #DestinyInspiredConsulting https://t.co/HJdkfwZCzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The year is 2025  The Galaxy S16 has been announced  It has 42 cameras, each at a slightly different focal length]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you decide to obey the Lord and step out in faith, your life will change. His presence will go before you, and you just have to follow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg All my love to your family today. We need to make this country safer for our kids and future generations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaGbb @Bailey3Conrad @liv_ritter Congrats girls!   Way to work hard!   Excited to see this team next year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trigonis30 @Hsquad99 @JimJonesBB @MwaniWilkinson @RonMFlores @wreckingkrew44 @PangosAACamp Dearest Dinos ~I would… https://t.co/DKwP7zw70X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews Welcome home Mr President 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blows my mind how I have 40+ items in my cart at Trader Joe’s &amp; only spend maybe $60 #HOWTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you think I’m a rebel without a cause, you aren’t paying enough attention.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️💝💜 Loving the creativity 💜💝❤️ Happy Valentine’s Day everyone! @RobisonES #successatres https://t.co/jJCgnB7HFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anton47492193 @JenniferMlottUK @networkindie @MlottersNation @JenniferMlottNs Aww thank you! That means a lot to m… https://t.co/iv8Do3rurz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love, love, love seeing seeing how much you just love your players and how dedicated you are as a coach to create… https://t.co/ywl6xd6vXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a baby is born alive during an abortion  DEM/Socialist voted to kill it in name of saving Choice this has nothin… https://t.co/cI7MvIj9AP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusingsByGritXO @TheSilentLOUD @SpeakerPelosi Yes, I'm watching the news and it's talking about the memorial.  You… https://t.co/eajiBEWMUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We haven’t even left yet but somehow the airport had lost Kayla’s bag 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that @jordynwoods thinks this about her being a black women instead of her betraying her friends or “famil… https://t.co/YC35ACL85b]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend @TheBigEasy on Fayettevile Street.  Sat. March 9th EG Peters Band. 11pm-2am. Never a cover. https://t.co/wnoVJ5HLKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ali2011Alina Chris Brown is the best entertainer out there to me, after him music will be dead to me because I don… https://t.co/W8Tp8HoX1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never felt more irritated then I do right now at this very fuckin moment. I mean holy shit. 🤬🤬🤬🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out “Dawn” Rorie  @roriemusic and help this artist make her dreams come true and create more great music!… https://t.co/Du4B4wmxV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[george w bush is a CLOWN he did not deserve to win the 2000 election goodbye and good night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kevin Russell in the house! Thank you for sponsoring #museumsadvocacy day again, @blackbaud - you’re the best!… https://t.co/RxB4cR8rAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all the girls who felt special today from a significant other, friend, or family member, you deserve it that an… https://t.co/2fGEcIWZ6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Usually early arrivals are welcomed, but arriving @UnionStationKC at 6:15 to find the coffee shop closed is not the… https://t.co/t8OSO1xCUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyNeveragain @Thebeachlife1 @SpeakerPelosi @RepCuellar @txamiu Thank you 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t come back into my life because you got bored with the person you were talking too. That you thought you would go far for you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luv the cold and everything about it. It’s all fun and games until your room is a Godamn sauna 🌡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekjohnston Actually it was Barbara Eden in “I Dream of Jeannie” #originalhighpony]]></document><document><![CDATA[roses are red, violets are blue. snatches are hard. snatch pull/negative snatch/snatch balance + power clean to pus… https://t.co/qKllK8Czhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM NOT DOING ANYTHING DURING SUMMER EXCEPT SUMMER SCHOOL PARENTS SAY I NEEDA GO AND NOW IM MF]]></document><document><![CDATA[CLIMATE AND WEATHER AREN’T THE SAME THING. Thanks for coming to my TED Talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to listen to @SwindledPodcast - it’s so so good. I’m obsessed with white collar crimes. Also @DarknetDiaries i… https://t.co/BSWxBKGLYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jTp7hGD6hD 3:02 that's because men and criminals wear my shoes I have to keep starting over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cubbies2018 Nah that’s always number 1... but the Jonas brothers are a close second]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gym Jordan, worthless excuse for a sexual abuse facilitator-- spent zero time!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talkiestar @mediadiscounter @jjz1600 @IlhanMN This is a lie.  We love Isreal because God does, because they are Je… https://t.co/x6dcLOOKJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdaciousGardens @TomiLahren My dad a veteran and 82 years of age told me that he fought for the right to take a kn… https://t.co/EY5acRhqmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait-is this for real? If so, I hope they educate people on the river otter-a species legally protected by the Illi… https://t.co/AQuvyijJ1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petty bitches...this chic just purposely drove extra close while I was walking to splash my cute clothes. That’s co… https://t.co/nUehKy5iqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanessa_yanez_ @emilynussbaum Technically it was a tomahawk (tiny axe) but we threw it indeed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitter sweet moment, I know! You had a great middle school career, congrats- excited about the next chapter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meu almoço pelos próximos dias em Los Angeles! Quem ficou com água na boca levanta a mão! Hahaha 🤤🤩😂💚 Levei o Erick… https://t.co/qaOh7rVCrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmckenney Thanks for this Catherine I had been hoping to hear your takeaway]]></document><document><![CDATA[Were this the cover of a book, I’d name the book, “February in New England: A Practical Guide to Survival”… https://t.co/qdVzKoqGAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sherlaya @Nikki_deboer A Very Talented Actress &amp; you captured her perfectly.  Beautiful work1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was still singing amid the Irish Hills near Adrian, Michigan...for a few more weeks...  @DominicanAdrian]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pregaming for the concert!! Girls night out!! #lukecombsbeerneverbrokemyheart @ Matt the Miller's Tavern https://t.co/j2UqbkSFwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[shae and i painted her walls black and did glow in the dark paint splatters everywhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've got some news for you, broke girls love #robyn too! If you weren't able to get tickets to go see her at the… https://t.co/NLBK0nPD5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smcdonald413 Oooh. I’ve rarely had occasion to use the phrase “murder of crows.” Dig it! I’m enjoying your adventures from afar!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Key word here "co-conspirators."  “As a legal matter, the non-prosecution agreement ....does not bind other U.S. At… https://t.co/uXzuxfJIVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that @jan_dembowski posts about coffee often enough that it will eventually line up with other tweets in my… https://t.co/zaZfcPrMf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The idea an atrocity anywhere in the world is an attack on the US is insane. Someone gets shot in New York, that's… https://t.co/KJGO8tn2R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[as a kid who grew up on Call of Duty, I’ve given every installment every year a chance, however:  If we get Modern… https://t.co/qiUSxCY7Bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estás donde tienes que estar, solo debes encontrar tu camino 😏💋 #miamibeach #lovely #venezuelan #miamistyle… https://t.co/xFrNe9K8KF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gconway_UNDP @MoPIED_Somalia @MoHADM_Somalia @UNDPSomalia @UNdeClercq @EU_in_Somalia @mpfsomalia Too bad you’ve ta… https://t.co/lvM9sVZy6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else have a slight anxiety attack because they know they have to go to work or is that just me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed the one whose help is the God of Jacob, whose hope is in the LORD, his God,  The maker of heaven and earth,… https://t.co/DveEe5TG4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class looking might slim...Dicks and breast just flying everywhere today ig]]></document><document><![CDATA[WIN NTX celebrates International Women's Day 2019. https://t.co/FIfU6JUCaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kierstenwhite It conveys so many feelings and already the anticipation is KILLING ME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX But the point is,that the communities,at the border should be,able to decide on the efficacy of a wa… https://t.co/HPfuf0EECT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently rewatching old videos and I think my obsession with Nick is coming back. He’s always been fine 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dyuliharris In an American ad, those fingernails would have been photoshopped.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julia_the_hut These are so darn cute ! I am a backer . Love the Valentino pin so darn cute!! 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cherylynn617 @nwfamsp001 I was living in ATL in the 80’s and was visiting Chapel Hill Harvester Church a lot; that… https://t.co/M86eZjy0dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u see this make sure wish my husband a Happy Birthday! Hope u have a great day babe. Love u💕 https://t.co/RdLdagzFwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a mother, I ache for this stranger and cry as I go to get my son out of bed. Something, everything, has to chang… https://t.co/iglzk1kDEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re so grateful for our guest speaker, Rory Kent. He shared the importance of perseverance and has a very special… https://t.co/JQaOrvi3y5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiltonHotels Thank you I really was a fan of Hiltons I hope I can continue to be]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ingraham is competing with Tucker to see who can produce the most racist hour on television.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YaSimuse Fun fact i asked them what they do on the Persian part cause i thought they would assume it was mumbled E… https://t.co/qTfeydJmjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey could I point out something i feel is ignored in the massive obsessive frenzy re #BraGa: r they or rnt they? Ho… https://t.co/ug4Rkninsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeschlossDC will be worse when the current guy is out of office  who wants to celebrate him...:(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mehdi_Khalaji After the recent news about your wife scandal, I don't even know how to think about anybody and anyt… https://t.co/hpbsHeUrkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeannaMarie32 @TeamSalBrian @KimmijoGeib @Karen44494081 @jeanine_new @SharonG40210896 @PamelaVette @SpiritualGAC_… https://t.co/Wak5idAch7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome back eugeneleeyang AllThat90s Abbey TryGuys ‍ https://t.co/grX1DcQDFj https://t.co/GNSM1C9luw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RidiculousDak @Dnceao I’ve never had one of these actually be funny 😂 https://t.co/ClN8l8PdDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only people who post fb stories are girls who started smoking cigarettes when they were 12 and Mormons who went on missions]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking it with my sis! #LivingAndLovingLife #GrownFolksMusic #CharlieWilson #Babyface #Joe 📸: metria06 @ Bridgesto… https://t.co/9VovwdBWh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDramRob A review is a marketing tool. It's a form of influence marketing/testimonial.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How do you know it’s rigged if there hasn’t been a report yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just by staying married to you, she looks like a jerk.  That's an awful thing to say to someone, especially someo… https://t.co/AYZk0pbCzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunCountryAir It took several calls to multiple people to even get a @SunCountryAir World Tracer File. Last I hear… https://t.co/IKAywtEqNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@startrekcbs @actordougjones This was my favorite episode of the entire series. So far.   Giorgio by the way is ann… https://t.co/nn043TGnXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DHS report Dec. 2017 identified “problems that undermine the protection of detainees’ rights, their humane treatme… https://t.co/ObZSyOSepY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my girls have been online shopping for graduation dresses and ordering our cap and gowns together! couldn’t do this without them ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ankles really are just alternating on which one twists at each game 😔😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimdicker Ugh. Lindsey Graham no moral compass and such low self-esteem that he has to attach his worth to what so… https://t.co/7fSGPTZO11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayleeRoberson_ i get rounded square/oval! i definitely think you’d rock the coffin or oval look with any color re… https://t.co/gsZaHhjiAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[STG TODAY WAS MONDAY.. I COULD HAVE HAD FUCKING CHICK-FILA YESTERDAY😒😕😕😕😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kjack2018 @ike9_Eagles @AldineISD @drgoffney @tdavis_aldine Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Americans Like a Good Crucifixion Story...He’ll Rise Again #Hollywood ⭐️]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI - appearance by 🙋🏻‍♀️ myself about 1 minute 25 seconds into the video 🙏  Remember the Journey is just as import… https://t.co/1ugEshBNwU]]></document></documents></author>