<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[fast forward to 1:15 .. that’s why i like being in the back! i was surrounded by people headbanging and dancing the… https://t.co/I0haFoOjU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BandB_CBS @acejordan23 She is a mom, she needs to find out the truth about her baby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rozweston it’s not John Cassavetes it’s Nick Cassavetes who directed The Notebook xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaiderrr Oh my gosh! You're right! It's all in my head. Guess that's why it's called mental illness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Future bass never comes to Vegas, so that fact that Im not going is ruining me at the moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealBasedMAGA @John_KissMyBot Oh gee, has Smolett’s Get out of Jail Free card expired?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YELLOmelooo Oh VERY Dominican 🇩🇴🇩🇴🇩🇴..until I’m sitting there for an hour without passing the shit ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorkItBurke My creativity to finish my novel, and work on my photographic endeavors!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to send a very heartfelt Happy Hearts ❤💗💖💕🧡💛 Day to my awesome children Kelsey and Derick Wyatt.  I know we… https://t.co/TTNY8j6tLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just a normal girl fallen on very rough times please help at https://t.co/NIq5mzXXpx.  Thank you for your consideration!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrgarrettrox @Hutchinson_SMES @IDECorp They were able to give me a very thorough explanation of their project!]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a pre-show backstage tour, looking forward to "getting to know" "The King and I" @ButlerArtsCtr tonight!… https://t.co/fvwv6XV7sy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austinchanted things are......existentially a mess? LIFE IS WEIRD AND RELATIONSHIPS ARE CONFUSING AND ALSO JOBS AR… https://t.co/mU0zOhyuKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at the place where my love of theatre began ~18 years ago (when I was 3) https://t.co/Dqrls7DZxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a pretty successful day. I got things done at work that needed to be done. I felt extra pretty and didn't… https://t.co/k8TPnuYqME]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever just feel like you need to not be excited because it’s probably not going to actually happen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soapsindepthabc Heartbreaking after how much Franco has changed as a person doesnt deserve this at all!! Love… https://t.co/VV26mLY7oG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Screw it. I’m not waiting to see this movie until next weekend. I’ll go solo on Monday because avoiding spoilers fo… https://t.co/cPfkPVCbbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 days til first meet of the season!! we love u outfit track 😻 https://t.co/4puMgup7Tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind every passionate, strong woman is a tribe of other passionate, strong women! @ Greater Montreal https://t.co/FcPRmLLQzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day everyone! Squeeze your lover. https://t.co/OgxMbayaIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradleyjtice @LisaMarieBoothe I understand that. Did Trudeau commit a crime or violation. I thought I read somethi… https://t.co/WmxDphmb62]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsCrowLovinWOC @jmr___18 @gsmooth89 We got rid of satellite a few yrs ago, so no HBO here anymore. Internet + 3 st… https://t.co/blLdtp23sG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just remembered the time someone commented “I’m trying to suck the insulin outta him” on one of Nick Jonas’s instagram post]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time! (@ Chao's Mongolian Grill in Chattanooga, TN) https://t.co/DaAPMvjrs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @AmyLIllingworth to post covers of 7 books I LOVE: no explanations, no reviews—jus… https://t.co/PII0uqpkYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gaining so much weight it’s ridiculous. Freshman 15 is not a joke :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been so painfully sick for two weeks and the health center keeps turning me away with the common cold but i kn… https://t.co/hlkRBDY27M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iced, iced, baby. ☕️ #coffee #icedcoffee #goodmorning #saturday @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/i9uJtxaYPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least once a week a stranger tells me I look familiar. I’m pretty sure that I just, I don’t know, look familiar.… https://t.co/Ftyj0vn4wU]]></document><document><![CDATA[my head hurts so bad i have been at work since 11 and i don’t get off till 8, ughhhhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[so like, have politics become like wrestling? fake and just for entertainment?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm hopping in the dms if he keep posting pics. That booty probably taste like honey 🤤🤤🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Numbnuts at @CPAC need to know we have always been a mixed economy. @DNC can easily label @gop as #communist lovers… https://t.co/x4yrS40WfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 of Read Across America Week - It's WACKY Wednesday.  Can't wait to see our WACKY Greenwood hair!… https://t.co/RziB18i4tW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darediva Thank you and you’re right about the photos - so hard to photograph mirrors]]></document><document><![CDATA[365 Days Ago I Saw My Absolute Favorite Artist/Person @kmichelle In Concert. Can’t Wait Until The New Music Drops B… https://t.co/smB1KkddKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[im gonna clean this up later but here's todays mood https://t.co/UgQoFjlx9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuneelDhand @LISAMACNCHEESE @drnickUSA @ArthurCaplan @kksheld @DrLindaMD @jorient @HConomics @Hewett1Tim Agree! If… https://t.co/JBIvhetY04]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite PD events every year is @esu13fb’s Mid-Winter conference.  This morning is #specialed case revie… https://t.co/c2mPgVIm9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like one big dance party! #Robyn #robynkonichiwa #dancingonmyown #oakland #sfbayarea #foxtheater https://t.co/iByimRxxae]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m sorry but i can’t say anyone has been solid. all my “friends” only hmu when it’s convenient 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIRGEN DE GUADALUPE IS A FRAUD  USED TO FORCE CATHOLICISM ON INDIGENOUS PEOPLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[so that you may be able to discern what is best and may be pure and blameless for the day of Christ, https://t.co/cRAZJ7cFYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gave myself a “living in Atlanta” timeframe and the closer I get to the deadline the more suffocating this city feels. I’m ready to move.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BIGROB2271 Lmfaooooo I TOLD YOU THIS BUT YOU CHOSE NOT TO BELIEVE ME 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leilua18 WOW!!! Making your mark in Mississippi! #stud #beast 👏🏼👏🏼🔥🔥💪🏼💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think my favorite thing about my friends is that every time we go to any kind of convert, we get security called on us 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamMeakins It might be the pelvic physio in me....  I saw the belt come off and I was like 😳.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCheapSeats18 @ACPinternists @TIMESUPHC How do you know what the women were paid? Is your institution completely… https://t.co/VA9nZ62zOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ketnipz University of bearded dragons please?? 🧡 https://t.co/O5YkFv6pHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmarshallWDRB AKA Cupid Helps to make  @WDRBNews the best place to work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValentinoAndy77 @Anton47492193 @Sugarshack60 @sheri_lynn95252 @doitright651 @Bozesgirl66 @JessieLynnFans… https://t.co/HL4AuUMFBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrsrosales10 @TickTockQreal @Swishcity44 @AzPatriot1979 @qanon76 Read FBI AnoN from 2016 , fairly sure the choice… https://t.co/oKCa01iio2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooper cracked me up tonight.I believe his words were, “I’m so glad I have 3 brothers cause I’ve heard enough girl… https://t.co/pyzpTwwyWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marwilliamson Then reduce the cost of care. Do real health care reform. Not health insurance reform]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain @HuntsmanAbby She definitely does! .....totally unrelated, probably shallow and not my habit to comme… https://t.co/Q0pXCgsIPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little #motivationmonday on President’s Day from GW #inspirationalquotes #challenge #triumph @ New York, New York https://t.co/76VNT7aFUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could say that I talk &amp; I dress all funny but you can’t say I ain’t country]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nolte: 8 Times Michael Cohen's Testimony Cleared Trump of Wrongdoing https://t.co/twJrOeNgmC via @BreitbartNews… https://t.co/Ydfv31CKLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @StarleeKine, now that you are spilling the tea, I have wondered what you thought after MS was cancelled, Gimle… https://t.co/nfRkghfvlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day 2019! Explore powerful words by women &amp; illustrated by women from around the 🌎!… https://t.co/0cpYEwLwR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, Simone's not even here. Why are we talking so much about her? She is amazing, but so are all of the gymnasts competing right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeking all color lovers! Check this awesome design we printed and delivered just in time for #Dance #JAMZ2019 !… https://t.co/OR3SLl3Wtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[so thankful to have someone as special as you in my life. thank you for always being the best! love you so much, ha… https://t.co/j1UAvGrqNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hostess with the mostest @suchthekaitlin introducing our theme #CMSymmetry #cmpdx https://t.co/Q4FdA2PaYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to dream.  I want my delusions of gradeur that make me feel like I am beautiful and that I can have a future… https://t.co/KoSiATcVDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I thought the long-distance nature of the relationship would encourage a scarcity mindset. But what’s actually hap… https://t.co/yWQKDZGZQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay is it that hard for boys to put on their big boy panties and actually say how they feel instead of ignoring you all together???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieDaniels We are a drop in the bucket in the world population and of course it's our problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to NSBHS  Track Team tomorrow at their meet at Embry Riddle. Starts at 10 AM if any one wants to go and s… https://t.co/EPDqXNpiE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew73310992 @BadAstronomer @AOC They are the taxpayers and do are we. We know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@branchtruevine @theghissilent @BishopBarron Bishop Barron is not of my Church - and he does not know Byzantine the… https://t.co/O2lOICTZ9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Cleveland Clinic plans to build a new small hospital in Mentor, which will be its first location in Lake County. https://t.co/uwV8l4TnhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian So @khloekardashian it hurts that jordyn hurt you because she was considered family? I guess it wa… https://t.co/VCijPuKmN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m marrying an old man  Sounds about right tbh, we love a good and rich silver fox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @DATV240 To understand this better go to Amazon or a good book store and buy the book government by Judi… https://t.co/bYlVFXFtij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why ON Earth would we pay taxes to fund everything including making billionaires another billion last year to not h… https://t.co/1vU0sF1MbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life You know, we haven’t tried posting a cat yet but I was just telling my boss that we really need to… https://t.co/LQU77jeJ0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so fucking ready for a nap, but I still have  Cohort meeting and then a leadership meeting after that]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Have you ever seen the segment of our show, called animals riding animals?”   Niall : no but that sounds messed up]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not gonna lie @Kehlani I didn’t really fuck with Morning Glory on first listen but I fuckin’ feel this shit love🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WarriorWednesday #JamieFraser #Outlander #SamHeughan #BestActor #Bestscreenacting #LoveForSam  😘👋  Credit to rosan… https://t.co/36l4kBHneB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesWieand That's truly sweet. I don't think it is. Good luck to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending my nightly @cavs game tweet to my favorite broadcasters @CavsFredMcLeod @MrCavalier34 @cayleighgriffin… https://t.co/GbZO5EvfUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@u16173 @subanski Same here. I made 3,000 less and owe 3,000 more. That is a difference of 6,000.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#QuestionOfTheDay If you had intro music, what song would it be? Why? #WednesdayMotivation @obxcat914 @DBock2010… https://t.co/ByiIMfANv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nathan working on homework while waiting for Lydia to get out of school.  When did this kid become so grown up?? @… https://t.co/NDQpageVie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't call myself a man by avoiding life's unsettling confrontations. All that's left is to scream loudly before going to bed forever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VincentPerryJr Lmfao I think about this all the tine. People are so weird 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It takes someone to be left in critical condition to arrest the person who purposely crashed into your car 😒😒 smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SafariLive Hello all just jumped on hope y'all are well my wonderful SL Peeps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donations are doubled up to $50 if you use code LIFTOFF. Thank you in advance 📚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Obama said “he had a pen and he had a phone and he would use executive orders and executive actions!”  It was ok for him??]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re so fine...gold stiletto sandal by @Alarcon_Shoes. #madeinspain https://t.co/Uhzfj8KPdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraceSpelman You should check out the Marie Leveau house/museum &amp; crypt for the Voodoo Queen of New Orleans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida Trip Update: I MISS MY PUPPERS!!! 😭😭😭 But I’m still having fun and learning tons of new things. 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Trends in Sublimation Beachwear That You Must Get this Summer https://t.co/2Om81qXu6G #SublimatedBeachTowels… https://t.co/MkNiEkg2j2]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANNOUNCING @AcousticExchang FEATURED ARTISTS: we’re thrilled to welcome yesthatsphoenixx , iquemusiq and… https://t.co/coGb3t19VK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost choked up telling the audience what it felt like to be the first person in my family’s history to be in a… https://t.co/fRbUAhGQ4z]]></document></documents></author>