<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheTestyTarheel @JulieReichwein1 @wvufanagent99a @ImabitcSumtimes @TheBeaSmith @hickorymtnman @christianllamar… https://t.co/dF0g9hINpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Choosing a wedding photographer? The choice is simple☝️😍💪#ohioweddingphotographer #weddingseason https://t.co/DsXeRVHEuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Movie Review of #TradingPaint: I'll say this without telling everything, it isn't just about dirt track racing, it'… https://t.co/zg8EYz1Cso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man straight up 🤣🤣🤣🤣like where are they hosting this survive lol and I peeped they be deleting movies after like tw… https://t.co/bqbMGiPRCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GailSimone "I knew a girl named Nikki I guess you could say she was a sex fiend..."  GOD I miss @prince  🕊🕊🕊🕊🕊🕊🕊🕊🕊… https://t.co/CdHrARf8e4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think this is how either coach envisioned the first half of tonight’s game would go.  Reed and Warfield eac… https://t.co/rJEbjZRTOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice seeing you again Laos!! Thanks for dinner! @ Walnut Creek, California https://t.co/hqt1arooWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Terror10_WMC @LRiddickESPN @Steelersdepot It didn’t sound like it this year. But...ab seems to be poison. For such… https://t.co/LO4ULA6Juh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BourbonNBlue I think they stay right at 5. The LSU loss prevents them from climbing, but the win against #1 in con… https://t.co/di9NOjhCic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoPrawnik2 @StanleyPanama @pisorgpl A co mnie ochodza dialogi kakie prowadza Zydzi? Ja chce rozmawiac z Persami. M… https://t.co/xLP8T3aeHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[getting a cramp in my leg and just thinking what happened if i said fuck it and just let it be]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have maybe 15 things I can get the time from in my house. I have only had to change 3 clocks for daylight savings… https://t.co/aaEAwQ54x9]]></document><document><![CDATA[yo if there was a meal between dinner and breakfast it could be called dikfast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gary Clark Jr. SNAPPED on his new song "This Land." Rock and hip hop fans will both like this song.]]></document><document><![CDATA[El miedo lleva a la ira La ira al odio Y el odio lleva al sufrimiento...  Una de mis frases favoritas de una de m… https://t.co/8oWFTNCJmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[POST-#redmareinnj food with RV discord folk @ Tops Diner https://t.co/3fBRZWEPpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 well it's a good thing we're penguins so we can swim and walk with two left feet. We just can't dance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump Pay or go to jail. In the other hand maybe just go to jail for an attempted coup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Bombing has stopped; they're all running from " Godzilla " Blue Oyster Cult on Spotify at 00:05 Friday March 1,… https://t.co/ywhq8bclQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder what donut Twitter thinks of Bernie's diverse rally in Brooklyn. Let's find out lol #Bernie2020… https://t.co/hbUYFHcMLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[t’s sad to see how unfair the University of Minnesota treats it’s students with conservative views.  Why is it that… https://t.co/p418cQcEop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityofVisalia are you f_n joking me you close down Ben Maddox noble and Tulare ave to run a race and forget to tel… https://t.co/xaH3CiWjah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FGSaints True or false (just so I know I am not crazy). Did one of you leave the morning after the Bowling Green s… https://t.co/SkGt2z7d6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabrielToribio @bolivarvalera El boli esta bien, a la tal Laura Bonnelly es que no deberian dejar que vuelva a pon… https://t.co/joWZx4Itbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @EdKrassen yeah, that 1.6 GDP really helped put people to work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, now we know one thing for sure, April the giraffe is a slut. @woodyandwilcox]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SundayFunday is all about having fun with friends that we call #family!!  . Come out and join @Partytimecrew and f… https://t.co/O5NpUFlRg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turnerjoylynch please don't tell folks what to do with their own bodies. It isn't necessary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCNews l see @realDonaldTrump influence is spreading. #HateCrime #racism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump AGREE WITH ME ON A VOTE  WE ARE DONE WITH DEMS YOU DID THIS YOU PUT HER IN SHAME ON… https://t.co/B9VaV0djB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT!  Dinner with the big guy himself!  BIGFOOT!!!!!!😎😎 https://t.co/PNVoAv8UUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a leaf fan look at Saturday March 9th 2019 leafs play 58 mins their winning 3-0 after 60 mins the score is 3-2 w… https://t.co/2SwD4nNzQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came to visit my parents in Good Old East Texas. Glad to see landmarks along I-20E that remind me of where I came f… https://t.co/fZ5VsNWF0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaysmallz92 @DCpoodles2 @qanon76 LOL. nO OnE waS AtTacKiNg https://t.co/0onek6ZgqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Trust in the LORD with all your heart and lean not on your own understanding; in all your ways submit to him, and… https://t.co/2lOq6CiCvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were seeded 15 and finished 5th overall (from the slow heat) with a time of 8:05. Singh: 2:02.7, Troy: 2:01.0, K… https://t.co/ZhlGqaw3ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SMaxwellStory @MsJayLee22 @dirtlife0 @com3t0think0fit @jdstalnaked @of_ramblings @lauralaxla @sweatsntopknots… https://t.co/njlHCruAok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC pretty crazy the committees star witness has already perjured before Congress in previous testimonies. I guess… https://t.co/Mnwr04kNTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork So how much should Jamaican/Indians get? https://t.co/8KEDDtHyWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning tomorrow gotta watch Tottenham get smacked #ItHappenedAgain #NorthLondonDerby #Arsenal #Gunners #Gooners]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBTA_CR your ploughing contractor at Stoughton station could do a better job if they used a front end loader. Less… https://t.co/Jv8Tw96FCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standing next to the captain on the MK ferry.   Captain (over pa system): Folks please remember if you have an iPho… https://t.co/X13y7b5w1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with elizabethheiskellofficial at the @chswineandfood. Of course we had to talk about good ole Southern coo… https://t.co/VG0JU4i6cy]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOSTON GOAL: Marchand buries a one-timer from the high slot.  #VegasBorn 1     #NHLBruins 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[1979 Minolta 50th Anniversary XD.  Near mint condition.  Tested.  Only 1,500 made, this is number 302.  For the per… https://t.co/iukx8Gkl3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I called this the minute it happened. It doesn’t take a genius to predict the shares dropping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting up late strategizing about how to respond to the fact that my home precinct, @NYPD13Pct, has apparently joi… https://t.co/QytCo5uylS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump It was great you idiot! Hillary has always been one of the most corrupt people in our… https://t.co/qMMW7utGbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[So true and so sad... they are encouraging tribalism and purely interested in agendas not orople as a whole]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenDuBose Could his decision to Houston have anything to do with the cap and delaying when to sign bought out players?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not letting up. In fact I’m doubling down on efforts to #ExposeTheFrauds https://t.co/33FiMdslW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having on Linda Holmes of all people to talk about a movie about race underscores the entire criticism of the movie… https://t.co/zk7INDa79M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @BillSimmons what planet is Kyrie on tonight? Third rock from the Dolan?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eventbrite | Georgia Logistics Summit Regional Forum https://t.co/EzSGhdS3bv]]></document><document><![CDATA[House Ed taking up HB 2330. This is the third anti-bullying bill spread over two committees. HB 2257 was proposed b… https://t.co/ReJRSL2CwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapasitoRamone @RashidaTlaib @IlhanMN While the establishment tries to distract with false charges of… https://t.co/UnjzRmpDHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DukeFansZone @LtownZag @GaryParrishCBS Lmao Tillie averaged 6 and 4 when he came back. People act like he’s a 20/10 guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allifarm Part his hair by blowing on it against the grain and see if it is white, or brown to the hide. Trapping s… https://t.co/Nz7CgceZBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slackamania how’s harbough going to make offers to 7th graders anymore?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilocrek @slcdunk Mitchell? Isn’t Simmons in the running racing against another rookie this year? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FortMill wrestling Joshua Sturgeon heads to the 5A 120 pound consolation finals with a third period pin against #RockHill]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad world  we live in Really sad @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/ibqwNIVLKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[we seriously do not deserve the jonas brothers in 2019 but here we are, life is good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLegere I have the VM to text enabled through the One Plus International add on, but iOS already does this. I w… https://t.co/VfeqMzysnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obstacles get bigger but you’ll be strong enough to conquer them on sight @ryderwear ELEMENT x D-Mak CARBON. . Use… https://t.co/uv6RUh5dfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge Andrew Napolitano: Trump's brazen, unconstitutional overreach  https://t.co/jESXAMzWE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dandrezner @nadabakos @FWhitfield @realDonaldTrump Now it it formal -- we have already made a bad and dangerous de… https://t.co/ntYSIKYP1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another sign it’s 2019...now the debate RAGES over the effectiveness of #WalkAndTalk meetings over traditional sit… https://t.co/ut299Kdh5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Registered_Rep @Billy04959629 @someideasnstuff @reddit Well if she said that it's wrong. The bottom 20% make 20k a… https://t.co/yONmzVi6oe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casserly evaluation of Kyler Murray rates higher than Patrick Mahomes going into the draft. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love that this annoys so many people. It's just #clothes : U know it took real balls to wears this. I wouldn't be b… https://t.co/3JrVc4s07i]]></document><document><![CDATA[bemorechillmusical @ Lyceum Theatre (New York City) https://t.co/UaAMlCmpLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[She should’ve went into that split when she fell down them damn stairs lmao 🥶🥶🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJoniErnst Moron, #GreenNewDeal is an aspiration. It’s not set in stone. If Congress worked like it used to both… https://t.co/yEBOVExXJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corey Graves yelling ‘This is dumb!’ Pretty much sums up the Lynch, Flair and Rousey story]]></document><document><![CDATA[... study work ... line to plane to find form, a search for patterns and figure/ground... @ West Branch Studio https://t.co/ADGrS5un87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comcastcares thanks for trying to rip me off. Luckily I caught it before the bank paid the bill. For some reason c… https://t.co/zjq2BnfoYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSquare87 @JohnKasich Kasich is about the only pure #NeverTrump Republican politician.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats 2 our own @WestMillbrook Ms. Kokenes being named the best school psychologist in the country! Wake County… https://t.co/JKC5zbtvUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually look like I was born to put people into the wall and then shoot a commercial after. https://t.co/DRvqTB3HB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sencillo por fuera ,hermoso por dentro. Tazón de carne hoy lo prepare en genteregiaoficial . #chefpalaraza #carne… https://t.co/TnN4ixzxTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #MondayMailbag is waiting for your questions. I’ll answer them on #CBJin30 presented by @TelhioCU today. Also,… https://t.co/q7zhXwsnol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when the #media calls out own! #FakeNews  New York Times backs up Trump's migrant claim after WaPo ridiculed… https://t.co/jvybU22ak1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmitchelllittle Im happy to debate and discuss ideology after 2020 but getting rid of the Trump is the single only shit I give.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shameful! But HOF has to keep Steelers out because the place already looks like The Great Hall and they can’t have… https://t.co/9N74AeMRQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariahernandezp @alvarobetamax @MaihenH @edgarzambranoad Yo no he dicho que sea traidor, solo dije lo que la gente… https://t.co/sl1jZrkD9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to be selfish but i need one of those make a wish kids to not go to disney land and just ask for title fight to come back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelSontag @chetbrowndotcom @QuashTagGaming You bet! He never touched the home!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmaikumeh @Wonderfullycre1 @YeleSowore SOWORE , would have started as GOVERNOR/SENATOR. When we see the the effec… https://t.co/EBg9RtCQeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a twitter famous pup doing twitter famous pup things https://t.co/HAoori8XWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone sees that the new generation of pokemon starters are all homages to some of their predecessors!?!? Grookey… https://t.co/JvtGne8knQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[29-28 Lara, big round for Castano #LaraCastano @ShowtimeBoxing @premierboxing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Solarte say anything about running out ground balls in either language?]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Bledsoe No Brogdon No Problem!!!  Let’s finish this game strong fellas @bucks #BestInTheNBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow this is amazing. - Drinking a Træblod by @mikkellersd at @BrewHouseSJC  — https://t.co/eIp2IQPehk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday morning ride ... (@ Courtney Campbell Causeway Trail in Tampa, FL) https://t.co/OrbZL8l5e4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mjlamp Everything is great! You should swing by the office sometime for lunch :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #CadetBonespurs how’s the #TradeDeficit doing? @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/AvoWUVBJA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/OsRz9oyrXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonnyBunch You could get away with such absurd storylines so simply back then. Nobody understood technology, you c… https://t.co/iexMkp6Jaz]]></document></documents></author>