<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Parti Gras is at Val’s TONIGHT! Ask me for a coupon to get $2 entry, $3 at the door!!🎊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marie_Lu will rebel pick up after the amazing ending of Champion where Day tells June something was missing? I lov… https://t.co/qP2nSVcqm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/7/19 At Rio Del Oro elementary now....want to know ANYTHING about meals at school? Come see me. Here till 2pm, at… https://t.co/zEJV0nKLkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsSewardMath Yes. And then when b is a fraction, finding the period can be so tough. I need to work more w basic f… https://t.co/WUZeNJHlDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jccuencavivas @NTN24ve Tu me vas a perdonar mi JC. Y si esto fuese realmente un saboteo donde están los planes de… https://t.co/5r7vKcgKRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheProfitCNBC #FamilyBusiness #RezilirHealth #TheProfit https://t.co/JevloVyoZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I had a student jump 2 grade levels in math proficiency, after a team effort of RTI support.   Showing him hi… https://t.co/gXMhAZr5ZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TayshiaAdams you are absolutely GORGEOUS girl!!!!! You deserve the very best!!!! #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you wake up in the middle of the night and well. #Colorado is closed again kids. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[and I am SO PROUD of this v teeny v determined spider, that I want to stand out there and say “way to go!” and make… https://t.co/c8jV5QnQvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at NWO Orthopedics &amp; Sports Medicine in Findlay, OH https://t.co/Rb9DWWdr1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dirtgirlatheart @9PMRoutine1 @OfficialLivePD @PascoSheriff @k9_keno @danabrams @Sean_C_Larkin @TomMorrisJr1… https://t.co/8YRwYqPUFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk @RepDevinNunez isn’t a representative of District 22-CA as much as he is an accessory after-the-fact prote… https://t.co/o9ZvHgI4Kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JocyZapien Lmao yes 😂 like we only got the red bull’s in cans that are flavored but now how y’all do it over there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HemmannRay I can’t watch when he’s on ! I treat the segment like a commercial! GET RID OF HIM PLEASE !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like obama half white, half black pot smoking liberals . The media would love to marvel her as president. Well… https://t.co/4R44JnrbKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rundeirun @BibRave YES, that is the SHIT! And I know you are a fan :) #BibChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@purva_creations Not really a course for it - but if you really want to do it you will find the path!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day!! This lady believed in me since I became hers! She came into this profession when… https://t.co/gVJIwY4I4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenLoanyG You’ve had enough baasto iyo suugo to be Somali now. Lolll]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will finish the 6 part series and schedule to release them, but after that I need a break, for my family found ou… https://t.co/MNG0Sxaadq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arwen_ArMaine @VeritasUno1 @ed_maine @BellaDiva25 @thereisanocean Kahit super mulat pa ako. Walang makita.. as in.. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating the 3rd Annual Humble Middle School Day in Humble, TX! What a great way to keep the focus on this AVID… https://t.co/AXCafVXq8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MindaHarts I’m in the same energy today.   Can’t wait to see you at SXSW! 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I’m getting a half sleeve in about an hour so I guess I have to right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I took from that is the knowledge Kim has on some mega shoe lifts. Cadet Bone Spurs looks angry and distracted.… https://t.co/Lq9PQ5Mn5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ying Yang Twins are soo graphic. How did our parents let us listen to this as toddlers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesusSellsHomes So nice to meet you last night!!  Cheers to an awesome Day 2 ☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: *chewing gum in the lab* exam question 1: why is chewing gum NOT allowed in the lab? me: *chews gum secretly in the lab*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Dr.Seuss in #SeacrestStudios @VUMCchildren! 📚@RyanFoundation #ReadAcrossAmerica @NEAToday https://t.co/OzVByhii3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TurnerForTX have you heard about HB1792 supporting full practice authority 4 Nurse Practitioners in TX? I am askin… https://t.co/vXQTCCpb7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyraHale7 @NationalistCody @SenRandPauI I feel the same. I am irreversibly disgusted with @SenRandPauI attitudes.… https://t.co/o8gQqqOgL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 #WomensHistoryMonth #SheInspiresMe shout out goes to my sister @HaackKim Because she is incredibly smart and… https://t.co/KXQ7PEyFtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lakatesadilla My favorite memory will forever me is in Prague laughing at the birds @asdfghjklilian]]></document><document><![CDATA[that terrible moment when they ask you if you’re “wearing a shirt under that hoodie right?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ask_Spectrum When I close out my work week, I will. It’s day 4 with internet dipping out again. It could be the fa… https://t.co/YQLB2fdU1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[My moms fiancé tells me everyday he loves me and that I'm beautiful. That may not seem like a big deal but my dad w… https://t.co/dwTaLgctE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost  DO NOT SETTLE!!!  Go all the way and MAKE THIS FAMILY spend all their $ on legal and court fees. S… https://t.co/Wluw0OisCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Just 2 things WE need.... 1. The release of your tax returns 2. Your college SAT scores]]></document><document><![CDATA[24 more days until all the beautiful flowers and trees start to bloom!  #Spring2019 #cantwait #march20 https://t.co/jaOVcnp4iO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #UCET19 participants...and those participating virtually! 😉 Take some time to #TellYourEDUStory via @flipgrid t… https://t.co/894kDi7lrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio @AfterHoursCBS To be clear the shoe didn’t cause the knee sprain did it? Replays show he was in an awkwa… https://t.co/JIWwqrWo9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ll be at Fenn’s Coffee in West Chester TONIGHT. Music starts at 8! Come hang with us. https://t.co/HcxoVShTri]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5 of the Favorite Children’s Books Challenge! My next nomination is @mrsnearyk https://t.co/yWSHIvdf9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw someone say “stop sabotaging a world you won’t even be alive to see” 💀🤧👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but I’ve given chickuh filuh 3 tries and every time it was salty affff .... 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a difficult decision lol but here I am! Go Shocks! (@ Charles Koch Arena in Wichita, KS)… https://t.co/vHZLvHHsqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Money trap Thursday #starcandyinc #queenstarcandy_ #starcandyapprove #starcandyedit #stripperwear livetwerking… https://t.co/0wTt9qp1xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[An initial #Gun background check didn’t catch that the #Aurora shooter, Gary martin, 45 had a prior felony convicti… https://t.co/tbZn4PTw65]]></document><document><![CDATA[the taco bell by my house is closed because something broke and i don’t think i’ve ever wanted to cry more like... how am i supposed to live]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your Monday was anything like mine, it was a sleepy coma status struggle bus... So, let's all enjoy this picture… https://t.co/Y0CnKoiBQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a pleasure to meet Rehana Lerandeau from @checkr yesterday. Excited to explore how we can partner together!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpdel11 @NatashaBertrand @haydenblack @ScottMStedman Will see!! If will see... AJ ALREADY PLANS TO HIDE ITS FROM PEOPLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LastWord I still don’t understand Trumpanzees that insist #Thug45 is doing a great job! What metric do they use wh… https://t.co/l6HNSLhVDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @DonaldJTrumpJr Hillary Clinton loses emails and Republicans chant “Lock her up”.  Donald Trump lose… https://t.co/FbZ9uBEvHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my good friend Jeff Gund @INFOLIST  Had a fantastic time with my fellow cronies, Writers, Produce… https://t.co/Ke4edpouyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do It...Di It...Do It... This is such an A-MA-ZING Show #RenewODAAT @OneDayAtATime]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need allies and accomplices in all industries to move the needle in authentic movements. We don’t always have to… https://t.co/7HKaPTBZA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it me, or is "joining the re-election campaign" a synonym for "there's some sort of scandal here but we can pay… https://t.co/exRxscLntp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 They blamed him for being healthy, being in shape, eating right, blamed Michelle for a garden, blamed… https://t.co/I1ilpMjSrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where To Stay In Amsterdam For The Best Experience https://t.co/iSoBXVpWW9   @Iamsterdam @Kimpton #Amsterdam… https://t.co/2yV2TetIai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect day for a boat ride ❤️ @ Space Coast River Tours https://t.co/fPWFCCer9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBloomberg Please look into the 5G roll out. Significant unknown effects on our health, environment, animals. https://t.co/wbb0bkt5JY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just broke my nail and I’m so sad 💔 bout take them all off not trying to look ratchet with broken nail]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougDavidsonYR so glad you are returning! Y&amp;R hasn’t been the same!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so happy they had finally found an assistant for me ! He was doing so good all week and what happens ?! He just quit . I can not .]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart staggers; horror has appalled me; the twilight I longed for has been turned for me into trembling. https://t.co/tNM0tfBnDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryRarick @Hoffman8 Especially with a pause/rewind function :) https://t.co/eGIfifoh0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c_literacy @ClaytonNJSD @NeenahSchools @NJSDHoraceMann @AmyLSchumacher Love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @HeatherMallick  Seriously? Canada is bored? Speak for yourself! Our government is corrupt, inept and dangerou… https://t.co/6uDz9nKNv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOUTHPORT Location, Today from 3:30PM to 6:30PM, come check out the amazing Brianna Murray With allmax nutrition, g… https://t.co/AyiJsxUdkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcGarneau @NavdeepSBains @KirstyDuncanMP @JustinTrudeau @csa_asc Encore #alalune]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HU_ChicagoAlum @NYHAC @myvetteparamore @iamwandasykes  👇🏾 Please follow and retreat 2019 Hampton Ladies Lunch .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Georgia LHP CJ Smith strikes out two batters and none of Kennesaw State’s first three up get on base. We head to th… https://t.co/lFIfApYXUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lee County Sheriff Jones holds the latest press conference this morning along side Bill Harris, the county coroner.  https://t.co/WbT4ow1Zfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Black Gatekeepers https://t.co/gIVO3tooJV via @YouTube Pastor Darby speaking the TRUTH about black Americans.… https://t.co/RVsFArCETM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom just sent me the song she wants us to dance to for the wedding I called her and she’s crying😂😂😂😂😅😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it even legal to search for an excuse to Indict someone??? This is why nothing gets done the Democrats are consu… https://t.co/a6zI6MQdDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trans_tho If you ever feel dysphoric about that, just wanna let you know that this man absolutely adores cats and… https://t.co/AJVkPBGtCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Airvooocht @realDonaldTrump Oh, if only. I think you’re being way too optimistic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff #9PMRoutine just another snowy busy at work Monday. Have a great night and stay safe all 💚💖💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAlpacah @rriess16 @Enflyte77 @Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump HAHAHAHAHAH  BETTER KNOWN AS RUSSIAN ROBOTS!! 🤣🤣😂😂🤣🤣🤣😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am also a great believer in the healing power of touch - the laying on of paws is  extremely appreciated by my pa… https://t.co/zg4V0faxav]]></document><document><![CDATA[shoutout to @ICCSoftball for getting this win tonight over PR!!! making a has been proud😭🏹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Break in the storm this morning ♡ @ Davenport, California https://t.co/yowlElvcin]]></document><document><![CDATA[He called on the Nigerian government to respond and investigate the incident.  Aiteo Exploration Ltd. announced tha… https://t.co/rJ3TdIEePh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 I feel sorry for the farmers but they continue to support the president that did this to them- they o… https://t.co/fTW5CtTFal]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlaPanthers take 3-0 lead over #RedWings at 8:26 of the 2nd. Looked like Ekblad shot went off of Vatrano's skate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we have this patient at the clinic that anytime he has an appointment he brings in a box of donuts because he is… https://t.co/Dmw90hIJHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was sent this picture yesterday.. first congrats xomaddzz 😘 and thank you @megannshiness  for the super awesome s… https://t.co/RNPFwg3uN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HomeFreeGuys how about keeping good thoughts for me as I’m interviewing for a job today? @TimFoustMusic… https://t.co/4tDpWlTw2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn’t it crazy that @TheLizArmy is transforming #SXSW2019 while I’m #NAPForum2019 and @BethanyKwan is rocking it at… https://t.co/VUb2v8milT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sissypuckett3 @lesleyabravanel @MichaelCohen212 @POTUS @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/0TSeRovlST]]></document><document><![CDATA[That statistic isn’t out of her ass that’s in my textbook... 0.5-2% of reported rapes are false.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet your new Area 2 HOSA Officers from George Ranch High School, Marjoy Kagho and Brendan Pounders!@grhs_hosa… https://t.co/QuKXlNjt3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign here to stop scam artist Donald Trump from rewarding predatory payday lenders! https://t.co/HzzYQKfGNB via @CREDOMobile #resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the help of Matt Gaetz, who is apparently in charge of the threatening part of the fixer job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers, you made it to Friday! ☕️ I’m starting the day off with a few of my favorite things including… https://t.co/GYKHEB6oYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SideHustleWino @SashaEats @jflorez @suziday123 @RedWineCats @magee333 @GailBenzler @wineNweather @_drazzari… https://t.co/MY14iHgv9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[if y’all bitches that are under 21 and would like to go to my event hmu for guestlist 😘]]></document></documents></author>