<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to our Brother @VinceVicta !!! Live it up and enjoy your night!!! https://t.co/yJtglnyQRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_happy_rogue @jjuliejust @gaslight1944 @TracyCampanell @DivorceSayss @LadyBret @christinem1059 @SlowBoiledFrog… https://t.co/KWr1dNZ97s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning folks! It’s officially Friday Jr!!!!! I hope your day starts &amp; ends with a smile 🌞😇💫  #beauty… https://t.co/98mZ33HdOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendaryEnergy What is the obsession with your hair!? People, look at the message not the vessel!!!!! ( I love your hair btw)]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Friday!  I'm off today - and it's going to be a fun weekend!!!!! 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This anxiety attack won’t end. My hands won’t stop shaking, the tears won’t stop. The teeth clenching.  This is a f… https://t.co/bj3UnBNO1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[One in ten under 30 grew up as Catholic but became unaffiliated by age 16]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to the cries of this young boy. Just listen to them. He is traumatized, as any child would be. Now, how many… https://t.co/MOKZfezkef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertMaguire_ @realDonaldTrump @GovernorKayIvey Is there a grade lower than F?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RabbiJill Oh my, I didn't know about the diagnosis of pancreatic cancer. One of my best friends from college died… https://t.co/Jb2t9fRxhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was close call but I think that croissant with the surprise chocolate filling won this round @Fresh_Start_LLC .… https://t.co/1WGvz5rrBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just love when Instagram bloggers post about cute clothes being on “sale” and I get super excited. Then I go chec… https://t.co/dg1gAD36LO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @SalemBookNerd to post covers of seven books I love no explanation —just a cover f… https://t.co/RcryKWmiPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I was trying so hard to not cry after I said goodbye to Jarod and my mom said “your dad doesn’t care abou… https://t.co/NJCCSyqo8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[My gift arrived with a hand written note from our president jaybutler.fac  Swipe to read it  #FACStyle #ilovemyFAC… https://t.co/cAUZuIkUEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sntpvenezuela Señor ten piedad de Luis Carlos Díaz y que regrese sano y salvo 🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Could that loss have been contributed to by the photo of Hillary in black face makeup and Bill dressed as… https://t.co/jkahoLDl0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspired by Rocket's adventures, my Grade 1/2 #bookclub went searching for words today! Next week we'll be choosing… https://t.co/mps685QCqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabeDeArmond Did we know Mark wasn’t playing today? Missed that note until they said it on the broadcast]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think my favorite new hash tag is #RingThatJawn...@CristoReyDallas can we get a college acceptance gong?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drunkbtch_ Dude the complex next to me is literally called la villa and it’s so shitty. Also I’m living for your n… https://t.co/ac0reMorwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[STOP bashing r kelly for the same thing your uncle been doing for years. the same shit that yall act like doesn’t happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ephoustonbill @glennaatx @SpindleTap @baabaabrewhouse @SigmaBrewingCo @LonePint @badhopper @cellmavin @RJellyman S… https://t.co/VJJT19T9fH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girl ain't bad, she more like evil  Photo: @paulmcfalliv  Makeup: makeupxmisssquire Model: @CAMiLA_KiLLA  Stylin… https://t.co/qAukYTbY33]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceRamgatie2 I don’t believe anything they say. Until I see it on tv.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metromorning referred to attendees at Special Oympics as “mentally” disabled. It’s “intellectually” disabled (or better, “challenged”)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Crave Beauty Academy! The @STLRegChamber was honored to be apart of the unveiling of your new lo… https://t.co/BXrNooYfl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsschrapps I’m so happy your @Ethridge_Bobcat students have the opportunity to learn about these inspiring women.… https://t.co/ZJd8RZXUts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being at Texas Southern has truly led me to opportunities that I could never imagine. I swear I love my HBCU 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggforbes @joshtpm I meant, she’s getting paid for this shit. We’re not. This isn’t a creative ideas class, it’s legislation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird @MorSeaS Do you think he got the hint, no one likes trump! Bullys are bad enough, but stupid ignor… https://t.co/1vtVsP5EmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCHill7 @DDPYoga Proud of you guys 💥 @DDPYoga #PositivelyUnstoppable DDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited!! Thanks mom and dad! @ Chaifetz Arena https://t.co/LXpfMdz6vr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Euh...Hellooo ! It's still technically the weekend. . . . . . . . . . 💇&amp; 📷: maxime_allegro  #sixtiesstyle… https://t.co/zaBzOqK0mP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united why penalize people who take a coat onboard and check their bag and don’t put luggage in overhead bin? why… https://t.co/vSCTAgPrkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why Im single soon as I start being open mfs wanna be weird and stalk me.  Or hack into my email 🥴 can’t give no nigga no good pussy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoo00lia @morgihurd Yes ma'am! Ithaca is one of my favorites ♥️ Autum Leaves then lunch at Moosewood and maybe  Ithaca Bakery for dessert?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alisonvictoria3 I’ll tell ya something. You are one brave ass chic. I’ve never seen renos that cost hundreds of th… https://t.co/UoKzSvCBXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caseable Thank you for customizing my Amazon Fire ! 👍👍 #SebringMemory https://t.co/sIyGvsvQTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[can we come to encounter His forgiveness and His healing grace.  Speaking to God about our struggles, pains and our… https://t.co/TbYKyJxqTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @kenolin1   These 90 seconds explain everything about Trump’s base and how they “give” the news and… https://t.co/ngi6Xf8Q1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MajorMarkB @seanmdav @Uncle_Jimbo They infiltrate through caliphate instead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did I get so lucky to have 135 valentines this year? We are celebrating eachother and our loved ones here at… https://t.co/AGr0NEnE7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday afternoon FREE DDD class 😊.  Deeva~Nation  Deeva~Spirit https://t.co/wn79zfo19n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSon0fGod @TweetOfSpirit @SonOfGodAndMan @NotSonOfGod @realGrimReaper_ https://t.co/K3rZSC6WF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, we are‼️💪🏻👭 Happy #InternationalWomensDay ‼️ #BalanceForBetter https://t.co/xKvqABbzoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjaminwittes He has made a mockery of his oath, honor, integrity and citizenship. He is a disgrace. He may have… https://t.co/Qjg12h2IoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrantHorvath1 @Marcus_Freeman1 @GoBearcatsFB @UC_Recruiting @CoachFick Congratulations Grant! Excited for you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if iPhones just collected a collage of your Face ID’s and sent it to you at the end of the year? #thatwouldbewild #2019momentums]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time is up @SIAJaguars! Team Blue was able to complete the mission while Team Red fell a bit short! #WEareTheKEY… https://t.co/jTnI58ywd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherryngick @EveryLibrary Is this shirt from @EveryLibrary or another site?  Gonna need that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no ifs with God, Faith Rev Eddie Payne @ First Agape Baptist Church (Pastor Eddie Micheal Payne) https://t.co/DEH1Gpjw8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reddogsusie Anyone out there with empty nest? Kids gone? Grandkids don't call? Here's two ole gals that could fill the empty n your heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to see Pinkalicious at @lnkplayhouse with Liem!!! @ Lincoln Community Playhouse https://t.co/tW4G58zINf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we talk about how @MarenMorris can wear any color and it looks like HER COLOR 🧡 Also don’t forget #GIRL comes o… https://t.co/ybhOzfjDqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foi por pouco! 😜🤘🏼#oscar2019 #dolbytheatre #hollywood #familytrip #baristalife #iwasthere em Dolby Theatre https://t.co/KLQmok7Ti4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxCarRentals having a terrible experience in your Denver location. My flight got delayed the car I booked is not… https://t.co/bY4r90Oana]]></document><document><![CDATA[Billie Jean King liked a tweet of mine today. Repeat, OMG BILLIE JEAN KING LIKED MY TWEET! https://t.co/JLg6rqXHR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grayson told me to come to an unofficial party at west quad and my first thought was if the pool would be open 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FitChickFriday Repost from jhaas_photography kelsey_haas #flex #muscle #bodybuilding #strength #gym #lift… https://t.co/JJOkZwqkcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Don't know why you're surprised you're stupid crooked and always have been]]></document><document><![CDATA[ITS SUPER EARLY IN THE MORNING BUT HEY YO WESTERBERG!!! @HeathersMusical #HeathersUK #HeathersUKalbum https://t.co/qauAIaIWJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylor_shirey14 @HailStateSB @leilua18 @TysonGRodgers You’re killing it on international women’s day. Slay, girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_BigD1966_ @brainburp13 Democracts Don't Get Investigated! ONLY Conservatives!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 0 WALNUT AVE #Hamilton #NJ  #realestate https://t.co/7umLurS0zB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else have dreams about drinking mad water after a night of drinking and wake up like https://t.co/0Sz3cYkNIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUNDAY @ 6:00 pm BLACK@HISTORY MONTH CELEBRATION Music, Dance, Poems and more!!! @ Faith Christian Center https://t.co/fd8OqTvHzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Pal Such as Svengoolie… https://t.co/1A3ayUhFAI https://t.co/glLm4xvSJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ mothernature my pasty white skin is in DESPERATE need of some vitamin D. For the love of God, can you pls stop SN… https://t.co/PiZmH0njBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Sounds like rhetoric. He's been there long enough to know. He's just creating doubt and turbulence. Not helping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No fr though !!! Whether she did it intentionally or not!! This isn’t the first or second time... it’s not the wome… https://t.co/SqU6xuwsMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m missing Cali and sending love to my home so I’ll throwback to when to when I was being a true California girl v… https://t.co/J1xbty0rTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rockstar fashion accessories by celebrity designer @BettyMalo of bettybaddcouture  All New Collections! Now Availab… https://t.co/n40q86vzED]]></document><document><![CDATA[God Bless Rep. Elijah Cummings!  @RepCummings  @realDonaldTrump @VP @SenateDems @HouseDemocrats @HouseGOP @SenateGOP  @TheDemocrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@rkelly Tick-tock motherfucker   R. Kelly charged in Illinois with aggravated criminal sexual abuse  https://t.co/atjJSwuZlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivaVinophile @CorksConcierge @pietrosd @jflorez @cuvee_corner @Friscokid49 @CaththeWineLady @_drazzari @magee333… https://t.co/jNN2O0W8A2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustJared Her looks just are all busted on her. Fashion maven is not her bag. she's better off just being heard an… https://t.co/GLsje0fxxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say that bc that was me &amp; my toxic ex’s first baile/date together 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was driving through Pontiac today and im honestly surprised my tires are not shot considering how bad so e of those roads are]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well this easy schedule is going really really well so far for the @Raptors]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the substitute teacher would have went about her day this all could have been avoided. A grown person decided to… https://t.co/wXBIu4aWbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt &amp; I have two “songs” and both are @chancetherapper songs. Naturally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little sex pot hopes everyone is having a fantastic Thursday 😍😍😍 https://t.co/4QSeAmAK8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeSautterOWH @OWHnews @omahabryanbears @BryanHoops This is such a beautiful piece 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheriseguilfoil @KeelDrahcir @Ramtheramman @Wblscott1 @Brenderm1 @RNinMI @Bro_Charlie_ @Navy_Lady_45 @Lisette_72… https://t.co/6kJHsSslDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Servers bitching at consumers for not covering their employers’ borderline illegal wages is ignorant as hell. Take… https://t.co/gEaC7l2pm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Someday, someone will best me. But it won’t be today. And it won’t be you”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I think abt how I almost got punched in the face junior year in math bc I told some guy to shut up and he… https://t.co/AclbX86JR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[THY LOVING KINDNESS          Thy Loving Kindness Is Better Than Life; Thy Loving Kindness Is Better Than Life. My L… https://t.co/67uhRa6jrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your students use synergy and successfully complete the #marshmallowchallenge! 💡📏 These kids are really… https://t.co/wFBtRpkppk]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the people who voted for Luka Doncic to win rookie of the year over my favorite rookie Trae Young  didn't watch… https://t.co/Z8q4w5IWV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the hell is this #fireball thing in the #sky #ugh #icouldbesleeping #nightowl @ Fredon, New Jersey https://t.co/hnfcO4ZhdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just trying to get some game day Chick-fil-A today. Apparently there is a 5K running in front of Chick-fil-A on… https://t.co/9BnHuIXbjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowy #longrun of 10 miles this morning to finish off week 9 of #marathontraining at the cabin. Legs were rested bu… https://t.co/kb1S0Zinpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drnazimapathan How to measure intestinal barrier integrity? Biomarkers of epithelia damage (IFABP), Claudin-3, dia… https://t.co/kE14ePfoEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you aren't responsible enough to register on your own you aren't responsible enough to vote]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenBlumenthal Interesting banner on your page The American People have had #ENOUGH of you Democrats refusing to se… https://t.co/Bbb6BepYy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VancityReynolds I didn't know @deadpoolmovie had such big boobies. https://t.co/lnEfiGX9Er]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMonteroOficial Sr tiene que vivir aquí para sufrir en carne propia lo qué pasa nuestra gente. Solo quieren una re… https://t.co/FSgQVA1oLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am sure Trump is doing this to encourage them to turn from their evil ways while he autographs Bibles for all.]]></document></documents></author>