<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝😍😘 @latina @latinas… https://t.co/4iSaSGJGjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 I love how he always presents well known facts as his discoveries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman She’s such a coward like her traitor husband that she’ll only go to red states. Count on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajthebanker @JSEditorBrandon Ok, so we just had a brief delay at the Madison Co Commission meeting to ask the gent… https://t.co/BY3R27NEUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaprincess07 Not me bc my friend almost bought the place...basically got outbid soooo if cards fall right this time 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorenshleby What's the preferred term??  I know plenty of them and that's how they've always referred to themselve… https://t.co/f3RKtV8fPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join me this Tuesday in supporting the fight against opioid addiction with Darryl &amp; Tracy Strawberry… https://t.co/umJC5hLP8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grams just said “you got the job, now you can start makin money, get a girlfriend and take her out on dates”   ... yeah if only]]></document><document><![CDATA[#865life #basketball #collegebasketball #collegelife #sports #sportsphotography #vols #tennessee #florida #gators… https://t.co/2mT3zzLkBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisfitsTamara I don't get that either. IMO, Martian Manhunter should be the tallest and I'd like my Batman just a… https://t.co/eLOTQJqMTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greenbay4lyfe @USWNT Same. Hopefully when can beat Brazil with japan and England tie. Key word is beat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Black Metallic Stout by @ArrogantBastard @ Space Above The Sink — https://t.co/gAsd0TxFnN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeff_gluck The #fords have shown they have the discipline to line up and stick to a plan  .... the bottom will be where it’s at Sunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calvin81156899 @JoniMullock @davematt88 @PressSec @realDonaldTrump Your too interested in my ass. Not surprised th… https://t.co/q3G5A4c1PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[im looking for a specific junmyeon picture that i suddenly don't have UHHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING Tres años de carcel para el ex pitcher mexicano Loaiza.  https://t.co/ogoULpsW93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewMcWeeny I can still do Burt’s little hand maneuver to make himself invisible]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure there will be plenty to criticize in anyone who throws their hat into the GOP primary in 2020, but I will… https://t.co/7eWySGqSry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hometown show in Nashville makes this even better! ⚡️🔥✔️ · · · · · · #fleetwoodmac #bridgestonearena #nashville @ B… https://t.co/cY8DIjLuLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI that's less than a $50 per week pay cut. If that's what stands between you and starvation you need to reevaluat… https://t.co/6ErOP5GQk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterHoskinsTV I think the merch deficit is the one that is being effected the most by the new tarriffs. Its where… https://t.co/5u7FCtkKWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all my women friends and colleagues happy international women’s day ... 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hqtrivia @RPMatthews Yes I took the survey. No I did not get to fill in my username, because there was no spot. It… https://t.co/nIMpPRcLMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en US Army Fort Benning https://t.co/vk4ps2bpr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posted withrepost • makeupbycory777 #edgarallanpoe my all time favorite #genius ⭐🌠🙏  #poetry #dream #dreamers… https://t.co/XT9y62PAuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEGAL MARRIAGE TRUTH JUSTICE JURSDICTION ACTION NATIONAL SECURITY JUSTICE JURSDICTION AUTHORITY. 2. ANTI-AMERICAN R… https://t.co/qm43IuVKPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got slapped the fuck out of tonight. That was wild. I also did nothing to deserve it. Literally nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alienate friends and family with &amp;quot;super realistic&amp;quot; masks based on your pets https://t.co/Z7icZbkcHf via @AV_Newswire]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans like @DevinNunes have obstructed Justice long enough. This is long overdue.  https://t.co/m57QP8n8pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Irisheyesrye @chuckwoolery Ok that’s two now. I stand corrected. But Ford was speaker of the house and none the le… https://t.co/4Y0pFLxALA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesireeNavarro Que pasaría que después que Trump saliera de la Casa Blanca se fuera a trabajar con una empresa ext… https://t.co/lGyaEvrs6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wally B from Tennessee for PRESIDENT IN THE WORLD OF AVIATIONS EXPERIENCES WITH ME VOTE YES FOR PROGRESS AND I WILL… https://t.co/gj9BK4pYgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnitersCentrist Actually, his only contribution. 🤡 #NeverTrump #LiarInChief #CountryOverParty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DBYankees1 Hal also noted he is not against long-term contracts, but in assessing need, did not feel infield or ou… https://t.co/kYSIX9ymNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently listening in the office now. Some things are just too heavy and evil for some people. The power of the ri… https://t.co/2xmUy45dBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wise man vs. Intelligent man  This is so so good ... never had I know these  profound distinctions between *Intelli… https://t.co/PxcD89oRY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just talking in my DMs about people getting divorced, like you do. I kinda understand why it's hard, but guys, I wa… https://t.co/kUqXG6zbVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate Crimes on in increase. Or should it say  F  A L S E hate crimes on the increase. Build the Wall Mr. President… https://t.co/5PjPCqcSbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Denies Calling Apple CEO 'tIM Apple' — Despite Being on Camera Next to Ivanka: Report #Topbuzz https://t.co/llZar4bfHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Addison, TX, check out this job: https://t.co/IaDlKXwf8f #HR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redsteeze From the same people that insert "without evidence" when citing anything Trump asserts, as though the no… https://t.co/yDuQSWR0GY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CleveFan4ever @Madaketjay @JasonLaCanfora Chris Ballard came from Kansas City as well. Colts have huge cap space p… https://t.co/1Cqu76xDxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFreeze7 #BigDogSunday Ranger, Ocean Twp , NJ ready for St. Patrick’s Day! https://t.co/4rebiOG0Ly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy video inside the town of #Henryville  as an EF4 tornado 🌪 rips through. 7 years ago today.   OFFICIAL HENRYVI… https://t.co/nMmzdGQp0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[New DIA pop art exhibition revisits the whimsy and turbulence of the '60s and '70s https://t.co/2eMTyZnez3]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you have a home, please consider planting a pair of these for pollination and if you see the possibility to devo… https://t.co/Asvi4M7fAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Event announcement from growatncf SAVE THE DATE! This is our year to Refresh and Reboot, join us Friday, March 29th… https://t.co/GucQQM8pb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Founder of the company I work for said he respects my hustle . First person to ever tell me that...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dustin_Haueter @YoungToeSucker_ @KarsonFletcher @LowLevelTHUG @brianapacheco_ @jaidyn_e @itssskell It’s super far… https://t.co/gL1OtmlDX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sh0rtStackFilms the streaming game and I need to figure out a couple things. I am currently using Elgato but thinking about using OBS WITH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was today when I learned it’s “Cardiac Kemba” and not “Party at Kemba”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tested out the zeisscameralenses 135mm Batis lens on @nikitaesco . I’ve been fairly addicted to this spectacular ap… https://t.co/BAhwyB7xF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CassandraDawnxo @instagram Me too.  By the time I see them it’s too late to comment 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Did anyone buy it? If not, I’ve got a $200 peanut butter and jelly one too 🥪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Suite MNO by @sapwoodcellars at @sapwoodcellars — https://t.co/Hyw35SArfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[17 month Canadian girl from #Nigeria  boxes c metal strapping in #living room just $20 to them. Dad went back. Retu… https://t.co/Adzgt6oj8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBearPitTV Why was he fleeing the gang if they have his watch should be the other way around]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why hasn’t @realDonaldTrump tweeted or commented about the white nationalist domestic terrorist busted this week wi… https://t.co/FAUNunZBPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[And don't we know, this is going to cause a big stink, I agree with you Charlie]]></document><document><![CDATA[The scientist who coined "Global Warming." Well worth a read about a giant in #ClimateChange research passing. Wish… https://t.co/Zr1ikEOPRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryDMayer @SearchQueen @RepDanCrenshaw Why are their kids in school? That also shouldn't happen unless they are… https://t.co/9nLxxmZ4Sv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson The only reason you’re president is because you had Russia hack our election. Trump… https://t.co/aa43qE9Lhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBallImmersion This essentially “blocker mover”, which Blazers have run a lot of variations of in the past correct?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olivia_mutant @EmDashPython @BuntyBrown What do you reckon, like Gilroy? Livermore? Antioch?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re gettin there mom. Space out the agreed and @dwcase and you’re good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought spring break was this week, turns out I have a test tomorrow 🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayPowe19766626 @PureMichGirl @dumspirospero64 https://t.co/zgDA1JfAoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily Unvarnished Jesus Lenten meditations are available on my Instagram and the @WOLC Facebook page. https://t.co/62tky6Sb1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a Snow Day Tomorrow. Uncle Richard has the Hot Chocolate out already. @netflix in the afternoon @ Harlem https://t.co/Q0pUZRGZTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hockeyjunkie88 @isaiahholt10 @ProjectAvant But the point of the original conversation is pointing out a difference… https://t.co/VBxXVdMz5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am also not going to run for Presidentbin 2020! But I will help stop criminal Manchurian Candidate Trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awf4hf Zach Lowe is really good too. He doesn’t get talked about enough because of Woj and Shams]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapiYogii @Word2myKnicks Die straight or be gay and Live forever shit the chooses 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jersey Street Trivia Time!  In what year was the first game played at the Detroit Tigers Comerica Park?  Don't look… https://t.co/Ocfgd9aiMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#photography by #marinachoy #tvwriting #screenwriting #amediting #amwriting #amrewriting #writingmusic #scriptnotes… https://t.co/Q5BQAThXnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBATheJumpFP Ewing was well past his prime if you mean messing up the cap for the trade is correct but not because… https://t.co/GZBDfCwkZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jake_browning @les7spellman I hope you reach that next level! Thanks for making Husky Football Great Again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not gonna comment too much on the Jussie situation out of respect to victims of hate crimes ... but #JamalLying is hilarious]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to be back in the States 🇺🇸 @ LECOM Suncoast Classic https://t.co/HeZNn1htkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren How about enabling businesses to thrive wherein people can work their way up the economic ladder instead o… https://t.co/XldUz4t6VM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had the best Cuban sandwich and devil crab of my life. Hands down. Tastes just like my Cuban great grandmother… https://t.co/kmQdC82D6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_Dubner @RotoViz Gotcha, so it just isn’t displayed? Perhaps that was my confusion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just proves the @DNC’s corrupt alignment with the biased networks @NBCNews @CBSNews @ABC @CNN @MSNBC @PBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Diary,  I have been craving Red Baron breakfast pizzas for the past 4 days, I can't seem to get my mind off of… https://t.co/fmHd5TnTgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcwrighthammer2 2 pizzas, 2 big pizzas...Xtra Large...everything on them...&lt;so forth&gt; https://t.co/84sHbZE5pT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confetti/lightning bolts from my Refractor Piano™! #pianist #piano https://t.co/lhAGKwZDpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apollo 13 is easily one of the greatest movies of all time. Absolutely brilliant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sex robots are here, but laws aren’t keeping up with the ethical and privacy issues they raise #Topbuzz https://t.co/WBYmhz4m79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobPattersonJr1 @TheRealPest @DavidWohl Sounds like y’all some white supremacists. Y’all never fucked a Muslim chick?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hm, maybe I should double-dip on Captain Toad with this update... (I got the Wii U version)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WAC_Blackout @ESSManMurphy @Dolliecrooks @B1LL_Iam @Alyssa_Milano Whacked out on adderal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beer_pig @untappd Can you send me the checkin url? We can take a.look at it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bummed I missed @RemoDrive at my show in Springfield the other night. Realized they’re playing Denver tomorrow righ… https://t.co/ZaBSlyBDsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know if that DSJ was worth a 50 but it was damn near close. That was tough #NBAAllStar]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ended up only having three good pictures from my entire trip to KC in September, but I couldn’t be more happy tha… https://t.co/YOXb9bsUtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chloemmx Stop shopping in "sizes" like a child then and figure out how many inches your waist is and buy your pant… https://t.co/WGXmzyDMo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Phish Returns From Breakup 10 Years Ago Today: Jamming Through The Years https://t.co/UeVFKNvcAJ via @JamBase]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great day to go outside to the creek park. 🤓 🌭🍔🥤🥃🐕🐩🏞⚽️🚴‍♂️🚴‍♀️🚵‍♂️🚵‍♀️🏊‍♂️🏊‍♀️ @ Onion Creek Park https://t.co/scv1DvQjGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Girth-Quake aka (@CouRageJD @timthetatman and @BasicallyIDoWrk) are the most entertaining streamers... change m… https://t.co/te04I0QqZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time do not proceed with a partner knowing the have a child on the way with another woman #Karma]]></document></documents></author>