<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SallyTurnerNews @nowthisnews @LindseyGrahamSC @SenateGOP #InternationalWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[(There's plenty of other random parts that make no sense but that's the important part)]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re down subs in the building, nothing’s better than helping out your fellow @GRMSTBirds teachers and cover… https://t.co/KEdidS5swt]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one:  Me on my period: stfu get out of my face. I hate you. Wait I’m sorry https://t.co/LslJW4kaEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord, show us opportunities to tell our children who you are and what you’ve done in our lives.  Impress truth on t… https://t.co/cXWGBWie9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abbaacabsa ለቀምት ምን ሆነ? የሚሰራውን ኢትዬጽያኑን እባራችሁ ዝንብ ወረረችሁ። አሁንም ሰው የስራ ውን ለመቀማት ሰፍ አልችሁ። የለም። ሰርትችሁ ኑሩ።]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t sat in a college classroom in...well let’s not count the years...it was pretty fun! I don’t necessarily c… https://t.co/WRCsQwiSuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevenmnuchin1 @MickMulvaneyOMB @SecPompeo @SecElaineChao @AmbJohnBolton @SecAzar @SecAzar]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot stand being sick. I just want my mommy and two big ole shots in my booty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@planetjared At that rate, you’re going to sleep through Duke/UNC...for the next several years...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wutan) - Asian Glow Don Mills) https://t.co/ZAQdTNJONE via @YouTube I tell you  don mills wutan songs just be lifti… https://t.co/vtsYUQWV2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@29rain Ask men for money and sleep  with them u need to be realistic  this the real word this why I been I been te… https://t.co/bC9IVFx6Gr]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are sooo many great things coming my way this year, I already know it 🙏🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimfakeshow @graedrake @WolfgangPuck Grae!!! You look way too fierce for yourself in the photo!  Werk👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooooooooo... I want to play!!! One of my fave Pastors sent out a challenge to get creative on this beat... and I… https://t.co/p6ovPhp3hr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait til Game if thrones new season is on🥺 I could cry right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@undethebltarp @JohnJHarwood Ssdd! Reagan economics! Bullshit then! Bullish now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at this beautifully golden purse! 😁👀💖🦄 Love them photo shoots. 👀🦄 #photoshoot #photooftheday #smallbusiness… https://t.co/3P7zY3GYeP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imhartshorn @Auricchio_Laura @2nerdyhistgirls @ellencarmichael @RBrookhiser @sarageorgini Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait to see you sing tonight... What songs are you singing??? https://t.co/YeKNP4qeJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephyB79 The kid’s already on the right track. He’s smarter than most people I know. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Please address this National Emergency immediately. Democrats are American citizens, and we have a… https://t.co/74tVFA0P4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come to #NCTIES19 and join me for Google Classroom for Littles on Friday at 9am in RCC-303! Get your Classroom up a… https://t.co/qkHPl1kXmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@COLUMNAVIVEROS @PANLegisladores @alejandralopesn @GildardoReal @eduardo_urbina_ @pauliieC @PROSYCONTRAS1… https://t.co/Uzj09PYMKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[FumiDesigns Spring Collection 2018   Link in bio. . . . #fumidesigns #nycdesigner #nyc #brooklyn #fashion… https://t.co/oSCdpI1sYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top Dollar Drama  Pink and white rhinestone encrusted bands stack across the finger for a glamorous look. Features… https://t.co/Ah0BbJiUFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Guess again!!! RIDICULOUS!!!!! ABSURD!!!!!  #NotMyPresidentEVER]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love it when the guys I follow like or comment on nudes on twitter so they pop up in my feed. 🤣  I totally needed t… https://t.co/kRV5W7f90S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moonfloat LMAO true and I agree! but overall I loved the intensity of the season and I wish they’d bring back the true horror elements]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve laughed more in the past two months than I have in the past two years. Toxic relationships and people are the worst lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amid hostile federal policies, Philadelphia has taken a stand to remain welcoming to immigrants. Philadelphia recen… https://t.co/oxnEI3HGOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewartHaasRcng @Aric_Almirola @LVMotorSpeedway @SmithfieldBrand @FordPerformance You did great yesterday ! Man U… https://t.co/nox4ESZdoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job @chaseelliott !! Only one who wanted to race tonight !! Others like to play follow the leader !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trzpical_ @PontiacMadeDDG @queennaija She ft on his song 🙃 &amp; @queennaija told him to release their song 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justaskcb @Rsanso1234San @seanspicer @extratv @SecPompeo @KellyannePolls @SarahHuckabee Done]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the man in the halls yesterday, who was carrying a GIANT Coug flag/blanket (??), hat and umbrella, that replied… https://t.co/02mJ7W28de]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just signed a petition: Don’t let Mitch McConnell kill democracy reform. Sign here: https://t.co/htsklHimzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obsessed is an understatement. Are you kidding me with this dog treat box?! (@ The Cosmopolitan of Las Vegas -… https://t.co/Aq2fXdD1t7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to the homies who motivated me to go to the gym... a hueva pero si fui 💪🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InqPotosky @gina__salvatore @ChamblessHayden @erinkatedolan @JPerkins_Eagle @DianeStopyra @eden_laase @halliehart… https://t.co/R4tyDcHpUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So he would be manipulating foreign policy for his personal gain? Sounds about right. And I am sure the GOP will be… https://t.co/CtRmzaGt7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Fiesta Fiesta I’ve been crushing on all these gorgeous #fiestaware posts so I decided to start collecting too! Her… https://t.co/3eGwrbb7sk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@witchbabysoap @simonschuster @adamsmedia @ericsmithrocks @PSLiterary Thank you!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: hi my name is jamie and im addicted to drugs, alcohol, and the bbc nature documentary “south pacific” narrated… https://t.co/fQtMuRPkpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhodgesEDU Yup. Would love to see you or attend your session if you're presenting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este hombre se merece lo mejor del mundo y junto con los que lo apoyan. https://t.co/UAW0fSzbfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[KM vs Simley 126 @robbyhorsman @kometwrestling @KM_Activities @DCISports https://t.co/Sc78idwmDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like the last two seasons have all been “the most dramatic season ever” 🤷🏽‍♀️🌹 #Thebachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted to be first woman president. (I had already picked my VP — Hillary Rodham Clinton. Heh.)   Also, I ate cat… https://t.co/RkCEpDPcTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I should be doing: cleaning litter boxes. Things I am doing: https://t.co/FZP7DDSWFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tammi_inCO @LobsterBFFs1 @whitegirlsmooth @BuckeyeCuti @birdtracs @Katie_Elaine012 @lizheileman @tnormandeau22… https://t.co/EeFGWDSBar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, my goal is to actually be asleep before midnight. Let’s see how that goes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We think it’s colder in Nebraska but we’re still ready for #ColdinLA #ColdInLATonight @ImZachHerron @jackaverymusic… https://t.co/RzQkwsyCVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[She injected the cheeks right out of her face so she could have these ridiculous cheekbones but turns out chubby ch… https://t.co/xy6CjCBBNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMossEsq If you enlarge the picture, it looks like he slept in the make-up and hasn’t washed it off.  A portion… https://t.co/tqNjSqfv7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wrapyourhairup #washyourface #brushyourteeth and #gotobed #yougottasinginthemorning #highnotes #needsleep #mascara… https://t.co/UvgAIlRK5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WKCDogShow @WKCDOGS WKC lost all credibility this year. First the botched handling of the Non-Sporting group winne… https://t.co/07TynLpYqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @JudgeJeanine If Fox News heads left, someone  needs to start a new, conservative news channel and a… https://t.co/wlyXYA321R]]></document><document><![CDATA[#T3Learns at #T3IC that kindergarteners enter school with one question ...."WHY?" They are always questioning... https://t.co/kX4BrMdZhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeogiHunt Liar, it was just gonna be me and Frankie and u left me stranded]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when Mexico was paying for the wall? @realDonaldTrump   You ran on that lie didn’t you? Funny how the fake… https://t.co/7bMcAtU0xF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayharrington3 I use to hate working during a full moon...it seemed every weirdo in town would come in...to clarif… https://t.co/H4UpuCaeBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaksgoodangel @ghostofjohanna @Zak_Bagans @hauntedmuseum St. Patty's Day early!☘☘🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJ_2_FL @karli_bonne @marcorubio @realDonaldTrump Shameful! I’m so sorry I ever voted for Romney!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @agaveoil for the sleek locks while I hit the slopes 🏂 https://t.co/CroEubEoxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF. this deadass happened in the back of my dorm. how the fuck did nobody tell us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A @Eyshila1 já tá rouca aqui no carro de tanto que tenho ouvido #SenhorEuTeAmo! 😂 🎤 👩🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why, oh why did I schedule a PT appointment for 9:15 a.m. on my day off tomorrow?!?! I don't even get to sleep in. 🤦🏼‍♀️ #ownworstenemy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really blessed to have a girlfriend that will stop by my house (which is 10 minutes out of her way home) just to ma… https://t.co/AS3McjtdMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottPresler @RealMattCouch Malia is no ones concern! Unless you’re looking for issues.. IF YOU ARE... Look at @JussieSmollett]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HikindDov @SenSchumer @SpeakerPelosi @IlhanMN @tv7israelnews and the biggest mole did know everything he knew more… https://t.co/InAgUbwWYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_victorialarson We plan on it we just don’t have anything set in stone yet 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealTT2020 @adjunctprofessr @realDonaldTrump Yep, thats exactly why Hillary will run again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@umontana students- we are ready for you at the @MontanaGrizWBB game!  #gogriz https://t.co/29g8SRBcSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[On March 4, 2005 I walked out of prison. I was released in Chicago in men’s clothes and a windbreaker with $28 in m… https://t.co/NBETmRKKmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just speak Gummi! I want to know what your accent is? Do you have mine??? Or do you sound American like Daddy??]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s all I can do to stay awake right now. Hoping I’ll find my bed soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got family time with .@karleeseevers to go out to eat in Palm Springs CA. We walk into the restaurant and t… https://t.co/1E3JLCfpQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoamingInsomnia @GeorgeTakei Yes cancer does suck and pancreatic cancer sucks the most.  I lost my mom to it 6 yea… https://t.co/vuDTyD4DgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NDMikeBrey @HesburghFilm Love fr Ted   He was true legend and amazing man . He was so awesome. I can’t wait to see… https://t.co/n7beO9xFSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re in the La Crosse area stop by and see my brilliant friend BZ!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[TUES FEB 19th 7pm NO COVER! The NANNY TRIVA How much do you really know about FRAN??? Make reservations now online!… https://t.co/cyZ8MPP2K6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sum of a bitch!! @YouTube and @soulasylum it’s gonna be along night!! Thank you for good inspiration and music!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙💙Start the day off right 💙💙  #SundayMotivation #MotivationalQuotes #PositiveVibes #positivity #PositiveEnergy… https://t.co/iC9CPUkg24]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stellaacquisto @BlairCrgn @DinaPugliese What a little beauty. Love baby neck wrinkles. Congratulations again Stella]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little man with delusions. #SHAME #IMPEACHTRUMP and lock up his minions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all are interested in stocks @Stash is an extremely intuitive app!! https://t.co/W3mOLu8k2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HAVE H.I.V PUBLIC INTERVIEW🤢‼️ ( I GOT PUNCHED IN THE FACE!!!) https://t.co/flL8PS7aFL via @YouTube new video !!… https://t.co/1QAzalxJCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manuelgarcesjr @jamesvarlack @JuarezLincolnHS I love David Rice and his books.  My class invited him to come to ou… https://t.co/pLAGmpXEap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seliw59 @TwoInTheBushes @rfragan @ffoxxface @ProudResister @Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump No. I'm not an idiot. A… https://t.co/wC3piFXIku]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had a quarter for every time my man said something cliche Aquarius or Sagittarius I would be rich.  My current… https://t.co/TF2eqqqkFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisWiegman I would totally be up for something like this given a few things happen this spring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only reason I’m fw this social media stuff right now cause I’m still in the car]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Yorkers frustrated with Democratic dominance push bill to slice up state https://t.co/DuwZ0gP3lA via @washtimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Choco Hazelnut Wharf Patrol by @humble_sea at @humble_sea — https://t.co/21iiz3O96M]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's often so damn grouchy...but he's a fucking genius and American treasure  #SpikeLee n @ladygaga wins the best m… https://t.co/DARuXaM20E]]></document><document><![CDATA[My freshman year someone legit asked me if I lived next to the Toys R Us in Time Square-the one with the Ferris whe… https://t.co/LOWQGT4f2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a homework assignment due at 11pm and yet here I am watching tastemade ... in Japanese]]></document><document><![CDATA[This brisket, forking tender! . . . . . . . #sundaydinner #brisket #grainfedbeef #organic #carrots #brisket101… https://t.co/VaaULTjEsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[iii Points VIP Ticket for sale $250 Original price: $375 SZA plays today and A$ap Rocky tomorrow  DM Me #iiipoints… https://t.co/n3qSw0JKJi]]></document></documents></author>