<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KielNotKyle @kpccheer @NCAupdates @bleedinginteal Girl next to jada opposite of Diana is like y’all we about to fu… https://t.co/Dw5dFYcGqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyDCash Your comments aren’t blocked. Not sure what you are talking about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DontTouchMyWine We retired old bald guys hardly notice a thing cuz we’re sleeping in 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello #Montreal 😍☃️ Head Judging @OfficialHHI #Canada Hip Hop Dance Championship Laval Regionals this weekend! Can’… https://t.co/jHnLyrWrXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[About a crowler deep here in Englewood.  This is how we measure snow depth in Colorado. #9wx @ Englewood, Colorado https://t.co/7tTyrk4h7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paul Schrader, writer of Taxi Driver, Raging Bull, and First Reformed, does not have an Academy Award. Fun fact I guess!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Yo lil nigga, come out ya ashy ass feet on my head, I’m trynna see sum”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lestat's on Park - @lestatsblog in San Diego, CA https://t.co/sGwanshWlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling out of sorts today but far to busy with errands to hide under a rock, time to be running for the next 3-4 hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coimbra1990 @panchocevallosv @jacuentasbsc @HRUGEL Y no saben de fútbol y nadie habla de eso.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingsthings Please do an interview with Oscar winning actress Mo’Nique. She just started her Las Vegas residency a… https://t.co/jbmfUAT2c9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, #CaptainMarvel.  Brilliant. Absolutely.  Loved Carol before.   Love her more now.  PS: Kudos to @Marvel on the… https://t.co/wtUum9qi2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Design challenge: demonstrate understanding by creating meiosis “in motion”. Ss are exploring complexity of chromos… https://t.co/Z5trsqbyjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[por lo menos nos iba mejor a todos con los corruptos, había inversión, estancias infantiles, refugios para mujeres,… https://t.co/ZmOxdcrKa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7Jory I’m totally bummed out about Alex. Jeopardy has been a tradition in my family. I started watching it with… https://t.co/V76213aVKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cpickslay What benefits do you see them getting?  Corollary: What problems have you seen that you think this would… https://t.co/BAI3WPuWWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta find my way to your heart just like you managed to get inside mine...]]></document><document><![CDATA[After trailing 9-0 to open the game Bryant has cut it to 16-13 Northside with 3:43 left in the 1st half @THV11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snoop Dogg Wants the Lakers Shipped Out on a ‘Slave Ship’ https://t.co/bPAs6J8FCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, sometimes I lay in bed and remember that Sandra Bullock won both best and worts actress awards in the same y… https://t.co/0PEAIhLhGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[All New Cars To Have Speed Limiters Fitted, Rules European Parliament via @forbes https://t.co/LUH8hcTxcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickyRayada @futpicante @mexicoworldcup @Rayados @AlonsoDT Tienes razon y como es rayados no le dan merito .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@polotglass Probably did lol but damn boy got choked out, punched and still ejected 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annabrice @TCrescen @martinonyc @metsfanmurph1 What on her resume qualifies her? That she was a great softball player? Enlighten me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Baker McKenzie Annual PDAC Reception . . . @yyzevents ilikebeingsteve #beingsteve #ilikebeingsteve… https://t.co/fENENkdRmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[When folks are so panicked and don’t realize there’s an exact amendment process. Sad where education has gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Profiting From Pain  Read Romans 5:1-5  We have so many blessings for which to be grateful. And greatest of all is… https://t.co/45TJ2h0g9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbz_8513 Hit a 4 step drop back like he was finna hit @AB84 for a 50 yarder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sicko mode is nice but future did the two songs in one better with Throw away]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Vs. The guys she tells you not to worry about #Crew96 https://t.co/PyP3T0gXEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting a few years ago, I stopped introducing my surname as yu-eh, and started only using the proper pronunciatio… https://t.co/goqfSh9Jb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maketto1351 @barredindc Was your Pastry Chef able to get back her recipe book that was stolen with her backpack? I… https://t.co/LzaJ1koToP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dakich: "The push off on offense always gets called."  ::Ethan Happ pushes off a defender. No foul::  Dakich: "INDI… https://t.co/vPrdb88jHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont disrespect the Legends of this sport who paved the way for young unappreciative fighters like you just trying… https://t.co/lF6leQAHI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Pauly D voice* If she doesn’t understand this, SHE’S TOO YOUNG FOR YOU, BRO! https://t.co/eZeNd1l0Z2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tankotanko013 Yea dude love was aight even his worse character was loved lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m happy to announce that I’ll be joining 92.1 @TheTeamSports out of Tyler, Texas.   Very excited to be back in sports radio.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hunterhart2000 Yes they did. It’s just nice to see a coach actually follow NCAA protocol — even though I despise its idea of “amateurism”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Real_3hundred @Alex_Mecca4Ever @shadworld0131 @GILA_____ @PantherNasty @Retro_JordanG @MilesisOfficial… https://t.co/kW0rN8zXap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsaacBarnes11 From both sides, I’ll never hate on music without listening]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grab hold of the ones you love, who love you back...the blessing is priceless and timeless #family #love]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bar Shiru. New favorite spot. Hi-fi jazz bar, cocktails, whiskey, biking distance from home. #hifi #accoustics… https://t.co/PmBesN2dHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredNBCLA @RodneyPeete9 @RogginAndRodney @AM570LASports @kfigg1 @vicfeelingyou https://t.co/K4KLxpoPX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coldplay - Always In My Head(Lyrics Video) https://t.co/Qfbk944XRp via @YouTube #Musicmakesourwolrdbetter 🎧🎼🎤🎹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimNashMN I’m not entirely sure I ever paid on that one... https://t.co/IHpM4NGTNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm earning free rewards by collecting points with @FeaturePoints: https://t.co/4dni2V4qbH. Use my link for 50 free points!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se trata de llevar a juicio a quienes violaron los derechos HUMANOS de victimas INOCENTES ajenas al conflicto armad… https://t.co/dQH7HjwBV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukeobxx @kare11 Lowered to what. Luke, why are so you triggered and angry? I truly just want to follow up and ask… https://t.co/LsnZhCrhGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump It is not the Democrats! It is the majority of American people who  see Trump not… https://t.co/fAUIIvZ3JT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realdumbrunner @Nolan_Waters87 You know how people unfollow you because of your views on guns? Ready Player One is… https://t.co/AxB8F3FefU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not sure where the Disco Inferno segments are going, but I'm in! #ImpactWrestling https://t.co/xUlhdRD0KU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigjun31 Stuff like that tho doesn’t help current situation that’s what would irk me as a fan like if y’all could… https://t.co/jMyw4Gktbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mickmillsap @JoyceWhiteVance @BarbMcQuade @mayawiley @Mimirocah1 Exactly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidanElt @ELGazette @11thhourspecial Haha sure. I have a student right now with that goal. I try to redirect. When… https://t.co/4HDTvAQMMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeleMomodu Dele, with whatever name you disguise, be it known to you that you can't successfully reach my level. Y… https://t.co/ZW7Hv2qKu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually screamed NO when i saw this on my phone 📱....I'm completely stunned. https://t.co/XrWX6xKqkf #LukePerry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy ending to this week’s episode. Only two left! Listen and subscribe!! #TrueDetective https://t.co/P3PCBXxwkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite anime is a town where you live. Its soo fucking good https://t.co/BfzmxywvGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, did she put in a dress to go to Dolby Theater when no one was there to imply she was at the Oscars? https://t.co/JLY6GOfIdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. said @gabbs415 and I simultaneously as we walked by. @ Boston Architectural College https://t.co/vqRHEywnIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @ColinCFSmith and thanks for hosting your first eNASCAR Heat Pro League draft @ISMRaceway 👍👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[It can't be visible diversity Or cognitive diversity. You need both. https://t.co/HmC4iw4o9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on Dry Gap Pike #Knoxville #TN  #realestate https://t.co/sRhnS4fBD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in September I was kayaking in Kevin Tovornik’s neighborhood, inundated by fecally infused toxic floodwaters c… https://t.co/cS0QPzryXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShiftParadigm @HarveyAlvy1 @sgthomas1973 I can get more accomplished chatting with a teacher between classes than… https://t.co/s48wyRO18k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sick I just started a St. Patty’s day twitter war between all Michigan Colleges and slid out of the madness unnotic… https://t.co/JoZxNQCgGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old solo clip I just found from the @jazzisphish show in SD last year 🙌🏼 @ San Diego, California https://t.co/7Rql0RsX0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tyra_Martin Factssss broken toes and all we still walking to Starbucks at 4am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats and thanks to whoever is posting these video highlights. FANTASTIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dreamers and creators are beginning to populate our first ever #BloxelsEDUchat class...won't you be the next to… https://t.co/Y7dpTf0YlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why you get yourself a can of chew, partner 👌🏼killing smoking one pinch at a time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something very beautiful about rainy Sunday mornings! #NYCrealestate #WellStagedProperties #ManhattanLuxury #NYC… https://t.co/bFtGFu1wav]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityCinemasNYC @AzolandPictures Thank you for giving us such a fun and quality viewing in NYC! 🎸 https://t.co/HRAY7e9l5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmichaelDave It’s the exact same thing as Next Door...  “I heard something, was it a gunshot? No, it was firecrackers” 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @MarquardtA @TheLeadCNN Nope.  But I bet Trump would sell him weapons of any type if Trump gets a cut.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarrySchweikart @Dflorill Finally someone sees what I seen when I started reading this stuff. Democrats are out th… https://t.co/XSdilUcm1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what you read or see over the next few days. There is always 2 sides to a story FROM: ANGEL ARROYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emeka, I’m so proud of you! When you came to our program, I promised you three things. 1) You’d be required to work… https://t.co/Bi8wt6pnvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just gave the trash disposal people for work the SMOKE while at home in bed sick, don’t try a sick bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zucchini noodles with an arrabiata sauce jalapeno popper stuffed with mozzarella Parmesan and reggiano cheese wrapp… https://t.co/MyESosdIN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it really correct to characterize America as Christian, or is it a free democracy with many devout Christian cit… https://t.co/vov6fqWRqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[To get taken out of the cup, champions league and lose 2 Classicos in a week and our chance at the league this is depressing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone in the cannabis community for sending along tips for edible cookies 🍪 @Shuk_It_Trebek even calcu… https://t.co/iKtDdGLfUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Electabuzz que estas haciendo en la cocina   #GOsnapshot  #pokémonsnap https://t.co/ab3QXpch4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[BUBBLE WATCH LIST  Indiana ✅ Butler ❌ Clemson ❌ Utah State ◾️ Texas ✅ Saint Mary’s ◾️ Georgetown ◾️ Seton Hall ◾️ UCF ✅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came to Peach Valley Cafe, got a table immediately.  It’s a spring break miracle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @SheilaCalloway for an informative presentation on juvenile #justice today at the IMF meeting. Greatly ap… https://t.co/rP6yoSNjlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryDunleavy @EllenPage So sure of yourself. So arrogant. So willing to ignore obvious inconsistencies in Smollet… https://t.co/dRrJGsw8TP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise at the beach house, aren’t you just a sight for sore eyes?? @cwilson0 you make this life worth living!… https://t.co/slTbIn7MSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I’m not gonna fall for it again  Her: Hey  Me: https://t.co/dBNdAKuhgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl is ready for Jeep weather. ☀️ #Jeep #JeepHairDontCare #Asher #MyGirl #JeepGirl #RaiseThemRight @ Seneca,… https://t.co/yTQlhwKPKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Turfgrass_94 @MattGinellaGC @USGA @GCMorningDrive @GolfChannel @chambleebrandel @damonhackGC @RickieFowler That de… https://t.co/N0flsOxXJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#picoftheday #applepodcasts #podcastlife #thenutjob #harryanutz #spotifypodcast #anchorpodcast https://t.co/tgOhdUqaG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿A las cuentas visitas me dan tarjeta de cliente frecuente? https://t.co/AGndomQuye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RegisCollege When are you going to address @FatherRosica's academic fraud extending back 20+ years? #plagiarism #rosicacheats #blameinterns]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cleaning up pools of water in the basement leaking through the floor tiles is a 🔥🔥🔥Saturday night. #fuckyourain]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet another @POTUS "emergency" that is itself the emergency. And Georgia is one of the states where these exemption… https://t.co/QucxQrplL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OllieB_87 @BMS_Billy @BMS_Derek @BMS_Arianna @BMS_Felix @BMS_VoiceGuy @BMS_Show Well ill show you 2...theres one o… https://t.co/Xg06hpnGTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is disgusting. I understand not agreeing with every choice your kid makes but they’re still your CHILD so you… https://t.co/tUQJVvYGG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Ron's Crooked Hill Tavern in Pottstown, PA https://t.co/5b8lx35rmv]]></document></documents></author>