<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@OutnumberedFNC @HARRISFAULKNER @MelissaAFrancis @KatiePavlich @AndrewCMcCarthy miss Fox has just nailed what Cohen… https://t.co/6bocNY2QEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TankSchottle Thank you I have a nephew thats autistic and a cousin too , we all appreciate your support ,love..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakemiller Waiting for @jakemiller to slip into my DMs like https://t.co/595XANdBs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[just wanted to show off my boy ❤️ - - @WillFelts1  and that you to @olivia_shay06 for the 3rd https://t.co/qkz8ayO1tH]]></document><document><![CDATA[for a second there I was worried...but few, I confirmed that I was at work just after 2pm—actually, allafternoon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where does one find a regional bracket for boys basketball and eventually girls? Googled khsaa etc....no luck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natiibedoya Únase al escuadrón de la muerte de 700 “informantes “que conformó el enano malvado y el títere inútil,… https://t.co/ZPAzop3Tdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeytonList You deserve everything you have achieved and deserve much more too. you gave me the confidence to move… https://t.co/rAufldu0gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leave no words unsaid... And don't take any love/friendship for granted. Tomorrow is never a forsure thing. 💓💔… https://t.co/NC9C5EGfc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddbreckrealtor Could be any of us on any given day. Finn was up there w/ his team. I couldn't breath until his coa… https://t.co/HLLoTEhXOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Empathy, learn about it yeah? maybe you’ll understand instead of constructing your own opinion on someone else’s li… https://t.co/RNPqlabxgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennieEthan @Big12FanWill Without Doke we aren’t good.... no one was bragging]]></document><document><![CDATA[@accion_chiapas Me encanta @CHAYANNEMUSIC #DesdeElAlmaTour Imperdible #Mexico #TuxtlaGutierrez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMossEsq @MarkSZaidEsq Doesn't he jokingly threaten to fire you daily anyway? lol1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know about you America but Trump had Cohen lie for him all his life so remember that America when you judge… https://t.co/mn746HdeIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know Laurie will remember this - One year ago, I was preparing to deliver an IWD2018 PressForProgress lecture. No… https://t.co/eBGi35XCC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump v California: administration wants to get billions in rail funding back https://t.co/jFgS7MvMhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today reminds me of 6 years ago this exact day. Rainy and gloomy. After all the bullshit that's occurred these year… https://t.co/XU0cbAWebK]]></document><document><![CDATA[We went exploring— checking out the Eastern Shore and looking for Harriet Tubman’s history. There’s an incredible t… https://t.co/QZ0IYjl6sD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Sayings | math definition, funny quotes. Every first period class of my freshman year! #laughter #tee-hee… https://t.co/jwQHXtICO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok these are a NEED not a want 🥴😫 @twisted_x_boots https://t.co/cgtjQUcZfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayorPatterson “last year we saw a 3% decrease in the number of immigrant students at OU. This year we have seen a… https://t.co/KpK6PABlZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celinaX0 I was meaning to reply to this tweet you said “LMAOO I’m always thinking what are they going to ask for n… https://t.co/8enjKVUwvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Church ready.... Good morning! #HappySunday😘 #8oclockService @ Third New Hope Baptist Church https://t.co/FN9aHNB7KP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely evening with these lovies. 🤗❤🐶 @ Morgan Street Food Hall https://t.co/Tth2r1Y4bl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cms_squared @gostkillr Looks like crews are onsite addressing your outage. Should be up and running by 1pm today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POLITICOEurope Macron's own people are turning on him. France is rioting non stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudNanaK @ALoveThtJustIs Hate the Breastfeeders but seeing Sleazyson at the bottom of the Jason/Sam distraction… https://t.co/1YA3zf7Lo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Rocky! 🍾🎉🎂 @ Huntington Beach Beer Co https://t.co/2th3d4YM0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz People in glass houses @mattgaetz... are you the next Elliot Spitzer? What happens when powerful people dig into your past???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalAnim13 @JenBaty @benjaminwittes But test scores won't be considered for admission if more than 5 years ol… https://t.co/vcs9EJiSoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Media patiently awaits news conference on Milwaukee hosting DNC. Just a few of many in attendance; @TomPerez ,… https://t.co/DsZPOoMlr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Debated on posting. What the heck.  Do not click unless you want to read something short and filthy.   Dan/Maze/Cha… https://t.co/7KM4Np7pDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think, what bothers me in life is...Elisabeth Holmes is free and I was told to workshio her and be homered to be… https://t.co/fkW225i8kG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stream good by @wearetwinxl on @Spotify @stephen_james @CameronWalker @johngmz  https://t.co/Cql5SKTJyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladyimphoops Congratulations Coach &amp; @ladyimphoops On a great Season‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need to get my shit together because I’m trying to get out Georgia by next year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the new normal where the likes of trump, javanka et al shit on all of us in broad daylight. Enough is en… https://t.co/aZ5z4vKMNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would really love it if I could be asleep right now but my neighbors are apparently nocturnal and need their TV s… https://t.co/diokD6PcLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[We Finally made it to #skiTaos ... What a EPIC Day! @ Taos Ski Valley, New Mexico https://t.co/mIA5Tqntj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please CHIP IN  to Help #WIN the Wisconsin  #SupremeCourt Election!  Let's #DESTROYHagedorn Before he destroys the… https://t.co/6Y5JFxVBrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got this whole ass bed and Prince has to plant his big ass basically on top of me. GET OFFA ME YO! Making me hot and shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You knew all along that I wasn't the one for you So let's stop pretending like we were in love We never shared anything but the drugs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know if you play our vinyl in reverse it just sounds kind of bad/weird? #funfact]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preparation for transformation must come with expectation of manifestation!  Isaiah 1:19 #Transition   - Prophet Leon Forte]]></document><document><![CDATA[From @tisminesky preso at #XDW2019 about applying the behavior model to future designs. This was my favorite part -… https://t.co/5RVX7rc255]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? JDHuntr Attorney Law Jobs 25323 Corporate Counsel Litigation, Estero, FL -… https://t.co/h6UqB9RVxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSpeaker2018 @debrasmith48 Are we back in middle school, again? Trust the plan, people.   Stay strong. Message c… https://t.co/0nCNgkmFPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[God will always protect His people and help those who have a caring heart ❤! He is faithful and still in control!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe this was only the first hike of the season! 🦌 https://t.co/oXSjCGh5wZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tip it upside down yesterday at @USFWSSoutheast @USFWS at the Ukefenokee Swamp tremendous boat ride and docent!! https://t.co/G1suBDWep6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCTheNational @RosieBarton @ChantalHbert @acoyne @chrishallcbc What is she waiting for???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimCarrey Now THIS is something you should find repulsive.  WTF is wrong with you depraved Libs. You have to manuf… https://t.co/M8qEvDNxrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s crazy how the more time goes on, the more her lyrics are relatable to my current situation 😂 but hey if 16 yea… https://t.co/0BGxpHkurW]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉Read Across America Day Activity @HSpringsSTEM @CherokeeSchools by awesome #CCSDFam educator @CervoneJana… https://t.co/UUhEvU0Pgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m blaming this on my mother. She was supposed to fix dinner tonight.  She better make something super delicious t… https://t.co/OrdppwzD9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tpusalsu @TPUSA @charliekirk11 PUT IT ON A BUTTON🗣 https://t.co/buSritkQJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking my bank account daily to see if my tax return is in. Getting more and more disappointed when I see it’s not]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que le pasa a @netomunro ? Ya se le olvidó como dejaron los servicios de salud y todo el Estado, los del sexenio pa… https://t.co/88PKEvqB7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to the calming voice of @BindiIrwin not only does it immediately calms me and warms my heart, I wish it c… https://t.co/wwK70OirTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women convicted who save  dying immigrants while Trump administration is determined they die?.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrishFairx2 I’ve always admired you guys for what you have done for extended family. You have made a huge differen… https://t.co/4m4bVmTgRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuck  Schumer voted to kill his own grandson… One day his grandson will ask him grandpa why didn’t you protect the… https://t.co/XyaC5NkDwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[i corrected my professor during class  today so i think legally they have to just give me a phd now. i will not be… https://t.co/QeS4qaS3wv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready for February 15th so y’all can shut the fuck up 😭💯 sad ass bitches]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case of Russia, Russian Federation if it is smart, instead of Intimidation tactics, should try to find common gr… https://t.co/2MPErjbZCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The Senate is full of Trump haters. They are all corrupt and should be voted out!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my fav person ever &lt;3 hope you had a good day love !! thanks for never failing to make me smile :* @anthvny_garcia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Jussie Smollett should not only be charged as a Felon, but also for a Hate Crime!  Sometime before… https://t.co/Pu3onLSkAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lies. All lies with the exception that the press is 93% correct. They accurately record your behavior which is bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elynn1978 @ZeroFuckaroni I'm in menopause and watching these women I think they're all in menopause the ones actin… https://t.co/voGLc0fghx]]></document><document><![CDATA[he really had to use jordan just to get out of the kardashian fam and into another relationship😂 whos gonna say it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is behind @AOC and who is actually writing her statements on social media?  The girl can barely put a complete… https://t.co/9ikDsI5MtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if you already have a shirt. If you already support me. Please donate to this wonderful organization. It’s so… https://t.co/qj0g8tTfTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry @CNNnewsroom every time you have @RickSantorum on I have too switch to @MorningJoe_  you have no one to blame but yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The past is but a whirlwind of memories; there are those you want to  capture, those you want to forget. Hold on t… https://t.co/2evmX7b8Dk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite quotes: You can go back to your basket....wolf.... Little Red Riding Hood is all yours” -Drogo to Sebas… https://t.co/mVUjeTUHi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[21 yo: I really want to have babies as soon as possible!  Me: No you don’t.  21 yo: You want another baby though...… https://t.co/vrSBT6hMEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice work JP!!!! Proud of you all!!!  Fantastic showcase of some incredibly talented students!!!@paulwyman8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingsIslandPR There needs to be an all of the above option! I’m looking forward to all 3! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianisagoblin @gayfeeshow Once a year we’ll have an AUNT-thology ep. And once a year we’ll have a “Just Be-COUSIN… https://t.co/UBuWzLdQcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yoymiskosas @KamalaHarris Es la primera vez que vemos esos letreros desde que empezó su campaña]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powered by sugar...still going strong! #ostrichfestival #funfriday #tgif #springbreak @ Chandler Ostrich Festival https://t.co/zu5DguzuS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OSS_USA_ @maziehirono @realDonaldTrump The dems, as most citizens of the WORLD, believe in climate change and scie… https://t.co/7eYAs2Z0IU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Kristine. We couldn't do it without amazing partners like @SASsoftware. #iot #connectedcommunity #CaryNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blakmane @maryjveld @sledge_harris @gregorytangelo Take the express train! https://t.co/9jf1OtTZEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marlinaangelus FR i wanted to post pics of him for the longest time but i got scared that if it went viral he woul… https://t.co/ddFm8XNaY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrFan How the hell can you share a bond if it’s only for “Powerful Men”? If you were truly powerful, you… https://t.co/YjPcca5oQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Screenshot from a video I sent my baby daddy  #NewProfilePic https://t.co/kOa7fQp1bx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck no!! I’m throwing hands if this were to ever happen to my daughter]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry, but do you honestly think that anyone from your Gen Chem 1 class from fall 2015 is going to fill out your survery??!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like if you try to do this with Hispanic parents it just isn’t happening... all the uncles, all the great au… https://t.co/q8BqrnWQH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who just got her period on Valentine’s Day? Well played uterus, well played. https://t.co/C8FlYroayU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azsweetheart013 My mom worked as a janitor to afford her work as an artist. Work is work. Just do it sand don’t dr… https://t.co/74NeOHJu5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to help Crazy Rich Asians win a #ShortyAwards trophy! Vote now and every day to make it happen!! https://t.co/XF1APwTkRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun family or friends vacation picture!.... Lol, tried to do this kinda pic with the boys,... https://t.co/x066FkIPPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🖤🏙🖤🎤BIGGIE🎤🖤🏙🖤 Time-lapse of a mixed media piece I created yesterday of the king himself. Notorious B.I.G. Is one o… https://t.co/QZ6tpmDr32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. @MaraLiasson didn’t push back on Gym quite enough this week, but at least she did some. The misinformation pur… https://t.co/wwPYFWI9U8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch us on all online streaming services. Available now!   BE CAREFUL OF WHO YOU CAN TRUST. @ Los Angeles, Califor… https://t.co/IbCVfRwQEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Galera voltando destruída de bloquinhos e eu pensando que série vou começar já que maratonei a que tava vendo na sexta de carnaval]]></document></documents></author>