<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[In ear monitor and headphones drop in today to check out these items. #mondaythoughts #uhlikmusic #headphonesmust https://t.co/meTQs0IBqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddBrommelkamp Ketchup on eggs is revolting. I don't think that's strictly an Iowa thing but it's the first thing that came to mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLA_TV @TheHoopCentral Doesn’t matter how he meant it. You know how the media is and he clearly said he would fuck… https://t.co/YTVsAl6VQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 6 years @jordanleonard9 I can’t wait for these next few days in Gatlinburg with you! Love you more ❤️ @ Nassa… https://t.co/PFvmv0azey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well said Joe. Kharma can and will be a biaatch! BTW, I’m not in Any of those trades bro. Just agreeing with the Se… https://t.co/CHOfi89v33]]></document><document><![CDATA[In this video @davidcpreece1 Dave P.  nailed a big 3 reps with the hanging band chin-ups.  Hanging band drills make… https://t.co/LzGl8xc08F]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Tigers garbage cans at Joker Marchant Stadium are cool. https://t.co/Hjv96qlfn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisWeekABC @GStephanopoulos Try again @GOPLeader https://t.co/TkqMqF0OJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy smokes fast replies! Can we get to 100 in the next 30 minutes? Give us a retweet!! #edchat https://t.co/Yl8ZGyQOUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[ay foos it's @royalriptides birthday today!!!!!!!! https://t.co/7RPMXcbV6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Unchained Melody by The Righteous Brothers. - Like I didn’t know who sang it! Love this s… https://t.co/4KhXsnWX9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to my friends at T-Mobile! The more I work with you, the more I discover how special and unique a culture… https://t.co/Pamlta26Pk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched 3 of the Quebec games, very impressive team play. Unreal puck pursuit and then skill to keep it. Precision… https://t.co/rSebAUxSOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitaniaMcGrath Typical Millennial, can't spell. Check your OED and use a zed, snowflake!! Then, apologize!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cordovar97 @matheus_uribe8 @ClubAmerica Eso es todo Carajo ! Ahora vamos por las “ Chicas “]]></document><document><![CDATA[All us side niggas are enjoying our National day off already &gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HoopIdea What if we just had John Mulaney and Bill Hader on all the episodes of SNL again? HOWLING continuously at… https://t.co/rlrGia32q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever go to a rave or a festival or any similar experience and there's half naked white girls just spinning but… https://t.co/yYPH5Ahfk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we please just have a little boy, Hannah?  I know it is a whole bunch to ask but I actually do know what I'm doing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My beautiful family ❤️ #IPD #irondequoiters #CApeeps @ Irondequoit, New York https://t.co/h4caRmvmn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything you were trying to accomplish, you just sent it backwards. What a fucking idiot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Howard goes right back at Baker and #Syracuse has 2 FT with 2 seconds left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahRobinette1 That’s a song off born sinner... the fuck are you talking bout]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBaxterBean @realDonaldTrump You really believe that?  How about this: Benghazi-4 dead Americans when State Dept… https://t.co/sjIcVYb5Eo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao these spring break pics from when I was 20 😭 i weighed like 160 ol skinny ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HSchouten @FactCheckU @JeffHarperArt @JamesHunnel @Regan0002112 @DianeKovacs @MrsPerrin @MarilynCapps… https://t.co/yFb29PuaaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los #Castro de #cuba quieren quitarles sus turistas. #Mexico no te dejes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 3-Ply by Moksa Brewing Co at @thehopgrenade — https://t.co/vXDXR2mLjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posted withrepost • brokerjess JUST LISTED!😍 This beautiful home in Amber Fields Subdivision in Schererville Indian… https://t.co/8cIZJnAauM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamKeithFL Give me a Harris and whoever ticket, and I am right there! Any of the other women candidates are great… https://t.co/hyGfP5aRJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomSteyer @GovInslee To put the new green deal in perspective it will cost every household in the United States $6… https://t.co/igFdO3nuNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @mitchellreports I’m Jewish, but we don’t need Pence telling us how to handle this matter. He should concent… https://t.co/ZVYtGdm4Qp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ignore the trolls. Go see #CapitanMarvel  It was amazing! https://t.co/SDDnF06DvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The china cabinet.  #vikingglass #midcenturymodern #vintageglass #vintage #bittersweetglass @ Greenfield, New Hamps… https://t.co/gipLv8Izkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your son told you if you want Hillary emails just ask. You did it in front of the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama @MichelleObama ✨❤️Looking like early Diana Ross. Stunning photo❤️✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I guess since im off tomorrow ill be playing kirby all night @Swiftor @crash2burn @InventorBLADES  https://t.co/rNUTIA1nuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates Annie may only be 9 months old but she already knows that Sundays are pretty great. https://t.co/GTdk96Ifoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RLermaHcisd @fit_leaders @Asael_Ruvalcaba @mathcoachkorth @NickHoltvluwer @ValChavez2018 @jonflores_01… https://t.co/a8STgYZb07]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4: I also extend this to your ecclesiastical leader and your employer. Just because you think it, doesn't mean you… https://t.co/NJc1Go44VA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si vas a casa ajena vuélvete ciego, cuando salgas de ahí vuélvete mudo, no busques defectos que no hay, respeta a q… https://t.co/tvO7ITDKIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Samuel Adams Cold Snap by @SamuelAdamsBeer at @chilis — https://t.co/prjEWCEdWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Sean McDermott: 9-6 in one score games. Also most 8 times by 20 or more points in 2 seasons.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's early onset dementia Or A long term strategy to get out of jail with an insanity defense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZTACarolyn @UCFZTA @KappaSigmaUCF Your @UCFZTA 👸ladies were awesome as always.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Northwestern played GRC and Simon Kenton earlier in the season while Hamilton Southeastern's lone loss was to Ryle.… https://t.co/HgBrp4XabV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Vague Recollection by @jesterkingbeer at @jesterkingbeer — https://t.co/u4SHVnIWxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesindyan @CandiceRoyer @CIAnderson3 @Wehrl @whoknows0610 @why_two_wit @WinfreeJenny @Wrath_of_Comm @writerlygirl… https://t.co/ON3Hd9n74U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Mirror moment. Google doesn’t need a captcha to prove you’re human, they track your mouse movements for that.… https://t.co/A0WYGxeej1]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should get the Monday off after daylight savings, especially when it involves taking away an hour of my sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[to me, it’s good that we spend three hours a week, 52 weeks a year, arguing over whether college players should be… https://t.co/UPblrTTYTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charcoal over acrylic wash on Strathmore mixed media paper  #strathmore400series #sketch #charcoaldrawing #moderist… https://t.co/3LVMJRRkxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:41.4°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSkipBayless Been that way for years. Watch a game or two and you'd see]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I think I’m having a bad day I see this and get a measure of perspective. My 🧢 is off to the folks fixing that… https://t.co/QqVZz1yMiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[He already is self loathing... probably would have made him feel healed and part of something greater than him self… https://t.co/sKR8KRG174]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doc_Coyote @ComicAttack @DetPikachuMovie Bulbasaur is a very good Pokémon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Virginia lost a TOTAL of 3 games in ACC play the past two seasons. Incredible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There will be a informational meeting for any sophomore or freshmen baseball player this Thursday in coach Panepint… https://t.co/RAuUGWtKiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MintPressNews @TheRealYoG #Boyott i$LIErael, who did 911 witht he #Nazi swine bu$h #crimefamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not a big sci-fi fan, but @Stranger_Things has me hooked. I think it’s the banana seat bikes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🚨🚨🚨Spend $75 or more and receive 108 pcs golden desert charcoal and a coco flame burner coupon code (flame) @… https://t.co/xqQBXgYCEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Awe is the condition of a man’s spirit realizing Who God is and what He has done for him personally. Our Lord emph… https://t.co/MitsSKmUm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[26. Teddy Roosevelt’s wife and mother passed away within hours of each other on February 14, 1884. His journal entr… https://t.co/ONaIDz0pLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Pakistan used F-16 jet intended for fly-over cricket fields only to shoot down Indian warplane over Kashmir the… https://t.co/QnvKJDPaer]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GRATITUDE! #begrateful #cake #recognition #intent #costs #emotions #showing https://t.co/QJLOebcJP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattstopera If I didnt know better I would think this was an SNL sketch]]></document><document><![CDATA[This ain’t the shitty portion of your schedule that you’ve been talking shit through ... when this team actually pl… https://t.co/ZOqzMUxxj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inspiremelounge Amen! I encourage people to pray is tongues for at least a half an hour everyday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure to check out my professional website for ideas and links to all things Maker Ed.  In there you will find… https://t.co/voXWcn5XSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IRISHSTEEL12 Gotta catch him solo cause behavior you describe means he’s totally whipped and won’t speak freely in… https://t.co/lLKVxAQ8kc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jhumphries88 As good as turkey tacos on low carb tortillas can be. I added lots of salsa and guac.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@true_pundit Schiff claims?  Schiff believes?  Schiff runs his mouth a lot like Mark Warner.  Put up or shut up dem… https://t.co/1VCrQei4uG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomfsc24 @VP @NASA @AstroAnnimal @Astro_DavidS @Space_Station @SpaceX @JimBridenstine The Government paid for CONT… https://t.co/QOijCxtj24]]></document><document><![CDATA[The constitution gave the President the power to defend the border. Sick it up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dominator71 @DoppyMister I’d appreciate a DM on this topic too. Or at least tell me keywords to research online. #TeachAManToFish]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen is about to drop some bombs tomorrow folks.  Michael got 3 yrs for his part and now “individual one” insists he’s a liar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished season 7 of Game of Thrones and I’m at a loss for words]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve got to get these “On Course” microphones figured out @NBCSports . Sounds like a seashell has been hammered into my brain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vernon Fraley Jr. (WHS) splits a pair from the charity once again.  Timeout Wolverines....  73-71 Wakefield w/ 15.4… https://t.co/AgOwblYfC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahPollak @allahpundit It happened to the GOP two years ago, or do you choose to forget that? “The Jews will not… https://t.co/vqswSxzk08]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is there for one reason and one reason only to slam dunk Michael Cohen. He wouldn't even let him speak he… https://t.co/hBF3lQO7DS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Home Alone Tonight by Luke Bryan https://t.co/b232w9u6CU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who can you trust? How deep does the conspiracy go? Help bring our merged campaign to podcast format! The followup… https://t.co/RJo6RlOSic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baratisimo. $ 26.28. Mas $ 23.72 de propinas . Solo $ 50.00 @ Texas Roadhouse - Kissimmee https://t.co/2M2xMvw95M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NealSchonJTT @NealSchonMusic @JacksonCasino @greggrolieband @DeenTheDrummer @CasaMendoza2012 Sweet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back again renwaverly hotel at the Tosca Blu Bar 6-8pm. Come check me out! #atllivemusic @ Renaissance Atlanta Wave… https://t.co/dsYpZ68feV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @DerbyWrestlin  on the state championship!! Way to finish the hunt! #DerbyProud #OnTheHunt https://t.co/j0eC9RYotm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WRC_Kennedy @Outback @1stLadiesOfFB Beautiful Flawless that's how we do it! #Truth #HTTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MurphTWN @weathernetwork @CBCMorningLive @cbchh So there's a wee chill in the air]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamcbest Probably because I'd rather be rational, reasonable and humane instead of a brittle demagogue who makes… https://t.co/8IWWAKkJDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[this remote start has been sooo clutch with this cold ass weather lately]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming Soon  #BluntForceDrama (Blunt-Dorce-Drama) BAD WATER - Feat. SCOTTI MO (Beat By A-ron) #AronMusic by Phil “P… https://t.co/teNUUHKBX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeeganFlaherty @JArnoldTAMU85 @Nurly13 Come on down to Cleveland town everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @centsible They come on. They aren’t the political editor going into 2020. The second you let Bernie Sander de… https://t.co/8agc1GnOkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[You(r parents) invested too much on your college education for you to end up selling Ponzi scheme tooth paste.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Zeets Jordan has 3 first round exits. LeBron has zero.  LeBron will have his 3rd year where he didn’t make the pl… https://t.co/Sbtp311TXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[SICKLE LIFE PATIENT SUPPORT GROUP https://t.co/OftrOtJ86S via @Sickle_Life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elementary #SECME Competition! STEM Force: The Brain Awakens Opening Ceremony! @SantalucesHS @Erica4schools… https://t.co/hfoAZv3uIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure you make enough money in life to maintain your own place on the side I do that.]]></document></documents></author>