<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Somebody just need to whoop her ass one good time. That’s it that’s all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disculp? Como en una violacion los dos tubieron la culpa? BROTHER!!!!!!!!!!!! ODIO A ESTA HUMANIDAD!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still mourning over the fact that Panera got rid of their black bean soup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys if I don’t reply back or DM back or follow back it’s because my twitter is lagging from all the love your show… https://t.co/VYL78Lb9sD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ComePlayWithMe (@ The @ChapelRva in Midlothian, VA w/ @bryan_warren) https://t.co/sJ0Z5oCAoc https://t.co/0T4HtMptok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardmarx That’s nice that there are people out there who are still honest with others, so keep speaking the tru… https://t.co/TxQvc5RVOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t receive the respect, communication and attention that I need from my significant other and I have alread… https://t.co/TelqP6mjsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KnowYourObama @Acosta If he hugs a confederate flag.... I’m taking the gloves off ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one understands the excitement a nursing student feels by getting a text saying clinical is cancelled 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmudd19 @TeacherLadyKY @AvenCook @meme3rat I taught our kiddos how to use pictures as backgrounds on slides. I thi… https://t.co/sGaj2Pw08D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black/ brown hair looks so much healthier than blonde I just don’t like it on me🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t even listen to my favorite songs anymore bc i shared them with a shitty person and now they have those memo… https://t.co/9cDwSPE9R7]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least this time when my suitcase went missing, I’m home and have my cats for comfort. Oh wait. My cats are furry… https://t.co/5iAzEQrVl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree. Lots of candidates to consider, not ruling anyone out at this point. Issues please. Why does no one ever a… https://t.co/BVwbn0Y9aC]]></document><document><![CDATA[definitely clever. trailer+cake.jpg 325×280 pixels camper cake travel trailer vintae https://t.co/eFJVHb5iGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chinese foreign minister Wang Yi with Ram Nath Kovind, President of India   #PeaceAndLove  #ThunderUp  #BRAP… https://t.co/VohkrToUt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defend the 2nd Rally, Oregon Capital, Salem, Oregon, March 23 staring from 12-3pm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrownBrian333 Yes and I loved it💚 so many talented women in this category]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyZ13 @TruthMaga Occult Enclaves in Bronx.Her pic recently flashed next to one of those South American Cult ico… https://t.co/Rv7j26W7FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing so many international artists represented at the oscars tonight gives me so much hope for my future]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you #upwithFOX8 ? Because we’re keeping you up to date on what you need to know this morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching LVA’s Kiss me Kate.... Marek is amazing in the ensemble. Hard to believe he is a senior.  So difficult to… https://t.co/JoB5HBPOOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mountain is out and the sun is up. It may be 23 degrees, but I swear Spring is coming. #MtRainier #PNW https://t.co/DUf8UOiLCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely, and I want to know who’s sexual activities have been paid off on tax payer dime. How dare they have a s… https://t.co/4vC2Fhbm1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else get annoyed when all influencers post is merch or makeup.... lol I know thats their job but dang.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone going to see @GillianA in @AllAboutEvePlay in Sebastopol on April 11? #GillianAnderson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold me down, hold me up Hold me close 'cause my times is up Show they true colors, don't know who to trust Mind wo… https://t.co/ZfrFBCtNbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeoooooo people love talking it’s cute how all people reveal their true color sooner or later have you not NOTICED… https://t.co/xVcPM0Dmy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The LEGO Store in New York, NY https://t.co/R9lTitZh7r https://t.co/zd9tWmS1ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump When are you going to get a restrainging order against these people for malicious persecution and out right lies?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful to spend some time with family for a few days. 👋 DC! ❤💙 #teacheronbreak https://t.co/vdrrdwqhXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolynB2537 @SoapOperaSpy @DougDavidsonYR What she said!!!  He'll(Paul) save the day!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Society for Human Resource Management in Alexandria, VA https://t.co/BfJdSfhcDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Country Meadows is hiring in #Harrisburg, PA! Read about our latest job opening via the link in our bio: Community… https://t.co/iVVRabItpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thomas and I went out, came home, played Mario cart, and did face masks. If this is what forever is like, I’m totally in😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Bourbon Barrel Aged Drewcifer by @tailgatebrewery at @growler_hville — https://t.co/XmyVtWfy7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RutSpence4 @DebraSeals4 @Guchata_ @RickDaKick @robmtaub @DiamondandSilk @realDonaldTrump @POTUS The ONLY person wh… https://t.co/9JYaLSUPGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proponents of this bill claim to have scientifically identified the point at which our spiritual souls intertwine w… https://t.co/Us0f6vdnIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker’s bunny rabbit!!! Say hello to PANCHITO!!!!! the softest furball ever!!!! https://t.co/4whVPZEjbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beer. Breakfast. Board Games.  A great morning spent out with my best girl. https://t.co/z9hYrPuzED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tan feliz por el!!!! 👑👑👑👑👏👏👏👏#bohemianrhapsody #ramimalek #bestactor #oscars2019 #queen #freddiemercury en Oscar Aw… https://t.co/pibWvUzPYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pregunta, los que menos tienen ya son ricos ahora con #amlo? Porqué a como les alegra cada que dicen que se encontr… https://t.co/pTJhLCDUvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy illegal immigration conspiracy!!! @RealJamesWoods have you seen this?? #Illegals https://t.co/WzcNYa7orm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlidellPD I love the humanity that all these offers show as opposed to negative press all PD’d around the country… https://t.co/oyLVpj1mkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🕊This tweet made me think of the white winged dove in Stevie Nicks’ “Edge of Seventeen” so I queued that song on Yo… https://t.co/RZyAqMNsA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Garlfied Ave. @ Alhambra Rd. So sad, please drive at a safe speed. Prayers out to them. Don't know the status but t… https://t.co/Um72YbaeJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 newscasts later, my weekend is here! @producerprobs https://t.co/FAoBetw4LB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnneWHilborn Not doubting you but curious if it’s specifically Faculty not University Senate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me da mucha risa que mi novio me diga que soy celosa y sabe que tanto, cuando el es peor🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came back to Rez this morning after being gone all weekend and there’s two guys I’ve never seen before passed out on my room floor....nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyc311 and Department of Housing Preservation and Development (HPD) please stop sending these angry, hostile, men… https://t.co/xTLPAxxZDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[People out here with some horrible personalities. Like how the hell are you the way that you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a close-up of our @mayaromanoff Weathered Metals™️ handmade wallcovering and it looks pur-fect! 🐈 . Thank y… https://t.co/Xq1i5P9yob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto She has to go. How much more are we going to take of her against us and our government]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flight of the egret. #danapointharbor #danapoint #egret #boats #boating #birds #harbor @ Dana Point Harbor https://t.co/Ur2WdEcRJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was very impressed with @UofNorthFlorida on our College tour! Beautiful campus!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being heard is as close to being loved that for the average person they are indistinguishable. —David W Ausburger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madampresidn @SenatorCollins Never forget, McConnell doesn't need Sen. Collins to vote 'yes' on everything. When h… https://t.co/dxXxQ4pFS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My biggest predicament as of recent. Do I correct the person’s grammatically incorrect texts or do I just ignore and cringe every time?🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t even count how many times I have to tell myself to stop having an attitude]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT and Likes don’t equate to donations so please consider @AConnectedNorth donation to our #homehardware hockey tea… https://t.co/vd58iwM8LB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day ♥️♥️♥️ @ Chester, Virginia https://t.co/QXOanwwFlv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennaMoquin @paul_grealish That's funny. I had a beta reader tell me she'd like more racey scenes in my books. It… https://t.co/eQTWLczErT]]></document><document><![CDATA[And pink hair once. I call this Manic Panic Cover Art. #selfportrait #pinkhair #bellingham https://t.co/olB0KneNf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my residents is OBSESSED with Billy Ray Cyrus and lost her cd a few weeks ago. I found it Friday night and t… https://t.co/ZEzhn3mOOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @kelleyk70_key to post the covers of 7 books I love.  No explanations or reviews,… https://t.co/hGVdLnHGGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday from the littles! They got a little distracted by that bright light in the sky! 🌞 @ Casa De NOLA https://t.co/gk4GScADOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acakes421 Alicia why do people hurt themselves like that? Can’t they feel the pain and stop? I have always wondere… https://t.co/ijPovA6ooF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch You're anti-American idiot.  I suffer from no phobias.  I suffer from Support America and the American people or resign fool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrongIndy We could make recognition of this history a part of the Rethink 65/70 rebuild. It’s important to honor and never forget.]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT REMINDER: The Polka Show just started on @WXPR and yes you can live stream it.  https://t.co/qUVFPVCji0… https://t.co/zvszqNZfd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real Estate w/Samantha! Get that pool 🏊🏻 you always dreamed of...for your pup 🐶 of course! 🐾Summer 🏖️ is creeping u… https://t.co/BDNDnkL30f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsToriGalvin I’m only able to do Saturday with Diamond pass for Bobby, so don’t know how I can do others]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benfcampen @dangr76 Someone needs to explain to me what the and I mean What The Fuck is happening]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_mpetitto Caroline is performing at the basketball game today at half time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shemarmoore My plans are already made - Jammie's, puppies, remote and SWAT!!!! https://t.co/ykTrasdSMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sirmiwealth Have an affair tonight! Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight. https://t.co/D30OFvedLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister They’re mostly Christian. They already don’t live in reality. Easy pickins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here’s another ear worm for good measure? Rule of threes? https://t.co/lom1kmq4FU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolinascooter @870_hogfan @Challmark98 @SECNetwork He waited alooooong time! https://t.co/JpCDUGNFEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My reflections doesn't feel like my own , it's changed , it's missing something, deep down I know what it is. But I… https://t.co/Ivn3p5a07F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is “Every Night // Every Morning” on your playlist ?? (🎶 link in bio) —- 📸 : nat_reo @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/xERxfpWAor]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have ordered/spent sooooooOOOooOo much money in the past week it’s craZZZZzzZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can’t just be looking at anything.” I’m screaming. Females so mean. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of @charlsiekey_  &amp; @howiedeman who have served as @VirginiaDECA State Officers. They made… https://t.co/KCP4jHP7yv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because I tell everyone the owner of my gym, who is my trainer has a rule:  No fat people are allowed at the pool...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Undersea alluvial fans- love to see em. Really gives you insight on how much sediment flux is occurring the system.… https://t.co/yg1s41VDJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beth’s father wanting to support his daughter no matter the overtime or the odds. My HEART. My SOUL. #ThisIsUs @NBCThisisUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[college is weird. some classes you have all freshmen when you’re a sophomore and other classes you have people who have babies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmaooo I’m gonna throw my vans first thing in the morning to see if it’s true😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hack: you can create your own weighted blanket by surrounding your normal blanket with five pound dumbbells]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralHospital Wow so excited 2 see this!!! Cant wait!! Hope not end of Ryan even thou fond of the killings but l… https://t.co/5Er3cYP1o1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kerstin_1314 @dog_rates Hard to say because he is a rescue, lots of people have guessed that though! 😀😀💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WindsorMorning I was surprised that the interview at 6:25 this mroning regarding climate change didn't touch on ag… https://t.co/4u9b065n13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just thinking of one of my favorite movies. “The Thomas Crown Affair.” I believe it was a novel first.  “Do you wan… https://t.co/7DuOiur6Wm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question Dems: why no one smiled in Disney at Tatiana pictures? Answer is below.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chiachess I think they are calling this one wrong the drive home was pretty bad just now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton It still won’t help him. Love you https://t.co/DW6h7zEtBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seoul Gangnam-gu District Mayor Jeong Sun-Gyun: Seoul Gangnam-gu, S. Korea, Shut down the illegal dog meat farms, m… https://t.co/uWK5P8Xum5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really enjoy how the lady who sits 5ft away from me came to work with the flu. Thanks so much 🙃]]></document></documents></author>