<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Just received my heated eyelash curler thing and girls let me tell ya, y’all need one of these in your life 😳😳👍🏻❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio What about here in Florida let’s put  us first such as veterans, homeless, education, voters ID, and environment... 👍🏻😀🙏🏻🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much of a tax break did billionaires and corporations get as compared to the average working middle-class Ameri… https://t.co/aQBHf6RWr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosR20520323 RATA RESPETATE TU MALDITO DELINCUENTE PRIBAO Y USUARIO DE DROGAS. ADEMÁS, SI NO LO SABÍA CUERNÚ TU… https://t.co/bEhqHwxCyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yaay_Me Oh no. That would be disastrous. I’m just the chauffeur and head cheerleader.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkepticNikki I wonder how he feels about Trump bearing false witness 60 times in a 2 hour speech, and being a serial adulterer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Desmotimes I tried out the new multi-Strada when it came out but could not get on the thing on level ground… The s… https://t.co/wQZfJ8OvqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @maggieNYT @MichaelCohen212 Someone just figured out that they are going to be under some investigation themselves 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@99prcent @TomSteyer @SpeakerPelosi @RepJerryNadler @ericswalwell A convicted felon named Cohen says so so it's tru… https://t.co/TbdMYXbtB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton We need babies too but you people are killing them by the Millions. Pretty soon Planned Parenthood will cease to exist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This aged very well. Aw some caramel and bourbon flavors. - Drinking a Dankwood by @foundersbrewing @ Koch's High G… https://t.co/09e3RJwoiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even know why I keep twitter I never actually tweet anything just rt random shit 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[And people still doubt the war against Human Life is not a FULL FRONTAL ASSAULT?  Join @clif_high, @Unindoctrinate… https://t.co/MRumUuyPZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Argo @ChadOwens2 has just been released from a Brampton courtroom on bail following an assault charge. There… https://t.co/UI3ohG9dIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makeitsnowondem I earnestly enjoyed Nutcracker And The Four Realms. Some shit didn't make sense, but it was silly and fun as hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bullshit. No reason for anyone not to have a legitimate I'd unless you are illegal. Why do Dems support breaking la… https://t.co/eb1g8uvOXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not one for allowing my worlds to collide with eachother, but I also believe that there can be exceptions to rules too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know close ones talk about me but that shit is pointless af cause ima forever be me &amp; doing what I gota do]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you own a Tesla or an EV, will you ever buy an ICE car again? If you don’t own an EV, what will your next car be… https://t.co/OUjO15GwH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Ready For Negative Interest Rates When Next Recession Hits via @forbes https://t.co/QODStJqkeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLand @sfmnemonic @realDonaldTrump Oh, come on, man. #Trump is honest as the day is lonnn ... did something just blot out the sun?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok you little mother fucker....my back is a little tweaked but it’s core day baby. I’ll be easy and if it hurts I’l… https://t.co/hYAk5NC79u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRapp314 I didn’t watch it and don’t have insight on the game. It looked like the Coogs had trouble dealing with t… https://t.co/1oKGGjjtLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskPlayStation I never got platinum rewards for Bloodborne, Horizon Zero Dawn, and God of War. I love all of those… https://t.co/0Gj44tzCAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CtCathCorner @FergusFSU @PureSpew @Eschatologuy Oh, I know. That's why you believe this stuff.  This conversation… https://t.co/TZV1qXhXFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight felt like Friday #periodt @ Studio 305 - RAGEDancers https://t.co/sSNMQRkBaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[7-0 run for the rams,Under 16 timeout and CSU is breaking it open, Rams up 45-30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for the most MARVELlous Superhero (see what I did there?) @ Cineplex Odeon Queensway Cinemas https://t.co/AMES7MpOMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rest In Heaven Granddaddy Benjamin Campbell 💪💞💉💯🏆🏁 @ Charleston, South Carolina https://t.co/oqONopzV7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coupla jam packed work days on the come up. The good news is, it's just a nice lil self-inflicted front load prior… https://t.co/keMvlvTM6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nberlat @Barrontemple908 @robbysoave Essentially you might be exacerbating minority stress, for a nonexistent threat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor Morrison new home construction in Windermere. Priced from the $800’s #broker  #taylormorrisonhomes… https://t.co/kwUR5TzNVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Atlantic Aviation PHL in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/i2IZxPRCmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theNthJennifer @ByronsShade That sucks. Hope they figure it out. Took dr.s two years to diagnose my psoriatic rheumatoid arthritis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All y'all need to give this a listen! — ♫Illegal Smile by John Prine, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics ® https://t.co/qz8WySIMkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LasVegasWolf1 How can you tell from an opening line if the number is going to go up or down?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please can we have this match!? #WeWantWrasslin #wrestlingisforeveryone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asianboy0122 @SMii7Y Hey man they're very comfortable https://t.co/0VokVoyakk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meeting with @bgcmidlands to bring jazz workshops and performances to the kiddos via colajazzscene Outreach (… https://t.co/8x2gwQB0vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg!!! The Iconics are way more annoying than usual! I didn’t think it was possible! 😩😩😩 #WWEChamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[And who decides when episodes appear? Looking forward to #AndiMack tonight. Well, no. Or the year between seasons 2 and 3 of Bunk'd?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chickiepox @SomoraRocks @tina_tmjohns520 @mimibeck617 @KKay7777 @BeckyBo37839654 @LoriBrog @LeeAnneLocken… https://t.co/mY1jpGjTbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so trash for sleeping on HAIKYU!! this long man. TOP FUCKING 5. https://t.co/HoQf4m3QV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#day2 #jjfishweek #itstimetodance #oseadsportfishing #papasrawbar #jumbolicious #todaydayisagoodday #dfas… https://t.co/c5ECctOhU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHumble_21 come to Detroit! You @qdiggs6 and @TracyWalkerIII would be perfect together!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some ppl really hyping up education like it’s a factor to these athletes lmao it don mean shit even to me and I put my time in 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAI, what you are talking about the silence on XRP-Ripple, I have sent you an email "XRP enemies are within," which… https://t.co/7Mh7lqMIp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bethenny @SkinnygirlBrand @aliceandolivia @Dior @fp_journe You're so fine, you blow my mind!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro I miss the food scene in El Paso. Like if I wanted a good ass burger? I could try a new place everyday for like… https://t.co/O5pJhbldAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueJays @JoeCarter_29 I just watched this gif for 2 hours. Oh, and I love you @JoeCarter_29 ! Happy Birthday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this news to you? Stay current with all the news from ASU and earn Pitchforks toward great rewards! https://t.co/FB8BUnEFa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ed_Coutu I mean, don’t get me wrong, I am fascinated to see what they do with the picks. I don’t hate Carr like ot… https://t.co/AVOO4RBq6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zagaholicpod Four consecutive Sweet 16’s.  Title game 2017.  Math is hard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't believe they think this will work!  They have to think everyone is stupid !]]></document><document><![CDATA[just grin a while. #hilarity #tee-hee #smirk #cute https://t.co/xt0RDN8hJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StanfordWBB @lexiehulll “Achieving her Goals”with a 3 pointer https://t.co/s0HELM7Yam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HebertofRiffs Can’t say I watch a lot of Celtics but it seems like he may have forgotten how basketball works]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand No. You threw Al Franken under the bus. You're proud of that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Breakdown- 15 HIM endured Merkins in many hidden forms- Welcome Yoshi! https://t.co/xRphqBCFOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy belated birthday to graduating senior DL  @DallasCroswel - Justin is a Exercise Physiology major from Macomb… https://t.co/WWAseMAlfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPLGLocal10 @BrandonOrrWx @NekiMohanWPLG @TTongenWPLG @JulieDurdaWPLG @alexfinnieWPLG @BettyDavisWPLG… https://t.co/LqY9KkHwzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Eklund @Derrick_Tillery When I walk in the office ..... and then leave 😂 https://t.co/zBg5yfwO2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMek Use to like Amanpour but over the years I have developed a headache watching but more important “listening… https://t.co/GzBaFrahen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets It’s so crazy out here, that blurb is bemieveable in Trumplamd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too funny Tim Cook Changes Twitter Name to 'Tim Apple' After President Trump's Name Flub https://t.co/q1D7dE2FpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This could be a long few days. I tried to deposit checks while my bosses assets are frozen. He’s dealing with fraud… https://t.co/Ct9nm5r8QK]]></document><document><![CDATA[VALENTINES | #pink   WISHING EVERYONE THE D TODAY! 😂😭🤣 Whether it’s daisies, drinks, dinner, or anything else that… https://t.co/XtsadYYAFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnookiLoveDolls @ufc @BellatorMMA Awesome work today it was great having you both ‼️🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow Bro! Which end of the candle were you burning last night? Did you find that you were singeing yoursel… https://t.co/kOft2Q2wv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetruefailure He doesn't have to be so good though, especially not today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@puckandrally NBA hamstrings its teams by forcing the basketball. It worked better with older logos, now it's really limiting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JReidNFL Kyler Murray on the phone with Billy Beane like: https://t.co/dLu4DmjcOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was OUT when the girl got hit by a drink😭🤣😂💀 then my friends sister reaction ain’t making it any better 😂😂😂😂🤣… https://t.co/v7xwhIC4Tz]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi hello i met one of my literary heroes last night ! gracias por tus cuentos, @ValeriaLuiselli. thanks for inspiri… https://t.co/ToIrxW4iyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActionBronson @realtonycervone Don't forget to hit up Ghirardelli 2!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever happened to Baby Jane?  Keep your pecker out of politics 😺my kitty will find you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeoplezPen Definitely. Rizzo is rarely ranked less than the 28th player. He’s not even in the conversation. An arg… https://t.co/rs2gL9QLPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave873 Until Apple patches it... Ah, the good ole stressful days of jail breaking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarakcrowe @IMowat @Fern_Britton Not these days. More like “Murder on the Cleethorpes bone shaker”. 🚂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKingIA Plus the DEMS and Bernie voted against: 1. Woman for CIA Director 2. Woman for Education 3. Black man… https://t.co/2JvkXdGS4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well... it’ll be nice to let him now for a ton of reasons but she don’t have to tell him if she don’t want to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamKhabib @AliAbdelaziz00 @USMAN84kg @zabeast_mma Khabib your correct , Zabit is another Dagastad BadAss .]]></document><document><![CDATA[me watching the track ID drama from the sidelines https://t.co/vO4V4iQI3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[It snow time remove snow at jmu baseball field for today. Beep horn when go by the field.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Speaking of tropes...calling illegal immigration ‘immigration’ is a deliberate deceit.  Illegal immigration is… https://t.co/kAsi09kCLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadCopeland40 @CastletonMHoops Am I supposed to keep you on until you have kids coming to camp?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @RepMattGaetz lapdog? I thought @RepMattGaetz was Trump's bootlicker too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RizenGamer @gifyourgame @amustycow 😂😂😂 this is so much better from your POV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MATHHOFFA Yo I appreciate you bro. Not just off the Hollow battle but just who you are in general. Always will be… https://t.co/DFR7nEQAcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FapOrigins @amwalker38 @Serenesirenxxx @KenzieReevesxxx They are very sexy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidlagreca1 @bullyray5150 @BustedOpenRadio I think this is a case of “dream delayed, not denied” for Kofi. He’s… https://t.co/9gBoEs7nzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohmywavess @notallbhas @Hawaiiankuku I think the point is that he donated what for us is a cookie @ Panera. The re… https://t.co/Htny7DTzUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tahoe bound! - Drinking a Samuel Adams Cold Snap by @SamuelAdamsBeer at @ny_njairports  — https://t.co/B7YguO5nR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:43.5°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brhodes That’s the hallmark of the Trump era, it’s OK to say shit out loud now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/q4geZZC0dV happy #thursday ! #today is going to a #greatday I love being a #uncle @ Coral Gables, Flor… https://t.co/UV0QzsgDoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James_R_Stover ...and for extra points, the fact that the brilliant Joe Jackson takes the chorus. Lots of Pulp keeping me company today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattdracing gained a lot of fans today. Great run and humble interview!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OvarTaxed Maybe SNC Lavalin has something on Trudeau? Was he at the Saudi party ? Were there tapes ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[CORRECTION: My name is Sierra SHAY and I have doubly confirmed that I prefer solos.]]></document></documents></author>