<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It's time to tell someone you know how you feel, in a handwritten note! https://t.co/Tg4aE7rVWw #SHOP @ New York, N… https://t.co/H41xsNf67E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for having me on this morning, @UpfrontKPFA! I hope y’all feel clearer about the @AlamedaCounty Board of Sup… https://t.co/O1kPQoLVRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m probably just gonna post some pics of him for the foreseeable future (he hated pics and was very private but i… https://t.co/u2Omq7yrSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[earlier i was literally RUNNING to keep up w alexis walking and she didn’t realize until i asked her to slow down 💀😭 i hate being short]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmayarmstro surprised they haven’t gotten cuffed yet tbh. and by cuffed i mean put in the back of a cop car]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scotty516 @MZHemingway That’s like saying the US fought the civil war to abolish slavery. Not untrue at first glan… https://t.co/3T40H4FV7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @McCreadyForNC @GOP @MarkHarrisNC9 I really do not fell like going through another election, tv commercial… https://t.co/KpSquv4pfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been working on content and design concepts for a client all night... I think I need to sleep and revisit my work tomorrow 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@germannateclub @Chrissychatt @gcc4all @Elli_2305 @NathanFillion @KerstinDrefs @StephGambini @debbslovesnate… https://t.co/D1HTj6QJO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't been "single" on Valentine's Day since I was like 12. And yet I still think it's an utterly ridiculous "h… https://t.co/Cw4XjlGkGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahGoldberg10 @VCUPav @SpiderMBB Right in front of the old A.H. Robins Building correct?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t felt a collective sadness like this in a very long time.... #nowords @ Borough of Lincoln Park New Jersey https://t.co/JbSFhB2tlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#darkbrownhair #pinklips #winterinla #pasadena @ Pasadena, California https://t.co/NUlFsSQtjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is insane that this has not been a thing in 30 years,  what?! #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨Most Chilliest Streamer In Mixer 🚨https://t.co/s5YhwBNxLP  playing the new @HyperJamGame &amp; More  @MixerShares… https://t.co/UD8KhaAQQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mañana a las 8 pm una invitación a todas las mujeres hermosas de Miami de 0 a 100 años a nuestra reunión de Ella en… https://t.co/tonFH1WMCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsDubuque That’s crazy. It’s so frustrating to have to spend this much money in order to keep our jobs and make a livable wage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#phoenixnationasinspirit🔥 Dreams 🦅🔥 🍊🌃 @ Syracuse University https://t.co/xHIvDsWRpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You’re a #RussianAsset &amp; a true enemy of the people! #RussianAssetTrump #PutinsPuppet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinLovden @ProfJaredMedina @WiringTheBrain @3chordwonder @Anjan435 Thanks @MartinLovden — I agree that study is… https://t.co/z6CPUUzw0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jana__Tuttle I was next door at the College and Career Center all day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ms_NSarra it’s in our backyard :) Hope you enjoyed your family day weekend! 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanSekulow OUTRAGES THAT CONVICTED CRIMINALS CAN EVEN RUN FOR CONGRESS.  Omar was arrested in 2013 4 trespassin… https://t.co/cRAkpPp0aF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t usually tweet about cake stuff on here (unless it’s funny). But, I’m pretty stoked about this 4ft tall, 75l… https://t.co/iIDTft3ETL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astrodave2 Think lunch is busy in my schedule. But I’ll see you later tonight then!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can chase the money, but remember it ain’t a race.  •Week 1 is in the books. Last week started an exciting, yet… https://t.co/FqMRlHelyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catturd2 Check out the Glasses! He’s Not Batman! He’s Clark Kent!!😆👏🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Why can’t these men let women decide what to do? Pregnancy carries a risk to the woman and she, not some gover… https://t.co/UdDfPzhdw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RolndKarl @Dax_x98 @dmewing47 AND YOU ARE THE PRIMITIVE VERSION OF A PRIMATE! SO...??? UGH! PEOPLE LIKE YOU ARE SO TIRESOME!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And while I was never a "fan," I liked his dancing and some of his songs. And even I thought *some* of the alleged… https://t.co/tu44xVL4oj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing @muse (my favorite band of all time) was absolutely life changing. I am so incredibly lucky to have shared t… https://t.co/NBYKOc0a4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time, I was praying to Our Lady and St Dominic, for you, and I said if he ever stumbles, please do not let him… https://t.co/ky8jXsnIPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venezuelan Military fires on protesters, burned the trucks that transport Humanitarian Reliefs, kill inocent people… https://t.co/y2XD4jVgcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleEdmun I do too and the worst part is that the parents have done MORE damage to their child’s mental wellbein… https://t.co/jDjSlXA8SY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leafs fans praising Sean Avery is well... typical. He’s known for his class...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Australian Government. Department of Agriculture : Help eliminate battery cages by adding graphic imagery to cage e… https://t.co/OnuvLHFuOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterClines I'm lucky I can't drink and write or I'd be waking up with a vodka smoothie every morning ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/2 - When the fatigue/anger crept in at the sound of my alarm this morning, I thought of my mom who worked 6 days… https://t.co/TuhHcmaJks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattHaneySF The slogan “people’s car” is the English translation of the German name “volks wagon”.   It’s like a F… https://t.co/HbOfZZ0zIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[NASA is set to make 'last planned attempts to contact' Mars rover Opportunity  https://t.co/pOdAjJPUSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mystic_Mile @DanRyckert @ybbaaabby @VinnyCaravella ASSUME DEFENSIVE DAB POSITIONS. https://t.co/w0JqpEY98Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been mia for like 5 days bc I’M NOW A HOMEOWNER PPL 💛💛💛  still not super on the map bc moving/unpacking is no… https://t.co/fOZWGPIgTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yauzzie @BlackoutJoel @jahimes @RepMarkMeadows @realDonaldTrump @MarkMeadows How can anyone be briefed on a meeting that never took place?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyndonws @Alittleunwell67 @InGlockWeTrust @reviewjournal @realDonaldTrump @GovSisolak Yeah is expensive being a so… https://t.co/54g7BnlFov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetBenMax @Tammie4Change @ZackFinkNews @amazon @Newsday @NYSenDems @AndreaSCousins @SenGianaris @toddkaminsky Ev… https://t.co/JVNwaMYQr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kenzj26 is asleep and I know this!!!!! But I’ve still sent her 7 different text messages about random things. Hehe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SavoryandSpice @RepSwalwell Your hate is so divisive you have pushed most Americans away #SavoryandSpice]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just never took the time to learn.... I tried practicing a few times then said forget it. Always had a friend or… https://t.co/2IJoTqcZZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been stressing and studying really hard over my online proctored chem 2 test this past week and I made an 88!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Read Across America Week this week Greenwood @PriscillaSinon @GreenwoodPTA AND keep those crazy socks on for t… https://t.co/tTL4spNRag]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Any time that you are ‘the other’ in the room, you spend 30% of your time thinking about and dealing with that ‘ot… https://t.co/i5O5yzG5Td]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lonnie_Lala @BettyBowers @realDonaldTrump People like Lonnie put the 'so-called" in the term "so-called Christian"… https://t.co/eZlNMs5vEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t go shopping in Oshkosh or fondy anymore. I’ve seen too many people I went to high school with today. It was… https://t.co/tJt5T5Dq4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarnegieMellon @cianrobinson and I met @HeinzCollege. He was a year ahead of me so I kept going to his TA hours un… https://t.co/ahPRZJ7ze4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattressmuncher @up_kahyl @FirstGentleman @JayBranchin_Out Y’all, with your powers combined, bring the most disturbing things to my tl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MerrillHoops It’s been fun following your team all season! Good luck on Saturday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: everyone have a bunch of sex today and don’t use protection because we need more scorpios on this earth]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s one in the morning and I’m thinking about the hair brush from Opening Ceremony for $295 https://t.co/xJsF07bjkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5: I have accepted @MrPetrotta’s challenge to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews, just… https://t.co/nl22NmgqMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanPlasch @andrewintech @JillSommerset @nickisnpdx @anthonynotleon @CoherenceMed @jameyedwards Welcome and in the PNW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[...We don’t yell at flowers to bloom, we enjoy the unfolding beauty. Always reminding myself to go easy on me.… https://t.co/5m8nnGSuya]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Listing🏡 1117 Chelsea Drive, Lake Zurich IL. 60047▪3 Beds▪2.5 Bath▪Townhouse▪Asking:$265,000… https://t.co/L03Towz8Wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lena loved the @HPPMBobcats cheerleaders! #ElementsOfMe #RISDConnects https://t.co/8aESFazPUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PCC_PAC @smachel202 We are here!!! 💚🍍💚 we’ll be exhausted but excited to see everyone #WherePsychOsMeetPsychOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarryRozner I’m so so sorry for your loss. Baruch Dayan HaEmet. May your father’s memory be for a blessing.  🙏🏻 fo… https://t.co/mFsdBW2mBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mmm say no more fam. Bouta drag my husband and kid to Disney just to eat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@accpchest @ChrisCarrollMD Crystalloid bolus Alveoli get flooded Sepsis rages on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffburton1057 @fandango1057 Don’t start something you can’t finish! https://t.co/xx2ASMjPO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Methodist Church has 12 million members in the US, but 62% of that number is over 50. Like all mainline churche… https://t.co/ZZVO7VdejQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yoshirox10 Haha I was like TIM!!!! Lmk when you come back we’ll have to catch up!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it when profs help ya out, but at the same time, it just reinforces my bad behavior. Like this week I turned… https://t.co/n8KzlLKiCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[February Supper Club:   Iberico ham  Ostrich tartare, deep fried quail egg, pickled radish, garlic  Spring mix, man… https://t.co/gU1dR3gZWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMainEBrent Nice! Where at? And yeah I had to SCRAMBLE to find a Non booked room which was nearly impossible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[About last night!  #butfirstletmetakeaselfie #snapchat #cheermumsandfriends #reachthebeach #cheercompetition… https://t.co/MOjEY7pGrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m at the gym rn and some girl just walked by me and i literally jumped IM EMBARRASSED THIS HAS ME EFFED UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of STORM WARNINGS today and all on the road. There continue to be #RainingKs from @lakeeriebase in Maryland 🌪… https://t.co/zk7QLo2ZWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday afternoon with my ladies at @bevhillshotel with sharonmcconochie @CarolineAlexBH #afternoondelight… https://t.co/AhRcCP7heP]]></document><document><![CDATA[First thing I did when I woke up today was buy @mtrench #Phantoms and I listened to it o  the way into work.  GOOD… https://t.co/tYyXvkaeXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@learnadv loved working w/Ts in all content areas @cowanroad1 this year.  TY for always being willing to grow in pr… https://t.co/FenG892VMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me win a dream vacation from Diamond Resorts https://t.co/yiGOl2tuul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dyke, stud or whatever. If u try 2 get with my shawty or think you for some reason got balls, ima have to treat u l… https://t.co/EYKc6jZ6W3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kadeshow I tweeted you about harmony hall saying all I heard was 80s Paul Simon. I was wrong, now I hear The Dead like crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarreroCarolina Mira tu que privilegio tenemos los venezolanos. Por que no dices que Todo AQUEL QUE ESTÉ LEGAL TIE… https://t.co/7UffMU23rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews No one cares.  Only three people will be listening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This right here! Yes! 🙌🏼 Right at about 1:35! Service and silence are NOT the same things! What 5 stories will you… https://t.co/4I5lp7tXKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[bruh how hard is it to just comment on my post I stay getting gassed up in my DMs like uhhhh...WEAKK🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I fall more in love with her everyday. 🥰😍☺️🐶 #Tucker #Tuckeroo #MyTeam #MissYou #VIRescue… https://t.co/GfxdOi3mHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @redsteeze @lyndseyfifield Are u really trying 2 justify your stupidity Ricky?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BIGTurfTeaching That would require frequent updating and I’d much rather ignore all emails until January 2020 and then complain 😊.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnvirtuousAbbey May the Peace and Presence  of God be felt by all who love that young soul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shoobe01 @StacyHolmstedt @betterux_ @adam_ux @NatInteraction That’s excellent!! I think a lot of it has to do with… https://t.co/0bilFlGIUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[We went from a conversation on I-M to Joe Jonas being tied up in red rope. What a time to be alive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who can’t say I can win fort nite....? #girlsrule #pornstar #luvyou #FortniteSeason8 https://t.co/hTSN5lQ5Kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aldermanjoe @MomsDemand Welcome to early childhood education!!! Where do you think people’s kids have been? Did yo… https://t.co/53vw9LLKDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CongoMasks #exhibit @vmfa #RVA @ VMFA Virginia Museum of Fine Arts https://t.co/HzfqE8xxzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 8 Lee takes down No. 9 Turners Falls last night in the first round of the Division IV Western Mass. Boys Basket… https://t.co/Y71knhkvdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[While I was trying to put my makeup on, this dude was over here acting like he's not in my way. #bullet… https://t.co/5UPJLeyn5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlamandGore Showing up for the first time after a traumatic brain injury? Oof. Please tell your doctor. No messing around there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissNyetTrump @JustJaneinWA I would but she doesn’t sound like she’d like me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took my Newnan section of Intro to Anthropology to the Oak Hill Cemetery today! We had fun collecting data which we… https://t.co/QnJNa6jGNh]]></document></documents></author>