<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SmirkyboiArjun @realDonaldTrump The next President will be the most evil of all time. President Trump was put here… https://t.co/JvYt1TA24D]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MorganCarroll on #BroJeff We can make a difference with small money from many people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_dot_Will I think the trailer looks promising. It just depends on what story route they go with. There’s remnants… https://t.co/ytl5WU4aXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting my oil changed and I won’t be out until 2pm 😒🔫 I should’ve made an appt 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rs_ran @NicoletteMpls I don’t have one. Cassoulet and buche de Noel are my two culinary white whales.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahPesner @7sTruth Instead of guessing they should know WTF they're talking.  I just wish Fox and the Repugnacan… https://t.co/KWUZGqgviP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarochi1 Since we only have the "two directions" we lump a lot of issues into one or the other when life is more c… https://t.co/W6yYLF7Ovh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamosLawSP @RiverC_Official @AlyseTobler @oneworldonepeo1 @Dr1ven_Ind @SickNotWeak @ShawnMendes @Dakota_Meyer https://t.co/WCYx7YXgri]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please make a note of it! #PresidentsDayProtests  #PresidentsDay https://t.co/FkJ43MSRlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Pictures Of The Day – 101 Pics @Yuri Goytacaz Goytacaz Trejo Castellon this is what... https://t.co/95AbeyHiU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R24k_at I built this because more stuff is coming my way, namely a jointer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[”Woah I like this woman” Nick Torres   Who doesn't Nick lol #NCIS @NCIS_CBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coltonn baby. Noooo listen to Chris. #TheBachelorFinale https://t.co/QgYtqsFB1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shmee found a new honey. No shame in Shmee's game. 😉 @ Pensacola, Florida https://t.co/JnQ20dsstt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my mom I was getting a red handprint tattooed on my ass cheek tomorrow 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come work with a fantastic, diverse, and hardworking community of school librarians. #DCPSLibraries  🤘😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @CFCurriculum to post 7 covers of nonfiction books I love: No explanations, no revie… https://t.co/m1CD2o9X2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I heard the fire alarms went off today at school. Were they loud?  Caroline: They were loud and freaky! Me: Fre… https://t.co/MleEm1Z0kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my free chance to win $5 in points. Tons of wins here! https://t.co/GjDsK9v7jK #instantwingame]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just listened to Senator Amy Klobuchar’s townhall meeting. I pray that everyone will find this presentation and l… https://t.co/srEwfn70JG]]></document><document><![CDATA[hilarity is good medicine. Photo 43 of 45: Milk Mustache Bash / Baby Shower/Sip &amp; See "Milk Mustache Bash" |...… https://t.co/SQSsuSJjsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 We must push back against the anti-AMERICA democrats never have seen such behavior and corruption .… https://t.co/1fM60ahH7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually appreciated what she wrote. There are so many overused food critique words/terms that are dated or never… https://t.co/C027gr3Q0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are in Evansville to cheer on @AustinPeayWBB at the #OVCTourney.  #LetsGoPeay https://t.co/SgCaA0VdgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoldTV @CalWells @dianafalzone @Ruleyork @KendallJenner @TMZ @HarveyLevinTMZ @TMZLive @bellahadid @emrata… https://t.co/sEG5Kwx9kE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda scary, hard to read, I’m like a ouija board🔮 @ Mint Room Studios https://t.co/Q4L5L0uyBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii The first year is the hardest. Everytime you think of her the tears will come,  but I promise,  one da… https://t.co/u4M1l2zGfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RanttMedia Is the ash on the face of a Catholic, on Ash Wednesday, antithetical to the US Constitution?  Stop push… https://t.co/5uoJXFT5KW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Yeah they're going to have to decide whether continue to leak and go to jail or stop before they do go to jail]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaneharris @JerryLOakley1 They blew it yesterday! I watched his complete testimony. They showed what complete sli… https://t.co/i3AjqPvIhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr   Here’s another story you might have missed while you were rage tweeting about liberals and journa… https://t.co/hCfCQcDrkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@druinok @Sneffleupagus @sophgermain Doesn’t mean people weren’t doing the best they could at the time, but it’s po… https://t.co/1ZOeCI19GB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano May Angels guide you to our Heavenly Father's side. #GoneTooSoon. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the dudes that like me are stupid bitches can someone not stupid like me for once in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giving today the cold shoulder. 28 degrees?!? RUDE!! Do unto others as you would have them do unto you Mother Natur… https://t.co/7GhpjXntbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh sup @splashthat 👀  looking forward to seeing the team at @sxsw in a few weeks. https://t.co/nWM7EHzaf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its been an extremely hard week for me, and I’m going into an even harder month... I just want to be held]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say thank you to trump/pence/gop for that #TaxScamBill we all should pay our fair share and that includes these a$$… https://t.co/d55WPhr7I5]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I asked for Valentine's Day this year. A taco Bell power bowl minus the bean with lots of extra meats and chee… https://t.co/lSitMZFUnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@insertgeekname @elle_york1 @realDonaldTrump They still have to follow the laws]]></document><document><![CDATA[6. They asked for a urine sample. When I got into the bathroom, I suddenly couldn't go. This, too, is done by remot… https://t.co/L6KxSDtLlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao one of my coworkers literally told me I fall into a category of not looking naturally pretty without make up o… https://t.co/tdEGHh6yjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FarrahHaidar In everything in life together this is true #mommasays #ThePROFIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come join us! The party goes until midnight. #universeinmotion #allthatjazz #music #peotry #smoothjazz #livemusic… https://t.co/UKnGU051jK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is something coming from @CNN  At least they’re honest on this point #MichaelCohenLied]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joevp91 El Puente III me parece que a las 11:30 pm, el I y II no cierran pero no son de carga.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BelPlaineCSD Dr. Seuss week my reading intervention group recording Seuss books we will create iMovies and share t… https://t.co/rtKir8gkbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[at this point, it’s one and done. you got one time to show me some shit ion like and that’s it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry Darmstadt we had to steal @J_deannnn for the night🤷‍♀️💛 We love amd miss you sm💛 @CarterLoveless @collin_n98… https://t.co/Nh7UYPXSXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[and if you’re still breathing you’re the lucky ones ✨ https://t.co/h8XCdBCSRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christianrache8 Thanks! It actually went by super fast because it’s a very busy job.hope you are also having a great Saturday!😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of looking dumb on the Internet because I don’t pay attention to spelling errors]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ghanacelebrity Having studied Ghana, I totally agree. Too much corruption that the President has promised to address but hasn't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It remains vital to contact your state legislators and Governor Wolf to express your desire to keep Philadelphia a… https://t.co/4LsS7NqDfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolFosse1 @DonaldJTrumpJr Oh look a merde meme! Not clever or intelligent!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me : oh yeah this is why I started disliking them, wow they’re a shitty f person  My toxic ass : doesn’t unfollow them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. It's "a person's a person no matter how small" said Dr Seuss in "Horton hears a Who". It's a perfect #prolife… https://t.co/n5fDCzwFZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HOWARD100Quotes @HowardStern Not fooling me.  Why is your beard white?  Your hairline is almost at your eyebrow, impossible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodxs789 @6abc Are you serious or are you make an inappropriate joke about the Democratic party ?.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top #5Actions to Do This Week: February 16, 2019, courtesy of MomsRising https://t.co/oBXEnuFZeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw the news about Luke Perry, and my first thought was, has anyone checked on the @CryMeaPodcast boys? https://t.co/RKbpZTHqjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I’m 99% sure she was screaming at no one and that’s kind of terrifying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @RobertV12Larkin Hoping she gets triple the time Manafort did!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer @RedTRaccoon I second what hoarse said.   Had it for years.   If it's REALLY painful, go see an ort… https://t.co/HRirTBOWl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends won’t take me to my therapy session at the Chaos piercing chair. I’m sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[k sorry but I have to party with jack barakat before I die and that’s my one requirement]]></document><document><![CDATA[i dont want to cry every night at 2:00 am not able to sleep, but its become routine. love that for myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This moment is all there is” - Lenny Kravitz 📷: jsamsphoto  cc: @gibsonguitar @sesac #killakam #kameroncorvet… https://t.co/3q2e7aqhC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alyssabernal @PerezHilton @KylieJenner @jordynwoods I really, really, really don't care! I do care that this ridic… https://t.co/ZC5gqTNr8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoscoJVTeam @MAGATrumpster @sweatervest13 @GlennKesslerWP Yes. Facts matter. Which is why racist rhetoric has been… https://t.co/P3NJ9NlQMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's time for the @NRA to go.  They have just forfeited the right to exist IMO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have company while I'm cleaning! Love my kitties! @ Northeast Minneapolis https://t.co/uCdnSzmmrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cody Bellinger. #codybellinger #mlb #baseball #topps #lad #dodgers #losangeles https://t.co/NvnXn4Rsif]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Now he better get the punishment he deserves 😒 https://t.co/biNWePldaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KRON4WTran @kron4news The district office staff should have a cap put on their pay for the next three years so the… https://t.co/4fsv3Mn0WH]]></document><document><![CDATA[if they have a problem doing it I will GLADLY take their place, sweetie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecNielsen @DHSgov #Resign you are a threat in families... Baby stealer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VH1PNUT___ @fmedina62 Naaaaah, she found someone who treated her like the queen she is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyitsmerob @VirginiaDECA @GRHS_Stallions @MrsGilchristVB @Decastallion @kiaraaaperez @arianaraquell1 @bettyethi0 Next time Smith!☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell/"second death" is complicated in Scripture and theology. But I'm also grateful to have the fire in my bones re… https://t.co/nxgnYg9otS]]></document><document><![CDATA[How fitting that I would finish my 22nd half marathon in my favorite city! #RUNAUSTIN #RunForTheBling #SlowRunner… https://t.co/ov0ulcnNRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a moment when the time space continuum lines up just right, and you add bourbon and a @WhiteCastle Sack of… https://t.co/627WKyYQbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@News8Daybreak My favorite President will be the one that makes Federal Holidays paid mandatory Holidays for ALL working Americans!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@henakhanbooks,  I LOVE this picture so much!! 😘📚✨💕 You’re an inspiration!! 😍 https://t.co/0nCn3Zrd4f https://t.co/N9PtNTBV2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's 2:00am in the morning &amp; I can't sleep maybe if I go watch some Rowan Atkinson it'll help me sleep. 😴💤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hansakwast @directionsmag I have been looking for good international data for course exercises. These are helpful @hansakwast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Saintsfan5348 @AdamParkhomenko Anxiety is real ..... I know ...... (personally) 😞😞 https://t.co/2qQ6AxlQ1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lustrationsy I’m just thinking though that would be cornering himself, like more than normal, because in these wor… https://t.co/qQvvEFV3kv]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/V6M2jHIIyN  Atlantic Rhythm Section  "Imaginery Lover" ❤💖💕  #rocknroll #popmusic #70smusic  #Classics… https://t.co/xAgwwCe0xc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@News8Daybreak @SoniaAzadTV @roncorning  Appropriate that we have my love's funeral on #nationalmargaritaday. He LO… https://t.co/rUL5e611GI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton You interfered with the election more than any foreign entity and it blew up in your face.  Now you… https://t.co/ycUy58du2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know Lil’Jordan Humphrey is a good football player..  but he did not have a good combine — at all.  Measured in u… https://t.co/CGKclR6Hr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time making Gacha Epic Rap Battle: Cathy VS Macy. All characters, animations, and sounds belong to their resp… https://t.co/j5E8K3VupD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This beautiful illustration by yours truly comes from today's blog post:  https://t.co/rSt7iqkiN5 #KALEIDOSCOPE… https://t.co/xbfVU9UQVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I am Thankful to God for all I have and for all He is doing for me. Thank you Lord for your Live and Protection . Amen 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Souvenir from New-York #NewYork #USA 🇺🇸🏙 @ Empire State Building https://t.co/ZpBqIrVSkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fredy3000 @RalitoDigital @LaTaTcherOne Lo mismito pasa en Ecuador y en la mayoría de países de sudamericana, y no… https://t.co/cxyeCSYwyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO MUCH FUN,,READING MY TWEETS TO MYSELF!!!!NOT ONE HAS BEEN RELEASED TO THE TWITTER PUBLIC... TWITTER SQUELCHING O… https://t.co/MpAZDmD6BB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbyblujay Omg I have never heard that ever. What kind of crazy person says that??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/Z6ueMh4BpC]]></document></documents></author>