<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Are you a believer in #CBD?  One of our #Fox reporters did an investigation into the effects and risks.  Now on @FOX29philly #fox29goodday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read this and then tell me the NY Times and Washington Post are not peddling fake news, just like they did in 2003… https://t.co/xqcLV2rEVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cathmckenna All human live is only 4 % of CO2.  Industral is small part from this 4%.  This is not problem of poll… https://t.co/pIqjHIaFPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cferrera13 @TomFornelli This is actually the most confusing thing I have ever seen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open House today @ 427 Kendall Ave, Highland Park, 4bed 2bth, 1389sqft, asking $899k #highlandpark #nela… https://t.co/Xs2Vg9hFvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just need to talk to your friends about everything...or nothing at all! 😂 @bfoxxie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy crap, I work at Apple!!! There are some days, and there should be more of them honestly, where I look at the … https://t.co/2v45OiRCoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ewwjr53 Ooh, look! Here’s another screenshot from my AT&amp;T WiFi. https://t.co/k3a3tAjFTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaDesabrais @HeyJayJRogers @burakowsky She seems very aware of the words she’s using &amp; her intent. It’s a horrible look.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I WANT THE ROLLS ROYCE FOR ME AND MA GIRL, BUT SHE MISSING SO GIVE ME THE RARI INSTEAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claytoonz WHY DOESN'T PRESIDENT TRUMP DOUBLE DOWN ON HIS BIRTHER BS?? Obama's Kenyan Brother interviewed by Direct… https://t.co/GecUFTqXcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[btw i was guessing that it was only 100cc i was about ready to bladder scan myself at work]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm in train muthafucka (@ Amtrak 28 (PDX- SPK) in Portland, OR) https://t.co/9CHdu28dJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[You only got mad likes when you are showing your body off . I guess that was the only reason I liked you too .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is Almost here  Spring Starts In a Month 😍😍 https://t.co/FmSP0v3Ry7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not very happy with America I really wamt to move to a better country. And there are better nations to move too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simona Halep bounced in Quarter Final in Dubai by Belinda Bencic...SH 13 double faults in match..BB rolling after d… https://t.co/DKteanU3o6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohanBBT @rangercreek @MisterTHistory @sandieGOlakers @Fake_Canadian_ @Stef_Pellerin @RedStripeRocco @FhzFun… https://t.co/VUxAZ0qeLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi @MckennaMaycock it was great to see you play @BonniesWBB against Davidson a couple weeks back.  You have great t… https://t.co/ASoMYgEKTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last evening, I had the pleasure of being on the panel "Finding My Voice," which honored Dr. James Hal Cone. We sha… https://t.co/OkE0dPl1kW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My colleagues then found Az's charter movement was like the Oklahoma land rush, with a learn as you go attitude. https://t.co/oTq0BF9XOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social Media Is Harmful to Your Brain and Relationships | Psychology Today https://t.co/xaRI6YNRiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@profamymcgovern @overleaf Worth noting that Overleaf also saved the previous version in "History," so they did something right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 718 Shane Drive #Maryville #TN  #realestate https://t.co/KSnnLe721c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve finally got some peace after being destroyed and robbed of it. I’m proudly far from who I was. I’m back in my… https://t.co/XAfUdL0ezc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grats to @NerdiumPodcast for being follower 666! https://t.co/eXeAA62sZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @AcmeOyster House in New Orleans, LA https://t.co/mQ2beAB5bX https://t.co/d0zO8xfooO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pimathman @neontaster @RussianBear Only because he was angry with himself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSalata Agreed. Take a 9pt swing at 125 away and add in Kemerer. What’s the dual score?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are getting tired of his continuous unamerican sentiments of our democracy and democratic institutions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimH_Cincy @charliehatch_ Makes sense. So they didn’t even go to VAR in that case?  Same for all whistled PK’s?  Much still to learn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwaggXBL @PrestigeIsKey @ApollosMission @Tony_Flame Agree please make videos to the DEVS and ask them to remove it… https://t.co/c6isftb0Qf]]></document><document><![CDATA[No school for @BellevueSchools. Please stay safe and warm today. We will see everyone back in school tomorrow.… https://t.co/YqljWePKXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes i think about the jello shot girl at coyote ugly in Nashville a year and a half ago who gently stroked my… https://t.co/Sn0EW0d2fO]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the past 10yrs @seankelly2121 has scarred me from ketchup, I can’t even look at that shit anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Triathlon789 @MONTANEuk @ETO_2018 @terraglacialis @firepotfood @Talkultra @_LowriMorgan @Likeys @BBCSport Blown aw… https://t.co/E0wBHw82Vz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessPrian No es así. De hecho 21 pesos es un precio muy elevado. Tal vez hablas de la frontera de Tamaulipas y… https://t.co/bfoZPSiJDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KySportsRadio @MikeOudeh @william_said98 I was trying to understand the terrible comment. @KSBarAndGrille  wings a… https://t.co/CEvLgglwus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicagoland only not doing any trips until April! #letscreare https://t.co/asH6zZClOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got stopped by a homeless man last night while on a walk, asking me to call the police on him so an officer can t… https://t.co/MzAIHlG87R]]></document><document><![CDATA[...The only way to resolve the conflict is to blame an outsider—a foreigner, a cripple, a king, a woman. The mob un… https://t.co/W91qvkxTDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marca Marca-Madrid, cuantas copas van a ganar esta temporada? Marca-Madrid a llorar al tartagal!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning!  Follow your gut instincts and your good feelings.  This is a really good picture , right? #instinct… https://t.co/2eWl4U4dT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wafaalamimi @amhfarraj Oh no lol...we need an inside force!  Take a look here ⏬⏬⏬  https://t.co/qVQjsNgKIe  KSA❤️… https://t.co/UtilEUjCFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMossEsq @gtconway3d @mattgaetz He’s fine. He pre-cleared the tweet with Rudy G]]></document><document><![CDATA[A quick pop through the LA Farmers Market near CBS Studios! #lafarmersmarket #lunch #losangeles @ La Farmers' Market https://t.co/gZSweNrEvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[El que posee las nociones más exactas sobre las causas de las cosas y es capaz de dar perfecta cuenta de ellas en s… https://t.co/ashdvWkNWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleDigby @drewmckevitt @davantelewis Louisiana government is all about austerity, except when it comes to corporate welfare.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeAllen2ft8 @Matt_Baker6 Uh. The big white button and the button on the side?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dave73in Sanders is a nobody.  He praised Soviet Russia and was quite fond of communism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All four kids got Kershaw's autograph!  @Dodgers https://t.co/zWcL1Yjya1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be signing up for the Disney half marathon that is in Jan 2020, so I best be getting myself running soon.  A… https://t.co/mG89uOD5MW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roweeeyourboat @dunkindonuts if they don’t make it right for you i’ll never have dunkin again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonRuzycki @manwhohasitall Lol I hope leaving Linus Pauling out was intentional, that would be so on brand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomRaffa3 @isaiahthomas It was a good trade that’s why. Always gunna love IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Few weeks late, but it was still a great show. Thanks @corywong @ Lincoln Hall https://t.co/eIWB2xH9Xv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lkhtmn @mistermike1125 @AllisonLCarter @indystar @justinlmack Not true. Traffic fell. https://t.co/bHmPOf6404  https://t.co/Yoow1rM7Jh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pillager Elementary School February Student of the Month: 1st Grade, Integrity https://t.co/BDfpPGUP4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CGasparino @gwestr @LJMoynihan @WarrenBuffett @ElonTusk @elonmusk Buffet has one “t”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barmore27 @sandy___21 You were looking into your own empty, greedy pit if a soul, commie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharylAttkisson @AOC Elizabeth Warren - saw her video earlier today  Happy Friday]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know almost nothing about the Marvel universe, but Goose is a very good boy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when everyone was hating on LaMelo Ball after he dropped 92 points in high school, people HATE to see yo… https://t.co/SJHQh7eXRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaneDennis34 I wanna call in and tell my favorite OSU-WSU story. Involves Steenstra and Lou Lucca.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duncan Robinson, who didn’t play a second in the first half, starts the second for the #Heat and drills a 3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BLOG:https://t.co/NNHO6c74yq  Check out this video we produced for the @LinesBallet #SummerProgram2019 and REGISTER NOW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bankaccount #gunstore #groot #gun #money #broke #rifle #handgun #cash #ruger #glock #baretta #remington #movie… https://t.co/aZ3BPKg8oM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Affinity for Minimalism @ Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago https://t.co/YcxSYeERYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green deal is so stupid and ludicrous    Why talk about IT OR Alexandria ????!cortez or whatever her name is      S… https://t.co/7HHJENThM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of our listing on Lot 26 N Ridge Rd #Perkinston #MS  #realestate https://t.co/SJ5ybMqjwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertDDamron @andrewlangan1 @AlanShipnuck @USGA @RandA 💯✅...grow the game...scsring people away from it currently… https://t.co/9F3M1IUR1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks at Cano and Pujols🤦🏽‍♂️ this is why you don’t Sign guys to these type of deals. #PhilliesDontDoIt 🙏🏽🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @jenwiderstrom with 💣💣💣 ・・・ ☝️ BEFORE —  AFTER ☝️ Can you guess how far apart these photos were taken?  Her… https://t.co/jvVG5G66Z7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys keep my wife and our family in your prayers my wife grandmother just passed away this morning we are still… https://t.co/HXERiecfwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stonekettle @iMissMollyIvins It's all the Fascist propaganda of privilege and power, forever subverting human righ… https://t.co/2oKZvHqO9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m one happy dude right now.. Proud of my Legacy KZoo team. Being your coach is an absolute ride of a lifetime. Al… https://t.co/ZXjV55gR9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganCWallen @SXMTheHighway How do you single out one song 🤷‍♂️.....@MorganCWallen on repeat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJoeKennedy The rational-thinking people left in this country simply cannot allow this to happen. Trump is gross… https://t.co/cncGQqY42d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@W_Alhusseini @RiMartineau l'Indonésie, un autre "shit hole" où j'irais Jamais.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upcoming #Cannabis earnings, all reports are after market: MedMen Feb 27 $MMNFF, Acreage Mar 12 $ACRGF, Tilray Mar 18 $TLRY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What? Too busy playing golf and senselessly spending our tax dollars to worry about your " nationa… https://t.co/2ZXkGWzO52]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's hard work being a cat...  #caturday @ Sioux Falls, South Dakota https://t.co/KSxh4dIXmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny but that @realDonaldTrump is not a Christian is one of his few redeeming qualities (and his quote about… https://t.co/p5Ad1OWvdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[223 Remington brass casings for sale at the best prices! Inspected, cleaned and polished with FREE Shipping and NO… https://t.co/cPcAQXQE9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge gap between Mississippi and Louisiana. Here in the greatest state in America, we throw it on the grill. In the… https://t.co/4t3BlrtNuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother told me I was too nice. I also had an ex and a fling tell me the same thing... time to make a change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryLBowman1961 Go ahead at least it would be somewhat original!  UNC is shot and looking at all the responses the… https://t.co/mtXJF668kq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yamiche Reminder: HUD official Lynn Patton is an unqualified hack, who has no business being in public life.   She… https://t.co/DZ1wU35N3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @RashidaTlaib She called N accomplished black woman a “token”. THAT is “racist” and extremely insensitive. Sor… https://t.co/JQ8DBPj1B0]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many cool involved in tonight’s Valentines Day Haven Memorial Park Fundraiser. Please know my wife and I can’t b… https://t.co/396kQ1r7RO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BRADPAYNE @darren_fentress @jasonkinkade I’d already be in triage before the left hook came.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome opportunity to learn from @braves SVP of Marketing Adam Zimmerman at today's @georgiatechbsch MarTech Confe… https://t.co/osStLYZUu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_waleedshahid Honestly I really don’t understand Biden risking his entire legacy just because he really wants to b… https://t.co/AQenZcmRIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please get Jeff Goldblum on #officehourspodcast @timheidecker Why do you rarely use your hollywood contacts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been having this same experience every Sunday for the last 3-4 weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @austinfaith24  signing with @Lamar_Baseball . https://t.co/L4zmDA0S3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Srirachaaa @jaredjaffee21 @ChipLDR @WPT Well did he fk her? If so, how was his performance?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kari___D @James_NoahJames I like dive bars consider me interested for sure. I also think Noah should come up here]]></document><document><![CDATA[As of right now whose body is being held together with more medical tape? Becky or Tanahashi?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Morning at 9:05 am EST The Crew at @KBLUAM560 @RusstClark and @GeoBraunRadio Chat with an Old Friend… https://t.co/QDYY97cCjD]]></document></documents></author>