<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Man of the Woods was amazing!!! JT is a helluva performer!! @ Staples Center https://t.co/WHr9S2UldU]]></document><document><![CDATA[manny machado now making  roughly $82,000 a day...bryce harper (slightly less than that) but still making $156,600… https://t.co/25o7ENQP0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Plumas Lake &amp; Riverside Meadows Roadrunners! https://t.co/E1oyryYKTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[She shouldn’t have got dragged but big fella delete ya social media cause niggas don’t hold back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportsdrenched @h8rproof82 @kkwhb No, but he's a good pretend friend.  Bubba Clyde,  at your service.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your not bringing your Valentine's a heart shaped lollipop stick in your dick. You're doing it wrong. lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another happy patient that has been with me for 30 years now. He has had successful implant treatment and is obviou… https://t.co/bLni5J9mWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know we don't really do Valentine's Day. But I decided to do Valentine's Day. Love you @lahnnabell 😘😍😙 @ Golden H… https://t.co/7f5PB2d19K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhHell_Cherry Are you better today TN Cherry? Just making sure you ok. Always here to talk to you, my beautiful friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeycuts22 Yo that’s underrated give him the video you fuckin asshole we’re big fans @patstay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWNT @mattybiigcat They're making the claim, yes, but in practice, never happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brunch is definitely the best meal! (at @RepublicMn in Minneapolis, MN) https://t.co/vGZqCRy7SN https://t.co/sF5MZYjGbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MOVIEidol so I looked more into it and I think I got it https://t.co/ktvXqn4PDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadLabMMA @GuruEliteDFS My best lineup of the night! https://t.co/ab42AytXtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the greatest and toughest men i had the pleasure to know....mangia bene eat @MPizzaman  #whitestone #queens… https://t.co/FOxS3VMDS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny how the things that are capable of making our hearts swell to their brims can leave us feeling oh so emp… https://t.co/dQUxGmXrvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLasAmericas Han engañado al pueblo Graves riesgos y reacciones secundarias estan cientificamente demostrados como… https://t.co/ntmOoCrSIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2 sectional preview...Ever since their season opening win over OHara, Amherst has been riding high as one of the t… https://t.co/4Da5U17c4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone fucking respond. I got a whole paragraph for your ass you’ll have to go to the dictionary to understand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald J Trump again shows that he's a fucking moron. #TrumpCrimeFamily #TrumpLiesEverytimeHeSpeaks]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my eyes when John Middleton said he’s willing to spend “stupid” money this offseason I assumed that meant we wou… https://t.co/a9F8JSdRBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianLRenfroe @DOBrienATL Love Joker Marchant. The upgrades they did are tremendous. Now, their only problem is be… https://t.co/D3gar2B1bp]]></document><document><![CDATA[_ 𝘥𝘪𝘳𝘵𝘺 𝘥𝘪𝘢𝘯𝘢 - 𝘪 𝘸𝘢𝘴 𝘢 𝘮𝘦𝘴𝘴 𝘣𝘶𝘵 𝘵𝘩𝘦𝘴𝘦 𝘭𝘢𝘥𝘪𝘦𝘴 𝘸𝘦𝘳𝘦 𝘢𝘮𝘢𝘻𝘪𝘯𝘨.  _ 𝘤𝘩𝘰𝘳𝘦𝘰𝘨𝘳𝘢𝘱𝘩𝘦𝘥 𝘣𝘺 @𝘤𝘩𝘢𝘤𝘩𝘢_𝘢𝘴𝘦𝘯𝘢𝘷 @ Ohlone College https://t.co/R52McdSFFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moonshine 😋😋😋😋😋☝🏻☝🏻🤘🏻👍🏻💥💥💥✅✅✅✅💯💯💯💯 @ Levittown, Pennsylvania https://t.co/OGxc0EKAs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[A story spread on housing Twitter last week said voters are not rallying behind new housing. But election results s… https://t.co/rgEMqCaL0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Debber66 @DineshDSouza W huh o cares about them cause most of them didnt do anything but hurt America]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eisadore1 @JamelHerring Im not sure bro. But Dru Hill argues alot so I wouldn't be shocked if it was behind the scenes drama for real.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all think high school track meets are long???? Nah y’all don’t even know about them college meets 😅😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[2020! My time will drop. Release date will be announced Rt https://t.co/yeECu1dcUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuePersists @RepThomasMassie Nope!!!! Absolutely not..........that’s reserved for the left]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Corde61944395 It doesn't matter if it's evolved in. It doesn't matter if it's natural.  It doesn't matter if it fe… https://t.co/VkcYQNbPHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulcbetts TBC in the morning. It's 940pm over here and I can't risk opening my laptop near WiFi.   I am well, am… https://t.co/T02kVul63e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC You did pull stunts trying not to do your job of oversight of this and all administrations!You Are… https://t.co/9cA5IR0sLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[As última vezes que vim aos EUA foram em NY e Califórnia, onde vi muitos Tesla. E aqui no Texas são muitos. Muitos!… https://t.co/e9OQa2WkrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quite possibly the slowest half of basketball to ever have been played https://t.co/Ki5oTUXj2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[“🌙 ECLIPSE “ •Muse- erindurflinger  •MUA- @makeupbyjuan88  •Location- evolvemakeupartistry Studios •Photography- Aa… https://t.co/Yt83Z7cnsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outsilver87 @bertkreischer What an awesome show!  That Starbucks joke was phenomenal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anik says Cain is arguably the greatest Heavyweight of all time!? 🤔  What’s there to argue about? DC is the Heavywe… https://t.co/ua9voFqsqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[We sincerely hope that the humanitarian aid actually reaches those in need; and is not stolen by thugs of the regim… https://t.co/nepo0s3AYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelov13 @GeoffGrammer Imagine losing on the court and on Twitter 😬 https://t.co/fRCo9aTpBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mummsie2 🤣🤣🤣  Good luck!! Please be careful and get where you’re going safely!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RanesHook @Haydenfilms What we never find out is the actual balloting, and who got what votes, I got the feeling t… https://t.co/FpqduuVzEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski Yup! But. I do kinda like thin mints. But then, I’m crazy so.. https://t.co/XZsW0y7uvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone better wish my dog a happy six month bday cuz she’s a baddddieeeeeeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting. Do u suppose there’s some connection to #Russia? With @realDonaldTrump there’s always a connection to… https://t.co/YVlRgnwOGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GutterTheGreat Gutter I'm Fat Monday thru Sunday. https://t.co/ym31yexMsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StickmanBleedin Doing better on the lower fat content than I am. Been refusing to eat less than 80/20.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.) made it look easy, but staff worked with her for days to prepare her questio… https://t.co/zszockxU4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twisted_twins Feel better soon and get plenty of rest. My mom use to put peppermint ointment under each nostril an… https://t.co/bUEKPoU8xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spatzyspatz @atl_families @AFAEE_ED @sara_womack @dwhiteatlanta @CarstarphenMJ You are so awesome!! I know your pr… https://t.co/09pOFeCKJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Obama never got so many hits of hatred while he was in office except by the most hated people in America… https://t.co/hMmjMaS2aP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want three day weekends every week, six hour work days, and death to daylight savings. Is that asking too mu… https://t.co/DA2uTtbVY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy HUMP DAY, hope you are having a great day. I’ll be bartending and Lenny will be your Barback at GYM BAR from… https://t.co/Dg3Qbn3c5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only broke ass entitled people say shit like this, “yo i see you got some money, so imma just take that while i sit… https://t.co/vj3GsPyYpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can we believe your word against the crime boss when you're a literal criminal that the crime boss hired to do crimes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was a stunning explanation of how the status of victomhood is a plague in our society.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can anybody like this douchebag? His kids must be really proud......@russwest44 get yo shit together bruh. You… https://t.co/RPdA8BodaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Few days off and a radio conference and who's that lol. #ThursdayThoughts #ThursdayMotivation https://t.co/NNopzVmWYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are days when you must run indoors.  Waking up at 5am to 32° and rain does not sound like a day that I want to spend outside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteRowePhoto @footballkitbox @ballandthecity @DrSnowdon @Coventry_City @RealTomEnglish @FCKitGuru @The_Kitsman… https://t.co/blCJMb7880]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny really the crazy left are putting up a state of really crazy candidates to take on President Trump.The only t… https://t.co/znyHLuMrnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaOttery Gay marriage is not real marriage. The Biblical definition of marriage is between a man and a woman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swmckercher So cringeworthy this one will be a great one for the vault when Harper is celebrating a WS on Broad St… https://t.co/Do6ty16jl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn...I'm just now going to bed, but winning that 💲💲💲 playing poker was worth it 🤑 @I_Mar24]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemetricDWarren can you keep me posted on my Oklahoma boys?! @melvv7 @SevyMorrison28 @JJHester_8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumanistReport @SenSanders Our president has been working hard to bring our young women and men home. What has he… https://t.co/H9vhCDtFOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CartridgeBrosP2 @dege13 @k_song @CartridgeBros Watch Moana with the kid-o! https://t.co/SWJausoRmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[See below for how #racism works. It’s not merely closed polls and white hoods. It’s systemic and financial… https://t.co/lhO4Mvx33u]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 4 Wheel Baby - All set to go home. #toyotatacoma #5WD #snowstorm #harrison #chefmichael #princessandpop @ Harris… https://t.co/WXc7U8zc0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monte Vista CA Fri Feb 22nd AM Forecast: TODAY Sunny Hi 59 TONIGHT Mostly Clear Lo 35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billpeduto What’s so funny about peace love &amp; understanding? You’re my mayor and I’d like to know]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CapitanMarvel was enjoyable. Parts Thor, Parts GOTG with a kick of Captain America too. 8/10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wii49424264 It doesn’t affect the area we are going to. It’s primarily in the capital Port Au Prince and we are heading into Cap-Haitien]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayer tuvimos que irnos por un pata se hizo la caca en medio de la pista de baile 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know why I don't believe in God??? Cause I have blonde, basically translucent eyebrows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pensfannc5 Enjoy that off time!! I just got here, full day ahead of me!!👊👍😭🤣😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have lived in Colorado for over a year and a half now and I don’t own a pair of gloves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Samsung is able to implement a fingerprint sensor in an all screen display, as well as on the power button, yet… https://t.co/RUtZsJoU52]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's like a fighting instructor and suddenly end up on board then they walk away from the crash https://t.co/JJsRbdFmbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[What can i say....I love sweets....oh and tacos 😂😂🤣🤣 https://t.co/USuF7oo4Uc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson @GOPLeader @SenateGOP @POTUS @FTC It's past time to bring anti-trust action against @Google @YouTube… https://t.co/u88IxBvoh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cdnfarmgirl @MsJayLee22 @mco_xxviii @jdstalnaked @judyohtweets @lauralaxla @of_ramblings @MrsTyler78 @lovethat4you… https://t.co/fMNs3TO719]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_Moscrop @seankelly014 I just saw on Facebook that the yellow vest protesters are "neon nazis."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepStevenSmith @tedlieu Unlike you, he's a patriotic man who places country over party. Putin rejoices as you and… https://t.co/WxmmqGzU05]]></document><document><![CDATA[COMING TO https://t.co/TGHR8YPHeO  MARCH 16 th  2019 https://t.co/duh4g5EGvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love your drawing...It's creative and it gives off a nice #feeling of #wonderment!  Thanks for sharing Eleanor...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lozzercozzer @FramGommendy @truzzza @DailySquashRep Brilliant as always Loz 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CD1025Morning Korpi will be traded! Somebody wants him in exchange for D man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ndymium6 @selena_barber @IanSams @TexasPete Both but yes, particularly black people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Todd4Golf @VirginAustralia Heading in early to get acclimated to USA winter conditions 🥶 before heading to Indy fo… https://t.co/M2e7Gt3GbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordyn Woods just went live on Instagram. We’re getting a dramatic interview soon omg https://t.co/qrUPZaFvss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidSantoro1 Available at all fine bookstores and online retailers! https://t.co/xhTMOAuKa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oops, we did it again 🏆🏆😈🏀  #HarrisonBound #StrongerTogether https://t.co/Tetx8e1Fav]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarioLopezExtra @onwithmario In that case, i wish I was your newborn child 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarlenTrevino Esa laptop te extraño por irte de vacaciones, tanto que fue intento de suicidio y se auto  quemó un cable. ={. Oknot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WerlySportsLaw That’s as natural a fit as I can imagine. It’s nothing you won’t be able to jump into. You’ll be ed… https://t.co/ZvANRWbbCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you just do everything on the fly.... memorandum of misunderstanding]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tony1977tony @Oprah @HBO LaToya told the TRUTH about her pedophile brother Jacko! "My mother showed me checks for… https://t.co/kCaB2Pojgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Maduro Regime is capable of anything at this stage. From hiring armed thugs, to using inmates to repress and mu… https://t.co/zrRjIrIZIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARonReddit @NickBromberg Kurt isn’t one of my favorites.  Ryan Earnhardt was pretty good though, and I’m a hug… https://t.co/m2IaxVwafa]]></document></documents></author>