<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JCPSAsstSuptTR supporting @IROQUOIS_HS @JCPSKY #teamwork https://t.co/8K3HbAhQIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost 3am and @Carlos_Salcido1 still makes fun of me. Why are we the way that we are 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Cows that I know owned by my friends.” @haleymueller037   12 hours in the car is gonna be fun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@people @ladygaga Congratulations Gaga!  You were fabulous and that song with Bradley was just hot🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zackwagman @janekleeb @eccobooks Would love to see a galley of this when available! Key for this future scholar on rural life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only riveting, but terrifying...I've never seen @JoeNBC, doing his best, #Joe, like #EdwardRMurrow? I knew the… https://t.co/lBjOGryH05]]></document><document><![CDATA[The forecast said to expect up to 2 inches of snow by my house and judging by Mr. Prince Michael's reaction, the fl… https://t.co/UBeGdo7SXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chemm80 Two of the ones already in here are ones I made, the third was a gift to Stacy that she loves and the four… https://t.co/U0jQ8HM6e3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Off_SarahLouise #Timeless!! On @Hulu! @TimelessSPTV #SaveTimeless https://t.co/UwzVaC44Xf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday  I am my maternal ancestors wildest dreams... ——————————————————— I cry but I’m not weak. I… https://t.co/EMlDr54g7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[FREE. SAFE. HOME!!!🏡🏡🏡😭😭😭👍👍👍  Happy furever life, precious Rico!!!🤗🤗🤗😘😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The Perfect Disguise by @dogfishbeer @ Burney Center — https://t.co/Du6l5sUkUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still can’t get over the fact it’s youtubers that make more than heart surgeons but okay ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have to s/o Charles Wheeler of @100BlackMen who always comes through to support @charteralliance. Great times at th… https://t.co/k6R7ETw3XK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karap214 @Shvartacus The look on this dog’s face, like you have betrayed by shrinking the bed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So delicious. @gusandgrey #sassy #redhead #jam #strawberry #ginger #detroit #michigan #madeindetroit https://t.co/BoSKScjRBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #CaptainMarvel day today with @pocketwriter and @JakkiAMc. I am so ready.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCYB_Bailey Thank you so much for the kind words.❤️ Be safe and please stay in touch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lie #10,000 4 @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @WhiteHouse @GOP @SenateGOP @HouseGOP @charliekirk11 @BillSpadea… https://t.co/xCT4LaFDCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lopz...si no cumples como presidente y saludas a la bandera, porque si deseabas, suspirabas la banda presidencial??… https://t.co/cJiRVXhmoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[these next two weeks are eat, sleep, breathe school/DG so if u see me and I look dead that’s why]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dude was really tryna have me clock out and go out drinking with him last night]]></document><document><![CDATA[trying to surprise my sister and her best friend with ariana grande tickets but all the resales are insanely expensive 🥵🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noradaexploraa @lauraEwiley @sallymfox i’m genuinely so deeply invested in this it’s making me realize i need some hobbies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tv7israelnews the new version of the orical optical system lol Haha that's funny @netanyahu @IDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gop @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @SenatorRomney @BenSasse @lisamurkowski @LamarAlexander @SenatorCollins… https://t.co/wAakX8urco]]></document><document><![CDATA[listen. i’ve had both and in n out is still undefeated🤷🏾‍♀️ y’all in n out the knock off version anyway. you ain’t… https://t.co/tfEaOj9KEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[just like niggas be plotting to smash several friends in the group, women be on go too. win/win. 🤧🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #ValentinesDay love the way @MileyCyrus keeps us on our toes 😂 !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[De turistas con los viejos 🚂  #parentstrip #trainride #metrolink #daytrip @ Mission San Juan Capistrano, CA https://t.co/im1pRYawp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump I'm the same way! I'm not going to trade tweets with morons that just raise my BP… https://t.co/0lUlpGjBIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who the fuck you think you foolin’  With them lil ass guns and that fake ass jewelry lil nigga 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoHWFanClub Good Morning Helene! Happy Friday and Happy March ☀️ https://t.co/ptb6L9lRw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebmoti I hope you're not holding your breath, Moti. #ksleg has shown they're happy with no one being happy, as lo… https://t.co/7KKPboTvXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can still recite all of Jesus Loves Me in Latin that I learned in the 1st grade at a private school, but don’t as… https://t.co/1ZZtfoV3Y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The modern librarian is equal parts caregiver, local hero and geek squad member https://t.co/obcS9HFfhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are not going to find an honest mobster testify against the mob boss. Shut up Jordan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atticus_flinch @IndieWire Constant division!  So sick of it!  United we stand, divided we fall!  Old saying, but true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonHepworth3 @Ant_DC_ @gsmooth89 @ashnotatree @Romel_Garcia @fairyfiesty_fay @kasimarieDC @thechriswatt… https://t.co/F19AXS86Av]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you controlforever for picking me as the contest winner tonight for a meet &amp; greet with @ltsMoonBoy &amp;… https://t.co/4Ei7xAhTWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone who is at ease and at peace is alive and receptive. They embrace good things, good energy ✨ Higher frequenc… https://t.co/t6rUF1shZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_peter24 That’s me thinking and picturing it...... but you’ve interrupted me! 😡😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_baliad @KTLAMorningNews @glenwalkerktla @kaceymontoya @latimes @Davidlaz @MarcusSmithKTLA @jenniferthang… https://t.co/jYeC8GcGJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HandsOffVenezuela @realDonaldTrump @VP @SenSherrodBrown @senrobportman @RandPaul @SenSanders @TulsiGabbard… https://t.co/aq4Wk2pS4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTLizB I feel like, growing up on Long Island in the 80s, this was a hot topic.  There was talk about the State of… https://t.co/NXkEYaeril]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FennellKristen @KevinARing He should have thought about the consequence when he broke the law!  It’s his fault ... own it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aleanor55 @realannapaulina @SenSanders As for the Covington students? Broader picture was the video of the young m… https://t.co/8tviwkt7oK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @engineerwin, the truth @FoxNews talk about the Cestui Que Vi Trusts, fraud, enslavement Birth Cer… https://t.co/Vmr5gxUo6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[𝘣𝘢𝘤𝘬 𝘶𝘱 𝘁𝗲𝗿𝗿𝘆                  𝘱𝘶𝘵 𝘪𝘵 𝘪𝘯 𝘳𝘦𝘷𝘦𝘳𝘴𝘦 𝘁𝗲𝗿𝗿𝘆  ｐｕｔ　ｉｔ　ｉｎ　ｒｅｖｅｒｓｅ                            ØⱧ ⱠØⱤĐ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueHenArt @trawetsla @realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner The kind with money &amp; wives that say anywhere but here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[20 Days until Janet is  inducted into the hall of fame.... I love @JanetJackson https://t.co/j9z9gU6URV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Tattered Cover always leads me to a little bit of magic. I can’t wait to read this. I love the cover too.… https://t.co/vhQDhnytpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not and I will not respect an individual who thinks it’s okay to drink and drive. You are not the only person… https://t.co/O61iHs8Pfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remind yourself today ~ #nomore #changehappenshere https://t.co/HHrK4IYcAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mchavonnia I heard you’re going to Palm Springs. Have one for the band. 🤙🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[This free business pays daily.  We are building something special with our international team 🌍  The team is in sof… https://t.co/E9A4QSyng7]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am at such a good place in my life with friends and family. God gives us so many blessings. sometimes we just nee… https://t.co/lDQElYjYqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A busy week for @FSUCollegeofLaw’s #Professionalism Program! Tuesday, we partnered w/ @TheFlaBar’s Center for Profe… https://t.co/ccOkpLvb3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best follow up to an awesome workout, a great massage. (@ Massage Green SPA in Westminster, CO) https://t.co/8GEJUn8lVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought I was capable of feeling this much happiness #lifeisbeautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever needs to hear this, get off of Twitter and work on you homework]]></document><document><![CDATA[When women support one another, incredible things happen. I’m lucky enough to have all these ladies in my life 💕… https://t.co/ATcWXxd5Jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I totally understand Clint Eastwood in Dirty Harry movie “SHE IS A LEGEND IN HER OWN MIND”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I just say that right now I am so unbelievably and incandescently happy? 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashaDevlin People I like get baby things knit from superwash. People I don't get store bought whatever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A metaphor, maybe. 🥀🚪 // 𝘐 𝘬𝘯𝘰𝘸 𝘭𝘰𝘷𝘦. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/NPE7UrGT1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been in Portland for a day but it feels like I've been here for a week already lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chloeeelove193 Hahahaha you can always count on me 😂 we call each other out fr fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s petty bullshit like this that is STILL fracturing the Democratic Party. I could care less about @BernieSanders… https://t.co/SqHq4AtiMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[💝 #HiPam ONE MORE DAY! (@ Sand Lake Cancer Center Of Orlando in Orlando, FL) https://t.co/tWCOlkY5lY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe diGenova's advice to patriots: It's a 'civil war' -- 'I buy guns'. Are you upset about this kind of crazy talk??  @MichaelSteele]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big thanks to @nankr1120 for opening up her PLN to help me discover some amazing podcasts! I am so amazed at the po… https://t.co/eboywjZxa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcabarrus Reprocher à Emmanuel Macron sa "fermeté"face aux GJs? On dirait du Ruffin, c'est tout dire!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoes on the other foot now.  AOC has to see that her actions have consequences. That includes her socialist mouth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna know why I don’t drunk call one of my exes like a normal person🤦🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/SgkjPQCxIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoop whoop!!!!! Go get them @HawleyMO !!! I have full faith that you can be a bulldog when you want Josh. I love t… https://t.co/rVax0CZyeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Date night with JT. 💃🏼 #WereBringingSexyBack @ Staples Center https://t.co/ZMqkPCxZDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “I love my dog more than any human ever in my life.”  Soulless human: “it’s just a dog.”  Me: https://t.co/HlEdhRfH4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent thread here. And the defense by conservatives of so-called conservative “victories” mostly justifies the… https://t.co/1sCPxcSKXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhShxtDatsVar @Treelie_13 Had to send.....DEAL WIT IT!!😂😁😅👍 https://t.co/TMPZRfoaZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[All smiles around here 😁😁😁 #HappyTuesday @BenitaZahn @MulhollandWNYT @WNYT https://t.co/eAuMuFn4Ki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because every day is #different #LoveTeaching #PantherPAWsome https://t.co/XfUYBk9pYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guest list is full...but it's only $10 at the door! Get your tickets before they're gone 🌃  #womenssession… https://t.co/DwOyVoOVma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends Tell me again how much you love our military, “Pentagon may tap military pay, pensions for border wall.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trashedvixen is beautiful &amp; the most perfect person on earth, I luv her v much   that is all]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I love the black unis AND we're 6-0 with them this season! 💙🖤 Stupid L'ville.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won’t hesitate cutting you out of my life if you’re being fake or toxic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @KeithMills1090 on winning the Herb Armstrong Service to Football Award! Well deserved! 😘… https://t.co/sSDBcMYFZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man works, makes money, and makes a family if he wants to. A boy talks about it but never pursues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at the age where it’s not a bad idea to just hit up my “if we’re not married by 30 let’s just marry each other” friends lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry but poor people definitely don’t deserve any form of pleasure in their lives at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YusufnotYufus @qanon76 @realDonaldTrump So?  It’s not over yet plus he didn’t say how....just said one way or anot… https://t.co/XfOMP8NXUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIME @OfficialJLD Did I stop a heart attack? I’ve been very stressed, yesterday walking dogs I had a tightening of… https://t.co/cPpvXVxHFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s nice to see the Trevi Fountain without scaffolding since I was CHEATED twice in the same year]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m the universe and you’ll be    N A S A @sebtsb  #SelfieForSelfLove https://t.co/Rs1Rl7geCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINALLY SOME PASSION!!! his body language at the beginning had me questioned, but finally some raw emotion, take it… https://t.co/kSgHiQVI7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Onelife Fitness - Tech Center in Newport News, VA https://t.co/qcT6gaYiuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Communista2 @bunkybun @renemjclarke Or just go to page &amp; follow. - but are you back to time lord and not communists 2 ? I’m confused]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett turns himself in on claim of making false police report, Chicago police say https://t.co/4oCdIbnY0H… https://t.co/Bwl3x4kubP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very pleased my mom was surprised to see everyone. Thank you to my family for keeping a lid on it, although she tho… https://t.co/UpkXNjGo9l]]></document></documents></author>