<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Pretty cool that my commentary on @CoachDambrot and @DuqMBB made it on ESPNРђЎs college basketball section andРђд https://t.co/izGm7FVytt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSkipBayless roast Lebron tomorrow please! Someone needs to have a heart to heart with him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This ain't no party, this ain't no disco, this ain't no fooling around no time for dancing, or lovey dovey, I ain'tРђд https://t.co/t1JxrRyt5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotoriousAJM Seriousness this is not a day for who's hair was dyed first or who's leggings are better , lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisLongKSTP The only reason I donРђЎt think North Branch will be seeded is because Monticello was the No. 1 seed aРђд https://t.co/MUgMUn9WUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you fit the bill. Get chatting with Dani on this interesting hypothesis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Рђћ Comment РђюFAITHРђЮ ┬а РађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађ  The Bible says РђюIf you have FAITH, the size of a mustard seed... You can move mouРђд https://t.co/R1Ddjve9Bl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brooker_56 Dwight been to finals with an alright team and got 3 DPOYs nephew]]></document><document><![CDATA[#YouWillLaugh ­Ъўѓ TRY NOT TO LAUGH ­Ъўѓ (MUST WATCH!) ­Ъњ»­Ъњ»  #SMULE #JarOfHearts #Hallelujah #RichardBerryJr1 #RDBJR1Рђд https://t.co/1tKCJlZd0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I salute all who continue working towards their  #gold all styles of #music CHEERS #ONELOVE #share https://t.co/s2Psi0nqM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive said this before but I've had alotta stigmas used on me over my 43 yrs of being in this world I've had to proveРђд https://t.co/cNeGsr1dXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Born alive = alive. Abortion is legalized genocide of African Americans.  5 AA infants murdered for each white one.Рђд https://t.co/PDnWW8gmFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @realDonaldTrump Don't    kid ourselves, they R trying to make a end run around our freedom. We have to fiРђд https://t.co/al1xjkehuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOW DID EVERYONE AT @KelloggsUS MISS THAT WEIRDOS LIKE ME MIGHT CONFLATE LITTLE TURD LOOKING TREATS CALLED POPPERSРђд https://t.co/WxafWyDCkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@o_scurvy @Buccaneers @MikeEvans13_ Not really with our current cb situation and lack of salary cap he might have to]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few new and familiar members of the 116th Congress celebrating Jewish and Democratic values withРђд https://t.co/KSGz0UH2WT]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюIn light of the resurrection, the question cannot be РђюWhat is my truth?РђЮ or РђюWhat is your truth?РђЮ but РђюWhat is theРђд https://t.co/CBTPHBtNoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[On red table I was really hoping @wale and willow would have spoke more to each other. Dope watch tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityLab @createstreets So this is how today is going to go... https://t.co/9Acn0VyIWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The post-punky funky skronky no-wavy world of THE WORLD @ Rickshaw Stop https://t.co/pSzTNvi95s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuceoStar @realDonaldTrump The РђюObama intelligence agenciesРђЮ? Plural? WTF is he talking about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should all plant. Quit throwing away you ­ЪЦЉ seeds, ­Ъї╗ seed and such... We only get one shot at this human shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrooksLayson @marclamonthill And how many of these schools have you worked at to know they this mass fraud is occuРђд https://t.co/mafEKB2bN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeNimmin Yesterday I was about to pay at the grocery store, ran out to my car because I thought I forgot my wallet. It was in my pocket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quote for  today:      I always get to where I'm going,     By walking away from where I've.            been.      - Winne the Pooh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think i actually have one of these from my grammie. They always had either pasta or chicken cutlets in them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long day ahead. Keep the coffee coming #NHLTradeDeadline https://t.co/PHFak2PPP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zaney_Zoney @RandPaul @POTUS Rand should be ashamed not protecting the American people and NOT supporting the presРђд https://t.co/8AdavjSS1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to Hollie Doyle @HollieDoyle1 riding today at @ChelmsfordCRC. Keep those winners coming! #goodluckРђд https://t.co/5yrMBwKzMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YungDaddyAJ We left at the perfect time I feel like, it was sunny in sac and that followed us up, we had to put onРђд https://t.co/iwv3wyejqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sprayed my travel clothes with permethrin at Park Ave Laundry. Female employee there didn't seem to mind. She evenРђд https://t.co/1St2FikMFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to hit soMe bags at @TITLEBoxingClub with my Dad @GriffThurston22 https://t.co/THvqUUgB2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulaHouseman @MQuigley1963 @d_ast777 @Travis_Borne @Russell_Writer @bionicanadian @bagoflettuce @TobiasZSalemРђд https://t.co/VV7rwL5Db1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @Jeanleonetti1 @CommonCause @joncoopertweets @wikileaks @Snowden @RIPsethRich @FBI @DNC @HillaryClintonРђд https://t.co/nAEEeGbBhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@koriijeanne @BelloLdnnn @thatssofree what for? After its flushed, im on to the next not callin somebody over whenРђд https://t.co/UpqDo7ha8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MANCRUSHMONDAY ­ЪЇи full sketch COMING SOON! @ Charleston, South Carolina https://t.co/mv31Z4IBk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardStern Please watch my video and retweet if comfortable: https://t.co/PcXJLPWolm I am a stage IV HPV tonsil cРђд https://t.co/cGhqN8sbYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MyFavoriteMysteryIs Why does Walmart have so many people with fashion faux pas? https://t.co/ixrIPccmAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Kittatinny Mountain Tunnel in Newburg, PA https://t.co/nn4VWUk81Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day great day in Ottawa sharing stories of how important housing is to a good life in community. @TOAdamVaughanРђд https://t.co/7uonO4n38w]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you see this fat bitch taking selfies while she is driving for Uber and waiting at a WendyРђЎs drive through ­Ъўѓ­ЪЉЇРђд https://t.co/64swlKI48T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viola losing in 2012 was upsetting... but Glenn losing tonight was absolutely awful. How many more great parts willРђд https://t.co/cRqByxeKyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheyWereStolen @Sker4Lyfe @ninaturner @KillerMike @TheRealDaytime He released them. Pay attention yo the billionaiРђд https://t.co/zadfi5MkRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If IРђЎm being honest as a life long OРђЎs fan. I was kind of sad watching first spring training game today knowingРђд https://t.co/hvml6IJDhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Oh Ann,  please stfu !  We all know your trying to increase your wealth with another cold- hearted out-Рђд https://t.co/A1Kr1G4tp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimmiOsborne The one that's pulled over Crosby's head while he's getting pounded]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Kim called it his family's gazebo but wasn't kidding anybody.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who's ready for @AEWrestling , #DOUBLE_OR_NOTHING ? Sneak peak of what I'm wearing to the event. ­Ъњф­ЪўЃ https://t.co/WzkFjXT2Ak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande @borispvlikovsky @arixsolana @grandekordei @notatxpapi Pop off sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[This entire story is so fkn scary #PrayingForAmerica #MakeAmericaSaneAgain #MASA  is that a already a thing?­Ъцћ­Ъци­ЪЈ╝РђЇРЎђ№ИЈ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SacBee_JoeD Why not just take 1 Section champion into NorCals/State tournament from each division? Should reduce blowouts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherylwillwrite @Mike_Donachie If @Mike_Donachie had his own comic book super(ish) hero gang..... definitely the РђюunhingeablesРђЮ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThaGreatZambino SEND IT yeah fell asleep when i got home 630 didnt get up til 1130 so i be up all night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StFinbarBklyn I will have canned food for you this week my students have brought in]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiero al agente de Vinicius es la mmda, termin├Аndose el juego ya estaba haciendo las respectivas transferencias]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Macdaddy35Mac @JasonRo61151976 @WingfieldNFL IРђЎm all for using the head, but it hat doesnРђЎt mean u have to jettisoРђд https://t.co/bKgW9JzMBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump President Trump, has the True American People by his side , they  want someone like the Him that pРђд https://t.co/LiXEZuvbWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyPelas hi Lindsey. Always so good to see and read your tweets.  Love your opinions. ­Ъўђ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuntsmanAbby you're a typical Republican sock puppet. You couldn't simply say you were incorrect about 10% commentРђд https://t.co/CHPZq7hENo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP Wow! Meadows whinning about late intro of testimony?? Hmmm....kinda like the kavanaugh hearings when republicaРђд https://t.co/ajOm4lD55E]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will @moirarachelle4 go on tour in LA?? Or even in Vegas. We donРђЎt mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where?┬аРђЊ All of North Alabama and Southern Tennessee.┬а Storms may be┬аstrongest┬аover the western side of the state oРђд https://t.co/xoNXCZ7bs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom Ricketts on new broadcast deal: "Sinclair is going to be a great partner." #Cubs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC The selection process for the Democrats has to begin with who can beat Trump. Then winnow out those too farРђд https://t.co/8z4A09F0cw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOSHMBB19 Noooo! ItРђЎs awful if youРђЎre getting steak. The rolls are the only thing worth going for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting my steps in on the way to work! #selfiesasiwalk #selfie #selfies @ Community Education at Columbia CollegeРђд https://t.co/1vGBjsuuNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[An attorney from @GLADLaw making clear that the bill to #BanConversionTherapy regulates health care and doesnРђЎt impРђд https://t.co/JyfWNuB5Ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swavy33 DonРђЎt be sad brother man. Tennessee is still the best team in the SEC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I know niggas that even when they problems was a lil quiet. Would go rob a nigga to stir the pot. Just to keepРђд https://t.co/VfaqABtUd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BossBattleGordy with a wise message to the hoes: https://t.co/h3aLqPljkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATrapcard @EmilyGorcenski @FikeMartin "It is easier for a camel to go through the eye of a needle than for someoneРђд https://t.co/0yl6ZnPRnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hop Perfect by @YazooBrew @ Legends Corner Рђћ https://t.co/CRJ0q5bOrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SiriusXMFC @NeilSpyBarnett I am amazed at how many pundits say they have never seen it before. It happened 2 yearsРђд https://t.co/RJitXrrzHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My beautiful wife at the wedding reception! @ Hodel's Banquet &amp; Catering https://t.co/7mjaYIQs36]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Amy Easton and the international recruitment team for  sharing @StirUni with us. Hidden gem in the heartРђд https://t.co/QC2l1D2sOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@watchhorrorpod @FearScale @TnHorrorNews  only 2 days away to LOVE ME NOT my new #horror film for @horrorhousmedia https://t.co/qfcrc0mSdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first drinks have been ordered #NashvilleTrip2019 https://t.co/LaBOydN9IG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZerlinaMaxwell At the same time they will ignore the white supremestРђЎs terrorist who was going to kill high governРђд https://t.co/KYzDyr0DmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CestlInstantX @Negrita22 @CBCNews Indeed I doubt anyone would defend a avg stranger with the details we have here.Рђд https://t.co/o4ZhXZzWIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeminai2 @billmaher @BetoORourke Yea maybe but will moderate Republicans in Wisconsin, Michigan,  PA, Iowa, FL? IРђд https://t.co/Z7PxeK9JLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dscvrrstl @TonyToulon @SeanToulon @RealBigBert_7 @HashtagChad I have an Austin on order. I think there are severalРђд https://t.co/farBfvOr4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Sonora Dinamita, presentando a la Morocha, cantando: " El Viejo del sombreron " .­Ъўј­ЪЄ╗­ЪЄф]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanRoth @Slammy_P I'm clinically depressive and love seltzer. I may be a daywalker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you  absorb solar heat at the same time! @ North Bethesda, Maryland https://t.co/z7AePPO7HH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachjayjohnson @pntrack @BldrRunClinics This was such a great presentation! Thanks for teaching us how to Feed the Cats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ItРђЎs been awhile but today I reached 12k before 12 noon #FitBit #KeepOnWalking @ Redhawk, Temecula https://t.co/puLbzyrn1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[as always, the pre-game meeting spot is "under Shaq's ass" https://t.co/PkSWshzd4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, IРђЎm playing a game called HQ Trivia. You should play too. Use my code 'MandalynnJDG' to sign up https://t.co/3XGmGOrXlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLPlayerSafety when will you be reviewing @PKSubban1 and his headshots and or attempted headshots....  Sincerely,Рђд https://t.co/0VTumOh6KK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Avitrade No, definitely not. They don't accuse 800 people of being racist, every 20 minutes. All day long, every sРђд https://t.co/pvXWKH5tEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[In fact, she would be in trouble if somebody came in and challenged her with more business-friendly platforms and sРђд https://t.co/MW633GGZI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro @DonaldJTrumpJr This entitlement attitude needs to be addressed by reality that nothing in this world is free...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StomataMargret @PeterBrannen1 @Palaeoecologist Oops, s/b Kovenock. Anyway here's the link: https://t.co/cFFYG99BcHРђд https://t.co/4XDuX8RiBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, he doesnРђЎt. HeРђЎs expanded his nuclear program. This is all wishful thinking until we get a leader who actuallyРђд https://t.co/7QkGbhOq5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[This birthday weekend has been great so far! SixFlags today! Turned 25 today but still a child lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggaz shine a couple times &amp; forget that it rains, ion really give a fuck courtesy of da drank]]></document><document><![CDATA[they've seen it all but they ain't seen this before https://t.co/mVNzQL0bTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen, itРђЎs fine to disagree with their vote. But, donРђЎt flat out lie for their reasoning. @mitchellvii]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanna girls basketball rolls past Hillcrest in opening round of playoffs https://t.co/TBpt892KQp viaРђд https://t.co/3qNlrYqTa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My city is better than yours @ Winter Village At Bryant Park Ice Rink https://t.co/SDdrXy8vZb]]></document></documents></author>