<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@lyricalarrow No, Oliver, carrot sticks and yogurt AREN’T the same thing. https://t.co/3XEXtMADIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Ari_ yikes. Well. It’s all going down as you planned. https://t.co/EhkqmTNWyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have off today? Check out some houses for sale...DesireeWhalen.com https://t.co/joSZOx5vE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear God, please give me the strength to not tip toe to the fridge rn. Amen. https://t.co/AcIrZp7L0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanelleBrown117 Yes! Grew up Baptist, so there were many teetotalers around us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricWalker97 @CPeoplesStokes @AprilBaskinld2 Basically. DSS can but in Erie County they haven’t prior to this. In… https://t.co/fd3Wn3taff]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m eating so much taco bell as well as a full skin care routine i am a goddess]]></document><document><![CDATA[God takes care if the rich and famous..and pisses on the good and the ones that no body ..and I think that's just p… https://t.co/dMjPLDBefW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurieWulfand I might..we'll see how the night goes 🤔 https://t.co/32h07WgnOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rose Peters crossed 10K. Time 01:06:03, pace 10:49 min/mile, est. finish 8:00 am https://t.co/9umIwQVNph #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyway I super need to rewatch SG1 and Farscape give me all that good 90s scifi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah! What’s up with this contrived “national emergency?” What a crock of 💩.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThyBubbyking @DestinyTheGame this looks to be lead into them bringing back thorn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go to the principa’s office. Click here https://t.co/b2CIeX6wW4.  #NCED]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fool’s wisdom always leads to a dead end, but God’s wisdom always opens up new horizons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesCraigmyle My cat does that too. She woke up because I was moving too much for her apparently haha. https://t.co/mrVxwzQYNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! 🎶She's a baaad ma'am-a-jamma!🎶 Congratulations, Coach Taylor! 🏀🏆🤱👊🏼 #allinadayswork]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕️ ICYMI How Lindsey Graham Went From Trump Skeptic to Trump Sidekick https://t.co/Ha1Os3XD23]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nails done. Always representing the Black &amp; Gold. @penguins  @WBSPenguins https://t.co/UfqlN38RTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a HUGE “screw you” to gate-keeping nerd bros who think that women don’t have a place as main characters, let a… https://t.co/0zfhIjvNVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[loved seeing @grizfolk at @fillmoredetroit. 🎶 it honestly refreshed me, getting back to detroit with @shannosulli a… https://t.co/873WLs6ZNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 Due to weather all 9 AM games will start at 11 AM. 🚨  Please be on stand by for any further updates throughout the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlyNewmanU Paola is rocking out with financial aid discussions.... what questions do you have? https://t.co/HXfWa9Ack1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kucherov, Nikita Alex Ovechkin Yandle, Keith Lundqvist, Henrik Artemi Panarin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mkskee1 @PhilipRucker That's complicated.😁  But the fact that I can't go there tells me my mor's spirit is hoverin… https://t.co/RXKWSfwf6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boss walks by, “Whatcha listening to?” “Pitbull.” “I’m Cuban too y’know.” “Yeah, not Cuban like Pitbull.  He’s...CU… https://t.co/SKxUm4bmvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog may not be my dog anymore, but I don’t give a fuck, because she’s still going to be my screen saver on my phone 😭😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will become sensitive to His voice, know what He wants to do and say, and perceive the spiritual atmosphere aro… https://t.co/M3GGQFHE0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yungblud um help is Houston actually sold out sold out or is it just presale that’s sold out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hace dos semanas conocí justamente a la persona que siempre había querido conocer #queridodiario]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Well me I fall in love with you every single day” https://t.co/V5mOmtWzEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t wake up on time to turn in my homework but I woke up in time to watch the Jonas brothers show so yeah I have my priorities straight]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve drank &amp; been so social the past two days ugh I can’t leave my bed for the rest of the week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlieputh Maybe it’s cuz  they say one is yelling if the words typed are all in Caps and meant one is angry as opposed to being calm ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently trying to hide from my professor Bc I skipped morning workouts....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decisions: Get beach house in Galveston and get rid of RV or just keep RV??? I love camping however, I LOVE THE OCE… https://t.co/6DPllWIbKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MimiTheProblem Just cuz you love us black men dont mean you gotta judge others 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[In software development using #agile, desire for #data from engineers surges, per @donpega: https://t.co/gnCxA6vtZw… https://t.co/NzdPzASnRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bmillslc @vegetarianj @NoirAmnesiac @Ilhan It was 14 million, and it was paid back. Hid dad wouldn't have had 400… https://t.co/BSjCsZ1DKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plan de domingo #soMiami #carnavalcalle8 #calleocho #carnavalmiami #calle8musicfestival #elcroquetazo #croqueta  https://t.co/miOn5nMFAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenHydeSmith Not your average Tuesday night. Enjoyed learning what happens in DC and the importance of staying inv… https://t.co/98Tc1Aw0ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved teaching Ms. Connelly’s 4th grade class about all things weather! What an awesome group! ☔️ ⛈… https://t.co/JYJYMuYGoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#toronto vista de cima, toda linda e coberta de gelo. https://t.co/nFESOtWhcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[(gif set) ""Be my Valentine." ||| Supernatural 5x14 "My Bloody Valentine" and 6x14 "Mannequin 3: The... https://t.co/u89FgrSN3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to #monsterMask for keeping the judges STUMPED until the very end! #themaskedsinger]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is in my neighborhood 🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️ and since I got home at 11 they already had these streets block and made me d… https://t.co/2cI9Mni9ge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its been 5 weeks since Marea a.k.a. Princess Meow Meow went across the 🌈 bridge and I miss her cuddles, meows and s… https://t.co/gaVs0jLHpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redpainter1 well, #Trump INSISTS @MichaelCohen212 LIED. #MichaelCohen said Don doesn't PHYSICALLY ABUSE @FLOTUS so… https://t.co/0IsreTDy0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mexican president pushes on with compulsory higher education plan https://t.co/uE8RJjdPIf via @timeshighered]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida es corta, sonríele a quien llora, ignora a quien te critica y sé feliz con quien te importa🤫😉🥰 https://t.co/GOVJQWnzV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a lot of talk about guns now. I hate guns and think there are way too many. Why not require an annual regi… https://t.co/1YpzpA3sGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tip Managers/Recruiters - #Onboarding Onboarding (https://t.co/mOEQv6yoQi) *30 day training plan  *Supplies  *Guid… https://t.co/kbljD84Ykd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh some hilarity. This isnâ??t really funny, but I donâ??t have a category for beautiful disney stained glass ima… https://t.co/c7SOvas1C5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaPutrelli @acidoviejo @adribilu Por qué la gente huye de los “paraísos socialistas”?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Chris Wallace today.  Take politics out of it.  He is a swamper journalists.  They bought a red hat… https://t.co/UbGgilckfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @RepAOC Congrats on your tour. The punditry believes the midwest doesn't want GND, please come to Michigan, no… https://t.co/cXN5EVgB0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @Nico_Lang! Hey @USATODAY I’m ready and waiting and so are all these fabulous #trans people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Verse of the day. Hope everyone has a great blessed day!😊Every way of a man is right in his own eyes: but the Lord… https://t.co/cxJcKjUFTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TeacherGoals When asked to take pictures of notes, I got this snapped at me. XD 🐦📃 #BirdAteMyNotes… https://t.co/8GYB3kIQJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[to provide loans to farmers. That developed into today's Farm Credit System, which is a government-sponsored financ… https://t.co/BA7nVaHfId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@punkstephphotos Tbh I set reminders and try to eat at the same times every day and drink a lot of water so I’m not hungry between meals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fl511_turnpike traffic is at a standstill Northbound from exit 23 is there an accident]]></document><document><![CDATA[Considering he didn’t hear the requests for help from the athletes he was charged to protect it sounds like it’s ti… https://t.co/d0bRJxxbMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yeahRIFAsaidit I would never want to leave the house with that own. Jesus Christ the wealth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Termanater6 Follow me, I follow back all #MAGA #KAG #MAGAVETS #DEPLORABLES  #TRUMPVILE #TRUMPSUPPORTERS… https://t.co/2gPwrohtas]]></document><document><![CDATA[An American Canyon teen posed as a police officer and asked hotel staff if they had seen wanted persons,… https://t.co/rzum1NpAQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@likaluca Sonny's Blues in junior year. But Go Tell It On the Mountain was the real revelation--my auntie smuggled… https://t.co/6c3uqta6HW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Randomly play my placements and managed to link up with a pretty dope squad and won 3 and lost 1. Pretty good for the evening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So that estimated "6 minutes" took an entire hour. Maybe their system has a multiple of ten issue... ¯\_(ツ)_/¯ https://t.co/t9X1RIIEf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @jeffrey_wood09 !!! Good luck at States this weekend 🎉🎈🏒🖤💛 https://t.co/WSILdUmEyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still haven’t check my bank acct from my Vegas trip. Low key scared to see the damage.   Tbh I love playing the slots 😩 💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bopp is there something fishy going on between daughter and pops? Cause I’ll be damn if I’m putting my child in har… https://t.co/Y2BVpK2wqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeGero You’re right I’m sorry to disagree - #peaceandlove #BohemianRhapsodyMovie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsLisaVanity @TaylorNettnin @shanedawson @JeffreeStar Hell watch out. The queen has arrived:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coryedwards @Adobe @joeDmarti @markboothe @mattyroze @chadwarren @Lauren_Hannah @karendo @ranimani0707 @BradRobins… https://t.co/hWw6wxuho8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posting a little later this morning since we got to sleep in thanks to #presidentsday  A little #mondaymotivation b… https://t.co/THxSyDOZhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make new friends but keep the old. interspeciesfriendship @ Delray Beach, Florida https://t.co/2AnsU5pMiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM BEYOND FURIOUS.... NO ONE SHOULD EVER BE TREATED LIKE THIS EVER!!!! 😭🤬 #STOPBULLYING]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨ Is this the real lifeeee? Is this just retrogradeeeee 🙄 #mercuryretrograde @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/xStXDLvnFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWhiteSpade21 For the longest time I thought screen shots of night mode tweets were tumbler posts lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eeeeek! My new seeds are here! I may be a little too excited about these Atomic Grape Tomatoes. I've been meeting t… https://t.co/c0VG6z6dQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@withconfidence_ TY 4 making this beautiful song I'm sincerely happy this one is getting a lot of traction as I thi… https://t.co/apTInXQDNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a first date last 24 hours and is that good or like watch out???]]></document><document><![CDATA[#URGENTE #21Feb A esta hora Presidente interino de Venezuela 🇻🇪 Juan Guaido @jguaido ya se encuentra en el estado T… https://t.co/YoiR5FoB6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jganschster @RobertPBayer1 @CNNPolitics @cnnbrk Yes!! We want proof ! GOP , talking ,BS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to pick up your copy of Jeanne d’ arc Living Magazine at Brissonte. Each issue is filled with decorati… https://t.co/zmMpIVWODG]]></document><document><![CDATA[In other words, the Trump team is fundraising off of racism and fear-mongering. Nothing new here, folks.  https://t.co/ANeXP3A3Yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[flashback to when tcu tried to give me a ticket for “parking somewhat crooked INSIDE the lines”🙄😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cheers #congratulations to  All @costumeawards @cdglocal892 #great to see all of U❣️ barbarachennault  therealruth… https://t.co/AyqMlfwcfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyJ_aLLDay @kevinr_oc Jojos is apparently only an Akron/northeast Ohio thing!! Found that out recently also. Sad for everybody else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tophersouth Also I had no idea you’re having another baby! Congrats!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of yall grew up with parents that unconditionally loved you and it shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg NOOOOO the guy next to me is watching Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows: Part 2 I’m gonna cry the whole way… https://t.co/KfJbHhpYB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldorco1 He is spot on here. The media is failing us at our most perilous time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking forward to the warmer months when this 183 miles will increase. evgonetwork @chevrolet #boltlady… https://t.co/Ooujfywg2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomjeff @johncutlefish @SamuelDev When I was on product dev teams at IBM, I was a Lab Advocate. I was assigned a… https://t.co/BTweklkBzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I’m eating good today lmao 😂 lunch on dad , dinner on my 12 corazones date lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dallasnews @BetoORourke #WhiteSupremacistTerrorists are the #NationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best birthday present I got today was an A on my Linear Algebra exam!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GCHDutta @rpskataria @nmehta4 @IamSunitha777 @AnupmaMichael @u_mirella @fghdil @GsjpJyoti @greatairi… https://t.co/qHBzJ2aC7a]]></document></documents></author>