<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir I will, but I’ve checked. Last one to Columbus from Philly leaves at 8:40 pm, and we haven’t even left Ottawa yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[QOTD: In order to be a winner, you have to look for ways of getting things done and not for reasons why things can’… https://t.co/oV90QFdFps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go figure.  So much for wanting big bold change led by their  contemporaries]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a universal equation wherever you go especially if there is plenty of money it will have working girls. Beauti… https://t.co/5mO4gY6LSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSSunday Let me get this straight, hospitals closing tragic story followed by 6K curly tree chairs. Got it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or do you lead teams in Austin and you’re not sure you have something to share? That’s cool too, I would love to gr… https://t.co/sOsKPhT4zl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MYSTIC7 You could try going for a hike to clear your head and give your self some time to process the bigger issue… https://t.co/3RQyxRl7yF]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Austin is a music center. #SXSW if WE can’t play Tom Petty, Springsteen, Foo Fighters... and Prince in an Uber??… https://t.co/YAX8eP1Fz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitter world. Have a Blessed and Wonderful Week https://t.co/VbBdPV9Qe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone: Man YouTube rewind was a cluster…  The oscars: Hold my beer… #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Product manager: we're rolling out a new feature called ghost ads Coworker: did she say "ghost dads"? Me: https://t.co/YZ4fJgG1bJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PostOpinions @marcthiessen The only big lie, @marcthiessen, is that Republican lie that climate change is a hoax,… https://t.co/tOCusFCZPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hulu_support 🤠🤠🤠🤠Hope all MI 5 get Doctor Who 63 to now Get Torchwood to. https://t.co/d7wXBywCle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks fellas, for a fantastic 2018-2019 season! @Waukee_Hoops @WaukeeHS @Kee_Crowd https://t.co/B4tT6lSygX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practice 5️⃣ coming up this morning‼️   #RaiseTheBar #BlockC #BleedBlue 🔵⚪️🔵⚪️🔵⚪️🔵⚪️🔵⚪️🔵⚪️🔵 https://t.co/IqOP8JBnUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WGME @KatieWGME @AmandaWGME @LaurenWGME @Liztorrey2017 @AaronWGME @WGMEReynolds @MovieQueenAri There’s a reason I… https://t.co/WG913sF8Ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got the neck done and fitted in its new forever home, touch up is done and now ready to finish tomorrow 👍🎸 @ Destin… https://t.co/2gUtpIm2vX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate how we are at Fuzzy’s enjoying mimosas and @NASCAR is being played.... #GREAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khyleezor I understand your pain. I’ll be here to talk if you want. Anytime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mightygodking Better than Nolan’s Batman? Them’s fighting words. https://t.co/Xv6JhMB2T2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terrancesavery Shut up, I was like 45 or something. I’m on a monthly schedule now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KasieDC @RepDebDingell @kasie To own a gun legally is not a crime but right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggturkington @OnCinemaRafael Hi Gregg and Raffy: are there any stars from the Decker franchise booked to appear… https://t.co/ve9nIjjoF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: Rock Bridge boys basketball advances to class five state quarterfinals with an 88-51 win over Camdenton.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeekMill Yea...... I gotta pic with dude too!!  #nbaallstarweekend2019 https://t.co/562a5iKpH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepMindAI opening huge new headquarters in 2020 in the #knowledgequarter #London https://t.co/LIpE8B6kC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elalbertomedina @ManuelGilAnton Si en un área de Gobierno debería existir el Servicio Profesional de Carrera es en… https://t.co/6jhMgQBun5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler Park NJ Tue Mar 5th AM Forecast: TODAY Sunny Hi 31 TONIGHT Clearing Lo 18]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Campain11 Like  1. Hope they wash themselves 2. Make a deal with wife  3. Pray for a dish washing genie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had some nice bullpens today with @DiamondKinetics and got some great feedback! #BJB https://t.co/cM5gwRTVA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m countin my bullets, I’m loading my clips, I’m writing down names, I’m making a list, I’m checkin twice and I’m… https://t.co/nEn2a92ZWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first night after I moved into my apartment I stuck a tapestry over my bedroom window because I was too tired t… https://t.co/MVkSQj5KPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@watareulookinat Thanks I appreciate that I moisturize so I’m glad it’s appreciated by someone finally]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you tomorrow for the ribbon cutting ceremony in #ElPaso @AlaskaAir 😍💙💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new favorite thing is to blast cumbia throughout the business school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m like a little kid on Christmas! Didn’t sleep all night because I was excited that today is the first day of the… https://t.co/nGhqRLwWYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 7K IPA by @santafebrew at @BarrelsTaphouse — https://t.co/UQ1lmWqsKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @DonaldJTrumpJr This isn't about @realDonaldTrump winning. He's president of the entire country, not just… https://t.co/4CcfBzJlZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadmMonstrosity I like the idea there’s a population of Gill Men living in the lagoon. Gill Women, too I would say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all ever just wake up with random cuts on your legs? Am I being haunted?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a great time skiing ⛷ until the storm hit and then what do you do...start a snowball fight in the parking lot… https://t.co/dw569YyCdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a given we know what they do and how vital they are to our nation. The reasons you listed could it be that's w… https://t.co/FrumhieMdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LanceStorm Hurts the prestige IMO to be labeled a “Legacy inductee”. Surely even if they’re gone, they can have so… https://t.co/nGrDAjDL7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkwsaw @sarahkendzior SNL gets it. Thank you  Sarah and Melissa  and Mr Davidson for telling the TRUTH. America lo… https://t.co/6Uz825eO00]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come join @JessicaMooreTV (alongside Janelle @BurrellTV) with the latest local news on #CBSN New York this Saturday… https://t.co/SCNjB8s9oT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerAbernathy3 Some of the best ladies to ever wear the Jackson uniform.  So proud of them all.  #Family]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goosecamp7 @realDonaldTrump Is this the same judgement day that the Christian God talks about the same God I thoug… https://t.co/ID6GBcsEe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signup to be the first to hear about Beto's 2020 decision: https://t.co/hALy8jA6CQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snuck two pork roasts into work today in the form of my fat love handles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summer can’t come soon enough! Stoked to ride some jump shows with this guys again! @jeradlarue_56 #outdoordrinking… https://t.co/sihvd0uzwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuskerHaHa @JimMFelton @KatyFevans @Luiseach @supermathskid @Astro_Jonny @tommyhale91 @bexin2d @davidallengreen Brill'.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bigdoggpinc  Just sayin Bigdoggpinc on Pinterest to see more... https://t.co/9faESoNLCf #tennis #world    via… https://t.co/fBFtGBPktQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Thanks to decades of dem/socialist leadership. Giving away free stuff always leads to collapse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessieAThomas @Beni2Tijerina @GageAm @PaytonBerens @881TheBurg I take meetings very seriously @881TheBurg  Also is… https://t.co/jUdIEhZ9Sp]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an awesome day celebrating our first international student-athlete Courtney Gettins of New Zealand 🇳🇿. She has… https://t.co/GjuJcoRbEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Myraid Botanical Gardens  Oklahoma City, Ok @myriadgardens https://t.co/0SM8K1ph2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems to me our forefathers fought a revolution to prevent people from controlling every aspect of other people’… https://t.co/HjPWrIn3GR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLuckettG @chadbsingh Nice!  You learn quickly.  Looks like a proper diversion from Rosen. Spent an hour collabora… https://t.co/doqPM4THVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@posey_miles It’s in the work  @DefyGENETICS  they will have you next level ready physically but mentally it’s up t… https://t.co/G3TqbkKZcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 more @ 8:30 pace...AMAZING evening for a run...#winning #gettinripped https://t.co/ubtfzt0i7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump And what have Dems ever done you flamboyant bastard?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Babyboy Shiva closeup..some asshole behind him #4Ness #BabyboyShiva @ Woodbury, New Jersey https://t.co/wy6mvTan6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the highest I’ve seen the Eel River in some time. https://t.co/ydoJtxQeuf #CAwx  #humboldtcounty #Fernbridge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa @VFL2013 @DavidJHarrisJr God will bless our country for what Trump is doing. Praise God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[UMKC student newspaper report quotes unnamed current softball player saying women accusing coach of sexual harassme… https://t.co/l8DGD008mz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizzylynngarcia @ScyneWaive @PiperWhitaker4 What uh....what exactly are Toilet Kisses? Inquiring minds and all that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiteSport @MSignorile @GottaLaff If that is true, then it is possible. My problem though is there news investigato… https://t.co/CiTfB5d571]]></document><document><![CDATA[SEC asks judge to hold Tesla’s Musk in contempt: The Securities and Exchange Commission asked a federal judge on Mo… https://t.co/n9irrTO73Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCBlindGazza The guy that attacked him should get 10 years of hard time Labour.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oil (@ Mulitz-Gudelsky Theatre Lab in Olney, MD) https://t.co/4GHyr9VqDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point, Millennials are between 23 and 38 years old. Forget about being “entitled” to get paid for your work… https://t.co/k0mtH3PI1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[A cogent reflection on our culture. Thanks @arthurbrooks https://t.co/W66LEVnOmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travis_view Tolerance for disappointment is inversely related to intolerance for having to change ones outlook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Mardi Gras! #FatTuesday #ShroveTuesday #paczki #MardiGras https://t.co/w3IdiEqMyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffGoddard2 It was an awesome experience for me and really enjoyed playing for Coach Z and the Tigers!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tsnooks37 I hope they both get in. Gates’ PED’s &amp; Rivers’ playoff record will create debate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So today is Valentines Day , and unfortunately I can’t be there with you ... I just want you to know that I loved y… https://t.co/yczcQ3yhxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaccioppoliMike @BethLynch2020 @JDmillennial1 I don’t trust polls we know they’re doctored.   If he (bernie) runs,… https://t.co/E1cMldGSL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani @realDonaldTrump @kroger A conservative US Trumpeteer @GOP Drug Company CEO, not Martin Shkreli, rais… https://t.co/anc8iVWZrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great last night in Florida. Our hotel @eaupalmbeach let me play their piano and within minutes of playing alone tu… https://t.co/FLaQjzhf1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Playa Balandra in La Paz, BCS https://t.co/Fwxlzown9Q https://t.co/mv4czsjiEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaPresto She does have the fish out of water look. But please, fifteen thousand of her constituents voted for… https://t.co/bOpsWBJumC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@go4itbas @FairyQ15 @DeplrbleRzistr @cheri4trump @CocoKAG @LadyNY4Ever @Layla0406 @PatriotRising6 @potocki_paul… https://t.co/9Ks3dHD0Wq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppleSupport All of these cool new features seem awesome, it’s too bad I haven’t been able to do ANYTHING with my… https://t.co/UlhP2w0A7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlie I just watched this video, your going to kill me smalls.  If this is what is coming out of college we are d… https://t.co/JWk0Yw96v5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adam_judd Did your dad clean off the roller wheels on your luggage before u were allowed to bring the luggage in the house ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsanityPilgrim @TheMrPasquale So if they Retconned it, why not try and take a different approach? Have him on mis… https://t.co/L54Fzclgcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#throwback to the time I thought that lil girl was a alligator 😂🤦🏽‍♂️ was on go 👊🏾😹 https://t.co/KU17tUMeIi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurynricketts Good morning  sunshine how  are you this fine day going to be a  great day someone will finally got… https://t.co/vWjDmVeKiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[HBD, Bri!! Hope this day brings you all the cheez itz you could want and you throw them up in someone’s driveway..cheers buddy! @Fr3am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terminating people via phone rather than in-person ... Is that really a thing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing #breakfast #menu #kale #tonic #Italian #Rustica #fritatta #maple #pepper #bacon #foodie #dining #SanAntonio… https://t.co/zbM8AsHfCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duchp @guycrete Voici la réponse de Robert Spencer à l’article écrit par le « journaliste » Marc Thibodeau de La P… https://t.co/bysUzdj2d6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rwfishbu1 When you include trickle down w Corp you are missing the basic purpose. It’s about the people. Corp tax rates are diff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreedomWorks @RapidFreedom @steveforbes @FoxNews Have any of these Einsteins ever taken a history lesson?  Name 1… https://t.co/3tZEQGmWln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reid is an anchor, without him the Cats are adrift on a sea of inconsistencies.  You like that analogy? I have more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Then we need to vote out members of the moderate wing ... names please]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AimeeBrunelle @CapriceLeonard @injurypics I had an athlete tell me he thought he had an “intone grownail”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LIVmiami @bellathorne @dani_thorne Wish I could party on stage w/ you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably like 99% not including going to class 😎 I’ve hung out with one person a few times (indirectly hung out wit… https://t.co/lruoDYDvMJ]]></document></documents></author>