<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Damn, Reggie will be missed. Even though I am a Sony boy I can respect Reggie and the incredible legacy he left beh… https://t.co/9YI4WHmXWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kasual_Kook It's Walmart. What can we expect. @Target it's your time to shine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cirEzleH You think company’s care more about checking out who they’re bringing along for an unpaid internship than… https://t.co/0BCd4q83Ic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwcongdon @dietchinator Seems to me like you have an axe to grind, so I’ll let you get back to your ever-so-scholarly grinding of axes. 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another thing to add to the list as to why Star Wars fans are toxic. This is getting out of hand. It’s ok to not li… https://t.co/NGfKGoMPdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidewaters @ConroysWestwood @BarleysOP @LlywelynsPubs Also O’Neill’s in PV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisismenic70 This caused my pun detector software to sound an alarm at 4:30am local time 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @LittleMissRina @LilveronicaR @SyrenDeMerXXX @EvelinStone69 @officalzoeclark @AngelSmallsxxx… https://t.co/Uz7dPv7atQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ddavis3clemson He’ll be a contributor. Just not as a weekend starter right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DangeRussWilson @ciara Are you really wanting to leave to new year ??? Please let us fan know the truth #GoHawks]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got nothing about #ANoNo @MariahCarey what’s happening?? I know she gon surprise release the video and shut us u… https://t.co/TosA8WGj9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your website crashes for seemingly no reason 🤷🏾‍♂️ #Entrepreneurship]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last sunrise walking in the sand. #saltlife @ Melbourne Beach, Florida https://t.co/ddQdQFNGuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsonMeyer @CamerinBrown12 @chase_s3 @chance11or @erichards23_ @KnoxOlyn @TheKid71403451 @samaad35… https://t.co/cwPToe5tFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Air Force Secretary Wilson to resign in May, return to academia https://t.co/Ldcjw88DG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 87% Off Chiropractic Package with Massage and Adjustment https://t.co/QVrXNHurQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me trying to constantly validate myself is literally impossible I want to correct people but at this point my fans… https://t.co/kbpufzBnAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Talkmaster you are just like my parents, reading something online and spreading it without even a fact check]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ghyxion @StuartGrist I'm listening to Queen. Hard to focus. Like The Beastie Boy's"]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally would say the lines before they happened every fucking time during umbrella academy and I’m pretty sure I’m the time travel kid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pauljimerson I give you Alamogordo New Mexico's "World's Largest Pistachio."  😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[☘️ 🇮🇪Month of Shenanigans has started. Time for #KaliforniaKarl to brush up on Irish songs. @ Rhode Island https://t.co/ZnTsPpAsjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aislinteran_ @violeta_garac Pues el sábado es mi cumple y están invitadas 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somos agua @naufragoentwitt  dir: carlos_yidi en Cutler Bay, Florida https://t.co/pRm8yrjYhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[No shit!!! This guy may be worth $300k/yr if he actually believes this and manages BPD with the goal of rooting out… https://t.co/TT6q4piqND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@globetweetin @CNN Change within the Church is LONG overdue. Finally, the truth is being revealed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your role is to govern to the highest standards for your constituents, not to raise the bar...to exceed it.  These… https://t.co/Ap4cmBr88n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plgcgreens Hopefully the odour is also the organic fertilizer and not the other option. This is the time of year w… https://t.co/cyX1Kd7O9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[A in-depth documentary about his childhood would be sooo dope!!! https://t.co/IlQdLvQ2kf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elyrozc @arrobada_ Jueputa Cali es Lo maximo, nos vemos en Junio mi Cali Bella]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 game turnaround in @SouthlandSports play from last season. Amazing coaching job by @CoachJustice10]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will miss DD greatly, I learned so much about the game from him! Prayers for the Dawson family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAY 1 - Johnathan Cromwell "Pokémon Go" murder Trial  - Pool of 80+ potential jurors are questioned/narrowed down t… https://t.co/RilDV6WUbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch I've read a few of the opposition to Dana's tweets and their profiles/They ether live in a state where the… https://t.co/Ott3BdYKTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@undertheskiin Not my movie podcast, but my wife's:  "Felix Drags Dale Though the Marvel Universe" @FelixDragsDale… https://t.co/EHsiBArDDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when people doubt me. Brings the best out of me. Makes me stronger. Doubt of people is a great source of ene… https://t.co/hHNDu5sEk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beauty4Ashes_1 not certain what has happened?  If you wish I will not mention you in future Tweets, if you wish?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sanctification (2014) by Russian River Brewing Company @ Kandahar Lodge — https://t.co/W7JXTrMFOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lineups are official. Adam Lowry in for #NHLJets and Par Lindholm, Matt Hendricks, Bogdan Kiselevich, Josh Morrisse… https://t.co/UCJWFhtPOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CristinaAimee @mchicon @ZackFinkNews @rubendiazjr @revrubendiaz This is what we should be fighting 👉🏽 Sandy Creek… https://t.co/K9lBWOHIyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The greatest curse brought down on us by technology is that it prevents us from escaping the present even for a br… https://t.co/hfVYDRodBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[D3 South 🏒Playoffs: #7 @UpperCapeAD (15-6) hosts #11 @CoyleAthletics (12-6-2) at Gallo on 2/28 at 8 PM. https://t.co/VYMN6xN7N7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plays “Hilda” on Netflix  Me: wow the soundtracks pretty banging already yoooo  “Music by Grimes”  Me: Oh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeStuchbery_ @ProudLondoner05 It seems to me, with the volume of mail you're getting, you might need a bigger ha… https://t.co/fmXXXo9yu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rms5539 @capitalweather Would love to see analysis of what this means. I have two preschoolers so first theory I n… https://t.co/GNEE33U6vG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zay_devon He just smiling too like he ain’t about to face the death penalty in Florida if convicted 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time to eliminate it. If I am expected to send my three daughters to foxholes to be shot at to make a point a… https://t.co/kCvfpEjOs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisWardle77 But failing a test often leads to punishment, doesn’t it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madison_lugo @laineyanderson_ @Langerbanger11 Gotta take care of your woman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TR401 @AriannaSimpson @patrick_oshag @JayBilas does his 94 feet interview for basketball.  Your pod should be call… https://t.co/YzrsqeuFeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blndebabe1202 oh my. Absolutely stunning view. WOWZERS! Have an awesome day young lady! I know you made my day better!!! 😍😉😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on twitter ever day I get people following and number don’t move just got 8 more just now and number same]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lorena yes: great picked up to ari and November show . Too busy to finalize 25% Lorena no: bachelor until all deals… https://t.co/14ITuvugaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leesmit73676033 @ksugiuraajc I'm glad you're on board because this is fixing to get good and I mean real good!! GO JACKETS and THWG!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Muletrain65 @VandyMBB Yeah but Atleast he’s living up to the Vandy standard in football, Basketball is supposed to… https://t.co/6BzYSvKIVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nika723 @MiguelANunezJr @EddieGriffinCom You do know R Kelly did go trial before it didn't go the way ppl wanted b… https://t.co/njurCjdGTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any Orlando photographers that could help me out with a few photos tomorrow am?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimboDiddleyDoo @essenviews Yeah, you know it is bad when talking to my mom and she says something along the lines… https://t.co/G7AvC9EDXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scotteTheKing @danieledobish All those included sugars are a killer. Still a smart move.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GilpinPeri What’s the world coming to when my favorite actress misses my birthday?!?! I thought for sure it was circled on your calendar!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjbowles4 @Spring_Harbinge @Aug1405 @GIJoeOPS @ffjeff @rkinseth @Politick_Rick @suprdupe @formulalol @PrayerFactor… https://t.co/AafUBUlRCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamOrr3 @consmover @DrSueDVM Think he knows how AMERICA began? I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing… https://t.co/tyvnwHK39n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LazarBeamYT Laserbeam can you play with me in Fortnite my name is TheBlacktiger555 #usecodeLazerbeam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acosta I wonder why? Maybe lack of qualifications? Afraid of heavy questioning by the Democrats?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankFerragine It feels unstable here with high winds, is there snow or rain coming to Stratford today Frank?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwardVanWinkle @This_Tinyviking @Krilliams The movie  is  "Bruce Almighty" (2003). He spelled the word 'beautiful'.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are you doing @RapSheet lol   RIP to your mentions today and especially if he doesn't go to Buffalo.… https://t.co/xrYHQVEePR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC When can we expect an investigation into @AOC for campaign finance violation?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I generally believe illegal immigration is a net economic benefit. So why support a wall? The issue is #RuleOfLaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenMikeLee But HOW does that protect them from the CIA... OUR election meddlers since 1941?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In like a lion, out like a lamb. The March of Ides.” - Em this morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW REMEMBER MAINSTREAM MEDIA PROMOTES THE HIJACKING TERRORIST JUDGES A LOT. IN DIFFERENT FORAMS. THAT IS BECAUSE T… https://t.co/Ebs2RHNXAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HLNTV Does anyone think these 2 are in a relationship other than the obvious one that they are in]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prosperous05 @villasgia @silverhelen2093 @HenryAlbaFrank @krenidalia20 @Eltox1 @Fer66deAlizze ..... y ahora ?? Qué… https://t.co/ckUqwRHTcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/DtLwUyUTbr #DRCongo This study showed that #household size, income, WASH status and #rural site were… https://t.co/EPUXVsAXBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaitlinLong_ @Tyler_Lindholm @TraceMayer I haven't read the whole article yet. While I like what Wyoming is doing,… https://t.co/HkEXSFkr1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[F*** BOTH the Rephuckkklicans AND the Demokkkraps! BOTH parties are BLATANTLY WHITE STUPREMACIST/RACIST, DIVISIVE,… https://t.co/3Gxf1jcEdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Just_Win_Baby_ @BlackFoxRaider He is getting assisted suicide in 2 days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI @PennWBB is back in the @IvyLeague Tournament for the third straight year after a victory over @HarvardWBB on… https://t.co/wGETWRWOi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPMajor @SueSmrekar @alha81005 @PlanetaryColin Really, it's a plan I'll propose, in which we'll tow Venus to Earth… https://t.co/wCpnKz6BSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[i let my nose piercing grow in bc i didn’t realize i had taken it out :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune into our game today at 3PM vs. Monroe CC. #GoJayhawks #SUNYJCC🏀🦅 https://t.co/aOG5wUM1sN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the pleasure of meeting Bobbi-Lyn during our @CF24 event for @SOOntario at CrossFit Odeon in Hamilton.  Such a… https://t.co/YlUiBJ8KLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeensCa @SariTreks Yes, AOC wants us to eat cow dung as it will clean up the land.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cereal_Saiyan Here are my two team Palkia and Dialga team one and team two https://t.co/efpNCpn3DT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kyle Wright with a magnificent game today against a tough Yankee lineup. @mlbbowman]]></document><document><![CDATA[De-icing the plane wings. OKC. Headed home. @ Will Rogers World Airport https://t.co/fwYwIIKO2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FloridaGal0814 How do Those Folks tell BlackFolks to go back when thier ancestors funded the process to bring them here....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsROCK2019 @stirgryguy2 Most people don’t know that Ladt Train To Clarksville is a protest song! ✊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottmerkin Sounds like the 2019 Sox slogan, post Machado fail, and with the fragile state of this injury plagued rebuild. "Just Feel Sad."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clovis69 @alllibertynews @TezJosh @LPNational You have the right to your own body. You own your body. However, whe… https://t.co/nWa2wQKJk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC This is the America I know . Willing to drop everything and stand by and fellow American in his last steps home . So awesome 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Sooners are 8 of 16 from 3-point range with 14 minutes left in the game. https://t.co/aI1u9KU0CI]]></document><document><![CDATA[i be thinking of the randomest shit &amp; i just wanna tell my friends but ion wanna be buggin 💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy found with lot wepons didn’t cause trouble yet why is govt worried bout someone who has lot weapons your r… https://t.co/V6hB8dpAMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green book winning best picture is a loss for humanity smh whack ass movie whack ass academy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldClarke63 @conorsmurf @ElementPictures Oh my! Finally people more wholesome than the British royals in his last movie!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This mornings 46th Annual Los Angeles Mayor’s Prayer Breakfast was excellent. Strong messages of Kindness, Love, en… https://t.co/wrRHTZkD5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my God...... here we go ,...... it’s hard to feel happy for Solsjær when I wake up to bullshit like this. Really… https://t.co/PWBQdIFrEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheForum1510 and @devilradio can we agree that @NewsTalk1510am needs to give up #Gary for lent?!!!]]></document></documents></author>