<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Y'all I'm so tired... Dropped an entire 8 places on Spotify. Troye and Lauv stans need to keep this in the top 50. Keep streaming]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElektroChik ME TOO! i lost it last night at that movie and what prompted this question!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza Nancy never bothers to look into facts. She just uses hateful histrionic cliches and never admits she’s wrong. Some leader.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing her more than ever tonight. All I want right now is to be in her arms ❤️ https://t.co/nrwnrN0yFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[She Walks in Beauty: A Woman's Journey Through Poems INGRAM INTERNATIONAL INC https://t.co/1W4VQZU6DM via @amazon]]></document><document><![CDATA[We always have @andrewmcmahon. 10 shows, 3+ years and you can still bring me out of a mood @ The Truman https://t.co/aycR03bjv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ruth_Terry @Banalization @TheoTypes @MedillSchool Huh? So wearing hand-me-downs, driving a car that almost always… https://t.co/TrfawCNI9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet @TheRynheart @senatemajldr If they can hear each other from their separate bedrooms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I rearranged my cabinets last weekend and when I went to get ingredients to bake bread this is what I found https://t.co/lGaiNfCcG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjamingoloff @sunrisemvmt What these organizations want is to get easily led people to vote liberal, grow the go… https://t.co/sK9PCLpg3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I typically don't use matte top coat, but my hubby suggested it and I love it! @OPI_PRODUCTS Kanpai OPI with… https://t.co/080O5fwASy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Holmer_K @mommamia1217 To those who say it would have made NYC richer: WE ARE RICH ENOUGH ALREADY!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pokes86 @brianstelter @MargaretHoover @CNNTonight @CNN The lady on the panel on CNN was reporting on what a Fox Ne… https://t.co/MLdn6BSA0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOVA Cavs would like to welcome Junior Lance Johnson to the program for the 2019 AAU season.   The talented and ver… https://t.co/LWZuwqIZqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s like men have special powers that make you irritated in .2 seconds with the way they act https://t.co/TD4JeC9ZgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YugiohMemories Wow two vids in one day good for you Dylan. Kusanagi dueling playmaker is going to be hard to watch… https://t.co/BwPW6HYulZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many thanks to @jilljillmcd for tonight’s @GrubWriters Submittaton. 70 pieces to 48 places by 15 people, fueled… https://t.co/r9LqwCA0OY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone!! Have a GROOVY weekend!!! https://t.co/L31DhR7Byf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory @mattgaetz #LockThemAllUp that is a terrorist threat and people of color have gone to jail for less it's… https://t.co/2WdzaLGJ5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurieGelfand2 @StevieHimself Not to worry ....your posts WON'T BE passed about   NEVER AGAIN!!!!  NOTHING WILL BE… https://t.co/qk8ViMZLo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Purging my closet and @rachm0301 just let me keep a dress with a sole purpose of if we ever go to a renaissance fair 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronSandoval10 you wild, you got me out here still recovering from last night, i had breakfast at 7:30pm bc i cou… https://t.co/SqQAj9mmWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @LindseyGrahamSC What has become of the Lindsey Graham who was a once trusted,  patriotic politician a… https://t.co/UuQOFDlugy]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if we read the Bible less like rules for holiness and more like assessment, helping us see where God is at wor… https://t.co/3eDwbYdsY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 CONCERT ANNOUNCEMENT 🚨 after taking a little bit to focus on finishing “Seasons”, young B is finally gonna be bac… https://t.co/RR2I6VNo3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DEADLINE Wait a minute? What the hell did Spike Lee do last night?!? He “slammed” President Trump but it’s not rep… https://t.co/KtCyeSQDFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@U_of_Towson @DaFlock12 @PVI_Athletics This was a great day!!! One of most fun games I’ve been a part of! 💙💪🏻🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@funtownusa testifying against paid sick days. Sorry but no thanks to sick employees working at a water park and s… https://t.co/5No7il0l2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[You haven’t seen crazy like Valentine’s Day at elementary school crazy lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I avoided more of the Pride long enough...so Kaleigh Franklin becuase RIP COME BACK I MISS YOU also why no gifs in existence....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered Frozen lottery to win $30 (plus service charge) tickets! https://t.co/brrIVDOCOP #luckyseat via @lucky_seat]]></document><document><![CDATA[This really is so much fun! Be a part of the action and hospitality! #iowanice #MarchMadness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sim_Pop @EthereumDenver @gkimbwala @GraceTorrellas @talandersson @hichrisfabian Wow 😂 you’ve changed your look… https://t.co/bi9u2Do8Mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time lunch with coworkers at Sizzler, Glendale. This is my 1st time dinning at @Sizzler_USA although I… https://t.co/CTRBUw99JP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I saw it. My jaw was on the floor. Notice how he didn’t even answer Gayle’s question. I 100% believe he was ab… https://t.co/efwKKr6kqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[A toasted/grilled Indian Egg #Sandwich, habanero mayonnaise and Curried eggs. #DancesWithRain #FeedFeed #FoodGasm… https://t.co/T5kIj9E3Me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vital prograns that supports healthy aging and reduces more costly care need to be adequately funded!]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the right you can see the @Amtrak train still on the tracks. (It’s unclear if any passengers are still on there)… https://t.co/phNoYxeB7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarochi1 I took a political compass test when I was in the hospital for the two months- found out I was farther le… https://t.co/dhN7pZFyUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[only good thing about waking up before the sun  does https://t.co/jUSw9Xcwzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[AG Barr your first job as AG should be to purge the upper echelon of both the FBI andDOJ in order to restore trust… https://t.co/OtSNSdmEpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Southwestern (main campus) stay away from library. My recommendation is to go home, be safe, call it a day]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about he “steals” it back from sanctuary cities&amp; all of the illegals???]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just disrespectful making the west coast have east coast weather ! @ Ricoh USA https://t.co/XdmorEnJ0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[54 year old Mark Skinner of Niagara Falls will appear in court this morning. @CHCHNews @morninglive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well still no full week of school, but maybe we’ll make it on a Wednesday this week?? https://t.co/GRA3jvFsC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Security Forces/USAF before civilian law enforcement is the best decision I’ve ever made. Everything we learn in th… https://t.co/qqFn8BNwET]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desejo de segunda? - Férias na Disney 🥰  #pandora #avatar #naviriverjourney #disney #animalkingdom #vacation… https://t.co/ExJfTt8JOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haydenblack Jordan, shut up‼️Your two-bit cents are NOT even being heard, because you are trying to coverup BS tha… https://t.co/Ppv5eONEGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they say all the right things but their actions dont back it up. 🤦‍♀️💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its my pleasure to share the amazing experiences I was privileged to have with so many of my heroes and SHEROEs. Th… https://t.co/7BQUrGZUF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain Obviously, you don't understand the law or facts. Now run along, little ignorant child...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Chicago friends: I wanna go out n drink tonight Bar tab on me, who’s in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter this contest to win a $200 gift card, winners drawn weekly! https://t.co/RvkONFLh7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyFavMurder @GHardstark @KarenKilgariff  @StevenRayMorris Y’all see this? https://t.co/JPcow55vKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've really been enjoying going to this awesome coffeeshop in my town. It is so chill and the coffee is soooo good.… https://t.co/VyYo54Zuut]]></document><document><![CDATA[...for you are dust, and to dust you shall return https://t.co/NcqybaSSeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpreadGirlLove @aliciakeys I was trying to find it, but I don't see it anymore.😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[How would our children experience mathematics learning if we all embraced these values? Love the core values… https://t.co/sAdivt6Sye]]></document><document><![CDATA[“How is it that you work here but @dabombchelle worked here just that one summer as a punishment?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waynepzink @SpeakerPelosi @JussieSmollett You blaming the President for these 3 hoaxes??? https://t.co/SjUw81UFZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and shine ❤️🧡💛💚💙💜 #photooftheday #lingerlonger #riseandshine #florida #beach @ Sanibel, Florida https://t.co/gGItlZGPVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inner thigh and ab work for your Sunday morning fun! - I always love to combine yoga and Pilates- I find inner thig… https://t.co/N0tOZqoHUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does @POTUS not have rights to protect himself from all these false charges?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all. I finished my hospice volunteer training!!! It’s not like a HUGE deal but I am proud of myself bc I had to d… https://t.co/rH9oJviVuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m doing my week late sub assignment to curve my grade it better be worth it 🥺😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ptbrasil A reforma e o pre -sal! E o povo escravisado!!! O. Débil qie apoia isso e' ant cristo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sillzmom1 Makes sense to me. So many other shows like Roseanne, actors were fired. Why not him? It just seems as i… https://t.co/BQyn0sKkuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the vein of Jillian Venters, today's stylistic approach is 'convention committee running on too little sleep, bu… https://t.co/ymvIr3Ouev]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY: The best gift you can give a realtor is a closed deal. I'll bring the #candy. #home #humor… https://t.co/E3SJbQ3HTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody wouldn't let me study today. #badkitty #cute #cutenessoverload #kitty #cat #cats #catsitter #catsitting… https://t.co/gqKz9Y4A3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[So anyone notice that there’s a trending # for #KirpaForBachelorette...guess figured out who actually started that rumor. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irenekcastillo @JusttGabrielll @Lilopez97 I’m still so confused, please come back to explain to me tomorrow morning when you’re sober]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraLynneXOXO there’s the house I was arrested in for underage drinking. this is the bar where I got blacked out o… https://t.co/0dTRgSucz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can anyone tell me if HEB still has chocolate covered strawberries? I didn’t get any this year so I need to find my own. 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is another member if the GOP who's mind has been corrupted by greed. Russian money buys a lot.… https://t.co/ORVmjEo33w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreMac_VII Right?!  Me trying to pronounce it... https://t.co/ZTcImJ02j0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are absolutely correct, Sir, &amp; TY for exposing their duplicity. A $oro$ plan all along?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome home cat #2. Abby isn’t a snuggler. But she is today. #abby #mama #themama #calico #polydactyl… https://t.co/EExhVF2RJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kristy23111 @DiamondandSilk talk to demms and republicans and tell them what you want. if that dont work, shoot em just kidding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Tate_penn legs out an infield RBI single. 12-3 Niners. Runners on the corners, one out for Dom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast Megan MCaind daughter of the  Late Sen. John McCain is seriously damaging her father view view of Am… https://t.co/z5yeiJFDus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DallasBrownin16 @VicCervantes3 @j2nmeyer @222girl @SaveBenSolo1 @jonz970 @GoldStuart @GurlPower72 @Legacyband12… https://t.co/cOlN0E13Tu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup. Officially digging the new ‘do. #shorthair #45yearsold #readingglasses @ Minneapolis City Hall https://t.co/k1aZHYBu8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paul Manafort Gave Konstantin Kilimnik 75 Pages of Polling Data, Docs Suggest https://t.co/CdV9dI5exF via @thedailybeast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyTClemson @MYSTIC7 This would still be his Birthday moron  🤦🏽‍♀️ He died Sept 4th so that would be his "death… https://t.co/DcWbn9w3BN]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL ever get called in twice on your day off? Cause same and I’m annoyed about it 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnpaidPiper @CNN It was because firefighters and etc saved a newborn that was found in a drain. Saved her life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wowww "Everybody's out of the cars and everybody is OK" #Daytona500 @NASCAR 18 cars piled up!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve met a lot of famous people but I think @DreKnott is the most popular]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibyaLiberty Vise, like the clamping tool that holds things steady in a construction setting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NYCYouth has been tasked with managing the prep of this city’s next generation of leaders to fulfill their potent… https://t.co/rrt8IK1IH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithboykin @dawn_macc And those of us with cable are funding  Fox News in our subscriptions,  which pays Sean han… https://t.co/lTQJqouJQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve literally had the worst day ever and can’t wait to go home and cry]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought that live action shows (like the ones on Disney Channel and Nickelodeon) were for older kids and that I w… https://t.co/0ZZXzFySA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[me when someone doesn’t use their blinkers: “well you obviously didn’t ask for blinkers on your car”]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week has been full of auditions! Thank you @GtmlaLa taradise_live !!!! You are amazing! • • • #model… https://t.co/NC9CLXpsIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally!!!! Good time to come home to see that the struggles have been perfected!!! Great job guys!!!! #HB126… https://t.co/M2X1YVed1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, I’m sad @lysaissa will not witness the experience that is The New Day tonight. No pancakes for us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123  Answer to your questions bon your insta story 1. Yes things taste different in the different ways you… https://t.co/cro1T7U0Oe]]></document></documents></author>