<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Man there some legitimately good-hearted ppl in AZ!!  #ThursdayMotivation #ThursdayThoughts #HashtagBlessed 🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold Hearted by Seven Lions x Kill The Noise  Thanks for coming to my Ted Talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[There isn’t a real emergency.  Thus it IS about separation of powers—Article 1 stuff from Constitution. Simply put… https://t.co/nLGkAyb15u]]></document><document><![CDATA[The headline is misleading. The crosswalks will be temporarily closed and won’t be permanently eliminated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RizzShow all Chinese joints you pay before you eat and there’s no wait staff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianschatz Actually, I'm showing my guys An Inconvenient Truth, and we're laughing our asses off at all the bulls… https://t.co/bvMtkMrpX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metrolosangeles Thanks for having the driver check on him. He's out of it, and covered in blood, but responsive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got word that I lost a brother. He was looking he found it. Stop with the @‘s he was a warrior. #ruizing]]></document><document><![CDATA[My instincts after drinking or eating too much is the same as a dying cat. When my belly’s full I’ll have a whole g… https://t.co/OA9ZsTLbdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fawfulfan My thoughts, too. Robert Morton, author of spy thriller https://t.co/m9bwxgItYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saying...  you have to fight through some bad days to earn the best day of your life. @ Long Beach, California https://t.co/hM0IgOefRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots to be proud of and thankful for from Day 1 at NCA. No matter what place you are in going into Day 2, winners w… https://t.co/4XIrd9cvyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASOS_HeretoHelp my package is estimated to be delivered on or before tomorrow, but still haven’t gotten a shipping notification]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is just too cute for words! *📷credit:@mrsjfreezy  #DADDYSGIRL💕 #MYBRAEOFSUNSHINE☀️ @ Amarillo, Texas https://t.co/luZ9QVZXQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinkontink @Steelerschic85 @Kovie1961 @kamcam65 @Kcmichelle2017 @jawofsteel2014 @7brdgesroad @MagsBitchs… https://t.co/nsoCEKYzwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[spaceykacey you have to listen to the end of this video 😂 I hope you saw my bright light from the balcony! I was se… https://t.co/yFSgQuYv8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[#photography101📷   Know your Footing and surroundings  in your effort to gain preferred angle  and perspective!… https://t.co/aWoIan4Ef1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi, I’m Nathan Poumade, SBTS @FCPSFranklinMS and just put my kids to bed. #NoVAedchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mnwild @MichGoldenLight Watch out. Looks like the Wild are starting to have fun 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FFAaroneous @iKezims If the Falcons had done their job after the Super Bowl, it could already be a rule lol.  I ag… https://t.co/XazPz4YuOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClevelandRuss No lie that was the one I didn’t recognize. What is it??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyWilliamsMBE @AnjaHuberSkel @TeamGB I remember watching this , nine years goes quick huh? Congrats on the WIN an… https://t.co/Ws2Gc3fZtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThoriumWealth @EconomPic @jus10castelli @jvogs02 @michaelbatnick My best line ever. Coaching varsity baseball eons… https://t.co/l80LwnyegR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrecisionGuessw &amp; @ravimotha I decided to wear this one in honor of the #umbraco v8 launch today :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NIH_Bear @hutchins_e Why do I get the feeling your days as a circus cub were spent being beaten to the music of Sc… https://t.co/CqLFOSUFyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanlchung @sarahohjessica Hey, I was doing just fine before I met you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigbangtheory @warnerbrostv I still use ‘Bazinga’ often with my wife and teenager. The pure joy of that and the ball pit was pure magic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kady makes some good points - I don't buy the characterization but I do respect the views]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's children have the audacity to blame others for harassing their execrable father.They say it's a Pres… https://t.co/jWqBHL5ikJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Taylor Norman 3 forces a Yukon timeout, 31-19 Bulldogs with 3:31 left in the third.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some shots from a quick session with @leveebanks while testing out the EOS3 | #35mm https://t.co/9UPUk6CtFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uber says 8 mins away, takes 25 minutes and then proceeds to cancel because he can’t figure out how a one way street works 🤦🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanidaPeters @OutOfRegister lmao......good,   come over to jersey if u want to dance, and get flattened....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random thought while sweating to death on a treadmill at 10:30 pm. I’d like to find bands influenced by… https://t.co/MUVwCWlmG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathanghall @kamilaofprague Personally, I’d lean away from faceless webinars and toward something like a zoom chat… https://t.co/07DX1zb78r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ero has decided that my beard belongs to him. #catdadlife #cats #Eratosthenes https://t.co/fBZ83UMNtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lena Dunham cashmere scarves and $100 limited-edition lipstick: MCA pop-up shop features photographer's...… https://t.co/JP2M3dkhd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dontDieGolive You can’t be serious. Everything else will inflate. Good luck renting a porta-potty if that happens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msgarden_edu @austin_carla @KCHankerson @DC_STEMtastic @MsNardosG @DG_Teaches_AVID Good work Garden!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khyatt2876 @drayzze If that naked  dude standing there had any “facsimile” of a brain, he would at least get out o… https://t.co/Yd6lV5C6tl]]></document><document><![CDATA[the country. The Arena at Faith Lutheran is a really neat place to play, and coach. All the banners, the stands, th… https://t.co/EOxtit1gX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charleswsmithjr @philipnation Only the wildest documentary you have ever seen. I would say it is unbelievable, but… https://t.co/nVA6kNuKsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNewsSunday Wouldn't that be like going into battle without going through basic training? Trump will be waiting for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made fried pickles and like hot Cheeto fries pickles but they weren’t as good as I thought they were gonna be 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[get your children vaccinated (and I cannot stress this enough) ....that’s it. Just get your children freakin vaccinated]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a lifelong fan of the Washington, DC team, I am fully on board with the idea of trading for Josh Rosen. #HTTR https://t.co/OylDqm70rB]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT WAS ONE TIME, TRICIA. I WAS IN HIGH SCHOOL AND I THOUGHT IT'D MAKE ME LOOK COOL  -me explaining that one night i… https://t.co/kbuShUzTM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[And again the number 14 for 6:27 at stop 5800 is a no show.  I am sure @OC_Transpo will have no comment as to why t… https://t.co/hE2GZTObL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re in search of some #MondayMotivation then you should spend your #presidentsday watching our YouTube video… https://t.co/9GBfNyboOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the dopamine spike from a reward is what sets up the attachment to the reward. Dopamine Spike - Part 1 (Episode… https://t.co/BE2quGzsCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien It is so absolutely embarrassing that this Dolt is POTUS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Anchor Steam Beer by @AnchorBrewing @ Beer Co. — https://t.co/XVv76GFgRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Email me if you’re interested in participating in #Celtics Post Game. We’re looking for staff. Any recommendations… https://t.co/1XMPWLOYay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMooreAthletics  @letsgohornets  @osvarsity  @orlandosports  #BishopMoore Girls #1- #4  vs #LakeMaryPrep Feb 20 https://t.co/5FEalYy5PF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the passion of this song ❤️: Beth &amp; Joe - I Love You More Than You'll Ever Know - Live in Amsterdam… https://t.co/c4DqiqIZAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UncleAL_2012 Equality for all have always been a facade and good rhetoric. Social media has alot of stuff worst bu… https://t.co/pEMTPJsUlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fighting used to be so much fun an now i'm just like..."get lost" for every situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every single one of us Indiana Hoosiers basketball fans the last 30 seconds of that game 😔 https://t.co/77gdHWmCgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sky looked really good today. #myphotography #myneighborhood #floridaskies #sunset #floridaskiesneverdisappoint… https://t.co/R6S2GqHMKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Music Label Spotlight February 26, 2019  Celebrating 15 Years Of Cosmicleaf Records  Side Liner… https://t.co/gDSFRpxhTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NomadLounger @RedSoxRedShoes @j_legally @JodiCab Elliott is introducing 4 of her friends to Hoop for her birthday… https://t.co/6PdfshWEo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 274: The Dark Vanguard(Fortnite) #fortnite is the popular #videogames that has strange #characters and #violent… https://t.co/0rVFJwQMDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we can see runners showing up in the distance, they gotta loop around and then come by the school]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today has the most Blessed Ash Wednesday for my in a very long time. You know, Scripture tells us that when we foll… https://t.co/w5sy08oUIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite the expression, we’re all extremely excited about our current situation. First time in public since this jo… https://t.co/EXaIRKgc7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin Angelica got a million fans on Instagram because after she left the dating site I saw her Instagram page… https://t.co/jtpw7MXmxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[September 27, 2018 at The Let Love Inn Leo Genovese - piano Juini Booth - bass Lawrence Clark - tenor saxophone Geo… https://t.co/kIAxoJIWA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[They look good in this @sandlotgoods koozie for @TheKeepAtTheK. https://t.co/ON5K75wFmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GracieLovesUSA @bbusa617 @deborah_berch @RealTCBoyle @Vagabundo_4 @SpiderJ2044 @Quin4Trump @J_Allen_CA… https://t.co/RDaVpeoSlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mr_e_us Or plucking the hairs out of her chin... 🤷🏻‍♂️ #thethingswedoforlove #10cc  https://t.co/S6ENqcEPHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe there will be more women on the radio, now that scumbags are being outed for trying to stand in their way. 💪🏼🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[trying not to focus on the love I feel my life is lacking and more on the love and support that already exists around me]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@mschlapp you must be kidding ... you are proposing precisely the “1984” approach to government— accept newspeak a… https://t.co/bRTswTOD1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dan55980561 Jordan has that edge, he's got that killer instinct, that I'm going to finish this team, close this ga… https://t.co/TaiB74sEdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Surfermom77 @steph93065 She’s got that finger point, head nod thing going. Throw in a “Full Stop” and I think she’s got it 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALF: Southeast 34 - Crestview 12 A 13-0 run from the Pirates to end the half. Everything falling. Rachel Neer 3-of… https://t.co/j4m3YDvlCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[You said what you said. Don’t try to flip it. It was bogus, take the L. Do better next time, and keep it pushing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My office for tonight. We'll see how the 450SX riders do in their second Triple Crown of 2019, and we'll get a glim… https://t.co/dBzsZWuGNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Nothing from @senatemajldr McConnell @GOPLeader McCarthy about Evangelical Republican Special Persecutor K… https://t.co/ArGQVd0SME]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the only pictures we have but it’s da best have a great birthday buddy, I’ll see you tonight.… https://t.co/64lVsgeLCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[...I have categorically proven to myself within the past couple of decades that there is indeed much less Autism AC… https://t.co/vYKtHDhoB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of all the comments you can receive from a guy I get the your eyes are spaced out evenly. Jokes on you you beca… https://t.co/riDem462Fh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inrogers29 Yah been watching #RAW and #SDLive the last few weeks. Very entertaining. 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACH0N3y @animalcrossing Is this even the #FlowerPatchGlitch?  I thought this was normal? https://t.co/OAo4nIusxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast bitches! (@ Starbucks in Brooklyn, NY) https://t.co/cnnegKjLbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dukedynamite Just glad it seems like they are doing more than last year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sestze2 @FreddyCaple @clairlemon @Quillette @RespectableLaw Listen, the point is that there’s nothing racist about… https://t.co/e1uIdzJCkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having confidence in yourself is key to success in life. (Song is tongue and cheek). https://t.co/SV0mIeusfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you run for any political position knowing that every detail of life would be exposed? Trump did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindarutter @Nic_O_tine @auntieamy90 In honor of spring training starting, I’ll just leave this here: Rob Deer wasn’t very fast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The throwback Magic uniforms look great. If I squint I see Penny and Shaq. Oh and Nick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dallasmavs is there video of the full length shot that didn’t count but went in?  I couldn’t believe it wasn’t sho… https://t.co/vS3TH5HJVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t want to be a parent past the first 18 years then don’t be a parent at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislongview Ok. My jaw dropped when I heard him say that and I’m glad I’m not alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[We go live now to various locations around the country, where the #JeopardyAllStars have all coincidentally issued… https://t.co/1LuvTWD59Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots to be proud of today if you’re an @USMGoldenEagles fan, alumni and student!  SOUTHERN MISS.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Harris is the biggest sleeper in the NBA from 3-point range...don’t @ me. @BrooklynNets]]></document><document><![CDATA[No bueno.   You pretty much have to increase your withholdings which makes your paycheck a lot smaller.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Remember back in the days when niggas had waves Cazal shades and corn braids” #RIPBiggie https://t.co/mxqwDdc2K0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgent15 @cincygreghoodin Hey now, let’s believe the dictator thats known for torturing his own people]]></document></documents></author>