<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@char_stokely Happy Valentine’s Day ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️💕💕💕💕💕 https://t.co/fAN9kodr4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick little update on the #Blog!  https://t.co/bn2SkRkoEj #crueltyfree #unitedstates #Australia #Canada #Mexico… https://t.co/DrEsg1iSiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[In less than 2 minutes, this precious dog proves that it has more empathy than most people today. 🐾❤️🐾  Empathetic… https://t.co/U0tVo1mhBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you City of Gallatin Engineering and Storm Water for reading to our students and telling us about your career… https://t.co/WyHFwMo0Mz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also the kind of sweet but sad part about this time is I was only allowed to listen to Christian music growing up (… https://t.co/jC74wrlbWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@serenawilliams @OlympiaOhanian There’s no Limit for the love of you r  child I love my children my grandkids my gr… https://t.co/bA19Ce7dGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Am I bar tending tonight?” - Kam “Why? Did I hire you last night?” - Bradley “Yeah..”. - Kam “Oh. Well you’re fired”  😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pandavoice007 @JudgeRinderTV @neal_katyal @jimwaterson @BillKristol @SenBlumenthal @asadowaisi @krassenstein… https://t.co/kWZo8D0ZgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[My last beer of the festival. Peace out Belgian Beer Fest  2019. ✌🍻 - Drinking a Sump Coffee Stout 2018 (Ethiopian… https://t.co/2hcBcZgS0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bien emocionada yo de que mañana entro a las 10 pero salgo hasta las 8pm xdxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shine bright like a diamond...💎 @ North Park, San Diego https://t.co/TQNEeFkoN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little team building with the eBoard before the @amasnhu meeting! @snhuoncampus #ama #snhu #amaicc https://t.co/uqc0kW1UJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[A real hug from a true friend is an incredible thing. Wonderful to catch up w beautiful, kind, gifted… https://t.co/m093hfoObC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FranncescaRobi1 @MSNBC It’s ok when he mocks disabled people though.they are showing him the way he is.they have p… https://t.co/oUKKL8lavM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was sitting here writing and I forgot about daylight savings time. It surprised me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was just woken up by the loudest noice of my 55lb dog falling off the bed in her sleep and crashing into my dresser.. happy sunday lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#charlesphoenix #disneylandhotel #dapperday #waybackwednesday @ Disneyland Hotel https://t.co/C6UiZVOovq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen Most texts need responses but the like button is good if the last text was just your run-of-the-mill… https://t.co/Rs0EnbxCJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things are just playful. 29 dogs who forgot how to dog, seriously so funny https://t.co/vgruBTt684]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Underground_RT @RT_com @AlanRMacLeod Yea because the Media says so https://t.co/Khu6Xwn6Lm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching old @taramassicotte vlogs I’ve never seen cause I just let YouTube pick what I should watch next https://t.co/ssZ24DJDFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LivePD I watched east coast showing of #LivePd and it was SO GOOD, I may watch it again. @deputyblanding from… https://t.co/bMnC0VDSiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is Day 1 of the book challenge given to me by @andierusso . The challenge is to post a cover of a book I love… https://t.co/kFCbjDG8TG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beltrandelrio Unos tostitos que traigan un tazo con la imagen del mesías de macuspana. Con el cuento que se aparec… https://t.co/UYrkVkOtcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw a great Charlotte @hornets game and met @CodyZeller last night with my CC Flight teamates. Today we take the fl… https://t.co/rG44jTt0zz]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a long tiring day, no matter how late at night it is, iced coffee is my go to comfort drink]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffGoins This is really beautifully penned, Jeff. Cannot agree more. 🙏♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was just informed that the vampire diaries is being taken off netflix march first and IM NOT DONE YET]]></document><document><![CDATA[Future - Promise U That (Audio) https://t.co/xgCrS3bXeq via @YouTube https://t.co/h4UbqjTPRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[when the driver in the lane next to you won’t let you merge in as if you won’t swerve and kill you both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lastly, while I'm drunk, I'm sick of reaching out in friendships and nothing being said back. I miss you but I'm re… https://t.co/C1grfUyl0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nybestseller7 @DonaldJTrumpJr Oh Sweetie. History will not be kind to Trumpism. It will reflect poorly on those who supported it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I ask my boss if he has an extra chair in his office because they’re usually placed in there for storage on Wedn… https://t.co/LRg5ZA0CJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUESS WHO IS GOING TO HAVE @Smashburger TONIGHT? After craving it for 2 weeks now??? This girl right here https://t.co/WbiIlmZIx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing snowflakes in March and wishing for spring... https://t.co/kWVjPggKwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss him every day...😢😢😢  I Never Expected Andrew Breitbart to Break My Heart https://t.co/HYksioO0db]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I really hope that our involvement with North Korea will help the people of that country live better lives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And away she goes! Amazing first round match! Watch out for this fresh face @CatyMcNally]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moonchild_30 Totally in line with what other friends (also fans) have said...it’s a shame they didn’t do his story justice :|]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patriot Militia before the battle #moorescreekbattlefield @ Moores Creek National Battlefield https://t.co/TAVapGK3Vi]]></document><document><![CDATA[just ordered all my grad stuff! can’t believe i’ll be a csulb alumni in like 3 months!]]></document><document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion: this was the most delicious medicine ever @vanessahepner]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crash on Hwy 24 involves 18-wheeler carrying chickens; coroner responding https://t.co/PD9pKwd7u8 via @cbs46 @bedge7767]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@American_MBB here's your 2018-19 POTY # 10 @TUMBBHoops @InternatlShizz !  #AmericanHoops #TempleTUFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating my 50th with women of Delta Sigma Theta Sorority. Thank you Sorors! https://t.co/VHylKoKuLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my dad #daddysgirl @ Tarboro, North Carolina https://t.co/cGrmYInO2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some detail shots of what I worked on last night.  Learning some new techniques 😊  #bombayink #watermedia… https://t.co/5j9LNjL4LX]]></document><document><![CDATA[you are so terribly missed. my heart will never feel the same again https://t.co/Gj6oatdBGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nrmentalhealth @healthmediagal1 @BethFratesMD @gary_hensel @AFR365 @AnneCooke14 @CutePicsOfDogs @KarenUnrue… https://t.co/tPXC8MBEQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just cant help getting exactly what I want how I want it knowing that I can. The only thing is I dont want it onc… https://t.co/pvhYQnA4hZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Co ngratulations on your accomplishments! I wish you the best for all your future plsons. Thsink you for your sqerv… https://t.co/HJPd3K10Ng]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must be nice to be asleep... I'm wide awake and have to be up in 3 hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tim_Caputo @DoughertyJC Especially in the Possum Capital of the World which is Wasau, FL, the tiny town where my grandparents live!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One look up And I saw gaged ears and neck tattoos and that’s really a huge part of why I’m such a mess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinsmurray @owillis I’m a book reader but at this point I think it reasonable to say that I can want TV series C… https://t.co/66cOuXn4oe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_____marisol @madisonrdaniel What I like most are the products that I can shop for before the box actually shops B… https://t.co/3U4Sw3I9MF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyO @NBCPolitics Rest In Peace thank for your service to our nation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[people deadass be feeling one some type of way when I don’t pay them any mind ? lol odd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @TinieTempah PLEASE put the UK version of Disc-Overy on Spotify man  I'm American but I need that disturbing London version]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gauchos gave it to you like a 3-peat🤪 National Champ 💙💛 https://t.co/0OWD7HQhGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simplified version of work interaction:  Me ~3 weeks ago: This desk is red. Coworker just now: Actually, this other… https://t.co/kALaE7lU9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haydenblack @CNN If there is no such thing as climate change, tell me then, why are the glaciers melting along wit… https://t.co/8HJ0JhMp7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EB_FindingMercy YES!!!!! Yes!!! Also, this can look differently depending on each situation - but too often, adopt… https://t.co/OZAvaHgs2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachFurr1000 WHY DO WE NEED A AMENDMENT? THOSE THINGS ARE AGAINST OUR CONSTITUTION]]></document><document><![CDATA[DaVinci Day!  It was so exciting watching and listening to the kids explore and problem solve!  Even Larry Llama go… https://t.co/23gm7jl9uL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The proof is always in the #screenshots!!! #sorrynotsorry #randompost #random #mondaynight 📱 @ Anaheim, California https://t.co/DZSm6APZDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Several “new” diet plans, strangely resembling Adkins, recommends eggs (protein) for breakfast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecksWrecks @renaudbedard @bad_tetris wow i cant believe im talkin to someone from the future..........]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMVivancoHRW Usted aun no ve que se cumplen los requisitos para cumplir con la obligación de proteger??? De verdad… https://t.co/67QVNwDNvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[trying to convince jessi to get her twitter back &amp; she tells me to get my facebook back... 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Touring the grounds at the US Naval Academy @CsdVikings @DrL_Barnes @Counselors_2013 https://t.co/5i6k0RM04X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, except for Lincoln’s commercial of Matthew Mc’s drunk relying on cars auto pilot]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to look that word up. Nice that you are using a good cover crop the fixes nitrogen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone needs to send me Sol Food! I have a serious craving! @ Sol Food Restaurant https://t.co/LQ0XSJPPPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow I wanna come see you!!!! Please!! I’ve had three major surgery this last year and was in rehab for a… https://t.co/nuYklxTX73]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess we’ll wait to see your sincerest sympathies for the next (inevitable) hate crime victim then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this family photo...lol. Zack is in here, just waited til the timer counted down then darted in an attempt t… https://t.co/WKNreLiVM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trust the wait. Embrace the uncertainty. Enjoy the beauty of becoming. 🕊 #freebabe @ Woodbury, Tennessee https://t.co/fHMXH195v0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever got denied dick by your man, he’s fucking someone else 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trevor8520 @espn @ScottKarlson @DanielMiernicki Hope the @packers get this cat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week, the window will be up! Visit our page on @MobileNom for the exact locations. https://t.co/Z3TqsYG1NR]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this funny there's something wrong with you. #laughter #lol #grin #clever https://t.co/TdxuvDEVs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking back I wonder how I didn’t see all of this symbolism 🥺#pedogate #wethepeopleareawake #TheGreatAwakening… https://t.co/LSpRVHNHYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_S_P_O_O_K_Y @lidp23 @RobertMosesIII @TheRickWilson @RadioFreeTom @DNC What's with it with the whole beta male thing? Are you a fish?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far we will be in the house for 4 of the 6 going to the combine!! Allana is excited to see her @UMichFootball pl… https://t.co/0BDZgwnKZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hi_meh423 😂😂😂 if i owned one!! I still need to apply for one tho! This was all from investing the loan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AggieKKL @ran_lowry Karen are you obsessed with bashing Florida State and Willie Taggart?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul you really need to decide to protect Americans, to end the human trafficking, the drugs flooding our bord… https://t.co/jPjmVdRnWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews No. The biggest scandal will be your Presidency - how you sold weapons to Iran and collud… https://t.co/DLM3h5RHWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soul_of_Nowhere Knew you’d like that. 😂 I ride alone too.  You’ll need to figure out what to do with your friend...   #anahuac2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @PBAcoachcolon !!!  So happy that you found “your person”🥰. Now let’s play some baseball ⚾️!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siempre quise a alguien que se preocupara por mi, me preguntara por mi día, siempre quisiera verme y lo más importa… https://t.co/42GfEQKvcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call Congress about The Border and Presidential Harrassment  202-224-3121  Retweet everywhere #MAGA 2,000 Migrants… https://t.co/3LXTNjK7nJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson  That Nichols think 16 year-olds are capable of making an informed vote is laughable Looking back I… https://t.co/KSw5PgHFdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaPutrelli @acidoviejo @adribilu Necesita insultar para sentirse mejor?  “Los insultos , al igual que los regalos… https://t.co/b1RekYq6I5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elliieejo @Yak2102 @johnkriesel I am beyond bummed you’re not going 😩 what am i going to do without you?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a side note, is scapegoat ever a verb? Can something be scapegoated, or have I just committed a serious crime ag… https://t.co/MkrzpFFADk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hola 👋🏼  . Te invito a que vayas a nuestras historias destacadas!💁🏻‍♀️ @vanessavlsqz  . Encontrarás nuestras public… https://t.co/53tpTHlAqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I washed my car, did laundry, got a full tank of gas and went to church today, I feel like a have my life together for once 💁🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I feel more strongly about this than anything else in coaching:  Anybody who lacks discipline, who doesn’t want to… https://t.co/f0UBmsxkjX]]></document></documents></author>