<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Dripping in Sauce all day long at wingsonwheat 💦💦💦 come through and create your flavor today!!! If you want them dr… https://t.co/91HVB2vBfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darkvictoryy How many times can u name-drop Brando challenge like holy fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why @AlanDersh? Afraid some people will be implicated that you don't want the pubic to know about? How about keepin… https://t.co/BGxVsmS3op]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @Trumplar FBI STOP THIS COSTLY BULLSHIT OPEN YOUR EYES AND SEE WHAT YOUR DOING TO THE USA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slytheringa @_love_juice @Wethejips so what is your ranking now??  1. josh 2. pi? 3. jin??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Where did this #Wind🌬️ come from in #LaLaLand🌴 Today?!😮 #Video: #JamminJo 2019🎥 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/n5NpkLzLWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jshanny14 Duane wouldn’t let me interrupt the broadcast and say hi! Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a big ball of baby Peach 🐱🍑 #peachball #Peaches #babypeach #cutie #cats #kitty #furball #thecutest… https://t.co/cLPNtzqN1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PROUDXTIANMAGA @RealMrAleem @HanyuuHiiragi @brotaku2122 @Quartzking20 @FCKthisNoyz @SabrinaResister @Kris_Z_Massey… https://t.co/wTuw982pdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiding my Sleep Deprivation well • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • #teamnosleep #whatissleep #sleepdeprived… https://t.co/PzPEPmreS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can only hope that this is another strong nail in his coffin. This man cannot continue to destroy the integrity… https://t.co/osdK7dUodT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you rather have super loud farts that don’t smell, or super smelly farts that are silent? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Durham Councilman Mark-Anthony Middleton was the first to publicly suggest eminent domain. He told me today it’s a… https://t.co/d2qgEE8DWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day Part 2.  #InternationalWomensDay #BadassChicks #WeRuleTheWorld… https://t.co/qorR49fZ96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trenaway11 @MrBrownBison @Yakekoge @phxtobama16 @eye2winner @Lonestarmomcom @FactCheckU @WalterLapp @lisalbarjas1… https://t.co/vXCAY1WRIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[{  i g n o r a n c e  i s  b l i s s  } . . While I am currently on a leave of absence from my day job, it seems I… https://t.co/znAJ9c1t5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avenatti is going to be next Lawyer for Jussie Smollet? #JussieSmollett #JussieSmollettHoax #MAGA https://t.co/RW3fbYQSo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slphouston @fred_guttenberg @gehrig38 You said shooters “pick” gun free zones. The study I posted demonstrated tha… https://t.co/B4pe1J2kl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or did people in the 90s announce their romances by starting, perhaps spontaneously, to wear the same… https://t.co/kUmKX3jjgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaMaria_pasch @AnaMaria_pasch 🙏 namaste my dear Amiga☕️💫🌻🙏☀️❄️buen dia]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s not very “progressive”, but I would hate to be Bradley Cooper’s girlfriend. I don’t think there is a wo… https://t.co/F5Jcrx8wHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This may sound fruity, but you’re a fineapple 🍍💕 #photocredstoJanice @ The Menger Hotel - San Antonio https://t.co/Zg2nEbM3aC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really do not feel like driving to Toombs county Georgia this weeked🙄🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameOfThrones #TyrionLannister #forthethrone #endcersei https://t.co/GYig9Wb2uX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s nearly a year since my NYC visit and I’ve been meaning to make this since I went!! It’s my favourite building… https://t.co/shduV0d5gM]]></document><document><![CDATA[How often do you crave something healthy and reach for the takeout menu, believing that only a chef can make “healt… https://t.co/YRR6WsbqZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Cohen Closing Statement was a bullet straight into the DEM party heart. It was OBVIOUSLY written by someone in… https://t.co/5TluKuurL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaceyMusgraves @RedRocksCO @paramountdenver Thank you for a terrific show! Enjoy the fresh ❄️❄️!]]></document><document><![CDATA[me watching the women tell all last night #TheBachelor #WomenTellAll https://t.co/YG5uVA4aki]]></document><document><![CDATA[you ever just get so excited to lie down in bed and crack your back and then immediately fall asleep? that’s the shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dan Rather served up a tasty retort to Donald Trump's national emergency. https://t.co/4LnoAWL61u # via @HuffPost]]></document><document><![CDATA[it's official, I'm a dork. just downloaded @cspan app https://t.co/e1b0SbsQf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmie_cowie @FisherP22 @MikeCrawshaw4 @westcottpiemont @RedSoil23 @tgminish @darty_sp I’d throw a dinner party for y’all any damn day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so Blessed to be Beloved Creations of The Lord God Father of All. Amen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feds say Salton Sea won't be adversely impacted by multi-state drought plan; IID can join when it chooses… https://t.co/yLsUibt66e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Amen!!  I totally agree. They’re getting in everyday by the hundreds. You multiply this by the las… https://t.co/EigH5esINc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelsclair @Cut4 @ToddZolecki @MLB 🤷🏼‍♀️ idk, LA Dreamers? LA Tanners? LA Plastic Surgeons?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best notification I got all day @SamsClub. “...this limited edition cereal includes a sprinkle of edible glitter”. https://t.co/iuLrwG30V9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc if you like other females pictures but now ima keep looking at her like “so that’s what you like?” and then wishing i was her ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekelseyowens just thank you for putting a voice to MS. For their caretakers and just who they are. ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karikimmel @blakeshelton @KeithUrban @johnlegend @joshgroban @ShawnMendes Great show]]></document><document><![CDATA[even though I already know how the bachelor ends I’m so pumped for tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tapjoy I’m still awaiting my reward for the @skinnymechoc   They’ve arrived already (before the reward🤷🏽‍♀️). Look… https://t.co/85PC48uMuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to meet Jimmy Fallon! 😉 @ NBC Studios Rockefeller Centre https://t.co/KW67B9Z0mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly 2 months till the wedding and my bridal shower is this weekend then in a few weeks my bachelorette getaway… https://t.co/7ZgwzLFQd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ant_kneee A4 we usually have gummies, granola type bars &amp; plenty of water. #ParkChat #FoodTravelChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[In love with this feminine pixie by Amber #ambermichellesalon #pixiecut #shorthair #haircut #dallassalon… https://t.co/lCuNL26Ho0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Needed a run this afternoon #foggy #rainy #evanston was the right choice.  #weekendviews @ Evanston Lake Front https://t.co/uK7nXzpgpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happened to Instagram I feel like my feed is 85% fake people and 15% “real” people]]></document><document><![CDATA[So naturally I listened to the @jonasbrothers the entire way to class and I realized they were ahead of their time.… https://t.co/Wib8uhmC3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spread the word...Delta Sigma Theta Sorority, Inc. sponsors “Books and Bears” every 3rd Saturday.  Ages 2-10. BC-U… https://t.co/gKmkrTsPD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seankeane Brills. And who better to determine if a pitcher is tiring out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctcasl @aasl @cte_ct @ctreading64 @ncte @MrSchuReads @Scholastic @pennykittle @livluvlibrary @SLC_Online… https://t.co/YGNSW6LvFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stockman214 @AlissaBjerkhoel Lol, yes I know....I was following the saga but then you left me hanging!  Glad to he… https://t.co/4jIWUJF6iZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamECastillo @palomac02 SAMMY: THE FUNNY ONE!!! Hahahahahahahaahahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiiixfish I am always in awe of people’s commitment to finding photos of their friends deep within their camera ro… https://t.co/r0iJQbF1Mm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GymskinCoach @AHSRedskins_AD @AndersonRedskin @anderson_SALT Thanks, coach!! ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please excuse me while I clear my schedule due to the @jonasbrothers reunion. https://t.co/6IwpuibX9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a trying day. Glad tomorrow is Sunday. Church family, worship, Word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blkgrlpoet This is only the beginning, greatness for your hard work and endurance. ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what's the point of privacy if you're going to act this way PUBLICLY and post it all anyways AS A CHILD. I get i… https://t.co/qshmuJhIRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the Derby preps today, I like The Right Path on top in the Tampa Bay Derby, I like Haikal in the Gotham, and whi… https://t.co/RANWgMyUzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stingrays Cobalt is such a fun team to watch! The performance and technique JUMPED OUT this weekend, can’t wait to watch them at Worlds💠]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do some spring cleaning for the people/things in your life. Are your friends toxic? Does that extracurricular make… https://t.co/naCxbtJfVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any minute is the best minute if it's a chance to slay I love being one step one call away  I S L A Y L A  #fashion… https://t.co/N0AhCokCxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[From #Chicago to #Ferguson it’s been a Movement. Been on the ground. I too, was a front liner. Now I am an… https://t.co/xoMVPQ36F3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rabbitranbitrabbit #happyMarch1st i hope today brings the beginning of great and exciting things this month for al… https://t.co/7L9BykGNFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[From hiding my true gender identity and wearing women’s clothes underneath my men’s suits so no one could see I can… https://t.co/MPfr24huED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScribeUndead I mean she bothe was being raped, AND she witnessed her dad kill her assailant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josueeguzman I knowww I remember I would save my money and not go to mama ko just to get one lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Harold. So appreciate your work. @HaroldSinnott also appreciate @Onalytica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyDoyle47 @LindseyW1978 @MrsWallace1978 @StrodeMorgan Can you subscribe to my YouTube channel https://t.co/AOcy0zOUSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wolv54b1 @bodyfit67 @cellmavin @excitedtofeast @afrobeerchick @HermannTLombard @bertrand_boily @CasaskullMark… https://t.co/qMMBDVUmp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaSchwartzzz I bought this book just so you could call me a slytherin (the best book marketing tactic)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rynchantress @HashiCorp Congrats! And yay, you now get to work with my beloved former colleague @paddycarver plus… https://t.co/rQA444zWav]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lgreen66 Will do! Congrats on this one (and Versailles too)! And congrats on having an awesome family too. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[White collar criminals usually get hooked up.... WE should take a close look at the "JUDGES" that are responsible f… https://t.co/qSdhjZiW82]]></document><document><![CDATA[I worry about my friends, I don’t want them to be upset about anything. I wish I could be someone who gives everyon… https://t.co/CsQkJ7eg9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Garciaparasoco @IDEAschools PLEASE check your facts. Appreciate your opinions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Levons notre pouce ensemble et soyons Expositifs, ExposNation, Les Chums du Groupe des Expos! Fierté /  Québécois B… https://t.co/2cbfUNhmzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsJelissa18 @Degu0818 @charliekirk11 I live in California and I worked for Riverside County.  They have received… https://t.co/Wp7nQS5YN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a similar conversation with my son except he was asking about thermite. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[such amazing service at the managers reception last night. the manager went out of his way for us. yummy made to or… https://t.co/igk8prn55I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still cannot watch that last scene in the blair witch project and it takes a lot for something horror to shake me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ainsleyearhardt Just a note you looked extra great in this dress today. At 66 I think I might wear more dresses;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@farcreading "When what we read stirs our hearts and minds...not to make a character puppet...We must slay these in… https://t.co/qNG2UcH6eb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The End....of my day off! Time for bed! @ United Skates Tampa https://t.co/4esEIpsRHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 17th anniversary to my amazing husband. I'm so glad I married my best friend. ❤️💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davelucas @WTEN @MaryWilsonNews Don’t worry you’ll still catch me on social media forecasting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good nor bad Chinese food that smells eggactly as it did entering and leaving this living cosmos within my belly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gay lunch! (@ Kona Café in Lake Buena Vista, FL) https://t.co/GwJML33uAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that racing season is starting,  I sure do miss my buddy @txnanna4jg24 Not a day goes by that I don't think of her. ❤🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rip 🙏🏾 #jesterangel 👼#stjosephhighschoollakewoodca #missingyousheila 💙 @ All Souls Cemetery and Mortuary https://t.co/14aUveyasN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS This is what Hillary Clinton and Obama did to Libya, Obama wasn't in office for 10 days when he ordered the… https://t.co/F5ClDgjs1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cindyingram000 @Glist77 @balleralert Omg 😂😂 What am I gullible about? Literally said nothing. But if you’re asking… https://t.co/HDJh4Z24gy]]></document><document><![CDATA[other government-stacked institutions such as the supreme court to have no legal authority.  While Russia, China, T… https://t.co/yZexkxRMiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I’m saying is I now have a ticket to @divarobbie’s March 1st show @54Below, so.. 💅🏻👑🎼🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACog1984 You to. We get 2 inches and my my Sisler got 3to 4 inches stay warm have a great dat]]></document><document><![CDATA[It truly amazes me how many people you go through in life.....like dang....where’d those people go?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great! I actually dvr Shepherd Smith so I can watch it and gain a little hope. I like his show, can't watch… https://t.co/ka060R1X6B]]></document></documents></author>