<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@emailtimw @sturdyAlex @Rykalski @RemainResistant A larger Tory majority could theoretically make ERG irrelevant an… https://t.co/MXCnCgUIan]]></document><document><![CDATA[All children are “our own children”. A quality public education system spreads opportunity and makes us stronger as… https://t.co/tbhK8Ru8gM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The Gang Will Be There” 🗿🌴💀#ZombieVillage #Bartenders #Tiki @comstocksaloon @ Comstock Saloon https://t.co/H0sZ0xNskS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aryanna at Full Sail Behind the Scene #fullsailbts https://t.co/WzDT97UFgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I’m bummed out I talk shit on others in the form of comedy or humor. When I’m happy I champion anyone and thei… https://t.co/p5h0jrSlRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[We turned the Lou out for Mardi Gras😄 🎉🎊 @ St. Louis https://t.co/kpOSBDLcLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceschi - and always puts me at a show (mentally) where you’re putting everything you got into it. And even at a mo… https://t.co/mXoK2sO8cw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning was awesome had Juan  (new bank manager) who is hotter than hell here to sign paperwork finally got to… https://t.co/RCeCFu4zSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill @cthagod is correct. The 3rd Batman was garbage so you have to compare 2v2 and Cap was superior.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn, I don’t remember the HBC limping like that getting out of the golf cart on the practice field at Williams Brice #thisthatandtheother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two 2nd Place finishes for sarah.zyskowski ‘s elkriverjfk squads today!! #justforkix @ Together We Dance Just for K… https://t.co/hOLe8aL5rG]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEVER understood people who comment on podcasts but this is next level https://t.co/jZjYSqX7mT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Professional Coding Auditor - https://t.co/PPKPTcMZUl #hospitaljobs #Accounting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quidsragesage Not a bad suggestion. He is a local. But his gel tips would present a challenge to even the best sculpture artist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark fucked that shit up. Yesss MR. LEE! A man Oof. Y’all need to really stfu tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@santiago4kd Ajajajajaja ocupan que vaya la gente a apoyar no los trapos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you post a snap story of a baby, you will be unfollowed immediately, don’t need any of that negative energy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still goin in the rain! @CareForKids @ Riverview Elementary https://t.co/XXRZhr7dsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I got $5 on "your honor, the real killer is right here in this courtroom! "]]></document><document><![CDATA[@franwellerwect snowing again here. Ground truth roads ok. Temps near 33°. @ Town of Chadbourn https://t.co/QTb95swoc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[PASTORAL THOUGHT  As a man pains for hunger, he should pain for the fullness of the Holy Spirit  (Matt 5:6)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I WILL WRITS THIS WHY S.LEE DIDN`T WIN BEST PICTURE=THE IMAGINATION A BLACK KKK\WHAT GREAT ABOUT THE REVERSE OF WHI… https://t.co/TYzAeVtFHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[1920's "Mack the Engine Man" good luck charm #fob from Mack engine boring and parts Newark nj #anthromorphic advert… https://t.co/hvT9HiHMlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanetodd I live in Boston, are you taking like bars? there is a lot of bigger Irish bars that could host a show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaintTouches So sad for you and your wife, nothing I can say will make it better and for that I feel terrible 😢 Yo… https://t.co/3KfCdtovpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Eubank applies greater pressure I think he could stop DeGale. As it stands DeGale has a lot of work ahead of him… https://t.co/YR2NxHM5z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianVLuc Legitimate question: Do you feel better or worse after you put them in their place? Haha I always fe… https://t.co/ZTqgWcoGKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a busy day.  Morning nap. Afternoon siesta, followed by a little nap, then some deep sleep time.  I’m exhaus… https://t.co/ZmIaYh3sDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE THAT DUDE!!!! @rjosi90 CAPTAIN MY CAPTAIN!!! LETS GO PREDS!!! @BrdgstoneArena loud now!!! @PredsNHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MajidaIssa @ImagenTVMex @LaGuzmanTV @FochaRios Escuchando a #laguzman en #Spotify la primer rola fue Reina de Cora… https://t.co/SqMnVVCBtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wahotaho MAGAts are up in arms (tiki torches)  over the truth and rRump being aped to keep the people laughing..… https://t.co/kEHaDWyBCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff And you spent 10 hours with a witness before he testifies?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is awesome, Congrats to @MrJacobEspi and Salem @btb503 - impressive!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dana Brooke interrupts Ronda Rousey's bitter tirade: Raw, March 11, 2019 https://t.co/awutttJ2Qo via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back home... aaahhh!🇺🇸 (@ U.S. Border Crossing in Calais, ME w/ @lorettahall13) https://t.co/htyeRS50xL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MNMUSOXFAN @BIGEASTMBB If Howard got the same whistle Shamorie Ponds does, he would average 30 ppg.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommyland9 Sessions was a small sample size, but at least he was capable of penetrating a defense and gave us a sp… https://t.co/HfBt5JpRRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tu vida puede ser la única Biblia que los demás lean. Actúa bien, da testimonio.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Baseless? LOL, Matt, how many guilty pleas? How many indictments? You're an idiot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thephotoist Sad thing it's not satire. Which is sad, look what we are up against. Stupidity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With pediatric cancer survival rates in the USA &gt; 85% and rates in some LMICs as low as 10%, this points to how… https://t.co/bniUtVOMYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration non-citizens should not be permitted to buy weapons, nor any privileges guaranteed by the Constitution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top of the morning let’s make it count!!!! @ New York, New York https://t.co/cuGx4x4bMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My latest for @CharlotteParent on how we designed a cool playroom for our kids. https://t.co/ux5J8Fr9Us #parenting #parentingtips #DIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noticias24 Estamos a punto de salir d régimen d malandros más ladrones; asesinos d la peor calaña que gobernó a Vz… https://t.co/6MiMLh66cl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always lifting each other up lol. Great work Team!   #RMNU #BJJ #bjj4life #jiujitsu #Jitsu #mestrong #martialarts… https://t.co/0GmL0LNjDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Online Discussion Tools to Fuel Student Engagement https://t.co/lSzoN7KG7V via @CommonSenseEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craigwchoate SIU fans hoping Bryan Mullens is the next Darin DeVris.  We will see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the best time taking my son to his first @hornets game!  We are @greensboroswarm season ticket holders and he w… https://t.co/UDdz5t3KPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We treat social media platforms as public spaces where we own our content, but nothing could be further from the tr… https://t.co/4hUY3gZ4HI]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Ethiopian Airlines Boeing 737-800MAX heading to the Kenyan capital Nairobi has crashed near Addis Ababa with 157… https://t.co/6OnS3wR4ND]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the dude on the left wearing a “don’t tread on me shirt” when someone tread all over his foot? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Seems to me that the Democrats and liberals don't really care about anybody's lives but their owne… https://t.co/gIHrUaUj1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Downtown Walnut Creek in Walnut Creek, CA https://t.co/0AJJlYjuY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 I wish they do and give the example to show how bad it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAIT UP! @mcweekly’s Squid🦑 has to do a little better legislative reading. My bill #AB2016 of 2016 did not create a… https://t.co/xOVPXH3F6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Renzo Ruckkng it up on a Saturday afternoon.  Go SC Red Hawks!! https://t.co/gkaaVjLuLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ so understand I’m the over analyzing type, panoramic views while I’m planning out my life”]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the test is to see the activity, because the engagement on this tweet says 28 and 272 impressions, yet I only ha… https://t.co/CP0MazKmeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Manuel12716975 @jmolaizola Además los Jesuitas no tienen rama femenina. A este “religioso en via de extinción” no… https://t.co/QAX0LzGRzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that food you're cooking for me? #dogsofinstagram #doglife #dogdad @ Southeast Raleigh, Raleigh, North Carolina https://t.co/myfZKrrrQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet P.S. 3 1/2 stars isn’t that great. Respectfully, hit up Yelp/Urbanspoon/Zomato. They’re great tools t… https://t.co/Fn01HRSB7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cecil_joyce @EaglevilleB @EAGLadyBBall @DavyMcClaran @TomBeckwith_ No changes as of now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Francis Awerkamp carrying HB2126 relating to electric scooters. #ksleg https://t.co/hYddacJo2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ga_twin1 Mam's birthday is Sunday, her mother was Welsh and her dad was English. She thinks a win is her birthday… https://t.co/pRdWPtIHeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inRICHweTRUST @_Juice13_ Of course . Half these players wouldn’t be on here 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SBucci If you watch the video from the other angles bad guy 1 has his hand in his coat a few steps before the draw… https://t.co/GkcvnfTbkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[After seeing Quinnen Williams af the combine it puts into perspective just how good that #Clemson offensive line wa… https://t.co/OmDMGg4dYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJayapal Medicare is legal tender to create all debts public And private...with no premiums or fair premiums to keep out of hoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE CRIMINAL STATE IS NOT PROTECTED BY AMERICAN STANDARD LAWS AND CONSTITUTION. YEP CORRECT.  SOME OF MY FRIENDS OF… https://t.co/ZuNLh16A4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLostOgle Your complaint is seriously that they're using expensive cuts of meat. How could they survive being in… https://t.co/AFQthOKNdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[21 Savage, Offset, Metro Boomin - Ric Flair Drip (Official Music Video) https://t.co/XtnEtx5fyS via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks you @Jasonih @SocialStudiesSS for coming to GISD today to provide training for #ActiveClassroom today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradley. Just because i loved the movie and his acting in it. Malik was a amazing too though. Shit. I like music.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thank you @realDonaldTrump MY PRESIDENT, for working so hard, for this now very proud #American!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kneed a 6 year old child in the face at work tonight and his mother said “he’s fine, it was his fault.” And it made my day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisaJC Also, sugar cane fields are in the south lots of “cocolos” immigrated there during the 1800’s to work on the fields.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Luck to Big Walnut Wrestlers Ryan @Coletta_7, Max Lenz, and Josh Halbakken (Alternate) tonight 3/1 at Darby HS… https://t.co/XCzDCOhSE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile #TMobileTuesdays #contest  hey guys me and my pup Tika have had our 👀on the S10 since the rumors!! Hope we… https://t.co/aYHyR1922U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was great catching up with my boy @CoachCLewis87 tonight! One of the best 🏈 coaches from SC now doing big things in… https://t.co/kZ9kOQy5Ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tom_Schad @ByKevinAllen @usatodaysports Would basically kill division rivalries]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys voting MLB are the dudes that go 2-4 in a beer league softball game and automatically think they can hit a 95… https://t.co/GRgaI9SQ60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who just learned that “astigmatism” is one word? I always thought “a” was describing the word “st… https://t.co/fJIaQrBzro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rick_scinta @Tesla @PolestarCars 2021 is sooo far away. Everyone is just so far behind. We need mass adoption and options now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lookin’ fair in Jackson Square @ Jackson Square https://t.co/kEfFyGSnao]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nshs_baseball spring break schedule.  District play begins!!! https://t.co/V3nfVzB5cL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I was born in a small town And I live in a small town Probably die in a small town Oh, those small communities… https://t.co/PUP8Axy5PO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Saint Peter's University - @stpeterscollege in Jersey City, NJ https://t.co/IJAYprlkXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Physics explained. Via Bilbo's Random Thoughts. https://t.co/lS6Iucp3u4 https://t.co/TQv9Zbc8Wd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 2nd of a 2 part post on my misadventures in #kerning is up on the blog! How to kern in @FontLab VI, some standa… https://t.co/CetkDqVfTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have really missed that’s a fact, although if life or God puts you in my path one more time, nothing would be the… https://t.co/91FtramE6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Olivia Coleman or Melissa McCarthy deserved that award. Great job Academy. #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimCanto @tedbauer2003 @nplusg @AnOrchidInBloom @TPorter2 @joshmccormack @ScottOntiveroz @katyb_spencer… https://t.co/FWQOCoituS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m gonna write for a while! No one will know... but any ideas where I could post stories? I had to close down my blog.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the best Birthday/Valentines day with my girl today thank you so much @karissakusy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephanie Mansolf #hotelsmotels Group hotel room exhibit with Sarah Tell sarah_tell, Anna Feil @annafeil, and Steph… https://t.co/zIR5hNHr7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stassi , I’ve been watching this show from the beginning, this is the best I’ve ever seen your breasts , take that… https://t.co/VKnWaSDW6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @Auburngirlx @realDonaldTrump welcome to my world. It’s not just Facebook. As usual, you’re barely scratching the surface.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I FEEL YOU! 1 day I looked up and I was in Australia bro! Like, this lil brown boy from St. Louis found himself in… https://t.co/k3kM8UAkST]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Jr․ warns students against 'loser teachers ... trying to sell you on socialism from birth… https://t.co/VDsJ0W6oW1]]></document></documents></author>