<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @realDonaldTrump Someone give this kid a lecture on economics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i finally put all my christmas presents away today btw. right on schedule. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHERE IS HOMER??? The OA: Part II | Official Trailer [HD] | Netflix https://t.co/NJOtxgUV7N via @YouTube @The_OA #emorycohen #whereishomer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom Why is it that younger people who believe they hold the moral high ground when it comes to climate ch… https://t.co/5ksAi11PMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dumbrobin Four straws! We have to be better. Get reusable straws. Ask for no straw. We need to reduce the amount o… https://t.co/nKsT57KS2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind I wonder if the US drafted the "beautiful 5 page recommendation" for Japan to submit to Nobel committee. This guy has no shame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yumm Bowls make me so darn happy. Love me some @CafeYumm sauce. #VeganLife #VeganFood https://t.co/mqy98kjqQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is raining big clumps of snow flakes in West Des Moines 🥶 Good thing is, so far they are mostly melting on conta… https://t.co/RZRnbYlwgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone stab the nerves around my eyes with acupuncture needles Feeling a bit like a masochist today]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m convinced that every bad, depraved person in the world has a connection to trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[meu deus eu odeio carpete e toda casa em las vegas tem carpete.... ODEIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[*at Macy’s* yo: ¿cuándo era niña me comprabas ropa de aquí? ma: “sí, hasta te dejaba escogerla” yo: en serio😲 ¿y qu… https://t.co/gXtHQ8T1wa]]></document><document><![CDATA[9-0: SCOTUS Delivers Devastating Decision To State Sponsored Seizure Schemes https://t.co/3lUiKj1MwH via @BigLeaguePol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm SICK of seeing news articles where moms let their musty ass boyfriends around their kids and the babies get bea… https://t.co/jrOZMZpYRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I visited the horses that’s were rescued from an icy lake in the Poconos yesterday, Watch at 6 p.m. on @wbrewyou to… https://t.co/euPeG0X0x5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wired4story I’m so sorry about your sister.  While I don’t have brain mets, the affect of depression is so much mo… https://t.co/P8QcSflpNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget! Support a woman who inspires you to be incredible TODAY! Tag her or DM us her name and phone number a… https://t.co/YzK2ThDWn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. Ruth E. Carter did an amazing job. #BlackPanther #Oscars #CostumeDesign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rach_thorpe Same so I brought a Dr Pepper the next week bc I’m petty 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My All America Girl has a busy day for us, track meet and soccer game @MilbyLadyBuffs #milbytrack https://t.co/PwrTKNZBUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @realDonaldTrump, Please, enough of your lies. https://t.co/wcZW4uH1AP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like a stealthy velociraptor... #LivePD @LivePDNation https://t.co/Z1hucJx4ud]]></document><document><![CDATA[I lied! I didn’t do it. Brushing my teeth, washing my face, lil dry shampoo and I’m sorry general public, you’re ab… https://t.co/QMiJwUYHhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jonathan_Conley @WSJA @MayorJenny @kcexec @seattletimes That is strange...I follow them as a reminder for stuff go… https://t.co/NccEnavNj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MamaPKL That's good and same here. Been a wet winter but we need the rain]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mentoring is a win-win for both the mentor and mentee! After hosting mentoring sessions, I always leave refreshed,… https://t.co/YbXbH2TUD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArthurSchwartz @DonaldJTrumpJr @brianstelter @CNN Smollett wanted the  two chocolaty Nigerians and they were not i… https://t.co/awCIYEatR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeenVogue Just making sure the bitch on the cover wasn't Olivia. That's not afro textured hair. Phew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annslisek @THR Didn’t I mention the script being flipped idiot?  Open up your brain and understand what I’m saying.  You’re closed minded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Given who the most (in)famous Amy is right now, I am definitely NOT going there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I caught some show on HGTV with a big beautiful spacious home with a huge yard that was $149k. 😳 Liiiiiike, that’s… https://t.co/A5d8OkwKYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never buy a pickle from a gas station regardless of how enticing the name may be. No thanks Big Papa 😤 https://t.co/BFZixljoBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sushimademedoit Oooop, I don’t think she puts onions in the Chile though 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone this week has asked me if i was sick when i really just haven’t slept in a month. well guess what! now i’m sick. are y’all happy! 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very happy to see the Veterans Villages of America secure a location through this legislation. This facility will h… https://t.co/IbxYnR9I25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angjo_ @erwalio pena que o terror vai se virar contra vc. Deus me livre, fora pt, fora Bolsonaro. viva o trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bravo y adelante!  Women work very hard in agriculture &amp; deserve attention for their efforts. #WomenInAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback to when I was in an airport in Turks and Caicos and Chris was having brunch with my parents in Murfreesbo… https://t.co/4sr9XMCvd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got some puppy kisses today. Nothing’s going to top that, so I declare Valentine’s Day OVER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndigoMinx Naw. After i get out of the marriage that im in, i dont want another one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris @CantrellCarol Wrong Kamala. You're not even intelligent enough to understand how beneficial the new… https://t.co/AfTgYW1Bhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FranklinFoer But he's led a "blameless" life.  What planet is Judge Ellis on????????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to buy two tickets for Tuesday March 5th for 7-8pm for $50 lmk please!!! 😊 https://t.co/QarETYpUVM https://t.co/u43pzEPRq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[W @realDonaldTrump poised to sign the spending bill, @senatemajldr hails #Kentucky priorities in the package, inc.… https://t.co/KOfgtiWP0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Representing @katlofficial on our way to see @wtofficial for the final show of our crazy road trip! #resisttour2019… https://t.co/9oz1bck7sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CCRJSamson @DouglasConley13 @NumbersUSA @RoyBeck_NUSA The refs r very clear about H2b visa overstays.  Employers p… https://t.co/AB3Al1VLdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkBullockNFL I’m with you. More likely either speculation or the Cardinals are looking to move out of the top spot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBTA_CR Thanks. I understand, but “stand by until further notice” isn’t the best plan for folks trying to make mee… https://t.co/QGRCaB6OOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewVic @mariannamaravi8 @BurgessOwens But it's the truth,  so it should get in our heads.  Just wish it would get in dems head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look mom...I’m a cover girl! 😂 thanks to Catholic Digest for the awesome interview! Photo by @abiroad95 @ Nashville… https://t.co/sSNDSMpQv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorJLH Ooooh, sub chocolate with cheese and I'm ready for a food based reward system!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning air travel on a weekend is a special kind of torture no matter how good the reason for doing it #ihatehumanity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to all the boys who were drafted last night. So excited for Chase to be part of his new team with the… https://t.co/c0j8SKQpxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth! Also add: work Advil especially if you work at @CHP_Can #iselfcare https://t.co/Xh45LUEmpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flipping through Satellite Radio, and had the urge for Mary J Blige. Next button I pressed, there she was. So weird… https://t.co/nkU9m86zOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@njassemblydems @LouGreenwald @GovMurphy Punish law abiding, 2nd Amendment citizens and reward the illegal, gun car… https://t.co/F1BDrxGkjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reaction to the idea of getting a bath! #pitbull https://t.co/2J6h9sTkD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @KimStrassel Well Pinocchio you are a lazy and corrupt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren @WhiteHouse ENDING CORRUPTION SHOULD START WITH YOU !!!!!!   LYING IS A VIOATION OF YOUR OATH OF OFFICE,… https://t.co/Hm5oMEjKI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one that misses sleeping next to their boyfriend? Like I get to about 1-2 times a week and I wish it… https://t.co/OHSerZGIvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbyJohnson If your testimony does not change hearts and minds I am not sure any thing will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJJackMillz @TheBoltUpright @SchettiniErnest @amber_athey @ChatByCC @POTUS @realDonaldTrump 🤣🤣🤣☀️ are you REALLY that gullible?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hagelin working hard in the neutral zone on the PK! Much needed! #ALLCAPS 🏒 #CapsSabres]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrated our 4th Valentine’s Day together, holy guacamole 🥑💛 https://t.co/bLX1Q2XJUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum @TuckerCarlson @JennyCraig @SamsungUS @Bayer @JennyCraig, @SamsungUS @Bayer if your corps are good with… https://t.co/J3FdIPsumD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curly Fringe is EVERYTHING 🤩💇🏻‍♀️ . .  #chambleega #masterstylist #atlhairstylist #chamblee #getoutofyourownway… https://t.co/5GwGFjR33F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello adding to my LGBTQ+ chat! 18+ iMessage only Be kind Like/RT/dm your number to be added :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime So are you saying your afraid to find the truth - so you won't cooperate? Or if all the allegations… https://t.co/O9H9cwgn9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my differential's course, everyone did so badly on the first exam that the professor asked the class to  "self-reflect" for five minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York to open tallest outdoor observation deck in Western Hemisphere https://t.co/1lnzhUQkK4 via @CNNTravel]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna take my life seriously and finally book a one on one makeup class to improve my skills.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like the #Kardashians waste so many flowers. Where do all those huge arrangements go??? I swear they have so… https://t.co/pC4uO6TvHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know #lauradern sure did bring her readers, chile #oscars2019 @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/2YqlF1FdOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[He will get used to it anyway, since he’s there for the long-haul. #13Years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ummm excuse me Avery I think it’s time to sleep. So you might want to slow down the movements 🙄.… https://t.co/4J5U2kjzxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kd_rose4 @Delecioso @abbeyjohnsonn Omg I’m crying &amp; also have ptsd rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoziinaiEsther @nenyloks @MsAshleyDevonna “What’s the problem?” Umm be with a man for years, get pregnant with y’a… https://t.co/JEsAxNeuJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melania’s in the shop, so they gave Trump a rental. https://t.co/NWyN4BonqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌲Con Sue Photography and Design🌲  ♥️On-Location.... March 9-14, 2019♥️  🌲Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌲  ♥️This… https://t.co/6CN9fhOQlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @NewDay Alisyn Camerota knows that most ppl find Andy McCabe 100% Credible. We know how Corrupt &amp; Ruthless… https://t.co/lWWXie5COF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidkelly92 @MeghanMcCain Meghan is a Nasty Condescending Right Wing Partisan Bitch who Never Knows What She is T… https://t.co/oX8dpBWPmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brodie_XVX Focus on scapular retraction, tighten up your muscles esp hams and lats. Pumping hams and pretending yo… https://t.co/c7tfjLgH2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me tomorrow 😩 even though my ass is up studying for it I better get a decent grade man 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have y’all ever had a dream so realistic when you woke up you was mad 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defend. Hydrate. Boost. NEW Prisma Protect is our newest product crush! Hits shelves soon. 🌈 #yourbestskinever… https://t.co/edEDYvAshG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to my favorite @dunkindonuts for making my coffee on point 🥳🥰 https://t.co/tYY2Ic9AsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get jealous because he chose me over you! I get mad because it’s so hard for you to see that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckayla_may @ayaabdelhayx excuse me at least i have my damn license @mckayla_may]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm hungry. Anyone want to bring a hot dog or some popcorn up to the press box? Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimpGail @KensingtonRoyal @EFAMorocco I’m certain thePrince can do without your hate-based love.  Many women are e… https://t.co/VQUkWnZB6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[A week from right now I will be on my way to see @DanAndShay! I don’t think I’ve ever been so excited! 😁 #DanandShayTheTour]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once in awhile it’s just SO FUN to play with your team. Great fun morning on the pitch! 🦉🏑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NavadeEghtesadi خوب مصادره اش کنید چرا خراب می کنید. کلی پول هزینه شده.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudreyNixx Lol I never noticed until now. Lol I seen Detroit then I looked at the pics and I was like 👀 I know this mf 🙃😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are you doing at your institution to address #Burnout? Share here and we can share live with the speakers!… https://t.co/1uCwDfjJbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Denying our POTUS the ability to do what we elected him to do is a crime. The supreme court needs… https://t.co/001Ngukzwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basically me this entire week outside testing locations pumping my 8th graders up for their SOLs.   Take breaks, st… https://t.co/XjaYvS8EHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will I ever have enough courage to give the cute guy in my math class my number? Stay tuned🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Featuring for #halsparks this weekend arlington_drafthouse Saturday 7&amp;9:30pm #virginia #laughter #standupcomedy… https://t.co/rj9rK5ybPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shorts yesterday and cold weather gear today- gotta ❤️ Texas Weather! @ Brenham Sports Complex https://t.co/4CJbDfW1d5]]></document></documents></author>