<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Education4Libs @realDonaldTrump demoRATs worried about illegals when detined by ICE, they wrte laws tht allw this… https://t.co/yQnFSNwu5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or do a lot of these artist that be going viral on Twitter be Nigerian?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillWineBanks @kendisgibson Always a thrill to be on with the great @JillWineBanks and @kendisgibson!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toxic masculinity. Gotta love dating apps. 🙄 #embraceyouridentity #singlelife https://t.co/yRd1vn4HD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ocean State • jponcemedia @ Narragansett, Rhode Island https://t.co/HqD7Edl8Qd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live feed on Facebook of @AllBlacks808 in semifinals of @PylonEliteCamps Vegas #Pylon7v7 https://t.co/Mx1OikP8bG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristophDollis @KenDBerryMD @MikhailaAleksis @SBakerMD Add to that to the fact in the last 24 hours @SBakerMD was… https://t.co/33q68IVZM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has been worse hotel ever stayed at. Like is level of soundproofing even legal 🙈🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister He's turning ICE into his own STASI. They'll be the ones he sends out in the night, to eliminate or… https://t.co/7D4y0I2LvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OscurrV @BleacherReport Especially playing football where your body is using a ton of energy. He'd get sick collapse/pass out often.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mulvanyc is a master of car meetings. The best way to get from A-B while talking shop and sharing music. Great cat… https://t.co/oYEMDi6s4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Twitter app needs to quit playing with my feelings. Telling me I have notifications when I know damn right I don’t haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember who’s ass you’re starting a fire under. You don’t want this heat, I can promise you that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at It's a Small World - @disneyland in Anaheim, CA https://t.co/sDbWkgFavP]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least @jenhenddsand I are back in #FirstClass again even after the last minute @Delta flight changes! #HernandezCanada2019 🇺🇸✈️🇨🇦]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are y'all still doing up? It's Sunday. You have to go to work tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McClure_SF I just use a bent paper clip, two seconds and no human interaction👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hblodget It is also a continuation of the polarization of American politics.  How can correct thinking politicians… https://t.co/HDKW1HfRu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayraJackiee @drillingninja @BatallonEb @SeanRingrose I'd like to thank God for this opportunity because without h… https://t.co/HkDyGNYpNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennaMoquin @jbdarroch It also demonstrates the limited scope of that character’s imagination. Not an interesting… https://t.co/EZVuFOb63U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MA_Deuce That’s the absolute worst. The more north you go the worse it gets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kleenex/Lilliput. This stuff is great! #np #Kleenex #Liliput #Vinyl https://t.co/kUiTB6AXB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[No queda más que seguir adelante, aprender de los errores, para ser una mejor persona.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeChristakis @NASPA2 @DeanTMartinez @NASPAtweets Thank you for your service @MikeChristakis and look forward to… https://t.co/A8mLkuccac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kealasettle I have to say thank you for your amazing performance of #SeasonsOfLove in @RENTonFOX and we look forwa… https://t.co/15wJAf1Go1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hipchecker I hope so...Need to win against these teams. Hopefully @mattymarts17 comes back Thursday. They miss him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shameful, if I was in her employment and she tried that crap on me!! Very shameful of her to think she is more impo… https://t.co/AAljNtP2FV]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦷NATIONAL DENTIST’S DAY🦷  Annually observed on March 6, National Dentist’s Day was created as a day set to say “Tha… https://t.co/v8xBVq98jf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jump That Fence!!! Jump That Fence!!! Jump That Fence!!! Jump That Fence!!! #Bachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man this @amazon prime driver has been driving around our neighborhood for the last 30 minutes like such an asshole… https://t.co/j3MUcQAHHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you realize you left home without deodorant do you go back &amp; put some on? #cleanliness #hygiene https://t.co/oMoCP3jP87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @susaneCody1 Because of how Trump became president his presidency and all the  decisions he made shoul… https://t.co/3drUKvS49C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayasax Played  18 holes of golf with Alice Cooper when he got added to my two-some.   He introduced himself as “C… https://t.co/pFu53fVYV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a person of color, she doesn’t even need to answer that question. IMO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN just needs to stop bringing these lying sycophants on the air. Debate is healthy. Unhinged fucking screaming i… https://t.co/UrmLwDm9Kj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klyphnelson @mapleridgered @MCW16591775 @Dimcl2 @MeaneyJim @BonnieLCarter @plumbkeith1 @RUalreadyawake… https://t.co/U7nzMm2ZUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregDArmstrong @Frogalumni @SeanTPendergast @McClain_on_NFL It’s very simple and it’s getting old...the NFL has a… https://t.co/uWfxXAPo3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[New business idea - solving the last mile problem for scooters. Every Bird in Austin is currently out of battery #sxsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenSchweigert @RaichartRanch @FarmChicJodi @ranchingaround Maybe a bit better than yours https://t.co/CYgDjwQXDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump For supposedly being such a smart guy, you hire a LOT of really bad/stupid people 🤔 https://t.co/L76OK0sRFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[but you were just hanging with trash and i wasn’t trash then?? confusion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWENetwork I just subscribed because of @KacyCatanzaro @AlexaBliss_WWE @BeckyLynchWWE @WWE_MandyRose @SashaBanksWWE @itsBayleyWWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstiloDF @EdySmol @MurielEbright @CDLC_oficial Yo digo que 10 para @LaMurielHe, se ve espectacular. #CuidateDeLaCamara]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandalWansing @NCCNeon @s_crabtree @DLoesch Most guns manufactured from 1856 forward feature some form of semi-aut… https://t.co/gNl8rsgkW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Browns_Beard32 No. Jabril is a stud, and will be one of the better safeties in the league for the next 10 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DADMVXX Some bull shit, I was ready to have a full sleep after a long work week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jswatz An old timer and a young fellow were sitting at a bar in a small town out in west Texas when the young fell… https://t.co/fUW65ZL8j0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couples playing golf with their sweetheart for Valentines @ Lufkin, Texas https://t.co/e7G5j7Xc3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Photos from the Jacksonville, East Duplin, Northside &amp; Southwest playoff games Tuesday.   https://t.co/N1NGRrCqun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EugeneHowardCo2 @thehill You have any proof of that...? No, of course you don't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTFisherAuthor @SteveScalise No free man shall ever be debarred the use of arms. Thomas Jefferson, 1776. The Const… https://t.co/hQKWwfEoEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[New headline... "Oooopppppsss!!! @RepMaxineWaters , member of #TheKlanWithATan , automatically blames white people… https://t.co/7M3sO6y6et]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @B1GWrestling - can someone tell your producer that NOBODY cares about two unranked basketball teams when the w… https://t.co/4PKix8i8wf]]></document><document><![CDATA[definitely merry. Paul Rudd. My all time fave. Google Image Result for https://t.co/L8LZy2gSuD https://t.co/xw7sAoojPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come to the #Avaya booth and see all our new endpoints and now headsets!! #ConvergeOne #ExperiencesThatMatter https://t.co/owHtWXW0FC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodgers_randi It’s the Padres, not so much the team...it’s the city that’s cursed. No championships of any kind ever!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roma se reconcilia con Cardenal | Internacional | EL PAÍS https://t.co/qFbvEk1hAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s rare in this biz to have one generational altering show... but TWO!??  Plus ... have to add he had a great tur… https://t.co/4YK7vx4qOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craig_7T2 @GoldenBrookss @NikkF07 @vinman905 @TheHappyGreek70 @fnveenie @DarthAlexander9 @EllersDad @akita1916… https://t.co/sZdZO6Wn0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoppyinCalgary @TheophilusPrime Why not? I always thought the science versus religion was the dumbest thing. Then… https://t.co/El1ox297Hi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robin Crowder of @JMUCoE introduce @dintersmith and @VDOE_News Superintendent @DrJamesLane as the #VAis4Learners In… https://t.co/KUIYuVR7Qa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since my wife got sick I’ve taken over all of the house hold work cooking to laundry cleaning and taking care of my… https://t.co/Fsc6NPS93K]]></document><document><![CDATA[This handsome fella is only $2 every Tuesday at @WholeFoods Downtown! https://t.co/kWj7F1XrE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not watching the Oscars, and not because I’m on a “ooooohhh the Oscars are so bad” kick. But because I’m going… https://t.co/2I5kSTfBtY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle I mean do you and @DonaldJTrumpJr just sit around making up fake news websites?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay you’re a goon but (and I cannot stress this enough) what’s a goon to a goblin?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanWeigel Apparently they screwed up the DC United broadcast from their road game at NYCFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEPROCESSFball @PylonEliteCamps @THEPROCESSmark @THEPROCESSNick @THEPROCESSCorey @JoshuaBorne https://t.co/KtFXBWP2iP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democratic Party Official Says 2A Supporters are 'Homegrown Terrorists' https://t.co/L77mWOipqj #gunsamerica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Academy Awards don't always pick deserving winners in Best Picture category.Critic for New Yorker A… https://t.co/3Wrcg81XlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ And he didn't even have to return the coat to the ostrich.]]></document><document><![CDATA[fog &amp; foam, St Augustine Beach, Florida.  @StAugBeach @travelFLA #travelUSA ##travel #floridabeaches #surfing… https://t.co/mmPis2Hayz]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment you realize that “reducer” is just a fancy word for a function that takes 2 values and returns 1 value.… https://t.co/WtpPSMbKWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was in Toms River today and took Gregory by my old high school, Toms River South.  Good to see my old high school.… https://t.co/7LPdSpCsGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Super70sSports Boo ! I do . Royals first. Dodgers second. No go to either . I’ll take the Padres]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO @RealJamesWoods Soon the liberal leaders of DC will be putting up cardboard silhouettes of her... #WhereisRuth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @RepCuellar @txamiu Hope you can hang in Washington and do some work? You are so good to us Americans!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllWaltrip @NASCAR @visitmusiccity Amen I love it we need @NASCAR in Nashville TN]]></document><document><![CDATA[a puzzlement in the wild #wild #puzzle #santacruz @ Eastside, Santa Cruz, California https://t.co/bnZMjjNEQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnah181 @TGirlsAddict @jockosrocket @lithium66 @PassiValerio @ironPenus_JPN I wanna fuck that ass so bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dinner tonight was a raw egg on top of some fresh steamed rice so I’m back on my asceticism and Henry David Thoreau ish]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the highlights of my time in politics was getting to meet Ed Nixon the brother of #RichardNixon He passed aw… https://t.co/9kKQwsPhdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cityofwashpa There are TWO traffic light intersections without power.. in Eighty Four, PA.. the 519  exit, next to BP has station]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nzthiago @MicrosoftTeams All of this, but far and away the “mute a thread” feature]]></document><document><![CDATA[As if the beer at @CityBuilt wasn’t enough, there’s jibaritos, Puerto Rican rice and tacos too.  #GrandRapids #MiWBF https://t.co/klc8piNYVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cubs FS! Cards, autographed balls, game used! Baez #gameused bat also available! https://t.co/XPOwEM0yQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arbortender @Kimbrulea @amyklobuchar I have no bias, you're the one who said you don't need any form of ID to vote… https://t.co/oLe8B1zFkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southlandsox Anyone who loses games for the Dodgers is a true Padres hero.]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 Steps to Becoming a Better Thinker https://t.co/yq9N2JGoby via @copyblogger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EWErickson So Trump falls in the categories of being sexually immoral and an adulterer. But he somehow gets a pass? Is he a good person?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We live by principle, not by pressure. Don't let the culture pressure you, but the Word of God guide you. @CoachTomMullins @milestonechurch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@314TruthSeeker @ward24stl I think the goal is to limit violence from the start.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimminsRock @derekseguin19 @NOJHL @josh77anderson_ @tymasternak3519 Congrats !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always support black small and minority business’s. Sweater by: @courtofwolves   https://t.co/LppPuMx6v4… https://t.co/8o2lj66fXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iowa State releases renderings for proposed renovations to Hilton Coliseum https://t.co/MJJkfk19Sx via @DMRegister]]></document><document><![CDATA[She should be deported. She obviously doesn’t support the U.S. Constitution. She has violated her oath of office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rdub04 Super young. Year in the minors obviously would help him. Ton of potential though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cee_slorck @katiedoesntknow @pussyhatlawyer @AOC We live in different universes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every media org likes to call out companies for not paying taxes, yet NOBODY ever mentions the guiding principle of… https://t.co/6JFB760oPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[🖤10 days until I'm in Tokyo. 🖤17 days until I'm at a @junjiitofficial exhibit at the @spanart_gallery  🖤🍥🔪I cannot… https://t.co/lXP7neOJvH]]></document></documents></author>