<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MsSammyMichelle My problem with zevin is that it came out of no where as if Sophie didn’t matter to Kevin. Why are… https://t.co/LPAadA6T5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lalalaurabee Ohhhhh, I thought she got it from a baby.   (I'll see myself out)]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s spring when cute little old men take the roof of their corvette and go hit some golf balls with their chaps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino The billion dollar debacle from one in a billion @AOC A Valentine’s Day 💎diamond who actually is only a “… https://t.co/opBTo1lRON]]></document><document><![CDATA[These floral arrangements are just a few examples of what you can see at Cathedral in Bloom. The event features 30… https://t.co/u5nnPVdqOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TonyGennaro_ @SpamuelJohnson Yeah if he goes O-line at 10 I think you’ll have potential]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saoirse_vapor Get well soon sweetie! It’s a nasty thing a stomach virus. I had forgotten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week a new podcast is launching in NM! The first episode is all about TRUST in schools. Follow and listen alon… https://t.co/FnlHhZwmQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1a2a4life @Ilhan Sick is putting it mildly!! 😠 https://t.co/iDk9pghEb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iadamroyer @MeetThePress @chucktodd @Jim_Jordan Never knew this syndrome! Thanks! Interesting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PartyChilensisFtViña2019 @soycamioficial Ya no tenemos miedo #YoNoTeTengoMiedo]]></document><document><![CDATA[💃🏻Night out with these beauties!!  So happy to see your pretty face in town bmwolfenden 💕 buttapecanang @ Punch Bow… https://t.co/Kt1wH553GF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegoHelmet @rjfdickson68 If I don’t remember the little steps - I can tell myself I’m failing at the big ones. Thanks for the reminder!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣😂🤣🎉🤣😂🤣🎉🤣😂🤣🎉🤣😂🤣🎉🤣😂🤣🎉 Yep, absolute BEST accomplishment this crazy green deal @AOC will ever have‼️🤣😂🤣🎉🤣😂🤣🎉🤣😂🤣🎉🤣😂🤣🎉🤣… https://t.co/ocFINxem4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codyontheradio That’s sweet. I could get run over by a stampede of buffalos and dragged to my death and I’m not su… https://t.co/z1uQevFDHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feminism, which teaches women to think of men as the enemy, has made women “angry” and “defensive, though often unk… https://t.co/WS263avn5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY DOES EVERYONE HAVE TO FUCKING SHUT DOORS SO FUCKING HARD. YOU DO NOT HAVE TO SLAM DOORS IN ORDER FOR THEM TO FUCKING SHUT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout-out to one of my Sheroes. She inspires me in more than education. She's an awesome mother, wife, and mentor.… https://t.co/ZzVmHsw8nF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @RepCummings @TheDemocrats for demonstrating yet again what complete slime-balls you are and reaffirming… https://t.co/bwW7zcORgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFL @AP @ABC @BW @WSJ @cspan @cspanwj @axios @thehill @ShepNewsTeam @foxnewspolitics @Acosta @maddow @60Minutes… https://t.co/LBlAk6Th3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only thing i have ever gotten mad at chase for was leaving the damn pizza AT THE BOWLING ALLEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tictoc The ANC is doing a bang up job. Don't ya' think? What do you mean "no"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicaleigh_LA @Perdikament @RashidaTlaib @by_the_ppl @CREDOMobile @RepAdamSchiff 😁😆😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had one of those moments where a word doesn't make sense. Plans. What a weird word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[so sick of depressed being the “cool” thing for teenagers. like it’s kinda fucked how some people use it for the ae… https://t.co/fGNbJWvvNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the Challenge from @Jsupple28 The challenge is to post covers of #7Books that I love. No explanations… https://t.co/MpRPA7GWeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been so close with myself ❤️ really just getting to know me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @dbongino @BetoORourke please explain to me what these illegal immigrants are suppose to do for incom… https://t.co/h6e9IudC30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luci Howard crossed 5K. Time 00:34:05, pace 10:58 min/mile, est. finish 7:59 am https://t.co/i9o9sBG3UZ #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[She won’t, because teachers aren’t directly below her. She will only take care of her own peeps. That’s how sociali… https://t.co/5Cw7XJxuKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[if it werent' for laughter . . .  #comedy #tee-hee #smirk #cute https://t.co/Jbg3tjxFED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@royalghostmarch My favorite was when ppl would ask if my fuscia hair was “natural”.   Yes, I grow it out of my hea… https://t.co/30ltFQs2rt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't make us do this thing alone. Come on! #Heartland Ty and Amy are such a fun aunt and uncle duo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So yeah I’m bringing my sleeping bag to tentigersdc since I will be there back to back. TONIGHT is #PlanB with… https://t.co/IUH67MRZd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 TRAFFIC ALERT 🚨  Pellicano exit off of Loop 375 South is closed for the next few months. Here’s a s look at the b… https://t.co/BXS9ztt28M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gambotage So I will be watching for price to hit between 7280 and 7441, reverse and go back to 6796 and then fail… https://t.co/SGpeUIfsKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a lot of people i wanna see eventually.....but like the Jonas brothers are srsly #1 rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be clear Hillary is not running for any office and trump is in the White House. Sooo constantly mentioning he… https://t.co/baMG2Mjla1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost dr_terresa with  So proud of @PastorBHilliard @bgirlfoundation Thank you michelleobama for #iambecoming @ H… https://t.co/OLF2nt5Gj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just in time for Friday’s during Lent @NichollsState @ChickfilA https://t.co/ekGSPiTZmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grabbin some necessary goods from blairaus0 at the team store totalnutrition_lynnwood for this up coming season, cl… https://t.co/z35ED7Q6y5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently drowning in work why don’t we get a February break in college]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfaoooo I should’ve known my sleep wasn’t safe last night. They set me up 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonD0613 @jleonard_43 @NHLFlyers True. They arent pittsburgh after all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @AOC $885 Million funneled from campaign funds  into her Campaign Mgrs 2 private businesses..  jail… https://t.co/oJxclYIehK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@King_Gregoro @AP Sorry the General Assembly has already make the decision. They will come to Virginia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimMitchell18 great piece today about higher ed. Love the focus on collaboration between K-12, CCs and universities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBloomberg @realDonaldTrump The weather, oops, I mean the climate has been pretty steady at Mar-a-Lago of late.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamInTaunton @SamanthaBusch That would be great if they did. It was working. Over the fords.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ YOU LOOK LIKE #EDDIEIZZARD  @ Jacksonville, Florida https://t.co/5qSFNBUTbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to my girls today I can’t wait to watch y’all play!! Miss y’all so much hurry up and bring home the dubs… https://t.co/ST1CqAEDF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[So it’s 356 am and I can’t sleep the excitement of @WWERomanReigns  being on raw to!! I can’t wait !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fj nxkc CBC cockfighting dogfighting tend bff 👯 I love fjfnf f https://t.co/SytgwAKVQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Assembler - https://t.co/cMifCUpm9F #Manufacturing #Mason, MI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need some mirth. We Speak the Truth: Social Media Works for #SmallBusiness #comedy #tee-hee #smile #laughable https://t.co/aSonOuxNKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift - Style (Thirdstory Cover) https://t.co/iJsiLt6mnq via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I nominate @awkwafina and @mulaney to host the #oscars next year. https://t.co/gLOG29U6yv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys I was so scared to tell my parents that I wanted to take a gap year, but they’re being so supportive. Looking… https://t.co/z6eezQD5zf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greenbay531 @RoseKellyPC That would be great. Genie said they had 1 year of story for her... that would be until October]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donjefferis214 @SenBlumenthal On what grounds do you say he was illegitimate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity So many private jets. And they're worried about climate change?  That's a lie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaSuhler @realDonaldTrump You mean how far into the toilet and cesspool we have fallen with Trump as president,… https://t.co/PiVRaWgDqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great interview with thoughtful ideas for using @greatbigstory in the elementary classroom!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t think the time change would hit me this hard. I need a damn nap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didja catch me in a little bit of #LAByNight 's season finale? Here's a hint! https://t.co/dOHtLivR7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It would be nice if you got your head out of your racist ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NAFlagvisor @old_running @HenriSwarts @vbmlwilson @logriffey24 @CaraAnselmo @squadrunnerapp I joined a team mid Ja… https://t.co/9Tjd6PC4lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday and #NationalMargaritaDay everyone!! For anyone celebrating later, how do you take your rita??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TornerCheryl @RJNewsflash NPR thought jaun was to main stream and fired him. He has a tingly feeling towards Nazis… https://t.co/32ERNi4vjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶🎶I'm so excited, and I just can't hide it. Cohen's about to testify, and I think I love it. 🎶🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should’ve never watched Empire years ago because somehow my dad is blaming me for what Jussie Smollet did??? Like???]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 minute!!!!! @AmericanIdol #AmericanIdol @LukeBryanOnline https://t.co/HdwH3rgPBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI: I voted for @jamessmurray in the #ShortyAwards. Who did you vote for? https://t.co/I0ergpvfmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[ashleywgillett is an established author of the acclaimed novel Red Flags Run and as a relationship consultant.⁣ ⁣ R… https://t.co/jMczoUtcCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP And how about tRump's NON STOP LIES. And just look- now Kim Jong Un, brutal North Korean Dictator is tRump's n… https://t.co/MqB0pFMguS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianRep Remind US, remind me, the answers our Country needs is not in DC but with you.  Crazy, upsetting time… https://t.co/qSgdwliqOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#capitalism #airpods #residentsnek #bubble #bye #springbreak #douche #douché #mywharton #whartonwoman #discislife https://t.co/m0tNj3sCo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods Girl gone Lmfaooo b mad your cheating ass HUSBAND TOO tf 😂😂😂 HE BROKE YO FAMILY UP!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoy March. It’s a good month. I like how it’s the end of winter and start of spring with a day dedicated to Pi in between!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tipo eu to gostando de uma pessoa né e essa pessoa não tá nem aí pra mim. Postei umas coisas no instagram e literal… https://t.co/Nc6QjlevZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[There you have it...@cspanwj There are people who would lie for personal gain...Go Figure?]]></document><document><![CDATA[One last Festival of the Arts stroll for the year... #UntaggableJason #adventure #wanderlust #adventureseeker… https://t.co/3bGZBc11DO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@say_naja @Thelovely_Vonn @MaraliGrace @QueenGemini13 @CorriMava @SnickerMica @patriciaorteg13 @OniciaMuller Cute!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof;”  Co… https://t.co/Y9dLba57Li]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched my Mimi die in a span of months after we found out she had stage 4 lung cancer. If she could've had marij… https://t.co/CorDA02z2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommytotyler @JSOPIO @propacop @GoodCopStories @GoodNewsCops @FLSheriffs @NatPoliceAssoc @PolicingNews… https://t.co/mQAul2On9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@9e76a351efa944f @senatemajldr Which party praised tax cuts that had folks actually thinking their wallets would be… https://t.co/Dl66zHGSRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlmostHeroicDnD Willowisp: tiefling ranger  Song: #pokemontheme by #variousartists]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @AdamSchiff @JussieSmollett Frightening...this is THE WORST Congress.  They think only of themselve… https://t.co/jRWcEf1MuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm just ready for the candy to go on sale 😂😂😂 @ Tyler, Texas https://t.co/E03jsIFwRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reason # 375738 I don’t trust LVP. Love Ken, but.. Here’s a lesson on screen shots of iMessage conversations. They… https://t.co/Z5GY4CaeMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Takeout (@ Chris Jerk Caribbean Bistro in Toronto, ON) https://t.co/8RWyl8nKk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[the majority of the United Nations General Assembly adopted a resolution urging the Israeli regime to withdraw from… https://t.co/tsEKym6s8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shortymac09 @cjane87 @willsommer Well, AOC's Green New Deal did say they want to make air travel not relevant with… https://t.co/4ySOFrCiaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bunsenbernerbmd Not for another 13 or so years and a lot of love and happiness 💕 (she was about 2 when I got her)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like DT This Judge Is Unfit For Office.He's Indicating That White Collar Crime https://t.co/tYkSR9N7RO's A Spit In… https://t.co/uyhqySgLfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rayfashworthjr @DFBHarvard She should be convicted for committing fraud but as usual..the law doesn’t apply to democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHRISScabello That whole documentary had me pissed off the ENTIRE time lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Jim Brantner is the best! Make your appointment today! #johnsoncityfarmersmarket #localbakery… https://t.co/xvlBweSL2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspan @ReaDonnaIdTrump don't worry Mr. President. You are doing the right thing with good records in US history. W… https://t.co/e18eBqQH88]]></document></documents></author>