<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@zelenny Buenos días Zelenny, que tengas un excelente miércoles 😀. Abrazos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 Toss Up: Laura Nyro's, " New York Tendaberry," and Joni Mitchell's, "Hissing of Summer Lawns."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peek a boo, I see u!! #metal #guitar #gibson #voodoo #metalhead #metaldude #metalheads #numetal #groovemetal… https://t.co/CQOFf7zyPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@textfiles The natural language compiler used for RACTOR? Has he tried contacting the authors?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet 5 mo puppy Mari, a koreank9rescue alumna adjusting well to big city life with her loving human.  Is great to s… https://t.co/IbI88cYHwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEPFuller Know what I learned from this...never, ever, will I place minorities on stage to justify that I am NOT a… https://t.co/7XDwO6elb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[انڈیا کے خلاف مظاہرہ کیوں؟؟ کیا انڈیا نے مہاجروں پر کوٹہ سسٹم لگایا کیا انڈیا نے تمہارے گھروں کے تقدس کو پامال کیا ہے @AltafHussain_90]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we have a 60 man 3 ring battle Royal and in the end WCW who at the time is kicking WWE ass duplicates the end of the 94 rumble]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vjmc La única explicación y no hace falta que los bancos la den, es la hiperinflación, mientras exista, nada tiene… https://t.co/vx4CD1mlDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[McKenzie Deville 5-3 PG LA 24’ has a little flare to her game. Will be updated on the ASGR App. @coachcjbball… https://t.co/5Z4jDs61Q8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AugustusBeau @McAllisterDen Did you determine the source of the noise?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kedz i legit have a date planned for the next 4 days lol. tinder is lit here 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow...that first 10 seconds,  I was “Noooooo”🗣🗣🗣.... but alas...well...watch for yourself! 🐯💕🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews No Russian hacking. I still say Seth Rich downloaded DNC docs to his flash drive, got them to Wikile… https://t.co/Mlr0KMK3rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christinaXlimit Take a shot for me! Definitely sending love n well wishes y'alls way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tix on sale now!! @ Harrah's Hoosier Park Racing and Casino https://t.co/nCyZoRtPA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ravenpitmann I don’t see how young people travel like that 😅 maybe when I’m old and have saved hella money but I’m… https://t.co/Cm28buyaLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC So, here’s the problem with this logic. The city didn’t have $3 billion to pay Amazon that it can now spend on… https://t.co/ySLjujudjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ruth Bader Ginsburg Isn’t Looking to Retire Yet, But Is Another Supreme Court Justice Ready to Go? https://t.co/oIBUM7IdTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aish... Semana del Open! (at @CrossfitHoboken in Hoboken, NJ) https://t.co/oWdoT8qv6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have some b-roll from a shoot yesterday that was perfect for a quick little edit. This is Don and he loves the came… https://t.co/i0sKbGOdTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clinton comes in at 11-19 while Lanphier is 15-15. #sjrpreps https://t.co/k4jKIaqXB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kansaskim88 How many times is he gonna bring up Matt D. He acts like he was the only one who backed him. Does he r… https://t.co/2jWybOyQNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nick_rothschild Last year I was at a @Kadet_Athletics girls basketball game and had a student just roast me for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo llame a esta etapa: Soñar despierto ! Gracias a mi equipo, toda la vida seré Madridista ! Hala Madrid y nada mas… https://t.co/78SLxk2GN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi, I like to post negative things about people who are made in the image of God, bcuz I think it glorifies God. An… https://t.co/4oD49ZU8Fa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@affinity292 @realkerryfrench @RubensteinAdam @IlhanMN @HelloLauraKelly “CBS News correspondent Bob Simon was worri… https://t.co/UnyrAtF6sD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ed Bouchette's Steelers chat: 02.26.19 https://t.co/2LnWgHZmXk via @pittsburghpg @EdBouchette #Steelers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Están con las horas contadas, el tiempo se les está terminando, Venezuela será libre muy pronto!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FutaDross Que Rica chupadas de culo y unas mordidas de guevos unas mamadas de berga y que te bengas en mi boca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelledeidre Every time I see it, I have to watch it at least 5 times through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so peaceful out in Elkhorn Slough today!!! https://t.co/YKumn2Maoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[FAKE NEWS. CNN,,MSNBC,,,ALL LIES,,,,BELIEVE  IN ANTI- SEMITISM...KILLING OF BABIES AT BIRTH...VERY SICK PEOPLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/BnpC4AlK0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think William should testify, too. A silent client seems guilty at trial. Like, he did it. That is why he is not… https://t.co/Rns0bRXIap]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: Slidell 47, Oakwood 45. Greyhounds advance to their first state title game since 1943. #UILState https://t.co/D6UYyHBXD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So infuriating. They kept allowing Duke to set up the press when they had several opportunities to to get the ball… https://t.co/Lb9T1g1PdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this week’s @jonlovett or Leave It, @waitwait’s Peter Segel was absolutely fabulous. Lovett wasn’t so bad...maybe fab!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cameronarn @YouTube Really cool! I watched all three videos, but I didn’t see how he came up with his plant/human… https://t.co/OkEOJXEVKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The Technology Behind OpenAI’s Fiction-Writing, Fake-News-Spewing A.I., Explained” by MIT Technology Review https://t.co/uR9l2iND3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_BOOGIE_5 is a 4-star DB sitting on six #Big12FB offers from #GoFrogs #WreckEm #SicEm #rockchalk #OKstate and… https://t.co/OHeFapmy3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rosiest recruitment advert I`ve seen in awhile. Neglect to mention the trenches. https://t.co/RahLk2YWIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eclectic curation ✔️💕👏🏼 #connoisseur #mosesnadel #eclecticdecor #shearlingottoman #sheepskinthrow #mandala… https://t.co/ZELhNFY95A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats! #TeacheroftheYear Kristin Murphy of Nova Middle School wins #Broward Teacher of the Year – WSVN 7News | M… https://t.co/k9nD6WHQWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLS_Buzz @adidassoccer With 45 seconds and Microsoft Word, I could design this “clean and classic” kit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leading scorers for @LexHSBasketball were @mason2carver with 20 points, @R_Green02 with 13, @BradleyFoulks with 11… https://t.co/13MmWiP5aB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thoughts tonight (1/3)    Green girls basketball hits 10 wins. With their 59-30 win over East, they won their first… https://t.co/WOs1yUeTLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We get it.  Everyone else is corrupt, crazy, and conspiring against you. Somehow, with all your m… https://t.co/FBr5u2Eaei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNWestPalm @EvCoRadio @ryandlieber @BRowitz Kylian Mbappe, if you would allow for outside of major leagues in the US.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanmdav @PoliticalShort Mr Barr better bring track shoes, he has a lot of ground to cover]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimmyReagen 2/ I favor, as an alternaative 1st step, charging a carbon fee for non-residential parking in places l… https://t.co/2o6TnOO0k5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This decision might have been even worse than keeping Marvin on for the extra year...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcIMT122 @simonfromharlow @DrJenGunter Strangely enough, I’m from a small family. One sister, 5 yrs my junior (we… https://t.co/XQRsAy7yz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just over 18 hours to go until this @SpaceX launch from the Kennedy Space Center, starting Day 2 of our #NASASocial… https://t.co/kuM2IE7Nva]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone is in Santa Fe, there’s some cool films playing at the Jean Cocteau]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oytaki @motivateme2011 @AnkeDosedal @miss_speech @KathCLeSage @strive_mightily @Aaron_hunter13 @LocustAutoX… https://t.co/gcJUyyDncL]]></document><document><![CDATA[So when you make the puppets Nazis - and make no mistake, when you have a lesbian couple killed for making out, a g… https://t.co/hSyNTxcEmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's so very very British of them to say they'd "loan" the Parthenon marbles to Greece for a little while, but expe… https://t.co/45ViUKNaYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andyhre I’d rather get paid less, but not fear losing my job after one down turn season. “Economics” entering coll… https://t.co/50C6d68F0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[City crews have been fully deployed all weekend and over night plowing/sanding/salting our main roadways and downto… https://t.co/2SHASSjmaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickDugan @nytimes LOL, Collusion was the one crime Democrats have been trying to pin on Trump from day leaks, FBI… https://t.co/mifd4wBuRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cynicalmatt1 @1EverettAnthony @BMS_Billy @BMS_Derek @BMS_VoiceGuy @BMS_Arianna @BMS_Felix @DosMasPorFavor… https://t.co/Df2UrIRcNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Wanna kill whitey” I going put that on a resume. 😂🤣😅 https://t.co/u7BF5ByhwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow...that is impressive. Also hilarious, look of the size of that first bite, that's lethal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justindiben12 He need more volume. Meanwhile Morris looks like Kobe out there throwing it up every time he touches the ball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tom_beshere @joannehaagenson @TheRickWilson Is "kid gloves" what you mean by intentionally distorting Bernie's rec… https://t.co/EFcKR65FgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattknox I did, but I was stuck inside the elevator. There isn't a badge swipe (or floor selection mechanism) in there AFAICT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamBede3 @ncRobronfan @emmerdale He’s only 15!? I thought he was 16 going on 17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Use code HYND20 for 20% off your entire order from blenders eyewear. LINK IN BIO @RogueRTs  @ShoutGamers @FlyRts… https://t.co/p814o6ZtnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone should be reading a https://t.co/gDnuEs9Anc #pophorror @PopHorrorNews is your one stop horror news shop on… https://t.co/QEwvnCEDhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway up escalator from NRW platform at 3rd Avenue end at 59/Lex is stopped]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cuntneykardash @elena_hatib John &amp; Dorinda v. Bethenny at the bra party in season 8 is the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point I owe most of my education to Sal from @khanacademy because my prof is confusing the hell out of me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadnotkyle What middle school science teacher is telling kids this 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @ValerieParks248 Pence is a treasonous traitor to America that must be held accountable pence is just a… https://t.co/KTrHfNslz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daenku32 @SamusAran2020 @cbschicago WHY? I hope he doesn’t! But he’ll probably plead guilty to a lesser charge. An… https://t.co/3400kLxXx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shipwreck I don’t know if you heard but @footlocker and I think @ASICSamerica are doing some sorta GI Joe sneakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is pretty sad that asshole are watching and making rude comments you fags should be ashamed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im glad Manny went to the San Diego Dads...but who would of expected that 2 months ago???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge waste of tax payers. At least Michelle Obama was exercising... Melania can’t even hypocrite well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to learn how to go to bed at a normal time and big 3 in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kbay6413 @RushJohnNabors He actually said it during the block, not during the stare-down. I know it include a big N-word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Venus_Serena @TrishelleC but where are you watching the reruns because i’ll never leave my house 📺👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ziggystardad @charliekirk11 @realDonaldTrump Probably the Rasmussen poll but from a week ago. Rasmussen only calls… https://t.co/ftrTY8lyD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t need a fire cracker smh. It’s nice for the temp. I’m looking at long term success residual income...I have… https://t.co/QCw8dpPUxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstasiaWill Wait you serious?! I love her album! Have it on repeat everyday 😂😂 https://t.co/5fX1Zslck5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMarieBoothe @RepSwalwell Ask him what the hell he’s doing in your town? Go back to Washington..... oh yea he’d have to work there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quincy_walters @WBUR @GovBillWeld “...kowtows to Putin”? Entire Russian economy is dependent on income from oil an… https://t.co/nPrmtfJqdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NyleDiMarco @Jenny_Stanton @MailOnline We are all in this together... I’m more than happy to engage in a thoughtfu… https://t.co/zaf3WmYqGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSeaRose I don’t like actually reach for anything I just Lay there and try to forget the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I know I’m different then a lot of other people. If you think I would ever send 1 fucking penny of my hard earn… https://t.co/kEkgu3R0EC]]></document><document><![CDATA[What ?!? Y’all have to pay for papers to take test that the teachers require ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1SFpodcast @joe_dombrowski @TheAndrewPalace I’d sing Oasis and we all know it. https://t.co/qvPczdiHUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Bovaird @fatdogsfrance @PennerLaurie @watchingthedai1 @HeroicAnimals @2ndHandCathy @TommyCarbone212… https://t.co/iABYNAdEce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeteoAntoine @cluke5 @ellefabbro @environmentca Most French speakers know at least some English   I dont know why… https://t.co/p1gvLht1Tp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRobCapewell @ValueAnalyst1 @elonmusk @GerberKawasaki I may do a video on this. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it normal that just one side of an outlet stops working? That’s seems unusual]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philwahba @shoptalk @Recode There are a few Vodka bars that will make you feel right at home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottfawcett Outstanding information! I know a TV commentator that needs Decade Golf!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get to the damn mall , 2 hood rats come charging me up about a tweet from 20 motha fucken 15 birch FIFTEEN!!!!! I was a child 😭]]></document></documents></author>