<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[anyway healthcare should be universal and people shouldn’t have to go into massive debt to not die ✌️✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning!  Lisa Sheppard here.  Instructional Coach from Wayne-Westland!  #waynea3]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Vibrance please!!! 💚💛💚💛 say’s talented hair color artist @rossajurenas ✂️ . . . . #hair #color #rossajurenas… https://t.co/nX6hPgtUMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Hate crimes are on the rise in America and I am hurt that Smollett filed a false police report on an alleged h… https://t.co/cP14TPq7Rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Write me somethin!! It can be sassy, emotional, goofy, whatever..you decide! I’m group 11 🎗💃🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannaChamp @BachelorABC I don't  know if I feel bad for him.If you look at the whole picture, I think he went int… https://t.co/vGAOSeLQJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Christine Candio and Kenneth White for receiving the Gold Medal Award From ACHE #ACHECongress]]></document><document><![CDATA[So lucky to glimpse these true #snowbirds who  arrive in the fall in Florida and stay until late spring. #boatlife… https://t.co/cfMPzf1JJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Panama6715 @TheJusticeDept Mr. #Hypocrisy - plotting to overthrow the President. What rule of law???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update! Kelly (it’s okay using her first name, I think) and I are going to set up our first video chat soon. She is… https://t.co/2KKYMsm1ct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeyaSophia @GamecockWBB @GamecockMBB We turned around on the way to the game. Great granddaughter is almost here!… https://t.co/QjOQlLzAxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[this doesn’t mean your parents hate you, this means your parents are trying to teach you about what life is like be… https://t.co/ofzhqhRE84]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social Tech, deep Tech, BtoC empowering : proud of our 15 🇫🇷 start-ups on the @businessfrance @LaFrenchTech pavillo… https://t.co/3UJWXoApJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allisimpson  I’m immensely proud of you. you're achieving so many great things! you inspire me and many others aro… https://t.co/FHPKXrpye3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Passions5Words #special #MyPassionsin5Words #FlowersRadiateBeauty #ValentinesDay #ThursdayThoughts https://t.co/mj0N3Nsm0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got some unexpected #DisneyMail today from my agency, mandmmagicaladventures! It's been a year of hard, but SUCH… https://t.co/5cR92Qx4O3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was beautiful yesterday but this weather today 😩😩😩 I’m supposed to go to brunch but this weather is a buzz kill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKingstonBooks @amwritingbot I had to make this decision with my first book. I set it aside (always telling myself… https://t.co/T862waCuvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The students got a Northrop Frye joke, so, gotta say,the kids are alright.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The uber I ordered didn’t provide the license plate number ...y’all think I know what a Honda Accord is?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #InternationalWomensDay I spent it with the greatest leaders of my generation, at the @NCWITAIC award weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since UAA school of education lost its accreditation I just applied to graduate with my AA, totaling winging this s… https://t.co/kBzaods1vY]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone who “loves” U tries to hurt U by bringing up ur old traumas, pain, fears, uses these wounds to attack… https://t.co/MkfWK3yOJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoHoesShxdy This is definitely an unpopular opinion, bet u won’t say to my face]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bueno si se chuparon todos mis stories de Universal Studios me voy a tener que chular los de Bad Bunny también]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously love my internship. So excited to go to work! #paycom #DigitalTransformation]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my weight loss comparisons so here’s a little #facetofacefriday! Hello chin, cheekbones, and jawline ;) I ca… https://t.co/MfevlNLHFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growth is more than time elapsing, growth is enhancing the quality of life  ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumpDayHashTags @Freedomofdoubt @JoyceWhiteVance Hallelujah ! Hallelujah ! I am so glad Roger will get punished fo… https://t.co/1bJmCsrscP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fucked that bitch now he don’t even matter just spend 30k at moncler on some sweaters]]></document><document><![CDATA[We nudge students beyond their comfort zone. Presented at GAGC today. My empathy for students outside their comfort… https://t.co/luUYKRFvS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isaiahthomas It’s that SLOW GRIND, friend. You did it, and it’s good to see you healthy and playing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve got a Dave’s Cosmic Sub and you won’t catch me frowning at all the rest of the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[on my break I walk around southpark hunting for celebrities lmao. i saw @RaeSremmurd yesterday 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vaileboleyn My boyfriend legitimately gave me thousand island dressing because he got it from his work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I #admit I always #like the #super #shiny #make up #look ! #selfie #actress 🎭 @turnovermovie 🎥🎬 #hope to #see you t… https://t.co/BrqlH6FVYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlamedaDowning We did!  But I must admit that I felt guilty not picking the lemon curd! Lol 🍋 #POstables]]></document><document><![CDATA[MOTW 😍 #JustinTimberlake #ManOfTheWoodsTour #LasVegas #Concert4WithCalimag #IBragAboutYou #BoyGotSwag @ T-Mobile Ar… https://t.co/twE3GAz2HH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beastcoaster91 Well Trump probably got the popular vote too if you subtract all the dead people who voted... So.mu… https://t.co/D89Q1pG3ps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec I've never watched award shows where elitists self congratulate themselves]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to be dramatic or anything but I actually genuinely hate my existence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse you really need a BASICS of Government handout for dumb Donny]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe the Mars Opportunity River died on my birthday and Colby is mad at me and won’t tell me why. Heartb… https://t.co/zY26pDgU0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’d rather fight demons with you  than live amongst the angels without you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RKELLY; GALATIANS 6:2; BEAR YE ONE ANOTHER'S BURDENS, AND SO FULFIL THE LAW OF CHRIST:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hall on capacity issues: we’re trying to keep things as continuous as possible ... using cnr facilities in city campuses and New Ro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DevinNunes @FoxNews #Trump there are war crimes happening in our family courts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my classroom on @DonorsChoose! I'd love your help to bring my project to life:  https://t.co/1fAGt8Pn8f via @donorschoose]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can life fuck me any harder  This is an actual concern what astrological moon/sign whatever is fucking with my life rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gayer_Than_Thou @nhmeems "Best by" [date] really does mean only that  True expiration is months and months later]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dice mi amiga de la universidad, que desde que nos conocimos ha pensado que mi forma de pensar y actuar es de algui… https://t.co/fgJet2KLL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen... as much as I hate this weather, I can put a coat on. My lips DONT LIKE CHAPSTICK!! They can’t keep doing this!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess the idea of family is important to my dad and he keeps telling everyone hes gonna be a grandpa but like...… https://t.co/gitXY14dPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of our #STH crew is here at #WPB for #AstrosST. #AgsWin #Astros #TakeItBack #grapefruitleague #STBaseball @ Fi… https://t.co/evjFtcaNVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying a slow morning after yesterday’s 59.71 miles of 🏊🏻‍♀️ 🚴🏻‍♀️🏃🏻‍♀️ in preparation for Ironman Texas 70.3 in… https://t.co/gpQdnXrKK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooked chopped bacon, sautéed spinach and sautéed fresh mushrooms and red onions that will go into the frittata I’l… https://t.co/1CIHP3wHA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigManPauly @Redskins Eric Weddle is getting up there in years. He was very good with the Chargers but not as prod… https://t.co/BQgRub7ZZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations and Enjoy your new home! #blessedtoworkwiththebest @ Hutchinson, Minnesota https://t.co/HhLzllryUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd song 'Hold Your Heart Open' is so close to being done. looking forward to sharing it w/ you. #montemann… https://t.co/VMW0Ed3A8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hay una chava que sigo en mi otro twitter y se me hace súper súper chida y no sabía que me seguía y me comentó una foto. 😭💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign now: let's keep guns out of the hands of animal abusers!  #care2 https://t.co/FEnel1HEUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmfao darian hates when I talk in a British accent and it’s the funniest thing ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callmedomooo @TeashaLashawn @LSL_Laya @Its_just_jayy @lovelykasie @InnocentSinner_  IM THE HONORABLE FUCKING MENTION]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time last night at JT concert!!!   Thanks @sunny1065lv  and Joanna.... https://t.co/lb184HAfJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldnprgal I don’t know what kind of work week you were having but I can guarantee you I thought Friday would never arrive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliwashburn Save the phrase for when you’ve got a ring on it at least!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityRichmondVA why has HMI Utilities been jackhammering outside my apartment in Manchester since 5:30am? Was there… https://t.co/vAzsPRpaFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nationalmargaritaday #nmd2019 (@ Callie's in New York, NY) https://t.co/j3WBmAwEkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling on ALL School Employees!! My take-home Spring Break assignment for you all is to CARE FOR YOU this coming b… https://t.co/Zn6D2PaaSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elcaminoaFI I feel you. My dad isn’t Hispanic and I’m not entirely sure it will happen but I’m still going to plan… https://t.co/a6L9gtZAlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anjelahjohnson Tweeting you as requested- tacos del Gordo on H street in Chula Vista, Mitch’s in Point Loma, Las C… https://t.co/bilVoUQl9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a great Sabbath Everyone. #sabbath #dayofrest #GodgreatGod @ Altadena Seventh Day Adventist Church https://t.co/iztDQr6ojn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulmagers Does that FitBit know if it doesn't shut the hell up it may have an "unfortunate accident"?  "You've be… https://t.co/4OCZyJwtol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zipcar your customer service is terrible. definitely not recommending you to anyone lmaooooo y’all are trippin]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOT EXIST AS FAR AS THE REPUBLICAN LEADERSHIP OF THE USA IS CONCERNED, AND THEY ARE BACKED BY THE COUNCIL FOR NATIO… https://t.co/nivdFKv8Ff]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my new fanny pack so, so much. It’s sexy. We just went to 7 eleven and this girl freaked tf out over it. Thanks, Fashion Nova 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[DRA is seeking request for proposals from institutions of higher education within the Delta region to help build up… https://t.co/J5uggdN1rs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet Tommy. 😻 { #cats #catsofinstagram #adoptdontshop #whywerescue #catmom #catlife #catlover… https://t.co/9X1ZZVSjrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow She not only needs to be removed from Congress- but removed from our country as well! And don’t let her come back either!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s ride. @admiralelite15 @GrWill2 @JordanBone23 @JordyBow3 @KyleJamal4 @LTurn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @LindseyGrahamSC @senatemajldr @realDonaldTrump @VP https://t.co/5EsIYTIXyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to my beautiful mom💞 I hope you had a great day! I love you https://t.co/VrqN9swcSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t wait for pride this year so i can wear my “move i’m gay” shirt that shannon had made for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update cause the wig glue is STILL stuck in my hair will not come out so that’s where I’m at]]></document><document><![CDATA[Levanten la mano los que se creen el cuento del periodista comunista #jorgeramos que lo detuvo el “líder” (como el… https://t.co/4KWQbkbOY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtf is the momo challenge. These kids have nothing else better to do??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLalancetteTVA Vous avez oublié le record des Cataractes de Shawinigan en 1982-1983 qui ont  joué 31 matchs ( 30-0… https://t.co/a1kS5XYDh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bon matin #TwitterVille ☕☕☕  Rien à faire, mon horloge biologique ne catch pas que c'est le week-end   🤷‍♀️😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UpstateSpartans @UpstateBSB @UpstateSoftball Hey, Auburn HR finally made it into something @HawkinsChawkins @KenzieRoark @holly26mckinnon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yikes! . . #bookstagram #psychologicalthriller #crimeauthor #lovebowling @ El Jebowl https://t.co/zSbsdkbjC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizizFine @mitchsnyder45 @TrakkerJane @del_vol @RNelson1994 @Ranger3079 @myizonorion @MarkTJay3 @RamBoPirate… https://t.co/0apOp1h6pC]]></document><document><![CDATA[in the video “what are controlling images?” i learned that the average person in the united states spends 10 hours… https://t.co/0A1xDJmGmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar this is exactly the thing about you that makes you so... you 💙 miss you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol Would love to be there ! I am proud of my country and of president Trump ! Trump does not stop until i… https://t.co/6ZidPhZZeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot I’m getting braids this weekend 😲🔥 #TheSwitchUp if I don’t like them I’m taking it out the same day 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vincentdonofrio And it went SOOOO well! 😄 Worked 5 songs. Here’s a snippet: ☺️ https://t.co/xzTjyAAvuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the man that makes everyday feel like Valentine’s Day: I love you! 🥰♥️ @ Madison, Alabama https://t.co/EWgUts1yZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barkingdero @zaceubank @Hyper_RPG @Frankly_Emily @jessicaverdi @AlizaPearl Poor Clyde and Floyd 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7anthea7 @ProudResister Too much CONSPIRCY CORRUPTION within REPUBLICANS.YESTERDAY REPUBLICAN PROVE UNINTELLIGENT… https://t.co/mOptQxAMgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many congratulations to you, Poet Laureate Jaki Shelton Green! We had a front row seat to history today, and we are… https://t.co/liO9j5OfcY]]></document></documents></author>