<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@dlbowman76 three things I love about you: 1. Ticket to Ride. 2. Catan card game. 3. Babel. #JustBecause]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gve it a listen stay strong Resisters. Much Love https://t.co/74pQHrRdPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonoHerrman @bigyahu @NSydInnovation @venturecafeSYD @InnovationManly @NewportNetcomau @clarktweeting @DKAdvisor… https://t.co/8LQVlt5lbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gutsy_gaming @EmmaEmmaFoFemma @TwistyShape @CrankageGames That’s an interesting interesting job. I’ve never known anyone to work that]]></document><document><![CDATA[JAJA le mandé un ss de wha a mi hermana y se me olvidó lo que tenia de fondo🥵🥵🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited about this, but do want at least 50% of the original cast in it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My whole life has been a lie. I feel like my world is falling apart. I really don’t want to be home 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know everyone is asking, but “Time (is)” is my new favorite Solange track.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuna for one breakfast and chicken crepes (thin pancakes) for 2nd breakfast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nobodysbabynow1 Sorry you’re having such a crappy night, Vee!  I hope things start looking up. https://t.co/hpyrEdBXDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just want to show some appreciation for my beautiful best friend. She deserves the absolute world and so much more.… https://t.co/YZvhxrmDM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love his passion!! Too bad they ain't listening to you though bruh smmh..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Educ4J @BeverlyFolkers @bfam113 @BIBARECORDS @bigben127 @BigBenTuckerman @bjaninemorison @BjFridenmaker @BKOH4062… https://t.co/cDfyHabskE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Glassifaction @SandraBundy @FactsMatter123 @SenMarkey As for health care, if the US has worse outcomes why is it t… https://t.co/oOTdvA3Ss5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sally578 @JeffTeravainen @redTamsen @CamilleSully @MsChoiLee @Summersett_ How delightfully... unpredictable 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BitchPuddingO_o Yes. Pork belly. I could probably do it with chicken thighs too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AOC my son wants to apply for a summer internship - he has cover letter, resume ready but when  he went to su… https://t.co/kL6D3TH1DE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 @realDonaldTrump He doesn't understand that abortions are done to save the mother's life or if the fetus… https://t.co/06BliLXElo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#worldnewstonight can you really not tell the difference between @JussieSmollett and @michaelb4jordan? Isn't that M… https://t.co/1rlMs1XkRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sad when our media takes the bad cops and twists their reporting to make all cops look bad.  If it weren’t for… https://t.co/E5xSl9MOda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once a cheater always a cheater!! And with her sisters best friend🤦🏽‍♀️ Nooooo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the #CUEhike info, y’all! Excited to see beautiful faces bright and early on Friday!!   #CUE19… https://t.co/lLnb8tkeNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Branko_MA @sherrynron @luluHru @GaryDWalters3 @pjbowles4 @CensoredC1 @Sissy4Trump @JD_MAGA_4517 @AllenJa71169152… https://t.co/vCFn3t7GJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylanmsmitty I am, I am   #60Minutes #traitortrump #EnoughIsEnough #MarALardass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizpearceVCS @EPS_Bobcats @chelylindsey1 @beckyporter67 @ParodiVCS Thank you for supporting our Bobcats &amp; VCS! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcusGilbert88 Good Luck Marcus!! Steeler Nation wishes you nothing but the best!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tatehowell5 @JimmieAllen You got this.  Remember  you gotta work for it - and you did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @BrenMarPark_ES Cultural Proficiency Team had our first of four #CulturalCohort classes today! We did a lot of… https://t.co/qynsgtgOXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/24/19, 5:54pm, my Tower of David apt...nothing new. Haven’t been downstairs at all today so laundry 🧺 not washed.… https://t.co/fLOOTMV1Ar]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m too dumb to figure out how to use emoji keyboard anyway, so ignorance really is bliss for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyCampos Jajajajajajajajajajajajajajaka se pasó de v....🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/Vbnzm5t9Bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Wells woman survived a scary crash during Monday’s wind storm, when a tree branch shot through her vehicle’s wind… https://t.co/g2zPJZi065]]></document><document><![CDATA[We didn't realize we were making memories, we just knew we were having fun. @ Somewhere over the Rainbow https://t.co/tKyFsi1Mhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StSmallerie Venezuela has more oil than Saudi Arabia and never held back from USA. But they dont want any nation i… https://t.co/KLyVuWqlZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[be mindful, extremely selective and very intentional about the people you allow in your life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tess_Harkin I was one of 3 who voted for Al Gore in MY 6th grade mock election 😂 #imoldAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevin_barnacle Lol honestly haven’t heard that one yet. I’ve heard an older matt Nagy and Bruce Willis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JhTV3 Lol.. it all makes sense. Especially because it’s easy to just charge that card they have on file for the room 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My playlist for the past week has been baby shark, the wheels on the bus and  some song about sharing and my daught… https://t.co/VWKoxm1iSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTorontoZoo I know you try to mimic the bears' natural environment, diet, etc as much as possible, so are the po… https://t.co/WShANaXvRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding and falling in love with the man you prayed for is the most amazing feeling. God sure blessed me with the m… https://t.co/oMrIeIGfKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all my roommate is leaving tomorrow but I’m mad at this nigga...do I fold or stay strong in the name of self worth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clairevhill Ahh!! So sweet Claire! Pretty garden too. They do take a lot of work to keep up, but the results are r… https://t.co/INVDPXWUGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@labrahamson13 Not sure when that happened? Wow! The nation of Quebec????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grandin Date Night Giveaway: Win a YEAR of Free Movies for You and a Friend! https://t.co/A5QQ3de5Yl via @Roanoker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonasbrothers just had to do that to my heart didn’t you...😩 this song is AH-MAZING!!! 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hulu I didn't appreciate you guys adding on showtime without my knowledge to my next Bill. Thank God I always check my account. #WTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don’t like how people think a female should cater a man 🤷🏻‍♀️ cause I don’t serve you food you not gonna e… https://t.co/pc9u15ZBJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else feeling the time change this morning?! 🤦🏻‍♀️😴 @WGME https://t.co/y0vN9ttXNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hyygashi Yes they did! That girl wouldn’t be anything if it wasn’t for Kylie. Doesn’t even have a place to live now 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning about the advantages of large print books with @KathyKLTran @SabineMcAlpine @ThorndikePress - Reduces anxi… https://t.co/my4oXwp40n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DbenavidesMReal @HCFanego @muyevil La pongo donde quieras, ahora más te vale que remates a puerta Jajajajajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielson5374 @erinscafe with thinner or small handles. They make them for children all the time :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Fat Tuesday in the south suburbs is Paczki Day!  So delicious and a good way to splurge before Lent.  Also a Kin… https://t.co/zoBvJT3A8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quien quiere estar, está. No me vengas con la distancia, el tiempo, tu madre, la vecina, el trabajo, el miedo, el gym y spm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our @braswellsoccer girls are a special group! Loved hanging out with them today! Tuesday night vs Little Elm start… https://t.co/ORLjh52IEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shazam @Camila_Cabello @ShawnMendes #FriendshipGoals I love my bestie/big sister 💕💕💕💕 @SunMoonStarzent https://t.co/f7tnUIcBea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaySekulow Your lies and crimes are catching up to you! Disbarment and prison for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To say that I’ve been blessed is an understatement. Interning with HLSR these past three years has been the most am… https://t.co/freqsnjm0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyjenbartel @JCastroPhoto12 @adidas @footlocker And once again, we are the ones that have to adapt to men? Is it… https://t.co/Ba0yjWH22h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you gotta get knocked down lower than you have ever been, to stand up taller than you ever were]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PippiMarried @ghouldilocks85 @kerfaffle @AllanJLA @TatJB @evildanwallace @renatesol @DragonStepsOut @nomikkh… https://t.co/MUjsxkpw9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarrieNBCNews Who are the 18% of women? Seriously? Pussy grabbing, adult film star cheating (while Melania was hom… https://t.co/GaBHadn1lT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was gonna add more, but I lost my train of thought lmao. That’s adhd for u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassandraSeven And even if we did have an official language, who the hell cares? I love listening to people speak… https://t.co/sEsT171vJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bleck1022 I am relieved that no one ever cared enough about my interests to bother me with these texts and emails.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicheleDelliSan @NorseBounty @Heightzz @figue32bj Ill send you a post. Leave the address. I'm staying in NYC. Happ… https://t.co/giVfhSrZJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@tanfrance please teach this man the beauty of a french tuck and well-fitted jeans!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PacificSWIB thanks for inviting me to collaborate with you on “How to Land an Internship” talk tonight. What a gre… https://t.co/dS54IhMRdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s YOUR story? #saylavie #maudegrahamjewelry #jewelry #madewithlove @ Plainview, New York https://t.co/qrZtRTRvpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllaMacavoy I’m disappointed in this storyline. It’s really silly. And Erika, man she has one hot temper. You can… https://t.co/mpxzybBtj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good job to the Liberty Center Tiger cheer team as they are now 3x STATE CHAMPS!! ❤️ Kick some butt at nationals!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my cheeks and my double decker say hi @ World Domination https://t.co/pnORLZbCRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[And Ball OUR Eyes Out‼️😭😭😭 https://t.co/fJrIQ5kt9J My Heart just 💔 Broke for Him &amp; His Family‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOR SALE! $225,000 US Dollars Former TAXCO MODEL from Pilar. Stunning two story condominium with much light and cha… https://t.co/2Vi1NcASpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried my best to squeak out encouraging words to @lyssamf as she left for the gym. It didn’t work out well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[READY TO KICK OFF OUR SCHOOL-WIDE TOURNAMENT OF BOOKS ON MONDAY!   #ProjectLITBookClub #MarchMadness… https://t.co/YKEkmSQu5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tll631 @TieDye_Squirrel @ardenstowe @Seajay603 @AngrierWHStaff Those would go nicely with a baby canon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si pudiéramos hacer una proyección de la temporada 2019 por este juego de #SpringTraining2019 los míos @RedSox se l… https://t.co/A2gSXqjy95]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAY 2: I have accepted a challenge from @WabashPrincipal to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no revi… https://t.co/dF1XfM5crg]]></document><document><![CDATA[A pesar del trabajo en exceso que tenía mi novio ayer llego súper rápido a mi casa solo a verme, lqm😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Texas @tsalliance team had a great final morning on #CapitolHill. Sorry we missed you, @JohnCornyn! We’ll be in to… https://t.co/TVb6wjViKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiftingPhoenixx @IAMDNDL @OhioStrength I love you! I’m sorry we didn’t get to chat a little more about stuff, so I owe you a call soon!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HindsShala @Rainbow_Whisper @Jim_Peoples_ @SpeakerPelosi Yes, I remember. I left MN on 9/10, the day before our na… https://t.co/gpK9vQXCzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in bio &amp; book now 🗓  . . . . . #minklashes #expresslashes #muaatlanta #mua #lashlife… https://t.co/sbfXeUsNRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man right here has stuck by my side through everything that has ever gone right or wrong in my life. We have a… https://t.co/vF0C2r5noF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HomeopathyPlus Cholera is a deadly disease caused by bacteria in contaminated water.  Homeopathy is vitalist nonse… https://t.co/5ukaHJEFgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah Spring is a little over 2 weeks away so father Winter is sticking it to us now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nowadays you can’t tell if someone is drunk driving or just dodging all these fucking potholes in Indy. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jrprotalker Slow news day move on! Obviously trying to drum up a story/controversy. @GeoffShac]]></document><document><![CDATA[ACTS 2:38; REPENT, AND BE BAPTIZED EVERY ONE OF YOU IN THE NAME OF JESUS CHRIST FOR THE REMISSION OF SINS, AND YE S… https://t.co/2EL06czAXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump They asked if he knew of any Trump crimes, what about any other Cohen crimes caught or not, confessed to… https://t.co/MkRgntPVaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Impact Fitness - @impactptfitness in Newport, MI https://t.co/HvENsq8Dkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colorful Madagascan Sunser Moth black leather bracelet with black spinel and seaglass beads.  COPY here to purchase… https://t.co/lMa5j6DsX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re not getting pushback, you’re not pioneering. @equalman @SAP #IETour https://t.co/4p1LVaHWZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump What she is really saying is that she has the Chinese selling her clothing line and she wants the rest… https://t.co/qDkBzOL5hn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sonyairyna I'm in Canada with no AMC in the hotel https://t.co/XAfmiYKRgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[my nana is unreal, literally ran across the house in heels and no pants]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSavvyChef1 @SteveKubota @WineFoodGuide @JeremyPalmer7 @DivaVinophile @CleanDropMobile @NorthWestFDMB @FDNWHour… https://t.co/JWe3DujumS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmbJohnBolton The American journalist Cody Weddle has been detained by the venezuelan directory of intellegince. T… https://t.co/k4OdpJE8kJ]]></document></documents></author>