<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@colinobrady So impressed by your accomplishments but more so of your humble inspiring demeanor. Your @joerogan int… https://t.co/bTw3xy5JkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss my grandmother crazy ass. She was a great source of entertainment. I will call every one “a monkey mout biat… https://t.co/sLzZ2p4C2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y fue justo en ese momento q su sonrisa desapareció... #mounstrilio1  #BasicoySencillo en Long Beach, California https://t.co/gTD1TLfidz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyyyGinger @Sassyredhead20 In wasn't the fact she hurt me she just died on me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally saw a kid from my area post something about the patriots and then say he likes the Indians for baseball after lol. What a joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sundncefn @Unite4Truth These are great times to watch the Democrat Party's demise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@credly at the #IBMBlockchainAccelerator showing how they are improving the talent acquisition process. Allowing le… https://t.co/TUc3lQhbn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luizlemuz @mmfa Thank you. Cannot follow you back right now. Over the limit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Fox news and the National Enquirer are the shithole press services you must be referring to]]></document><document><![CDATA[#experiencethe6 #inspiration #motivation #coffeelover #weightloss #weightlosscoffee #fitness #healthandbeauty… https://t.co/ZnG8dM9GBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maple Springs Tudor clean and crisp, ready for a new owner. #oaklawn #DallasTX    Check out this listing:… https://t.co/VoQXcc2tDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[stoned@off@esibles weed pen and the rest i can’t say aka non disclosure stuff tbqh https://t.co/hK5UXmQVnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASUNTO DE TIEMPO, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/BvDYtXhI5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MurphyCartoons @OlmstedParks502 We now have 10,004 “persons of interest” in the Castleman vandalism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continetti: ‘We Have Room in Gitmo’ for Hoda Muthana, Alabama Woman Who Joined ISIS via @freebeacon https://t.co/61nyGaXpoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Digital media founder, Niall McGarry seeks maximum return from Joe https://t.co/tEiqikLRfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kitcars88557088 @FlyingEagle555 @POTUS Based on a phony document...  ...and firing a traitor to the Constitution a… https://t.co/I9FwyZ1Jih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judyohtweets @jdstalnaked @LifesStyleBlog @katy_fit @RichP222 @Mr_Spikey_Head @A_verynicegirl @MrsTyler78… https://t.co/xjnG8skhGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 big thing: Democrats&amp;#x27; post-Mueller plan  https://t.co/m1qAnfW3Wk #axiosam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@downeyballs @xan_desanctis @SenDuckworth Verifiable facts? You mean that infanticide on demand is only going to be… https://t.co/drQTiTyojs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I know that’s really dangerous and stupid to do but I was just a little fuckin savage and I wanted to see if h… https://t.co/DRW4jlGVoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveBellone https://t.co/JbikhokHf7 this is the other app, it showed function in NYC for Good Citizens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HLAurora63 @sonmist7 @SpeakerPelosi @SpeakerPelosi Mexico made her come and pick up her own drug supply, And for her reselling]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the only boss hogg I wanna see trending https://t.co/FaH2LSnhG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dominating day as Georgia covers for me....putting on a clinic @benmaller @BearsBarroom @ESPNDel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Planning my work. Working my plan. On the shoulders of giants I humbly stand.. @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/5zui2SgdBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my brother man😪. Only a God knows ALL of the stuff we been through together. It’s a blessing to h… https://t.co/QT3GlGoZj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone used these? I'm thinking about getting them for my back porch for the spring &amp; summer.… https://t.co/kbsdoyIqXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will get shit like. "well, you are standing up.. the water is too tall to ask a question.. stick your head back… https://t.co/UguD2G3pf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing night at Del Frisco’s in San Diego! @ Del Frisco's Double Eagle Steakhouse https://t.co/pmfvZnpyZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the beautiful Central Valley! This was along I-580 southbound around the outskirts of Tracy, CA. Why was… https://t.co/pxRUODXlz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kyrie and the Celtics been trash all of sudden wanna play good against the dubs 🤣🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do y’all blow y’all food or do yall Hasafashafas until you can chew it?😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spino_powerlegs CAAD13 shows up in the list of UCI approved frames. Any insight or movement in the industry you’ve… https://t.co/roDhihBtbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiltonHotels @doubletree Help please! At the DoubleTree Anaheim Resort $ paid for fireworks view. Unfortunately, w… https://t.co/1yImBQ3sOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some things you only see in the country. A dog walking down the road with a dead chicken it’s mouth is probably one of those things]]></document><document><![CDATA[#latepost #phonediasters #longstory #customcakes #pipingskills #rosettesforthewin #jbbake @ Jay Bear Bake Shop https://t.co/0DGKWKxsEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WritesTruths That’s why there’s no rush on the early charges. Trump probably had his lawyers prepare pardons for 6… https://t.co/Ftdgedav39]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jay we've been married for 7 years stop getting so drunk and telling people im your new gf!- Conversation happeni… https://t.co/BKlVhvHlxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Urge the Oregon Department of Agriculture to ban the use of a pesticide that's already killed 1,400 majestic ponder… https://t.co/qt6hw7iJXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sophia_Camille You can’t pair it next to the correct spelling to prove your point though 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did my roommate just turn his lamp and the lights off before 2/3 am?? Estoy: shook]]></document><document><![CDATA[A one *microwatt* voice detector using analog feature extraction and a binary neural network: https://t.co/9jmLZvKbVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adam_Jacobi I didn’t even know he was wearing a hat. That camo stuff is so good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justin_Rogers Detroit Vs Everybody is not related to this at all. It’s an actual cultural thing for Detroiters and… https://t.co/wKmeU9n749]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ideally, I’d want to put them both on a team for high Damage output, but I want this team to resist as much of the… https://t.co/PIGHDoyYZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like hearing the maroon-white chant very loudly @ThePavilionOM ! 😂 #hailstate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JoeTalkShow @dbongino @SheriffClarke @EricTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @SheriffClarke @seanhannity… https://t.co/8gy04OCV9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivien2112 @RushFamTourneys Might be my favorite from Vapor Trails! Plus I love to dream!😂  Good morning Vivien! H… https://t.co/ypLWL2p9CY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ripbiggie 22 years ago today @ Columbia University in the City of New York https://t.co/mBqqodcRrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do any of y’all wanna be in a group chat on here? Preferable one about shits and giggles on Twitter 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another nice @PACC1620 event. The Women Mean Business Lunch (yes guys are welcome also!) is a great way to meet oth… https://t.co/gxXHboaXxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen’s testimony includes three remarkable allegations against Trump: Two of them suggest that Trump was m… https://t.co/S65SfhRsBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[ever since i found out the scooby doo movies are set in ohio i cant enjoy them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys A Passion for LEARNING! Because Enquiring Minds want to KNOW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a wrap. 3-1 win and Peewee Rangers advance to @tournoipeewee Quarterfinals tomorrow 11:45am against Czech Kn… https://t.co/VecOW7RVZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAdamsEra 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂superbowl😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂like they were close to winning… https://t.co/pCl8gLZf6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandamarie2pt0 @ATT #Facts... they got me over here with no TV or nothing lol.. can’t work from home or none of that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nora is here! Mom is a warrior. ❤  Happy and healthy. 😍 https://t.co/LMAA2iUnRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I really just be in the mood to listen to junk and clog up my playlist with stuff I'll never want to listen to again]]></document><document><![CDATA[A shy Eastern Bluebird from earlier today. Experimenting with my new camera. #canon #eosr #backyardbirding @ Montgo… https://t.co/hFWBobhDX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, befriended a student that has a #vanlife Sprinter camper, which he’s open to renting.   50 states in 50 days.… https://t.co/GwFaUfBdsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came down to the night’s final 2 possessions tonight as @PCScrusaders holds off Williamstown 28-27 for @wvssac Clas… https://t.co/MUAHuSU9DC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you been clubbing all night with a chick you think is fine and then she finally steps out to the light: https://t.co/Ezax5qJX16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSagett @emuyshondt @alcaldia_ss @SSesTuyo Ok, sabelotodo cuanto costara el nuevo escudo a los capitalinos?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSPrior Typically I listen to The Intelligence and The Globalist first every day and that’s all I have time to lis… https://t.co/SpzgHxfRiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m no Lib &amp; voted for Commonsense President Trump &amp; proud of it. Can’t wait to vote again in 2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a little creative last night.  - BBQ Marinated Chicken Thighs. Applewood Smoked Bacon. Provolone Cheese. Roma T… https://t.co/0UAXC7wQON]]></document><document><![CDATA[They got Queen and Adam Lambert starting up the Oscars. What a great way to start it up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[America needs high speed trains. Cut defense 25% use for infrastructure. Rail being one of infrastructure. Rebuild… https://t.co/VauBBVsEi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duhhhhhh finally figured out b&amp;w mode on my new Samsung #9 phone 😁😁😁😁😁 https://t.co/DGxx2j29Hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyMalarkey @JackPosobiec Sometimes one can be too subtle on Twitter, right? Know what I mean? By subtle?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioWires @NonesuchRecords @ParamountPics Wow soul to squeeze on vinyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_verynicegirl Thanks for the update now I need to take a shower to clean myself up Aim 🤦‍♂️🤦‍♂️ I wish I was the… https://t.co/HeV1p2sJMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Bible app, I use my actual Bible too. Can you send me a notification to update my streak so I’ll quit losing it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week's #andnowyouknow is about earnest money.  The Washington state residential purchase and sale agreement ou… https://t.co/dqj29c0YLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I grab a card out of my wallet I have to open up the cash part just in case]]></document><document><![CDATA[A newly introduced bill in California (AB 624 by Asm. Gabriel-D) would in essence require that the phone number of… https://t.co/E0bKT0kcCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump Why you don’t resign into acceptance?  He will be POTUS for 6 more years!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerricaTaylor03 I haven't heard somebody call it an 'Andy' in a long time...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith currently rewatching Mallrats so good can't wait for Jay and Silent Bib reboot!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally. Someone made it perfect. #Saugatuck #IceCream - Drinking a Neapolitan Milk Stout by @saugatuckbrew at… https://t.co/kXuhXskELA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drumming to a WIP.  Here’s some weird video gamey arpeggi thing. . . . . #drums #drummer #drummers #drumming… https://t.co/z4jqOoztc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t say enough about how much I respect this guy right here. He has had so much hate thrown his way for nothing o… https://t.co/Tk1o7xSgeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly why did he get a slingshot from and why does he have it. This a grown man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Str8_Edge_Angel No more shield reunions we had like what 2? They didn’t make sense at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennyhardest DEVO's "Turn Around" Compilation LP Jackets - Factory Footage 2019 https://t.co/FU6hXTuKrr via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davereaboi A "nutjob" with a mouth &amp; no evidence! Never produces any evidence!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnArtist99 Bryant is going to command crazy money when that contract expires. I have to think the Cubs would ser… https://t.co/27OzINYhkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNanceAnnouncer @boomking69 @9NEWS Arguing with strangers on Twitter isn’t my thing. No one has ever seen a loaded… https://t.co/knmD5NV5FB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tytlive It's because left-wingers are defensive by nature. We defend those who can't,we don't attack!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started exploring washington.#snoqualmie #waterfalls https://t.co/kOhjUjWWqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec @realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump A child rapist and best friend , all that partying they did together and Do… https://t.co/jSbc77L3Cx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinlc555 Greg I don’t support hate by any party , all I am saying since that young lady got to Washington and me… https://t.co/xo7QpXfbBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ericbryant5 @kwilli1046 @leticiaVShep Instead of sand it's a wheelbarrow full of s*** though 🏆😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[FA wish list  Landon Collins  Trey Flowers Darius Philon Adam Humphries]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can never understand how some people are just that BROKE to steal another individuals personal belongings]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Baile de luces” #light #luces #baile #dance #antro en BYŪ San Pedro https://t.co/iKvPnoCP3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Well done sir ! Thank you for all your hard work in stopping assholes like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BriiightEyes That's what she said lmao JK I have to wait till tomorrow to go to the dentist]]></document></documents></author>