<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@liscainfluencer @SoaresLMS Todo mundo tem o direito de estar enganado. Igual vc falando de bandido e desejando o m… https://t.co/y3Eqh8DDWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xzyliac Yeah! @videocognito and I are comin’ for ya Memorial Day weekend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This might be obvious, but the thinner the rings, the less growth. Mostly means that there was a lack of precipitat… https://t.co/dTmwjXu1tK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out via team mate I am ranked #44 in the world in apex legends. I just want to say shoutout to @FaZeClan]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have so many YouTube videos filmed but I’m just not sure how I wanna start my channel; literally don’t know why I… https://t.co/lRbivrAETs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asked Jordan Jones about his decision to stay in Lexington and train. “Coach Hill and Coach Edmond have been traini… https://t.co/CbPgWHd5tu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo One of his best speeches EVER! @POTUS @realDonaldTrump knows his audience and how to deliver the good… https://t.co/HaWrMfHIOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markymarkqw They took down the article about the alumni donation, bet the response to criticism on those other thi… https://t.co/rBgJ9JInC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JorgeLara1 @DanaSenna Amigo no sea ingenuo. Este satrapa de Ganso @lopezobrador_ está desmontando con terror esos… https://t.co/QxoKrDNAXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC11_WTVD I’m sure Trump had a direct line to the guys with the chainsaws and personally told them to do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a great 21st birthday 😊 Can’t wait to have more fun with friends this weekend in Seattle, and next weekend in Kansas City!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Googled Rihanna and my bday May 27; voila! This fabulous look!  Happy Birthday Queen 👑 https://t.co/8Pbrt27cCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like the idea of kicking off the month of March in the best city in the world! Come chill with me at… https://t.co/0k163mJZfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, cancer. You can’t have Alex Trebek. Take Charlie Sheen or James Woods first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of 1, @CovCathColonels down 12-3, @FOX19Joe @clindsey70 @FOX19Jeremy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most powerful person in the world is the one that can hold their pee mid-pee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Loma Prieta Imperial Stout by @scvbrewing at @scvbrewer — https://t.co/dTLBiMgSac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConradMBlack is absolutely right about the reality of conducting business in countries where payoffs are the cost… https://t.co/nwd9l9MOeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX2News #TheNine I'm on my way back home to Detroit after a 2 day booking on Empire...episode 16! #tcreal… https://t.co/s0kLdBeVQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming up on the Randy Wang hour - you really cant afford to live here, bird hoarders, and weed wednesday! @ KABC-A… https://t.co/vGIaIUdauI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greg_Maden_HDMS @PicininiDwayne @ChrisGHDMS @WorcesterBrian @THDGarvey @LindsayBertell1 Great people! Great class!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealErnieGreen NXT is a lot like mid 90s Raw. 1 hour show. Really good matches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DESMARAIS. Vous préfèreriez qu'ils s'investissent en Ontario? https://t.co/aM4QVFD2N2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNewsMACH It looks like a plump Mellon, but in monochrome it is difficult to tell whether it is ripe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an update to clear up all rumors and questions...  -Guy Thomas has retired -Maggy has been moved to another… https://t.co/E5YS1qT6Cx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mid 5th: Coastal Carolina 2, Washington 1. Due up for the Huskies in the B5 will be Nick Roberts, Mason Cerrillo and Ben Baird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StlCardsCards @CornLongust I think Matt Carpenter would be the guy to talk to about plate discipline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s up with this? Snow, finally, but on March 1st. #NYC @ Central Park https://t.co/6c6Yf0D0X1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daveon Odom pass to Furb Mitchell for layup. Jack Arnold a steal and @cooper_bizjak a finish. @auroraathletics 72,… https://t.co/EumruNSNUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like Moose are back in town... @ Jones's Outdoor Emporium &amp; Nudist Colony https://t.co/NezeEIAdUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are looking for a buyer on 246 61st Street Avalon, NJ 08202 #Avalon #NJ  #realestate https://t.co/0XE0dbCXO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuJu_Bee53 I'm Looting!!! The Avengers got it and when it's over I'll have a couple big screens and iPads to sell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweet2t @MarthaStewart Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/tMeAqNstna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@btsssssvt @ibleedpassion @reggierocket_ @ILoveBeinBlack Never heard of people being this scared of lizards before]]></document><document><![CDATA[and for the final hour of my 6th year of recovery, I shall play Clean on repeat 🤷🏻‍♂️🤷🏻‍♂️ @taylorswift13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TangerineBank Hi, if I were to open a USD savings account, can I deposit USD cash through a scotiabank atm? If not, how?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Source: The Pittsburgh Steelers are closing in on a deal to send star WR Antonio Brown to the Buffalo Bills.  #NFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a book I wrote, edited, and laid out with @AbTabletop and I’m so happy with it. It’s such a surreal feeling… https://t.co/eDX39dUlXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieReichwein1 @Vicky4Trump Did he find the missing millions his wife spent?  Why has that story disappeared?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirstenPowers @benshapiro I'm a conservative Kirsten. I do not agree that the boys were disrespectful. The Indian… https://t.co/DQDgrXfhCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a joke! Nobody yells "THIS IS MAGA COUNTRY" —that’s a scene straight out of a movie, when the big bad proverbi… https://t.co/TzYfMyIxkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI: An asteroid hit earth 12,000 years ago and triggered a 1.4k year long ice age. When all the ice melted the sea… https://t.co/Uf6gpsWmg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just SO MAD that I’m not as pretty as @Zendaya  ... like WHY ME?!?!? WHY COULDNT I BE BLESSED WITH GOOD GENES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Hasn’t he benefited adequately from his years as a corporate shill?!  He is not a loyal citizen but a moneygrubber!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trish_regan @louisvelazquez Like when we installed Saddam as dictator in Iraq.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TianaTheFirst @Barnes_Law So the DEA sucks. The ATF sucks. The FBI sucks. And TSA sucks. Maybe we should create another #organization]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moonrakerkih @margarethodge @JoRichardsKent @thetimes So what, its not about limiting immigration, its about havin… https://t.co/GiIQjiYZ0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Ilean is her name now what is her Husband name now I guess they go to this church 7th day Aveve church over he… https://t.co/8UnYaUGUPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nigga he’s mad at the fact that at nigga shooting 28% from the 3 hit a 3...]]></document><document><![CDATA[As expected, I 100% want to fuck my own self after getting my hair cut.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FinishTicket ive been listening on repeat for 2 days when is it dropping officially so i can share w my friends 😌👉🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaloneTerra Thank you for always loving me even when I don’t think I’m worth loving! Thank you for being my rock a… https://t.co/KAqQrXmAhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidYoungNB I try to use it for the purposes @rickmurdockagc mentioned, but lately people I follow for said persp… https://t.co/91HmKzEbvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Absolutely ridiculous no apology for fake shit posted here. @realDonaldTrump fake news comes from house republicans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cyber Security at Disney should be linked to senior executive performance metrics and compensation. Vote to protect… https://t.co/KJYWLKLqRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked for 6pm as I want to provide some good sounds for those getting that first drink on, the crew all girding t… https://t.co/Gp7rOUibxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les Habs jouent tellement mal depuis hier que j'allais écouter mon nouveau Blu-ray 4K de Black Panther mais après l… https://t.co/5xeRFzVEnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smb_ryan Yes that is the game boy BTAS. I also have the converter to play it in the SNES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBanryu @UltimaShadowX I really enjoyed SuMo for the story. Team skull were very enjoyable and lusamine was a good villain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markneefuzz @11DanTheMan11 Gah. Now I’m torn. … maybe I should bring the bacon with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Candy Roaster Grisette by Twin Leaf Brewery @ Twin Leaf Brewery — https://t.co/pVto8xlkbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @BuffaloJimmyz @realDonaldTrump If I’m not getting the p, I’m not paying with my tax dollars!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loaded Monday in Decatur Illinois for Minneapolis. Unloaded and reload and two drop California by Thursday afternoo… https://t.co/8Z5sUblW4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstuardoReinoso @barcelonaSC Las directivas tienen el control del club sin ser fiscalizados, al menos no deberían… https://t.co/H02xtBN7mF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early work edition of #AvsTwitterPsychic tonight. Going with the goal scoring machine that is big ole Carl Soderberg! @Avalanche]]></document><document><![CDATA[[LPfan2018] sings Battle Symphony by Linkin Park, what an incredible voice on The Voice! #music #karaoke #sing  https://t.co/HNToLq7KDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zypisfy @Cern_lXXl @noah_nonsense @Tribal_Eagle70 @BiblePoop @EndtimeApostasy @horusrage @SoberHootOwl… https://t.co/x3k9vM1Aeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iIIcoveryou Thanks! Be sure to sign my petition to help #MakeBroadwayWildAgain! Click below and share it with othe… https://t.co/94vOQeWfWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Binotto on himself, Mercedes, Arrivabene, Marchionne and more  https://t.co/l1LQL4rgNP #F1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephdebeau Definitely beautiful you are!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss you everyday Lisa.. find me somehow be in my life Lisa I really do love you... https://t.co/Y16vbn8abM]]></document><document><![CDATA[High winds cancelled our flight, but thanks to Amtrak, we’ll be in DC for tonight’s alumni event and meeting with o… https://t.co/wRxHrqC9Ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJFaron You know that's replacement fencing that started in September by the army corps of engineers-- not "the wall"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@6ryeson 😂 a little respect is due but they don’t even have my major thooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, an unusual order came through today. This pair of Signature Tele pickups is going into a... Gibson Melody Maker… https://t.co/TzAChH0v3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Milk Stout Nitro by @LeftHandBrewing @ Craftsman Row Saloon — https://t.co/X8lICZWYSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gordonkeith @Dave_L_Barnett @realDonaldTrump @AOC Age is only a number and can be what you want it to be like gender.]]></document><document><![CDATA[☄️🌸🔥⚡️⭐️🌟💥I Present The Photo Of The Day!!!💥🌟⭐️⚡️🔥🌸☄️ . . Photo by me @mygolfinggirls  . Will you look at this!?!?… https://t.co/CPu1Bs36sn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Torrance Barrens Dark Sky Preserve https://t.co/2kkDpvKUFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This just shows how STUPID you are Donnie boy! A judge will decide Cohen's sentence, not Congress.… https://t.co/Rv9EGuAC7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got third place at the Smash Ultimate tournament at "The Drop" with Lucario! What an inclusive place run by the lov… https://t.co/slvxn98eUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@jorgeramosnews Saliste bien solo porque eres mejicano, y .@lopezobrador_ intercedió por tì..pero en las mazmorras… https://t.co/4fXz0vTFT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thunderstorms on the porch would really hit the spot right about now. #sodaksummers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swipathefox @Simplemachines_ Smh. Kings gonna Kings https://t.co/kQxSrKKdQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are more book I recommend 💜💜 📚 #blackhistorymonth 💙💙 #readdaily #childrensbooks #library #swfl #capecoral… https://t.co/afRM978xaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn't have asked for a better week ending. After good lunch meeting with amazing people..! Village boy at the mo… https://t.co/q45MYCeQDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m only in school to better my chances at landing a job in the area of non-profit work and jobs I care about. It’s… https://t.co/hsWtGf8MiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andrewemcameron @CNN Why is it we still kill babies like neanderthals?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwolfers It's as though Mother Jones was reading my mind: https://t.co/crCe3eTH8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanWritehead @GailSimone @prince So True.  My man Prince had a way with words.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The North Maricopa county "orographic rain machine" has kicked in over the past 2hours as the third moisture surge… https://t.co/AfWdRZBlA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sexyarmpit @ECFNJ Nia has terrrrrible ring gear. It’s so unflattering WHAT IS WITH THE HIP SHIELDS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines to #1...  I post a lot of ish that would boil most women over and I catch shyt, believe it but to… https://t.co/LEaoAPv7AK]]></document><document><![CDATA[BP back to optimal on second last day of #QardioChallenge https://t.co/WDBdpvT41v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iTeachPLTW @PLTWorg @microbit_edu @m4ttbit @Mrsklgarcia I know someone who would disagree lol.  Am I right @Mrsklgarcia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooo I need this at some point. Not right this moment, but soon. Imma finish working on me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andre_Reed83 @TheBillsMafia @BuffFanatics Rather have juju, it's the real reason the lady is upset]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit. After waiting 2 weeks for this eBay seller to send my poster, he ends up sending the wrong thing. Fucking awful experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my mic today!! I’m officially ready to talk shit!! https://t.co/bzqnLKf58r]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the leftist controlled CO state government is seriously debating the elimination of the death penalty in our st… https://t.co/Nxc4qejiK5]]></document></documents></author>