<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @AnnCoulter That means he “knows” her.  He might even know her in the Biblical sense.  Who knows...Right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here I stand with a couple of the leaders for New York Life African American Marketing Unit. We have been blessed t… https://t.co/7IJ0J9Dofn]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you ever hear me playing my favorite ost or any fav anime/video game theme song either mind your business or get hip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quinn and Madeline wanted to get in on the reading challenge and post some of their favorite books and challenge th… https://t.co/6FVFiwxWdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[You nailed it through the heart Tucker. Tucker Carlson: Yes, there is a fascist threat to America. But it's not fro… https://t.co/cIjYy4VdRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like @Lin_Manuel to pop out. I would also like him to crash the #WHCD this year. #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[this pic describes me and my roomie way too well https://t.co/oVnRXJZeBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sallyboo27 I love you sally!! Don’t worry you aren’t alone you got us!! Always and forever ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holly_dellinger You’re beautiful holly. I love and miss you everyday ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that Annie is over, can somebody find me some tickets so l can see my home team play. I didn’t get watch the ga… https://t.co/15rNUdQWyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other weird thing is that my cellphone doesn't work consistently in my home. Sometimes it works but most of the… https://t.co/KujF0epyzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gen Ed provides an awakening of intellectual curiosity in students - they interact with big, comprehensive, troubli… https://t.co/8iRKwzdjhb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @CharlieDaniels How did people who believe in policies that fit in countries we are at war with get electe… https://t.co/O1XwgzK2xl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in Savannah, GA, check out this Accounting/ Finance/ Insurance job via the link in our b… https://t.co/LyslVQHxy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m proud of these guys no matter what that score board said last night. one hell of a season.  #SOE #districtchamps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you! And thank you my dear friend and sister @ELEANORANNNWADI, @IlwadElman, @1AlfredoZamudio and @WomanTreaty… https://t.co/xm9qqX338B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to our fabulous  @GTGrizzlyBears second grade parents for meeting with us to discuss their child’s growth… https://t.co/FFIs6kBjAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is clever. #funniness #lol #grin #humorous https://t.co/F5MRLjQD8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[i told my mom there's no reason for humans to drink cow milk and she yelled at me for trying to change her diet. i… https://t.co/eS5Y0GiQHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to junior Lady Cat @snowdenscott22 today! 🏀🎂⛹️‍♀️  We hope you have a GREAT birthday on Game Day! https://t.co/eYzU9vtOx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASavageNation Yes it’s concerning. But I live in an Intel community and it helps us 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[New show coming! Dog’s Most Wanted is coming this year on @wgnamerica #DogWGNA #DogsMostWanted #DogPound… https://t.co/hxwl5Gdsbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Himalayan Salt Lamps: They need #nofilter and I need one of them. #tinyprettythings #himalayansaltlamp… https://t.co/TeW7WfpRTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing i love more than going to the barbershop and hearing all these niggas tell stories about how they cheat on… https://t.co/04GgriRS56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmarettoKitten @elliemaygottasa @DDSSpectacle @bmandy1012 @BrandtBrickell @erikmenendez848 @Mochene @AOC You are p… https://t.co/Cb37J22EaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff @JL_BK_NY There is little doubt who is the chief executive of this country and it's not Donald Trump… https://t.co/DtVzQLtyOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annuraonaik @Acosta He doesn’t speak for me... or anyone else with a working brain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I barely made $20,000 in 2016 but somehow am being audited by the state of Iowa where I “lived” for less than 3 mon… https://t.co/iybdN4Rfs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are they comparing Kavanaugh and the tv actor? Is it because they’re both liars?  #morningjoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then people say I’ll never be able to do what I did before. And I try and do things and I just can’t. I’m so weak and it’s so frustrating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone pray that my tax return is fat as fuck so i can buy myself out of my lease 😍😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity The Dems are falling aren’t they?  Their desperation is apparent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krosenthal14 @EdKrassen @BarackObama @MichelleObama Awe how sweet! Wendy is beautiful and it sounds like it comes… https://t.co/Gv9vN5bsNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite time is spent at the beach 😎🌴⛱️ @ Folly Beach, South Carolina https://t.co/kKv3JYEq7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brett Lashbrook &amp; Eric Wynalda from the @lvlightsfc announce their partnership with the @lasvegasymca… https://t.co/FOKeejwSVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don’t tip or don’t feel entitled to tip you’re just a bad person period lol don’t go out to eat if you can’t… https://t.co/iBig0GM0zy]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine being able to have a close friendship with a guy that has a girlfriend.. no female would ever let that happ… https://t.co/8EicT3tp11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump The Deep State is mostly in DC so I don't care what they want. I live in Texas...I want… https://t.co/QmFu1qCuf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mobile World Congress 2019: Doctor uses 5G to direct surgery live onstage - CNN https://t.co/W8HeUenoV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adjunctprofessr @AdamsHasten @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Just keep it up guy,  people will see you for wjat you really… https://t.co/3T9ZIC4iau]]></document><document><![CDATA[11:28 on a Tuesday night is not a convenient time to get all hangry for chicken tikka masala...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely Awesome!!! Standing with my fellow Canadians that work hard for the prosperity of our country giving us… https://t.co/E4cboHMTBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re-commit!... join Saturday 9am corejamfitness 💥R U Ready! $16 single class! FREE for members! #TorchCalories… https://t.co/CyfG5vbsKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know if this has to do with the full moon last night but I’m so hungry today and haven’t stopped eating since I woke up.🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone told me I keep me feelings blocked in and I realize I do that A LOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t all the rides in fantasy land are terrifying like on Snow White the evil queen tried to kill all the 7 dwar… https://t.co/MogeIAP2Ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist My great grand parents came from Italy but I don’t know where. I’m 62. They spoke broken English. The… https://t.co/OYQJOzaoOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got really excited that I got 2 oranges from Kroger for .20¢ until I ate one and it tasted horrible 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wrinkles aren't looking so bad in comparison... #madagascar  #oldlady @ Bay Trail Middle School https://t.co/EqwWlKhpV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early basket today from @mervm_22 ! @raptors905 @ Raptors905 https://t.co/hTBZwqs8OU]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my old Myspace songs came on in the bar ln and I lost my goddamn MIND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephensbrent Oh but depending on the admin support, many of those things are actually essential, if you want to r… https://t.co/7TVXcqwQ16]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then I tried being as pretty as they are #hitemwittheflex lol https://t.co/jpNpiHZicq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosasgamenight Hopefully they’ll make it past the first round. I voted and they were at like 29%]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep reminding myself it OK that I don’t know what I want in live!!! I’m young]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeff_gluck If @JEarnhardt1 wins today, there’s gonna be some kind of celebration happening!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@howlercon Invite back: @EaddyMays. I mean, does anyone really need to ask why? Amazing, badass, and SO ENGAGED wit… https://t.co/fLIjQpG14h]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t make it on here tomorrow, I wanted to send my best wishes to Marjory Stoneman Douglas HS. It’s already b… https://t.co/09LLFQWkpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @Jar_O_Cats Multiple resignations, Secretaries USAF, NAVY, FEMA, QH COMMS.  On Friday......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black women r not fucking accessories to u Blackfisher. Literally need to go get some real professional help.… https://t.co/serJS28ifA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave_Harden @IlhanMN You know this tarnishes you, right? You've also managed to throw dirt on Obama with your idio… https://t.co/fLNlqt1kFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GridironSchol91 @BrandonHerFFB @mikefreemanNFL Bullshit. Kraft paid for a second slave. He’s in this up to his eyeballs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My old high school compadre’, Beau Sylvester, was on House Hunters @hgtv tonight. It airs again at 11 Pm MST. I set… https://t.co/gYLnPDC9uU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss living in Havelock!!  I miss being near water!!  😳🤗😁 #AtlantaisLandlocked 😶 ImreallyaMermaid 🤓😉😆… https://t.co/Wm9Gw61k46]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words cannot describe how proud I am of @EKUHoops squad. The hardest working crew in the OVC and the best group of… https://t.co/DKPGUD7fKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mantra 🙏🏾🧘🏽‍♀️ BUT THE LORD IS WITH ME LIKE A MIGHTY WARRIOR JEREMIAH 20:11 🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🔹🧘🏽‍♀️ #yogafriends… https://t.co/ACHU9pcNL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[You probably can’t read that little text in the bottom.. this is a 96oz box.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love looking at videos I took and how much fun I was having in the moment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ce_murphy I’ve seen a couple authors do newsletter only serials. A section of a short story per email for a few months that’s NL specific.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBONAMASSA Crossroads (Steve Vai as the devil 😈)? La Bamba? Just curious...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepPressley @Ilhan Why is it that the Trump supporters  can initiate such hate and racism towards blacks hispanics and  muslims?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Candids only 😉 @ Pittsburgh International Airport https://t.co/mZQrzC1IUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking bad (@ ARIA Resort &amp; Casino - @arialv in Las Vegas, NV) https://t.co/EsIWJqBcmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cumcusion @XtinaG @Violaine_cq @90sBellaDonna I’m just here to tell my story lmaoooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessblank_ Omg from the beginning it was obvious that she was just there to be famous]]></document><document><![CDATA[Step 1: Have a grateful heart. Step 2: repeat!  #youcantoo #gratefullness @ Tabor, New Jersey https://t.co/eVPflrrkxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was super excited to see the lighthouse 😊 📍San Diego, CA 2019 @ San Diego, California https://t.co/2jPbCbr9ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fablefy @YourLifePart2 @BiscottiNicole @thewrightleader @DisruptedTv @MaireCervenak @ShiftParadigm @TaraMartinEDU… https://t.co/xFKpxaOR04]]></document><document><![CDATA[The things we get up to.. That’s a wrap on classes til mid April. Time to direct a play. #OnCamera #WorkingItOut… https://t.co/PkA4w2TA6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I committed, I climbed and today I CONQUERED transform_20 🙌🏼💪🏼. . I wasn’t sure I would make it when week one start… https://t.co/O27l7SmkVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to try to diet this time also. I just want to lose 10-15 pounds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kalrina Pierson GIRL TAKE OF THE FAKE WIG SO YOUR HEAD CAN GET SOME AIR DONALD FRONT GIRL FOR B's HE's DONE NOTHIN… https://t.co/HwJ0GnbWmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevens6129 @realJoseLazcano @AnnaBrosche @lennycurry What was childish about his response?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you rather be stuck in space craft or in a submarine?? I’m curious 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually think I have a headache from all the overthinking I’ve done today 😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a fun four years watching @lincoln_216 persevere through injury on the football field, basketball court,… https://t.co/8idTN0z15Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Stanley Donen during the In Memoriam at the #Oscars⁠?! How is that possible? Did I blink and miss his name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly? So tired of being home.. so so tired of it, but I can’t complain bc I put myself in this position in this… https://t.co/EOt6qfUQLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know, like I need MORE stuff to do... but @jbzivko said she’d partner with me to get through the TED Masterclass!… https://t.co/oc0jcOQALd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles I hate to be a bitch but can people please retweet my pinned tweet and help me save my lizard? I’m so… https://t.co/V4sqyJbhMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The World gets you. Not a cult. @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr  @LindseyGrahamSC  @GeraldoRivera  @AnnCoulter… https://t.co/jGtCi2twX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeautyChickee ME BECAUSE THE JONAS BROTHERS ARE COMING BACK https://t.co/bBAAjjWLn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer Husband &amp; I out of the country.. no tRump in our faces!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my cousin makes friends with people she doesn’t know over social media but she won’t text you to make sure you’re ok...]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Nigga Will 😒Have A Bitch Blocked 👀🙅But Sleeping Right Next To Her .🤷🏾‍♀️😂 #mylifestory]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jukehorse50 Unfortunately for us, Khrushchev saw further into the future than any of us could ever imagine.  ✔  We… https://t.co/05oxkpruCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UTChargerTom @broken_medic @JSOPIO Awwww!  Thank you, Tom.  Hope you are doing well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love Rep. Dan Crenshaw, he is always so good at explaining what is happening in Congress and so easy to understand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's wellness table will be featuring a FYUL- Blueberry Green Tea Fresca! Did you know that natural sources of c… https://t.co/PR4EsjPgO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SherylKlingbeil Still healing, but out of the woods, so to speak! It's because I had only a small tear and a parti… https://t.co/h6M4o6i7J8]]></document></documents></author>