<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[5 native kids in a room talking about how incredible this @Kehlani drop is and how re-inspired we are! Lit that artРђд https://t.co/OozDs8vKGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lraitt This is why people donРђЎt trust politicians nor should they.  Jody Wilson Raybould would make a great conserРђд https://t.co/pgX38ttRHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I canРђЎt understand how or why you have so many followers. The misinformation that you spew is crazy. People neРђд https://t.co/rwhd2bn1X6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huber strikes out one but the Aztecs manage to score one run (E3). Aztecs up 1-0 heading into the bottom of the first. #AZPreps365 #azhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think a counter suit against the father for reckless dissemination of sperm might be warranted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want either you or me to win this prize. Please  help. https://t.co/d5rvywFKlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GingerJoye @JordiVilasuso Ginger, I think all of these people are crazy. ­ЪўЏ­ЪўЏ I think Dylan should be recast and heРђд https://t.co/GWD1AfCMo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always forget that there are actually good guys out there. Thanks to the boy from tinder who just did my homework for reminding me:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Representing the potential in all things indigounveiled #gold #diamonds #jewels Inscribed with the Latin wordРђд https://t.co/Br5vapytM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@webdevdave1 @freeCodeCamp I have been raising money for @hpplnj for about as long as the Amazon smile program hasРђд https://t.co/FjyHFoO292]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSG_54 @SpicyPurritos @RogueWolf2001 @NCLady50 @jmkillingnyc @Anthony4242 @AuntTritsy @TheSarge11 @louisanamomРђд https://t.co/SDEqIJwzVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out near #Timber, #Oregon. We were trying to get to #Cochran #Pond which is 1,788 ft elev. With the #snow, we couldРђд https://t.co/SMYsVKUVyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrussell20941 @RBPundit Are you brand new??  We've always known their names. That's NEVER been an issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HeWorkin and back doing what he loves. Email me at Van@OfficialVanJohnson.com to book your next tattoo appointmentРђд https://t.co/m105yg7a68]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessphoenix2018 Aw!  I want to them them home with me!  Please Jess!  ­ЪўЅ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a better idea. why not make a blue suit w S on it, re shoes, &amp; red cape? It's Super, Super, Super Scampi !]]></document><document><![CDATA[The QUEEN theonlymayhem AllThat90s Abbey Drag Race https://t.co/3i1VC9nShM https://t.co/pspJOrjH4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[#U├▒aNatural #Ba├▒oDeAcr├Гlico #Esmaltado #NailPolish #ORGANICNails  ESCR├ЇBEME WHATSAPP 8184769966 Judith Dom├Гnguez enРђд https://t.co/HfbIjiqalv]]></document><document><![CDATA[iРђЎm so glad my phone screen is shattered iРђЎm going to go psycho right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sulliview Or maybe you want to start talking to the adults in the room before you start making allegations about FРђд https://t.co/tni41QJ2TH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feels like a good day to re-up this:  Shoot Someone In a Major U.S. City, and Odds Are YouРђЎll Get Away With It https://t.co/knQ6BD5nUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Puddinn_Head16 @hane_1964 @lenlucas46 @FinleyRhea2 @NahBabyNah @ShotsRangOut @IceMule__Nation @LissaLove123Рђд https://t.co/Wejwn1Yzfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[So fierce. yilena_hernandez owning it on the runway rocking @SmileyFaceJonez at artheartsfashion New York Fashion WРђд https://t.co/ZOjitezW5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cover22_ Rottys are cool. The Roman Rottys are as tall as a English Mastiff. We had one and we was the best big baby. RIP Hooch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscar tried drowning me/ teaching me how to swim by throwing me in this]]></document><document><![CDATA[HavenРђЎt taken a long bath in a long time­Ъў│. Taking the suggestions from a friend and niece. Taking a little time inРђд https://t.co/ytm2yp7OwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was literally at the concert where Nick announced he had diabetes and I cried the entire drive home because I thoРђд https://t.co/K6OospcY3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iwork24 @russ_ayers @TrueEyeTheSpy Indiana is big with the sex trafficking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcspocky After a bad week abroad and home ­ЪЈа trump has the guts to strangle and kill the United States ­ЪЄ║­ЪЄИ flag whicРђд https://t.co/wBfLfk0rKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like last week with the girls, our bigger classifications all fall in the Regional Finals.   Still a great showingРђд https://t.co/DXNPMwJJ23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krispykuf @hulu just take all of them damn commercials or at least switch them up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blue_angel0126 @saferprint @ThalaBeratung @SamosumSihammm @CarolynNewsom @BiggiPommerin @viajanteblueРђд https://t.co/a7cB6dDcH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Santa Barbara CA Tue Feb 26th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Chance Of Rain Lo 50 WEDNESDAY Rain Hi 56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BedazzleCats @TVInsider I preferred the more serious episodes, but Nikki Heat and That 70РђЎs Show made me LOL. #10yearsOfCastle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PFDSullivan @deannadurante @PPDTroyBrown @PhilaHomicide @TheScottCharles @AGirlInPhilly @jockowillink @SOA_USA Great job D!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chartel77 @Kassanmccan @yosemitehker @BLMWHB @BLMWyoming @Blueequus775 @lindaleblanc111 Damn Straight! They areРђд https://t.co/xFBmzPcfn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[soooo first thank you all so freaking much for the love and support yesterday... I know I havenРђЎt updated you all oРђд https://t.co/t9KMefpv48]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if your pay was averaged like we average student grades? Students shouldnРђЎt have to carry the weight of earlieРђд https://t.co/yS9GJB6TKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KickSomeNash @theskinnypop @elainadsmith I dunno ­Ъцћ but I'd be happy to take the #WhiteCheddar and #AgedWhiteCheddar off your hands lol ­ЪДђ­ЪЇ┐­ЪЇ┐­ЪўІ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cars #suvs #predator #moviecharacter #lookalike #frontgrill ­ЪџЌ @ Gainesville, Florida https://t.co/ITd1OoKzqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bourgeoisalien Incase you missed it, she knows best. I mean she was just re-elected! ­ЪЎё #FuckFeinstein]]></document><document><![CDATA[This team inspired me to come up with the idea for #TackleReading on #ReadAcrossAmerica day! Thanks @RedskinsCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAIT @Alanis  was just listening to РђюIronicРђЮ and realized that like, rain on wedding days arenРђЎt that ironic. Weather is totes unpredictable]]></document><document><![CDATA[No caption needed! Tim McGraw is a stud!  Great time celebrating Andy's Birthday. Always stay humble and kind!Рђд https://t.co/8CyOTA0H9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stlukesportsmom @PhinsTweets @SportsTalkBarry @AOC Sure i wouldn't encourage any parent to smoke dope with there cРђд https://t.co/77s1yBJsIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_sipher @Teddysmom1 Yes he should have. For his current depression and ill health, I say to him Boo f***ing hoo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIME TO RATIO TOM, PEOPLE. One can NEVER have enough fries.   @creynoldsnc have you seen this deeply wrong take?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaleyHanna IРђЎll probably join the crowd Hahahha I just didnРђЎt wanna be the only one with a knock off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday evening, North Myrtle Beach (Cherry Grove), SC. First time here--won't be my last!  #hellowarmweather  . .Рђд https://t.co/pXQJVOk3hM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelgetsindy @doozerblake @crsofr we all know heРђЎs a corn-trarian (iРђЎll see myself out) https://t.co/DobQXSHK4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themarketswork @farm_live @GenFlynn @DawsonSField @drawandstrike @STUinSD @HeshmatAlavi @MonsieurAmericaРђд https://t.co/JptmEMFemE]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@IlhanMN on the Islamophobes and war hawks who are working overtime on her failure: "They would like us to be afraРђд https://t.co/Gu4rCwOdfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AineMcAuleyCros @mrorahilly @seanna68 @HeidiMessenger @Drniallmc @BookHubPublish @DrConorHogan @karengallen2Рђд https://t.co/N9aPAHY1p1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5 of the book challenge by @LiteracyLerdahl . I challenge @downlinker to post a favorite book for 7 days and taРђд https://t.co/zUe6xAWmPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics @twertz55 Yes. I will not vote for a candidate who lacks either or both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamroooo sometimes I use them interchangeably but IРђЎm guessing itРђЎs bad form to use them both in a paper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews @Carmen23379700 He insisted and demanded they be his РђюadvisersРђЮ so their roles as РђюchildrenРђЮ became nulРђд https://t.co/IzKCsDFh3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 years ago, i discovered a singer from chattanooga on younow who i thought was absolutely amazing. over the years,Рђд https://t.co/gSD5WZ5VNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 IРђЎll hold my nose and vote for him if he gets rid of Trump. Just pray he has a good running mate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you like green eggs and ham? K Ss @BlackshearKISD predicted whether they would like or not like Green Eggs and HРђд https://t.co/XYJRAF7cCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[ItРђЎs apparently New York Fashion Week but my luggage is still en route from Atlanta. Well hey this jacket is stillРђд https://t.co/KlPoggbwCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Good morning Ed thatРђЎs just too much to hope for on a Monday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dark age is nigh.  The United States doesnРђЎt deserve @elonmusk anyhow. #wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lamentablemente Clara falleci├│ hoy. Que en paz descanses y libre como siempre fuiste!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited for the @mushroomhead show later on tonight at the whiskey a go go in Hollywood­Ъцў­Ъќцcome say whatРђЎs up if yРђд https://t.co/Bm196xJfNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crankywxguy LI and NJ snow freaks are not happy with you...it would seem from this map you are extending your warmРђд https://t.co/UcsZaEHdKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kissimmeepolice Congrats and welcome to the family from @FloridaChiefs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Podcast series with brilliant scientists? Cant wait. ­ЪЉЈ­ЪЉЈ­ЪЉЈ#PewMarineFellows @pewenvironment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miabella4u @DanielsFamily00 @MidwestArea @tedlieu The Democrats are really bad at keeping track of details!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart still hurts from that terrible event and my only solace is that God will see me thru. So, I pray that thosРђд https://t.co/t0cZXj91Ud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iDavey I was the effeminate nerd abandoned by his biological parents in a rural  homophobic Jamaican community whoРђд https://t.co/pIpSyD5OAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliafspa I say no. What we do is personally interview the teens including asking questions that get at whether thРђд https://t.co/bEsLTVQeEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilhova1 Lol @ Did I stutter? Well since you a beast, I may wanna challenge you in the kitchen.. cause IРђЎM A BOSSРђд https://t.co/OqCJDI7pk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing at fauxtography again. One of my models was a bit more compliant. Take a guess which one. #fauxtography @ TРђд https://t.co/zVmFzxyxN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soo the Jonas Brothers are back together and 8 yr old me is freaking out]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the commencement address today. In between tears. #proud2bcia @ The Culinary Institute of America https://t.co/N8hsVfmi1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's shameful an disgusting, for Trump to take money appropriated for military, constr. projects, military pay, anРђд https://t.co/g6NH5hZ1tH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DaSickesst Never ignore it. I believe your gut and vibes are the biggest tell all about a person. I can know a peРђд https://t.co/5bBGSG4smx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ariiee__ ThatРђЎs fine I need my ass beat anyway for the shit I tolerated ­Ъўѓ­Ъїџ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dana4bama okay..... IРђЎm off tomorrow and IРђЎm going to start my day with going to the gym....please keep me in yourРђд https://t.co/X9oc48ZIed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coincidentally? There was a gas line explosion in the same area a day before the mystery boom was heard  https://t.co/59IR4Rftzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks­Ъўю.... i know you already have a job as an engineer but IРђЎm in need of a crew chief! Let me know if youРђЎre  evРђд https://t.co/iOsMq0zVWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[12:44am ab to lose my mind so i make a call. nothing more re assuring than to hear immediately after one ring РђюhellРђд https://t.co/SDKnjGeLPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think IРђЎm going to stop wearing fun clothes and having cool hair just because some people donРђЎt like it- youРђд https://t.co/zMx918In6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PodSaveAmerica Rep. IIhan Omar, is she saying out loud what some are thinking? $38 billion in military aid to IsraРђд https://t.co/c9E7hkI07T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chances are you know several people who  need something (perhaps nutrition) to help them FEEL better! We are in theРђд https://t.co/m0DQuFP3Xj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoteWojcik @Visionzeronet Wearing seat belts and staying off the phone reduces deaths as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY does my dad keep trying to talk to me knowing damn well I canРђЎt respond]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna know who was shushing everybody? So we gon act like all them didnРђЎt just fall through the floor...­Ъце]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started my day at 5 am and now ending it to start it at 6 am again tomorrow. All the weeks extra shifts and extra hРђд https://t.co/T0zWVzlmGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next drumline competition is this coming Saturday, March 16 at Colony High School in Ontario. Show time is 2:10pm-Рђд https://t.co/ObGNiJzCYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#growthmindset #whatdoesntkillyou #experience #homelessness #chronichunger #lessonslearned #lifelessons #imtrying tРђд https://t.co/lcN3KxaMlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatureAttracts @LoganJrChef Whoa Unbelievable!!!! ( @joeylawrence voice #blossom)  https://t.co/MtlGtP9Xhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a45cooper @marcosanchezorg It is tiring. I have been working 6 day weeks for the best of 3.5 months. At first it wРђд https://t.co/gPYHal1KwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh You said it Alan.   Psychiatrically incapacitated. Trump is a clear and present danger to the country]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kharyp @CheriJacobus Awww, you had the Michael Jackson РђюThrillerРђЮ jacket.  Only the coolest kids had that back in the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last rehearsal before the SEC Tournament starts!!! First game at 11ET: Florida vs. Ole Miss on SEC Network!!Рђд https://t.co/SVZeCuTTzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only upside to having fraud on your credit card is finding out all the autopay shit you had set up that canРђЎt bРђд https://t.co/wmdCJiDmSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am more excited to ride this vs the rides.   IРђЎm going to need a fast pass for this ­Ъўѓ  #Disney #NowMoreThanEver]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice crowd arriving at our #MarchBreak Open House at @AlgonquinOV Waterfront Campus in @PembrokeEcDev. 300+ registrРђд https://t.co/JdALAR3gpr]]></document></documents></author>