<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[COLUMBUS, Ohio – David L. Dobbins, 39, of Urbancrest, Ohio, was sentenced in U.S. District Court to 240 months in p… https://t.co/kXMk5MmV2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DuPontCC1920 new 9,000 sq.ft. Golf Training Center, w/ 6 bays, each w @TrackManGolf w fine dining/bar/fireplace.… https://t.co/NJ2von8HzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no. #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old and new, bright and dark, a city with a bit of everything #sanfrancisco #california #shooting #shotoniphone… https://t.co/02nS0z44eZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrownbagBenny Cable might have to go big fella 😂. Health insurance is recommended as well in these wicked times. S… https://t.co/HELqLD773H]]></document><document><![CDATA[why are you even renting?? Bruh you have the money to OWN properties. The owners of that house are cashing in]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the OG real fans watching at home now that ticket prices skyrocketed the past few seasons. We’re all saving up… https://t.co/j2Z49LM8SL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man this #timechange has really messed me up. I’m not the only one right? https://t.co/dna8eeSVJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[so basically I'm learning that I matched with an ABG......🤦🏻‍♂️  #tinder #help https://t.co/P40Osc2FXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a friend in critical condition right now after being hit by a drunk driver, really struggling right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayorHancock @nflmom54 @Broncos @BMarshh Type of guy you need in a locker room]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FergusFSU @PureSpew @Eschatologuy Verse 23 is more than a verse apart. AND it is his own words, not a quote. Funda… https://t.co/cHlF4Gw0GB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upset: Clayton Utter knocks of second seeded Kelly Dunnigan 6-4 at 106 with a reverse in OT #njwrestling @HPRwildcats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KRAZYKAZIAH great meeting u on Twitter, enjoy my latest horror film review PSYCHO SHARK https://t.co/KQQWhoAmGr https://t.co/hFSMOZLK2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dancingonpoison I am so glad this tweet exists. that jump is impossible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very proud of another radio special with @beats1official team on 1 hr. tribute #oscars2019 w/ @kendricklamar,… https://t.co/Z51gzqvCmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some very big buildings. #newyorkskyline #empirestatebuilding #freedomtower @ New York, New York https://t.co/MA0Et8d139]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @RealMattCouch @realDonaldTrump If they all a True Patriots if Not they are Phony &amp; False !! Sincerely yours me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making pulley systems~fixed, movable, and compound. #bermpride https://t.co/y7ZCxrC2Bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2HappyKittyz @TheEmpir3 @mshowerton @amkat82702 @amarakhbaranth1 @JimCarrey @RepMaxineWaters No IRS Criminal Inves… https://t.co/EUDRpkuRht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BluntStatement @pops3284 My friend Bentley and I got lunch once and he was like “Hey what do you tip?” I told him… https://t.co/hRt6OozSX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The marketing team in Cupertino are working overtime to make 'Apple Video And Chill' sound even the least but inter… https://t.co/OlOWZkOgWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndrew_lawrence Oh yeah?  Well, if everything's going to sh*t then why is the sun out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diego_Cantu27 Jajajaja no entiendo que les emociona tanto este torneo ligas en Mexico, ahi es donde se hacen grandes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BinaryNine @SeoulDynasty @overwatchleague You putting it on today too? 👀📺]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those of us old enough to remember a similar type TV Show in the 1960s called Laugh In, they made fun of then P… https://t.co/DDnkw1QK5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York City... always growing. Never slowing down. . ●  .    #glrosario .    George L. Rosario NYC's Hometown Rea… https://t.co/AIEjtQ6ozc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you like winter, this could be fun.  https://t.co/vef0cJ0mC1 #roadtrip #iceroads #Minnesota]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I march to the beat of my own drum...this generation is lost...looking for likes and mentions...” @criscarter80 with the big facts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Offres de la direction de l'ABI: des réactions https://t.co/LYo2dqw244 https://t.co/YtNSGQHmeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This country is screwed. When the nxt President (if we're lucky) is caught lying repeatedly or profiting from his o… https://t.co/JMZIWRjupx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS Trump will be re-elected regardless of the sour-puss @TheDemocrats And #MAGA2020 is an opportunity for #ADOS… https://t.co/BTEquOgxX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BirdsGiveBack, Illinois State's first-ever exclusive giving day, is officially underway! Join us as we rise to the… https://t.co/2oLkPob8Zm]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY? - this question unlocks the motive behind the mission of Jesus. Sinners needed repentance leading to salvation… https://t.co/Tm5Ue9nkBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vikingsspin yup I rather trade rhodes for o-line, that's why I was asking would we trade 1 of our wr for o-line th… https://t.co/Sf9JdSawwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There is no reason why we should not have a world 🌎 free from #LGBT 🏳️‍🌈 criminalization by 2030” -… https://t.co/1dERMYLCpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my mom is in in a bad mood you might as well guarantee the whole house is going to be in a bad mood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, I’m home and I’m dealing with it. It’s a long season. Some very good things along with moments of bad defending… https://t.co/lKCC0pmUkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[HIPÓLITO MEJÍA EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en… https://t.co/T49EiYEmzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[When fascism comes to America it will be wrapped in the flag and carrying a cross — Sinclair Lewis Trump was going… https://t.co/lN2S8bpuXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomsThoughts "Independent factual knowledge" is a somewhat tricky way of saying it was a purposeful lie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FiveThirtyEight I've never seen it and I refuse to watch just on the principle alone. #dealwithit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBambino97 @DemBoyz_News @letzgocowboys Appreciate the correction. Of course I meant antonio brown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@808GRINDS By cahnce will your place be open on Sunday at @GiganticBrewing for the @timbersarmy viewing party?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hanskristensen Apologists receive a set of conclusions from their denominational affiliation and work at developin… https://t.co/5MYm8PGeVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's good for Memphis is for Team Thad, Bluff City Legends, Memphis Magic Elite, etc to ALL be strong. What's goo… https://t.co/eK90t0jNEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never realized how important music &amp; PA are while calling a game. Very weird silent between whistles https://t.co/Y9fhXIplQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mga Awit 18:1-2  Ang Biblia, 2001    Sa Punong Mang-aawit. Awit ni David na lingkod ng Panginoon, na iniukol ang mg… https://t.co/TdyUqGgA16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManTruthLegend Exactly. It's a too big to fail situation. It's hard to find anybody in GOP leadership in Congress… https://t.co/4dUGt7dOKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like to take pictures of @RyanHigginsRyan taking pictures of @petermurphyinfo. It's my thing. https://t.co/bSfyWhkcqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaylaraOwl @ladyred1956 @cherokeesher2 @andrerucker51 @FKNFairyPrinces @Grady10101 @Al14146961 @joelytrumpshate… https://t.co/zstz0GusYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyKerobi @Colbywrld @Pittsburghfan97 @CopeGerry @PJbleedsgreen @ShowtimeTate @steelers No one player is greate… https://t.co/d2uD754Qyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best story I heard today at rehearsal. I was at a sweet 16 I asked  “Why are you wearing a mic pack” Response: “I’m… https://t.co/SaTKiPEDvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some recommendations from the man himself. Get up to speed on Kody Rice, because 2019 is going be a big year for th… https://t.co/TMBDB5rrkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @HitachiVantara for hosting a few of us from @4Roads this week. It's been great to spend time discussing… https://t.co/lvxfKEeJd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosM90992450 @djrodak @zonarayada Aun si tenemos más títulos que su rica y mediocre existencia!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Letang would absolutely get smoked by Simmonds. It would be a blood bath.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone heard @USC_FB spring practice is underway and wanted to gear up! #theoalert #theoamosjuju #FightOn #USC https://t.co/ul7Hw2dUem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eat healthy and exercise so that you feel good inside and out. #truebeauty #passiton https://t.co/qfdcIdfBJh via @valuescom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissMandi00 @therepublicbbq Get 4 food groups yo yo dieting dosnt work its callin the food additives. You wanna cu… https://t.co/Z8dTfMqygt]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re talking about how they’re going to get to their next destination once they land but they want to save gas a… https://t.co/3gpH7Z1jqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finished my short story!! Is there anyone that would like to look over it and suggest revision ideas? It’s due tomorrow. Let me know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have so many questions:  -Why is he playing pool by himself at a party? -Was he the only one that was allowed to… https://t.co/xbHssWqZn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s smoke with any nigga behind my girl 🤷🏾‍♂️ don’t even look her way too long I’ll smack tf outta you 🎯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite Kofi being out of Fastlane, I’m still rooting for him for Wrestlemania, I mean #KOFIMANIA 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilyIvyMFC Till the roof come off till the lights go out till my head give out can’t shut my mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennClarkRadio Do you think for a run-heavy offense like the Ravens will probably have, you need a WR like Parris… https://t.co/JpBvEiwen2]]></document><document><![CDATA[O dark thirty on a bus. Must be #IHSFA Sectional Speech. Good skill to the speakers and may the odds ever be in your favor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been a little over a year since I woke up extra early on a weekend morning to run a race, and as soon as I ste… https://t.co/EekDXyX6jA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenjaminEnfield @MikeTyson I also like his new outlook on life. Thanks for posting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[💪Never Skip Monday💪Hiit circuit  workout 🏋️‍♂️ A great routine that works your strength and abs🔥🔥#MondayMotivation… https://t.co/HiWWmvuLGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to my friends at @InnovationPtbo for presenting me with these cool sunglasses 😎. Will wear them proudly!!… https://t.co/c3j4pYSopM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like waiting on a long line only to realize you forgot your wallet 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC @Peter_Wehner You are a traitor, I guess hair pie over the republican party for you!! You are not a conserv… https://t.co/rb19Ig2gDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMartinezArias @OKaneCahir and the field STILL benefits from the fruits of all that labor! sometimes, nothing beats the originals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darabont73 @pedroj_ramirez Santamaría es traidora, con ella no quedaría nada del PP...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talkhoops Rolabi Wizenard sounds like he should be Cornelius Fudge’s dim-witted assistant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t tell you how blessed I am to have a friend and brother like @SayreBedinger. Spiritual growth I’ve had since m… https://t.co/G7ThpX04wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Ghostbusters2016 #CaptainMarvel  #Walmart  #SJW https://t.co/mlzJA1ocEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ILMFOrg A idiot, keep it up , for every time you open your mouth the democrats loose more votes. most Americans lo… https://t.co/lik1XzSMw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c3convertase Good on you for standing up for yourself! It's beyond ridiculous. It's, well, for once I'm going to b… https://t.co/MElddSKIGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHumble_21 Landon I am crushed your gone! Best in NFL at your position! It’s a sad day! 😔😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LPRIPPER24tv Wow hope you get better I saw some guy wearing a mask that looked like scorpion from my it was crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Glenn Hamby around here in Jay okla He had another Brother his name was Wayne Hamby around here in Jay okla se… https://t.co/aqgEJn7IJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So is the #TheEricAndreShow the same thing as Space Ghost Coast to Coast @adultswim]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días amantes de las casualidades bien planeadas, para desayunar va mi columna https://t.co/4GvNHELBFi… https://t.co/raykmfj2pu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids whose age doesn’t end in teen wake up with 50+ notifications every morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so this is really corny but the first time I watched love Simon I was DEEEEEP in the closet and now I just watch… https://t.co/BiO4FivfMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FatChickinLA @lindachilders1 @JBirdFOF @StillLangdon @strangevista @donholley0 @GregCartin @mesealake… https://t.co/NjxcfHTE3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minneapolis you are so many things to me... 1965 promotional video. https://t.co/FDNyx3TFvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaoulSDuke1 Bialy confronts Bloom about hiding his arm  Bialy: Fine, take it off  both throw the arm bands in the trash, Bloom spits on it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to end your final home games Jonny T !  Don’t get off the bus yet.. you have some trips down the pike 🎱💍 https://t.co/f091KL221L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lyndsay_CTV Good morning Lyndsay... I seen that episode last night.  Sometimes parents step too far into their chi… https://t.co/DLwEMXlK5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Michael Thomas catches a 6-yard slant*  sAints fans: https://t.co/t9kymhIVuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please be advised due to the changing forecast conditions @COL1853 🚛#trash and ♻️#recycling will be delayed for one… https://t.co/OIpQ6TnuPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Focus. On. You. Please. Please. Please. Young. Entrepreneurs. I. Love. You. ❤️ #Entrepreneur #entrepreneurchats https://t.co/C4oE6af51v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blasphemybunny @georgehank @TakeThatChem @pmgeorgic To achieve herd immunity against measles, vaccination rates must be &gt;90%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all put these things in your house and don’t expect them to be recording everything they possibly can? LMAOOOOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Listing Alert! Awesome new listing of mine in McCordsville, IN. Take a 3D Tour now: https://t.co/bGRrw0Tv8p… https://t.co/rFZS1DQSdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stealth40k I just want more info on the 3D world tease.  If we can make 3D levels... it's over.]]></document></documents></author>