<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tryflin09 @JustNateLoucks @heathpearce That’s YouTube’s fault blame the algorithm mate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #IT jobs like "Principal BPM Designer/Developer" at Fidelity Investments in #Westlake, TX.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Para los servidores públicos que se relacionan con la PV. Lectura recomendada. Si, hay una relación entre función p… https://t.co/tTpjnOAj5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 @IngrahamAngle @JussieSmollett @realDonaldTrump Haha! Touché!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tommy lee and Pamela Anderson next to me in checkout line buying completely normal things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I loved that ‘01 team and was convinced Zeljko Rebraca was going to be a star]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Dems are brainwashed! Look at the Democratic party history and the treatment of blacks. Get your collective hea… https://t.co/eVp5f6ql6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow night! March 1st stumblingoat in canadian_tx -Team Z @ Stumblin Goat Saloon https://t.co/Sh3cLAkoaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about getting out of these never ending wars? That’ll help.  Cut some F’ing spending.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold sunshine Donut &amp; coffee  Good Sunday in #Seattle #CapitolHill https://t.co/OZCxUQkwEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BroadStBull Are u kidding me. What a disgrace and joke. You can’t tell me the league doesn’t still hate the Flyers… https://t.co/tFrUXmuqEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoooo @Drinkchamps is talking to one of my favorites @therealredman ! Shout out @noreaga @djEFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BGSUHockeySite Do they shake after every game or only the end of a series? TV broadcast said only end of series]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baked #blackcod last nite at #harborviewsf #chinesefood st the Embarcadero 4 Center #sanfrancisco nice #seafood @ H… https://t.co/uKn4kfXyVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been listening to a lot of Canadian AM radio for some reason lately. Idk why, but I enjoy it. Only thing is th… https://t.co/BBXcw0N2dC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come out to the new Kenton Field House Ribbon Cutting at NOON today! https://t.co/uo1Q3nQ3C7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@extratv @seanspicer @SecPompeo @PressSec @KellyannePolls Seriously? Who cares? Is this a lying contest?]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump #ThankGod you are #POTUS. You're the only one trying to #MakeAmericaGreatAgain   All .@GOP should… https://t.co/Pzd7cp4nv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Bullshit.  Liar in chief.  Quit lying all day every day will ya???]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let nothing be done through strife or vainglory; but in lowliness of mind let each esteem other better than themse… https://t.co/XiIU38pv1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrCoachRentz @Mrsklgarcia @PLTWorg Brand new, Less mechanical engineering and specific computer program focused. M… https://t.co/p5ATyHIKl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jovigirl888Gail @AngelaBelcamino @AOC @GOP Me too.  The constant challenges to cultural and constitutional norms is...overwhelming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trabernlaw Yup. The doubters (I was one) should take note. The haters should pace themselves: She will be on the s… https://t.co/52v1uLVdzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting maybe read and follow hashtags never know what you might find]]></document><document><![CDATA[Profesor @jochysantos yo fuera un BlackBerry de bolita de esos que se jodian de una vez si lo joden mucho y con poco espacio en la memoria 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Love not the world, neither the things that are in the world. If any man love the world, the love of the Father is… https://t.co/jXkrCy6WPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trim_often @TGENashville If you ever come back, check out The Great Escape, 2 locations in the Nashville area, 2 i… https://t.co/GU8oP6OWra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BramonKarla @Ms_ShaLeeLee Your right: #1 women mental health issue and the #2 men's mental health issue over #1 men's issue addiction]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the lakers are in danger of missing the playoffs but Max Kellerman said Lebron is better than Steph and kd combined 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andddd STILL ....💪🏽💪🏽 #ironaddicts #ironparadise  #whatsnow? https://t.co/zoCjaeCE1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wyo_advocate @therealgynomite @becausewecare1 Yes, I'm 30 years in the field and many relationships wirh individua… https://t.co/6Wyvm06dZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@igorb4662 Thanks for Following! Like a good spy thriller novel or know someone who does? Please check my author's… https://t.co/RBpqzbtTDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silverstein @shanetold your Music has meant the world to me since I was 17, and I’m almost 30 now. I’m so excited… https://t.co/NVNtthGRKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett How about this guy? https://t.co/vsHUQuy7DN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look what love did for us! Happy Valentine's Day! And check out the story in @Advocate.com https://t.co/M3j7TCGZt5… https://t.co/PTNCEkvhCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g_golfam That picture set it off. My mans looks comfy 😂  I say maybe a finger. But a whole 5-8 inches ?? That’s wild 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a rewarding way to spend a couple of hours this afternoon!  San Franciscans for Sports and Recreation, a non-p… https://t.co/eyC5hcg0Oy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGoldberg Seize them @realDonaldTrump, close them all down. Please! Please..... give us an excuse to string you up! You jackass!]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the @ggwash live event w DC director of planning Andrew Trueblood. #ggwashlive]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🙌🏀monday motivation #OneLastLob #Brotherhood #BiggerThanBasketball #mondaymotivation @dwyanewade @kingjames @ Char… https://t.co/bClUbVV4gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraBenanti At end of show Laura runs up aisle. My aisle. As she runs up the steps and gets close I blew her a ki… https://t.co/BRuw7wQm4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@esargent184 Thanks, twitter friend. I appreciate it. https://t.co/HnZuvfw6GT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Luckiest? Asking my future wife for that first dance.  The rest is history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a longtime Chicago police sergeant, Eddie Hicks thought robbing drug dealers was the perfect crime, the feds day… https://t.co/UOmOc4o47U]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏈 FOOTBALL PROSPECTS 🏈  Under The Radar❓ Under Recruited❓  ⏰..Time is Ticking..⏰  ✔️Be PROACTIVE ✔️Have a Sense of… https://t.co/yexhH0btM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomKozz @maydaymindy9 They both lost in their bet for presidency and senator]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfessorAMuse Got my fingers crossed. Like you said, if something doesn’t happen soon I think they will fuse together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How y’all look plugging cashapp anywhere you can 🤦🏻‍♂️ https://t.co/pkao97teni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @NBCNewsTHINK This country’s men are turning into a bunch of pussies.. and the liberal media and their LGB… https://t.co/UugJ1ZZ927]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off to work soon i drive crown pallet jacks for a living and I love them]]></document><document><![CDATA[TDS is worse than the bowel malfunctions @RealRonPhillips has!! @realBradStaggs @TheBrandonMorse @Mojo50Radio #WhatILearnedToday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  will France demand the arrest of all jews that Turn on jewish leaders?? @netanyahu  was betrayed by his own f… https://t.co/n9Cfkkprz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not love the world or anything in the world. If anyone loves the world, love for the Father …… https://t.co/CIqCfsvcGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This workout was everything I needed after this weekend. Should have done it Monday night or some time Tuesday inst… https://t.co/8vU3Oi2g6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[PROBANDO MIS REDES ENSAYO DE STREAMING POR SI QUIERES CURIOSEAR: https://t.co/6FuAgYQWJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRagingCrow @GailSimone Also the extreme shoulder pads and hyperelongated thigh &lt;chef’s kiss&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[View from the @wsp @cityoftoronto office, could you ever tire of it?!? https://t.co/vG4pMC0dkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dallascowboys Smh 🤦‍♂️ this shit got too stop 🛑 somewhere I mean come on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebrannon_ @AOC So... You only get your news from propaganda outlets?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlos_agsmx es lo más rescatable de ayer, regresamos a esa etapa donde jugamos a nada, nadie parece estar bien en… https://t.co/FByI2lD0x3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nischelleturner @TiffanyDCross @VanJones68 I seen you emotions on Don lemon and your concerns. l see as a journali… https://t.co/fqJoidoE9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just booked tickets for my fiancé, best friend and I to go to Disney and honestly I couldn’t be happier 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these people talking about spread love not hate, but when you see em in person they stay having a bitch face be… https://t.co/9hUBzmUnW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to relax a bit.                                              • • • #hibiscus #BnB #wedding #love #bookdirect… https://t.co/CpukPp1vy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys please check out this link - I’m running the London landmarks half marathon for @guidedogs on March 24th p… https://t.co/Ayr82XeohD]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️CONGRATS TO THIS INCREDIBLE WOMAN‼️ @thekelleyparker  Today &amp; Always 🙌🏽 #internationalwomensday #girlpower… https://t.co/bgxUD5QsM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a manager, my view is the world is shitty enough. We don't need to be unbearable to the people we manage. That's… https://t.co/Y0P6qOirDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFried_GDP @GSU_PAC @GeorgiaStateMBB Still have the bottle and it holds a place of distinction in my display, righ… https://t.co/O9YZvcnOPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnWDean Mr Dean love your honesty but keep your emotions to a min, it’s pants not paints. But thank you for making your point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@consumerpal Every time I read one of your ads, it confirms to me that you are not operating in the best interests of American consumers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amaxsmith Yeah and they're going broke paying $65 one way for a Lyft from DC to Fairfax County which leaves them w… https://t.co/3stUMzxHgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain I would really like for you to talk with my mother. She is an OB/GYN and has been practicing for over… https://t.co/FdEY8nhK2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iRONMANCSGO From what I'm told the guns are named the same on Apex and Titan Fall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@incorrectpsb Whoa whoa whoa as long as no one compares Jack to Simon of Love, Simon #PleaseDont]]></document><document><![CDATA[here u go.    https://t.co/RVT7pWigvW  👑🌟🎳  my sweet @SelirioJennie  will love this show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hunter2baseball @mikebrannon_ @AOC You believe in God but you don't accept him giving humans stewardship over the… https://t.co/ptBm6ONVof]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING INSTAFACEBOOGERS @ Power Plant Fruitland NM https://t.co/i2C4deXVOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should be an interesting quarter, this is an absolute must win, Kenny and the players know it but can they show it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people tell me #Bernie's too old to be President, I'm just gonna show them this video of this wonderful 106 ye… https://t.co/miAcXxcAk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBeatWithAri @AriMelber You are the best news anchor on television. NBC better not lose you to another network o… https://t.co/VIEUOtgTpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s our team including a dark looking @RicciReports in #BreakingNewsOne @AlexandraLeslie @dnorth50 @plittletvguy… https://t.co/vDJQOnX0HB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoja de Vida de este innombrable corrupto miembro de los Pandilleros del Narco Regimen que usurpan cargos Publicos… https://t.co/Xa4AZzMiVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[no one:  republicans when they heard Bernie Sanders is running for president again: https://t.co/Xx9BTjSwnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[- “Il pericolo nucleare non è estinto” - “Oggi la sicurezza nazionale deve difendere elementi essenziali come l’acq… https://t.co/fDnTgXlQq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cane_alytics Oh geez, my bad. The author was an Oliver and I thought it was you. Very well, carry on! 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made a random purchase today, but I couldn’t be happier! I’ve wanted one of these for as long as I can remember. We… https://t.co/AQgPCkoPDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@blusanders Great set tonight in Philly!  Can’t wait to hear more! (hoping there is the music at merch)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas with the wifey #mezzanine @ Foundation Room Las Vegas https://t.co/ZB9L2s8wir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rlwitmeyer @BrittCranston I would think that it would be well appreciated!  Hmmm especially by the mothers that ar… https://t.co/dy0nt47ZsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two screenshots to summarize this game. Terrible. https://t.co/PM5eQdHP8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brm90 @MaryHowle @valor4us @USArmy Same here, sir. Every LGBTQ+ person that I served with in the @usairforce alway… https://t.co/gAFuoxVCSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uncuttool8 @RedBear35 @jbttm4u @Big_Blk_Cock @DeviantBeach1 @dikbreth @nctomcat74 @Lkin4bigjohnson… https://t.co/ukmLy5L0DP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GNSoomro5. Thanks welcome aboard !! It time independent conservative women !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisStrub I have a pocket sized Apple computer that has a phone built in. (and a camera)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Socialist AOC very happy to stop commerce in its tracks. Today Amazon -  Tomorrow the rest of commerce in… https://t.co/yZzD6rRSIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You getting the crap off of faux spews?  https://t.co/5pOCPl5WsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gallagher  Rodger  Clinton     Don McLean    john kay Stevenwolf Cheap Trick   The Coasters   The Drifters    Grand… https://t.co/Ua5j60hJ8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an encouraging stretch for Auburn. The Tigers aren't just playing "up" or burning energy that won't last. T… https://t.co/scJPzeQQaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me the start of every month summiting my rent payment https://t.co/4NR4cxSylR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCHockey alum Steven Santini is on the 3rd defensive pairing for New Jersey   #NHLBruins #NJDevils #MetroBoston #BC #HockeyEast]]></document></documents></author>