<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[El Capitán América y Selena, presentan un premio #Oscars2019 #Oscars https://t.co/iOs4epkvrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left without taking my drug test today cuz it was taking too long. If I go back to jail over it after I been doing good ima shoot somebody]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Business Analyst (71224)" at AMD by asking for referrals. It's a great way to get a… https://t.co/DUjfrK2J18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 8% of HS seniors could identify that Slavery was the primary cause for the Civil War @NYSCSS @Tolerance_org #hardhistory]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monicataher @AlejandrinaCF @ravelpak @ARENAOFICIAL Donen la deuda política como lo prometieron vieja asquerosa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie I think he meant he’s never heard him tell the truth. I think he got it confused.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a special moment! I introduce to you, my beautiful God Daughter Lillian Renee Simmons. Congratulations… https://t.co/mXWM8ozCPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidArchie @smokeyrobinson @AmericanIdol I would love to hear your version of Tracks of My Tears, or Ooh Baby Baby 💝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expert: R. Kelly body language leaking the truth  https://t.co/AEFxPGXrp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit this Birdie wants to get up! She’s lookin pretty. Fire her up let’s get her in the sky. @beansiemax https://t.co/uCECuSJSVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaSardelli We currently have a fully involved auto fire in the breakdown lane of Rt6 west at the Hartford ave off ramp.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t ask me to compare and contrast glycrrhyzin and anethole at this hour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett @foxandfriends what kind of country do we have where free speech can Be trampled o… https://t.co/oUjea8Iwmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickCode Lebron was more of a team player so of course it appeared that way]]></document><document><![CDATA[BW claiming GM made a better mix is priceless at the end. Love the convertible red caddie too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Suplinaaaa Foreal tho, like my guy how can you be sleeping cozy in that heat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julieroginsky Both situations merit serious discussion. Go back and listen to the CPD. Commanders Press Conference👍🤐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMoran93 Hah! You and my both. Probably my biggest pet peeve about Twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StealVc @IsoCuisine2K @2KCrewFinder @WalkOnWarriors Let's run bro i need you add me OGBalla34]]></document><document><![CDATA[“How can you not be romantic about baseball?”  Love you @SamanthaWa11ace! 😘 There’s no one I would rather road trip… https://t.co/nj0YBgJwG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@km_scannell @HumanoidTroll @AngelaBelcamino Thanks for the website. And thanks for reminding me how important it i… https://t.co/MMz9Oat2qR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#live #living #love #people #cook #cooking #tasty #flavors #lineage #logan #cookingclass #cookingclasses #goodeats… https://t.co/FKo4r0vlZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[How in 2019 this is still an issue of belief?  Kid goes against his Mom’s wishes to get vaccinated. Spoiler: He’s 1… https://t.co/MWnBJJwoTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basically worked 15 hours today and I went to bed at 6am last night got up at 8am. #champ]]></document><document><![CDATA[*whispers* They’re not going to need or want your consent to murder your children soon, you morons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seen a rose with a pineapple junk band as I drove by. ☹ I hope you're doing better than me. I'm glad you blocked me… https://t.co/VnVjYc2qxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealJenCandy @ChrisCandy4u What a guy. My thoughts are with you, Jenny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Toronto! 🎉 185 years never looked so good.  #TransitSafe #TEU #Toronto #birthday #celebrate https://t.co/c5UEomwNYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelicaross You got this, Angelica! Positive energy and light from your friends in DC!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omar Khadr est l'exemple même de ce que je déteste de la politique de Justin Trudeau. On s'excuse, on leur donne de… https://t.co/3cTljUGOjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWG_1WGA_ @RepAdamSchiff Liddle Adam needs his time to show he's a big boy &amp; use the secret decoder ring he got for Christmas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smh...imagine writing the caption “the power of three” and disrespecting the most powerful good witches the world h… https://t.co/XBSDfhEOxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wheredthesodago as someone who has been on both sides of the spectrum, this video is dumb!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rennergizer @dbongino Lol. Everyone gets it EXCEPT CNN! https://t.co/TmT7DcQFnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t find excuses to not, find a way to do....come get your Q!    #trafficsucks #parkingsucks #weatherwillsucktoo… https://t.co/CYBjYKJZZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's mirth. #hilarity #giggle #smile #hilarious https://t.co/GcjnYmtbZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manchester United vs PSG in the Champions League 02/19/2019 @ Long Beach, California https://t.co/i5m0CD1rjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbeSnowman I wrote an old PHP script to give lots of data about GHE orgs and repos... Much of it written overnight… https://t.co/pNmyzJ0yxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Nashville bound - and look who I get to sit next to! @tallcathy @961KISS https://t.co/kmp9FaMXr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartyBrink @TheMeadowlands @CyberChampDan He’s very good capper and bettor too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like his classic Oscar ceremony feat the great actor Jack Palance, demonstrated a daring one armed single handed pu… https://t.co/HSE9xzN45e]]></document><document><![CDATA[So hear me out. What if Polite is dropping his stock on purpose just so that he can be drafted by the Rams? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InTheMAGAlane You seem practiced at beliefs without facts. For example, I’m not a Democrat nor do I follow the peo… https://t.co/w3RoGZ7Hl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The state will continue to provide emergency personnel and services upon request as the high winds continue. For ex… https://t.co/1VN4gs1NjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans are afraid of powerful people like her! White politicians are not used to being held accountable by a n… https://t.co/JJ5b8cCk3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it an attack if she was the one who jumped into the jaguar’s territory? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[His desire wasn’t the best at times. I saw too many times he gave up on plays. I understood why Dorsey cut him afte… https://t.co/TAaHxqc1HZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[CRC Speech Meet @ Meridian (Daykin) has been rescheduled to Wednesday, February 27. @DaniBethune @CrossCounty1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zinkmi313master @SenTedCruz @realDonaldTrump @HoustonChron Why don’t you take it out on the people responsible for… https://t.co/o0VqsdMJJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarielStoll @ahandleforian Has LD retired again yet? This will never end, will it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuavangogh @cakefacecutie I guess not everyone can be as blessed as I am💉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorrisAnimal @cherylt2000 That's good news. Come on people, let's make it a trend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tax1percentat99 @rjcrock2003 Yea. Requiring a funding solution to a legislative proposal is just crazy talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you will serve our Maker with a full and faithful heart, He will put people in your life strategically, when you… https://t.co/vTb5O0jqGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#art #trump #FakeTrumpEmergency #SNL #NotesFromNationalEmergency https://t.co/JvydQQFitm]]></document><document><![CDATA[This stretch of W’s in 2013 to close out the year and make that Wild Card game was insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my beautiful wife @CDParmer showing two of her outstanding paintings today at Mill Pond Art Gallery in… https://t.co/yMsAlV0KwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because you don’t understand something doesn’t mean you need to be scared or hateful. Not everything you can’t… https://t.co/VVJbPGEeu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enough said. But the damage continues. #nofascistusa @ New York, New York https://t.co/v5KKwOJUiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[After several days it is done.  Easily the best face I’ve ever painted.  Hope all r having a good day! https://t.co/8jgPlych7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HolbertTerry @TerrellePryor @JimTressel5 Thanks for sharing this Terry!🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you start dropping stats defending Lebron the only thing the person can say is that he’s 3-6 in the finals but… https://t.co/FmzXkZ7L8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Butcher of Gujarat meets the Butcher of Yemen. Two blood thirsty butchers, one picture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a Fantastic Day! BDay, @stlouisblues Win, &amp; @badgerhillbeer @ Badger Hill Brewery and Tap Room https://t.co/JemqQUgEmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at NYC Dept of Sanitation M-12 in Manhattan, NY https://t.co/6bVDzKaoys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the next four weekends, @AdamSniderNews will try out these four looks. Vote for your favorite at… https://t.co/JKqVdsZLnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally all i had going for me with the ladies was that i’m 6’6 and the short king movement has taken that from me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early in Cup practice, Austin Dillon is fastest with an average lap speed of 179.784 mph.  If you’re wondering how… https://t.co/gA2KLh6IBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was at the @fwhistorycenter tonight to talk about his new book on “Indiana’s President,” entitled “Mr. President… https://t.co/1LUGo4sdoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lesley_NOPE I feel like this is probably your fault :-) https://t.co/kZOkJAHHmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadIrishRebel Just a reminder of how powerful a man in a dress actually is....#nuclear]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do You Know What Time It Is Brother? (Dash Snow Commemoration.) New York, NY. 2019. #art #contemporaryart… https://t.co/5fI46PAjhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ St. Peter's Church &amp; World Outreach Center https://t.co/H6ztdZzHEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevDon With a Chinese friend, in a Viet "supermarket"(no refridge) after neither one of us recognized the fleshy… https://t.co/koyXaqwhqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tremendous snowy evening “Confronting Climate Change: Boston-based ideas that can change the world” with superb ins… https://t.co/2P54Nk7AsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact y’all have Zion up with MJ and Laettner and he hasn’t even played in a unc duke game yet is something else]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oct ‘04, I got 5 tiny tattoos so they knew where to line up 15 rounds of radiation during my treatment for Testicul… https://t.co/1U5n0QnpUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillianmele @FoxFriendsFirst  : on the peeps I'm very surprised no bacon or pickle peeps . Ugh!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day of learning at Kennedy Space Center!!!!!@DeLandMiddle https://t.co/QpFpIvGg1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iAmBrooksie And from what you posted and what @ChrisPotter413  posted it was a hell of a game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @JoeBiden @realDonaldTrump @VP We all trust Joe. Americans do not trust The President or vice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yikes @realDonaldTrump. Did they not teach you how to count in private school? https://t.co/1ExzjqRy1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my wife’s birthday.Its also the anniversary of my mom dying 4 years ago today I lost my mom on my wife’s birthday so hard 😔❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justin Trudeau’s reelection bid hits the rocks – POLITICO https://t.co/JztLddG3M7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie should have been groveling to stop this a long time ago.  His grandiosity is going to have a nasty price]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaredwoodard Come on, Jared, I don’t see a basis for prying wedges between our team members that are just Swamp me… https://t.co/GVSqi3vCG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @andersoncooper Anderson Cooper glad to hear you're perfect and never had misspoken in your life a******]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahmdkhalidd_ Thank you @ahmdkhalidd_ I am glad that you enjoyed it! 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[*previous tweet was accidentally deleted, but from the 10:11 mark to 6:31, @DubCQuakers went on a 17-0 run in the f… https://t.co/HLXMUm5s6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosA14301861 @thecliniccl Le costo mucho argumentar con tanta profunfidad ? Tomese un año sabatico.. lo necesita..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbetensky_MD @Dr_Santangeli @DrFerminGarcia @rdschaller Gorgeous. Total gift.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No “man” has ever looked more like a lesbian than this fellow right there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skier017 @thecjpearson Actually I never said a word to you until you harassed me. Pointing out facts does not make… https://t.co/7gGlLkSiZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey have you read the Hey Wayne column on AFP’s website? Give me a shout.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donpako7 @Claudiocor85 @SoyMonark @VarskySports @fantasmasuarez Por favor ustedes traen pura sobra... Y todo lo qu… https://t.co/hMj4enaY83]]></document><document><![CDATA[Updated my iOS and my service has been terrible ever since. Why I don’t do that shii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kerikss0nEk I totally forgot there was an office without him so forgettable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LFC_Fezz @PhlyGunner I’m taking all this into consideration can’t wait to get back on lol first year with bvb ther… https://t.co/SQEY62tzZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our boys are going to miss seeing @trev_7 as the Mountaineer @WVUMascot #MountainMen https://t.co/2nryqAgxFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReinaldoProfeta @LulaOficial @jairbolsonaro D3ben meterlo en un manicomio con camisa de fuerza de por vida es un v… https://t.co/ichoVkIHHv]]></document></documents></author>