<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Rewatching Criminal Minds always reminds me how great of a show this really is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @CBP They are from another country...not another planet you insensitive pricks...where did that term even come from]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeptuneSeahawks Seahawks, Get ready to get defeated by the staff members!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JumboHart @Fred_Kirsch @EwellMello @Kat_in_Chicago  @E_Scal @pfwpaul  also when Trump’s defending you as he did Kr… https://t.co/vXJU7AKd5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaroncarter You can do this.  It gets easier as you get those foundation blocks down and you build on those.  Have… https://t.co/p8znUztoTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorLankford @ItsDarciLynne No Money shall be drawn from the Treasury, but in Consequence of Appropriations mad… https://t.co/s1jUZWAQF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are the same Olive Bistro Midtown that was at the Whole Foods on Ponce. We relocated to Juniper St across from J… https://t.co/gRmV8iNyhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afrxdiasporaphd Evil flourishes in the dark, help us shine a light!   https://t.co/vUtpzGrDOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can tell mom is home when we have to start posing for photos again. 😂 In her defense, tonight’s sunset was real… https://t.co/ruTsQSvfbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whatifisaidit Definitely not, but I also don’t think it’s fair to choose a candidate NOW when we haven’t seen a de… https://t.co/4nNhCJ14Vg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRedWineGal Is that what is wrong with me?  I thought I was having a mid-life crisis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @darrelljbarber That doesn’t make forcing the wall right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper Keep covering this and don’t be bullied into staying quiet Jake.  These girls need their day in court a… https://t.co/4sfgVBLro8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I could I’d never leave I would build a time Machine❣️ https://t.co/0CYvM6Umee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh I’ve never stressed about the future this hard until I started applying for Law Schools.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kathryn Merkel crossed 10K. Time 01:02:28, pace 09:45 min/mile, est. finish 9:20 am https://t.co/xfmbtYYmdp #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I was asked (more than once....thanks Singles Awareness Day!) why I choose to be single. This is the short an… https://t.co/GFsqJkKLcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaolaSNews @JaclynDeAug @JeffAckermann @_SarahSikora yessss ok I did then posted a photo wearing a Snuggie on my i… https://t.co/7j93GMfWOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keith’s  Fra. Diavolo... on the diavolo.🔥#lobster @ Etna Ristorante https://t.co/9PSTCpTNKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Friday: And another rainy morning on the dreadmill!  🌧☔ T.G.I F.  🍻🍺 #rebuildhealthplexfitness … https://t.co/Tnf6RqJpqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PHORAONE FINALLY! I've been waiting for this; wish I can be there March 31st but i can't go.. But I'm so so proud… https://t.co/5P3T8Wo9aG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@momma_toad usually one hour before feeds if i’m engorged! or just any time i feel engorged in general and he’s not… https://t.co/GlMopNj8M8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor quality #video, but it's worth sharing because it's #lovely.   These #geese were hanging out above my house, c… https://t.co/sJ6dpuX165]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein REMEMBER!!! AND N E V E R  E V E R FORGET!!!  IF YOU DISRESPECT YOUR DAUGHTERS AND YES EVEN YOUR WIVE… https://t.co/jnJsoy1kVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toda la vida es compromiso y el resto son excusas   Frase célebre de @DidierArmel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, thank Goddess ‘Leaving Neverland’ was done in 2 parts. It’s so heavy!! Fuck Michael Jackson! 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rain has stopped &amp; the sun has come out! Already a #blessed day! #Nashville #Nashvilleflood #Homeless]]></document><document><![CDATA[My work cancelled because of the snow and I just woke up and there’s no more snow on the ground than there was yest… https://t.co/uEpgpDjVmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a whirlwind weekend, but what fun it’s been to celebrate and honor @RonWellman and @John_Currie! #GoDeacs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@avasman @YRInsider @CBSDaytime I think Mia paid that pregnant girl for her pee to say she was pregnant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heycathylou @emmhimes Thanks! Can’t wait to see some of your favorites!]]></document><document><![CDATA[UCLA women’s basketball used nitrate-rich beet juice to fuel their game against a higher-altitude opponent#sportsnu… https://t.co/3EmCh6paOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know about anyone else but after seeing Sleepless in Seattle and You’ve Got Mail years ago, I was personall… https://t.co/GojPbitSzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[More LGBT events at #OurTownLA https://t.co/1lrvUlEuBk https://t.co/j0KmH3K51W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we come Golf Ball @ Epcot - Walt Disney World https://t.co/RVkWpK0yav]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rodeo + The Hideout until 1am, then having to wake up for work by 6a... Why do I do this to myself? 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelockhart Joe, you don’t necessarily know what is what since you are no longer an “insider” like you once were,… https://t.co/1LDZO47nsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson Conservative women don’t count. Diversity of thought is not allowed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Night owl Namjoon has me freaking out! @BTS_twt https://t.co/o2y1Zptj41]]></document><document><![CDATA[The watchman replies, "Morning is coming, but also the night. If you would ask, then ask; and come back yet again." https://t.co/GyaeNnBnWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom bickers with my sister’s dog and I just heard her angrily tell him he’s “insecure, spoiled, and fat.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I would in eat lecture during Freshman year 👀 https://t.co/XWRTs4TuNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[...If you love Chicago architecture, history and art, you'll love this essentially, richly illustrated work.  Downl… https://t.co/at4a63O3kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralCattis I’m not sure how your human feels about that but you could get treats, popcorn and spring for a in h… https://t.co/58GgxWHIPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was the Queen tribute a nice way to start the Oscars? Yeah. Do I still wish Billy Crystal came out with a charming… https://t.co/bjN3EWvEPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 months and counting and I get to marry my best friend in this spot 💕👰🏼🥰  #wedding #happy https://t.co/qQsBValVQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marwilliamson I used to follow you because of your inspirational tweets. I think you are doing a disservice to tho… https://t.co/AWo8WEqdTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3: I try to find something that makes me happy and do it each day during my down time! Gardenscapes and Homescapes… https://t.co/mgpaw166hG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump #LIED to Mueller’s face!  Robert Mueller has EVERYTHING he needs to #TakeTrumpDOWN!  Please CHIP IN to… https://t.co/HyH8mynnyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lobster Risotto ❤ Homemade Lobster Stock  Steamed Asparagus  #lobsterrisotto #homemadelobsterstock… https://t.co/Jz6bNZkUDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏆Say hello to your Mid-South Conference Champions ucumberlandscheer !! 😍🤩#GoPats #BackToBackChamps #OneBigTeam @ Bo… https://t.co/8d1XA7eSgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I went to Cali I noticed ALL drivers are like this lmaoo you either hit someone or get hit]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sick of the narrative that we’re the same people. We are not!!! We are different.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article! @sciencebanshee and thanks for posting @ar0mcintosh -Especially like thinking about that part of my… https://t.co/L6Kr3f3SQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dentist: “Your inner lip says TRILL what does that mean?”   Me: https://t.co/mmhm5eXWiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunterBergsma Underpinnings of Confront Your Fears Head-On  https://t.co/tqdfNyOdIx   via @jamiegruman aka GuruMan… https://t.co/5URLB7GOFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkZuckerman It’ll happen soon enough.  And the former 34 will get his swings in.  Our boys will get their nasty… https://t.co/PH4Ts8NeU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’ALL. It’s SLICK out here. We slid all the way here. Even the sidewalks and parking lots and impossible to walk on… https://t.co/9labvxkg5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a good day ❤️ always thankful to work with the awesome teens at Write Girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude I’m so proud of myself. I held my tongue when these kids in my public speaking class were talking shit about t… https://t.co/53ATwdVkqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[kiara’s holding me hostage and making me do a full ab workout send help]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted @c8lin17 challenge who accepted    @LowndesPam challenge to post the covers of books I love. No exp… https://t.co/H3GPoqmf2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golden hour gaming ✨ #SarahTheExplorer 🇺🇸 @ Disneyland California https://t.co/HB9FRBlqSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/a66VVjkaCh   #technology #distresstolerance #immediategratification #mentalhealth #MentalHealthMatters #mentalhealthawareness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greenkozi @tdlove5 I suppose folks could sign in as whatever-T'challa, God, Mickey Mouse]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so glad I was off today bc day2 period mood was not gonna cut it at work tonight lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 @Ashluelaroe I'm a married, straight 50 year old lady from Podunk Alabama and I absolutely don't care. You be you! Love all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone send me luck so I can go back to the casino and keep my winning streak 🎰 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuned into @WafflesRadio on @CFRC at the perfect time. They’re playing Ghost rider by Suicide. What a great way to… https://t.co/q2OZiqnr3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apokerplayer @dwallacewells Good thing people are finally caring enough about climate change to finally do somethi… https://t.co/UD7K5P4Fzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Congratulations  to Tesla, I saw a lot of people driving Tesla on the street.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many true crime books did Alpha read before the Apocalypse? Too many!!! #TheWalkingDead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else have iPhone X and constantly accidentally screenshot peoples videos because you’re trying to turn… https://t.co/mOA7kUs5xY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaPustor123 @SamHeughan Oh my!!! Gorgeous collage of a gorgeous man!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nana and I heading to see @makenzy_bennett play! 🌪 https://t.co/RnHfLL00Ki]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt I’m still on cloud nine from all the love at my birthday lunch last week! Thank you to all my beautiful friend… https://t.co/duh7nmpGyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[So...unless he works for the company that has been contracted to refurbish it I have nothing more to say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at #TMZ still stirring the racial pot between cops and rappers. #ShutYourTrapHarvey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si no hubiera recibido ese mensaje, @brunovilla017 y yo no seríamos novios😋😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so excited to announce that we were awarded an OpenTable Diners' Choice Award!! Stop by and check us out for… https://t.co/RXhEILlpvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richie_G5 @BethlehemMoore I told Beth “watch Richie is gunna respond”. U know u love it bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@partynxs @realDonaldTrump How old are you 10 or just stupid as cement?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@captnsensible @realDonaldTrump Unfortunately you don’t get something for nothing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny how people are still bad mouthing Bernie Sanders. The man who started the revolution who found the corru… https://t.co/IoRTIjM68i]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are at @Ont_Good_Roads #OGRA2019, don’t forget to vote for me tomorrow from 11:30-2:30 on the Concourse! Mak… https://t.co/5PDW6wWoef]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting to a point where I’m kinda bored of Gilmore girls but it’s such a habit so it’s always background noise]]></document><document><![CDATA[Space is limited! Register today for this awesome session presented by @MalloryDiehl &amp; Jennie Richardson!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr @LindseyGrahamSC @TheJusticeDept It Exists: DOJ Finds Letter Ordering Scrutiny of #UraniumOne, Hillar… https://t.co/c1nn7t2HKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 7 months in immigration detention, 15-year-old reunites with her father  https://t.co/XeuPqWnchg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to make it a “political night” (jk I do) but the number of white cis gays I know who try SO HARD to compare the… https://t.co/nQsbehalQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hadn’t hiked this trail for over 20 years...it was nostalgic being back to these natural pools this morning✨ {If yo… https://t.co/2vaWYL4Wvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ebay Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  Clic… https://t.co/dqPdeefzLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[L,m A Beginner's Guide to Mezcal, Tequila's Divine Cousin https://t.co/kvOTeJSaMg via @gizmodo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Mégas Agapé Mastiff's-Great Love Mastiff's https://t.co/Q7XRPDLhy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommamia1217 Aw, no, sorry but that looks mean. Why would you break trust with your little kid like that just for a stupid video. 🙈🙎🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was out walking 0.87 miles with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/PzbaRoYve8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The nice ladies who served us today. Thank you girls, it was so delicious. https://t.co/Sy63TQtNXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know there are prizes inside every OREO cookie? Check out The Stuf Inside for your chance to win!… https://t.co/24mkRHMeeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[KENTUCKY DRIVERS — Remember @KYTC is filling in potholes this morning. This time they are working EASTBOUND between… https://t.co/B9adHV2zdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad that even though I am a mess, Jesus said I was still worth it! #neverendinglove]]></document></documents></author>