<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Eastlake JV softball get the win vs Riverside 20-0 to improve to (3-0) in district play #ASAP #TrustTheProcess… https://t.co/qT3Jc3Ge1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudraEqualityMc @KamalaHarris Did Ms. Chisholm tell you “Run, Audra, run” ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My eyes are the only thing I don’t want to take off of you 😏 @ San Diego, California https://t.co/S504Ah8aIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amouretguerre @greggutfeld @billmaher The point is a comic entertaining liberal followers with an elitist attitude… https://t.co/8F55LghY3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[new YouTube video is up! Go check it out! Spalding's Bakery donuts based in Lexington, Kentucky is the best. I am t… https://t.co/vzOUE4zIqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[At what point do you stop pretending you’re gonna fall back asleep and just call that bowl of cereal your breakfast?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know a couple of those guys!  Great people out of the classroom as well!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JorgePedraza @RampCapitalLLC Um, no one is willing to wait for a GIF... https://t.co/KRoCLK9ZXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@firenzapizza is my new favorite!! @ Firenza Pizza https://t.co/QrlGi1b3kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy I could make my debut as @NJITHoops’ emergency backup free throw shooter today 😂  (Third time was the charm 😜) https://t.co/LULKNJP86x]]></document><document><![CDATA[As long as the pacing is good, and the story is complete then keep it at the 3 hr mark lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColinCowherd This is rich coming  from someone who was cut by a Spurs' team that made the Finals because he had issues with Pop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DelReyBooks @JoshMalerman @CrossAlistair have you read this brilliant author yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyOstroy @helenecooper The bar is so low it's almost under-ground. It's as low as Jared's voice is high.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amtrak train with 183 passengers stranded in Oregon for more than 24 hours: report  https://t.co/YhCpQFbZFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had one of those last week. Dallas Wednesday, most got to bed around 4 AM, game at home Thursday. It can be done… https://t.co/hIVKlVdx29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkbjournalist @SallyDeal4 That's because Dersh is afraid his name will come up when they re-open the case. He know… https://t.co/H9Rjwhrlx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Jacksonville Airport in Jacksonville, FL https://t.co/Ns7uAAF6YL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would have been a sailor on the Great Lakes or a soldier in the Boer Was were it not for my sickness as a child.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PennDOTNews hey it’s been snowing in Pittsburgh for two hours. Think y’all might want to start doing your job sinc… https://t.co/dbJ2wjetIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly cannot believe how stacked this team is. In the 22 years I’ve watched this team we’ve had some units. But… https://t.co/vT20XeJR7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[ESPN: LeBron James set to step up intensity for playoff push: 'It's been activated'  If I gave a shit about the NBA… https://t.co/O42ZKYuffm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidStevens78 @mylittlevictory @AmyImms @chrissyteigen No.  Obviously, she's implying it's overrated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending our day at Epcot.   Only about 1 week left of the Festival of the Arts....... @ Epcot International Festiv… https://t.co/t4HP5h2Rfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Leeeno_ Low key might delete this thread. 💀 but yeah it was wild when he said he didn’t like concerts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@board_weather @KristinEmery typical snow fall for this time of year, not a big deal.  Why are all the channels mak… https://t.co/6ivNB80u13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iWasZeroCool1 Seems kinda insane just to hit production numbers for the sake of it without having buyers. What hap… https://t.co/xYowxeHMBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[We about to have the top two quarterbacks drafted being black. Oh how the times are changing.  #Haskins #Murray]]></document><document><![CDATA[People given the gift of action are ashamed of this and desire the gift of the word: for action does lead to destru… https://t.co/YD8UygHPNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting mind map.  Not a direct correlation to the science standards but I like the larger lens this uses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg... the TEAAAA!!! @TeaSpillYT Better GET 👏 ON 👏 THIS 👏 😂  https://t.co/PnSppGFVXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can always count me as a huge fan of yours. You have inspired me in so many ways. I don't like when the haters… https://t.co/C9d8uXGG4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBiomechanics @bballbreakdown Looks like it’s coming off of his pointer and middle finger too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up to hearing child saying "Poop, potty" on loop. It was time for us to get up anyway so I put him straight… https://t.co/SnP1Kg57ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAM4DonaldTrump @DallasMimi @gatewaypundit @JoanneColombo @bigbangtheory Hate crime was committed https://t.co/XtN2h1i8Uv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very sweet 2019 Hyundai Elantra Sport with the 1.6 Turbo, black leather. @ Hyundai of Jasper https://t.co/qExw3FIGJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 out of three fights I was out played, out typed or their team pretty much said fuck you to everyone I brought it.… https://t.co/QTKgb4qZZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ottawahockey @CasselBrewery @sawdustcitybeer @DrunkPolkaroo @SudburyHomebrew @david_buist @ontariobeerguy… https://t.co/d2sVlihXeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many people are wearing these stickers supporting changes to address climate change https://t.co/lGCPTw1XjZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Risky business ordering Uber Eats at 12:30am after running on fumes all day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamonFoster congratulations big fella!  Happy to have such a good player and great dude back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just put the current book I am reading down next to a frame I have at my office and realized the juxtaposition is a… https://t.co/OvFydozp8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@watch_jdotb @Lightee7 @NerfTankTV @YoDaOrie @shakibdh Shak actually moved Pog]]></document><document><![CDATA[How the hell did #StanAndOllie fail to get nominated for makeup and hairstyling?? #Oscars #fail #anotherfinemess https://t.co/3iYJUNpXRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jengletweets @_ClassicJeff @NFL @Eagles @Vikings But that still doesn’t negate the fact that it’s marketed the way… https://t.co/dS67AE4L2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanahProx yeah having a kid rn in MY life being single and only 18 and about to leave for the military. people wh… https://t.co/k18PXjKnjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justingiddings  Thanks for the follow. Please subscribe to my YouTube channel it's brand new and needs some love. https://t.co/XptqiksC4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Poor little rich bernie, is trying to gain support for his flawed political system of socalism,  which means A… https://t.co/U9hD75gAVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeatballNonner That's always when depression seems to creep up. Keep perspective, and power through it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something I don't understand: Fans of @PCFriarsmbb stand at the beginning of each half 'til Friars score, then sit… https://t.co/r7hdehLBp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life behind bars @ Northlight Studios https://t.co/hg2UYucTsr https://t.co/guZFGfTU37]]></document><document><![CDATA[#firsttimebowler #daugther #dad primera vez en el boliche de mi cachorra en Boliche Metrobol https://t.co/Re18QZWvjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol nice... not crazy at all! You’re very brave... I won’t b able to take part in your creative movement because I’… https://t.co/NB5HMGUnbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the half, Frontier leads St Mary's 30-25. Falcons pressuring the ball very well and have rushed SM into some turnovers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at MTA Subway - Borough Hall/Court St (R/2/3/4/5) - @nyctsubway in Brooklyn, NY https://t.co/LZPRUi16lR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Curieux by @allagashbrewing @ Elements — https://t.co/9eg6t94lsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who think paleo/keto diets are healthy/sustainable are just plain stupid. All this research and you're gonna… https://t.co/UCSVmM6fbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KLRMelancon Man, something really uplifting about seeing @MissCollege students and faculty out in the community doing good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro I real life got accepted to Texas A&amp;M Commerce Social Work Masters Program 🍾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebron James is no king Michael Jordan is the goat  he stay with one team to win 6 championship  never moved on dif… https://t.co/kp9Mam3nPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are you doing @DennisPrager ? She is uninformed and very bad for conservative movement]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly It’s called evolution, you moron. You still live a couple of centuries ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/MPjwlJcooS]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I bought nba live 19 for 10 bucks a few weeks ago I’m usually a 2k person but for ten bucks I decided to go for… https://t.co/uJoOIyMMVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kavitabatra77 @heARTISTatWORK @LindaEdwardsi @guay_ms @mraspinall @pattersonaubrey @DrFrankRud @Rdene915… https://t.co/Fg1RDhiFRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mizkris18 @PeteSampson_ @punknshine @SB_ShovelSlayer Kris I have watched ND hoops since Johnny Dee coached. Sat be… https://t.co/w8djyb8vEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone know a quick way to search all your past tweets? I want to find the first time I tweeted to Matt Gaetz… https://t.co/GDA9PtzlfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️ #ducksdj #letsgoducks #djlife #family #anaheimducks @ Honda Center https://t.co/HmHftRK9tN]]></document><document><![CDATA[So...... we CAN get snow on Cape. Hmmmmm. Ok, let’s go back to bare ground now.      #Weather#NewEngland#Rain#Snow#… https://t.co/JTMpcWa9bZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMAZlNGNATURE So exactly what is the English proper name for “baby camel.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes What a shame, another hit piece on our President !  Orange Man Bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebarrywe @geofffox Geoff, meet Barry, one of the best guys I know. Smart, kind and extremely generous. (sent me… https://t.co/Rj0h92t5vg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimCindric @jeff_gluck @GPSTPETE @RustyWallace @Team_Penske @DaleJr @IndyCaronNBC @TeamChevy YES ! GREAT QUES .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, I know how this works. My question is: how do you get a shot at the title!? What kinda match would it be?… https://t.co/8feNMTBGw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenCarman @SportsBoyTony @DustinFox37  Dustin Fox sources also thought the Browns were going to hire Pat Campbell as their next head coach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home cooking officiating in Duke N.C. game, charge calls on Barrett are ridiculous. #boughtoff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah Kendzior is losing her shit on MSNBC, and I empathize with her exasperation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why Brockhampton gets criticized so much. Personally I just think that Isaac Brockhampton’s music is incredible]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I’m tired and I should go to sleep Also me: there’s an entire tilt shift subreddit I just discovered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the Hell happened to Loomer? I don’t always agree with her tactics, but this stinks of leftist BS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No doubt the guy is a good coach and I’m sure he’ll be a good analyst but he’s a scumbag of a person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Lupulin Mutant by @sloopbrewing at @strangebrew610 — https://t.co/idddhsM8m6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gonglei89 @WaltFrench There should also be an depreciation charge embedded in future GDP that is an offset against… https://t.co/vJrmulBGfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom Waits being fascinated by the taxidermy in the Billy Reid store where I worked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yesnicksearcy @GoHeels Lucas should have mentioned that it was C D Chesley that started broadcasting ACC basketball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jorge_OnilH @laluzjose @ElCaribeRD Tienes tu criterio pero no debes imponerselo a otros.eso es básico en la democr… https://t.co/u142UZiPBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahahaha I Just have to say I love @ChrisCrocker Fuck Any Of You hating Fucks who think anything less then amazin… https://t.co/2RcvNK60p2]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s going to be lit when the security guards start dancing! #UCF  🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥 https://t.co/ZZeeZltTv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsnell No worries. Love the show, appreciate you taking the time to engage. Had never heard of Pattern Matching, picked up a copy. 👍 📚]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to announce...I'll be drawing "Smarts!", published this year by @FreeSpiritBooks. Here's a peep at a few of… https://t.co/vL0q5vRU9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t even finish watching this documentary.. just throw the whole fucking family away 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesACrockett @KamalaHarris This is the one that gives DC statehood, and 16 year olds the right to vote, yes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/PeCU8Jhi41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Like secret Congressional slush fund to pay sexual assault or harrassment victims. Paid for with tax… https://t.co/NIIV7ha3YW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776Stonewall @skloba I suspected that the other day. Too much of a coincidence. Her and booker sponsor it, then j… https://t.co/XqmWWcUsH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @breannastewart @_BonnBonn @M_Tuck3 @rachelbanham_1 @M_H2OMan24 @am_bam14 @HoopItUp_34 @CaitCraft… https://t.co/AwEyVK8IlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JinxSuspended I speculated maybe it was end of run there. Was just a guess. Now trying to get a little more perspective. So we’ll see]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattyMurray @SenatorCantwell I cannot believe the DNC has rejected banning Corporate PAC money! If you support thi… https://t.co/OBGZY1XH9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bwaykippen @FalsettosBway I heard the score in college. Fell in love with it. This role in particular spoke to me.… https://t.co/VlChpRnTzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[SMH y’all had a golden opportunity to use “I need $” teeth from how high and failed]]></document></documents></author>