<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AlexStepney1 @Alan_Tonge @SirBobby Can’t blame you for that!!!!😂 I remember being a ball boy at the S End and you… https://t.co/XygxqfsJXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading this 3 second tweet took away 15 minutes of my life... I need a beer 😓🍻 @budweiserusa wya?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Bryce Drew things what we saw today was “sensational defense,” we are screwed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[View of one of the Water Tower out in Lake Michigan. @donnie_phares @iahrainman https://t.co/5SBhQpDAg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[45 u were elected by the EC, u only won 45 % of a 1/3 of the voters who actually voted... u lost the House... u are… https://t.co/Nxpwcj376M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes life takes you in different directions/paths, but you always got them if they need anything🤞🏼 miss my hig… https://t.co/5jYdVTmjrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting young and showing him how it’s done! #dapitislit @ Corpus Christi, Texas https://t.co/LAwn2E6syT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianHamel_ On WHO do I lie about being 6foot+ 🤔🤔 don’t start w me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEVinceRusso @mattkoonmusic @RussoKoonTWC  This is why I’m a SUPERBRO! So early, so uncut!! Brand NEW truth with… https://t.co/kyQulS1M2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDincauze @ChrisFrancis54 @spopslee @kasie @HotlineJosh @BernieSanders Of course she did. She is a never Bernie fool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amelia_draper Wow we wow wow Amelia draper you are looking very beautiful  love the hat  ok  your friend   Jim  Wh… https://t.co/Mh9RqJsON2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Varneyco @RepDebDingell Does it encompass the ruling elite also?...Thought not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will be part of new Animal Science course at Montgomery next year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do i have a haughting memory of a child who was hurt... 🤔 wish i could help this child i can only rest assure i… https://t.co/7S4h7m0SIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Human being in 2019 making just a little over minimum wage: wish I had more time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tvnnoticias Que clase de gente se ve que son unos vulgares que no respetan la autoridad]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only thing that is making me get out of bed every morning is senior trip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todays #composerwalk is on a bus? Heading into #midtown #NYC to hang out with @kennebreww and @bourquesimmons !  It… https://t.co/BCxWwMD919]]></document><document><![CDATA[How good of a chance was that for Edina? Hit the post once and missed the net high the second time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyrieauniece @ItsKortney https://t.co/u16BeeiJ8E how can people like this really exist?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AC360 @CNN @SenBlumenthal Or he is afraid Russians will poison him or his family]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cant #wait till #spring n #summer so I can thro my #shoes back on #her #26inchrims #gmc #yukon #cordelldrakemusic… https://t.co/CsajJUfyhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely Thursday afternoon at Suds Monkey Brewery. https://t.co/QHNDFQgiym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deptulahasrage I fucking agree I put $40k plus not jus my Iptay d my tickets r my travel to all away games r bowl game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shanemgillis  "He died on the track..... Like a man".  Just too funny. #sheetz #mechanicsburg #camo #bigbull]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a great Friday. Today is as good a day as every to make a change for the better! It’s your life!… https://t.co/ctFbMaWAw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BFerrisVerified Thank you lol I could not find that info online anywhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamWThomas hey dum dum, cussing to make a point means there is no legitimate point to be made]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all wanna claim y’all were born in houston, texas but lift up that sleeve.. aver que pinche nakos! never forget where you came from!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthonyVslater How can this be the same person? https://t.co/EIOgfPiimg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phew 😅... for a second there I thought Ripple had already pivoted to HR and I.T. software after the JPM announcement https://t.co/XjDVvxuKJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been doing so good with my restrictive diet, but the past two days...where is the diligence? I haven’t gone of… https://t.co/9sU8JNlKRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peabodypress If we could depoliticize the discussion, we might reach a compromise]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: From the Archives: L.A. County Sheriff’s 1934 ‘aero quadron’: Volunteer pilots and their aircraft… https://t.co/vTN14byTEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[when ya dick small but she pretends to choke on it to boost ur fragile male ego&gt;&gt;&gt; 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspiration leading a world of lnspired progress and participation.          #SparkChangeSummit @ UCLA - James Brid… https://t.co/UKAJVeX11j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whitewater Valley Friends of the NRA Banquet. @ Kuhlman Center https://t.co/hhF2VV7iI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning’s latest: it’s done, per multiple reports. Fee is over $11m. Four-year deal, $4.5m per (so the total o… https://t.co/sgCygE6W6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doug65295444 @superhooper50 @RyanAFournier @Shapiro_2024 Its official MAGA is the new snowflakes, 😂😂😂😂 he knocked his hat off😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetsGoDU @jovenitti Only one necessary for DU puck, although I would entertain the thought of two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erik_niel @bwright635 @WaltDisneyWorld That’s so awesome!! Happy Birthday Griffin!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost makes me want to take another ride down Bragg Blvd. Almost ..  lol  #nba #northcarolina #theville #hometown… https://t.co/QPwTsxuJO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlyZone36778026 @MFS001 @RosannaMrtnz @StateDept @CIA @rnovoa @MossadNews Then what did you mean? You brought up h… https://t.co/10baQY3499]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrifying when your opinion columnist becomes executive editor of the newspaper @PittsburghPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GAUAHAR_KHAN It’s horrific, is there any rule of laws does work in India! These culprits got to be bring to justic… https://t.co/lnP3Wh6wNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylertringas I was just thinking “if there’s one thing Tyler needs...it’s more bags”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VH1PNUT___ yerrr everyone knows that t was a pathological liar anyways😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@builtbydoozers @jaycaspiankang Well, I've never lived in Buffalo, so can't say either way. I've visited, seems nic… https://t.co/2B44Xy4riz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#latergram - More pictures from the Royal Ontario Museum @romtoronto in Toronto! Saw some artifacts from the Japan… https://t.co/SE8w45UKj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_AKA_Becker @derek_mafs @AOC Not even remotely true. Many people have seen outlets like CNN and MSNBC for what… https://t.co/kBpq2HdnWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roxxibabe @HillBuzz @kathygriffin From Boston ma.  3/5/1770  Fake news was sent everywhere about murder. Soldiers… https://t.co/bEJ6Ae4YaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eli_Bitan תודה רבה השם שהאישה הזאת לא יהא בכנסת'הבא אישה יוצא בשאלה ושונא חרדים ברוך שפטרני]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just in time for #WomensHistoryMonth on March 1.  Toni Harris commits to Central Methodist University. She is the f… https://t.co/XqW4253sAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO ms. , I have been every color there is on this planet more than once. Therefore I really don't unders… https://t.co/n2b4MUTQZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one got on dis app saying Jordan would make it to the Finals with any team he's on. That's something yall did co… https://t.co/jz3Uq1KNYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never seen a more perfect example of shit parenting. If your kids are like this I hate you and I hate your kids]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting... Ex-Trump White House lawyer calls Mueller 'hero,' says probe is no witch hunt - ABC News - https://t.co/Flp7A8KNHm via @ABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many teams in the state are on the field for an intrasquad on March 2nd? @PikevilleHSBSB https://t.co/oAOdhDaGwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you’re stuck. Teachers want their students to succeed, and in the current system, you can succeed without engagi… https://t.co/eAUJFIV1Dj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman I believe the demoncrat's are racing to the far left all too set up Hillary to jump in the race at t… https://t.co/6PJh42CMX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should be illegal for the big fella @JaayUpNext_ to be moving like this!! 6A football has another year to deal with… https://t.co/IquO0xvcsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollegeHoopNews @Trekking_Wombat They haven't watched the Tony Barbee days of Auburn basketball. Then, you would k… https://t.co/oxpYFASN60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay away from them stay away from them stay away from me Bieber stay away from them just stay away from Justin Bie… https://t.co/iaJV5jS40L]]></document><document><![CDATA[The venue we were gonna have the show at got shut down for illegal activities.  Found a new venue,but illegal activ… https://t.co/ior0r1JB5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anytime a waiter asked me if Pepsi is ok. I replied “I’ll take a water” https://t.co/d4bzn5Xsro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@audrieonline Me giving you support and reassurance https://t.co/dxfxrTHAe1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GilbertoVazquez Aquí si van, este fue del último (2015) https://t.co/4NiFu0PX0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had my dms set up weird but now they should be entirely open. My bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duke lost because they have zero depth and experience. That is all. #GoHeels]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump trump (the idiot in the White House) promised (a faithful pledge) that he’d be too busy to golf (r… https://t.co/Ni5bQD6Lce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnlyStarGaming @Jackhyper35 @CrankageGames @FlashPointLive @buck_dman @FruitJuje @TwitchSquarll @runningwolfTTV… https://t.co/wmei6f4RDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of the 12 hour watch.. I usually don’t work more than 4, because I finish everything so fast and efficiently]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a meeting after work, so decided to drop into sipbrew for dinner and a beverage first. Started with the Hound o… https://t.co/iM8wDw7rK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GamblingExpert2 @CWFHollywood @TheEliDrake @TyMatthewsPMA Yeah your ridiculous.  We both are of good size there plusnthata like 7 years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not hard AT ALL to stop making promises you know you have no intention of keeping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beth2_k3a @b77_sarah Miss Cortez will be come a Magnificent rich Person like Miss Maxine waters. $$$$$]]></document><document><![CDATA[My message to Jay Wilds: the truth will set you free (let people know you lied cause the cops pressured you)… https://t.co/X1daZB3dvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael @XTrillian It's the same as when the white trash are just now hating Trump because of their umm TAX… https://t.co/QwEYgUEbRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Isles vs the Leafs/Tavares this season:   2-0 Goals 10-1 Tavares: 0 points, -1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxTemkin I see this every time I go to target. :( https://t.co/sCFHj4XY7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marti160patria Cuando nacisteis votaron al nene y criaron la placenta , y para colmo está ,nació esclava e hija de… https://t.co/w5nUD7mwYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[who would #LetsGoDucks fans rather draft? assuming we draft near 5th overall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve came a long ways. It’s hard sometimes. I used to steal ppls leftovers out the break room at lunch cause I’d be… https://t.co/cNN7mN24sq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaneDavs Pretty much, yes. Rowers will however practice in a boat. ( shell actually) However the strength program… https://t.co/GOr3Uq1ZJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VosPere @aboutsqualor @GrantEubanks @CryptoCanuckk @AOC Your pie chart there represents carbon dioxide. Do you hav… https://t.co/s9eiIiKhN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beemerpga @GOLF_com @b_dechambeau As a GC Superintendent people that do that absolutely disgust me.  Sergio did th… https://t.co/jnovNL1Yv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pondering the better guitarist... @hurricanenita vs.  #ruytersuys going see @nashville_pussy tonight, so I am biased.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To take away #opioid medication is BEYOND cruelty. 🤬 Its #CrimesAgainstHumanity. @FDA_Track ' 'We can try and take… https://t.co/m1Pb9VLG4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing brings me more joy and happiness than being with @heidimwilson, @sydneywilson_55, and @spencerwilson11!  I… https://t.co/Yy9Yw5W4NM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kare11 Absolutely!!  Folks lack common sense....Funny...many Presidents before were applauded for bringing up the… https://t.co/aNva5V2gxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ambeezy10 @TheJamieNeal Hell Yes... leaving Chicago a day early to make sure I'm at that]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RolandMartinUnfiltered uncle Ro Ro @CJPearsonFrauds didn't have his bottle this morning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consultas para megaproyectos siguen en 100 días de AMLO: Tren Maya, Huexca, corredor del Istmo https://t.co/CYN2WOII1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I challenge you to go out of your way today and do three small nice things for those around you (kids or adults). R… https://t.co/PsYAbvY9w7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Liberty! Headed to the ASUN Conference Championship! So proud of this team. #RiseWithUs @libertymbb! @ Vines Cen… https://t.co/SsOJo6WeV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The World Created, False Ego. Has Done Something Very Un-Cool. It Has You Convinced. That Your Mind.  Is All You! W… https://t.co/9SMaSVdZ4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adeyanjudeji It is not INEC. An adage in YORUBA says: "AMUKUN ERU E WO, ONI OKERE LE N WO E WO ISALE" Indeed, gras… https://t.co/8RICbWxCiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂  In the midst of watching Miss Maisel, and I just loved this scene... https://t.co/Q1SOzacKsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't trust people who only use the Slack web app. why would you do that to yourself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you leave clothes at a guys house and he doesn’t return them washed, he don’t fuck with you.]]></document></documents></author>