<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LoveAndyC @rrregss @NineDaves @daniellestaub Day was made with this one! I’m..🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking back on all of my decisions I've made in highschool and the only thing I regret/wish I did was I wish I took choir freshman year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you should know right from wrong when being with me for a good amount of time without me having to tell you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Barrel Aged French Toast by @angrychairbeer @ Angry Chair Brewing — https://t.co/I148JEweJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dchinn2005 I read online yes I informed myself ahead of going to doc I’m ready to ask questions to get this over with]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Christ the King Lutheran Church in Cary, NC https://t.co/FZivqvAxiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you help this family?   More than a year after a deadly hit-and-run, Lun's family is asking for any new leads i… https://t.co/vmcf3F7Mk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[im just kinda confused as to why ur doing this... like i know ur still going through it but are you really doing an… https://t.co/tKcxXVt5zw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any art friends have a preferred cheap canvas brand? For acrylic paint? I’m in a creation mood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late Post....Same Page with our D38! It’s “Taco Wednesday “🤷🏻‍♀️@506!! Give them fuel for all that Freight💪🏼coming… https://t.co/4vtU25rPd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminiscing on the days when I had zero anxiety/depression and had zero cares in the world except just giving love… https://t.co/bbpx9NhZJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had all you can eat sushi &amp; other Japanese goods for $18 C.A.D. another reason why Canada is better than the U.S.A. #freedom]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a #mondaymood face. I’m coming back to life! Finding the appetite and a bit of energy. At least enough to f… https://t.co/wmDZ0jzdfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetCuriousNow @MedSimulation @SuzieEdgren @BULEON_Clement @JCPalaganas @JenArnoldMD So excited to present our cutt… https://t.co/eGzTBUIJgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t be nice to niggas cause they swear you want them like no bitch i was being nice to yo duck ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morgan was supposed to call my mom “Moma” but here we are. https://t.co/JYOP5IHlTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinktaxiblogger @CityStrides I know. But I have OCD when it comes to maps/numbers/running. I don’t like how my cur… https://t.co/uuKYibW4O6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiffmgraves and @TheMSBar great job on The Gandy! I had the lovliest time as a panelist at The Gandy conference th… https://t.co/C5goVmLRBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name, India, translates to: body of water. Great, I love water. My dad partially got it from the film ‘Gone With… https://t.co/5Nrc9EwYoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie Your wife will become 21st century Doris Day. Go buy an island for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is by far one of the best bargains I’ve ever found in my life! This top/halter dress was seriously marked down… https://t.co/yWoavxOypr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandaarusselll @collburke_13 Gasp!!! Amanda! What is wrong with you????]]></document><document><![CDATA[legislators support farm bills because of the inclusion of conservation subsidies.  In 1996 Congress enacted reform… https://t.co/7MVymFcLfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEBrightbill My mom was calling me her 📕 library rat 🐭 and now I make a living of writing manuscripts on rodent be… https://t.co/snxgxOmcaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[First things first: feed @DrakeUGriff! #Griffentine #MyValentine https://t.co/kHlhvLRJpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@satodaycatholic @frMichaelBoulet This Pic really touch me deeply Pregnant Mom in prison ArchBishop Gustavo Blessed… https://t.co/Z5a3kEfndD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anything for Salinas 💕 siempre . . . #weekend #vibes #dfw #dallas #plano #kumbiakings #selena #selenaquintanilla… https://t.co/gmGBmb3nyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lauren_Alaina can we get a live version of Faithfully on the next album....? Or just by itself. Whatever works.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parqués and friends. 💙 Yet another epic fun day with the fam.  . Parqués is the Columbian version of Parcheesi.  Fu… https://t.co/HYr1a0AmD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got me some good baby lovin this afternoon! You are loved Parker Finlay!! 😍 @ Chattanooga, Tennessee https://t.co/2t6O3QZt8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly who’s idea was it to put Hugh Jackman and Zac Efron in the same movie I need to personally thank them]]></document><document><![CDATA[BITCH your mans and I dated FIVE YEARS ago and HE DUMPED/CHEATED ON ME! Stop giving me dirty looks, nobody gives a fuck but you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TakeCareersByStorm #TakeEducationByStorm #TakeTomorrowByStorm @GSWEduDean @GaSouthwestern https://t.co/iuDWjC73dO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Jesus: please let me sleep this well tonight.   **  #brittany #brittanyspaniel #americanbrittany… https://t.co/MT4Y8GaFWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeavnlyAngel76 We seriously need to give animals more credit 💔 thanks for sharing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep up your night time regimen with pincurls. Do you need pin curl help? Watch theses quick videos for assistance.… https://t.co/nQRZd6Zqvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Maddie- ask about POTUS’s lies!  Do you care about this country?!?!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this . When will us humans ( meaning mostly myself of course ) realize that life is not picture perfect and we… https://t.co/8VbLewmuZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of Valentine’s Day, my all time favorite story..... In 7th grade on Valentine’s day, Trey rode his bike to… https://t.co/5IadrqlA0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennisCode Lucky to have you on the team! You bring such a positive attitude, drive, and customer focus...look for… https://t.co/cm3LJFRg9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Washington doesn't have a line that you can't erase,just like the lines people draw in sand,poof and they're gone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara Yes.   I’d also like to know how often it was over not receiving enough sauces for his Chicken McNuggets...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travthroughlife @visitRaleigh @LafayetteVill Where we met 😍...so I agree!#NCFaves @Zanyunoodles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TNTbr 🙏 Please 🙏 don’t forget the Venezuelan’s struggle with the Maduro Dictatorship in the country right now. Ple… https://t.co/SkOgyPcotp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sog36 @RevLDReed @annamagnelli @Duckhuntinggrl @Cheryl_L_Davis @arsborg @intrinsictweets @cat_kizzy @AngeicaNewsom… https://t.co/XyGJMcW7tP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooooh, I love you so                                       But why I love you, I’ll never know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sendavidperdue Says the man who voted for the #GOPTaxScam which accelerated the growth in the national debt.  Have a seat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isabelascb Ahhhhhhh é que ela é tão descartável que eu esqueci q ela existe e li errado.]]></document><document><![CDATA[13 PERGUNTAS ALEATÓRIAS DEMAIS PARA SEREM RESPONDIDAS RAPIDAMENTE:   1 - Janeiro 2 - nem lembro kkk  3 - nunca tive… https://t.co/bGW31uLs7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You don't honestly believe "highly liked" do you? Because if you do, you're a lot worse of mentall… https://t.co/0ustNeTqNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savageharvi Thank you because I’m dead serious. I’m out of concealer, so I’m thinking, why not start a channel and… https://t.co/qxj38ihU0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump While you are in Viet Nam, why don’t you just stay there. Go squat in a rice paddy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have listened to sports talk radio most of the day on @680TheFan and I’m so disappointed.  You all have daughters… https://t.co/2QQVd8yg6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome Wednesday kick ass session ilovekickboxing_nashville_tn Best cardio full body workout ever and we have the… https://t.co/GlwZxy1Hvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me in San Marcos this past weekend when the guys ate Dairy Queen and Whataburger 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leroisays it is he who should be ashamed. who mistakes in-n-out for whata??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time at dinner. Goodbyes never get easier 😌 https://t.co/Mo1D9TngJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all, @rgay is my favorite on Twitter for many reasons, but especially for this kind of consistent, relatable cont… https://t.co/ufuep4iSi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox News confirms Mexico deported 25 gang members linked to MS-13 who were hidden in caravan of migrants |  https://t.co/TH8UvBF2o4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sheesh just when I felt good I’m back to square one. I’m going to lock myself in my room.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jetblacktori @mushyhpg Wow. Y’all look at 2 celebrity pedophiles get dismantled from their pedestals we worshipped… https://t.co/qtMYJPXsoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[To lead with #integrity and develop and coach his or her team @EverLearnTweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[┏┓  ┃┃╱╲ In this  ┃╱╱╲╲ house  ╱╱╭╮╲╲ we  ▔▏┗┛▕▔  ╱▔▔▔▔▔▔▔▔▔▔╲      use google ╱╱┏┳┓╭╮┏┳┓ ╲╲ ▔▏┗┻┛┃┃┗┻┛▕▔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to TJ tomorrow for like 24hrs maybe less just to party and come back home and I’m packing as if I were going for a whole week lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a joy to watch @stanfordwswim seniors do their thing at their last duel meet v cal]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am pro life but I believe people would benefit from reading this woman’s story about the horrors her mother faced… https://t.co/vI5PZql9Og]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GingeeyMinaj @CloutVonStroke Yo I say “hoes don’t get cold” alllll the time😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leadership is not about being adversarial, says @JustinTrudeau. It’s about being open to criticism. “She (@Puglaas)… https://t.co/cwifXTwgNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[En FCPPC: Uribe plantea cambios en extradición para exguerrilleros de las Farc | News | https://t.co/LQtFya3HFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our CEO, Scott D. Pattison, answers questions from John Harris of @politico at the State Solutions panel on the sid… https://t.co/ncsDzZt8bx]]></document><document><![CDATA[10/10 had a customer come in today and hit me with “fuck dude, you’ve lost an extreme amount of weight. You look go… https://t.co/KYoyFfJRBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to destress on the #blog today https://t.co/gfExIdwxyO #blogger #destress https://t.co/WPh8DMGwPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noraborealis @StillKickinCo WAY more fun. And too late. Thanks for a great weekend. So fun to be with you. 💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeepCares Can you send me a private message with my case number? Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trizzy4l He probably always got doo rags on and they finally got on him about it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Sad that poor @w_terrence wasn't able to be there because of his accident.  He… https://t.co/g2MmvCBz02]]></document><document><![CDATA[me when I check my bank account &amp; I actually have enough to pay for the iced coffee I already bought]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching bands with @danbickley - what we do best ❤️ #britishinvasion https://t.co/trSYYIH5ez]]></document><document><![CDATA[And another loss with Mata man what is going on?? 2 subs due to injury in 25 minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught a #ditto earlier today in Dtla on #PokemonGO if anyone’s in need]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just bought 4 natural hair products and spent $37 😭😭😭😭 LORD. Relaxer me pls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeborahNorville Thanks for our previous interest in our #TackleReading piece. Thanks to the support of NFL teams a… https://t.co/AFBN6wBgL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USEmbassyAbuja @UNHumanRights @EUinNigeria @BTBreakingTimes BUHARI HAS ALREADY CLAIMED VICTORY DUE TO HIS CORRUPT… https://t.co/3VgYHGT47M]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is so wrong. This rhetoric has become normalized by 45!!  No, it is not acceptable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 @VivJo27 Must be. Near me in Alabama. I’m forever amazed at the willingness to hate and judge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @rpetty Is he visiting the guy who he let get hacked up with a bone saw?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mika Brzezinski Burns Donald Trump With Barack Obama Border Wall Gag https://t.co/zV0thjxnsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Ghostface Killers (feat. Travis Scott) by 21 Savage, Offset &amp; Metro Boomin on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/HnjTbGJDnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter As pissed 😡 as I am I think 🤔 she would be better off at Fox News where they run 24/7 propaganda mach… https://t.co/fk2fI05Aoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing day getting our outdoor learning area ready! Thank you Kingsland Baptist!  #StallionsDeserveIt… https://t.co/FXBrJf3uPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling the love today thanks to my family and friends! 22X2 is good so far! 🥳🎉🎂 #unpresidentsday #birthdayjoytrumpstrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[CONGRATULATIONS @ItsRamiMalek !!! I knew you would win the golden statue!!.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for taking time and thought to put together a long list of shout-outs and accolades Richard.  We have inc… https://t.co/gh08EnTHHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday Dinner: A Valentine’s Dinner for my parents 💜💜💜♥️♥️♥️ @ Jurupa Valley, California https://t.co/pfkJ1YCDE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you are telling the American people you don’t give a shit about what we want  we are sick of paying the price of… https://t.co/BLrH75ymDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS WEDNESDAY SHAQ IS BACK CATCH THE LATEST WORK FROM #shaqfamous LIVE, THIS WEDNESDAY NIGHT! #therageweho • •… https://t.co/ep5MiN5iQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sumeriankiing @MeekMill I was implying that-that song ISN’T on championships which was so obvious to so many others 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Download THE  ULTIMATE 2019 Content Calendar Template to Get a Grip on Your Social Media Content FAST… https://t.co/J0krZvpOlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t reached 70 degrees in a month. Thoughts and prayers are appreciated for me n my bronze during this difficul… https://t.co/J6TK4gdWEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoDOT hey just a heads up the highways around the Perryville area are really bad.  Looks like no one has done anything to them.]]></document></documents></author>