<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Koolaiddddddd!!! #win2more #final4status #wearePVHS @GaQMcK1 #FORTHEWIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I hate being bored... my mind wonders and i start overthinking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve awakened with “Sexy Boy” stuck in my head for reasons unknown, so I guess this is a good sign for today’s phot… https://t.co/u7lOuTL0gI]]></document><document><![CDATA[i read this and i was like damn.. then i find out i knew the girl that cheated and i was like DAMN smh. this is so… https://t.co/9RF0PpiBFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this idea! Get ready, Heath teachers, I’m choking to ask for your poems!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Biotest Pharmaceutical Corporation? We're hiring in #Hinesville, GA! Click the link in our bio for… https://t.co/hDM5V1KEOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ Conservatives don't think things through before speaking, because they lead with hatred not love, racism… https://t.co/QPW2IxejVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSports who would’ve thought something like this would happen in probably one of the biggest games this season 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are going to leave Hilton tomorrow night and there will be 4 inches of snow on the ground that was not there… https://t.co/303T5uWoiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimLangevin Please support the Baby Born Alive legislation in congress. This barbaric practice has no place in our… https://t.co/h47fs07TtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DPNJ @RepSwalwell Of course it should be - but my money is on that it won’t be. We shall see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I CANT WAIT to get away for the weekend not to mention my first time leaving my laptop for more than a few hours si… https://t.co/FukpU4MN5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricVictoria6 @danibryan_ @thaboi_austo tbh i don’t really care when u started playing but just please look up the… https://t.co/KbQeLuv6Dv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theFordon Thanks! Now I’m out of bread until I bake more this weekend. 😖🥖🍞👩🏻‍🍳]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how i feel about the new @judahandthelion album https://t.co/60r8Uva4b0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaJeffries_ Welcome home, sir. Thank you for your service. God bless you and your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tmbeanie415 @JoannBagno @MatthewWolfff @B52Malmet @TheLoyalO @ybbkaren @Clara_Resists @Augustus709… https://t.co/P3lmQBi9Mu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby boy Leo  is looking  at my friends  he saying Love  you Everyone @ Albany, New York https://t.co/38lWSdeUQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know why I drink coffee w/ shots of espresso at 8 pm. Literally still have at least 5 more hours to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[We laughed A LOT tonight! • johnbcrist — thank you for a fantastic night of laughter. What a great show! Great seat… https://t.co/IWAUgREqXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not much of a decorator, but I couldn’t pass this up for my 1st kitchen decoration. 😂 @ Janoski's Farm and Gree… https://t.co/ksu2g3kKh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeabodyLove1 @IvankaTrump @hadip @codeorg She’s a pathetic excuse of a woman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SparkleTea @davidhogg111 Then you do not understand #GrassRoots activism and why it is so important to listen to a… https://t.co/FjggruLhh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFreeze Happy Big Dog Sunday from Lucy &amp; Lexi Whippany Nj https://t.co/zS78AdWYg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep John Lewis is a civil rights icon, a living legend and American treasure. Happy birthday @repjohnlewis !! Thank… https://t.co/OEvhW9TocG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wiselike_imsure @PatTheBerner @johncusack Where have you been for the past 30 years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Есть ли вообще надежды, что меня кто-то полюбит просто как Таню? Просто меня, ни за что.. Просто так... полюбит...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stone_719 The very hairs of your head are numbered. He is an ever present, an everlasting God.  He holds you in Hi… https://t.co/f5fVwj6Njd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBaier do these young people understand that Medicare means the gov chooses your doc but won’t pay for medical… https://t.co/TJKzZMfLtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotherGoose1919 @EdKrassen The problem is they cant protect you from the Constitution and Federal and State laws.… https://t.co/juWOFla8XU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpear02 @TODAYshow @SavannahGuthrie I thouraly agree with you that she always interviews people very combativly an… https://t.co/ArEYfc2gyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Rossome Bluebonnet team is ready to ROCK!! @rossomerams @yvetter91011 https://t.co/xZ78doVfjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much to reflect on. I met #petertork at an amazing venue for musicians -- good food and drinks, too -- called… https://t.co/OMYma46uNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just listed last week and this brick colonial in Morningside is already under contract💪   📍1257 Duffield, Morningsi… https://t.co/BAKDVL8E3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow it would be cool to have someone at my games or come home to tell someone about them LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP You have no voice in our government. You and Trump are traitors and Mueller will be coming for y’all. You were… https://t.co/PEwD6hM2hD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another 5k down on my list 😁😁 . . . #rundisney5k #princessrun #rundisney2019 @ Run Disney Princess 5k https://t.co/G5yRw7VPu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InfantGoose6565 @taddmike You make an assumption but that’s okay.  Look at his work in the community, regardless o… https://t.co/5JkXnMdFUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidBowieGlam Happy birthday! Mine was just on 1/28. Aquarian’s rock!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk what it's like to have a deadbeat babydaddy. So can't relate, sisters 💋😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm hoping he'll go to prison. Not sure there'll be room on the trump cell block, but any cell will do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I disagree I do not think violence is coming from both sides, I think it's coming only from the Democrats and the L… https://t.co/EmdcDszUIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help I started mini dabbing to be ironic and now I can't stop doing it after I say anything ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris asks: who are we?! Then: “we are better than this.” https://t.co/iRa6fif4JO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissPassey @Hollyoaks @AJ_Woodward1 And I love this new #Hollyoaks couple! 😍 #TeamBrienna #Brienna #Bonnets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodbye blow-dry, hello frozen hair ❄️🖕🏼 @ Upper West Side https://t.co/xz0hy8LGw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Speaking of enemies, your friend Putin is threatening the US. You have alienated our allies. What… https://t.co/RySbu5kbIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@17SHONUFF17 @eyesthroughmy50 @adab3la @gordonpreece @stonecold2050 @Jackstar009 So republicans did that to the oce… https://t.co/bEryZiCB5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does that include the Thousands of children incarcerated for seeking #Asylum? #ChildConcenrationCamps by TRUMP!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_gracepowell I still like him, I just haven’t been to church in a long time :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si le enseño a hablar a una niña de 2 años me dan $500 MI MOMENTO HA LLEGADO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noah Syndergaard open to extension with Mets https://t.co/MoRO4OQa2Z via @SNYtv @Noahsyndergaard]]></document><document><![CDATA[The golden opportunity you are seeking is in yourself. It is not in your environment, it is not in luck or chance,… https://t.co/S20spMM9Wr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real feel -24 #wthell I have I have never in my life been someplace so freaking cold and snowy I'm done.… https://t.co/1YsUXp77es]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ObfuscateClear Did you see this? Those stats? Something doesn't add up. Maybe it's me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grew up in Autauga County and went to Auburn in Lee County.  My heart is breaking for the good people of Alabama.… https://t.co/Xhe9nsXSNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charrly95 @realDonaldTrump Si la impresentable de La bomba Tucumana se postula a ALGO, asi sea para vicepresidente… https://t.co/IWURXhaZh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My workout today will be snow removal.  Is there a @Garmin or @Strava app for that?  If it isn’t on Strava it didn’t happen @LeindeckerWoody]]></document><document><![CDATA[#COLDCASE CLOSED:  Cindy Borgeson's sister disappeared while walking home from school in '73, her body was found in… https://t.co/3ZQiG7RkMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrated  #IntroduceAGirlToEngineeringDay yesterday by talking to middle school classes in South Carolina and Min… https://t.co/Y59Ftg9bcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Just Entered @BiGGsGolfTalk #February #Giveaway to WIN @golfpridegrips. ENTER TO WIN! @wcuebas #Giveaways!   https://t.co/7GtR0N6qy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think about it. The world can see what 40% cant!  Almost half of our citizens go along on board 100% with a corrupt… https://t.co/aF9peMERQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLEASE SHARE! @butts_sheriff needs your help in finding K-9 "Rico" in the area of Keys Ferry Road and Finchersville… https://t.co/yNRJtEToyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yourillus1onist Omfg bitch, I wish I had gotten this. I forgot it even existed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you a go-getter on the job? Do you dream big and go the extra mile to uncover the next groundbreaking idea? Lea… https://t.co/rGzvJLKCgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOFLiiRT @franamati @CoinATMRadar @CryptoPenguinAR @Bitcolution Pardon us.  We corrected in subsequent posts.    P… https://t.co/QPRrK4nQ9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Primary Health Network Charitable Foundation and Laurel Technical Institute are hosting the 6th annual Shamrock N R… https://t.co/ttvjiyvr6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕️☕️☕️☕️ (@ Home Kitchen in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/mEe7tuc9KM https://t.co/LzbCLV9RQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone said look heaven sent then another person told me i look hell good i’m here for it 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator Kamala Harris, on the campaign trail in South Carolina. @mollyharrell @kamalaharris @ M Vista https://t.co/tcuSOvaGyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesireeNavarro @lopezobrador_ Digna “dama de compañía” de un lozasno igualitos de “talentosos”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will forever be thankful for how much Jesus has taught me within the past couple of years.  Never lose your faith… https://t.co/NsDqSPMMoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter bloom!  I thought this wss Black-eyed Susan's growing, ...turns out this is second generation Tiger's Eye Su… https://t.co/Rn3I8oamR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pc: @RC3_440 #NYFW #streetfashionweek #jevonterance https://t.co/DO2W9cqVnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moral compass? Anyone supporting death to newborns, however they enter the world, is missing a SOUL.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[#joycemeyer #prayer #amen        Put Yourself in the Offering Plate  In 2 Corinthians 8, when Paul was talking to t… https://t.co/tFxbhBikGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me bout it   Feyi gets a bike  Feyi learns to drive  Feyi threatens people with a knife  Feyi loses glasses]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1: honestly, when I’m excited about something new and better, I drop the old immediately.  Much harder is when you… https://t.co/2Y7CDE7Sm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[oml fuck i look like being cool with a bitch knowing we fucked the same nigga !!!! YALL WEIRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are all I ever wanted love to be. 💕✨ @ Huntington Botanical Gardens Conservatory https://t.co/ceMNuJ2JjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToscanNick You must be in a crossroads: you went to Fyre Festival and Ja was your favorite rapper. Where do we go from here¿?]]></document><document><![CDATA[all i wanna know is how she’s being SO serious i would start CRACKING TF UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see it I like it I want it I got it ✨  @barriewrestling weissshotme  ————————— #BGP #prettyandpetty #wrestling… https://t.co/zthxaN4ZoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS You know darn well that not all American voters are on board. Matter of fact, a huge percen… https://t.co/pnVVYFrcu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Black Memphis, Beale Street Can Talk https://t.co/cfKsSdx78W via @kirstinlcheers]]></document><document><![CDATA[casually awaiting our next adventure @ Oklahoma City, Oklahoma https://t.co/4usnpmYnYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh breaks my heart when baby girl is sick, ugh ready for a less germs season even though I try so hard to prevent… https://t.co/GLj6USFehn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dennis just broke down and told me what he got me for my birthday and I’m over here like https://t.co/V5HN8bSpyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noah Rothman is loathsome. Wouldn't you know he'd be on one of the few days I try to watch Ruhle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson You need to change the name of your book to "the book of fake conspiracies" the criminals struggle to stay out of jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SCHOLARSHIP OPPORTUNITY!!! If you’re entering an education program and you are graduating from Cullman HS, you may… https://t.co/fVIANOILiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just ordered my tickets.  It’s for a great cause and is being done by one of my favorite Podcasters]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see us @ Fresh Plus - we’re heading into the final week of sales! @ Hyde Park (Austin, Texas) https://t.co/7NovUUgUFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just practicing our come-hither look. Not quite as good as @JesseKOO’s but I think we’re getting close.… https://t.co/1S2ELeTtmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donttrythis Enjoyed your kit-bashing vid and your tips about Weld-on 3!  I use a lot of CoroPlast (polypropylene)… https://t.co/0CSXBL4Vi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simple design to be honest. Probably just a way to keep them looking nice.   Van's are great shoes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can be in the worst mood and then I read a Grumpy Cat quote and... #laughter #tee-hee #smile #amusing https://t.co/E6LvoicK1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuseofIre DO NOT give that person a single dime more. You’ve already given her 2 chances. Move on. But before you… https://t.co/p3F21idgRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patty_nightgown @WhoopiGoldberg @ABC Lol, I won't stop 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣. Ty for your view.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dropping 200 calories has me feeling so lost 😂  I feel like I have to relearn all the things I used to eat to fit into my plan 🤪]]></document></documents></author>