<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Donald Trump, once again you do not tell the truth! I checked your poll numbers out! They are low,… https://t.co/HT18BQmUx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say girls can't fight... come check us out we will change your mind 😈❤️🔥 #girlpower #boxing #muaythai… https://t.co/b0kDZ8Slzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JolaLoila @TOPTVPINFO @DoRzeczy_pl Z nienawiści, jeżeli mówimy o politykach.  Jeżeli chodzi o elektorat to raczej… https://t.co/RmpuOdJwxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’d like to know: how has a paid family leave impacted your family? #MORisMore 👇🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone told me this at a party cause I was all like “back in PA” but I would never say “here in CA”...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4—I have accepted the challenge from @MissBlair87 to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations or reviews—… https://t.co/wyS03LjVx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robertinno53 @IngrahamAngle @CPAC @ChrisCuomo @realDonaldTrump #FeelTheBern2020 #FakeTrumpEmergency #FakePresident… https://t.co/s8UWzdlLTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukePerryIII @Jason_Priestley @TheGabrielle_C @jenniegarth Nooooooooo I am so heart broken 💔to hear the news today… https://t.co/pok3CV2LNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anuradha_murthy @gowithinco @thumbtack Aww thanks so much for coming and sharing your experiences with the group. 🧡]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more you try to defend yourself after already denying it makes you look more guilty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign the petition: Tell Trump to stop paying his own workforce poverty level wages. Take action here: https://t.co/PXOvvcB6NG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ralph Breaks the Internet (2018) dir. Rich Moore &amp; Phil Johnston https://t.co/MKpdBtZTyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisisweedies I’m February 6th....@axlrose @rickastley &amp; @bobmarley are my birthday twins ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gorgeous #mermaid #cupcake is available at #disney #artofanimationresort  Swim over and grab one! Contact me t… https://t.co/Sf2377NQAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love everything about a drug dealer and that’s rlly my problem lmfaooo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Manafort Lie to Mueller to Protect Trump?: A Closer Look https://t.co/hjD6FdlVT4 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the burger misterparadisenyc but don’t miss their fried chicken. Definitely one of the best fried chicken I’ve… https://t.co/yQ2t52mVDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a great day to be a Wildcat in the Orchestra! https://t.co/49dZMlIBJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@victoria_yyj @mondinion @Rob_Scanlan @realestateHants @BCHOMEHUNTER @REALTOR_Jacqui @jamescdwyer @kimcanhomes… https://t.co/2hPrl0dgCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bring on the King Cake #FindMeByTheFeathers @ Louisville, Kentucky https://t.co/vYQVauVwtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#iamachildofgod #iamstrong #drawings #godisgood #godismyrock I want to thank @c_strizzle for bringing God back into… https://t.co/Z1telFkgua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to Sprouts for the first time ever and I’m high so wish me luck https://t.co/wsY2XIObfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCEMSwatch Hopefully the drunk realizes his actions caused all of this 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my boyfriend @justinbieber !!🎉 So proud of where you are and how far you’ve become! Hope the marr… https://t.co/cJB9o8XR6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes on Instagram I block people the. Unblock them so they essentially I unfollow myself on their behalf ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[*tries to give my grandma a fist bump* G: “I’m going to leave you hanging because you don’t care about me”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SAloverElena @Uber @kwaye Then the day Uber informed my phone a total of It was $17, so I paid $15 in cash, Uber d… https://t.co/mUQwVSYonT]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fruit cake piss poor comedian no Political wisdom poor rateings AND A TOTAL FAKE AFRAID OF GETING OLD YOU NE… https://t.co/TqN3Yj0Mla]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Judge Who Let Manafort Off Easy With 47 Months Is An Arch-Conservative  https://t.co/2AtjUrph0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bearmyheart1973 @NLL @stevepriolo23 @NLLBandits @NEBlackWolves @CurtisDickson17 @NLLRoughnecks @DLintner14… https://t.co/o0xihIQqlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Writer_DG This is the way I write as well...not novels, but speeches, presentations, etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrjimflorentine Just watched the entire thing. Wtf. He’s still writing her love letters. 🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how I remember what our duty as Americans is. This is the First Amendment in action. Going to the theatre i… https://t.co/Rck0C5UdT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sempre é muito bom estar com você 😍😍😍 @ Lowell, Massachusetts https://t.co/ZdZw1xazcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[my future cell mate is @carkinn11 , hmm i wonder what trouble we’re gonna get in]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy me enteré que el 100% de mi calificación parcial era el examen...espero todos estén teniendo un mejor día que el mío]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genesis 3:2-3 (KJV)  And the woman said unto the serpent, We may eat of the fruit of the trees of the garden: But o… https://t.co/Nj3OrxRoDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proving the point that the Libs must be descriminating against conservatives]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need diverse texts in our classroom that celebrate people who are not white. Astronauts, writers, scientists, en… https://t.co/GP61PeFeVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know why your teachers were wearing jeans and white tops today? In support of Vera House and the White Ribbon Campa… https://t.co/D5Ei9RZPUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[text 305 four s|x seven 4967 #Russian #Femdom #visiting #Miami #dominatrix #bdsm  #mistress #model #hypnodomme… https://t.co/i2TwyA4Hmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three breweries in one night! ❤️ @ Big River Grille Downtown https://t.co/B5aFX6qtD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@npandey25 @OfficeNews @msexcel My job was to work out the UX flow in relation to other Office OCR technologies, li… https://t.co/lrOU5Awca0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pushed my button for @karengalera_! #TheVoice https://t.co/USC8z9hUXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out about the super talented letterer @homtweethom weekly #homwork thorough my equally talented letter… https://t.co/b3yZUXnu7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Chicago you still have an hour and a half to the polls close! Go vote!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperWiki Not everybody has to be represented for people to care.  If they do it now, it would seem like pandering… https://t.co/WSRXwx0vt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find this to be the most effective for me. I never really had any “formal” mentor established but I do reach out… https://t.co/rp1vw3SWN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetrews @TheDanforthMH @HermitageGreen Really happy to be here but wow is the sound distorted!]]></document><document><![CDATA[From her 1st birthday to her 21st birthday! #livingthegoodlife in Italy. We miss our baby today as it’s our first b… https://t.co/kY82ZVTJUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to #MivaCon19 (@ Birmingham-Shuttlesworth International Airport (BHM) in Birmingham, AL) https://t.co/Jx84MkDFhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Harris, I wish there was a way to fact check your words.  Personally, I don't believe a single thing you say!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfaooooooo On me Idgaf if you say he don’t bite, he’s nice or none of ts get that fucking dog on 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m always working on becoming the best Version of myself 🍃  🍃🏋🏽‍♀️🍃🏋🏽‍♀️🍃🏋🏽‍♀️🍃🏋🏽‍♀️🍃🏋🏽‍♀️🍃 #bodybycarol… https://t.co/ItXQUUN3bh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne @AOC That’s exactly what she’s suggesting even though she’s an example of how even the dullest knife in th… https://t.co/PmGSvw11C4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @LiftOurVote You’ve lost my support Hillary. Please go away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dear Don: Every morning I wake up and read that you are screaming about one thing or another. Whet… https://t.co/TyQySgRFlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't look at Maddow. She knows better. A Rhodes Scholar sold her mind and soul for $7M/yr?! I get depressed but th… https://t.co/7cd9cWQdU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaynieDane @doctorjenn @JessicaValenti really so that is why when the founders of planned Parenthood targeted blac… https://t.co/X9hDHbHj90]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @NerdvanaSpirits is playing “Face My Fears” from @KINGDOMHEARTS III over the speakers and it’s making me so happy 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOtransitLE  do you know if there is a signal issue between Guildwood and RougeHill westbound? Sitting between sta… https://t.co/qiWI3bkihq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllAboutTRH You 1000% have a point, but Katie is a mean, bitchy, bully also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joemtheoddball @HillaryClinton @arenasummit I can see that you look pretty clueless. Grow up little man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only place on the island with all house all night! Come see us! @ Coconut Jacks SPI https://t.co/7a7gcPnl6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrWrightNowTV @Twitwit08270216 You have people out here calling black immigrants vultures, leeches, trying to take… https://t.co/U55I8jK7uU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity When will this creep give up? he is a liar..guess he's terrified of the future when it's the Republica… https://t.co/rp8GUkNUuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHS_2015_1997 pretty sure I known you for 6 years but I don't know the date?  Do you?  🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InsteadOfCleaningUp I'll take a nap and dream about a different house. #needavacation #CleaningUp #sleeping #NewDAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RanttMedia @GOP Or.. because evil knows how to lie and get away with things. I knew a kid in school, awful kud, ev… https://t.co/uUpnxqZrSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto @SpeakerPelosi is no longer relevant .... #AirHeadAOC is the new mouthpiece of the Democrat party]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone know what is going on at IU North Hospital?  We are on a Code Red.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll be encouraging two very special friends at a planning meeting tonight!  @amoon606 @JoAnnSavoie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaSoprano That’s good, and many krewes are similarly strict,  it not all of em.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Central Park Condominiums in Cincinnati, OH https://t.co/mDmE6bt4Gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rach, you are so dang sweet! I love you more and more each day! Thank you💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I like that old time rock n’ roll!” 🎤🎸🎶🎹 I do like that old time rock n’ roll, it’s what I grew up on, and I STILL… https://t.co/DczNBo4zIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo @Montejp231 As long as there are Epstein's, Trump's, and Kraft's there will be human/sex trafficking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Innovation requires the new, not the same old way we taught it 10 years ago. What are we doing to truly be innovati… https://t.co/dsVfhiHSya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexFranzblau Tifanny is the best! She’s organized so many demonstrations and educational workshops in Broward and Dade!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another time ⌚ like getting another year onto wasn't enough more change 😂 😂 😂 🙏😇😉😊 @ Windsor, Canada/Detroit, USA B… https://t.co/RTSSiqU1J1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorbmurphy Never thought I’d beg for a 4” needle to be shoved into my spine but there I was...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been limited outside interaction while I balance these energies, cleans and continue metamorphosis. (*insert cocoon emoji)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lymepolicywonk @Lymenews Privacy, stigma, and discrimination are major concerns for the Lyme community, particular… https://t.co/Mul4Rtuiud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResourcefulMom @marleykristin 🍨🍦🍧Congratulations! A #FrozenFoodMonth #Twitterparty lucky winner happy dance for yo… https://t.co/myoSGxnrYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[No se que es peor haber tanta gente de acuerdo con la falta de ética de lvari@s que conozco y gente queriendo aún c… https://t.co/q1xIaP0sf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Not much on his buddy Kraft seeking sex at sex slave establishment either, is there more to that story,??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will realize you were everything im missing and you will tell me you’re in love with someone else..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JESSIEgraffPWR @slaniel @thebriankretsch @PapalNinja https://t.co/uIEI553Gb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[the amount of times people have told me my feelings are stupid... is stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[People ask "Can I take marijuana with me when I travel to another area where it's legal too?" The short answer is N… https://t.co/8S3pYPGAOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnTory @TorontoStar We weren't with the closure of Ontario Hydro either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She deliberately left the USA to get messed up with Isis so she has no right to return]]></document><document><![CDATA[*on facetime*  Cousin: *stirs imaginary Mac and cheese with a spoon.* Cousin: “yeah that’s good.” Me: “on a scale o… https://t.co/ojQCyyMId7]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’ve never believed in reinventing the wheel - I just want to bring the wheel to the people and communities that n… https://t.co/YONxcJrLtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 No Thomas, I didn't even get ANY REFUND. This year, my Air Force Vet husband and I make 55k a year an… https://t.co/1Y0BIbh8qy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrip751 @TylerDM13 @TomiLahren Well go figure... I built a house and got large tax returns...Sold it and rented fo… https://t.co/M7YsBEg1SS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump administration pushes for end to worldwide criminalization of homosexuality https://t.co/FJ3YHJnPGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TracyLovesSean @JSmirk252525 @tonebone35 @BballMichael @sharimacm @secupp TDS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did I have to go off 🤦🏽‍♀️ SOMEBODY take my phone away from me I can’t shut my mouth 🙄 I’ve got 57 year olds in my mentions HAILP 🚨🚨🚨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaye_gallops @jdefl61 Now, this really really makes me mad. That useless Congress needs to get our immigration pol… https://t.co/vPM8Kf8m3G]]></document></documents></author>