<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AOC You are a hypocrite.  Why aren’t you using green vehicles?  Why aren’t you living in an energy efficient green… https://t.co/Gnlf5GmKtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's all Libertyville in regional final https://t.co/g2W1JJXNuS via @dailyherald]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please visit https://t.co/pBgRRSHDN5 for our February English newsletter. Por favor visite esta página… https://t.co/lKbhwOqAhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaKe_5_SHURLAND We should have a convo, I want to hear your thoughts and things that you would like to wear or see… https://t.co/nD2uC9oojE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why but Casper just opened the cabinet from above and then walked away. #cattitude… https://t.co/gSsJL6woym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okStevie_ @dvsk6 @cha_killa @CashNastyGaming @KingJames Dgz isn’t really anime]]></document><document><![CDATA[City and province open doors to housing project focused on Vancouver’s racialized people experiencing homelessness… https://t.co/Ix4h5VQk27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter sent me notice of those I might want to follow. One was Obama. Really? Barry? I guess Twitter doesn’t know me like I thought.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamvietDSM It’s so slow moving though, I’ve been there. You think it’s all filler on TV, wait until you’re there.… https://t.co/sEcbgV5JSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Alabama, but there’s no way that poetry from Lord Byron is our top Valentine’s Day search.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sexy_Lovely_Sam You are worth more than your weight in gold. 💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋👍👍👍👍🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥👅👅👅👅👅👅😘😘😘😘😘😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍🌹🌹🌹🌷🌷🌷😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently betting Roomate pushups on who snitching  first on the first 48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanPurcell_Jnr And as much shit as she’s gotten, I have really enjoyed Jennifer Lawrence as Mystique. She was esp… https://t.co/ivV6pNFu84]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was fun... This 2 guys were funny and 2 other ones too... I told the bald guy to make a funny story about me tel… https://t.co/HCR2FOOnje]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is little reason for US to be so supportive of Israeli policies and so blatantly anti-peace and anti-Islam. A… https://t.co/ZFMfzulq3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Syracuse shooting over 60% of course they should be winning. No way they keep that up in the second half]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleased to announce the publication of our methods paper in @AmericanHeartJ (https://t.co/QODHvLQ5iY) - describing… https://t.co/YQDzcR3PNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you missed the #1 #hat #podcast on #youtube! Here are some of the #hats you missed out on seeing! Please check o… https://t.co/7XpaVpTzOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Guess in a time when NY is losing tax revenue this is a win for your state?  Can you even conceive the economi… https://t.co/Rdz1Z0A0TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiscardtoReroll @ArrowBrookGamin @TheHyperloops @RollOnSWD @MonksGB @TheJediTrials @Artificery https://t.co/jWcEsULJtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhatTheFFacts It would be nice if you had GIVEN A LINK where we can see these studies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dude_mark I mean, don't get me wrong, high school was a pretty crazy time for me. But I think middle school just barely takes the cake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #hickfromfrenchlick workout this morning @ray_stable @bobbyu27 fini_frank at the world famous Goshen Historic T… https://t.co/yAuNYbopox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flickervlogs Hello I’m absolutely CRYING I love u &amp; cannot wait to see you 🤩😭😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Retail job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. barista - Store# 27432… https://t.co/IF7Zs2G1Ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walden Galleria under emergency evacuation | https://t.co/tzCVRP38Fp https://t.co/VdgcyWseEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp if Trump hadn’t already lost the entire Jewish vote im sure it’s gone now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wolv54b1 @903Brewers @DaveK72 @badhopper @DRE_Go_Fish @MisterTHistory @lhtetrick @cellmavin @JonMontag Folks try a… https://t.co/QZnhIeIanN]]></document><document><![CDATA[De paseo por Key Biscayne con @cantamananasofi #miami #skate #board #keybiscayne #kid #play #wednesday ✌🏻 en Key Bi… https://t.co/vQ7yi58up4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoyed this more than the wife. @ Charlotte Convention Center https://t.co/8WiNncUGU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkEmmert @ZackCreglow @Hawks101101 Leave me alone. I’m trying to watch I Know What You Did Last Summer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NBAAllStar #UFCPhoenix and #AAF #SDFleet game tonight which I was needed to occupy my Lazy Sunday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ my future wife, please have cool parents bc the in-laws need to be just like a second family 🤞🏻🤞🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fouroctets @hacks4pancakes Because authy and duo aren’t enough, we also need Google auth and Symantec VIP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan @USAPowerlifting It’s not about discrimination, it’s about FairPlay! An M to F transsexual has a fundamental… https://t.co/4penAfUnae]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @DuluthHuskies have announced the signing of Sophomore IF Billy Cook from Pepperdine University. Cook played in… https://t.co/6QoB3ORefR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we celebrate Virginia for being named Dixon Foods Department Manager of the Year 2018! Congratulations Virgin… https://t.co/EUoq6w0vv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up 3 with 7.6 left, Remsen St. Mary’s misses 2 FTs. But they smartly foul with 2.5 left before Prince of Peace can launch a 3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re totally on to it. They are able to operate without guilt or conscience. Precisely because they’ve completely… https://t.co/wcktK9grsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My work headshot turned out OK although I hate my fake smile https://t.co/HpbWCviMmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another brick in the wall.  @gozwift  NY Central Park. 10k run, 10 mile ride with 1000’ elevation gain. Getting int… https://t.co/mLKdOcxBtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AVPhenom And while I know that comment may offend some, let's be fair.  There are lists of bugs in an issue tracke… https://t.co/zLslBSUjO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Penn State finishes @TheCrownLax with two wins, defeating Jacksonville 24-11. #NCAALax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fnoluga Kilicho na mwanzo kina mwisho, hopefully these are signs of a tired people who are ready to take back thei… https://t.co/Hx768zUWuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man y’all whip out some McCormick seasoning and think y’all some type of material 🤣 comedy asf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think some of the young guys on the Celtics like when Kyrie is out or hope he doesn’t resign 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating IoT applications with Azure Database for PostgreSQL https://t.co/cIvhw79brK https://t.co/WR1DugbN0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC So you know, this disappeared from my feed as I was starting to read it. They are terrified of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisR757 @IBSLivesMatter I don’t think he could get in if were being fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean... Penises are NICE!  I can stare at one all day but unsolicited pics automatically make the penis look ugly… https://t.co/wW6cHHHDcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@satyanadella 😀 Great job speaking about privacy and cyber security but what about the rural broadband project that… https://t.co/fyiEi50xaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They are a Fake Fact Checker because all you have are Fake Facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t say I care for fast food in general. If I want any of these things I don’t waste my money on these places. Bu… https://t.co/rXGmjmPx47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesBrantTrey @alllibertynews @TheEconomist Weird to claim the Soviet Union lacked the rule of law.   Because whe… https://t.co/E0Rnuove2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKateGrace Haha. You’re renting a seat, not buying a plane. Let’s see how you feel the person next to you busts out an egg salad sandwich]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UltimaCodex @ultimadragons @UltimaReturn @EbornIan I think an adherence to the original plot line and story would… https://t.co/UqDGo7vTaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeagueOfLegends Ah darn, when I saw Brand I was hoping you'd finally just delete him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AleLaveza @Jl94Jl4 @XeniaOrdonez @ABA2016DIA @eyragorhamsalda @PoggiDe @ACaro_Ayala @hernanpog @maria28rodry… https://t.co/eqOKIQ3hVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredOstu @ThatRealDani @al3xw1nd @DLoesch No, you didn’t address the age thing. Explain how he would travel forwar… https://t.co/S7acmd6Ypz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last workout before daylight savings! 😎 … Shift wakeup time  in 15 mins increment until this… https://t.co/qz5p0Yig7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelpingHearts1 @CBSSacramento @tomhoganlaw @sacbee_news @SacramentoKings @thegrupeco @SacPolice @SPDOutreach… https://t.co/40jPTgwaME]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels like if #Ravens are holding a press conference for a player re-signing it would have to be Mosley or Suggs… https://t.co/HgRsQmMeSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Aviation19 @CLEARken explained that flexible solutions options are what works best for airports. Look for solution… https://t.co/ZrVsEPuypU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The turkey is ready to come out of the oven. Winter development is over, time for the season. https://t.co/RFIkllttKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowledge is power  #PrettyFlyForAWyGuy  #NewellKidOnTheBlock @ Connecticut https://t.co/vIpQNu6J5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveMcCannKSL @byutvsports @WCChoops @kslsports Im coming... don't let them start without me! 🤪😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelRushNBA @jmorton78 Jokic has been really good in most of these regular season games when it matters. The quest… https://t.co/54NMJpuJ71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@godisgreat122 @BushLeague101 I think he he retired from acting to become a firefighter. He also I think had some legal troubles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful #BlackHistoryMonth celebration in #CoopCity by Assemblyman Benedetto! Great to connect w/ community leade… https://t.co/xLRgYW2z25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPostPol this BS is such a GOP thing.Destroying peoples lives mean NOTHING to them.The poor deserve to die, peo… https://t.co/Dn23FWcU2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Festejamos en Altata el fin de nuestro curso de francés del doctorado @UADEOoficial. Merci beaucoup professeur Serg… https://t.co/16vsuUvPMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForceTheIssue @brian_d_vaughn Good call. The Financial District / Battery Park is a steal these days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDebidour @ewarren I can find just as many “ economists “ that defer from yours so what’s your point ? Try actuall… https://t.co/yq66pkzntJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blueblood_Rams Let’s add, how soon he will get in trouble on the strip when they move to LV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConservativChem @SeanAstin Twitter hid your reply until I explicitly tapped the link to show it.  I’d love to know… https://t.co/IeUShYlDB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody loves to judge and put me down for hella shit. I’m so sick of it and it’s while I isolate myself from everybody.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I earned this today 😋🍻 @ Marlborough, Massachusetts https://t.co/BD1obVPWlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennycohn1 I want to ask you a serious question but I never seem to be able to get your attention. What do you mak… https://t.co/3lFr6NLkmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best parts of being a campus 🔥 dept: getting to regularly help neighbors during their time of need. Yolo… https://t.co/L8SavKG2G4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DjAWill Many people post their accomplishments and flaunt things on social media to people they don’t know. Why ca… https://t.co/UCbBObiIXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can find fit, the two seasons of @Detroiters are a watch worth your time. It’s a shame that @ComedyCentral d… https://t.co/fzdbbgoxTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was a fun little series.  Always like Mysterio as a villain.  And of course, you can’t beat Lee Weeks Art!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Graduation is right around the corner. I have slots open now. Book with me to secure your date and time. Still have… https://t.co/PQxqdejDTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve not been in Bakersfield for more than 10 hours and it’s already been tough]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelDubron @FCSNnational Way to go Mike 👍enjoy your sights and be safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teamfroglogic Your podcast with The IceMan was Epic ! You guys always 🔥me up 💯and today was no different ! I've he… https://t.co/qlpsDE5zLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SensNation @SaveSens Yeah well you’re a cop out, at least I’ll go through the 💩 storm! You know !?! like a real fa… https://t.co/tXbKc0XM9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoHWFanClub Excellent. On the Ferry heading into NYC. How about you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #RedondoBeach, CA, check out this job: https://t.co/ED0zV0Vc4H #Beauty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed this week’s @WHWMonday, sponsored by https://t.co/vVdhfdkvq5 😆 But really tho, hope you’re feeling better… https://t.co/tkNlTtJrNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This professor's really gonna start the post exam lecture and I'm gonna start bleeding from my ears and eyes I can just feel it]]></document><document><![CDATA[That pilot season thing in NYC for a killer good and gritty role #pilotseason #actorlife https://t.co/ARPGNYkPpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @PNCArena for Carolina Hurricanes vs. Winnipeg Jets in Raleigh, NC https://t.co/GtgmEhuclU https://t.co/1N6fGUoVA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_MJF Shut up.. go back inside until big brother @CodyRhodes lets you out to play!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @AOC Charlie, you must continue reminding Alexandria what a hypocrite and liar is! She talks s**t to… https://t.co/mgdefilMId]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible bagels from incredible people that also happen to go great pre or post-workout - especially when you’re… https://t.co/UG4AntERYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored that Harvey Pass highlighted our @JTOonline publication on the neoantigenic potential of complex chromosoma… https://t.co/e03K6s2wkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh it literally triggers me that as son as I start making little storytimes on my Snapchat every copycat ass bitch… https://t.co/g71gS2kBpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comedy is the hoes that think they’re good looking but it’s just a thought lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danshawsmith I literally heard Derek from @maydayparade scream this in my head]]></document></documents></author>