<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@joeBlah6 @LindaSuhler @realDonaldTrump That's been the Trump narrative since he's been in office. Ride the coattai… https://t.co/kr91QZMzjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've had an adversarial relationship with coaches my whole life. If I got in trouble in PE me Irish mum would be in… https://t.co/11TIrBd614]]></document><document><![CDATA[HERE'S TO STRONG WOMEN. MAY WE KNOW THEM. MAY WE BE WITH THEM. MAY WE RAISE THEM. #InternationalWomansDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasLandis1 Hey Thomas! $45 gets you in and 8:00pm... $55 gets you in at 7:00pm. Festival goes until 11:30pm! Thanks for watching!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markfischetti Mark, energy corridor along border is great idea....who are any Senators or Congress folks been told… https://t.co/U3qGZTc6l1]]></document><document><![CDATA[tryna be hot tho, cute ain’t cutting it in 2019 https://t.co/cRO7Dec9N5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LotjeFun HELLO  Lotte !,how you older ?, I  LOVE COUPLE-SEX !!!,text me !. G.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT DID JOHNNY DO NOW?!   HOW DO YOU GET KICKED OUT OF THE CANADIAN FOOTBALL LEAGUE.  ITS LITERALLY THE SECOND CHANCE U FOR THE NFL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍 same but I'll remember it and bring it up whenever I ask him to sign my jersey lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VTDukefan The Lakers have a more attractive situation being in LA then the Celtics do to attract free agents]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giffroy @GolfDigest @K_m_Mitchell Travesty!!  If someone forgot to tag El Tigre, they’d be fired.  Let’s go… https://t.co/6VFTqyXi2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @1Jodi4444 persons like obama don't have children.  Or empathy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think we are doing this thing proper with some late night White Castle. I’m a virgin, pretty excited. @ White Cas… https://t.co/fpAvxC9Qtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York, New York. #timewarnercenter #manhattan #monday #winter2019 #february #citylife #myhomefornow… https://t.co/83hgYwAdQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PositiveAboutMS @SelmaBlair @GMA @RobinRoberts @YouTube I'll tweet you the link if you don't already get it. I'm n… https://t.co/1voC39WJSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xdreamisdead thanks girly I’ve started to look on there I appreciate you 💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st  bday Momma let’s create more memories and fotos.  Thanks for being the awesomest #goteam #stayinyoung @… https://t.co/jipDg9sl6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Cassidy I wish it wasn’t the case but it’s inevitable no doubt. Players now are throwing harder than ever. Th… https://t.co/6wkdxsto4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HNTurtledove I was at this 1983 Bowie Show, hours of torrential rain that ended as Bowie appeared on stage, as if… https://t.co/6cFbgkt1fq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wilder/Brazeale... Also I don't really see Brazeale giving Wilder any angles. He'll come straight at him at a slow… https://t.co/7mMTZSlXUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#runner #running at the kms on the #tmill at the #gym tonight! (Kms, not miles) https://t.co/5OEo8ykEif]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we actually won this match with 3 people. One of our guys got disconnected and we still won lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things in the pipeline:  1. Unnamed album 2. Gold Pulls, “Smoothing Fur” 3. Unnamed album, Vol. 1 4. Unnamed album, Vol. 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's me giving UMES men a standing applauds on winning in final seconds against Morgan State University along fro… https://t.co/L0ZufapDc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brian Elliott's helmet might be better than Carter Hart's.   Eagle wings in orange https://t.co/pqO9jdJyVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ottaross But my computer should at least acknowledge that there's a disc in the drive, even if the files are corru… https://t.co/f0yViBQhsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curious, Are you referring to our flick @circle_film or the one with Mr. Tom Hanks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you quick to throw him to the wolves because of are afraid to address the real issue at hand?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneDaisy18 @DrJenGunter 🌻🌻🌻👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼 #Troll #Bot #TrollBot  REPORT. BLOCK. https://t.co/b9dDG0PeFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm one of those guys that truly enjoy engineering and how it works. The more involved the it is, the more I like i… https://t.co/jkzbdAqwcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyrcummings Can you messsge him on the app and ask so many more questions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Danny Green isn't the only player wondering why Davis Bertans isn't in the 3-point contest. “He should be here,” LA… https://t.co/NpZ1yzl2Bv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Further evidence you are unqualified and unfit to run for anything remotely governing ppl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a “slippery slope” in postgame when dealing with a ruckus... attempting to bridge both sides of the situation… https://t.co/rZT967MDea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antonioguevara @Rafa4224 Esto, ni aún observando el vídeo me lo puedo creer. Dios ten piedad del pueblo venezolano… https://t.co/m6lHeyAbFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WJXT_CorleyPeel @WJXTRobSweeting @wjxt4 Need to see this.  It’s our landmark, but might be good to see it go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBoozman SOLUTION TO BORDER WALL PROBLEM During WWII the Treasury Dept sold War Bonds. SELL Treasury Dept WALL… https://t.co/q6GSgVXEB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dustinchristen6 @cvk35 @HerrimanCity It’s true! They caught it and relocated it: https://t.co/jYiPYxRaer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allygator007 Progress or not, an anniversary shows that life, does in fact, go on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@autiger61998 @TurfgrassMD I tested five golf courses in SC and GA in grad school 20 years ago and all five were resistant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atlanta_amy Writing in the middle of the night while the masks are lined up on the night-stand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monerohernandez muy bien ..felicidades--haremos https://t.co/Nvxeq6wbVT @TuriCultSLP @elpais_cultura… https://t.co/CzTvskzEPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Auditions! BHAHAHAHAHA @Letty Billesbach Alvillar @Jamie Wise Truter Patzke #comedy #laugh #smirk #absurd https://t.co/9HQhxEb9am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dope Mahershala Ali won for best supporting actor and Into the Spider Verse won which he is also in.#oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sari-  what is the rules for your house now? C- no alcohol, don't steal or break my things on purpose Sari- that so… https://t.co/7IgaX2Ilw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@francesbarber13 @jeremycorbyn You should follow @vnbateman. She states the case against #Brexit clearly and forcefully.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlancoIndian @sygarte I'll check them out, but on the rare exceptions I've seen its always evidence that falls apa… https://t.co/OH6RatyKRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Belgian White by @BlueMoonBrewCo @ Jake's American Bar — https://t.co/yr611OKtTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @Talkingrockgolf (@blairsy16 @generalgrieve)... but also to @SalmonArmGC (@jessecrowecpga) Two great co… https://t.co/sXEaEXXC4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulsiGabbard All these politicians are playing drama games to keep us off balance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Socialists are not accustomed to being resisted.  They will use the courts, and once they have enough power, they u… https://t.co/5uJMzt4rBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter #CantHide the illogical reason why any @NBA or @NCAA or @NJCAA or @NAIA basketball playing surface do… https://t.co/90Qw6amIPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[💎 📚 Stacked! 📚 💎 Single finger elevation begins with some pop color like this #londonbluetopazring and #14k… https://t.co/ZwJClULess]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't always eat red meat and drink beer. But when. I do, it's #foodporn staring a lot of grass fed mooo with a h… https://t.co/5WS00crULp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart breaks for my little guy I miss him so much https://t.co/hEvQPJjcfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say never to regret... there was so many things I still wanted to say to you. For that, I’ll never forgive mys… https://t.co/8DhC2snJfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for having me on the show &amp; talking me through the fact that my hotel room is probably haunted. 👻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sophie2078 Because I am so desirable and most women can’t help themselves. But I can’t help being a ALPHA MALE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are going to have your news anchor, man or woman, do a report on last nights #StadiumSeries hockey game, any… https://t.co/xC6uyOwKfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sources: Bucs shop Jackson, who wants Philly https://t.co/zXToupFjJb via @ESPN App https://t.co/B4e2bh39lT]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY FUEGO REMIX VEEERRRRRSSSEEE‼️‼️‼️‼️🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🚨🚨🚨🚨🤦🏽‍♂️🤦🏽‍♂️🤦🏽‍♂️🤦🏽‍♂️🐐   TAG WHO I NEED TO PUT ON THIS TING‼️‼️‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's update “when pigs fly” to  “when Frank Ocean does a NPR Tiny Desk”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steve87069071 @KatrinaPierson They got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Qu… https://t.co/E5U1Ds8D5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smartphone sales 📲   Samsung  2017: 317 million 2018: 292 million  Apple  2017: 215 million 2018: 208 million  Huaw… https://t.co/ZYh7pv7Axn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you party more than pretty much never. Don't say motivational quotes and say that your grinding.. Cuuuuzzzzz ya not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle What about a little focus on Republicans Ms “reporter” or whatever they call u at Fox.  Start with… https://t.co/ppbUoh2Kkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LCUgalde Y eso no es nada, Luis Carlos... espérate a ver lo que viene más adelante...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lion on top of the hill is not as hungry as the lion climbing the hill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn’t just a bad performance this is an absolutely disgraceful performance. Haven’t shown up against the numbe… https://t.co/9dYSagnfu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[uscschaefer #golf #desertlife #biltmore #phoenix #arizona #jayjasper #desertselleraz #berkshirehathawayhomeservices… https://t.co/BdCXLfUzTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@e360mktg @RevistaEresMx @Sargentoleon @nataliasubtil @OmarYubeili @PriceShoes María se ve de maravilla.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The 25 Million Dollar Man by @3floyds at @dukesalehouse — https://t.co/9UVoj4fF6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tkweaveractor *Happy Tuesday* TK! #ActorBuddy 😎👍 https://t.co/WeZBPt9RCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainbow Slip-Ons. ======================================== #igsneakercommunity #paint #styleinspiration #styleinspo… https://t.co/XFJruWnK3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost in all of the Ottawa Senators deals of the past week is that Pierre Doiron has done a remarkable job working u… https://t.co/7zOBvJw4GZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @dbongino The Socialist Suicide Squad with their lying mouths locked and loaded for action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to PREVENT, AVOID &amp; STOP DIVORCE! (408)772-4321 bobmiller022002@yahoo.com STOP SOLDIER SUICIDE… https://t.co/MKPWH1MT0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddya_torres @islademiencanto @Ojoos_de_Bruja @LcdoTrafala @boinaverdeyulin Buenos días Limbersito de Notiuno!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@louisvillemayor wants to triple the city’s insurance tax to prevent devastating cuts to law enforcement, EMS and… https://t.co/IyNLsmfUTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjonesx @jimfiorentini Oh and what about Obama’s justice department and those phony fisa warrants?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briantheguppie @DropkickBro If this were bowling, that would be a “strike”🎳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @Amtrak Maybe unplug for a few hours and take in the graffiti painted across the industrial wastelan… https://t.co/3KuSFqbF1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Study Soros a bit! He's not complicated! A Jewish boy put under Nazi care so not to be assassinated and then took t… https://t.co/SVL9i5UwBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE KOOKS! (at @RamsHeadLive for The Kooks in Baltimore, MD) https://t.co/KMlOr725h3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro Hey @SenSanders, is TDS going to be covered by Medicare for all?  Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karoli @MSNBC Um .. Bernie Sanders isn't a Democrat?  Hang on, there may be something else ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theAdamGreen Neither. Hopefully he’s just pissed at the situation. You’re   acting like that cause you’re   pissed… https://t.co/6p8UYoZjYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Camila_Cabello you know that thing that makes people dress colorful he just sits and eats good morals]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when you think Dick Vitale can’t be any worse, there he is glad handing know abuser Floyd Mayweather. Pure class, @espn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to get my own copy @theestallion @ Downtown Portland, Maine https://t.co/aYPvnggECQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you tell your dad that hates tattoos that you have four and half of them don’t mean shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one repped the Mid-San Fernando Valley harder than you. For that, I saw thank you homie.   What a tragic loss.… https://t.co/W482Tjon0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[HIPÓLITO MEJÍA EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en… https://t.co/wZO6d5Be4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: where are seated sir?  80 yr old Wheelchair passenger: 4c......4c's a jolly good fellow ..😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse You and your “team” of future co-defendants?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#animals #animal #TagFire #pet #dog #cat #dogs #cats #photooftheday #cute #pets #instagood #animales #cute #love… https://t.co/RExLGW8g3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I can’t ask you for something when I need It , Please don’t ask me🤦🏽‍♀️!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my #favorites from the great #craftbeer state of #oregon. @ Ponchatoula, Louisiana https://t.co/JJ7CuGD48Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulStanleyLive Did Gene still charge him for the backstage meet &amp; greet? 🤣 Cool pic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump  If you sign this bill I am done with you. No more money support. Fuck the Dems. Of you sign this b… https://t.co/fKRwGZOfpV]]></document></documents></author>