<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[he knew damn well what he was doing when he put on that stupid ass costume. i’d hope the rest of the trump supporte… https://t.co/LWSj6QDN1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikiFontaine Will you Write up an FEC Complaint/Investigation For Foul Mouth, Disrespectful Rashica Tlaib WE HAVE… https://t.co/iV1tQYjRD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCWHL great broadcast on the @TorontoCWHL @InfernoCWHL game tonight. Thanks for providing it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstorAaron @DiegoFalconVE @AmyBirdCLE @Peaceonwards @ChrisMurphyCT I recognize that many people have been very hes… https://t.co/phPlfUIwL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nvm y'all, he freaked out and said some shit then cancelled plans! Whew that was a close one! Everything is back to normal now praise 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had these on each person’s desk this morning 🙌🏼 — just getting started on the #IWD19 celebration at the @IBM_iX… https://t.co/WQ7IKLJQZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaffiMagarik I don't know enough about Ilhan Omar to know if she falls into this category, but being antiimperiali… https://t.co/xDDQ19CoLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFienPrint What no go at last season of Catastrophe? Series finale was great last night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maluma ven a MINNESOTA!! POR FAVOR 🙏🏽 yo y mi hermana queremos verte en vivo #maluma #cometominnesota #malumavenaminnesota #malumaworldtour]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m wrong, tweet back at me tomorrow. I’m betting you will think this is awesome. https://t.co/OEJXXl5xqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toby just gave Kevin that i’m gonna  deal with you later look😄😄#ThisIsUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @cafreeland @HeikoMaas I WANT TO SEE YOUR TAX RETURNS NANCY PELOSI AND AN ITEMIZED LIST OF ALL YOUR SPENDING]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay I already knew from the jump who the monster is from Masked Singer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st birthday to one of my forever besties!!!! So thankful to have you and baby Leland in my life💙 I love you… https://t.co/II2vQEbROx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not know how old she is but is really smart and really capable of making a difference in this world of ours,so… https://t.co/Sw768JL1IW]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍#OHMYMAGICALWORD DISNEY PARKS SHOPPING HAUL PART 4 | 2018 DVC😍 https://t.co/oB4D4wk6O9 via @YouTube https://t.co/BQoKgYBu8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rodrigo Salinas gets the first yellow card of the night for a bad foul on Gutierrez. #SKCvTOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner @Trump @GOP @GOPChairwoman @FBI Wow, they all are into sex trafficking]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @jaybleszz  ・・・  Thanks @bleszmedia For The Wonderful Opportunity!!! #FifthWordFilm #Actress #filmlife… https://t.co/ni9yagGwGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the beginning of the end of our constitutional democracy. It is the fear I have lived with and fought agai… https://t.co/nE8HHJkbj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Madison: clear sky, 32°F 47% humidity, wind 8mph, pressure 1027mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right...congesss needs to stop this..house can vote to do so , which would trigger the senate to take a vote..congr… https://t.co/a1k6XdNCuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[No more tax cuts! Our schools need funding! Our students deserve to be THE main concern of our AZ government!… https://t.co/UcXF0vSERR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scored some Meyer Lemons aldivegan and made some Meyer Lemon Marmalade. Oh how I love marmalade#  This was just fre… https://t.co/VOWXIA1Ssp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth bombs and key ACTIONABLE take aways (in pics ⏩⏩⏩). Great panel to start the day!! 👏🏼👌🏼💪🏼 @sxsw #SXSW… https://t.co/OWhi1fhUeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveVescio @KatieReneeLind4 I think we are disgusted equally with both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesertEWO @WilkowMajority @dbongino No I say what I mean and I do not play word games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the office whiteboarding again and it feels so good to #create and #innovate! This time creating a innovation la… https://t.co/ihlenlACru]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to my fellow Slytherins, I fucking love all you snarky bastards]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conversations with Mami ❤️ Always looking out for me 😊 https://t.co/dKhfYJtsHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_GeorgeBailey Don’t give up. You have so many that love you. So many you mean the world to. Just because of one… https://t.co/T5uhZbUvlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPENING NOW: A police presser from #Providence on the now murder of Jassy Correia. @wbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinDSGB @darkdiamond0713 @tommyktweets @RealDeal32 @cooney_philip @Krizantto @lifeofkeezy @itsJhonnyA… https://t.co/ksB71045VO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spektader @TooFaced I like the tutti frutti line waaaay more, tbh. https://t.co/5hDl56OvB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleyrm There’s also a World Of Disney and a Disney Springs one, seven designs in total.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practice at game speed. Utilize left foot. Thanks BK. Elly’s lucky to have you in her corner. @futebolformNfit https://t.co/QTPdPL8Rvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have an acoustic guitar and an electric guitar, but I have never gone beyond some basic stuff on the acoustic. I… https://t.co/Jfe3sHhhn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NPC #NYFW #Pier59Studios #ChinaDay @pier59studios @nyfw @ Pier59 Studios https://t.co/86sMJUKkV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[TV fans and experts question Netflix's sudden wave of cancellations  https://t.co/3Dh0ILTQVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve started measuring my stress in relation to candy heat stages. I am solidly in a firm ball stress stage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is, I think, that we are all so alone in what lies deepest in our souls, so unable to find the words, and perhap… https://t.co/jomk79Vt0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[died fighting with the IS in Syria. In June 2015,  he slipped across the Turkish border to reach the then IS capita… https://t.co/LfVVWVTbSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 5225 NW 112th Pl #Doral #FL  #realestate https://t.co/JDexJ51r2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #Legal jobs like "Compliance Associate" at Yardi Systems in #SantaBarbara, CA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one loves @whoisluka more than I do so you bandwagon hoes need to go somewhere thanks. ( I was mad that day, I m… https://t.co/A7bDgff986]]></document><document><![CDATA[And sometimes I get so scared of what I can't understand But here I am Next to you The sky is more blue In Malibu… https://t.co/2F33GLHJ2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is a horrible horrible person. A cheat , a racist and a liar.!  I hope he ends up in Jail]]></document><document><![CDATA[#suicideprevention Walk pearsonranchms 🧡💜 @ Pearson Ranch Middle School - RRISD https://t.co/HbZSDNTDTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwiHusband @RightWingWatch I'm sorry that happened to your family btw.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aturnz11 Lets get the facts before we vilify Rielly ... league is investigating. Nobody really knows who it was at this point]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump wants to export #nuclear technology to the Saudis. Can he do that? Nice read by @BlakeSobczak in #Energywire 🔒 https://t.co/gXix2OgaKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HAVE TO BECOME THAT UNAPPROACHABLE BITCH THAT NO ONE FEELS FREE AROUND .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clarkewkru It’s ok my friend. I’ll check it out myself. I think@belkamyblake is soo hot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itswoori @li_danika_m @GayleKimberly @hanubuu @KelseyRemige @_liquidpyro @yoonahlol @AriaSaki @koropup… https://t.co/ACQho1HXX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never understood how someone could be so cold blooded but then I guess that’s the fucking world we live in #TrustNoOne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter @AnnCoulter is definitely a nut job....full of herself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an One Man Mosh Pit (2019) by @surlybrewing at @bensbrewing — https://t.co/ndpVq8WAoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lawnatural @MellieAdamson @BioChicaGMO https://t.co/H6912D3KcB An adverse event is anything medical that happens d… https://t.co/bHrYqklCEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[А ведь хлам это не только старые вещи...  это слова обесценные людьми это прошлое с привкусом нелюбви...  это отнош… https://t.co/Z7LeGecV73]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at My Family Room ;) ;D in Independence, MO https://t.co/YWsNMfV5w8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarioMocciaNMSU @NMStateWBB @KMelendrezNMSU He fits right in with our crazy...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djk007 @JeffProbst Well now, Jeff is what makes Survivor , so I guess you need to put your ear plugs in cause he’s awesome !!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on Lake Ferry Drive #Loudon #TN  #realestate https://t.co/qxVJTdxkhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made it drizzle showing my monetary appreciation for artistry of t/ pole dance. Young lady gestured to my bosom “… https://t.co/EPln4bmp4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a treat it was to visit #pbvU and spend some time with these talented &amp; dedicated educators! #KCSOSproud]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kind of miss working as a teacher assistant 😭 I miss being surrounded by other people’s kids all day lmaooooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Lee_H_Glenn watch this and tell me you don’t at least like hockey just a little bit!! @JBStewart @walker_2411… https://t.co/PHkva4YHpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[When making popcorn, wait until there are 3+ seconds between pops. That’s when you know it’s done]]></document><document><![CDATA[Odio con todas mis fuerzas el frío y la lluvia 😤 #CosasQueANadieLeImportan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ed650b @RunADZ_ @warriorsworld I hadn’t thought about that, I like that! 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[#yellow #coldplay #coldplayfans #ahfod #ahfodtour #coldplayeveryday #parachutes #coldplayers #coldplayfansunite… https://t.co/Y1dVuJLtMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. B Arañas 2. A Worth It 3. B Worth It 4. A Alicia Keys 5. C 11 de agosto del 2017 #AllyBrookeEnRazeLive @AllyBrooke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealOCEmily Beautiful Emily! They couldn’t have found a better person to model the earrings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods They'll probably write a script about how conservatives framed the liberal black gay who hated Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnni Shame shame shame on this society! This country is headed for a big fall and there’s country going to come to… https://t.co/4yGqk8qxY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[13 Kirksville Youth Wrestlers from Region A advance to State!  🤼‍♂️ 5th Place as a team! #moyouthwrestling #kvprpoud @FredBeckKTVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 things that have made me happy so far today: hot sauce and printing in color]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitter fam! Make this Monday a blessed and Jesus filled one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ngl driving around in a truck made me feel like quite the bad ass today 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi He needs trump to tell him what to do he has no brain or balls to act like a man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nodrump @PatriciaKAdams @realDonaldTrump That's gross... he has ridden the US like a paid hooker... #TrumpLiesEverytimeHeSpeaks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Umm they could meet on the South Side of Chicago, or how about downtown LA, SF or Seattle, you know..better yet alo… https://t.co/tBZthKRuxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTH is wrong with people, like it's normal to see an older woman with her head stuck in the door? I bet if it was a… https://t.co/3zA2Rsf8uH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reason u r single is cuz u r ugly period thats just facts no go tuck urself in]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabyGhia It’s the same friends who hang out and call me mom so yea LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HWaiver I’ll engage your nonsense and help get your followers up. #mrtowelwaiver]]></document><document><![CDATA[#vsco#vscocam#igdaily that old old @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/whagSBn5Oj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalfJewish I felt that. Like I really am an emotional mess who overshares and gets triggered in person too, lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to breathe so much high science..even from outside.. @WhiteheadInst @harvardmedical @ScienceMIT https://t.co/vDPnkZzCKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 @MailOnline Oowee... FUN With Guns. And if one of the b------- happens to stray, well that will be okay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronGleeman @RandBall @RandBallsStu I felt the same way about Bobby Kielty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These last couple weeks have been rough, but I couldn’t be happier with where I am headed and everything that has h… https://t.co/YsnQQNXonl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#margarita #nationalmargaritaday #tresamigosbrandon #tequila #chipsandsalsa #rocks #frozen @ Tres Amigos Cantina https://t.co/nqzziLwyGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Substitutes in college should not be a thing. Either show up or let us all sleep, don’t have some random guy come i… https://t.co/PPFsIFs6cy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot how amazing it was to walk around without pants on. I miss having hotel rooms and the money I made with travel nursing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @nbcsnl, you may want to put subtitles under your skits. My mom just texted me asking me what “swoll” means.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico ....TO TRUMP ADMINISTRATION : ...GET ON AMERICA'S SIDE !!!! ... INSTEAD OF RUSSIA'S SIDE !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsSammieRose This was literally like a PSA. I had no idea. Windows are now all open 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t say enough how amazing this woman is for what she does for students at OHSU, including discussing her own jou… https://t.co/h5IGwjtvQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This one has an ear infection so he wanted to stay home and take me to the dr for my earache. He’s very excited I h… https://t.co/iP4FUdIL52]]></document></documents></author>