<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Eating well starts with fresh organic produce. Every healthy diet includes lots of vegetables. YUMMY!  #organic… https://t.co/nV5VOKGK24]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday afternoon ❤️ Elliott and Lucille helped me do a little indoor gardening.  Love love love this!  So much fun!… https://t.co/UCNkVhThEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrookeWMcKeever @PRSANonprofit @SCPRSA @JenAnnaHoff Looking forward to it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Azealia Banks is draining... Sis doesn’t ever get tired of being a hater bitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat Why does he wear such baggy clothes? It's not hiding the fact that he's a heavy man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like 5 years ago this guy stole a really cool lighter cover from me and I’m still mad about it FUCK YOU JOSHUA ROBERTS I HOPE YOU SEE THIS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SMOK SLM Kit😎😎😎 #smok #slmkit #vapefam #newestrelease #vapelife #stopsmoking #smokslm #vapeon💨 #coolvape #easyvape… https://t.co/IGhzWNgR1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream that J. Cole and I spent an entire day conversing and really getting to know each other. I like celeb… https://t.co/pvJUBiRLfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[So help me GOD if Einstein’s takes 30 minutes on my bagel I don’t know what’s gonna happen to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to have the opportunity to hear from distinguished speakers at today’s discussion on American Politics and… https://t.co/10e4ZY3Bw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more I think about it the more mad I am that Suspiria, Annihilation, were so ignored. Suspiria not even getting… https://t.co/AXInMLSxBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @solangeknowles, that is all https://t.co/vIV470VXuu https://t.co/JDrprjuuHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day! #NutanixEmpowers  #IamRemarkable https://t.co/C2Mg0WJBOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If we are not willing to wake up in the morning and die to ourselves, perhaps we should ask ourselves whether or n… https://t.co/dYNYKVoG9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[You a stupid mf if u let me go. flex all u want but that L gonna hit ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re purchasing flowers for yourself or someone else today, don’t forget, lillies are poisonous to cats!  https://t.co/kL932uGiYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicola_scherer @Harry_Styles @KaceyMusgraves My all time favorite 1D song . It got even better after Zayn left and… https://t.co/P55S7ySZGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanHammonds2 @kritter1963 Thanks, I’m German, can say it, can’t spell it!🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear god. Does any of this suggest an opportunity to improve rove the human race.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At a #DomesticViolence training with work, and this just broke my heart- a man is most at risk for violence from so… https://t.co/JsshMIIQGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity No, it's overreach. What if you get a president that decides to take your guns away? Or cuts your elec… https://t.co/63ZFWG0zN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[You want to mess with a black nigga and you think your Kardashian pussy is that moist and makes you exempt to the f… https://t.co/3EPH1yEBIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Recording purposes. Brand or breed of communism by stole 2016 ones likely reason they made American servic… https://t.co/kC3oyRQXqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally so tired. woke up at 559 when i have to be too work at 6 😞😞😞😞 didnt wanna get out of bed this morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Softest bestest bread ever @ Local Foods Bakery https://t.co/zL37bt4R7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oogeyofficial @ghostgirlflow That magical wook knew what she was doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey .@JoyAnnReid - look what you are missing back here in your home state of Colorado - MASSIVE avalanches that cro… https://t.co/ARpemBUE0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely love our cooling oil ritual at Bella Salon, comes with every service! Relieves headaches, pain, stress,… https://t.co/pAWTx3krBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TamaracTalk @Michaeludine @SharonAronBaron IMPORTANT REMINDER:  Schools Safety Town Hall Monday February 25th at 6… https://t.co/MgsHtZpvDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karoli @MSNBC I mean, they didn’t even throw Julian Castro in there to even try to look varied. Just straight up o… https://t.co/6BpeUDmtTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cybill_Troy happy belated birthday, Goddess. We'll have Your prezzies when we see you in April. Nudge-nudge-wink-wink]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so proud of these ladies + I am so confident in their leadership. Such a joy to watch them grow! Xoxoxo… https://t.co/PQQbzOwPWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My version of Russian roulette: wearing big sweatpants to the grocery store with no underwear and heavy things in my pockets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care how much of an adult you think you are, being sick af and away from your mom suuuucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please excuse the south side vernacular, but @KamalaHarris is an abject #ShitHead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliaJoyceHall @Mbladam @WhyUnion @Slouchybear72 @MarkDice @AOC You people need to get off the Russian crap! Let's… https://t.co/Rg19HAhISW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 @trump_gays What pare of their not legal don't you understand Nancy Pelosi?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so glad I made it out of school before I had to sit through an anti-vape presentation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LLeeki @washingtonpost 4) “Medicare for all” is not only terrible policy, but it’s ignorant propaganda. If he is R… https://t.co/DX26GFen5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[To see full video check out: YouTube channel (Tracey Wilhelmina) or FB (Tracey Hatton Hughes) @ Westgate Lakes Reso… https://t.co/Skp2N0pJZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pete Buttigieg: The Case For A Younger President https://t.co/oLe4NlTGRN via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msinsulindpndnt @JoyAnnReid Oh God. ismh. Thia is SO FUCKING RIDICULOUS AND WRONG.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a sign of a great day to come when you get to school early to make your copies and walk into this......… https://t.co/lXUzhEeT0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephlormand @RaleighPACT FYI: our recommendation was sent to the city manager. Still denied the opportunity to sp… https://t.co/U77UOAry63]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miazga_s @SoapFanForLife @cindy4419 @SIJFG @wien_sulzbach @GenieFrancis @thejonlindstrom @Bedollz @hagerman_becky… https://t.co/gh8YlnJTqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[But god forbid a comedian make a few jokes. The world ends. Right, WHCA?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeauStack @fitsnews @amyklobuchar Played since the first grade, coached for 14 yrs- not gonna say how old I am but… https://t.co/YuT3QKeHVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gemma &amp; Remi🐶💙☃️ #crazymuthapuppers #snowmuchfun #snowdogs #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy… https://t.co/C5cWvKZXgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EscapetheRoom #JurassicEscape @ Glendale Galleria https://t.co/Ovfc8eV93v]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cashier asked me do I want to donate money to the troops with my change. Excuse me the troops use half of my t… https://t.co/4kQj88cNWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Areola’s team Issa scam. Never again. I better get my vinyls tho. https://t.co/QEUFjxH5HJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adriandt31 I laugh every time I hear her  speak...everyone bashes Trump for how he speaks yet they lift her up wit… https://t.co/kcyPVJLlnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FollowMeToo3 Apparently the person that wrote this didn’t have ADHD. 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McConnellWendy @Green__Rays @CHEERSPORTCorp @ittybitty_mats Thank you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And to all the folks w disabilities out there trying to find work - I got your back and won't give up on you. We're… https://t.co/fHYO716vvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great story! And a throwback to when we found Fic-mediated adenylylation of Hsp70 protein, BiP. So many exci… https://t.co/OXCmMyPuYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmmm..let’s ask Hillary. She’s the expert in this. But not just on social media. She has CIA, DOJ, FBI, MSM, DNC,… https://t.co/btTo3JGPIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just landed and here we are! Only because Chico’s is closed right now. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllisterDen @BernieSanders Technically speaking you are full of shit. Crossing the street against the crossing l… https://t.co/PgQVbganPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get a better sex life - meet over 4000000 registered members with thousands of sexy photos in this adult personals… https://t.co/w0RFSsBCyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews @racoonraiders U See That Fist Traitor Trumps Always Pumping? In Boston, That's Sign Language U Can Rea… https://t.co/kvBEl8ed7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF?!  Is all I can say.  I got most of it from reading @JinathHyder tweets and having @jaynoonies for clarifying it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job is now open at Starbucks in #LosAngeles, CA. Follow us and turn on mobile alerts to hear about jobs like t… https://t.co/rkJtfcnisi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Papa just told me I’m a sweet gal but I need some new jeans #rippedjeans]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You can make your story interesting through editing, are you using archival footage, black and white, different ca… https://t.co/WAt5S4607v]]></document><document><![CDATA[omfg i just saw someone with a south side serpants hoodie and i need to know where tf she got it]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TWD New podcast episode from @TamecheTracey  🎧🧟‍♂️🎙https://t.co/PmZEko2I0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arasmusKTVU @KTVU .... and I’ve moved away but I’ve always come back!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretending to be okay when you’re broken is so much harder than just allowing yourself to not be okay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryRauch17 I hope to see you again soon too. You are fun and so interesting to talk to. I love Lucy too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke is an A-hole. A manipulating prick.Kate run. Demand off this charade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to document bc this outfit is 🔥 also this lash curler from Finland is giving me a lift like no other 🙌🏻 @ Los F… https://t.co/JydqDH2J82]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Liquid Alpha (2019) by @woodgrainbrew at @OverheardAtWG — https://t.co/w1fjC6Jyuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatherineKeyser @FCSchoolsGA @LambertHS @ATL7452 I saw them last weekend!!! Pulizter was one of my Horn students!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs Small does not do things small!! Cannot. Wait! https://t.co/pg5Gs6TKW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to delete my tweets cause I don’t feel like getting the cops called on me for harassment even though she says s… https://t.co/cKgORtSpo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @nypost Sickening, did she want his dog arrested, too, caught “humping her dog. Maybe she thought c… https://t.co/I6yXZOVL6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @MicheleAtTriad to post covers of 7 books I love. No explanations or reviews, just t… https://t.co/WEG9qAuk5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family time @ Universal Studios Orlando/Citywalk https://t.co/RegJVAoHiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always beat myself up over the fact that @brandygarciaa__ and I live less than an hour away from each other yet o… https://t.co/RWewzPWnMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey,  Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/cNPTP31NrU… https://t.co/D39nRD3tNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accidentally sat front/centre at a #IWD2109 and just saw the photos: looks like I’m posing in front of a crowd of p… https://t.co/KMkOmLhlVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MystryeDragon @Pathryn34 Thank you for saying this. I'm frustrated because I haven't been able to put my feelings… https://t.co/czZDKUufpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarderNatalie @cianrobinson Ahhh another soul who enjoys glitter! Work hard ... play hard 😎...just bring the kids some good takeout!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look mentally challenged.  You have destroyed all my female sexual psrts.  You made e live through it.  Cops have… https://t.co/eLNqFNezYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe America is not the place to live, bc officers are corrupted and fucked up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrimeCreator2 @AboveTheBurgh @HeARTofGod99 @2newearth777 @davidsodell @tee10202 @WILLOWOOD2 @glammalg11… https://t.co/JxaUuvohB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tusk_UA Happy Birthday Tusk. Hope you were able to find a mud hole to play in. ❤️🐗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, so you gave me a random hour six months ago, but now you’re taking it back and then in like six months you’re… https://t.co/VWREcYgxMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voy a ser papá  fue el santo remedio para olvidarme de mi ex. 🤮🤮🤮  La integridat y la dignidat la tenemos bien es… https://t.co/eHNDvcBOkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrsimkins @AvantGardeGoth literally don’t eat the plant. If you want to eat cactus, come over and I’ll make you some.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are becoming a BYOS nation. Good straws are hard to find.  A few good places:  @ChikFilACali @Hardees… https://t.co/f6F2joQ0X2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennycohn1 @Phire2Fire Is it not better to have them as friends than as genocidal enemies?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilredtriskele Sure! This is my daughter’s direct ship link: https://t.co/ms3GfuTXB7 ❤️🍪🍋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @AOC You literally said that you don’t want to argue, yet you’ve been up all night harassing and beli… https://t.co/Mtxo1FFnx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @ckubeNBC Military money should never be used for any other purpose other than being ready to protect the… https://t.co/KDs5BbsEkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out the Old Mill district of #minneapolis Who knew you could make so much with @heyheatherangel #vintagetv… https://t.co/2X05D69L1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philzzzzzzzz @emmachamberlain I CANT BRATHE HOLY FUCK SUDHDHBDJZHDJDHDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been to the gym on a Sunday morning in a long long time. I’m usually hungover to the point of death on Sundays lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so vital to stay connected to our personal kids and our school kids... Becoming a Place of Healing Grace fo… https://t.co/KF3U0IeAFC]]></document></documents></author>