<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JodiAttar1 @JodiAttarzSpace @MO_AfterSchool  21st CCLC building bridges of academic enrichment to the school day c… https://t.co/hEmJrcR95s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregoryGAllen @PeteButtigieg Ha - maybe I can be in charge of the White House tours!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few people have commented that this image is “photoshopped.” Let me assure you it’s not. From touring all over ‘m… https://t.co/KK0Lu1qCCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/fZ53YlkQX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StopTheInsani15 @amairanymc_ @juste1etudiant @cmclymer @AOC Look up the amount of co2 we have put into the air the… https://t.co/8Kl6yGWNVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport Is that two chainz looking like he’s about to star in the revenant 2?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace He has to yell in order to hear himself over his stomach growling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling everyone with a love for tech in Northern Ireland!  Start-Up World Cup Belfast 2019 tickets are now live to… https://t.co/XGDWtdQD3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @PeteButtigieg gets to be president do you think we will keep calling him Mayor Pete or switch to President Pete?]]></document><document><![CDATA[About last night | pants status : cracked clouds #cycling #sf #coffee @ Pacific Heights, San Francisco https://t.co/zJw1NEx6Hj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johngriesse @parkRdavS Some athletes do ballet to get an edge, bowling seems to be working too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CliffordDMay @NoahPollak @BretStephensNYT @splinter_news @Samer That’s funny, I could swear you just made an accus… https://t.co/4PacJ0XTqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[To @DarrenElias (WPT-3rd,$473k)  “Oh here he goes. He’s at it again. He’s on the felt, and winning again. He reads… https://t.co/hHXhzjzHPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj @everydimeonline Trump and the republicans plan to balance the budget is more tax cut scams for the rich w… https://t.co/QM2eo6MKjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PWM62 @smileyt22 @dthomicide @SusanDanzig219 @dk_stephan @kahuna754 @raventerp1 @babyspittle @xdelmar59 @samboa… https://t.co/vu86eOcah5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Local24Chelsea bales of hay, on the roadway? you don’t say sounds like something that should happen in May, on a S… https://t.co/E7RWdXPl1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venezuela has the world’s greatest oil reserves. For decades it maintained a robust economy and a thriving middle c… https://t.co/Djc6r8W95i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riversideeagles players and students react to defeating Walker in the second round of state at Riverside Military… https://t.co/xoyCQkjz3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday brotha !! Enjoy your 21st and go drink your ass off 🍺🤙🏻 https://t.co/HeU1sxHXVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshBarely @JCapGLJ Yep. Now same writers killing lou for not making a move. Does anyone really think lou didn’t t… https://t.co/NSj9wOZVZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a great night for some @gatorsbb !! Love this time of the year! #letsgogators #baseball #uf https://t.co/fy542Djcrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hands down, BEST SHOW IN VEGAS!!  #CrissAngelLIVE https://t.co/dDw8iNkmq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Simpsons..... the best animated TV show of all time and all around great comedy.... https://t.co/92O65SgLOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why should Carlson apologies I don't hear One Damn DEMARAT APOLOGIES.  #BULLSHIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbyRosinski My gut tells me if KD signs with the Knicks he will get his pick of who he wants to be playing with.… https://t.co/Src7bz8KLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jk7PJJeA5p good news, with the layoffs at union Pacific this is needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like I need a new website to have a Christmas/birthday wish list on 😒 #BoycottAmazon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to a newly opened salon today for a haircut. They have an online check-in system that had two people in front… https://t.co/MxbOwJblM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Domi, BAY-BAY!  Let's get this W! #GoHabsGo  #Habs https://t.co/ds3eK3lJSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump 1. He DID say that he was in thrall to you for many years 2. You should have been as loyal to him… https://t.co/dpiguAlDi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to get electrolysis on my cheeks. I have just enough hair to get ingrowns, but not enough for a countour beard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeashby317 @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Past behavior by another doesn’t make present actions by the current pres… https://t.co/HubvHYPrly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleCurato @serrano_rene #Duterte is using #marcos playbook short of declaration of #martiallaw and if he does t… https://t.co/J8CdboqHKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainbows make me BELIEVE!!!  #awesome #doublerainbow at 5:30pm 2/17/19 on the 134 freeway near Eagle Rock. Absolute… https://t.co/EkyXLblgKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who put this into motion? We're not looking out for the next distraction. Didn't matter that he was failing in Nort… https://t.co/XnZc2ouxwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guarito_21 @clausantander esperemos que sean las fuerzas especiales de Colombia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reezy’s killin it! Check him out! One of digital inspirations for sure!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning family: The greatest gift you can give someone is your time. Because when you give your time, you are… https://t.co/0SKDSxxq1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Females think just cause we men we ain't got feelings watch what you say or it he the last thing you say to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sun was shining today and it felt so good to be outside... Do you see the snow capped mountains in the background?… https://t.co/tf5wTZpFOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My last 2 weeks. Red State is a huge yes. Suspiria = meh. Overlord I loved. Ricochet is an old school classic. Mand… https://t.co/1fPmmZqRIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mackletrain @Jason_Millet @baseballcrank @KevinMKruse @IraStoll The crank getting taken behind the woodshed. Embar… https://t.co/IW8jiJex9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GirlNamedBoston Unrelated: the My Pillow guy is even more annoying in HD 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to go hiking. It's been a couple of months and sitting in an office every day kills me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanChariton @RonPlacone @YouTube .. it's a free service .. you could create whatever you want, it won't matter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of Long Island Wildlife Photography - Pacific Loon on cover! 2-16-19 - https://t.co/hRJzQtuUgq @audubonsociety… https://t.co/P84ENsBl6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weeeeeseph Taking Barça and Getafe. Getafe has won me $ before I've woken up a couple times. Took a 3hr nap so I'll be up at 4am anyways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@majornelson Nero. He was a fresh change into an already awesome series! #freecodefridaycontest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalKathy Two subsets of socialism, naziism and communism. They both use coercive big governmental instrument… https://t.co/Mktg0mS8Fu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a fact.  Mass Murder based on out right lies!  What do you think? https://t.co/piBiIj9j0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Sargent: I was the first person to do a flat earth license plate and then everyone started doing them.  Just... wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[visooutfestival @buhosunison @imcahermosillo @iscsonora quinta.deanza  Hoy último día! Viso 2019! en Quinta de Anza https://t.co/CHOXshHEBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Limitations live only in our minds. But if we use our imaginations, our possibilities become limitless. #nolimits]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astevesoccer_22 @breeny40 Thanks for the kind words guys- I’m a lucky guy to be able to coach the kids I coach and… https://t.co/PpNuTlcZSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Stan you all @AvalancheTwitch @Froste @Mako @Classify @leahdb98 @FatKidDeals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stratus10601 When i heard the you interlude I was like is Roly gonna be ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plugapatow @CoryRossColeman @Trip_D21 @IanKarmel @miel you think hes rich writing for the late late show lol?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Really should hope that President Trump Never goes to Prison KG. If he does. America's going to be in Another G… https://t.co/0cOkHQQbXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women &amp; people of color are taking the #Oscars by storm this year and I love it!!! https://t.co/8QJJyQNVWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pics from my New York trip last week. #timessquare #NewYork #photography @ Times Square, New York City https://t.co/QrY3cplJtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[To never know unknown, the paradox of the knower and the known. . . . 📷 Byron, salty_ketchup  . #thoughts #poem… https://t.co/7Hd7ZLFyIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewstoller @WGladstone @SilverEye91 Their accounting practices along with all these other non-GAAP will make t… https://t.co/xzaZTXHblu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glitter_2em13 @MarinaTiina @Liaisti_1 @SilviaMaidorn @JenJoyCampbell @TimoBeil_ @Rivin84452214 @PERSANOTAMARA… https://t.co/tiOfhcspnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseCox @Kell_Scribe @masson_nico Left your settler on a floodplain, it probably flooded and insta-dedded you. Th… https://t.co/PbmD6SODKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucky number 10! Thank you @MarthaQuinn and @iHeart80sRadio for the winning opportunity!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it invoking the wrath of God to point out that the collapse in Spurs form seems to have coincided with the retur… https://t.co/bQc7AtE5Ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[These coaches demonstrate an amazing, ongoing commitment to push these academic athletes to excellence.  Truly a pr… https://t.co/w2XwOboX56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@declangmurphy @allaway_matthew @PNLogic @tsoburol @uretericbud @michael_gorin 😴😴😴😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamMotion I am an alta cocker, @TommyBahama-wearing, “Purveyor of the Island Lifestyle.” My grandmother was a d… https://t.co/CTeSJZI1aJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlaunmillon Upon further reflection, my reply was superficial; you have an emotional connection to Madrid, I was… https://t.co/pyqDxV5mz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sac Fly for Purdue and now it’s 6-4. Runner on second still.   Hunter Stanley warming up for Southern Miss in the bullpen.   #USM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recovery efforts will continue as weather and resources allow. The Sheriff’s Office says they are concerned for the… https://t.co/KhXYxh5neQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels so good to be back #atlutd #UniteandConquer https://t.co/WkrM3k0Laz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Iowa athletic department is slowing becoming the Iowa intuitive department.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@David_Folkerts &amp; I brought the northeast weather to #Texas https://t.co/tqQvxfhES3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for writing this, Jon. I’m from West Branch, too, and although we didn’t grow-up at the same time, I’m able… https://t.co/eraBGKINfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andradebryan @franco_esca Se escucha que se la pasarom con madresss y es de a huevo @franco_esca es el puto amo de… https://t.co/dLc6bydjcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WerIstDeinPa @SunshineLeft @RepAdamSchiff Ok then you’re only allowed to have guns available in 1789]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bern_04 @VaiLambert Je ne lis plus @LaPresse_Sports parce que ça n’a pas de bon sens la ligne éditoriale anti-Expos qu’ils se sont donnés.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 @DylanJStanley1 Took the fall and turned it into a Zoolander pose all the way down. Well done, Sir!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent the day sightseeing in San Francisco before kicking things off for @madehoops #WestLea8ue session 3. Now read… https://t.co/PzwHIwz8q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_bevacqua @EdLatimore “Last night at two Went home with a 10, then at 10 I woke up with a two.   i’ve never b… https://t.co/QBjaNCy4AX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The whole soundtrack filled with absolute bops and they're gonna play Shallow?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubinReport @Timcast Which likewise means you can engage with impunity in a certain form of Holocaust denial, or a… https://t.co/MajmaZaBU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino The #Left’s fantasy collusion bubble finally bursts &amp; they’re staggering around like the walking dead in total disbelief.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hatchdaren @WarriorsCoachK LOL!!! We both know who supplied the statistics for our classes to get our Master’s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to people asking where i wrote this new book and casually answering “oh, you know, at my desk in pe… https://t.co/2oMeqsParK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TREALSPILL #RIPDJSCREW🔩 I remember bein in lLake Charles Louisiana at club cherry late 90s down south doin illegal… https://t.co/Bu6dseCOIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Please release the names of legislators that used the secret fund to cover their butt over things they did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andruszkiewicz8 @SaccoEric @MES_Principal @principalkimmi Yep!  It doesn’t matter how fast or how far, but that yo… https://t.co/3wBUvtqgFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you own a business.  And make a lot of bank transfers.  I secretly hate you.  . . The client I’m speaking about… https://t.co/H6oHm3O4RB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roldanj1264 @epigmenioibarra @EPN @PRI_Nacional @KarennKiowa O SEA, YA QUIEREN ENTERRAR AL pri RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I get older I need to pivot yet again , first I was in IT , then digital , and I guess now it’s called product .   #itsallthesame]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much does this billboard cost?   Try and tell me how @AOC is not effective https://t.co/dqgYuXoUxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this blue holographic dust. @oceannailsupply @nailpromagazine @nailsmag @HardRockNails @ Hard Rock Nails https://t.co/tAFfmJo6Av]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @PramilaJayapal @SenSanders Make no mistake organized people will defeat you go home and take Bernie with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcelodacruz @JJ66616 @rianjohnson @SuperBroMovies See bro when we talk about Star Wars it’s fun. Instead of atta… https://t.co/555oEz2f14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoryStolzenberg @LyleSollaYates @ethantate @NikuyahWalkerCC @DrWesBellamy @mtgillikin @hillforcville @MPayneCville… https://t.co/Vdi44I4Xw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late Post Epic moment for a friend that has moved on to the next level... it’s not goodbye MR D.. it’s see ya later… https://t.co/JZKQ2UG7o0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Dylan. Sorry I couldn't be at council when you received you Mayor Building Award.]]></document></documents></author>