<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TinaRoseRad @SsssamanthaaMUA There are some that's come in unsweetened flavors now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brandon_Bird @maggieserota I thought you meant it was the step dad, so thanks for clarity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpOrBust2020 @RodStryker And yet he did.  They all coolly lie.  How is that possible to lie with such a straigh… https://t.co/FRsmTseAgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom: *starts playing Cardi’s verse in Thotiana in Claim Jumper* Me: Omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is actually how i drive😂😂 ask any of my friends @ashley_lewis9 @HavekostHaley]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3; I accepted a 7 Day book challenge from @tamurai63 One book cover each day, no reviews or explanations, and i… https://t.co/EZqCFh7eM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsTylerKSR #dogslovethecatstoo @UKgirly05 #Cozmo https://t.co/A5VTYVp0F9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Maybe they're tired of watching her lick &amp; suck her teeth like she just threw down a side of beef...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FloWrestling  Why can’t we watch mat 1, the 1st place mat for Big 10?😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[the new @Nike ad gives me goose bumps! girl power to the max! happy monday!!! #justdoit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HopkinsMedicine In conclusion, healthcare is a fraud. Knees dictate health. Muscles reign supreme. Both government… https://t.co/6YHXWLtV1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[This new Chick Fil A store needs to open already because everybody at work is stressed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’ve concluded that rugby bitches are the worst creatures to walk this earth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg Love the video!!! It’s awesome!!! Can’t wait to see you on tour this summer in Boston! ❤️… https://t.co/wm1qlTcvZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[actual footage of Blake hearing the boys singing in the background on cheer for the elves for the very first time https://t.co/KPYhy1198V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @roedio73 Mitch has made a career out of giving the finger to election results. He finds new and inven… https://t.co/NT9aCrIMw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing y’all come together even though you guys are the youngest is aaamazing. I hope you guys stay doing this so w… https://t.co/I9QZABDt4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[📸 When I catch you #slippin ... #howto #adultgames @ SLS Las Vegas https://t.co/eL2PBUo8oN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Icy road conditions, despite the slightly warming temperatures overnight, make a delayed opening necessary for safe… https://t.co/PYwnjDDAiK]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone: are you getting ready for spring break?! me: no, i’m too old to have spring breaks anymore... everyone: o… https://t.co/6PnF8iEAUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone fucking tell Kristjen Nielsen that the people crossing he border aren't ALIENS they are IMMIGRANTS.. They are human people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cityoftoronto @TO_WinterOps snow clearing is cool, but being woken up at 4am because a fleet of trucks is parked o… https://t.co/8D7J4oh9m8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday night fun: “I side with” political quiz on my iPhone. 😂 #ThisIs32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love to you ALL!!! 💕 #savvygirlhomes #realtorlife #704lifestyle #valentines #vday #lovewins @ Charlotte, North Caro… https://t.co/1LK8U9xc2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V_Rheault Oh I’m sorry. I hope you heal quickly and that the mechanic finally finds what’s wrong with the car. 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Dry Hopped Kettle Sour by @ConcessionBrew @ Concession Road Brewing Company — https://t.co/9zk5d4cJiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jebus_abe @AGsmiles @el_ewill @_DJREAL I already have my ticket can I replace Willie]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I’m guessing he will be announcing his candidacy any minute now. What a jokester.]]></document><document><![CDATA[El dinero no compra a las personas y si las compra es por qué se vendieron como objetos con un valor definido.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Henry Fonda photo found at Fort De Soto @ Fort De Soto, Florida https://t.co/WbggqZzbQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandsmartin When you don't know we have all black universities the dialogue ends because you are are plain stupid or purposely obtuse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw the clip with Thomas More Women’s B-ball. i must have missed the UC clip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will my future self invent the time machine and come tell me what I need to do to make the time machine? Also,… https://t.co/4KBGpeZzCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PresidentTrump just gave a textbook speech on Venezuela, Socialism and its logical conclusions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@largeicedmal it is, and one of these days I’m just going to have to drive there 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  You are such a despicable and unprincipled man. EVERY.  FUCKING. DAY. Your ignoble acts prove how… https://t.co/YxZD2EQJxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[a drew a pic of my dream man earlier n have just matched w someone on tinder who looks identical to my diagram . ma… https://t.co/gWWjc1aeLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL @RyanAFournier @realDonaldTrump Continued prayers for your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am far from alone in my opinion of the disrespectful treatment of Senator @Renee_Unterman. #GOP leadership in thi… https://t.co/zI0UmOX1Nz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Played @GetKahoot today in English. Students wrote questions based on Roll of Thunder, Hear My Cry. #gaming… https://t.co/AhZg2QotDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bigger than you think @ Georgia Aquriam and World of Coke https://t.co/7RCHn8Q7gw]]></document><document><![CDATA[How little do I care about #ValentinesDay? I just got food delivered and the delivery guy wished me a happy Valenti… https://t.co/xHaYDE4Qtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_ashleigh9 He’ll be sending you little signs of him all the time. Especially when you need them most. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Football players barely know howto dribble a ball without banging it off the floor w there strong asses]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa @realDonaldTrump The only one that ought to be praised.  Okay maybe not only, but for Americans pe… https://t.co/fJKdXdWWng]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special music set by J GRGRY during the 7 PM dinner hour, April 6 at Gay D.D. Presents *Nerds*!  Tickets available… https://t.co/ok0gUJ6nEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irshroz @Blondie55Plus “Baby Boy” Swalwell doesn’t know that there are many ways payment will be made. Can’t see t… https://t.co/xqFcde0HiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS You and your family are a disgrace. None of you know right from wrong or lies from truth.  The whole lot of… https://t.co/ATFsn4kKto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a sweet man always on the go and always taking time for people with such smiles 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epic #ketogenic meal last night.  Organic herb and garlic chicken sausage, Avacodo, and fresh green beans braised… https://t.co/9NhYQZzuk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comcast/Xfinity scalped me $70 for a visit when their service is broke. I pay a fee each month for service repair.… https://t.co/OBqKIjJjtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaronschneider @rtargenton You replied to a thread someone else started the day before you posted the video.  Not… https://t.co/Y7m3PDx5gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sara_Uzer This tweet makes me glad that I have not said that on any of my podcasts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your nigga started a argument yesterday just so he couldn’t get you nothing, its b/c he was probably waiting for… https://t.co/qoQHv9qUck]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have millions of dollars to invest and unlimited access to influence and power YOU 👏🏻 ARE 👏🏻 NOT 👏🏻 SELF… https://t.co/SOlJz1r9Gd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Officer Teel in his Mother’s classroom talking to students. The next day someone shot this young man to death. #RPD https://t.co/Neos0cF4Hg]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: The deceased individual has been identified as Elizabeth Ann Stropp, DOB 06/12/81. Our investigation remain… https://t.co/2ZrrDvqTlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[(I’m actually serious about the ‘free’ action plan. Has anyone put anything together on how this could work? Blog p… https://t.co/fbEjKF5MJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke and Winston are at home and he keeps sending me pictures of them and i just want to be there 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are a bunch of hard working men and women at the @HawkinsCounty Rescue Squad. They are also incredibly suppor… https://t.co/POIPj7ne56]]></document><document><![CDATA[I now pronounce you... corpse and cake | ⚰💕🎂  #25 https://t.co/zRwZDMTNT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyBoydActor Loved seeing you on @GreysABC and @Outlander_STARZ both great performances!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christinerandyy Ctfu it’s annoying like I’m sitting here like, ok so right now I’ll go get everything else I neede… https://t.co/he9HvxgPMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[ew every time i see this video i think of how this bitch is gonna dislocate her arms]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when I was 11 and I would do really gay shit and be like nahh couldn’t be me. Lmao who would’ve known]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT @dandrezner Cohen: "He speaks in a code. And I understand the code because I've been around him for a decade."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrFreddyColon @realDonaldTrump Omg but a racist who raped a 13 yr old and was installed by Putin and called NeoNaz… https://t.co/0DNwNQshW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chairman Nadler--GIVE IT UP!!!NO COLLUSION. All the Democrats have been doing for all this time is look for a crime… https://t.co/DKrKmId4rW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vickpo_33 @kyliemoy Lol i didn’t realize it would tag you. I just think this id the dumbest trend ever. I don’t fi… https://t.co/P89781ZaIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obligatory “nobody likes you when you’re 23” cake 🎂🤘 https://t.co/JTxArX2TUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @liz_simms2 and the rest of the Butler Girl’s team!  4th year in a row as TSTCA indoor champs!  Next stop.… https://t.co/4SjCrXpSkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I definitely followed him, I might cant touch but I surely can look 👀😍🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber turns 25 today so plz no one talk to me during this sensitive time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @NBCNewsTHINK Stick to her record. Leave her race and gender out of it. Don’t stoop to that low]]></document><document><![CDATA[I put people that listen to music through their headphones while they drive in the same category as serial killers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo rico del reencuentro y la re-conexión ⚡️... y lo rico del dulce de leche Argentino después de unas mollejas y mo… https://t.co/cvyr8Pt9Dj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielSchulman And it just keeps getting weirder.  Who’s running the country?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Errriee Oh yeah sweetie. It made me sweat like Mike Tyson in a spelling bee...😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time ⏰ to get this butt back in action. Incase you missed it @danielaryf announced today she’ll be racing… https://t.co/scknZq3Pa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone’s trying out the self operating napkin @pghkids #rubepgh @ Children's Museum of Pittsburgh https://t.co/HPMJVirYOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen.. for the record. I. DO. NOT. CONDONE. DOMESTIC. VIOLENCE. howeverrrrr, all I’m saying is.. a woman cannot b… https://t.co/OOT9R810wZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@illegitamatepr1 @SpryGuy I think you may have seen a video edited to specifically show her as a shrew which is not… https://t.co/gJcmqBRWKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu sinto um desanimo muito grande quando lembro que vou ficar mais um ano aqui na mesma função, queria que fosse de outro jeito]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to play it off like I don't care about the Jonas Brothers getting back together, but let's be real, I'm fan girling so hard rn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Racism's long painful history denies anyone the right to use it as a bargaining chip, #Trump used i… https://t.co/KHbxtARleK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had so much anxiety watching this I swear I thought u were gunna drop it on your foot 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cat31s @heiba11 @LadyBlackTear @Dzsozi22 @DeannGoss @HWolson @saladesvertes @VampireEmperor8 @XXXYRobin30… https://t.co/gtNaHif84h]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We have to look at each other and look up at the challenges we face,” says @amyklobuchar, on restoring faith in th… https://t.co/4of9qb7Yh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSMidland Freezing fog in Snyder happening now. https://t.co/QWdJRhiwC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok let’s try this again....not leaving airport today unless on an ✈️  We are here so early Southwest gates aren’t e… https://t.co/JuHofpPmR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Precious child of mine. 💕  #ElisandraSariah #BigSister #EzriellaVera #LittleSister #cousinlove @ The Historic Pearl https://t.co/4qPJVnNMfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrs_Malkowski @mrs_collins6th @annebaker83 This would've been my next choice if I could get a day 8!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland I was BORN to LEAD so Say: "Hail to the CHIEF" https://t.co/Nn9T2vgGZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cranker101 I do like it. Here it's 12.00 a bottle. Definitely a good wine for the price. I'm thinking it needs to… https://t.co/sYBG7SKoh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible illustrations by Mildred Codding, medical illustrator to neurosurgeon Harvey Cushing https://t.co/hXCzABj3fZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or maybe the Hanged Man, thats a good one too! A diff perspective-its a highly spiritual card as well. 🙏🏻 https://t.co/ELRjtq9FOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[To: My Twitter Family From: Dania Micala #HappyValentinesDay https://t.co/Oyr2DI6ecQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: what’s the 2nd Scooby Doo about again?  Mariah: (super serious) it’s about those monsters I think 🤔  Me: 🤦🏽‍♀️… https://t.co/RQytb2jJYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxghostguy @charliekirk11 @kimguilfoyle I think all you want to do is bash our President so please do not reply t… https://t.co/rX4GNN10wp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just read who the new Bachelorette is, and I’m not quite sure how I feel about it..]]></document></documents></author>