<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[PRICED TO SELL Most popular Floor plan by Lennar  https://t.co/nqUjwOQ0KY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to our amazing students!!! #50yearsstrong @NWMSgcs @GCSchoolsNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ate tres leches for breakfast at 3AM and don’t know if I should be proud or ashamed]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CarolinaFamily love these guys!! Definitely gonna miss them next season, but will continue following them in life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Holden114 @RBPundit @AG_Conservative @SethAMandel More like a participation trophy. She doesn’t want scrutiny or o… https://t.co/KsZbrZk0Fj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmakaCamille Many many congratulations. I look forward to adding this tome to my collection.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @RepSarbanes If the @GOPLeader tries to stop this bill then I will know without a doubt that the secret tr… https://t.co/jA5Qunospf]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happens when we empower our students? 6th grade students teach 2nd graders all about space! @BwjacksonSCI… https://t.co/krJJbc1Wa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@s8n Satan is a Catholic. He’s saying the same holy thang every morning. Before you know it, it’ll be his red backs… https://t.co/UOnxMf4Vxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao this whole thread has me thinking how did any of us survive childhood especially if you had siblings 💀😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So if Gonzaga has been going to the tournament for the last 20 years, those attending college there have never know… https://t.co/QpVYurHlYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cali_Artaveli @CJinSF1 @SherryMcMillion @MassRoots @askjillian And thank you for your sweet words. I’ll be an advo… https://t.co/S7nIEImJqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[live photo of my actual reaction to sameer dancing during tightrope. https://t.co/NOeNnrcI8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooooor, lukewarm take here, we could make movies and story lines about characters who ARE minorities instead of rec… https://t.co/rsYOOta1mV]]></document><document><![CDATA[so i can get some dick  i mean suck my dick  i mean get my dick sucked   we’re just blonde boys doing what blonde boys do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard someone talking about blue M&amp;Ms the other day, and it brought back some good memories]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STARZ_AND_BARZ Oh do I hear you! I can't understand WHY a business would let non-service animal in when a small ch… https://t.co/etfSZucEWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[For we have come to share in Christ, if indeed we hold our original confidence firm to the end. https://t.co/dKrnmGVuDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesShakir I don’t want to speak for people I don’t know or an academy I haven’t attended, but suicide rates ar… https://t.co/w0I63xIRRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate really just dipped, so I get the whole hotel room to myself??? Dope!]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF KAYLIE AND NICKY DONT GET TF OFF MY TM AO I CAN WATCH THIS DAMN MOVIE IM DELETING THIS APP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Last 7 years has been amazing, my baby love Grandniece Kynnedi will be 8 tomorrow! She's a gift! #auntielove… https://t.co/QnkdEwL6JJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wspd2pio @wsdot_traffic All that lovely white snow!!! Wish I was young enough to go skiing again!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pip_says @GeorginaGrogan_ Absolutely. I am similar to you where travel is my passion. I traveled well before my we… https://t.co/iuTnMx4gw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This woman wouldn't know respect if it fell in her lap, wrapped itself Around her and smothered her in kisses!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is some of the stuff that was stolen when my prius and kids were asleep in the back seat clothes shoes equipme… https://t.co/0UsxFN8YyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really feel bad for @Nike and @SEGA for this nightmare fuel of a disaster that’s way out of their control… https://t.co/8FlduJVvMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BennieGThompson WHO'S MORE IMPORTANT HELPING ILLEGALS OR HELPING BLACKS IN BELLEVUE GLADE, FL/CHICAGO/ATLANTA/MISSISSIPPI?]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you go grocery shopping when you can barely push the cart??? I am out of everything! Yes even on my last few… https://t.co/gAfZ28AUpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are photos I took of the #McLaren 570S. ⚫️  #photography #carphotography #supercar https://t.co/Zy6U0mJpkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jelly, much?    One difference between you and Spike Lee is that HE CAN READ. HE IS EDUCATED. NO ONE PAID FOR HIS E… https://t.co/hqgXOAXD9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d Perfectly said, Mr. Conway, I will forward this and hope all my followers do the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlfromhever On the right, the one in the middle I have seen used as Lady Jane Grey , if memory serves it was the… https://t.co/tLm2nGeWNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LEXXXLIEEE  u did awesome!! What are u cooking next?? Flautas?? Tostadas de pollo.. that chicken looked yummy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAG4All Hmm #RandPaul thinks he knows best 🙄 but Mexico drug violence: 9 hanged, 14 decapitated in Nuevo Laredo. U… https://t.co/dJEblkxyJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewamiller I hope in 2 years you have good taste in tv shows, food, the best beaches because I expect twitter… https://t.co/1L2diorMTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my friend and world’s best @EastsideHope #SquadMom @ConnieSpotts!  Hope you have a wonderful day… https://t.co/htXT1XQAbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabs_greyy I liked it because Chad and Jack don't have a back and forth relationship like Chad and Jennifer do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This commercial should get a trophy for the least helpful solution to a bad commute. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello biblio beauties 🦄💕 ~ I have today and tomorrow off work so I will be doing lots of writing, reading and of co… https://t.co/Sz7vIV7p8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait to see what the Rm 6 Stars come up with for their Dino characters for our soon to be published book, ' D… https://t.co/leKIxDOIk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiffthetechie @TMobile @BobStanchina @TmobileTruckMD @JMobile4U @joshua_kirsten @TChainzDC @TMobileTruckPHL… https://t.co/pPfhqnYRmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried a crab dip sandwich at this place in cary town and it was heavenly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erepsnake That is what I’m thinking we are getting something Friday not Saturday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive turned in multiple late papers this semester and not lost no sleep over it lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Version 2: “Any Resemblance To a Living Or Dead #Socialist is  Purely Coincidental.” ##Draw #Drawing #ProcreateApp… https://t.co/Ac0wcGhjEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollisDoolittle Love you, Lola. Just keep circling-you’ll get there one day. Bless her heart 💜🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[New 25th Anniversary Knob Creek on the shelves. Price was, well,  unbelievable so I took advantage!!! This ones 120… https://t.co/WbPSNMpn7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[They all drink the KoolAid before they go in that has to be the answer to why they still follow him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday you emotional 😭 father of mine #piscisseason♓️ @ Dodger Stadium https://t.co/rhiAvrZFaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Junior guard Matthew Murrell led Whitehaven with 18 points in the Tigers’ 65-49 win over Bartlett Monday night to s… https://t.co/grAYOl8g87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunflowerdoh you don’t deserve any of this hate :( i’m so sorry people are so fucking dumb and thinks it’s okay to… https://t.co/gdHakGAFap]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Alamo Drafthouse Cinema - Tempe in Tempe, AZ https://t.co/ViFL0wBgma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daisymarquez_ Too many good things happen today ..how can you sleep with so much excitement 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soulstcoffee @OleMissEvie @CRagan_finsup @BillisKing @TheRebelWalk @Robinthe21Ou @OleMissEvie, go a LITTLE bit eas… https://t.co/Bn0loh7no1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout-out to my Advanced 10 Ss! We did a fishbowl discussion of TTTC, which was a first for me and for them. They d… https://t.co/3KdetushkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @joncoopertweets @amyklobuchar They’re bot ting candidates down.  Leave the personality and focus on the message]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Long_liv_Larry @deniseatpeace @espnW First of all you don’t know me or what I’ve done. Nice job assuming I’ve neve… https://t.co/GWLZKMqP03]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re moving on to community questions with @VoteRussell Holmes keeping time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The UES... Where people walk their children and push their dogs in double strollers 🐶&gt;👶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gototheshack @JamesCraigmyle @GreeneCountySO So totally bummed that I missed out on buying these. That beautiful g… https://t.co/3m5qQ80PM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ LUZIA by Cirque du Soleil https://t.co/VeDvGRGeWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DlEDlEmyDARLlNG Thank you 😭 and you’re right I can’t be the one to croak first 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fam, Ariana said she brought the crib just for the closet. Why am I broke? 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qtf Ya dejense de estar metiendo sisaña, toda la vida se a echo parodias de algo o de alguien y nunca se había tom… https://t.co/m2WaK60oxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blaster151 @BryanDawsonUSA No. A person’s ancestry isn’t determined by how Donal Trump thinks they look or don’t l… https://t.co/L5mIzKc0rx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#blackgirlmagic on fleek! Dance class with these Brooklyn Just-Teens that I stumbled on but the energy they hadddd… https://t.co/nJzdNJbReX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love these ladies. It’s gettin’ sweaty up in here. On Ride 3 of 4! #CycleForSurvival]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the subway post dismissal time and a group of kids run on holding the comic book, The Baby-Sitters Club. They ar… https://t.co/eCPSGcm5Dv]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE BIG TEN IS PLUNGING INTO CHAOS RIGHT BEFORE THE TOURNEY(S) I LOVE THIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[me &amp; not including my GPA on my resume because it aint shit, sitting in a tree]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJonFuller My God, you realize the Penguin is *made* for this crossover?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SNLDREAMS @KellyannePolls Ok fat shirley his a child and did nothing wrong. He was just attending a pro-life rally… https://t.co/OhUihT1pFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should have done what you did years ago and opted not to go to Vietnam. I guess you wanted a big win master negotia… https://t.co/oZMyHKZhcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take chances and go beyond the norm to xplr places you’ve never thought to go 🖤🌙 https://t.co/ARfc3QBBfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sit in the back of the bus, take up space kind of mood. @ Portland, Maine https://t.co/t7oK7xnaRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DirtyMoMedia @DaleJr @Spotify This should be great for a road trip to Charlotte in a few weeks. We will be stopping by to see you all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[13 years and I couldn’t imagine my lifetime bestfriend being anyone else. It doesn’t matter how much you talk to yo… https://t.co/hnws8tv5f1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanGutmanBooks @Ford_sdford Absolutely! Get them all! They are ALWAYS checked out! My Weird, Weirder, Weirdest (et… https://t.co/7acpq12zda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Of course you do...you’d loose your job if you didn’t....🤪🤪🤪🤪😂😂😂😜😜😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul You are a globalist New World Order Swamp Creature...you exposed yourself voting against the WILL of the… https://t.co/uL3j8PkV6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#QuickDinner (at @Five_Guys in Midlothian, VA w/ @bryan_warren) https://t.co/U0bX4KmyIc https://t.co/dyOIQzT7jD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many Oscar viewers were stunned to see Green Book win best picture  https://t.co/lcBIwX40hA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Introducing @KaceyMusgraves to a friend and trying to explain it's not a Taylor Swift situation is really difficult]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liloldforallth1 @DPNJ @RepSwalwell Thanks so much! You enjoy your day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steelerschic85 @kathrynresister @CindyinMemphis2 @PollyPapaya @pam_brundige @Kovie1961 @nicole_bertrand… https://t.co/v9tE8NOxTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is your Monday morning reminder that you are AMAZING and you can handle ANYTHING. Have a great week everyone!!… https://t.co/DplFMPI9Rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[58 today in Monrovia, California no rain today! https://t.co/uzsbR5tlT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sectional Saturday.  #WorkHard #onegameatatime #LetsGoWarriors https://t.co/onQ1oYAPvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of attention has been paid to @AOC's effective questioning at hearings, but @rephankjohnson was particular ef… https://t.co/KATIvzk3L5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JazzJennings__ Thinking about Noelle today, hoping she is doing okay. #ParklandStrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really proud of my brother, @brittenoli and his track team! Way to go, @MontreatXCTF !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bay Area you are invited this Friday! Women in Space! extramacsauce will be singing 🎤 There will be prizes. It will… https://t.co/WgIrlOex8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[In part 2 of our discussion Elad and I talk about the trip many will take this April with ICCM. The tour features t… https://t.co/UfaVcvf8u6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetoORourke hiding behind a wall at his Texas speach https://t.co/rSqjV2IDNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reko_Intl Wonderful photo - nice to say hello last night @DianeReko and a shout out to @laurenbrummell #yqg #iwd #iwd19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarkAndreFurry @ClarkCountySch @McCawSTEAM Yes please!  We will reach out earlier. Thank you for reading to our Las Vegas students!  ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of the #AmericasDIConference at the @UKinUSA with so many fab speakers and activities taking place to make a… https://t.co/zq6DFDOz3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraBenanti I hope your daughter is feeling better and that “woman” is not worth even mentioning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CousineauSherri That is such an incredible opportunity!  I wish USA Rugby had an equivalent.  I guess we won't be… https://t.co/tSJAo8fJxX]]></document></documents></author>