<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[COMEDY... COMIC CON... MURDER!  @SupergirlofSF Listen to Supergirl of San Francisco:Random #Podcast by ShawnSunshin… https://t.co/kif3Z1FFqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnoopDogg what up man. I heard you mad at the lakers and giving up your booth for five dollars.  Can I hav it.  So poor man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ewwjr53 @lauren_hoggs @FBI Like I said, the difference is easy access to guns like the AR-15. https://t.co/NbNXbBjWB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jgoss1971 @johngranato @reaganswinbank @LanceZierlein Dude do you hate d? I love d man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You lie every day, $100 days you’re lying 🤥 right now, loser !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You're only saying that because the Media brings to light all the Bullshit you do. All caps again,… https://t.co/DIdhr7eiEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie @BulwarkOnline The left now questions was her statement anti-semitism,and if one is going to condemn… https://t.co/3zcU7mrsUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raymackformeck @IlhanMN She's not wrong about that, but likewise, people who have different beliefs than her when… https://t.co/EITqxwX2tm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LesDeplorablesT @Larryputt @kimusastrong @BAM4AU @POTUS @realDonaldTrump 😳🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[2: The best part of The Observatory is the Del Taco right down the street.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisHewitt @HelenLOHara @jamescdyer Oooohhhh yep I think you’re correct. Ok good I didnt want to be right. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman The best thing for the Repulicans, the freshman class of the Demacrats... Keep them on t.v. and it wi… https://t.co/KqU23BJx1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Because the @GOP is still inherently racist and corrupt. And even in the 21st century they try to dra… https://t.co/datEWfHsyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like everyone to know that @Ali_Lucia created the MNLARS joke I just used on MidMorning when talking about… https://t.co/2YBf7NWPhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjchockey77 @Cyndifferous @Coheed @ZacharyACooper @TravStever @claudioPsanchez Yo you trying to kill us? Lol I’ll see what I can do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoppyKercheval Carmichael: "The fact is that they're going to pass an education reform bill today that does includ… https://t.co/5kjBhZBzbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ohh_Maliboo Mane everybody acting so hurt like you not suppose to cut the nets down when you win conference...stop it 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirJonesy @onepeloton @jmethodfitness Quick one! https://t.co/8FjCAAkoay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stupid Cupid Dance... #ConjuntoAmbicion #PuroPincheParty @ American Legion Post-41 https://t.co/k9BqUJRITI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that didn’t go as planned. I can’t be the only one who loves when Kerr gets hella mad and tossed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Tizzle45 @_GrandMasterJoe @1FlyRicoo Not playing you or shilo until y’all punch your information in correctly. Yo… https://t.co/3N7sVJfEfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Reality ALL Real niggas are obligated to me 👱🏾‍♂️ I’m the Realest thing posting 😠📲 and I’m the best to be❗️ https://t.co/GR8Ae81VWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF Zuck was my dad, who used FB’s network to propel my startup to a $1,000,000,000, would I be considered self made?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indiana Delegation #gc2019 @ Downtown St. Louis https://t.co/ZYmTsS4XsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[3L Austin Jones (Germer PPLC, Austin, Texas) rang the @PeppLaw Jobs Bell https://t.co/LT9V5cmFDI https://t.co/hMJaTz5tjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Non disclosure agreement. Boom. Greg Steube forget that Cohen is, in fact, a lawyer (disbarred). But he’s out of his depths.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man asked for 15racks then told yall he leaving the country lmao ok. People just giving that away?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an I Wanna Bock And Roll All Night (and Lager Everyday) by @TatteredFlagBSW at @pjspub — https://t.co/qrNf4nBRyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KonkreteKids @mcall @JoshFolck @NAHSKrew @NAHS1619 @69Sports CONGRATULATIONS GIRLS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stoolpresidente Now if we can just get her to yell “Sell the Team” at a Knicks game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just discovered today that one of life’s greatest game changers is the electric toothbrush]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Puppetry is the past, present, and future of theatre!” -Aretta  Kicking off the @NevadaThespians #NVThesRoadTrip w… https://t.co/mI8nVaH2O0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cranberry-Quince Berliner Weisse (Berlin White) ••• 4.1% ••• Very Limited Release ••• Spontaneously Soured Seasonal… https://t.co/G3iKC3NanZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eyak29 @DantasyF That's not even a deciding factor here. These two backs aren't far off from each other in talent.… https://t.co/XUVq4lKye9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports @VP Pence is a sycophant of the highest order. Trump’s removal from office will leave the country… https://t.co/AoILOcbaTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ford Truck Month has truly been separating the real ones from the fake ... 💯✌🏼👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao so everybody already had a feeling takeoff ain’t fw cardi and i’m just late i see😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well...  I was planning on sleeping in.  Purposely did not set my alarm.  My internal alarm woke me up at 4:00.  Th… https://t.co/hdmugQiK59]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me why @Barnesnsamantha  sent me a picture of a cloudy ass sky and said “almost as pretty as you “ lmao she ain’t shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helenium I’m 99% sure I’m dating Nick,so basically we are family. See you at thanksgiving dinner 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CIA argue hard and fast you can’t do anything rn to make me happy. If not that then why you won’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scaramucci @OKIndian1 Draining the swamp ain't easy.  #MAGA https://t.co/y6XNUxDzBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#teamhopeandfaith #recoverd #sbrana #Italianlife #trustyourgut #bae @chanelwestcoast n @sbrana150 fo ever love you… https://t.co/UXcyXVaTa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to check out Apex Legends finally and eat this pint of ice cream.   My brains fried after editing this wedding the last 48 hours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally found my car keys. Well , my mom did. Shoutout to that beautiful woman yet again #rider]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!! Former UNC, NBA player Rasheed Wallace named next boys basketball coach at Jordan https://t.co/noO6kbVe4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when one person takes a table for 4 at a restaurant like really??!!??!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vice Ganda, one of the biggest superstars of this generation. I’m sure kayang kayang kumontra kay RV and not afraid… https://t.co/IznetZzRv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that was pretty: Herro steal, ahead to Johnson, ahead to a turbo-charged Hagans for the layup off glass despit… https://t.co/zoLM65uoum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krishna7137 Girl I’ve got a list of kitchen appliances on an Amazon wishlist anyone could buy my love for]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinstaple It’s awesome how everyone who contributed to this film helped elevate it. I saw his name in the credi… https://t.co/pD8148KnbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rudepundit Trumpists miss the good old days Or racist chants and hating gays, Of feeling smug if you were white, A… https://t.co/ChRrhi4vQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tgrlzcom @lithium66 @kittysilk7 @jockosrocket @Vdsxx1 @ironPenus_JPN @Here_Diversity @theweirdguy007 @Tgirlfan69… https://t.co/aIdZ1wS3Ip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patricia_Traina If only he would have picked a long snapper. With a time machine, we could have won that 2003 play… https://t.co/j9gEhhNYAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jews are not a monolithic group. We all are different. The desire by the American Right Wing to tell me how I am su… https://t.co/oWfnS9tzFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending this Saturday morning, personally thanking everyone who has contributed to my campaign over the last few w… https://t.co/eAFhr50SDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Manny Machado signs biggest FA deal in MLB History*                                   Live look at Nolan Arenado: https://t.co/eJqUsqZM4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why they can’t withhold racist students transcripts and diplomas on suspicion. Library fines and parking ticket… https://t.co/BWiU1tDFpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deonjoelpolo We all do, we think that sexy shit is them being jealous. NAHHHHHH it get annoying reL quick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iron_lombardi @Mel_the_geek @HillaryWarnedUs @HillaryClinton If you are confident Obama or anyone commuted a coup… https://t.co/Vsho0o7Qtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[429m on stairs today. Lots more to do before the Tour de Mont Blanc #TMB #climbforkids #christielakekids… https://t.co/VVmEy547C4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read this and it reminded me a lot of Jesse Lacey, who hasn’t been heard from since 2017.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama @YahooForde If only could build a wall around those knees #everyathlete]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandonshoward @chaboi_DG Important to note it was a list of “college football cities” and not stadiums/in-game at… https://t.co/cgTqWbiFSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister is actually gonna get me the new air pods when they come out 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s going to the @TheVille_Hoops game tonight??? I am!  WITH MY WIFE!  Date night 😎. How bout a win, boys? Go Bla… https://t.co/dQsc8Qc2am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpikeEskin I could care less about Harper/Machado! I rather sign a couple really good SPs. Maybe a high level 2nd… https://t.co/SPOodYViTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MightBeReign @BIitzz @CIutchezz I’d say cod was the most fun 2011-2012]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrorism with substance in threatening letter. Mail Fraud. Submitting false crime report. False testimony to law e… https://t.co/ILtWsCk4Ye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSGray Currently in Nashua its 25 degrees with light snow and sleet @ 11:45 am. Snowfall thus far is 2 inches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Apostolic Lighthouse Church https://t.co/kkR4x550hl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ATX is so hot right now that they are absorbing more space than is literally available at a rate of 1.7x....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonteasyMoore Oh I'm not gonna stop because some internet troll or fanboys say otherwise.  That's big match/show gear everytime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyHubbard I didn’t know that because I didn’t fly B-29s I can’t appreciate my grandpa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 The only way to stop a bad penis with a gun is a good penis with a gun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity This is all politics. If you actually believe the crap you spew, I hope you are haunted by your fear o… https://t.co/ksW4WeBlLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSBCranberry Thanks!  I grew up in the Mon-Valley guys.  Next time I get back I WILL hit you!!👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 'Hawks have 27 shots on goal and it feels like 20 of them have been scoring opportunities! #NotReady]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebekahzombie @turtledumplin Not as gross as people. Well some people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved this @nyfw moment after my impromptu reunion with @lizeverettstyle ...it was a double pleasure meeting you… https://t.co/GWTWlxJBTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Via @WRAL: An Unvaccinated Boy Got Tetanus. His Hospital Stay: 57 Days and $800,000.  https://t.co/QrAyYzgoCz Ignor… https://t.co/xUBuSL3z59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bpolitics @guypbenson Money laundering is one of the oldest capitalist tricks, no taxes, reasons why the numbers g… https://t.co/arOmlkJU4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Softykjr Beloved is the key word here. Anyone who honestly thinks Earl or Sherm would be more beloved by Seahawks… https://t.co/QNd8KcrkqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #StLouis, MO job and click to apply: HCM Coordinator - https://t.co/nvz3g1U1xs #BusinessMgmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CutlerRidgeLAZ @Maureen52375 Dre was home for 5 days. Just went back last night. I literally saw her for 30 min, w… https://t.co/GWBZRfKqqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doris is being the best social mastiff she can be @tribusbeerco.... #mastiffsofinstagram #tribusbrewing @ Tribus Be… https://t.co/FpvtLHDOpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigVinceWicks Exactly 😂😂 i was diddy that time like fuck it let’s go get ice cream]]></document><document><![CDATA[nobody:  sorority girl that just danced for 36+ hours at her university dance marathon:]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/grfEcJuFAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les enfants n’ont plus le droit à leur enfance. Ils doivent prendre leur rang et entrer dans le moule fille que les… https://t.co/wbcD5cLbOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acakes421 @wawabilly I figured that darling so glad you are doing ok. The background didn't change so that's how I… https://t.co/QVMPRY3ydp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus doesn’t endorse any political party, but after celebrating the murder of babies, perverting the institution o… https://t.co/yQqge3sI4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Depression the most annoying bich I’ve ever met and she STAY hitting me up too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryAinsley @seanhannity For sure you can trust the republicans, wrong!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved watching @WWE #WWEFastlane along with @PatMcAfeeShow! @therealec3 @PeytonRoyceWWE and @BillieKayWWE @notsam… https://t.co/POuYvLoxFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOLs a laymans explanantion. You start a company hire employees and lose 10 dollars for the first three years. On t… https://t.co/0v57nrnlR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The teenager in front of me kept checking if I were okay, I swore like a drunken sailor with Tourette’s and slow In… https://t.co/mTxpiEv8gZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This phone is wayyy better than #GalaxyS10 and it's 2000% cheaper! https://t.co/juXNRJBInY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southcarolinafb @amigosteevo Not bad. Definitely nervous. Decent form though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aha!  I think I've finally figured out how Twitter works.  Say simple but important things about subjects you actually know about. ;)]]></document></documents></author>