<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This girl is on another level of stupid! 🤦🏻‍♀️ I hope he leaves her after the baby is born and keeps this as proof… https://t.co/nFG3NpYoqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyway, that got way too deep. Long Duck says fuck the snow and go Mets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning and growing will help you with confidence, and it will help you to understand what's right for you, what's… https://t.co/RGGfw3m6V1]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻 love it @NancyDouyon telling the @Wisdom2conf to ask ourselves what ways can we step away from our own per… https://t.co/jG8q5SKhjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mackscatering @SenSchumer @senatemajldr By addressing climate change,  we stave off the inevitable for our next ge… https://t.co/3PRj2aywLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lee_kotikod13 @IngrahamAngle @Comey @realDonaldTrump AMERICAN tears a flowing. He's not mucking up the liberals. H… https://t.co/FxdRYHyfuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi the brouhaha about @IlhanMN has gone too far!  Her remarks were not anti Semitic.  It is about time… https://t.co/7kEJht4Yar]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is World Nutrition Month 🌱 (every month should be nutrition month 😆) check the link in my bio 👆👆👆 for some in… https://t.co/iAxRxdja3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was one of those days where life just wants to poke at you and really test your patience 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t feel bad making fun of white trash people.   Does that make me a bad person? https://t.co/ktp3zLfW5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@depjorgesolla povinho naniquinho viralatinha tupiniquin resolveu morrer]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Strong women don’t play victim, don’t make themselves look pitiful, and don’t point fingers. They stand and they d… https://t.co/nWMzRkikO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[What New Research on Teens and Social Media Means for Teachers https://t.co/HYejCdRVGX via @CommonSenseEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@careeragfood When we have much we need to give help wherever n whenever we can; across the globe or next door.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Evsteiny @kalebkernan Oh my gosh.......seriously, WHERE IS HE? Do you think he missed the pic?! There’s no way....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackfpaylor It’s barely even started &amp; I’m already sick to death of Bernie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Please don’t go anywhere. Your pretense helps the Republicans. Keep doing what your doing #notawinner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTrueBrendanF Of course it helps that he’s actually aged really well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get ready...it’s TIPsy Tuesday time!! Stay tuned for more informative videos!!  . . . . . #tipsytuesday… https://t.co/kPQ9Fz2wrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE. What is love? Love is all around you, can you feel it?? Thank you to stevenrobinsonphoto for directing, shoot… https://t.co/sJkMgds8GO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating our d30 specialist Phyllis for her 20 years of service with Home Depot! @JoseOrt40780493 https://t.co/xHxB4tvrz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Fake president!  And whiny, snot nosed little twerp.  Reminds me of you and your whiny, snot nosed little twerp sons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a chance I live at one of the sushi by bou (@ Sushi By Bou in New York, NY w/ @kaylamosley) https://t.co/23IHOQ5KHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliciaMotter @alicekeeler @mrsestepscience The message was a lil odd but I was like, it’s Alice being funny lol💜🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National #LoveYourPetDay! This playful black feline is a central figure of Will Barnet’s “Woman, Cat and a St… https://t.co/KO1D6JzJul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Manicdj99 @RepGraceMeng @RulesDemocrats @RepPressley What moronic statement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericvale Yay! I'm so excited about this! To me, you ARE Yuki, and Yuki is my favorite. ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eve052 @wien_sulzbach @SoapFanForLife @GenieFrancis @thejonlindstrom @SIJFG @Bedollz @hagerman_becky @IQ38 @carrieunderwood Yes it is!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets I'd like to see him run for Governor of New York State. How many votes could he possibly get?… https://t.co/eofJOqEblq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a bummer. But then we had Cozumel for dinner 🌮🌯 whorehey1986 @ Cozumel Mexican Restaurant https://t.co/51aEA8xMie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tfw today: A. 48 sadiv sets deadlift in  12 mins B. Bar pullups(20), 10 Arnold press x15lbsx4 C. 10 step ups each l… https://t.co/ftlLcyBQFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@henryrodgersdc Democrats forgot too, as soon as they found out that a Republican was the next scandal-free person in line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So when people tell me to "suck it up" "you'll be fine" "you already see him on weekends," when I complain that I d… https://t.co/vKid8eX49f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do parents think just cuz they’re older that means they don’t have to apologize for being rude???]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of times that @WFAN660 on @Radiodotcom skips or cuts out would be bad for a first generation Discman on… https://t.co/BN1KAE2AcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[You aren’t listening to the Revisionist History podcast? Why the heck not?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was up at 7 am for work &amp; am now laying down at 415 am after work... Wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had an amazing customer service experience with Rolly at @fabfitfun. Thank you! #fabfitfuncares]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Imjustajew I’m telling you! Puxie Phill, Bullet, Staten Island Chuck, and ALLLLLL of them need to be brought up on charges!]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP Leaders #Knew FBI Was Probing Trump.   They Did #NOT Complain.  https://t.co/4c9XEFU884 via @truthout]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris92395980 @MIGS_AI @alexismadrigal Just wow! How about the firemen... oh and the people jumping out of windows... all theater?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breitbart lays out 8 times Cohens testimony EXONERATED Trump https://t.co/d6UQH5V2Fc via @ILMForg]]></document><document><![CDATA['Winnie the Pooh' was created by a vet explaining war to his boy https://t.co/xTZa966wxZ #UTSASSITN HS Psych. How t… https://t.co/3ffvOl6FFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[1450828_755418467817588_464719967_n.jpg (640×752) https://t.co/fAbBvM8apP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch, card for brother (@ Discount Drug Mart in Centerville, OH) https://t.co/Ob9lPNgXso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch now imma have to go back thru last season and try to connect the dots on how Emmett killed Nate Sr.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jettila @Wolfiesmom Easy.  A T-bone steak with bleu cheese sauce, Brussel sprouts with bacon and strawberry shortcake]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deejay90192 @AdamParkhomenko Well they will have to show tax returns in Cal if win in primary?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel so sorry for the girl i was a year ago. depressed, suicidal and unconfident. i just want her to know she’s l… https://t.co/eOm5BjAHaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherrynron @smalltownandrew I am guessing she will not be flitting around her mane anymore on FOX!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think y’all understand how excited I am for this food #AfterHours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Climate change is going to make these storms worse. Much worse. Costs will be very EXPENSIVE for government.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This shit the ultimate petty. You know that thing don’t care for that shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[McCabe, Rosenstein must testify to explain claim that DOJ discussed removing Trump, GOP leaders say  https://t.co/S5Nq3xr71Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carrie_np @DrBSlawski @DrSunilKSahai @KurtPfeifer @SPAQIedu Glad you could join us this year! Join us in 2020 for more exciting updates!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of y’all ladies need to control  “ y’all man “ or whatever you call him come get homie out of my messages begging. 😂😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happy #internationalwomensday to #all the #lovelyladies and #great #headshots today by @catfarnsworth and… https://t.co/5ctYhb1B2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone said “i’m happy and have nothing to complain about today”😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry Yes. But when he is released I doubt he will finally realize how stupid he has been]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone in NorCal at #EvoJapan2019?! Someone please get me a Hi-Score Girl x EVO Japan item!!! 😭😭 I want it so bad! https://t.co/UPBzMHh6sy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@e_weaver_18 @ADuckFanForLife I mean sounds about right. Play like shit all season &amp; then jk playoffs here we come 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work should let women wear sweats to works when we have our periods...😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend Lola unexpectedly lost her mother this week. If you can, please donate to help her family cover the costs… https://t.co/OWHhorFNdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylenntrayy Ya i can't wait to see tonight's episode now lol it's not on here yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If you have to produce your financial life The Democrats should Have to do the same!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@herbivore_club @paulettegloria @ChestnutPhil @herbivore_club https://t.co/MBM29ikblp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that you do this! This will never forget it. You see I am a Mimi of 9 yr awesome baseball player. What do I… https://t.co/fpKLpI4TTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Saturday nights are for baking. I make something special for our new members and visitors to enjoy in Sunday sch… https://t.co/DJsgcyHrTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody Awesome. Just waiting for other departments to try it!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re lucky.. a dog will come into your life, steal your heart and change everything!  #LoveHer #Dog #Pet  Her… https://t.co/UE7VLlBOqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussAlexia @MaxVelocity @If_ItAint_B The ones who truly believe in themselves will reach unimaginable heights]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBraeden Congrats again to your granddaughter. I had insomnia last night and what's on SHOWTIME,  Den of Thieves!… https://t.co/0Bvv2QDvDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertN1964 The lady with the blue house and all the plants is my friend... 💚💚💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay not mad at @ccps but I do hate my debate teacher right now, like you want us to dress up while you show up loo… https://t.co/HCat1F4yQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Does Ivanka actually earn what she is paid? What the actual f*ck? Who doesn’t want to be paid enough… https://t.co/x0D3IgZFb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrickesque See how desperate he is to hide them?  Just like DT.  Everything we've suspected is true, he's a comp… https://t.co/ZxbC7O7K6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY KAL 🎉🥳💜 I love you so much AND I like your Pueblo birds (; I’m so blessed to have you as a friend, t… https://t.co/aMezCrhMmj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo mil horas hablándole a mi mejor amiga y adivinen a quien le vale verga y se conecta y no me contesta jaja si a elllaaaaaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HawaiiFive0CBS @MeaghanRath @RealScottCaan @RealscottAcaan @AlexOloughlin16 @BeulahKoale @jorgegarcia @ChiMcBride… https://t.co/JzeQ2R51Yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 71: Today I am grateful for sumo stance.  [Gif: mr potato head attempts a two plate deadlift but his arms stay… https://t.co/9MeqPUoDvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[She was only gonna get one but they were the last 2 siblings and didn’t wanna separate em]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TakeBkTheNation @870South Hardly know him at all. He was only working for me a short time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell Love!!!  Pass the torch. We can learn so much from each other. https://t.co/PnAgjcc6ES]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was planning a nice lonely hike.. like I just wanted to go clear my mind…]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler_casper No matter how hard life gets, the one thing I would never give up is the Compassion, Kindness, Caring… https://t.co/qEdPOm3BHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The huskies are just getting outworked....work hard and have fun boys. LET’S GO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for hosting @dulcevegan! We loved every second of being at your awesome place!! https://t.co/zg1z0qEnxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be still my heart ❤️  Love these guys so very much. Thank you for celebrating with me, love you ❤️ #family… https://t.co/e8XPgmpgs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new Game of Thrones posters are proving useful as screensavers  https://t.co/Oba2MzeS8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I just would like to know how many Americans are serving in foreign Government positions to repres… https://t.co/pdc8uwthNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[At GraphQL Day listening to @__xuorig__ talk about distributed schemas https://t.co/tRlRsHTCf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SokkieBomb @Willav777 @sdinis28 @laur_kickedarat 👑😘 https://t.co/HhvoeZdzUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[engraçado que toda vez que passa all my heart de sleeping with sirens no aleatório eu lembro do gustavo hahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m training the new girl at work right... and she brings up our pay. Y’all, this white lady is getting paid more than me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where’s the warm up they’re taking about? I just froze my baguettes off when I went out to start the car. Brrrr🥶 #INeedSpring]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m seeing @BTS_twt at the Rose Bowl. I’m actually going to see them. What is life. https://t.co/8UPQKZABLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Do you really think the American people are so stupid that they believe anything that you tweet. Y… https://t.co/vbhgmwxjXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I blocked @AnnCoulter fed up with her. It's easy to criticize. but @AnnCoulter she does not have to deal with the D… https://t.co/0bX4U5mk2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasonstickers I had to freaking go outside when he started bellowing. He’s such a blow hard nothing burger. 🍔 🍔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheShieldLady @Saska089 @Mike_TWC @DoogieTWC @ChrisTWC @PorterTWC @BrannonTWC @chaseyray @MysteryChick71 Like i ju… https://t.co/cZu7zYEbVu]]></document></documents></author>