<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Predators lines in the a.m. in Vegas Forsberg, Johansen, Arvidsson Fiala, Turris, Sissons Boyle, Bonino, Smith Hartman, Jarnkrok, Grimaldi]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing to lose by giving a student a second chance.   Nothing. Nada. Zilch.  There’s only the possibility… https://t.co/C6cjyJ9OeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @LHS_hippert for hosting tonight a showing of If They Had Known, a documentary on the dangers of mixing R… https://t.co/NCBx1wxPlH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders says he’s Running For President https://t.co/JsrR7sRqUS via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We should instead address the causes: We ought to create policies and institutions that push back against rising i… https://t.co/fmUfjxz06L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @DonaldJTrumpJr @RealClearNews @realDonaldTrump Big Tech Hates America and our Awesome President Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pues ... ya me pusieron un apodo... "El Wino "🍷... estas amistades! 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would've been absolute consensus position from Evangelicals...now you're an "open borders", socialist loving, globa… https://t.co/Kzb2q88J5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kayden is tired of sharing a room. In her 2nd step towards her dream of home ownership her agent, David Thelin brou… https://t.co/Wxbl1VAZy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDennisLynch @KamalaHarris No Dennis - this will be done - get onboard or get out of the way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MARINE_99ZULU @D1v5C @POTUS The next question would have been ;what are you gong to do to punish Kim"?...then...wh… https://t.co/GaKj6E9bAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[He all my,,,,so you leave him alone some beaches https://t.co/WvqFTEQoDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC God help us if you two do to America what your Socialism has done to Venezuela. Who will come to our aid?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 614 CANYON PKWY #Amarillo #TX  #realestate https://t.co/ZByr2uvEw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we go back to when “the way” got released. Back when Ariana Grande didn’t piss me off and Mac wasn’t dead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in the shop working on the Toyota. Cleaning up some wiring, and building a temporary flatbed so I can haul som… https://t.co/26dZ0CVYb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we need to do isn't complicated... Stop the human traffickers. Stop the drug traffickers. And #BuildTheWall!… https://t.co/Mxvi5Nb13Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[The online disinformation campaign against 2020 Democratic candidates has already begun: Here’s the top fake-news s… https://t.co/Y3gQ3PSOIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lyndhurst_Group @MichelleNMoon You rock, Bob. I like the intentional, self-aware "fundamental reassessment" approa… https://t.co/UKnsE2RWLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMQ1875 @almostjingo @Slate @Dahlialithwick @Twitter I will say this, child molestation  is such a heinous crime t… https://t.co/7ah6cZrUAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockstarGames why do I have to continue to play the prologue when all I want to do is play online? It’s frustrating]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching The Oscars live has been so much fun. Lord knows I’ll probably never do this again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ I coach hockey and wear flip flops with my track suit to the rink... rain, snow or shine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely a better trailer than the first, as there were some shots that genuinely looked really cool. But it also… https://t.co/fQcR4aLHgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning.. Have a Blessed Day ... Support your own 365 Days a Year @ Buffalo, New York https://t.co/rTnITYnsuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The David Stott Building in Capitol Park following its $72.7 million redevelopment by Dan Gilbert’s Bedrock LLC.… https://t.co/4k1hWX4i2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday February 26 - Balance of Power:    Two of Asia’s fiercest rivals are at it again      Via @bpolitics… https://t.co/Jz25ZiCMnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@majornelson Dante from the recent DMC. Just snarky enough. #freecodefridaycontest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellpwtorch @zheydorntorch Two damn good lookin’ gentlemen right there putting together a podcast 😂 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldSchool80s @nightlounge24 2019: In Canada Diet Cherry Coke still as rare as hen's teeth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my disability inclusion colleague, @Joshua__Leonard !!!  Episode 392 - Black History - Making a… https://t.co/52sKdCnyfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelseaxrae92 No kidding! If I wanted to ‘build my own salad’ I’d go to Subway. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[getting on the vcu barstool page was my life goal and I’m proud to say I’ve accomplished it]]></document><document><![CDATA[But y’all already know I have a personality so it’s easy to bartend and serve to people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tropicália by @creaturebeer at @bwwings — https://t.co/MOAF09nFAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sari-  what do you mean watch dog group? C- secret organizations are not new.  A group writing anonymously online a… https://t.co/uCqW78fjI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The BKCB1 meeting is sparsely attended tonight. Including only 18 community board members (so far). Maybe it’s the… https://t.co/BPPf3MdHqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevpluck @_treysin @einandererblog @cathmckenna @NikolovScience @BudBromley No you just suggested that.  I’m sayin… https://t.co/U8e0AvNJXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cinbinbains Yo.   Can you guys work on saying Jarron’s name correctly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassandraSeven Technically yes, Congress could block Trumps Declaration. However, the Senate Republcinas have no spine. #jellyfish]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 I wrote a piece @just_security on this potent White House-Congress tussle here: https://t.co/qNkt7I3YAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[BLESSED 68TH EARTHLIGHT TO RESPECTED SOUND SYSTEM OPERATOR/SELECTOR, ANTHONY "DOWNBEAT THE RULER/TONY SCREW" ROOKWO… https://t.co/v0nHVYcFIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine signing up for college knowing how much it cost and then waste all those years on a degree that you cant ma… https://t.co/Ygt4YLbxzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[when we #believe when we #act when we stand in the gap with our brother, #Christ we #change the #world, we change #lives]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sudikoff He was calling Roman's timeline into question and what he was doing while he was gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamareesalyer69 Thanos vs darkseid she probably meant. Or my take is thanos vs ultron would be a thriller]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t put two and two together..sorry to hear that @raycomsports and you have been w/ the #ACC for many years! I u… https://t.co/CME8Do5xM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@25_male_nyc A band you will like I think that I’m just getting into is Oceans Ate Alaska. Covert is a bop and a half.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Sunrise #FL https://t.co/NpiyNMthET #realestate #realtor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I listened earlier. It’s a great episode. One of my fave parts is when @MattPacifici discusses how he felt his team… https://t.co/x4MKSlp6K5]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have @twinflamesband with us over lunch and they rule! #PMSeries   https://t.co/Na9CglRNHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maricarmenmarin Como estás soy un fiel seguidor tuyo quise saber cuando haces una precentacion en New Jersey 😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cinemassacre @SoCalRetroExpo @suprvideogmegal Cool seeing you again. May we 'das boot' better next time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet when #DCEU movies come out...🤔   If Captain Marvel's not for you, that's no reason to rain on someone else's pa… https://t.co/QdPMOd4E5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know pioneering paleontologist Mary Anning, but what about the Philpot sisters? @trowelblazers https://t.co/eMuaTEz1LV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brendajamesxxx I try to look at the bright side.  I'm alive and can walk....]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an excellent management strategy. Must better for collaboration! Well done! @gretchenwhitmer @garlin]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Particularly in manufacturing, the economic slowdown has already begun, and the new jobs report confirms this. Las… https://t.co/EpS7ZK5PQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Big Dog is back! Greatest day ever, get those wet diapers ready smarks https://t.co/VQG8eed6np]]></document><document><![CDATA[La carta pública de Monseñor Moronta al tirano y a los militares es a no dudarlo, una interpelación  categórica de… https://t.co/PztXK5FKLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[After devastating fire at historic New Orleans home, a look at place in Mardi Gras lore along St. Charles Ave.… https://t.co/iokVBeAn3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDolamore Thank you, I appreciate the endorsement! I will also likely begin doing journal citation mapping in the future.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 @friocarrieo If that dumb then as I have stated before she needs to be expelled from Congress]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsmaelIbarra2 Yessir! There might be a splash of lab in there tambien.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickyDavilaH Sería interesante saber el % de desempleo ocasionado como consecuencia de almendras regaladas por los… https://t.co/amYzqnXOOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubyRiottWWE will be Raw women's Champion in 2019 but Last night wasn't the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #StargateRewatch continues with Universe 10x10 “Justice” on the bright side, at least the character that died wa… https://t.co/EVWN1QpCNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mind blowing that we have to score more than 3 goals to win a game seriously]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timandsid @VividSeats That's ridiculous! I get it's a rivalry and all that has been going on since the beginning o… https://t.co/JVQkKGjiGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkelly can you pick up @JussieSmollett on the way to the jail. #SmollettHateHoax #Smollett #Chattanooga #Nooga]]></document><document><![CDATA[this Fig Newton sticker is dangerous and inconvenient, but I do love me some Fig Newtons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GHoungbo @IFAD @Quirinale @ItalyMFA @ItalyUN_Rome https://t.co/mP5NOkjSU5 explains how to solve world hunger witho… https://t.co/zykoHD3Oe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[8.  He gave that gift to every comic that came after him that night.  That’s why he was such a master at warming up… https://t.co/osInuP9KIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattinlincoln @JackMitchellLNK Yep. Open the purse strings and get a winner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylanmessina10 Na I don’t Stan for Russ but you do whatever twitter tells you to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourOldDroog Omfg I was talkin bout that shit within the week lol.  Channel 99 up in Delaware when I was younger.  Good times]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewsShuttle 100% Appreciate you sharing this for us. Means a lot.  Happy Monday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shade510 @frankart42 Nothing to hide, I am sure I am not a hero,I give that catagory to those who fought for us or… https://t.co/yjYcBM6fpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#College kids will be richer than their parents 10X $BTC.X $GBTC #Diamonds]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree but I don’t want to be like them. We need to follow our own code. The people see what is happening. Things… https://t.co/ejQXl3Dbws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkHarrisNYC As long as you're counting sign language as "spoken" Shape of Water should do better than most of those.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManagedByBlanco @ransom_jt He just don't know bout Killua! He knows not what he speaks]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if a platform has over $25 billion in revenue, but isn’t owned by anyone? @ewarren https://t.co/p1L8i9Nlnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andrew__3000 @the_bernie_bro @BethLynch2020 @peterjhasson @MeghanMcCain Underrated tweet. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber_Support is there a gift for a 500 ride milestone or at any point?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vialina @ercthms Haha i meant as in what they could pay him for this once thing. Staying with khole is generationa… https://t.co/NBklpcTpDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badmovieman It’s no Garbage Day that’s for sure, but here’s something for being awesome: https://t.co/8i25NdjLhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilkinssara @LaVelleNeal I read it. I understood it. Still chose to include Robby just for fun. Relax.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Data cant be considered its not as know as its presived unless there a contract of given shit like #Hollywood tryin… https://t.co/vO5YaPUMcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyyguido Damn, I gotta step my game up. @ModernLifeJon what does it take to get blocked? I thought the Color Me B… https://t.co/cCLuXAgXTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought I saw my ex while hiking Runyon and had a mini panic attack because that's the mental state I've been in lately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabrielkahane got the literal “Book” of Travelers today!!! Started with Little Love. Looking forward to working th… https://t.co/6JTTFS77Il]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDCVince Federal government program for paid family leave is another step toward socialism plus we can ill affor… https://t.co/lFsob5amPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevemorris__ @AOC What a moron, you can’t even add! $15x40=$600x52=$31,500  Go Notorious AOC Keep doing the right thing!!! BX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Okwonga @AndyMitten I don’t even know what to say, working at a Spanish bank in NYC with an entire office full of… https://t.co/iXIF0nAZI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You push until you can’t stop, you fight through the stomach pain and keep goin 😈💪🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though it feels like -30ºF, it's actually only -12ºF. #MorrisMNWeather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaVFrayer @MelindaHoward4 @LondonMarathon @nycmarathon @JavelinaJundred Oh that’s a far better anyway 🎉🎊 #hellyeah!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le tome estas fotos a mi novia y realmente me siento tan feliz y afortunado de poder estar con una mujer TAAAN PREC… https://t.co/6GSG8WWGm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#baltimore sights are actually #beautiful it's kinda sad that the people here suck so much #lile4like #like4likes… https://t.co/DC90B7nknb]]></document></documents></author>