<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[A photo of a West Virginia State trooper saluting a funeral procession is inspiring people all over the country.… https://t.co/tCoyHnKndU]]></document><document><![CDATA[‼️END’S TONIGHT AT 9:00PM EST‼️ Win a DELTA AIRLINES Gift Card, a LUGGAGE of choice, APPLE iPad, and FRENDS Headpho… https://t.co/6WBixTAGow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson Make  A Difference For Alexa And Zariah https://t.co/J4amWgrhtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted the challenge from @teachkjw to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations or reviews-just the… https://t.co/b3LYVHzx7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 I heard this on NPR this morning, pretty interesting. I was also just talking to a friend about how our… https://t.co/zFXQglYIAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scorpiomalissa fight that bitch. jk. Dont listen to my problematic ass lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to love what you are doing to do this job. These Children are beyond awesome! I am so proud of my Cadets!💙… https://t.co/2mkpsPE9Fh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katcat69 @RawStory Shipped straight to your door too: https://t.co/ms3GfuTXB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glow in the dark mini golf...definitely fun times!  #family #friends #niagarafalls @ Wizards' Golf https://t.co/FBBIMkRp2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[That nap you take after a good cry&gt;&gt;&gt; I’ve been doing that all day lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PACEOmaha @OPDdcGonzalez @OPDDCKanger @loltish Two of my brothers drive busses for OPS. I'll pass it on! @CubsFan4ever62]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check-out @PCInnoInstitute @PineCrestSch Sixth Annual Innovation Institute https://t.co/O9uHmXnp5Q #makered #STEM… https://t.co/1go1X4vf14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fellow Joker fans speak in such a way that others love to listen to you. Listen in such a way that others love to s… https://t.co/EipXKQ2i71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyc311 I have reported this to 911 multiple times and unfortunatelynothing has been done. Not so much as a ticket.… https://t.co/ZCv9pkHEOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes, you have to realize when people are holding you back, from being the best YOU that you can be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had I dream I was dating Ezra Cullen so here ya go https://t.co/jVPsWlwqbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be 24 in 2 weeks.... not like im counting but Incase anyone wanted to know 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Admiral Schofield for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/MmQlD9GWEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump Remember though, Manafort's paying for Mueller's investigative work and then some.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to #ISTE19 find me! https://t.co/4DGiv4Lmbd https://t.co/zAL7UsLOEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost jenineinf with get_repost ・・・ Please keep SHARING SOCRATES to HELP him get OUTTA this SHELTER and into  his… https://t.co/JPJ5s4JTJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VAVetBenefits @VeteransHealth my stepdad has been in a nursing home for 7 mo. discharging him bc he’s not “sick en… https://t.co/QW8GBwDh9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cafenetamerica Seriously??? Briliiance???  What did she accomplish pray tell???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me &amp; my French beau! @mjbuthion @ Banquet Cinema Pub https://t.co/YcLpKe5hVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a cleaning day at the apartment, getting ready for my parents to arrive Friday! Only 5 days left ♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinaMarkota Oh for GODS sake, Is there anything you people can take the blame for.. You are a result of the eve… https://t.co/J3iJ87MLPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like straight up S T U N T I N G on the steps. Chill everyone! It’s a museum]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the movie, I wonder what is the weakness of Captain Marvel. She seems like the counterpart of Superman who do… https://t.co/8l9oDabVL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ben_Faulstick @PokemonGOHubNet This one is from them to us... but they do have others you can use that don't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDailyShow @Trevornoah We are the heart We are the hands  We are the voice of spirit on earth All  who we are Al… https://t.co/N4DhNDLhfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can @chrislhayes be appointed to ask questions for the #CohenHearing?? He’s tweeter feed is speaking truth right now! #CohenDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students wrapped up today's lesson with a reflection of the purpose and application of the activity. https://t.co/rsMt8mWrz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Women Control the Money, Female Founders Get Funded https://t.co/MptB4q8ZRc Join The Texas Women’s Summit to h… https://t.co/VGWj3EV493]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact: two out of three of these books have made me who I am. I'll let you guess. Never mind, I don't want you g… https://t.co/mVXn8fsKHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcdonaldcomedy Yes pleeeeze. I will send you dates. And of course there’s coffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haleigh_twiggs @jayramirezzz @bassdragon @elisa__almanza I wanna meet new friends😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@People4Bernie We have toget people out to #Vote2020 Here's my inspiration, https://t.co/DJhLQDg5v1]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing experience at #AccessHollywood with @stellassocks. If you are interested in volunteering with us, r… https://t.co/8Uj3NncPEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacob_Watson21 @Nolan_Athletics @NolanCatholicBB @joeweik13 Yuhhh WATTYYY! CONGRATS BRO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going on my first trip with Dylan’s family this weekend 🤧🥰 I’m so excited and happy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man Accused Of Killing Daughter Dies In Hospital https://t.co/ftxrNkLcHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coopercordelia5 @RobbeeeRob @dawnstaley @GamecockWBB Wear your wristband and go to Suite 24]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fishing 🎣 king!!!!! It’s raining in Tennessee 100%. @LukeBryanOnline #LukeBryan https://t.co/iA3wR0REc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to convince my man to let me take this bearded dragon home but he’s not having it. But honestly $100 for a r… https://t.co/1SOnlsdcXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk if I’ll ever get over being mad at God for making some of the ones I loved most only temporary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[adding “period” to the end of whatever i just finished saying makes it 100x more truthful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long Live the Best Tv Show Ever - Znation!!  @Save_ZNation @SaveZnation]]></document><document><![CDATA[They should have thought about that before signing on with a traitor! Doesn't bother them when they are trying to k… https://t.co/cSScOSNC9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suziday123 @CaththeWineLady @Cbp8Cindy @SLBriscoe @FionaMorgan79 @Starofthesea007 @joneill55 @AkronWineGuru… https://t.co/m1D7SMmkHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rockin' out to music and enjoying 70 degree temps inside the blind, plus a perch and crappie bite! #icefishing… https://t.co/cuhPjez8IL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girls got the dub and a special shoutout to my superstar @AlleeJade for pitching so well that game, shut them do… https://t.co/GOLVHItSp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTonyVM @WaltDisneyWorld Thank you so, so much! Miss you too, Tony 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski Chunky  peanut butter is the only way.  Smooth looks like baby food.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @RickLapi for the challenge to post covers of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews. I’ll challen… https://t.co/gdgOs92Nz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A friend gave me her extra 3 day pass for Pitchfork last year, and I had already had a bought a Sunday pass. So I g… https://t.co/UuefJVX3PH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spectacular #SamsungEvent Show. Congratulations @SamsungUS https://t.co/CW11g1CGjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasRhett @nbcsnl He played with The Great Dierks Bentley Friday night at Bridgestone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday Timing!   This little light of mine, I’m gonna let it shine 💃🏻💃🏻💃🏻 #ProjectEnergyYouWantBack… https://t.co/4DaQymVSp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[1) Spicy Nacho Doritos. Nacho cheese doesn't taste like anything.  2) Cheetos 3) BBQ Lays  4) Original Lays 5) Frit… https://t.co/euS7UTM9mn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMillionABC Now how long do we have to wait for season 2? Cause I don’t mind sitting here on my couch staring at m… https://t.co/pZ34cw1UoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2:46 am . Do I drink coffee ? Do I suffer ? So many choices to be made .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilacjenn @yashar @Kaepernick7 CAN I KNEEL TO PROTEST COP KILLIERS. TO SUPPORT  THE MEN IN BLUE WHO RISK THERE LIVES TO DO THERE JOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBuzzBrands worked with #MGMA to develop their marketing department into a more strategic and data-drive unit.… https://t.co/kbcAhIHLZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pierre_rochard @CryptoAtNight @MoooRestaurant Revisit Target market! I would’ve joined but thought I’d be out of t… https://t.co/vDmn3Xy8gH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up with a sinus migraine. Might as well go searching for medication and eat breakfest.😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a reminder to anyone who’s been sexually assaulted it’s never too late to come forward and it’s never your fau… https://t.co/wGuVrBjD1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Los domingos se lleva a la mamá al restaurante” I would do that but my mom goes to church then out to eat with her… https://t.co/rWLx9PYlOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday loveliness from my roomie!! Thank you Zoie Moser!!! #EvitaNationalTour ❤❤🤗 @ Harris Center/Three Stages at… https://t.co/vu04C6A8JQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a pretty emotional and inspiring day. Fox is back doing what he loves after a terrifying year off. I’ve b… https://t.co/D7vzPBwx97]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PFAS chemicals from firefighting foam (#AFFF) continue to leach into the groundwater and private wells of the comm… https://t.co/9oiPlJs8Pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds a bit like what might have happened during the Pine Barrons episode of The Sopranos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate this and think it’s the stupidest thing ever and I don’t even watch the show]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having*** (the result of lack of sleep and staring at a screen all day)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeslieHanlon @NHSLMA If you haven't read Cutting for Stone by Abraham Verghese, its not new, but one of my favorites]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsGwyneth No matter who it favors.....too big of a price and not right!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My interview with Oakland Mayor @LibbySchaaf about the Oakland Teachers Strike: #OUSD #OaklandTeachersStrike  https://t.co/XWvkcFoq8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@informor @phonedude_mln It would be a better experiment if it was done with tenured/grant-rich faculty. I’m really… https://t.co/nRLL9Ecgdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_sowers I don’t consider 40’s cold either, Chris. I hope the rest of the winter is mild with little snow. Won… https://t.co/nuu4TMfaAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't miss Whitney Cummings, featuring Benton Ray, at @comedyzoneclt!  Whitney Cummings is a comedian, writer, and… https://t.co/eG8D4LG1hS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like Kyler Murray is not... nah, I'm good. https://t.co/s1CPjPYK89 via @YouTube  Just because I love this so much 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darth_na By “free” I meant in the context of: you aren’t continuously dumping money into a platform. You are sendi… https://t.co/UfMBezXWeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot express my feelings for you, I know it is not something new, But, want to revive my love for you, Coz peop… https://t.co/OQKK60iLH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Detalles espaciales 💕 😊  . . . . . . . #drawing #doodles #illustration #ilustradoramexicana #watercolor… https://t.co/1ATvdNmmj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmharrity I wouldn't necessarily want to do an outdoor run, though. What time is that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[go @shoostis, it’s ya birthday 🥳  happy 22nd trip around the sun. thanks for being the best brother a bröther could… https://t.co/luxkjQJ7HM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread!! I want to paste it on all the billboards and scream it from all the rooftops. 🗣🗣🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arkantart @bunnyt1960 @GeneralCattis @LolaKittySLC @LordGraydon @MochaIvory @WalterWhiteRab1 @A_affirmations… https://t.co/koKzbGXH9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s hope Allison wants to be a teacher someday - what a kind heart! @pattanupdates]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whole Foods Adopts $15 Minimum Wage — Immediately Slashes Hours https://t.co/JFwapW7ORo via @BreitbartNews Everyone… https://t.co/fJU8RHe0Tx]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/CrH4Uwgg81 sent me an email about my #benzodiazepine #withdrawl. They say minimal side effects? Holy s… https://t.co/zv93uEBmd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always manage to start watching “This Is Us” right after getting my lash extensions done knowing CLEARLY every da… https://t.co/YV9Vs44De4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great turnout tonight for the @AlabamaArise @LWVBaldwinCo Baldwin County Legislative forum with Reps. Joe Faust,… https://t.co/RWheXMmMKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our phones ring super loud at work.  This is accurate representation of me each time they do. #scared #work https://t.co/Kx6ctoczgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showed my mom the Sucker video and after, she started screaming and giggling, completely roasting me🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clou18 @CassTThompson @TweetmeJordan @peruvianJKlover @kristyhart24 @jordanknight @phillygirl8800 @JKsBronxGirl… https://t.co/MfONkE6xe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_mastermom @JohnHookfox10 @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama and not one iota of proof of  Collusion imagine that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop It was a scary, embarrassing, and heartbreaking time for our country. We had to fight everyday to sa… https://t.co/zZwnzLFAEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to have friends that would always point out my flaws, things that made me so insecure, but hey when I see yo… https://t.co/jN0lYkHl47]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday angst purging with @googoodolls like it’s 1998 and it feels so good. https://t.co/1oZZBeob8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There is no democracy in any love relation: only mercy.” https://t.co/PCBAXSsrvd]]></document></documents></author>