<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@davidtabrown @Medic968 Agree...you cant be the most famous and richest sports franchise and contunually be outbid… https://t.co/L79P3fP6zy]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a great representation of how to approach #SEO. Be skeptical, be weary, but cover your bases]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article for a coach that doesn’t get enough praise. Proud to work alongside @SWCoachSButcher !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vaccines are typically only 85%-90% effective --herd immunity covers the remainder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No sean cabrones no las traten mal, que por uno la llevamos todos  #InformacionQueCura #DeNada]]></document><document><![CDATA[Based on airport ads, air travelers in America only care about two things: cyber security and cloud based technology solutions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grachyelaa Mire, posiblemente le digan que no, pero posiblemente le digan que si. En esa posibilidad uno se la jue… https://t.co/94IoXDtgSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoVolsXtra Doesn’t matter any more. They’ll be lucky to win one of the remaining games. They are capable of winning but I don’t see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theodorelasso @K_m_Mitchell @TheHondaClassic Nice, personable, humble kid. All the #HondaClassic champs are my guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got home last night and fell fast asleep for three hours despite setting an alarm.   I wasn’t bound to be woken up by anything before 10:30.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nunyabiznasbro @RepDanCrenshaw 85,000 dead from guns in 2018 that's an actual crisis.  75% of opioids come by mail… https://t.co/MABelYcOde]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyDCross Ohhhh. .. they're enabling racism, bigotry, xenophobia, how about them being silent on "Jews Will Not Replace Us"]]></document><document><![CDATA[What alternate universe do you live in? You are as we say in the country either stump dumb or full of shit. Which o… https://t.co/me6ppW2LTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click on link in my bio to hear FULL VERSION also hit me up for the maxi single of this song plus a bonus track is… https://t.co/9uN7vJ3NeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@binz21 @DarrenHeitner @ScottiePippen Absolutely....Harry Giles would have been #1 out of HS....bombed in CBB and w… https://t.co/UVcdii7MDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsianOptionGirl @CEtoruom @realDonaldTrump FYI, vegetation on day 3(genesis 1:11-13).  Your bible, can’t spin it t… https://t.co/yYhevyHo9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tryna be ina relationship with two fine gay girls so when people ask who’s the man in the relationship I can say me proudly 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dizwire @KatAtDisney Also you might want to look into a cedar Fair annual pass that way you can hit up knotts when… https://t.co/DPbMU33L37]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm just saying!!!🎯💯💪🏿✊🏿👏🏿🤣🤣😂😂😂😂 #TearsFloweth #DailyLaugh #LMFAO #Funny #Comedy #Hilarious #Jokes #Flatlined #LOL… https://t.co/nk3APNhmeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[DANCE ON THIS LYFT TRADE!!!#usa #america #texas #houstonrodeo #houston #austin #dallas #sanfrancisco #sanantonio… https://t.co/U5hSj9cMAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AlitaMarch8th weekend starts my fellow hunter-warriors, let’s do this.  Our mission is to #SecureTheSequel so we c… https://t.co/Ijj9g6TWva]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be waiting for that special message informing me that I’m the lucky person that will receive this beautiful… https://t.co/vSczvao2Re]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC times are changing, bud. My generation (Millennials) is sick and tired of unrestricted capitalism. The term… https://t.co/ManEH0yH9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmMylesTurner @Aazaar23 @Coach_Restivo @PatCilento @Bullisfootball Congrats lil brova]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I cannot stand either political party, always have to go extreme to reach the fringe people.  Just shut… https://t.co/wZrSFkjYH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[And a mob boss lets him settle his score by racing his nephew, completely disregarding the vehicular manslaughter that just happened]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NealMcCready Did they handcuff him after that dunk? Because that was a filthy criminal dunk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chale Camarillo ya tiene jainita y el Roberto no sale ni en rifa el hijo de su madre. La vida te da sorpresas, sorpresas te da la vida.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NianticHelp i don't know what happened?? I got my 5 stones from team leader battles,  but i did not recieve any from pvp... why??]]></document><document><![CDATA[White ppl have the nicest eyes dawg. These niggas eyes be like " light hazel- green" some shit crayola never even c… https://t.co/NTLN5ylPUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjcheesecake Remember to jab and then go with the uppercut!! They won’t except that! 🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me a purist but I'm a little unsure of the opener tactic, but could see it happen in the starts that  Domingo… https://t.co/Ib5Qr5J8z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @Elaine_Greek @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren… https://t.co/xWMXaGAAXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 I would climb it for $1 million and I would do it in a skirt just like she did. #Facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TammyJaben @LonePint @JonMontag @ManvsAle @RedStripeRocco @cedarflats @cellmavin @zappafaye @TheStraightHops… https://t.co/oazSzDKUln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterStuifzand @NASAGoddard This shit is fun on Facebook, but get off of my Twitter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isareher_ Mira ella quería vivir en un castillo.... https://t.co/vnS5atNkBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bruinfan0804 @ewalsh90 Sorry but Heinen next to Coyle n Backes or Chelarik ain't crap for Heinen.. I really think… https://t.co/z9OYyq9jqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kkondik Canvassed there Sunday  Nobody mentioned Richmond, nobody mentioned the Middle East.  The voters in Herndo… https://t.co/9pzZDhmWyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just what do you think those differences are, apart from giving birth and providing nutrition in the first coup… https://t.co/UBdXsIFDtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dgkretz103 I’ve felt the same way for a while now. I feel nostalgic about the things that I got to be a part of an… https://t.co/nKkAye6AN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coincidentally this post is exactly one year old. https://t.co/6Gwm3Zhbj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunrisemvmt @SenFeinstein Think these kids are preaching to the wrong choir. Seriously this is a hatchet job on a… https://t.co/6QVFs3D7sl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachSheets3 something special has been brewing here in Pittsburgh! @rockycap9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaaaaaytoven @CristTucker Y’all see the amount of money in this shit it’s crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amor a donde quieres ir el 14 de feb .. “Al partido de hockey” ... ok #happyvalentinesday en Staples Center https://t.co/fWyl0846j6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My class got extended so work told me to stay home and honestly I'd rather go to work than be alone lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riotwomennn During their last phone call, Trump told Putin that he needed some reliable help (he doesn't trust any of his own people).]]></document><document><![CDATA[A set of four matched JJ 6CA7 power tubes arrived in the mail last night, to replace the mismatched ones currently… https://t.co/AHZcFc2qvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free standup comedy show tonight at Stafford’s Public House.  #standupcomedy #savannah #comedy #savannahgeorgia… https://t.co/Y4geqZE1qu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColeCuster good luck this year Kiddo. @StewartHaasRcng , Championship year .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jk67Joan Not surprising as Orange Country has always been Republican stronghold in California. It’s a predominatel… https://t.co/nRmKD6vo6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerrettKucera @argusmattz @dklattusd The bias is because SDSU has actually had success 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaceyBacaABC7 @MarkMcGinniswx beautiful color this am....have a great weekend #abc7chicago https://t.co/UHHvtlIsC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoundTown10 @DetroitRedWings Yea, hockey town...and that’s not changing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just something else to throw on the pile of reasons to bring @9Artemi to the #ChicagoBlackhawks. You can’t buy that… https://t.co/2KHPZwN4hN]]></document><document><![CDATA[So let's get this straight on #IWD2019 Sheila Copps went on Twitter to attack another woman who wouldn't protect th… https://t.co/HrpU1a0TES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wildcatnews Criteria?   If being blown out early weighs heavily - I agree he doesn’t deserve consideration.   Any… https://t.co/NFitm3mFg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gordonkeith @junior_miller @GeorgeDunham  I also think it took Robson so long to come out was he thought he had a… https://t.co/rUgaJraENr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LydiaKnoxWX @PhotogLanders @WXAuthority_CNY Welcome Lydia! This is were the action is!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steel_Curtain4 The man just can’t stop. 🤦🏼‍♂️🤦🏼‍♂️ https://t.co/p1YNKzEUl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Robert Cooke Cooperative Homes in Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/VEE7bUiBet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnitdaLily today's discoveries while at work/gym https://t.co/5Ct3iLgwEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m heading to the Design Conference. #becomeanarchitect #soyoywanttobeanarchitect #pachanza #architecture… https://t.co/B4zfoHoqYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[DHS $ bill gives incentives for underaged human trafficking. Pg. 24. @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samsung acting like this new folding phone does Ultrasound has Theranos written all over it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbmccoll One of the many great things about DPC! In-office dispensing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[During my job search I subbed K-12 for over 2 months, this article is spot on:  “The responsibility of a teacher ex… https://t.co/T4oF5z5FYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defeated Captain TJ 29-25 with a cooked shrimp 🦐 🍤 strategy. Fantastic solo variant!! https://t.co/eOlQyw4Onf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moddedLimes Also note that in the SpaceX shot we can’t see what’s on the screens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twisttay Check out https://t.co/AnvdAqxjng they import anything you can think of and a well trusted place]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeafsMaz20 @dallassmith @MapleLeafs @Canucks You should probably update your profile pic.  Don’t worry about it du… https://t.co/5atL2StvLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[New #PowerRangers #BeastMorphers footage! @Ranger_Liz https://t.co/1NhT7igbMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GqNyc1 @DubbyGoodell @LosFreaklander I'm glad they happened it builds character]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clemson has won the best 2-of-3 rivalry series with USC the past four seasons, the past three years losing the open… https://t.co/QuzvqCoIW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ended the night with some soccer 😁👊 . . . . ❌ignore these❌ #sunsetdistrict #futbol #exercise #SFlife #sffitness… https://t.co/2ecofEBxNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samjshah Hang in there buddy. I’m right there with you. Here’s a cup of Joe for you. https://t.co/ASIg9z2QKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brittbritt1219 @Disturbed @threedaysgrace @933WMMR Then you paid $19.99 too much]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSU has made a couple of tough shots but majority are on layups. Putbacks and steals. Making PSU make jump shots. Dare them to shoot it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirsten_gaps02 @itsbrandibitcch You’re more than cute. You’re Beautiful ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[L train project comprises tunnel rehab, infrastructure and station upgrades (incl electrical capacity), and station improvements.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bottom line is if someone likes you, they’ll show it. They’ll put in the effort, no matter what the circumstances are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These ppl up here blow their horns for no reason 😂😂😂 gahleee just go around]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dierks Bentley - Somewhere On A Beach (Official Music Video) https://t.co/o7bMOR08Pi via @YouTube I burned up three… https://t.co/LerXwNdUwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[At, yo, @JoeSib! Hook your boy up here in 203/4/6! Would love to see the guys up close!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zerohedge @rightwingertoo Ridiculous, waste of paper and effort...where were these “constitutionalist” the 13 Time… https://t.co/cr7lL43M8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought we already knew all this from @normmacdonald https://t.co/y1fSC5omyk #LeavingNeverland]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great analysis.  Happily the latest bad decision was, in fact, reversed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! How many minutes was that forecast? Nonstop soliloquy @DylanDreyerNBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MVPWabet @Pontifex ...editorial communications coming out of the Holy See. Don't for a moment tell me that… https://t.co/nACFKAD6VV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnySchatz @WorldofOutlaws Current situation in Fargo. 👀❄ https://t.co/3d3ipx1Xen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1CourtneyGannon Courtney I’m not flexing I’m budgeting and mathing things out I’m trying]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and here is the resulting pulled beef from the roast I shared yesterday.  I'm thinking about doing this again, o… https://t.co/pUHo41P488]]></document><document><![CDATA[One anti-American liberal should never have been allowed to infiltrate our Congress and the other anti-American cra… https://t.co/544Ihx1UnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if cable willl ever have a Chess channel ?  #DeepThoughtsFromNerds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elise_Jordan you are so right about DT being an absolute bully!! And @SpeakerPelosi punched the bully in the mouth… https://t.co/HNTRp6I7pD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yaleHFdoc @matthewherper Right or he could have just felt that his heart was racing which was actually what happen… https://t.co/GLNWfGnXeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! @geraldw2_  and I agree with this! @_KyairaF just doesn’t make it right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaZeca @whodatgirla @nohumansplz @larenard @sentinelisland @jade3457 @BigNasty_75 @Complex In all fairness look… https://t.co/iyhAn6z5ei]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of Regulation Jackson Lumen Christi - 2 Forest Hills Central - 2 @MichHSHockey @fhcsportsreport @FOX17Blitz #MHSAAVIH]]></document></documents></author>