<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 22 Schooner Landing Road #Smithville #NJ  #realestate https://t.co/hGTRJ5wMow]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a life... shopping for new “coats” (harnesses) #pennylane #captainjack #pupperadventures #petsmart @ PetSmart https://t.co/248Y7x72Cq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckftz @steph93065 @beequeen28 @JeanetteBruce18 @mikvance @NaeHelen @AOC How soon it’s forgotten]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup!!! 👏 The @jonasbrothers are back! ♥️♥️♥️  #JonasBrothers https://t.co/p9djprjOVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baaaabeeeee these Lightenin' Lemon Pepper and Garlic Parmesan Wings from worldofwingsep are DA TRUTH!!!🤤🤤🤤🙌🏾💯🆗️🔥🔥🔥… https://t.co/EMC67EMGhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you SHIRISH JOSHI @SHIRISH65149661  for retweeting my poem and Brian's artwork! Happy day friend!~💜💜💜😘 https://t.co/ObQBFu1FYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJellyman @almostablaze @CasaskullMark @ml2370 @HomonLang @ccsunflwer @LinemansLadyLuv @scottydog57 @ethan1655… https://t.co/yVRCmSajQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh look! That’s a really nice car right there!! ♥️🚘 @ Vero Beach, Florida https://t.co/7FOgvdWryn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samsmith @BBCOne @netflix All these lyrics are so Sam's soul-  i was out when i heard it but new immediately I hea… https://t.co/wI1hgcuyL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vegan_Jennifer @Veganmathbeagle Is that equally relevant to everyone’s life? I mean neither is algebra, I get it.… https://t.co/IMq11TV8c0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Mountain of Plastic Has Been Burning for Three Straight Months in South Korea https://t.co/PHnQ3MTSan #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look a tiny house built by high school students with elementary and middle school collaboration from a wonderful ST… https://t.co/YNFmhphufS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arrivals in Austin! #SXSW2019 #SXSWEDU #sxswedu2019 https://t.co/VH4LTnavUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexTheodorid1s @yelnats_eel @hotdog6969 Tell him Alex what he’s asking to see 👀😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Geeking out! Met Author/Teacher Kelly Gallagher today! @KellyGToGo https://t.co/sZ6ZnAPUBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Go figure!!! They threatened his wife with 30 years, he said and did whatever they wanted him to!! Fucking stupid people!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made it to the gym for 6 am. Winter is not going to stop me from feeling great. #CrossFit #fabover40 #power]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only person to appreciate me today and got me some paints. Was my fucking manager. 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[A visitor in my waiting area pulled the emergency cord in the bathroom the other day and set the alarm off. He thou… https://t.co/jDhjnsD9DQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're joined by @CCsCoffeehouse on the shows this morning! Get a taste of #MardiGras to start your week off on… https://t.co/Bgc6cgQo8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this week I got asked to go on three different dates and didn’t go on any.... I’m afraid to start dating again😅… https://t.co/oriJO0cwyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacticalDogLive @LivePDNation @OfficialLivePD So sorry for your loss. God bless you.  RIP Ricky thank you for your service💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s breakfast so far:  •coffee with Keto creamer  •kombucha  •popcorn  ...my body is so confused]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ciaraioch My whole life my mixed Irish heritage hasn’t been a problem-it’s been treated as something beautiful and… https://t.co/lQIY8WROPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning, have yourself a fabulous day!  #GoodMorningAmerica #GoodMorningAmerica #GoodMorningTwitterland… https://t.co/wQCYM6mLwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2: I have been challenged by @dulcez to post the covers of my 7 favorite books, no reviews or explanations. Tod… https://t.co/NVSgFcp54l]]></document><document><![CDATA[People do remember that Wonder Woman recently came out right? I’m legit not getting why people are acting as if Cap… https://t.co/gr4IpU44aV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherHanksDC @sarahkendzior I'm pretty sure not when they're in prison or a mental institution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re making @ChristinaTosi / @milkbarstore White Album cupcakes while listening to the Beatles’ White Album becaus… https://t.co/F35tyUyPvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judy and Mike had a fabulous time last night representing Amber Falls Winery at Tennessee Flavors!  @amberfallswine… https://t.co/68ZvDvfX3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this video about the science behind Zeal! (Click here 👇🏻) https://t.co/jILzZybQj4]]  #zealforlife… https://t.co/oWtFSLHNWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jayjaysbeauty i just wanted to say thank you so much for your videos on law of attraction. I manifested a beautifu… https://t.co/lEgOyOuKx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janbroberg It doesn't matter what any of us think in the end we didn't live it. You guys lived it. If you forgave… https://t.co/gY39WkNyzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. Believe me there is NO text that is worth risking your life or the lives of others. 📵 #donttextanddrive]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my brother ate one of two pop tarts and put the other pop tart in the fridge... that’s unnatural right? Or did I… https://t.co/f9qkuTYdVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[me literally yesterday: I’m gonna start posting on social media on Prime Hours™️ 😌 me now: Hahahhahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeremy really just said “go listen to some drake maddy, you’ll be fine. I recommend so far gone” lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LobosJimmy @itsnotRICO Damn ricz you goin have some competition up heaaaaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been reminiscing a little more than normal lately because my timehop has been filled with wedding planning. Can't b… https://t.co/JQeggKn2MO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skelechiwatson you rocked this amazing episode tonight👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼 #ThisIsUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[my roses are doing well . please respect their privacy in this crucial period of time. more updates later]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hddaddy90 It’s him.. I think he got a new crew chief tho. Maybe he took lessons from KYBU. LOLOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottMLibrary @IngrahamAngle @senatemajldr @RandPaul Scott stupid ? Learn to read statistics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CindyCardenasG @Timbiriche_35 Eso estaría increíble!! Soñemos juntas que si se puede lograr!!]]></document><document><![CDATA['Geek philanthropy' raises more and more funds for charities. Charity streaming is the new telethon ... #mppdigital… https://t.co/gn97ZYoDtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GingerDoll3 I haven’t had huge problems with my photos but I wonder if you could resubmit the same photos just cro… https://t.co/dTvh33AEOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patharveynews @AmberLeeNews @5 @CBSLA We are gonn freeze our patooties off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jd_chrissie maybe cuz he was never in the right place at the right time.. but now that he’s with the right person,… https://t.co/Iqcf1bhWxT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianklaas C’mon Trump hangs out w/Kraft’s madam and human trafficker. Water finds its own level. He shits on the… https://t.co/2vcxTWlyJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#islesofcollierpreserve #noretouch  #realestateinnaples #newlisting #openhousenaples #OpenHouse coldwellbankernaple… https://t.co/rXMoM7Xohr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jane_groosny @NYClara @NYCMayor @NYCMayorsOffice @NYCSchools Premature? It was a Winter Wonderland by 9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@njc2o Yeah well Bohemian Rhapsody is a terrible film directed by a rapey pedophile and it won the most awards I th… https://t.co/Leg6PCPNnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@my3monkees @Lexa_Merica @Derameth @SealeyGerald @Troy0811USMC @jonz970 @kbsman2 @skb_sara @pjbowles4 @T_FLgal… https://t.co/2j3ieBrk1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[TJ: “What did you order?”  Austin: “Knob Creek”  TJ: “What is that?”  Austin: “A goooood good bourbon”   TJ: “It so… https://t.co/wHe5gVgawd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Womens Day Hope everyone enjoys their day 👩👵👰👼💅❤💫💄👠👙 https://t.co/0SwlqgHvnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early mornings are the worst. Everything I tried to forget from the previous day comes rushing back to me and I rel… https://t.co/j60G28qgOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottyMcCreery this Carolina Girl got married to “This is It” in the big city of Ayden, NC on NYE. Celebrating my… https://t.co/1QxztAqMGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great guest blog today from portrait photographer @aundrelarrow, who asks "...what happens when that lack of access… https://t.co/tzmSGz8UUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much fun last night! Great #NHLDucks game, and we got to be the Season Ticket Holder of the game! Thanks for the… https://t.co/ygvnZJRsRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep on Nancy, you are going to need your roots done soon. And a little Botox.  But then again your tight face lift… https://t.co/1BaSdxsd4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy cannot and will not get enough votes to win .i am sure all the magas love him much, as all he will do is g… https://t.co/HbB3P0lY0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dattman25 @JohnSmi42284115 @greta Just stop.  You are a condescending jerk.  Take your advice from your feed.  Or… https://t.co/6GHpDj3TPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@localnatives Past lives, Villainy,  Heavy Feet, Mt Washington, Breakers,  black balloons,  who knows who cares, su… https://t.co/gX7MTzpTEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakotaDistrict @LakotaEndeavor @JimDayShow @amandaorlando Oh! There’s my babies and the box of tissues! Thank you so very much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My body has completely forgotten how to do a layout. Or my back handspring is still messed up. Either way, yes, the… https://t.co/I0rOdb7tPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[En que época pico lo que voy a superar??? Y seguir con mi vida normalmente 😕😕😕😕😕😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zoos celebrate Valentine's Day with a playful pun-off 💗 🐢  https://t.co/DikQjxAxvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to ball out today #10....You played the best game in setting and crazy defense against club Steele that I can’t… https://t.co/Yv1VVHQxol]]></document><document><![CDATA[And for those arguing in my mentions, this review from @odienator sums up what I think of GREEN BOOK https://t.co/ULVaC4WlRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a guy calling to report all the places in Ottawa where the sidewalk hasn't been cleared and it makes me wis… https://t.co/PZmEImntCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 might be the weirdest year of my life, and we are only 7 weeks in. Guess I better buckle up for the rest of the year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to my favorite Coach @ColumbiaBb 😍 Proud to be your wife and serve our girls alongside of you! https://t.co/ajP6uWxA7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelsCumber @ElenneMigo @yellowbelle @DestiniLozano @Lanasanette @LucyGee4 @marykk196051 @JilldarWu… https://t.co/jrw0jBGjG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly my dad watches my favorite YouTuber so we can have stuff to talk about @emilynels8  😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This child has so many toys but all he wants is the Olive Garden gift card. The boy knows what he wants 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[International margarita day 🧡 @ Grand Beach Hotel https://t.co/QbSoL37iJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making them stay with me today. Spent most of the week parked in Starbucks deep in revisions to new book. But I hit… https://t.co/Vj3ACQbsw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbara_lopez21 @miss__grumpy__ asi estamos todas, ustedes entienden todo lo que esta pasando con sus personajes ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisPopeWrites Yes she was lovely! Her husband gave me all her Paris originals as her daughter is much taller tha… https://t.co/LsLxoJhEkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DelSchilling Prayers for your healing. Blessings to you and your family 🙏 🦅 💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump calling Tim Cook, Tim Apple... wonder what he’d call @richardbranson 😂🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT I wouldn't vote for you if you were the last person on earth you and any other corrupted and derange… https://t.co/zdoCqxDYGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can personally attest to the quality of the vodka... and the gin.. and pretty much anything from @LakesDistillery… https://t.co/TeUMgLHkqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsfrancineally Lucky you! Enjoy! 😂 As for me and my 27 years: https://t.co/sj8sJ0z3fU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Main Street Parade🎉🎉#disneyworld @ Walt Disney's Magic Kingdom https://t.co/XqLHLj7hhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missfaugh @joannavrteaches @NYSCATE @MarissaMcNamara @Tech_TeresaM @RichardColosi @ncties @JeriB_EdTech… https://t.co/IcF88xMWjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[A friend gave me this beautiful vintage frame and I designed this one of a kind wreath out of it.  #brissonte… https://t.co/mjoroxVCzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiteshK68745466 @realDonaldTrump You are an uneducated idiot. You will feel really stupid when he gets thrown in j… https://t.co/E74tWlEU1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[The trouble with Matt that is he’s only apologizing after he got a lot of backlash from his statement. He was overh… https://t.co/jfW9El5x9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will be a game changer! Omg wish we had this like three years ago @30AMoney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DISupdates @NASCAR As @AllWaltrip would say "cautions breed cautions" #Daytona500]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weirdobutokay @bdbilotta @emrazz Speak for yourself, not for the rest of us. I don't know a single woman who lives… https://t.co/f7Glrx2ktp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey... @RainbowSquidInk...  IM GONNA WRECK IT!!!  (Found out they had both "nominee" and "winner" tags made that th… https://t.co/71hNt436oW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to Milo!  Hard to believe on February 25th he entered the double digit zone! Holding on to the fact… https://t.co/8AKxhYZV3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyBettonJrTV Drive safely son! 🙌🏽🙌🏽🙌🏽🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾‼️❤️❤️❤️ Have fun!  Learn more!!  Network!!  Because that’s what you do!! 👍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zenyanna As an atheist would love a religious family member, you must love my decision to squatch]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s gonna be so hard for me to keep my second job if I don’t get a car soon. The amount of traveling I have to do… https://t.co/CMhuHKmgwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bo_Fo_Show Brooooo. Ya can’t get anything like this in Belton/Temple either hahaha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just win baby 8 in a row @HoustonRockets beat the @dallasmavs yes sir #RunAsOne #NBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeccaCalifornia Wonder if he went to visit the new Temple in Rome on the way to England?]]></document></documents></author>