<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The evolution and redemption of “El Presidente” - La Vida Baseball https://t.co/e5tpJu7g2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mario Villaplana crossed 10K. Time 01:04:45, pace 10:16 min/mile, est. finish 11:39 am https://t.co/QSGIldMuD2 #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrkLvly1 @NBCS49ers @NFL And there’s nothing wrong with standing for something you believe in the mistake that was… https://t.co/oRmtp9Rw0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @Diamond  @nikki_capone @AlexaTomasX @ArianaMariexxx @Romi_Rain @TuckerStevens4u @TeannaTrump… https://t.co/jda7IE2lhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almond butter on pita bread and then sprinkle some cinnamon on it #yourewelcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe Wali Xavier Faulk Jr. this morning lol smh this is beyond me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALGThunder Women’s Basketball will be heading to Kingston Wednesday morning to compete in @TheOCAA Championship. O… https://t.co/YiSx8ouH0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@varepall @BreitbartNews QUESTION: How many blacks do not know that the Democrats were the party of slavery, the KK… https://t.co/XheaIV21kJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I owed this to Geoffrey. I wish I had taken more shots, but I didn’t want to be remiss on my caddy duties. BTW, the… https://t.co/LhVcNIx6ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Until I get full sentencing from the judge and everything, man idk this Melly situation so weird bruh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldMarine1 After what AOC said about America being garbage I thought that would be her hat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Because they know you are a liar they will fall with you and they know that they may Ope… https://t.co/IJ2jNlYfYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need @IMDb’s “Known For” section to peek into my brain and tell me why *I* specifically know them. Was it one ran… https://t.co/Ag7W2s6Kk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It all started when they put on the White gowns and hats probably have some still in closets, because they still th… https://t.co/XFtH0n4bJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The @mets are on the field” is perhaps the finest thing one can hear at the end of a long winter. And the first pi… https://t.co/fiOQAmvlM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawnemerriman @AB84 Maybe @SageRosenfels18 would've felt the same if he went to Buffalo 😉 #32outof32IGuess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnHoodNC One might add/remind folks of Pres Obama’s Justice Dept pre-clearing the maps. Lest we forget. Kinda ha… https://t.co/qoM8NtXJr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wrayzors @JonMontag @madsen414 @JohanBBT @badhopper @zappafaye @cellmavin @lhtetrick @craftbeerjoe @qblacklock… https://t.co/koJFpoN4FE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember everyone, a library card is free, but knowledge is priceless. Well, unless you go to college; then knowled… https://t.co/b4ATtl5Yt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[MOST PEOPLE WANT SUCCESS WITHOUT SACRIFICE, BUT LIFE DOESNT WORK THAT WAY. SUCCESS WILL NOT BE SHORTCHANGED. YOU HA… https://t.co/DfA7O9WHA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaceMullen Oh yea our major traumas won't get to a traa center for 130 minutes, easy. Transport to a critical acce… https://t.co/KmPHnKL614]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricIdle @ItsMeCathi @BanjoHfuhruhur Lol id nominate him for. That prize]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThirdWardScribe Sike. He better as a heel. I honeslty thought miz was gonna turn heel just now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blackvoices @X1023FM @UrbanLeague @BlacKkKlansman @RepHastingsFL I agree with this Verdict however ic the Black Co… https://t.co/a8yZSFYI60]]></document><document><![CDATA[5215 W 9th St 5215 W 9th St, Los Angeles, CA 90036 https://t.co/2poklBfgGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Linda_A_Bailey I hope so. Some... but too many of them have image/resonance issues. JFJ might be a good example. M… https://t.co/AbwInbIqNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i have you on snap then don’t act surprised at my story. i knew you were gonna see it and i posted it anyway. be… https://t.co/AVoPcdwupH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mathewlenning @Michael30271076 @RyanAFournier @DineshDSouza That’s not what the President said]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of our Pieper Ranch MS band at @uiltexas competition in Seguin. 🎶🎷🎺🥁🥇🎼 Both 7 and 8 brought home sweepstak… https://t.co/E7Ljc2ULCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[from lights above shar_zayn • 📸 @AnthDigiMedia #miami #miamibeach #night #lowlight #miamiphotographer… https://t.co/2oJeQtXpvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen I'm going to go out on a limb here and say you hate President Trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all have two lives... the second one starts when we realize we only have one... matt_schunke ... Realize time… https://t.co/MuBMAdZuF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaLizaKozma Actually it was building on that course... It was called Cultural Fluency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG OMG OMG @expresscheer SENIOR RESTRICTED 5 Exotic just did that! SQUAD WENT SO HARD AND HIT AGAIN 🌴💜😭🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jackie19021587 @doctorsensation Almost every person working in medicine would never venture a claim against vaccin… https://t.co/reUjiORCKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Missinfo @WESTSIDEGUNN Looks like your rappin' in a dentist chair!, is that rag 4 the drool??🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomasquigleyRE @JimCarrey Trump is stupid for building the wall. Trump caused  the Government to shut down for 35… https://t.co/XpVbE7pW8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[people whose name starts with j are just better sorry i don’t make the rules]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger Wow that is just a lie.  We know you made illegal payments to Stormy Daniels for whi… https://t.co/JJWHWgVcjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thinks it’s cheesy to complain and tag companies on twitter but I’ll give it a go since @GetSpectrum cut off my i… https://t.co/epYPS3QhfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[*internal screaming because I’m 99.9% sure that we’ll all be let down tomorrow* #Darvey #Suits]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheryl Coker homicide case: Texas EquuSearch to assist Riverside police https://t.co/Mipfe9IOXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[A couple more gratuitous snow day pics for your timeline. @ Point Shirley https://t.co/egMDvZyqco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited about going to see Hamilton today. Matinee in Tampa. Read the book, and listened to Soundtrack in preparati… https://t.co/Fb0NrqsPXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly if I reply to you I must wanna talk to you because I stay leaving people on read]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickASAVet You are an idiot. The link U provided said she admitted making the rape charges up. That means they wer… https://t.co/Hnvf81Yj6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clovis1931 @edncaroline @John_R_Berna @clever_patriot @GarBear4Trump @RightWingLawMan @Serremmy @NYCREMilton… https://t.co/kz5trSD5jg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmail this new look on the android gmail app is garbage. I figured the updates were security patches and instead I… https://t.co/ispW6qDqAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/TZw70V6JjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrepHoopsSC @Tyrone_Calloway @AlmightyBoyd @BoysRwa @NickChaisson1 @millhillscrub @Chsaintsath @GilmoreZyan… https://t.co/snPhZnQE61]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, confirming my suspicion. Any ancestral US slaves in family trees?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jojosautepgh Hertl has 8 points in 11 career GP vs. Pens going to third period (all goals). That’s 0.72 points/GP.… https://t.co/3tZy0y6DtY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacob_islive Lmfao dude if I get down to 140 I would disappear! I’m at 150 right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Birmingham covering the @aafiron and @aafcommanders game today! #ForgeOn #TakeCommand https://t.co/gh2tdGsW5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sloan_davis People don’t know what the hell they want plain and simple. Just get pets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@george070757 @gonzalesposadal Te dejo la foto de la oposición que ayer antes del mitín se estaban alimentando muy… https://t.co/TC5yRxkGj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already 15 min late for this Hazmat class because of construction on the 895 tunnel in Baltimore. So of course https://t.co/M3XsbCguIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkYoungTruth @chuckwoolery Not sure the make a decoder ring that could make sense of this young lady🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tometrics That is correct. Given all that, I'm very happy with the season JPP produced and the small positive shif… https://t.co/xXprDMXVQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thiccthiccerson @hennyson526 Just show up in joe Johnson jerseys and get buckets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorrinaDittmer_ Corrina, I hope your track season is off to a good start! Wishing you all the best this season! Co… https://t.co/0FKYWucH2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HERC_N_AG @SkylerGreer @SuperK_TFB No, Facts Do Matter. Here some Bowl Facts the past Three Years. Ask #UGA or… https://t.co/SCW8TN6FlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ethanosten @elizabethraine @devinforparks @KevinLovesDonut It may have gotten him a few extra votes, no way to know for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How often do you evaluate the people that you spend the most time with in your life. A childhood relationship does… https://t.co/NSdyfR3tI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#vegan #mushroom #cheeseburger #bites #horderves #horsd'oeuvres #bkc #blackkingscateringspecials🍜🍲🍽🍷… https://t.co/oK2ZCPNqEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggeett37aaa Glen unfortunately, intellectual  Noam Chomsky delineated Eisenhower's crimes against humanity while i… https://t.co/MxKudeCCRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her name is GiGi #pomeranianlove #producerslife #doglover @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/N31kz1IBe1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my team - can’t wait to see them launch internship week for @OhioState ... the Monday launch can’t come soon e… https://t.co/okEgIIyfVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickAnderson Flush, that is the sound of sunny ways career going down the drain.  #cdnpoli #pnpcbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 No it’s like saying wouldyadidya Instead of would you, did you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just about to start at Christ Church Austin #TheHumanAdvantage https://t.co/0wRpkUGbmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Star Trek: Discovery "If Memory Serves" review https://t.co/FrXEr8LrvS #StarTrek #StarTrekDiscovery https://t.co/tofv5TFvYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@intheMatrixxx #QArmy if you watch part of this video look in the background behind the guy there's a painting on t… https://t.co/MYjoFqKVVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi, @RepSamGraves. If guns don’t kill people, but people kill people, why wouldn’t we want ALL people to have a bac… https://t.co/6kcVOjjE6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[#60days60verses  500 new followers this week #thankyou #iappreciateyou  On reverb nation 5 #longbeach  5… https://t.co/dtHXyaC7lN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maria_SOLE22 @SOLEFinancial @nicthurmond You know we’ll be restocking the #ShoutOut closet — Vega’s got the… https://t.co/fYX0ON4GDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FBF to yesterday when one of our little old men aged gracefully for the 💯th day of school celebration. The other n… https://t.co/Hqp1ZfrHwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Russellsports vs @wcladycomets with tip-off at 6:30 LIVE on @Mytowntvhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the kind words and fantastic visual. We’re in #Detroit so don’t hesitate to reach out on your fishing ex… https://t.co/uhkkqkb4FF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real life Ruby Red slippers... There’s no place like home... there’s no place like home... Just driving to leave my… https://t.co/NJJAR2443T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #PLN Happy Saturday morning from the #GoldenGateBridge in #SanFrancisco. Getting ready for the next #WeRunSFUSD… https://t.co/t5Mu15ESFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tac Training for camera work with @AFolchitto with #actionatl 📸🎥📽🎞📷 #mauricePKerry #mpk #actor #stuntperformer… https://t.co/lVqlB2V2BK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, y’all remember last week when I was on here begging for a good Ron Frenz-style Thor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very good - Drinking a Brew Free! or Die IPA by @21stAmendment @ Dubuisson Bar and Grill  — https://t.co/RmI7BGxktU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch If you believe that you're in bad shape ,hope you got the right insurance coverage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go CRLS   — one “Step” at a time ... ti pa ti pa 😏 @ Wellesley High School https://t.co/sP4X6yzbBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me carrying and babysitting Baby Addison today! Of course my mom was here as well to help lol. We have welcomed Add… https://t.co/GSCFm7at6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[why are we subsidizing college education anyway? All the do is rake the students, and their credit, over the coals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaldRoberts @ncte I do every year.  But with Google Doc now, I can see each student’s work history.  So the only t… https://t.co/h3Kh1T88xy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithWh77606934 @Softykjr @corryjoel That's actually his goal - owning a Sports Franchise. Given the local ownersh… https://t.co/1sW0Yxzam0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2018CyclonesXII "I kept waiting for the screen to update, but it never did!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will absolutely drop @AmericanExpress and switch to Apple when they launch this. The fact that most credit cards… https://t.co/IrZp9hF1F3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been playing for my fam and for #TeamMia. Results coming great. NATIONAL BOUND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @HowardSchultz This doesn't sound like Howard Schultz. This sounds like someone else wrote this for him. S… https://t.co/tXgG1LsRGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurenduca @cmclymer And in other news, pizza is good with extra cheese.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conservtomax @GovMikeHuckabee No❗️ WALK❗️Too much rubber &amp; steel in the production of bikes😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harness in the good energy, block out the bad. Harness. Energy. Block. Bad. ✌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight up im lonely asf i dont want to just fuck no more loll, im done with that, but i never catch any feelings,… https://t.co/eddkva02b9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xotonironixo @MimiC1019 Compared to the other same-sex couples we got on US soaps, they got more of a dramatic bui… https://t.co/EoQvsLoI4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hereditary spastic paraplegias are a heterogeneous group of pathologies and share clinical similarities with other… https://t.co/pfeKYMiVPh]]></document></documents></author>