<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[99 Pele incoming 👀 @NepentheZ @aa9skillz @Castro1021 https://t.co/9j7WpqDvBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VellyB17 Proud of you guys!@gmblackburn99. You boys are going to do great things! Y’all built a bond that will las… https://t.co/o2IRGh75u3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A mega-rant this long deserves to be retweeted. I even learned a thing or two about agriculture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@owillis ...I don't think they're making the point they want to with this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a nice start to the day! 4 more bacterial genomes being sequenced overnight in the Herman Lab… https://t.co/c4MXCR7JQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We need to foster inclusive development and put guard rails on gentrification and expand access to high opportunit… https://t.co/q50xxrZOY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat was kind enough to welcome me back with three dried piles of vomit.  This makes me worried about Origins and… https://t.co/PTM2CgPbPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reesewaters Like I always say. Karma is a natural, unadulterated, uncompromising b*tch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[africa: hello this is Afr–  whites: come on richard.. https://t.co/ed1xJLSIoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hks55 You know on the surface I agree with this. But we have to look deeper and perhaps understand that what they… https://t.co/dXGjeaVfLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1: reach the reacher, 2vs2’s well do tracking drills for covered OL with baskside hand on a moving bag at the LOS.… https://t.co/k3vOm7H8rw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoupFrancMLS Ce serait encore le meilleur,  cette année ! Bien dommage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueCurrie20 @wdunlap @realDonaldTrump The Clinton's corruption started in Arkansas years ago they both need to be locked up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please support my GoFundMe campaign: https://t.co/cjDE7h2ZSS @gofundme https://t.co/2MpEbbAh1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing how this game will drive you nuts! Thought Stylish Beachwhere was going to surge past, but Ron Cushing got… https://t.co/ZSnQ9mSL97]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to Tierney Aldredge and @denveragency for taking the journey with me to keep arts in education in the Los… https://t.co/2RH5bzT9Vc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJamesFordIV It’s a huge deal but bro I’m telling you these scum bags are crossing the border they are traffick… https://t.co/iKSapRsq0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wrestlecon I purchased separate tickets for Friday and Saturday. Can I still check-in one time or will I need check-in both days?]]></document><document><![CDATA[walking to teach tomorrow is going to be GRADE A awful. but I’m a be looking fly. https://t.co/HoFS7yrB3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BriannaWu Brianna educate yourself outside of your echo chamber or you'll always be ignorant and just a waste of another politician.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman @AOC Math is not your strong suit. How much do Amazon’s employees pay in taxes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okonjo-Iweala honoured as one of world's 8 powerful women by Transparency International: https://t.co/xgaO2i8YhD 🛑C… https://t.co/TQesgxmG39]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/VSPsF4IYoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianB_5 He went off that game, it’d be disrespectful to him not to use that picture hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a friendly reminder to set those old school clocks forward one hour tonight for the start of Daylight Saving T… https://t.co/2NYTIqQdnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[GREENSBORO, ARE YOU READY?!The See the Light Tour is coming to your city, this THURSDAY! This is NOT a tour you WAN… https://t.co/UuEMeyhwdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You must all be quick to listen, slow to speak, and slow to get angry. (James 1:19 MSG)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well who knew watching 200+ years of democracy crumble could be both entertaining and horrifying   Good thing the p… https://t.co/3iijJLWX8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chandra Wilson Opened Up About The “Grey’s Anatomy” Episode That Will Make TV History https://t.co/e71ZlINNqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Valentines Pizza Last Night 😉 #valentinepizza .#valentine #pizza #heartpizza #heart #pizza #pepperoni… https://t.co/A4n1G0mY4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jzulgad How about a $5 a game Season Ticket Package. Or even a 10 game pack like the Twins Do !!!’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Progressive sunset from my terrace overlooking Beverly Hills.  Not bad for a little Pennsylvanian farm boy who has… https://t.co/ICFyKRl9zr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@candi_smyles Both @ the same time👍🍌💦 fuk I'm horny &amp; u want Blondie👌😍👅💋🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby Trump for March 01, 2019 | https://t.co/eSMqRsQRgf https://t.co/d4cBPec9f5 via @GoComics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uncle Steve! . . . . . . #jasonmontoyaartist #instaartist #instaart #drawing #artoninstagram #handdrawn #artlife… https://t.co/ewmcaFoQ50]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottMichaux @TommyFleetwood1 This ones’s better!  (AP Sachs Photography) https://t.co/boovL3pwPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I’d enjoy Mandy as Champion 🤷🏽‍♂️ #SDLive but after Mania perhaps https://t.co/rh2wYMEoAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to turn the world against the U.S. I believe the word is treason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeierBrainLab @Dr_Koraly Maybe if you wear gloves and hold it at a distance there’s a discount?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched the trailer for the new Pokémon game coming to Switch and while not a lot was shown, it looks good.  I pred… https://t.co/MLw4CzJFbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vboykis Thanks for investing the time preparing the blog. It was enlightening. I was attracted to data science to… https://t.co/sCUsNj7aGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMAO quit playing like September October and November babies not the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The only true weapon of the labor union is a strike, and scab labor renders a strike useless. For employers who wa… https://t.co/cHxZk1BHpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djshort I can see that. My only question is if the Phillies can beat out the Mets for 2nd. I definitely see regression for Atlanta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/eoIHsaZCYm BREAKING NEWS ALERT 🚨: The Hinds County Corners Office has identified the male suspect as 3… https://t.co/6OM24VmDCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Episode 55 - Bitwise: A Life in Code with author David Auerbach  https://t.co/7zYRSsw9rX]]></document><document><![CDATA[BRIGHT MOMENTS.  Steve Turre's joyous and deeply moving celebration of the music of Rahsaan Roland Kirk at the PDX… https://t.co/bP9vMwwKfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fatcatsofinstagram #warm #Woodstove @ Manomet Office https://t.co/ETjq59dGup]]></document><document><![CDATA[This entire thread on the @USArmy’s new physical fitness test is dead on accurate. 🎯  Terrible attempt to revamp te… https://t.co/g9S42LWgqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freerepublican Why not 11-year-olds have rights in a liberal world can’t they sue their parents .should be able to… https://t.co/MC9e8uUkDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[😱 increíble cómo pasa el tiempo ✌🏻#MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/vvya9QxNQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to the ranchers in the farmers, when they tell you about how many prayer blankets have been found left stran… https://t.co/D3MPbgibRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylacash1234 But the nap will just send you back into those nightmares.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never forgotten 💪🏽💪🏽💪🏽🙏🏽🙏🏽 thanks seriousndpgfx for this piece #HeavyD My brother, Always inspired 🖤 . . . #rip… https://t.co/osGlch5hXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a 19 point loss to Mississippi State in the midweek game on the road, I’d estimate there are about 8k people… https://t.co/7ZaL0Cdywb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucidchart thanks for making a free version that works. I use the full version for work all the time but needed to… https://t.co/wVjogSIRZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobWestendorf I have no idea how people placed faith in Tonyan while acting at the same time like we need 2-3 ne… https://t.co/Xg1QIjddIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just 25 years later Canseco invents steroids and hits balls to the roof.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Turbo Tuesday again. Show your turbo goods! #996brotherhood #porscheturbo #996 #porsche996 @ Newtown, Connecti… https://t.co/T0EcNA3Qd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my #juniorachievement JA Titan students getting deep into the effects of #marketing and… https://t.co/urJxCRgdxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jurassic-sized pea-brain explains it all. Has never read the Constitution. Wouldn’t understand it if he did.… https://t.co/QHbSgJGXo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sixers head coach Brett Brown’s thoughts on Joel Embiid’s game against Al Horford and the #Celtics https://t.co/jHkC2sUFJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s time for Florida to make EVERYONE retake their license exams]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and you don't have to be a push over to be liked.....#structure #relationshipboundaries]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Heels!!!#unc #carolina #tarheels @ Chapel Hill, North Carolina https://t.co/3qdGd3E0Fi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beaugrants @frailroses @Kennedyeryn2 @CameronJung1 nah, you were being condescending. you knew the answer. you wer… https://t.co/XnoDOPVUvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kimchi udon and veggie tempura for dinner. Yum! https://t.co/yecxwsI9LW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mfs be talkin bout they mind on grown shit , wit no typa money 😂😂😂 gtfo y’all not on no grown shit stfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[With our 600+ billion dollar budget, this shouldn’t be much of a problem...  Handle it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Solmemes1 Actually you don’t want to be carrying. When our Lord Jesus Christ makes his return. That’s what they should be worried about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTE_Chat strengthening   our partnerships with local government and chamber of commerce has been our focus this #CTEmonth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Sayers Club at SLS Las Vegas https://t.co/dQZ79Sfpzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDrummondArtist @Kinowolf @bryanedwardhill @OnScreenHeroics Lol, I like them separate but a crossover would be coo… https://t.co/vbw1CliYgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at LorMet Community Federal Credit Union - @lormetcu in Amherst, OH https://t.co/5SpjGEw8oS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Simple Answer to a Simple Question. Cut off Federal funding or Prorate Federal funding until Californi… https://t.co/D44ZywJ5fP]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of these issues that people discuss have so many blind spots. Don’t speak on stuff until you exhaust all the… https://t.co/4hW6vxjqvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffP_70 @jemelehill @danpfeiffer He’s a moron and doesn’t know how to talk.  Borderlands doc shows women taking a… https://t.co/N2lkUILjpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coreyholman @WABADC See the “Proposed New Initiatives” from Mayor Bowser during the Vision Zero relaunch. So stay… https://t.co/r0Stc0ePb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lonnaluxe Wait till a nigga put some act right in me 🤣 I’m act like I don’t know no one 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever click on a handle and realize your blocked and you have absolutely no idea why? Like, what did I ever d… https://t.co/L7o6XqGCLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/xb07LEGnLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fortlauderdalefoodies #fortlauderdale en Fort Lauderdale, Florida https://t.co/h3oeOyPIpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaraLisette Many men feel lucky...and grateful...AND realize that the [current] salvation of MANkind will be attai… https://t.co/OwKAbE9qr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so drunk 4 hours ago that I couldn’t even play solitaire on my phone Bc staring at my phone made the room spi… https://t.co/DmFJ64OFdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianasWritings  What? A worldwide real estate corporation that pays no taxes and tolerates ubiquitous child molest… https://t.co/6maLsW2rB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un voraz #incendio destruyó los apartamentos de varias familias #hispanas en Gaithersburg, #Maryland y te compartim… https://t.co/km3VHvn0QV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emancipator - Goodness https://t.co/mvK8bG7Df3 via @YouTube  On repeat today. @emanc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your good news for the day! Justice is served!  👍🏼👍🏼.                        https://t.co/PMAaCpLuMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Technology 202: He used to mentor Mark Zuckerberg. Now he's helping Washington take on Big Tech.: A conversatio… https://t.co/TIf9ni0CgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#12miles #12mileday #marathontraining #twoweeksleft #icandothis @ LA Fitness https://t.co/KvHacmyy6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like the gods were looking out for me today cause it’s #NationalNapDay 🙌🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[nobody knows what I’m really going through. I just have to bite my tongue and stay strong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most successful people on the planet sing the same song when it comes to “comfort,” and that is, forget about i… https://t.co/1qZ0cZex6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qualifying with the armed security team tonight. Notice on the first target how I am shooting left of center. I hav… https://t.co/UCefhM4U5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sincere condolences to the families and friends of the Ethiopian Airlines flight's victims. My wife and I share… https://t.co/tfoYtctRq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrMichaelLee You ever been to an All Star game? @bosnianbeast27 no? Maybe cuz you average less than 30 minutes bec… https://t.co/UhngS4X7e8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phaniebly @tomcolicchio Dems will still find a way to complain when they lose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WallingBrent @ewuemma It’s crazy how many creeps slide into the dm’s nowadays. I had to deal with a couple that we… https://t.co/zSnKnJcx5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewDay @ForecasterEnten I wish you guys would start asking these Republicans that are so against these Trump inves… https://t.co/b4aU762cAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JedBlackwell The issue with Wofford would be seating, I am guessing. Seating only 3400, could be difficult. A plac… https://t.co/tJlkrh3B3t]]></document></documents></author>