<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Read about our latest job opening here: Supervisor-Nutrition Services - https://t.co/6Q4vDZx4Hg… https://t.co/cw41ZJo4B0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianDawkins I legitimately cried the day the Eagles traded BDawk to the Broncos. Some of us are rough around the… https://t.co/XoJdJYYpEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always have a lot to write on twitter, but then I change my mind. Saving it for my book...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The things some females have to do for attention baffles me. I could never.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katrina_wiser @CorkySwift2 Good Grief People..!! Are you buying Her BS..!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand you would be fired,  because you aren't making your "bosses, " happy.  I realize we are on opposite… https://t.co/dIUugGuyDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXCUSE ME @Applebees how could you POSSIBLY RETIRE CHEESEBURGER EGG ROLLS?? My life is ruined.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YEPBusiness @ChiefBordeleau @RubyTeuzday @MoeFraser @OttawaPolice Praying for her safe return.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PucciaPatrizia @enriqueiglesias @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @TereOrt51687394 @ElbaklySami @janaplauen… https://t.co/ZiPJeZnMjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[We just got stopped by TSA because my Italian grandfather’s bag contained fly swatters, a loaf of bread, a block of… https://t.co/bE111hjt75]]></document><document><![CDATA[I THINK - Red-shouldered hawk.... ? @ Frog Pond Natural Area https://t.co/fAM0BIdYYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drove 5 hours to watch a movie on the couch with my boo after drinking coffee and him making Cinnabon’s with his… https://t.co/LPiGQn1K6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta say how proud I was of Adutt as some call him aka pretty boy . He put one out tonight . Still looking I thinking came down in GA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drain the swamp !😊  #WWG1WGA  #WWG1WGAWORLDWIDE  #MAGA  #GreatAwakening #QAnon #WWG1WGA #QanonArmy https://t.co/zXKxgowJap]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 330 am. Im watching MasterChef season 3 w/ @foodiephotog. Shes easily my favorite contestant on any season.… https://t.co/KG79LrenMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mom_paige Thank you. I hope they gave her sedation for that. They hurt. If I ever need one, knock me out w Versed.… https://t.co/APFM7x2NaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@txWhistler420 @tedcruz Mexico will pay for it… It is amazing what God is doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand ...  —————————————————— Entiendo ... @ Uncle Momo https://t.co/ryiVFzz6xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Union supporters chant outside the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette offices in the North Shore. https://t.co/vOh8g5RXpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you’re telling me that Colton sent Hannah home BEFORE going on their one on one date all because Cassie left the night before?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[#welp God forgives I don’t 👀 @ Downtown Orlando https://t.co/VzG43mUbBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight moves, no announcements 🌬️ pryingeyevapes #pandorablue #pryingeyes #pryingeyevapes #pryingeyevapesdotcom… https://t.co/3hqYCjTsf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want a mango smoothie from our Corbett center but honestly I'm just too lazy to walk there and get it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff all locked up here in central California #9PMRoutine https://t.co/LLlrsMIzi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never thought I’d admit this, but could almost mess around and move back to Utah after graduation 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prettyrainbow3 Gracias 🥰por suerte me traje algo para arriba ya refresco .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanSteinJr Just stop coaching from the stands. Period. It’s very distracting for all the kids trying to play. And… https://t.co/ccltEWUk7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few minutes of perfectness @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/YpoidYFgIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senoritao @corrinaaallen I need to do this! I would love a lunch audiobook club!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCLowe @LoganDobson @katriblack Oh Shmonkey! We are polar opposites in politics, but I know we respect each other… https://t.co/HOI2QUC3Jb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer ...."ACCUSE THE OTHER SIDE OF THAT WHICH YOU ARE GUILTY"....       JOSEPH GOEBBELS… https://t.co/9adGwuarBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marie77141292 @monsoon2112 @lyn_cade @notcapnamerica @chrisdameanor19 And continue to suffer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This place is so much nicer than it use to be! (at @OasisCubanCafe in Longwood, FL) https://t.co/WcSpGokY0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Bernie, are jobs and higher bank accounts damage? Are people off welfare and food stamps damage? The… https://t.co/IMVqAoGJvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alicia Downs started the RnR Washington DC Half Marathon! https://t.co/3FipUztRI7 #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t care how bad life gets, i’m not gonna go on instagram and ask people to ask me questions..]]></document><document><![CDATA[El Paso County Commission meeting today... @AHouseElPaso Executive Director Ruben Garcia is here talking about refu… https://t.co/ApRLvyO0rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#valentinesday special!! Dark chocolate cremeux//cookie//Speculoos crumb//Coffee jam//Torched red wine marshmallow/… https://t.co/8jyW72qfvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Lindsey you have lost your mind. A wall isn’t the answer. #nowall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP Yes god forbid if we put his career to the test while he was harming women and young girls. Shame on us. https://t.co/r3kUCbri3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does @AlanDersh not understand that an amendment is part of the Constitution?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracy_karin @megwatzke @NASA @saoastro Yay!  Thanks Tracy, big hugs to you as always https://t.co/88VT89SOm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SFCity_Hall the Civic Center Bart station escalators have been closed down several days at a time for months. I h… https://t.co/fw9wIkPgtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay I just made my verdict, I don’t like IPAS I’ve tried so many and I can’t sorry😩😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamboDonkeyKong @WalkingDead_AMC Welcome to #twdfamily Ryan we have been DYING for you to get here 🙌🙌🙌 #twd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fallenangel2100 @OneAngryGamerHD The knee's not supposed to bend THAT much...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justin Timberlake concert time 😍 @ T-Mobile Arena https://t.co/V0uKRDj8IW]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all my friends and family in Utah who want to learn about multiplying your money by foreign exchange. Don’t miss… https://t.co/pEC4Jb4SBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man identified as kissing sailor in WWII Times Square photo dies at 95 @CNN https://t.co/XEjPQsducv]]></document><document><![CDATA[my bf sent me this today and wow ts spot on. crazyy https://t.co/pJfYCIO9Fs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Wolf Pup Session IPA by @goldenroadbrew at @joes_crab_shack — https://t.co/S3QQXvus2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I practically passed out in the first minutes of Mass, sat down. and waited to stand for the Gospel Reading… https://t.co/9WjezwZ61v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s 6:50 am ma’am but can you not turn the light off on me while I’m peeing????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge Pullan entered a Decorum Order for this case. That means once court proceedings begin, no one can enter or le… https://t.co/8qZaN0PTek]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s my Gram! At 97, featured in this great article. https://t.co/DigmpnSM1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nag crave gyd kaau kog white chocolate nga kitkat ug cookies and cream nga hersheys. Aysus bantog ra ky gi dugs ta 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This poor little girl is having a conversation with herself in my messages 🤧🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to @barbie 60th birthday 🎂 party tonight w @candacebushnell ... best Friday night in a loooong time. #barbie… https://t.co/X1FgYtBCzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesileighs @dust2dust34 I haven’t even seen the show since early last season and I’m freaking out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rico_stathis @RickGriffin @MattsRoadTrip @MadHattersNYC @CharlesMcCool @VISITFLORIDA @VisitPCBeach @DanaHFreeman… https://t.co/JfaFJTKcML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HippieVol @GTA_Redhead I dont understand anybody getting so butthurt that they report to Twitter police. Its ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timothyharper_ Something ‘s weird.....message me an address and let me look it up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmorris324 @MrsSenesePR This would be great!! I need to wait until after regionals (3/9), to know if I can go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your generation I support but you aren't the first to do so..remember Earth day groups and host if other groups fig… https://t.co/NG3id0VRLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $60 Spotify Gift Card Offer     Enter Your Email Id And Complete A Simple Sign Up To Win $60 Spotify Gift… https://t.co/ugiOeLopii]]></document><document><![CDATA[So today I went to the @smithsonian Museum of American History were they had their amazing First Ladies’ dresses ex… https://t.co/IqUCDhn19e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Landed safely in LA! Now to head home and hang with my daughter! So happy to be back to the warmth and sunshine ☀️… https://t.co/Y8XgIQTu3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi!! I’m selling 2 Toronto shawn mendes tickets for the Rogers centre on September 6th. dm me for more information and if your interested ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dog people are crazy... but have you met horse people?  @KatBarrell  'POOCHED' IPF Trailer | Kat Barrell, Billy Kho… https://t.co/jLWrCvyi9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[#captainmarvel with the Family!!! #mustsee @ Cinema Cafe - Edinburgh https://t.co/KtbDnpGqAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to the doctor today and last time I went was January 24th and I weighed 176 and now I weigh 165! I lost 11 pou… https://t.co/1kRnBeZ0Dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something I else I know I can't have. @linklamont rhettandlink @rhettmc @brittonbuchanan @ Mississippi https://t.co/kHyUkjQWji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love a creative team name! So much FUN! Thanks for being part of it! #Ottawa #BBBSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basil found this small but really good #Mexican place so we checked it out.  🇲🇽 🇲🇽🇲🇽 Food was yummy and they make t… https://t.co/hszBBiUaUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made 2600! And it wasn’t my husband finally remembering to subscribe and doing it to be nice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks too nice outside for snowmaggedon #snowmaggedon #minnesnowta #wefinallyfoundwinter @ Saint Louis Park, Min… https://t.co/G1sENKGXcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mplantain @DeniseMTarHeel @UNC_Basketball Tell that to the players and coaches. We won not playing our best, which… https://t.co/CmwhkUjOZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch at the gristmillriverrestaurant in @gruenetx #Gruene #Texas #Weekend #Lunch #Saturdays #Spring @ Gruene Histo… https://t.co/4el7EtNKOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Destiny29466594 You know what's insane? I have a ghost tracking app on my phone. I was listening to one of michael… https://t.co/u5Jw7CqDio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quisiera saber que es todo lo que el hombre no puede hacer que la mujer si, que no sea estar embarazada. https://t.co/H8MoKd0ROx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahShachtman Spouses who both believe that vaccines cause autism when they don't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m the only person who thinks logo/monogram bags are tacky af... yes Louis Vuitton yes Gucci yes MCM. Idc… https://t.co/hbJbjBYnKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody is ever confused about where they stand with me. I hate confusion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RRBC #RWISA #BOOKREVIEWS #CIRCLEOFBOOKS #README #KindleEbooks  Good morning. Everyday is a good day to read a book… https://t.co/fkcikMFlIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseDemocrats Let's clean the HOUSE B 4 WE TRY TO CLEAN SOMEONE ELSES PORCH...WHATS GOING ON INSIDE HOUSE... https://t.co/1CPTMRuzbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do love God!  Btw, God, could you make it legal in VA?  Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is fine... for an authoritarian government #corruption #DrainTheSwamp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@velvetblade @RighteousBabe4 @DemopJ I don't mean to sound cold..I'm exhausted.. I have been trying for three years… https://t.co/PSlAxQzz9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pay WAY too much money for this apartment for this to continue happening. I would LOVE to speak to someone from m… https://t.co/GBPClRoLtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_Hotchkin13 That is awesome! The #WHSCAVE is a hot ticket at Power Hour! One of the reasons I’m thankful for you 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HBCompass @opennews Ty for this thread! We had a similar thought when we put together this list of news conference… https://t.co/6Jnbwm1LMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ "Always turn the tables. How would you feel if...?" is an adage my Mother always used. And she was right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang jolly. 25 Hilarious Marching Band Memes | SMOSH #funniness #tee-hee #smirk #funny https://t.co/Mtc3oiiwX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SBFNC @FishFunSun @Idclair @rjaviervasquez @herman_maureen @elder_jodi @DarinColville @TeamPelosi @barbcast60… https://t.co/J21cUD18xF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 🎶You can check out anytime but you can never leave🎶🎶 https://t.co/LFkT1CmqHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular Opinion: I think Jacquees is actually really good. “Mood,” “19,” and his Quemixes are fireeee. He’s short… https://t.co/oLEAs5P2kh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 18. Current favorite activities include: Stretching, rolling, standing up, wobbling back and forth.… https://t.co/jEN8UMH3rK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lent starts on Wednesday y’all how the heck did it came so fast this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[&lt;a href="https://t.co/5fOn4OLdiN"&gt;Organic to Green&lt;/a&gt;&lt;IMG border=0 width=1 height=1 src="https://t.co/17J5ltSpiq"&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep, not a racist at all Mr Meadows.  You’re certainly a douche though.  #CohenHearing]]></document></documents></author>