<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Every day I don’t work on refining a skill/talent feels like a day wasted. Then I get anxious and feel like maybe I’m wasting my life away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone that's mad at Green Book for winning best picture now knows how I felt when John Wick wasn't even nominated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NovexGG Yea.. that one might of been over ppls heads (I’m not being serious) what do you think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wanna fuck with somebody that actually wanna fuck with me and just me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCM @jessi_boseman @MeryssaMorgan @AshleyPHawks  @tanamongeau @DanicaPatrick @haileybieber @alissabutt @samantha_miani 😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dems desperately rely on people being uninformed or willfully ignorant. Some call it misinformation, I call it… https://t.co/Fm9SC0Ywia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ckeally Well he certainly deserves a fair chance. But you won’t find anyone who played under Kirby or coached alon… https://t.co/ynZIUJgIS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeLamentino @KateAronoff it's also going to lead to the government confiscating your toothbrush. sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClintOldenburg Ok, why doesn’t ID the mike work? Really annoying when you ID the guy and he whiffs. Doesn’t even try to block him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never chased an average girl. I sat back and thought about it and I was. SKEEEEERT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of possibly postponing the #StadiumSeries why doesn’t the @NHL move game time up a few hours to 5pm or 6pm?… https://t.co/mlzPLMNBHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Faitelson_ESPN Zinedine Zidane regresa al Real Madrid C.F. Canción https://t.co/1B3ij4yfy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico This is all validating the “Jewish conspiracy” crowd 1000x more than anything Omar said. It’s pretty sad really.]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES! @CALbasketballl   Is Cal the worst power conference team in college basketball history? https://t.co/N4BcGNmkM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oregon_history Though admittedly biased, I think Sgt. Williams’ story — and that if other Buffalo Soldiers associa… https://t.co/9ZxWjMAwCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBA can we end this one and done bs with the @NCAA and let dudes come out of high school?]]></document><document><![CDATA[El funcionario MAFIOSO @JoseMeadeK  a trabajar para los lavadores de dinero del Cartel de Sinaloa, no cabe duda que… https://t.co/gqOSBEMzwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riggs_chris Trade everybody because of a down year. It’s genius. Morin probably stinks. Myers will have to hit his… https://t.co/D3N81CkLTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giannis was six years old when Ja let J. Lo drop the N-word on a track.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you feel about the future?   #QOTD #Motivation #Houston #Texas #CrazyAsian #MotivationalQuote… https://t.co/pRMrRj5XCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hustle and bustle is the name of the game here in Nashville. #singer #singersongwriter #entertainer #vlogger… https://t.co/TziUmGnjrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo no vi #Roma....obvio no la que dice @GalileaMontijo y ya estaba hasta la verdadera madre con lo de la tal… https://t.co/IxkmTMELbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chas10Buttigieg Here is a blast from the past! You knew/know my friend Karen's daughter Kendall.  Small world. 😀 https://t.co/i7QbdoD61C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AStiller0 @pcnio @pedromazonb @j_moore_v @reyespebar @VictorCastroCos @FrnkAguirre @JAVALDIVIA @GenaroRuizMX… https://t.co/whfn1qvEvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the best managing broker in the business. Very excited and honored to be in business with John Johnson. He's… https://t.co/nQM8RVkBWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KNPACE Go anyway, I would. I wouldn't let rain stop me from going out for some fun  :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rey101101 @TommyTheBurner YOU and me both fam! I am sick of Seales already and don't even know the heffa really. T… https://t.co/isVkROccQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kunfupanda2 @AguedaBarojas @CongresoSon @rlizarraga13 @AnaGabrielaGue @MorenaenSonora No nos cuestan nada? Entonce… https://t.co/umta2cMDqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever felt alone in a room full of people? Isolated even when talking to friends and family? Do you feel a… https://t.co/cgYkd9muF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanMckenzie327 @rcrossm545 @FarrBrannon @tonya_mcelveen @AccettaPl @CharlieHHong @KMTovey @ChrisBergHD Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjcrock2003 I bet there are other energy providers in that part of GA. Seems like time to hit them in the wallet.… https://t.co/Hge4fHNVKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The office this afternoon! Stop by if you’re in the area. #real #authentic #music #phoenix #singersongwriter… https://t.co/5watcB3ibI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took last week off work and came back to find my coworkers had replaced my computer background with a collage of… https://t.co/xDlepi34AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @ACLU That’s Awesome! @Jim_Jordan has just delclared he’s WITH the @aclu who drlclares HR1 “mostly” gre… https://t.co/u1K4oAQIOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @RiceKing80 is live and we’re dabbling in some @TheDivisionGame  😂 Watch me potatooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all ain’t watchin #NBAAllstar2019 on @TBSNetwork with Charles Barkley commentating, y’all missing out! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinFree @megturney Fecal matter...everywhere https://t.co/ATKR0unyIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Food is an art and art is food for thought. #publicart #restaurantdesign #restaurant #lowereastside #art @ Hotel on… https://t.co/qE32pMJDcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the realm of books on news orgs navigating the digital age, a certain book has gotten lion's share of attention.… https://t.co/u0fTRBH699]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s have some fun. First person to name the player correctly gets a FREE online lesson from me. @ Rancho Mirage,… https://t.co/Z5apSm9ECr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damnit_shittany I was worried until I saw HIS reply to the boss tweet and honestly couldn’t be more in love w you two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll chat with #KyoungJooKim on #NYRadioKorea, 9:40 a.m., Eastern Time. Topic: #EthiopianAirlinesCrash https://t.co/LpBsuyoqks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kate_Amara @RRISC01 @9toed_Viking @djinnxxi @bonaevolentatis @udarnik @WTEpaminondas @texbrodave1 @marymjoneil… https://t.co/VrM6v5iymR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind-the-Scenes: The Miller Organization (my desk). #iLoveCVille #iLoveVa #SocialEntrepreneur… https://t.co/pULeR3B13h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost It always helps to have the local bishop distort the facts in your favor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight so many talented reporters, photojournalists, and producers from @WGNNews are out working the Chicago elect… https://t.co/SkkqS9WMDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I would love to be known as the person who banned the game about raping people. It's not like they can't sell… https://t.co/17yj7Exh2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another week with “double trouble”, what do we think it’s going to take to make top 16 after 14 games on the Shark… https://t.co/67AGjnrwpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me say that one more time. No matter the outcome of Jussie Smollet’s case, don’t sleep on the data. So happy to… https://t.co/COFUP20UYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamiemcmurray thanks for everything. We were there during your 500 win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY LAWS AND CONSTITUTION. AMERICAN WAY LEGAL MARRIAGE WAY, UNITED STATES ACTION ARMY WAY. ONE NA… https://t.co/44KkhzZweb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The internet is littered with insecure internet cameras. After the incident with Sensenets we decide to see what mo… https://t.co/UKipy0vdVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free Thank you printable for a subway gift card. via Free Time Frolics #giftcard #subway #freeprintable... #comedy… https://t.co/QO1pd2E3Td]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulioHerrada @PoleoRafael Son 15 días hábiles desde el fin del carnaval. La prisa es plebeya.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the president of @NISAmerica can appear in a Prinnie onesie, then I think @Ubisoft’s Yves Guillemont should marc… https://t.co/bjeG8hDL6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregTompsett @NateGearyWGR Enjoy your plate of alien meat.... https://t.co/0xuN6Qy7ur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wer1rrm @SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump Should’ve been done. These morons can’t just pass a bill they need to attach other needs to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BotW needs a hookshot, 4 empty bottles, some Pegasus boots, and big catching net, and the mirror shield!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mars lander starts digging on red planet, hits snags   https://t.co/kCnikNk1Gz via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsFridayNext @miel Have @miel as your guest of a guest on the next @pchh !]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JG9n8lIYg1 @MinSanteRDC #Ebola Virus Disease dated March 4, 2019: Since the beginning of the epidemic,… https://t.co/h1PWk4WvWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just in!! Mason and Off Shoot Collab! 6pk/$13.99 https://t.co/4aCBGQ8Cy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman And he isn't the only one I've given to. Hint the others have forsaken lobby $$, support the #GND,… https://t.co/NITlfY7oSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One on One w/ deandrejones32. Some Chest &amp; Bicep Work! ****I DO NOT OWN THE RIGHTS TO THIS MUSIC****. #Strength… https://t.co/BAu0l2ONzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m giving away an iPhone X in mint condition to someone who is truly in need of a good phone. A student with no in… https://t.co/Gw8CLAdS58]]></document><document><![CDATA[#boarding #snowboarding #wintersports #mountains #ride #ridethesnow #glide #float #fluff #powder #boardingpass… https://t.co/biCxTGHka7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve heard that protest chant before but theres a different part of it...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelodyBurst "I'm a vegan but my girlfriend is an El Pollo Loco combo plate!" was really good until the filler arc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a goddess on my wallpaper. @melissacee97 🙏🏻🙏🏻💔 https://t.co/lWuXbzjqKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning family: It's time to just be happy. Being angry, sad and overthinking isn't worth it anymore. Just let… https://t.co/9Uyfm5VeR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Assignment editor: Investigate the pace of Florida Gulf Coast real estate sales in the wake of last year’s horrible… https://t.co/XPPTwLmfRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #Avaya and #ConvergeOne, who's watching the game after the @Avaya event tonight? Hotel bar?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working with others Working with knowledge, technology and information, and Working in and with society.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell Maybe start educate the children properly and not bye left-wing Professor nut jobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebron is trash! Trash! Trash! Trash! Trash! Trash! Trash! Trash! Trash! Trash! Trash! Trash! Trash! Trash! Trash!… https://t.co/dV5BB7ITD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When health is absent, wisdom cannot reveal itself, art cannot become manifest, strength cannot be exerted, wealth… https://t.co/luT97GcjTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @JussieSmollett Live status update of this Tweet! https://t.co/wrBdirP57E]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my 14th semester as a college student after counting summer classes... today I have to sit through an hour… https://t.co/blyvMUzo7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimothyDeLaG Bro I was harmonizing with you through my phone! Such a great song!]]></document><document><![CDATA[David, DVH as been a constant with the athletic department as the Track and Field.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Snshn111 @mcmahon_tara @ritafoley20 @DewaynePerkins The show in question? It’s about profits.  The joy is a secondary concern.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mac: Your computer needs to restart to update files. Me: Remind me in an hour.  [exactly one hour later during Face… https://t.co/lMqcuqGnox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEP_mx @emoctezumab @INEEmx @SEducacionCoah @HiginioGlzC @jsalcidop @rbssalazar Trabajo colegiado con los Asesores… https://t.co/dRsv0y6mTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Did you hear the Jonas Brothers are back? Maybe i’ll finally get to fuck Joe”  - @Hansolo1610]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trenyce @hrcgreaterphila #entertainment #fabulous #diva #americanidol #vocalist #dianaross #whitneyhouston #hrc @… https://t.co/496OrF0tPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Susan Youngwood started the Princess Half Marathon! https://t.co/xtMroUsd6R #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreina Dios quiera y sea así nosotros saldremos de este narco chavismo a toda costa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cabers and bagpipes. Saturday morning done right. #MyDayinLA https://t.co/hG5rmgozj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_Fabiano @Dameshek Jerry needs to bring these back.  He would make a few extra bucks... lord knows he needs them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elinadoff its my personal opinion that HKBH will be tovea elbono of the Ungvarer Ruv for every smirking misread of his shut’s title]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNightlyNews @mitchellreports Trump aims kisses at Kim, Kim aims nukes at us. A bromance to end all bromances.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gotham She had to come back eventually. She’s an important character in the Batman universe and is one of the few… https://t.co/VQHb4qxKtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Le_Figaro Et la fraude fiscale.... Et l'évasion fiscale... Et l'optimisation fiscale... C'est bien de mettre les choses en corrélation...]]></document><document><![CDATA[👨🏼‍🏫.  #wednesdaythoughts Who opened the icebox door? The temp in GNV has fallen 45 degrees overnight.🤔☹️🥥🌴]]></document><document><![CDATA['A great big failure': Columnist says Trump can only be re-elected if his voters are the 'dumbest, most gullible pe… https://t.co/YNOU5ZKLAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[This happens a hundred times a cycle. Republicans say Dems will raise taxes. They say never. Fact checkers scold th… https://t.co/65QfNjDDvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A leadership is someone who brings people together." (🤷‍♂️) George W. Bush (Happy Presidents Day) @ New York, New… https://t.co/9MuzfCGB10]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to Brandon Redendo tonight last game of his freshman season at NYIT they won 100 to 84 he played 20 minut… https://t.co/RpujihxUDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got Lebron fucked up. He done clapped Beyoncé AND Rihanna if you ask me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to FaceTime my Mom before Izzy fell asleep tonight and it was beyond comical. “Who’s Dat?” @ Half Moon Bay,… https://t.co/ql92cM2k4A]]></document></documents></author>