<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#VansChallenge   Down the basement stairs they go!!@ https://t.co/AHcSJPuNIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy told me he was 6’2 and I just saw this mf in person for the first time at pbr and I swear he was 5’6...wtfffffff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennkirschner2 DOJ memo needs revision: High crimes and misdemeanors can happen anytime. A sitting pres who has c… https://t.co/KPivhrKqgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeTrumpEmergency you are rambling. You are not making any sense. Everyone is falling asleep. Why are you sniffin… https://t.co/x0BpfdI6td]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually, I would be THRILLED! @ Altadena, California https://t.co/ub2aNIYxos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reiko_Fuentes @foresthillci Thank you for supporting my nutty antics. I've never felt the love more. 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbyfuller Scene opens on a grizzled ops type.  “You wanna get into devrel, kid?  Okay. First get angry at compute… https://t.co/3kA34xCPF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cp24breakfast fam meet #pef fam #jerseyboys #frankivalli #frankivalliandthefourseasons #mirvishproductions… https://t.co/cogPg29HKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@euchreman1022 He doesn’t learn from his mistakes, he does have several bankruptcy if you didn’t know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @Jacket4Life to post my favorite books for 7 days. Each day I’ll challenge others! Day 1 of… https://t.co/qhXFFYLTKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCNewsnight @katierazz Meanwhile, the #Trump Administration doesnt even count how many #AsylumSeekers #children t… https://t.co/KfoOWtc4V5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@221Bcrow @fin__amour No worries, always happy to see my work being enjoyed 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win a chance to stay on your own private island! https://t.co/92heguEQBG #VRBO https://t.co/PWIKtevizZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go again snow but in a few hours watch it be gone lol @ Tigard, Oregon https://t.co/JOxz870XNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr you are a #disgrace and hope you start a very restless retirement soon. @SpeakerPelosi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to speaking about the role of Paramedics in organ and tissue donation @FanshaweCollege Paramedic Re… https://t.co/9jdWjpCUTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is here, and I’m in full research mode to prepare for the salon dinner I’ll be leading at @kulture_houston la… https://t.co/t6Y8Uyr5Dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win a Hunting &amp; Fishing Kayak! https://t.co/9m7cMGNUIm via @explorelacrosse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ianroot11 How much does a Vegas bomb run in maryville these days? I’ll Venmo you 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShellsBoysBball Congratulations Jacob being named athlete of the week. We are #RoxanaProud You are #ShellsStrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soccerrun5 @NooooSweat @JussieSmollett @DanCovfefe1 @ReAction10Folds @PatriotSmirk Lmao not even close you think I… https://t.co/Wc9Jos6cBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[And his cult follwers are believing every lie.. And mimicking his reprehensible behaviours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofiaealexander @AAAAAGGHHHH @chrlsthereeves @KristlePeluso @Livy_Brown Yessssss! Not only do I approve, I still c… https://t.co/5asJ1tGuYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay 🎶🙆🏼‍♀️ I am proud every single day to champion the role of women in the music industr… https://t.co/XAJIRVo12d]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT Tweeting is now congressional record. Can we all agree that governing by teeet is shameful. #MichaelCohenTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing pan! Love these treats! I have made very similar nutella and strawberry treats using soft tortillas… https://t.co/RmXVLur6L7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BossRobinVos And he blew through all of that and then some. Had to sell his house to pay down campaign debt, had a… https://t.co/m6CxuhjnDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Zettel Scheer is the one who said he was a feminist. Come on now.  He copies everything Trudeau says.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop &amp; realize: if you hadn’t met that certain person in your life, your life may be completely different 😜… https://t.co/UDvw9uLk40]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok Bruins fans - would you trade for Stone with the reported price? (2 firsts, NHL ready player).  Bonus question- if yes, which player (s)?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@55soAmbitious Welcome to the team @TorontoArgos you will look great in double blue :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is he going to be upset when his dna is what made it a boy? She can go get a new man and maybe he won’t give he… https://t.co/5sgkjHWfQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re enjoying the sweet sound of our choir during morning arrival. @JefcoedArts @gardendaleel https://t.co/zesvIfW2Ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I think people are insane for leaving off their seatbelt when sitting down on a plane https://t.co/p5P5XDiLOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @facebook for organizing a great #OpenUP event around #MentalHealth and #SuicidePrevention. Together we c… https://t.co/4i2siEdcjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥰🖤LOVELY IN LACE🖤🥰 #lovelyinlace #lovelyinlace🖤 #lovelylacetop #blacklace🖤 #blacklacetop #lace🖤 #lacetop… https://t.co/aSqCs7F5fl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reneekurilla Kid point of view: my son LOVES it when we have to turn a picture book sideways for a spread.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartaFKauffman have you seen this Facebook group? https://t.co/KO8vAUZjdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not getting out of bed until tomorrow afternoon prolly unless I am physically removed w a crane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG OMG #TheWay is my New Favorite !! 🔥🔥 #HangingTough30 @NKOTB @DonnieWahlberg @dannywood @joeymcintyre @jordanknight @JonathanRKnight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 They want them to read, and misunderstand the bible, like they do, instead of studying history, for example.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen 🙏 Robert!  I hope we can all work together and eliminate the murder of innocent 😇 babies 👶 here and around the… https://t.co/IHMoWtFCPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FFASiteTweets @OutlanderAmbass @TinyTunney @ClanHeughan @OutLandAnatomy @OutlanderCast Thank you😘👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Afro_Herper We were watching it tonight too! But we stopped halfway through to go see some live music at a friends… https://t.co/TAdEPCBq7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother has been telling me for years that he’s not going to college. This just happened and I literally cried t… https://t.co/pwmXZAOwF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottGrayMusic 2006 Toyota Corolla! She's carried me safely across country several times! 👍🏼🚗]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care how many times I watch friends I will restart it over and over, this is my favorite show there is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A headline read ‘roll back Obama-era regulation’ instead of ‘strip protections of mercury levels in rivers’ seen today. 3/]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is upsetting if she's trying to take us back into the sixties and fifties. some of the stuff that she's offere… https://t.co/7ph1o3hiRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; our hearts may be bruised sometimes, but I’ll be yours and you’ll be mine 💖 @wallofarmss @themaccabees]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is amusing. #humor #lol #smile #amusing https://t.co/bNOrHY0ySZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@EricHolder’s @DemRedistrict has sued @ScottWalker, campaigned for state Supreme Court Justice Rebecca Dallet and… https://t.co/sDORqds6Bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Baxter Bar/Arcade - @baxterarcade in Chapel Hill, NC https://t.co/KoR6AJePKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zigmanfreud Some idiots; some shameless opportunists. Either way, not sure how much idiocy (real or contrived) I c… https://t.co/gwjMMalcie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in Houston, TX? https://t.co/RErjpADLRG #Franchise #Restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[so I’m waiting for my sister to come out of school and this kid slipped on ice trying to walk down a hill and he go… https://t.co/1OGnmAnkgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can @soulcycle + @theDrybar please do a collab/giveaway or something 💛☠️💛☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnelaTannante @choupete450 J’ai de la misère à embarquer dans un camion c’est vraiment haut et inconfortable 😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thank you to lavishdulhan for featuring this beautiful day! It was a pleasure bringing this dream day to li… https://t.co/4pBV0F77FL]]></document><document><![CDATA[👀THANK YOU 1,619 FOLLOWERS 👀 I Would Like To Thank 1,619 Followers For Tapping My Page To Follow My Many Artistic J… https://t.co/bHhScJ50wP]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have a love/hate relationship with chemical peels 😫 i love them cos after it leaves my skin so nice and my scars… https://t.co/7yClxlUGqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a good day with my little boy. Kept his cochlear on for most of the time. He worked hard at trying to feed hims… https://t.co/yuRfbCzqbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time for a new shop window and we are thinking SPRING!  We love coming up with creative ideas that tell a litt… https://t.co/tGyCLezT7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuckin’ wind seducing My nipples’ll get shit poppin’. The cycle be crazy,sheesh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me to every passenger right now bc we were suppose to leave at 8:30pm and now I’m tired af from being delayed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s almost time to give birth when you contemplate going to sleep on the couch the rest of the night....r… https://t.co/J0QbZeIAeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/ The economic activity that #AmazonHQ2 could have generated would have been huge for New York broadly. Amazon doe… https://t.co/mLqbXM9Rew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mooredog82 @LadyBlackTear @saladesvertes @heiba11 @DeannGoss @Cat31s @goodenough_fu @fuckedchic @submissivemom… https://t.co/FVTH0I0vf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen testimony is nuts. House Republicans (like TX, LA, NC etc) are sinking to another low. They used to h… https://t.co/CcsSAw5YK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously, I wonder if I can gain muscle with the amount of times I move my weighted blanket around my house? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DopplerDaxWx @osusteelersJen That one guy standing by the window freaked me out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zhaabowekwe @bleeker185 @EgSophie As a daughter of a VietnamVet who’s father went to Singapore as far as I remember the war ended 75’ 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorCarper There is no climate change and you know it! That’s why you won’t give the State Air Quality people t… https://t.co/dnZgbAs3Xp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando veo a través del vaso, Veo a través del tiempo, Donde los sentidos se dislocan, Donde los temores se evapora… https://t.co/qzbC9dPLpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The struggle of day 1 of #DaylightSavingTime is real https://t.co/LRel2lam5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been dropping hella smileys on my work email today for some reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have an extra ticket for @SpaceJesusBASS in portland on the 22 someone pls buy it!! $20]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PremiosTVyNovelas @AmarAMuerteOf  @macabeso  @barbara_lopez21  #JuliantinaEnTVyNovelas https://t.co/GpkFlSzZLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[La caricature d'@ygreck #JDQ #polqc #assnat #CAQ #Legault https://t.co/Z6eOxnA5T1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knows the minimum age for a knee replacement? Not asking for a friend.. definitely asking for myself bc my knee is a GONER #sendhelp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMFlint He’s not a Democrat!🤬 Fuck Bernie! Missed 67% of senate votes! Sexual harassment in his campaign, doesn’t… https://t.co/Vf0WpnqVgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pinkney gives way to @Cgoods_15 with no outs in the 7th. Bases loaded. 8-2 Niners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R_Owl_Mirror @RepMaxineWaters I have seen abuse of power, obstruction of justice, violation of the emoluments clau… https://t.co/i9zEgvzoVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scarborough_ @JoeNBC @CuttingRoomNYC I'm very sorry, Joe. My mother was in hospice care at the time I turned 50. I… https://t.co/qRYxCEquwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[WEY YAAAAA por qué soy tan enfermiza últimamente ? no mames 🥺 no está cool, me siento de la fregada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi mejor amigo de Miami, está con mi amigo de Orlando....en Miami en un clajjjje partyyy....me invitaron....y yo? Tranquila en casa😇😇😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @realDonaldTrump OMG you can’t be serious...Oh wait, you’re a Trump supporter so you are serious! Ho… https://t.co/cioE4UEeMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Choir at 8:30 (@ St. Andrew Catholic Church in Clemson, SC) https://t.co/tG7CQCalG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Prof_Pownd The titles of some of the presentations are so creative: The "smell of the sheep" and "the Church as field hospital".]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anybody wants to get me something they can get me Carti or Trippie Redd tickets 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisfunksupt Helping our students 'play the game' 👌🏼 Up next, change the game. @RG1gal https://t.co/EeFflRb5QT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar @PaladinCornelia Our VP is a bit “wooden” in delivery style “and that’s a fact, Jack!” I am sure his write… https://t.co/eKB8cRJZhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to be less judgemental in. 2019 but I tend to gravitate towards people with actual talent, yes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second stop of @SherrodBrown’s Las Vegas tour: Lovelady Brewing in Henderson. His wife, @ConnieSchultz, introduces… https://t.co/6J4Dodpa7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another #FL school district using innovative ways to tackle difficult issues — and winning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @VP @FoxNews @JohnCornyn @SenTedCruz @senatemajldr @GOPLeader Good God. Trump asks Russia for advi… https://t.co/EwI7hF4l0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKoolaider @TheCumiaShow @LandauDave @holtcomedy Maybe if I didn't have these "roles" of fat..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zendaya So proud of you sis and thank you for including a variety of beautiful woman of all shades and sizes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most people think flowers for Valentine’s Day. I hear Valentine’s Day I think donuts 🍩]]></document><document><![CDATA[You mean to tell me that Bradley cooper wasnt even considered as a contender for the best director category....  K… https://t.co/ZwU1tXfyeF]]></document></documents></author>