<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett The act is over ! If you weren’t getting kicked off of Empire already I’m sure you will be soon !]]></document><document><![CDATA[#homeflow readying #workflow @ Paterson, New Jersey https://t.co/oK3lmC0BLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell @GoldinAuctions Darren you need to clarify he sold them for charity and not because he is destitute..… https://t.co/Y5aDMw8mBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skipbolden Baldwin was a remarkable man. Wonderful writer. He stood for something and spoke his mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥💥WARNING TO ALL AMERICANS💥💥. trump went full dictator Friday. 💥💥COMING TO YOUR CITY OR TOWN SOON. 1. trump imposes… https://t.co/e3j1hPSOV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay "Wathinta abafazi, wathinta imbhokodo." (You touch a woman, you touch a rock.)  - Sou… https://t.co/0J78BpZokK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonaldReasoner We loose when we don't address arguments that others might be convinced by... Interesting you are a… https://t.co/GA7QKaDko8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pops asked me if I’m on dope cuz I look hella skinny 😂 .. a niggah just going thru a lot ain’t got time to be pigging out 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VexingVixxen I did until my eyes went, got paintings in Japan Alaska, and a couple is europe..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a good look for the "only democracy in the Middle East" https://t.co/cKAaXEQtZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shirts are only $10? That’s a steal. One of the more comfortable shirts that I won.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy how the mind can convince you things aren’t possible. I made the first design at my chapel street store… https://t.co/xPftf20ztZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wrkhse82 @seanhannity Great question for the people of Minnesota. @illhanOmarpress ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad just said “...wait. Captain Marvel is a woman?? Why is she a captain??” I love my dad and all but I straight… https://t.co/JEVYrWz6Nj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanSileoShow Working late tonight and listening to you on @weei Enjoyed every minute of it.  Really entertaining a… https://t.co/wkl44sAwwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The polar vortex may have frozen the middle of the country, but it's also created a bunch of mini hurricanes out we… https://t.co/YMoEeaS2WU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“the olive drab resistance” here comes the grump. #grelfie = grumpy selfie 😡🤳🏼  . Song on spotify #playlist… https://t.co/xs7g0nBZLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late night music - #NowPlaying Jain - Makeba (Official Video) https://t.co/TYOqC0LGay via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fought/earned Win today thanks to our @PenyaBarcaLA family for showing up @ 7am #ViscaBarça Saludos a tod@s… https://t.co/lqclUta2TQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly Congress has ignored illegal immigration for years; advocating Comprehensive Reform that means amnesty… https://t.co/gDuI8TUlAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlecJStephens I hope that's not the case. Lol. That's why I switched to Samsung a while ago. Never had an iPhone t… https://t.co/X6v0A56G4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it possible for someone to be clingy but can still give you space when needed??]]></document><document><![CDATA[The explore page on either one of my Instagram accounts are either all about fire fighting and haircuts  or all haircuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobkornbluh @DanielBShapiro AIPAC should go back to Kenya, or wherever it’s from. - @MarkMeadows]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah this campaign is a non-starter. You would have to not be paying attention to American politics for ***at least… https://t.co/V2j21Xbp4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarah_SKG_1983 @realDonaldTrump That’s a given! He is a despicable asshole. Why so people keep asking? Change? Really!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByDavidMurphy If the deals are equivalent, or close, he's a dodger, and this isn't even a discussion. I just haven… https://t.co/r6lsEgml3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York’s rejection of Amazon could be a turning point for corporate welfare https://t.co/CwWyr2uP1x via @Curbed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vops16 @C_Shovald Creating legislation like this is how we lose sight of what it means to be an American and effec… https://t.co/LkrVXgQF2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tryna build that strong core 🍪 • • First time attempting 315 Beltless and I think that went pretty well 🤷🏻‍♂️ • • S… https://t.co/FJUme7yAuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Don't worry.  U r the biggest fvcking liar in the universe. @GOP Republicans lie.  It's what they… https://t.co/LPWSpMcz8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnAvlon @LunaLuvgood2020 @MJGerson That makes 72 years in a row then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time America it’s time that Donald Trump his entire organizational family and his administration along with al… https://t.co/woMthDLl3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open House Today 1-3pm            220 108th Ave #503 TREASURE ISLAND, FL 33706 3 Beds 3.5 Baths 2,940 Sq. Ft. Live… https://t.co/pQZLbvKkrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a perfect piece on what Nick Cafardo meant to everyone. You will laugh, cry, smile and simply appreciate ev… https://t.co/hrxh3vB0tF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early bird gets the worm aye? I’ve been up for two hours and I’ll I’ve done is read #xmengold and have ONE cup of coffee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter An AR 15. I’ve also applied for a suppressor permit. I prefer the bolt action Savage 22-250 for dee… https://t.co/11Xauk63uv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shiiid I do , fuck some rocks n Jordan’s , this what get the women wet . All that designer y’all buyin just to fit… https://t.co/rzmSGY4hMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH BTW ART DOES NOT HAVE TO BE WOKE  Calling something wack cause it isn’t woke has nothing to do with how well it… https://t.co/7FAdI97UZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[the amount of endorphins that are released when I say “I’m all in” when playing poker is like crack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZackAttack1884 @netflix Me the entire time bro https://t.co/fPXve2zkcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I was very small this has been my belief and has motivated me to be involved since I was 8. I will never unde… https://t.co/iCnOg8PNTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames Glad people paid hundreds of dollars to see this superstar effort. #NBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinningWordsPro Absolutely it is just disgusting. Talking points that the USA is horrible are just reprehensible right or left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me:  them: why do you always make everything about being bald? no one else even thinks about it I promise lol  me:… https://t.co/IeNmNEzkMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diana161cmr Uno de pocos animes en donde la segundona es la que rifa un poco mas.... :3]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@LightfootForChi⁩ at ⁦@CityClubChicago⁩ bright and early this morning. https://t.co/hcMZS2qwRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[We always have the choice to make the dream of love of equality a reality simply by saying yes I will stand. #resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Batchelor party in AC and the return flight is at 7:25 am?!?!? Hey at least i will be back in time for the finale against Louisiana]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamiePaizly Hi, We can definitely help you in design and development of your website at an affordable price.  See… https://t.co/8p5iHJzHXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Another lib leaning traitor to block our great President 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtomicMari @NASA @JimBridenstine Thanks for helping to prep us for the lobbying efforts in D.C. with… https://t.co/syzzhxhnSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaaeCiara @thekillakay_ @upnext__75 We talking material wise or pattern wise ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[U nvr see other rappers or singers as good as me lower there prices because a certain city wants to pay a certain a… https://t.co/VNsEG7eBQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[- “Si tuvieras que escoger con quien jugar... Diego o Leo..  ¿a quién escoges?   - “Messi. Con Diego ya jugué” - Ma… https://t.co/FSII2VUzsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[One collector’s view of how diversity happens. https://t.co/PFtTF5I7PS @sfmoma @SFC_Datebook]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport it was at this time the biggest snake in history knew he wanted to be apart of that team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveFoster17 Don’t want to cause a thing in front of his date. Or mine. Plus, it’s almost time for the Claire Dunn concert.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoadTripsCoffee @ParksandPoints @59NationalParks @naturetechfam @GalsWander @HHLifestyleTrav @RoadtripC Yeah, iron… https://t.co/fCXmT04ZIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rojo905 Thank “U” for having me!  I feel honored to be part of a great program that includes great kids, staff and… https://t.co/cUXiVXl1xE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fredsyogurt @rolandsmartin @JussieSmollett Usual response when there aint one... Carry on..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekParksTBSN @kinsellawarren Yep. Cannot imagine a recovery of indigenous and women’s vote occurring for Lib’s O… https://t.co/kjmPG2zvMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you don’t need a cation. Let your work speak for itself. #legacy #legend #corporatethuggin #tvg @ Detroit… https://t.co/b8JZ2xuU1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Italian city-states had the wealth because they controlled trade routes East while the Spanish didn’t. So world… https://t.co/kCQm9T8UqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Papa @ColleenPapa @WDWToday I was on that ride yesterday as well around 11am after wait time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MunchCleveland @MLB @cle_ItIsGone @BradWojdyla C-Sandy Alomar 1B-Jim Thome 2B-Roberto Alomar/Duane Kuiper SS-Omar… https://t.co/salPdwrYCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLundRadio taking lunch meetings at PF Changs in Walnut Creek 😎 https://t.co/i9kiGx1dtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had fun on GMA @michaelstrahan sure was  a good hang. @ Times Square, New York City https://t.co/KvzyR7bBIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh Why is no one talking about @realDonaldTrump association with Epstein and the accusation that he and Eps… https://t.co/UtQw3ridKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@LtJoeKenda showing the boys how a search for evidence is conducted. Bingo. #HomicideHunter #IfYouKillIWillFindYou @DiscoveryID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone that argues against this statement is literally just ignoring the way this show works so they can support th… https://t.co/8Tmmw6toth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skies_sgh Orrrr just don’t do tasteless and unclassy things, control yourself and don’t get so stupidly inebriated… https://t.co/MIsaoKuz5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[i like juice wrld a lot but i don’t understand why anybody would insist on creating 20 song hour long records like pleaseeeee relax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelS59419000 @MaxBoot Not sure how this helps move the discussion forward.  Prove me a fool with argument and facts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Democrats better start taking care on Legal Americans than illegals]]></document><document><![CDATA[We kept the best of the killer b's and the future will prove the past! Watch Ben not miss a beat moving forward!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GCraftyCouture @kenjimallon *sounds of wolves howling and eerie cackling* yessss, Mr Harker, and it’s the OLLLLLD… https://t.co/EMAlhPVhNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[See that shit is friggin racist act. I want to know how a government can be so racist an just because it is our pre… https://t.co/aXx8QGpuNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jruddy64 @KFLORIN @CTMirrorKeith @GovNedLamont @thesarahgordon @thedayct @melistargazer Sweet front page Mel @melistargazer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCAMERICA your lineup of shows gets worse and worse. Come on. Put British shows on!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I am afraid it is terribly obvious that you have been doing most of the lying. We are not as gulli… https://t.co/2u0w7vb7gL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spose we better go play some pool again @ Underground Bar &amp; Grill https://t.co/T22dHhrHfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loc8ingoil And some will think that will transcend into next year. It’s happened here a lot over they years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IBHirsch I had to show LAPD two different envelopes addressed to me here. My Ohio ID was not helpful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at the number of parking spaces there are near light rail and subway stations. https://t.co/XKyuKwFe24]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like we can all agree that it’s time to pay servers a livable wage so tips don’t make or break it for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/O @TroyScott24 and @Koop3 helluva a career to both of you ❤️ love you both]]></document><document><![CDATA[E3 - Farley with a tidy inning. She walked 1, but drew 3 ground outs #Gators]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of Drew Barrymore's birthday, here is a #blog I wrote about her. https://t.co/yUmmYWp0pS… https://t.co/JtyxqpMkxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol 😂😂  via sasha Instagram stories #BossNHugConnection #SashaBanks #Bayley https://t.co/zJj3tVdZ5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InvasionofPrivacy #KingofRnB 👀🌠💰💵🎼🎺🎻🎸🎹🥁🐐📽️🕶️💪🌎✂️✔️💯‼️  https://t.co/L6NMPExHxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @JosephMerritt to post covers of my favorite books over the next 7 days, no explanations or… https://t.co/hj3z0Eohpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s No Joke, It’s a Crime” Student PSA Contest  https://t.co/Ga1R0Dp4Oa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChokeOnAPretzel @steak_umm @dasharez0ne Me, facing @steak_umm knowing no corporation will be allowed to survive th… https://t.co/eNMRuaZYd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance @kasie @nickconfessore I don't particularly like candy corn either but as they say presentation is… https://t.co/E0EPVM2j60]]></document><document><![CDATA[MOMENTS AGO! Look at this! A tow truck just hauled away the burned out wreckage of the of the tanker truck that cra… https://t.co/obSKVN1v24]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby Jack Jack is my favorite character in @TheIncredibles funny take.... very cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillLeeVovers Yup. And it works. How much debt is Sweden in? How many wars have they been in? What country is cont… https://t.co/3ZScmD7FHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dimwitcrats can not do any better than this, killing babies, regulating cow farts, going vegan as mandated gove… https://t.co/sIZ3Jnw1DE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @HardballChris Just keep her talking for Donnie Brat to get re- elected . MTF never learns . Shut up ! Mrs Pelosi .]]></document></documents></author>