<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MariaLKanellis So this comes up on my FB memories... Happy Birthday Maria! https://t.co/fA9cPVdK1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE GREAT COMMISSION IS IMPORTANT TODAY BECAUSE JESUS COMMANDED IT, JESUS MODELED IT, JESUS PLANNED IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris , sleeping with everyone for nothing make's that person a slut, sleeping with someone for a price mak… https://t.co/ZXnElYi0kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tredogg84 Welcome to YSU, wasmy alama mater, now we are in Twinsburg. The school and surrounding communities will treat you well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabeWhisnant Maryland-Clemson first round matchup would be interesting too. As would Maryland vs. any ACC team in any round]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllysonApsey @burgessdave @burgess_shelley @TaraMartinEDU @tamaraletter @mradamwelcome @TechNinjaTodd… https://t.co/g01lIcPi7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting rekt on Apex right now. Come see my misery lol https://t.co/hYZAMlNWFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[man, you telling me there was a slab show down the street from me last night and I didn’t see it???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord help me! @deebler45 with the great tackle, the pace to get away from the first man, the quality outlet pass, t… https://t.co/m2qANTJjto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the course of four days in NH, thousands of voters from all corners of the state, traveled to meet one of seve… https://t.co/cT9GCsB2zg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Lildouchebag you are up to your neck, daddy can't help you there. Neither #FauxNews nor the entire #gop]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fashion #design #collage #magazine #mixedmedia #art #contemporaryart #paint #baltimore #worksonpaper #hands #paint… https://t.co/8zI4jABn3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing up I saw my Dad staring at his finances a lot. I realize I do the same thing now, trying to will money out of thin air]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeyRyanM In Minding the Gap and Icarus, you can tell the Directors started with one intent, but then something muc… https://t.co/ouIiJ7XO0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Indivisible #Democrats #Progressives #Independents #TheResistance #Resist #BlueWave2020 #IndividualNumber1 #MAGA… https://t.co/6xyjBGsIs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Oh Log Cabin Lindsay. Your credibility is so long gone. #Cult45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Whataburger your love is my drug. Thanks for the inspirational words @KeshaRose  #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/bsjTHdV2NW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USATODAY wins today’s #drunkuncle at a funeral award https://t.co/8WbbKma0k3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d never talk low on some one i once love I hop some will treat her better then I did]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign Falsely Linking Muslim Congresswoman To Sept. 11 Sparks Outrage In West Virginia https://t.co/oFpJVeCDqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[93% Off Chiropractic Care at Baker Family Chiropractic Center https://t.co/bT6HWp13Dh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinPHicks I’ve been involved in a number of cults both as a leader and a follower. You have more fun as a follo… https://t.co/CP1gM3vrsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[These housing developments could greatly improve the lives of some of our community members. And help make a dent i… https://t.co/MrWnskqV3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeySalads @iheartmindy I laugh so hard when I think of these things. Then I realize a good portion of our populat… https://t.co/XjvTYOxRy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAStartingLine @DavidRutz and yet Dumbacrats want to impeach Trump and make him President?🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eleebeck Yes, we now know twit is for the non thinkers, for the sheeple. Other #Socialmedia avenues are needed]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still waiting on @CNN to give @JulianCastro his town hall ..... https://t.co/qkyZuXrKLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Garrets running solid! Now if these drops of rain would go away...... @GarrettSmithley @LVMotorSpeedway… https://t.co/KApBXVX0gy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tgif2023 @forlornQuixOtic Unite to resist, resist and fight to defend democracy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbypocah Sweet and very beautiful pussy beautiful body sweet beautiful ⚘🌷💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who would’ve thought LeBron James-led Cavs would be better for tv ratings than a Lebron James-led Lakers team?… https://t.co/FwTpTRVyMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[📚Day 7 of 7...covers of most influential books I’ve read, no explanation, no particular order.  I was nominated by… https://t.co/j92nbk1KoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BardicLoreBlog You can charm the beggars. There’s was a rural American fantasy series about a wandering bard with a silver stringed guitar…]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/Vc82zOySs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those that listen to @ChrisClow via podcasts but have never heard his political commentary, I would suggest lis… https://t.co/xE0GRmOVDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roads were fucked up. Were stuck in Winona, MN watching Brother Where Art tho at the Super 8 motel and there's a do… https://t.co/WCPYMRjbK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast What does Cohens testimony have to do with North Korea? If Trump did nothing wrong / has nothing to… https://t.co/CaDYl5Rgxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatMarcWithaC Wishing your mum the best for the future dude! And you’re awesome ❤️👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffdotseth That’s like my wife’s student who received a C minus and said to her, “alright, that’s enough, right?” #Padres]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenRossi Sort of reminds me of climbing under your desk in an air-raid drill as you wait for the Cossacks to ride in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Jennifer Fraser @teachingbullies  for sharing! #playershealth #playershealthprotect #safesport #playsafe… https://t.co/esnYDcDe1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PodSaveAmerica @jonfavs Do we think the unpopularity of the tax cut will effect Trump’s approval rating?  As a fam… https://t.co/b9qVyr3xR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[the problem with fashion trends is i wanna bury myself in snakeskin print but i know it will be obsolete next year so i’m not gonna]]></document><document><![CDATA[Radio: I'll be joining @DFeuerstein tonight at 7:45p CT to preview #MNUFC's 2019 season.  You can tune in here: https://t.co/3SWEdY1xxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tim37191069 @realDonaldTrump Still waiting on your address so I can see and spend the night on your ranch..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger The polarization of Bernie supporters is almost like Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PantherPickle @JasonLaCanfora Just like his “sources” close to Tom Coughlin saying that he was going to step down… https://t.co/Y9cFPGAaZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunterLJohnson @marctorrence @JoeGoodmanJr @ChristinaWBRC @DrewChamplin @MarkJennings55 @KevinScarbinsky Are you t… https://t.co/NIAaJxDsW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Kamala Harris endorsed by SF, Oakland, San Jose mayors - San Francisco Chronicle: Kamala Harris en… https://t.co/YtV6l0ax42]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥PITCH PRESENTATION💥⁣⁣⁣ ⁣⁣⁣ I could watch a catcher make pitches look this good any day of the week! As a pitcher w… https://t.co/bcXLSgE5gN]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/zonEDPPnBU just having fun out here, my partner would clap 99% of players btw.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaMCottrell @LorenLGgroves @SarahM_DeGuzman @MikeJablonski5 @MrsJaronfelder @AngelaMCottrell  Soo proud of you… https://t.co/P4ED4r43wR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kiranansi I was full-time freelance for 7 years.  I ended up settling on something like 70–75% of my working hours… https://t.co/jbcZ047807]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMIGO (@), los problemas no pueden vencernos... NO TE RINDAS SIGUE AVANZANDO, porque DIOS YA PREPARÓ TU SALIDA Y TU… https://t.co/PVMuZwaGy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinKCourtney Wing chased by a bull or even an old momma cow can truly be a motivator to set a land speed record.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickSandersLaw @ethanjacobslaw But in general, can a sound engineer be a co-author? It likely depends on the music… https://t.co/onwRfVcb6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Here's a two-word piece of advice for Trump and his team: Jenny Craig!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Water and Rust performed @threadgills as part of the Soul of a Musician Series @waterandrust #atx #austintx… https://t.co/mdnRuH7wRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LanceStorm It’s amazing that we presently have more access to information than anyone who has ever lived and very… https://t.co/6mCbgTEALB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to actually be a fan of Dakich’s in-game analysis. This has been a rough year for his radio hot takes and co… https://t.co/iD38NElM6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iAmSocram @DeeTrilla Pretty much, I saw her dance 16 years ago. She was cute. Aha the end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DollyDwyer10 @Starrbryte67631 @cdwood_wood @redsfantexas @lisaponyexpress @PamelaM5050 @Brandonmartine @adones683… https://t.co/pvZOaXWBgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day in San Marcos! I love my beautiful ladies! @ Ivar's River Pub https://t.co/57e1uWO4jQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdriRM33 Si la ganamos all is well, seria historico, es el ultimo y mas bello trofeo, y la celebracion seria mucho mas especial]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamagedBttm If there isn't a very good reason and there was no attempt to contact you,/then there's a simple way t… https://t.co/5awswUmxev]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SCOTUS: In ineffective assistance case, 6-3 decision that counsel's failure to file notice of appeal when requeste… https://t.co/cHSG3lKQ2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseNunezIV @shelbylcole @EmmyA2 @arexismc Guess I'll just have to boo and hoo instead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkreutzer40 I agree with you on both accounts. I love Dawkins' game, but Taylor was a senior and also preseason PO… https://t.co/U7BriYhFQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[That time I chatted with Natasha Hall on @CJAD800 about my 150+ houseplants and Instagram. Do I sound nervous at al… https://t.co/BejOAB6iJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un niño en casa es un manantiál de placer, un mensajero de paz y amor, un lugar de inocencia en la tierra, un víncu… https://t.co/lWCfVqpXxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh this is shitty and we are still in North Dakota. @PaigeWelch10 @haytrudell @taylor_hunter20 @kaitlynhardwic1… https://t.co/SZGXXTi7g4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mulle’s witch-hunt already cost us more than $300 Million. For nothing Muller has no respect for taxpayers. Even wh… https://t.co/fCQ7nCOvUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Stone Ruination Double IPA 2.0 Sans Filtre by @StoneBrewing @ Rockaway, NJ — https://t.co/fKQ5m1yZFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdvanceAuto I have been stuck without a car for 2 days because you are charging a brand new battery that I purchas… https://t.co/7vHG5iV0Ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thread👇 containers in #HEP.... something I’ve gotten involved in via reproducibility and reuse with @lukasheinrich_… https://t.co/jn28fevrz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me tomorrow and Sunday at 10 am!💫🌟✨  Come have some fun, meet new positive energy people, clear your head, get… https://t.co/fiERq2q4lG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Super70sSports @Buster_ESPN Yup and then the next year their arms disintegrated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell your Chicago family members, friends, co-workers, and neighbors to get out and vote.   https://t.co/tx9zInwIgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolfDigest We share the same birthday September 10 ...the 1st person I admired in sports and will always be the ma… https://t.co/jy6kSoe8NH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KennedyNation @seanhannity @IngrahamAngle @TuckerCarlson @OutnumberedFNC @realDonaldTrump USA advisories along wit… https://t.co/jInOLf3Yzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benchten Since the first caveman's song, there is cave art showing someone trying to steal from him (or her).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @realDonaldTrump And my question to you is what makes you think that people are unable to work...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiserableSDFan We still have to get thru the next 2 years or so... but 2021 and beyond is looking promising.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re gonna do the wave at least get out of your seat. You can’t do the wave sitting down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith @captainmarvel @MarvelStudios @TheRealStanLee @Marvel It was possibly my favorite Stan Lee cameo, s… https://t.co/NhGKGcfIIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[〰 👀 🌴  💋  #WOW #OMG #WTF  #Red #Lip #Babes #Mecum #Pontiac #Music #Jackson #Trump #Chevy #Cannabis #Biker #Michigan… https://t.co/hBmcckIqEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son and I normally attend UT Dallas Explore Engineering. This year we a conflict in scheduling with another and… https://t.co/u8xhnHSPpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardiac Hawks do it again! Holy cow!!! Unbelievable!! Hopefully we have some of that saved up for #MarchMadness #GoHawks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pchdotcom 🤠🤠🤠Get all soon Will not order till i see some thing i like, Get all soon I Stoped any other orders goin… https://t.co/ExCxQnc7JC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unless something in them not working right like loosing their comm sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSO I saw the full video on TV while I was working out this morning at the gym.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up to a bunch of people defending a pedophile isn’t how I wanted to start my week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Girl you’re just copying the Obama care garbage and you’re just dressing it up differently, no offense… https://t.co/Jj4xf6YCUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed. He deserves to play a bit more. The team just needs same energy and effort as last game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikesDogshackOU @eliserowee @souljaboy I was in high school smh higher education has taught me to appreciate an intellectual like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[My summary of GOT season 1: Joffrey is an okay guy, RIP to Ned, Daenerys is a babe, Bran ruined everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids enjoy the game, sad because the @pelicansnba lost against the @sixers. Thanks @breighl 👍🏻👏🏻🎉 #letsgopels #nola… https://t.co/3iO0XpGTXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m new to #Oregon and its wonderful full-service gas stations.  POLL: DO YOU TIP? 💵⛽️  Bonus Question: How much do… https://t.co/pBqh4G5DsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’s member that movie “Field of Dreams?” Well, this is where they filmed it 🎥 ⚾️ #seaninanothercity https://t.co/6yGRvKDhL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RUN215 #MyPhillyRun #MyCityMoves #Run856 #RunSouthJersey #MyJerseyRun #music #running #nike #garmin #mapmyrun… https://t.co/QHTTvuJFoo]]></document></documents></author>