<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@elemz5 @DrJerLowe @matthew_arend @RLermaHcisd @PrincipalSJV @SoontobeEdD @RyanBJackson1 @fit_leaders @PhilEchols Nice pic! Great run! 👟]]></document><document><![CDATA[All kidding aside this is actually the way toward a more joyful life for the wealthy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoannVarnado1  I THINK THERE'S  MORE THAN MEETS THE EYE. ABOUT THIS! WAS THINKING THAT!  WILL COME OUT "NOTHING HI… https://t.co/8m3XGQTjEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BibleBeltDarlin @elgrizld @POTUS Pelosi's afraid of losing her job as Speaker.  The left is so radical, that Pelos… https://t.co/5cMzqTxoON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating #IWD2019 with Women in Wildlife.  @AustraliaZoo #InternationalWomensDay ❤️🦒🐊🐒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great turnout at today’s HIMSS presentation. Spreading the word about iGlucose’s valuable partnership with Vodafone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 Opposite. My children changed my political views. I was a life long republican who didn’t vote for trum… https://t.co/fzaq68VQx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @billmaher on this issue. Big corps should create opportunity in states that need jobs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[but the rest of the GCC countries as well, working hand-in-hand with the local work forces in these countries to id… https://t.co/eIYTFSC5zi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beautiful Ojai post office in the town. We thoroughly enjoyed walking around this cool town.  . . . .… https://t.co/yvcImP8FMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TechedUpTeacher @3_DLeadership These are the elephants in the room and students are hungry to talk about their har… https://t.co/7uJwKgICfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFlyTexas @kayb625 @Tigerlily_lady @fredsfam @Hiyaboopers @vah0603 @DonnaY1legwondr @ilseverboven There you go!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simonlamacraft Simon .... There have been a few studies claiming to replicate, but when one looks with more scruti… https://t.co/ZwY8iKjIuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[KARL LAGERFELD - FAMOUS LAST WORDS:  "Fashion Models who "complain" about their pants being pulled down or getting… https://t.co/WoITlYz7Bb]]></document><document><![CDATA[sooo like... i wonder if “right person, wrong time” thing is true.. 🤔 but not gettin my hopes up or anything 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I walked around in a T-shirt now I got to pack again to head back into the nyc cold :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GottliebShow Listening to you on The Herd today and such great points on Zion and playing college sports! Best tim… https://t.co/XrcV5PC92K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! Bitterly cold morning. Especially for March! #liveatdaybreak @tmj4 https://t.co/pJDHme5V0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @KevinGFox 1) Insurance companies should be allowed to refuse coverage for anti-vaxxers or charge a penalt… https://t.co/GpbWQtluav]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men in bars will literally make up anything to impress women.   Last night I overheard some early 20s weasel lookin… https://t.co/DRy0HTBRht]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@reviewjournal .@AaronDFordNV .@LasVegasSun .@KTNV .@SteveSisolak .@StevenHorsford]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenBlumenthal If you do not think we American patriots can see through you politicians that are obviously gaining… https://t.co/Df0I6wZecG]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @KirkWarmack and I went to see Werq the World @AlyssaEdwards_1 said to make sure Kirk and I stayed together be… https://t.co/Nfk9IFLdR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarayBooksDA @DanaNussio1 @isabelledrake @JewelELeonard @AilaStephens @Nicky_Adams_Pen @TheMuseCrew AWWW!! I feel… https://t.co/1uF51OGeu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smoothkaos She is a dumb tramp that was a druggy and thinks she is way more then she is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excuse me. I've just feeling really bad about myself lately...  Yeah let me just pitch this tent here. Have an inte… https://t.co/RYXmBAw9oA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs a little helping hand...#hamsa #saylavie #beadedjewelry #beadednecklace #maudegrahamjewelry… https://t.co/LfxojzXxwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain’t no way in hell Kylie could be my sister, how do you have to think about your friendship with jordyn???? ummm okay sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Technically, it goes for both types of same sex couples. I’ve met same sex couples that make AMAZING parents but th… https://t.co/zvVMYU4lX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep seeing everyone post about Girl Scout Cookies...but I haven't seen any Girl Scouts! Where are they!? 🤷🏻‍♀️ •… https://t.co/ezHbBlEy4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sierranwilson @JagSays Make your channel right now - I’ll subscribe. You can upload in 3 weeks. Seems doable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@retirednavy05 @SethAbramson @SandraBridges1 @SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer @NicolleDWallace Dear retirednavy05  Stop w… https://t.co/CwnfZvtIHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek I highly doubt that kid made up the bits about Pelosi and Beto, he is 7.. seven ffs. His parents influenc… https://t.co/tDxPU3yvG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You niggas ungrateful and you prove to me daily that being single is the move lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pioneering code education: Catching up with St. Pete's nonprofit code school https://t.co/NWM2jVWefs via @stpetecatalyst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acosta Hey @realDonaldTrump   Fabulous news!!!!!  No need to come back. You can stay in Vietnam. They won’t extrad… https://t.co/3MlXWD7MV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey smokers...the beach is not your ash tray. #savetheearth https://t.co/xI77oE6SmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko Totally disgusted by this. A few nice words and tRump is Ass kissing🤯🤯🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[We scare because we care 👻 @ Disney's Hollywood Studios https://t.co/NXKFHhwdgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[“His birthday is February 29th. He shouldn’t even be a real person” -guess that friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my team everyday but a special shout out on #EmployeeAppreciationDay #MagentaSnaps https://t.co/MigWJOT46d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sequential intercept map: Methodical way to come together at intercepts to examine their own communities to see wha… https://t.co/eGpigOb4JP]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a mission this week to show off Heritage at Vizcaya! How about this gorgeous kitchen? #builderboostaustin… https://t.co/Zk9cNwEd0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people were never meant to be married I think I am one of those people. I just love my freedom too much to be… https://t.co/6kdLEMOSRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gofundme @pedalthecause My husband’s stage IV cancer has nothing on him. He’s just been warming up! #BattleBorn… https://t.co/Shnq9YGQNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only ran because Erick told me there were bananas at the finish. https://t.co/ojSqPAaLEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMANGO @DannyLeBlanc24 @spyderrider63 @CupCakeLady1313 @Pixxydoodle @dega_boy_87 @KCJO_LABMOM889 @mustag_girl71… https://t.co/edY2NnMNQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Running out of dinner ideas? Check these out! ⬇️ #HealthyEating #nutrition https://t.co/VQ2KWd2rsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhayden21742 @LNW4Trump @KatTheHammer1 Karma will prevail without a doubt🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have to be done with trash Trump's kindergarten games !  Budget Sets Up Another Battle Over Wall Funding | NBC 1… https://t.co/ZQNADYf4yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[tagged by @creamsodabi, my lockscreen is studio ghibli lolol tagging: @brinkl3y @kimmmannn @emilynmelanie @tataevic https://t.co/AARVrLjksO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPain151 @rebeccaballhaus Trump would definitely offer a pardon prior to Cohen’s hearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happened with the belt?!  I   am going nuts now!!  Lmao you cant do this to me!!!  #RHOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just stood in front of the bathroom mirror for two hours crying over dumb shit. But anyways, how’s yalls night?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So....just figured something out that had bothered me for a few weeks. Reality TV show contest winner wins on netwo… https://t.co/NvfYT6Ix2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel the power of purple at West Ottawa HS https://t.co/q50f43H5kj @VAInstitute @WestOttawaHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies, how we are in our cubicle at work with our earbuds in hoping our co-worker doesn’t notice our rachidness and inner thot! 😂🎧🎼🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnnbrk Oh please do! While you are at it, start the impeachment process. Please]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner and #isles. And because "Freak show" was my favorite nick name. https://t.co/CpBRxhutGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the annual check m never drinking again tweet but I’ll sure as hell, will be drinking again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDept @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo So many negative replies to your Tweet, I really do not understand their thi… https://t.co/IFbHg0DVpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope all the people I went to high school with have muted me on here]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toda la mañana me la pasé haciendo dibujos para el profe que nunca le gustan 😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kjlcole @fablefy @DrMaxineWalters @aweninspiration @Mind_on_ASaP @inspirecitizen1 @BiscottiNicole @bbray27 @SUSHR7… https://t.co/guJQNklvGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Gallup had Trump up in the polls this week so he decides to use an unpopular method (national emerge… https://t.co/ZJCeC4kalo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Just admit you had a senior moment and move on. You're looking more unfit daily.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, I would not want anyone to think I agree with him. At all. Ever. 😂  They could tell me the reparations would b… https://t.co/vK3G12xpsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pierce Family...Agent Odell has got to go!!!! @CressWilliams @NafessaWilliams @chinamcclain @ChristineAdams]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAfee_Help I didn't order your software. You charged me over $80 for something that I don't want and can't afford… https://t.co/N2h06XMSIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir horrible experience yesterday at DFW with cancelled flights, missed day at work due to cancelled fligh… https://t.co/29gK7sUuoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Renevelation @not_aboutu He deserves nothing. He is a tyrant. Worse than Caligula, Hitler and Mussolini combined. But he doesn't exist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todas las noches antes de dormir, además de estar viendo chismes en las redes sociales jaja me la paso viendo trata… https://t.co/QIx8X8mSdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richard_HSIII @lynnv378 Well she was brainwashed by her new hubby Joe (Republican from Pensacola, Florida).  I was… https://t.co/IABdgrxHod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CJAMcMahon @JameyHarvey Why would it be a good thing for fathers to teach their children that it's ok for adult me… https://t.co/Rw7RnXP9J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's where we go wrong... @ La Mesa, California https://t.co/CT7CSXGg8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strong women. May we be them, may we know them, may we raise them. #InternationalWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurahelmuth @PostHealthSci @sarahkaplan48 @Open_Notebook are any left...........]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nealbrennan @NatGeoChannel Watch Dawn Wall too on Netflix! Same directors (and lots of overlapping casts) - I thin… https://t.co/67SOQMBcWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between Leaville &amp; Copper right now.  #cowx #ColoradoLive https://t.co/eQohiCcYHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badassbucho @khloekardashian @RealTristan13 Very true momma, very true]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Hundredth Birthday to my happiest place on Earth. @GrandCanyonNPS https://t.co/xnI6eE13z7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeonieBelcher @Stephanieannica @johnpavlovitz YEAH SO WHAT ELSE IS NEW?!?!???!!! CHRISTIANS DIED IN ARENAS OVER 20… https://t.co/B8OXcNgLuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wichitamgc @LChidivas Yassssss 👏🏻 thank you for the s/o - I’ll provide great content!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're too lazy to pull our loaves together today. #KittyLoafMonday #CatsOnTwitter #MondayMotivation https://t.co/rrv7Nba504]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @RashidaTlaib I loved it when she repeated herself. For the record.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#minibullterrier @minibullterrier cute photo of kiwi https://t.co/bK4AdkLH7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Más de 285 heridos y 14 asesinatos por represión del régimen de Maduro este #23Feb, estima informe de la OEA https://t.co/3IeRHlcTKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance I’d he auditioning for Wimpy on Popeye? Looks more like Brutus. https://t.co/Yw9WWlizDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The goal should be to get science and technology to the people who need them @CamiDRyan on the GM debate for… https://t.co/Li4gaeuCYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetsGoWVPower @realDonaldTrump Yes, that is exactly why it was deleted, because the musicians didn't want their so… https://t.co/edvqmPwz21]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #internationalwomensday and I’m feeling being alive, being strong and independent, and being a woman.… https://t.co/eWf1HF0Oih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesConner_ Hi James well when I lived in Pittsburgh, I would eat at the oyster house in the strip district it ha… https://t.co/uuFfCYFOiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeSite What is it with Germany? Is there something in the water that causes heresy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad this new agent/goofball could make it to his first convention! #ilovebeingaRealtor #BHHSeliteRE #bhhsallin2019… https://t.co/k980fH2fPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waywardliliana @SchneiderJamz BOO I DONT SLOW BURN UP IN HERE ITS HOT AND HEAVY FROM THE GET]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatoratanu @williamlegate Exactly. Plus he then boards Air force one to go for a weekend of Golf at Mar A Largo. S… https://t.co/Ku3lzMr1mz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son streaming #fortnite come by and say Hii.... #mixerstreamer  https://t.co/QJYtF2ZCcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think the majority of people think of dinosaurs often enough. Just my opinion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one that jumps when their phone buzzes and falls when they are watching something? 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@156Teacher @FLBATsA @GovRonDeSantis It’s not a raise, it’s a bonus.  VERY different.  #uncertainty]]></document></documents></author>