<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mommamia1217 @ShierBill Pro......life? Sometimes? https://t.co/ppiKrMwrQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Missouri Eating Disorders Association for coming to speak to our 6th graders about unhealthy eating pract… https://t.co/OishSFqnBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Ronna: guess who’s self-kicking his own ass? Al Franken. In the mass hysteria over the me too moveme… https://t.co/UIq3swoNb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFugelsang I started a support group for Erectile Dysfunction and no one came either!!😉😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haleystamey @PlayOsmo @BuncombeSchools Love it, those apps make me happy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning to all the little black boys you are handsome and blessed 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Golden Corral team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/LurMIl2PlV #CustomerService #Jacksonville, NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGno2trump I ysincerely doubt they see anything ironic given that would indicate a modicum of thought and analysi… https://t.co/brs7vb5kmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in awe of @beyondchron’s intellectual humility. We need a LOT more of that to get this crisis handled. We need… https://t.co/CmDobTYqAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fab shortlist of #wines by the glass carpentershallatx, particularly the #ThierryLandry #Chinon &amp; #BodegaPonce… https://t.co/zeDMGclEsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@howloften @JackLam42356343 @Debc14462368 @Wtg4Gateau @LandorMelanie @martinlovessto1 @vixmcintyre @TheSithChicken… https://t.co/CXKrGyyYeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clayarmstrong03 Hey remember when you used to work for free? Can we do that again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would just say thank u a million times because my brain wouldn’t work. Literally what happened at the concert at… https://t.co/Swot2ZDrbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[A glimpse of Sioux Falls, South Dakota... flat, wide open spaces, and snow at another whole level from Ohio!!  We e… https://t.co/U3BbGuFCUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 5 year #laanniversary to me on 3/3 🌞🌴💗 So grateful to my friend Laura for housing me when I first drove out s… https://t.co/XXwY2bh1au]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marketing friends - take note. Working with and for @MusaTariq is game changing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CybelNfotd I just had to get my DVR replaced and lost my recording of this movie (and it never comes on tv!). I am very sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reversemylove1 @RickyPDillon HE DID OMG IM HONESTLY CRYING KEEP ON KEEPIN ON GIRL YOULL GET LOVE SOON FROM THEM BU… https://t.co/udHquP0asn]]></document><document><![CDATA[due to personal reasons I will be spending all of my money at Starbucks &lt;3 &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/81fX2QX4BQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not ready to give this up for the snow @ The Cliffs https://t.co/JEwnO9btEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist my daughter @jackieroseb finds the best 👍💯 https://t.co/VGTDNmK3US]]></document><document><![CDATA[The production designer who just won an Oscar for “Black Panther” looks awesomely beautiful in that red dress!  A g… https://t.co/KU2HZQFuhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna be where the people are. ~Ariel The Little Mermaid   Not everything is always what it seems... What’s your… https://t.co/eTMbmFm3sv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Il ne faut pas juste être d’accord. Il faut agir et c’est ce que je demande à nos politiciens. @JeanBottari, vous a… https://t.co/TcGe6X7jpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xavier7191 @wess413 @MAGAdrumpf @joolzy71 @DKHiggs_Boson @JedRose17 @realDonaldTrump If Trump said the sky was gre… https://t.co/5JJouCXCsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0htayl0r No. Brakes are your cars first line of safety, they may work now but fail later. Especially if brakes are… https://t.co/Lj3bmQBm3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love Empathy and Respect at the Women and People of Color panel brought to you by #mustangsUnited https://t.co/bWU1sKrzkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnPersichilli But it’s a hell of a workout. Getting the mail has never burned so many calories]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz martes.  Que bella esta trinitaria, me encantan, 😍😘❤️💋 ojalá las mias se ok Agar así de Bellas 🙏😘 @ Dolphin M… https://t.co/Pp6J5teiBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Biebercome2me YES AMEN TO THAT we certainly don't and we definitely won't put up with it either ENOUGH IS ENOUGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this #girls #cat #handbag in my Etsy shop #etsyaaa https://t.co/g8iKUaPNcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey pal, your US$ 20.00 cash 💰 💰 💰 reward is here! Click to collect it in 3 minutes or it will expire! 🔥 https://t.co/GcSoWpFURv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson Climate change is not difficult to understand. You either believe it, or you’re stupid m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog ate almost $100 worth of shoes this week, told her to Venmo me by today.... I’m still waiting 🙄😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrTravis197 @BackJoeker @salemhoopcats Great example of evidence &amp; reasoning backing up your claim!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EsriEPC you needed to be here to hear this.  This is just for you partners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Franciscan of the Day is the lady on muni who just spontaneously high fived my dog.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems early in the day for toe sucking but everyone is different https://t.co/xlQF0vroLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[True...but WHEN is he going to be investigated and brought to justice! @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump @VP… https://t.co/jxJ0sA2Otc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Counting down to @NCCE_EdTech Conference! Excited to share about some pretty amazing accessibility tools!… https://t.co/LjafK2QqSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeNewsToo They need to completely separate the 2 businesses to get any money for women’s care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @noahh8ter !! Thanks for being an awesome friend, I hope you had the best day! ps love the hair😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hoffa8 @MrsRabbitResist @LMAO_in_Fla Looks like the dog was pushed in too. 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guerrero_rachel was doing my makeup and I swear I almost snapped my own neck cuz I kept dozing off 😂 but my makeup… https://t.co/IUp8XAkSOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheldon51955542 @JedRose17 @realDonaldTrump Lol naw brah, we have our own mess]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump explicou que o principal motivo da falta de acordo foi que Kim Jong Un queria todas as sanções retirad… https://t.co/mTKd9ZiKXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We appreciate tour #leadership @MaricelCabahug.  @sap @SAPradio #WomenLeaders #womenintech #womeninstem #SDGs… https://t.co/sM0waDlR9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiest of birthdays to one of the best in the biz AND one of my favorite people...the ever-generous @billritter7!… https://t.co/hPAS9ipd7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[To reporters in the field and anyone who has to work outdoors, stay safe and warm out there! #onsnow #ONstorm… https://t.co/THUlrlO7Bx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLBriscoe @suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy @cazij @JackConnie @thatsVeryKari @ja2cook @CaraMiaSG @ccatmpt @simplysallyh… https://t.co/WL3RZCRakf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one reason why Black infants are born with low birth weights and other prenatal issues. Black mothers worry… https://t.co/eOZpzrHb6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder what he’d do if he found his parents were first cousins. I mean. I’m not saying. But I’m saying.   ... possi… https://t.co/ylCzL9FKbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrPryority You’re in the hospital for days at a time. There is nothing wrong with this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYSE my money's on King. What a pic. What a dog. What a city. #WKCDogShow #bestinshow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poetry I cannot survive on follow or unfollow. I cannot survive on followback. I can survive when you order anyone… https://t.co/Cc4AkblCCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great evening at The Bald Headed Bistro getting a peek of what’s coming with SpringBoard... very exciting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[words can’t describe how happy i am but maybe this pic can https://t.co/llnEIa3bfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep in mind, I don’t agree with much of the third or fourth wave feminism. I’m not a radical liberal. I align with… https://t.co/LciJPA2YS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off to Costa Rica! (@ LaGuardia Airport in East Elmhurst, NY) https://t.co/WruBLWkvmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your Facebook/insta/twit bio says “loving wife, awesome mother...” etc., you’re probably none of those things 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DazPhd @replicantpinky @SuspiciousDuck5 Happy Weekend 🙌 https://t.co/q7M8onO1yb]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG. Shouldn't the producers of #TheBachelor have an on-site therapist for #Colton or any other program participant… https://t.co/9uMF9vfy2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gross old man told me to “smile” at the bar tonight so yeah, I’ll be up seething for the rest of the night and into tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol. Dropped my dinner right outside my apartment, went in my room and cried until jason decided to go get us more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC of course he has .not because it’s a bad bill just because it is Democrat’s.tired of the games]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just upset at the fact that main campus keeps having snow days while I am across the country!!! Keep that same energy next winter boy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjoseph7777 @dscc @dccc @realDonaldTrump Crimes has been in plain sight for this two to three years, those with eyes 👀 can testify to it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @sxdoc @ArchKennedy @karli_bonne @Rbigzs @RoseDC11 @dybarb @heyitsCarolyn @BRella315 @PauWitkowski… https://t.co/pyMxthvmPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luke5SOS if you follow me back my parents are going to let me go to three shows on the tour this year and i need t… https://t.co/Eczud7uywn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do NOT have any more openings this week 😅  The Prosperous Hair Artist @Dime_WineFine  💎✅  Thanks to all who have… https://t.co/YvpZe3WxCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌱MINDFULNESS🌱 . Thinking back on my trip to Muir Woods, the main thing that stuck with me was how PEACEFUL the fore… https://t.co/kNSgqTtl9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@citeblackwomen Arkansas State Senator Stephanie Flowers Standing Her Ground!]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG!! @devobrown @DinaPugliese and  @rogerfpetersen "breakdancing" on @BTtoronto is just what I needed this morning😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyPurdy Good Morning and I hope you have a great start of your week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just promise me that no matter what happens u will always be by my side 🤞🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_shutupmeg THANK YOU. Shit like that only takes a hit on your self esteem if you let it. Don’t let it lol. It’s th… https://t.co/ENTRjAmkMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[u know how crazy u sound to go out ur way to lurk on someone page to call them crazy? weirdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonandmichelleg excited to have you join the East family, looking forward to meeting you! 🎼🦅💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 59: The best of friends since Kindergarten. (The mamas too.) They know maria.schreibs so well, and her mama. Th… https://t.co/2LMYkzMjh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommamia1217 @CNN Quit watching CNN when they continued to give idiots like Rick Santorum a platform to spew their lies/garbage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SON of a BITCH episode 5 made me cry a little bit. (Why isn’t this one called “The Immigration Project”?)   Fine, I guess I’m in it now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no difficulty believing every single word @MichaelCohen212 is saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New goal is to be consistent with taking my vitamins everyday and increase my daily intake since I’m malnourished af let’s see how this goes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Via @SanandoVE Favor compartir ! en Broward County, Florida https://t.co/ffiMM8REIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DateLa #DateLosAngeles #DateLAX #travelcompanion #travelgf #companionship #adultconla #adultcon https://t.co/yyGUucDC4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LivePD dad-gum it’s been a crazy night on the show tonight. @danabrams, it’s been #Wicked CRAZY 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can build the wall AND have El Chapo pay for it... @tedcruz's #ELCHAPOAct is how. Stand with Ted Cruz and add yo… https://t.co/TymqYMLErM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the loml @whittramsey !!! thank you cleaning up my “mess” at abbeys😬and being the best person ever, ily🤩💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all think i didn’t notice a netflix film about an indigenous mexican woman that has its underlying commentary on… https://t.co/wGtRL6j8x5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMollieMarti @ResilienceInst I'm looking rather too shy in that pic! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning and happy Thursday. This morning inspiration for you and food for thought truly 🕉🐉 @ Lawnton, Pennsylv… https://t.co/o9Gy3ti1mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Walmart Neighborhood Market in Cary, NC https://t.co/mXNkPQKwFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@graujailene  tells her Garfield to calm down when she sees a guy she thinks is cute 😂😂 “calm down little kitty cat” 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Groundwork for Trump/Flynn/Russia/Saudi Nuclear Plans... #RickPerry #Oops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusieO Can we not mention Memorial Day...that's when my buy season really kicks in and I know I won't have the staff to handle it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi, what about the male, white, religious property owner that stuck around for like ever?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisarinna @lovinmybuseeli1 @IamNicollette This is the authentic Rhinna, great come back!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mitch just watches Gordon Ramsay roast people anytime he has 2 minutes to himself]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve only ever had one of those, and he ain’t even in my life no more smh:/]]></document></documents></author>