<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It happens dear! You seems to be a strong young lady!!! Stay focus! God gotcha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fabmorvan @streetlife Goog evening from here @fabmorvan and @streetlife today I have been working with The Arts In… https://t.co/ssVOVNhcRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[With God on my side, I am unstoppable! 🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾🏃🏾‍♀️🏃🏾‍♀️🏃🏾‍♀️💯💥 https://t.co/qdxhCveqmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A recent project at work had us digging thru the archives to find this epic moment in Bulls history. I won’t lie, m… https://t.co/aDlQtnx8WP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best to stay Centered...We have enough Whackos! ... And to think any SANE Person would vote for Bernie with Today's… https://t.co/c7Ax2qMlVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[U made it THIS FAR through things you thought u wouldn’t get through... keep going, U GOT THIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noah and the boys killed it tonight!! Go to his page and like his music! You'll thank me later. Meeting the parents… https://t.co/3MWTJlw2XC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theslumflower my 20s are dedicated to becoming the pond that has no choice but to overflow.  the love i exude will… https://t.co/UQjN4Gm3uc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love 💕 this beach house. Who wants to stay here next time you visit LA??? @shuttersca @StacyHopeSmall #elitetravel… https://t.co/l26Cp7CfL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardA_Esq Oh my, and you’re an attorney? You can’t even get the facts right on this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bae 🤩🤤🤤🤤🤤 Drop a 🤤 if you love me below 👇🏽👇🏽 👄 #AshleyNicole #atlpics #josephinelounge @ Josephine Lounge https://t.co/KlMXtcqq2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby living his best life!! At the hotel!!❤️🥰😘😘😘😍 Such a cutie!! 💙 https://t.co/fhIBm8AvP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next sober show is on 3/23. Save the date! 🏄🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/JSIbeODmP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UndercoverAbc @thelisavidal @ItsCarlosGomez @ItsCarlosGomez is the one who shot nina @LunaLaurenVeIez , the scean… https://t.co/UtLWMtK4yq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at all those beautiful souls showing off their limitless talent!!! 💜💜 @RonnieVillines @Jill713 @Alisheez]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1: Social emotional learning is managing emotions, having empathy and establishing healthy relationships. It is al… https://t.co/fCzOItUoqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTomme2 @WarrenShaver @STEPHMHAMILL @RashidaTlaib @LynnePattonHUD @RepMarkMeadows He was literally convicted on ch… https://t.co/2MkQKakXVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[posted the picture i got with niall yesterday on IG and got almost 1,000 likes and over 60 followers 😂 whaaattt https://t.co/GNTcRjXybx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonEuler9 @Ekonovah wooooo!!! i’ll be pouring your drinks LETS PARTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am really waiting for @danitheproblem  to open up here appointment book for April... cause I’m going to NYC and need to book her!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wrapped up a fab event with our new and amazing RDMs!! Celebrating a great week with a classic… https://t.co/7Pt7eUroOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday academy (@ Kenner Disvovery Health Science Academy in Kenner, LA) https://t.co/rnIxyog8Ph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch 🖕🏾&amp; the rest of yo crew 👯‍♀️🤣‼️ I’ll take yo nigga &amp; keep mines too 🕺🏾💃🏽🕺🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diego Chara gets a yellow, *now* the season has started. #RCTID https://t.co/QkIKTGU66A]]></document><document><![CDATA[That view. #mountains #parkcity #parkcityutah #snowy #pinetree #clearskies @ Park City, Utah https://t.co/xwdvUPvSlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are sore feet a sign of a good conference? Thanks @the_PDAC ! #pdac2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaleeJr6589 @kylejgood He wouldn’t do it either. I’ll just die I guess]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is comic. Soapy Shoot: Bubbles and babies! Fold up some soft and squishy washcloths behind your bug’s head... https://t.co/PwMHsgha6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[my car has the perfect spot to hold my sauce while i eat nuggets and drive :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/27/19 Wednesday 8-10 CST I'm speaking with Joshua Fleming of Vandoliers! @vandoliers have an Amazing Album Out No… https://t.co/AUyB81IL7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked @lea_greeen to come to super Saturday and told her it was April 27th and she said “wait what day of the wee… https://t.co/NlSBcuFsPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ross_Quintana #adobechat  experiential marketing = emotional content https://t.co/x5jlyQrPgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t know the Jonas Brothers fan side of me, you probably don’t know me at all. It was a LIFESTYLE and it’s… https://t.co/8WPfOpFIsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing more nauseating than when you’re sick and having to take care of people who are also sick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tone81571751 @complicated78 @ellievan65 @KaleJPhoto Yes asshole's are global 😠 https://t.co/47ILkXGI6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parham_vs_drama @TitosVodka I plan on making a special mule tonight! Raspberry or blackberry? Decisions...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimmiepearlman @alijsch @aliciakrop @k8rasman @PhilanthropyInk I’m thinking about getting a winter home in San Die… https://t.co/IH1jbVZodm]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will this #cough GO AWAY!😤 it’s been like 3 weeks https://t.co/XFutON1ao9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to New Haven Unified School District for hosting Joint Meeting with Ohlone Community College District. Ve… https://t.co/fBnIfliijW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some things don’t work out &amp; that’s okay. Just gotta move forward 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck Lady Bronchos! FLY HIGH AND STICK IT!! https://t.co/xn7seltBnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am deeply committed to a life of #beauty in body, mind, and spirit and sharing that to inspire, empower, and igni… https://t.co/HBpa9qJIxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DirtyOldSneaker @nycmarathon It felt like a 26.2 mile block party celebration!!  So much positive energy and happiness everywhere I looked!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching a blast from the past with a Blast From the Past #aliciasilverstone #BrendanFraser https://t.co/bMc5undRat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Snowcat27379323 I’m trying! My sister who has a sixth sense just called and let me just ramble and cry! Im propped… https://t.co/whX78nPD1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhoneyman @mjs_DC Right. Clarence Thomas was a key reason why GHW Bush’s farewell was for some of us necessarily m… https://t.co/xC21e8llzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@windh1 @Pattilee359 @belcherjody1 @Jayhawker4Trump @TXbonniejean @Kfuller8870 @my3monkees @hoppinmama5… https://t.co/0j0cE2rven]]></document><document><![CDATA[When attendance is mandatory but all the professor does is read off of a PowerPoint that you have access to from ho… https://t.co/ABUL8ZzLOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandma always looking out for me. Grandmas know best 💁🏼‍♀️ 😂😂😂 https://t.co/nH9djjEmZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alanmac_d @hometownhockey_ @NHL Yup-typing too fast and posting before ☕️.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Motivation Monday!!!! 💪👈  #everybodysfit #personaltrainer #fitnessmodel @ Every BODY's Fit https://t.co/401dR4qosp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meghan McCain and AOC should go bowling in matching pink satin jackets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't listen to this theme anymore without getting emotional as fuck. The people I met in the #LandDownUnder trul… https://t.co/p7yDV6mGby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hugs from Mr Mac are so special that they almost made me forget I’ve been crying all day. Night out at the SLC Star… https://t.co/Hk1BJOVEq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robert_E_Kelly The bar is so very low.  'No rambling, seems sane. Much better!']]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is coming along with the exception of minor details for @ArrowheadUW Women United luncheon this Thursday… https://t.co/vNl87Hzsq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacharyLevi now that you have the wisdom of Solomon, would you ever consider going on celebrity jeopardy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsaiahOnThaRox @peta I completely agree. Bashing a DEAD man at that! They are such a complete joke.,]]></document><document><![CDATA[My school had Multicultural Night tonight. Greatness!! such a beautiful celebration of diversity. #WeareWhitt… https://t.co/J7AfuL8BlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[People make fun of my semi-secret fandom for lil BUB, but she’s actually contributing to science.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedState Must be the Democrats who are not running for office, this woman is nuts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veronica Castro #ChiquitaPeroPicosa #MalaNocheNo  1er Show #TempoNightClub en Tempo https://t.co/rPSAvI0rJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LadyGaGa may have a point that people who want tabloid info, SM is no better than the tabloids, But people who are… https://t.co/kB4Prxhv2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You know very well they have you dead to rights.  The time will come when the time is right.  For… https://t.co/XACnyUI0w1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gator36b I dunno. Those all sound like pretty good snacks to me, not punishment food at all.   https://t.co/RocQ19Gngy]]></document><document><![CDATA[JObs individual's responsible Couldn't sleep a night RIGHT Knowing its screems many didnt do their job as eligibili… https://t.co/OF2HamZFHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaPustorino @APeijer @AthanasiaTrian1 @NancySimonds1 @LiseNilsson2 @odyssey158 @Pennyyo79 @LilleS80 @gandusio… https://t.co/bnNBMkcOej]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes i’m aware fsu has one but the one on kendall and 162nd hits different]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next NAMIC Detroit event is March 14!  Looking forward to the networking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inbox me if you’d like to make some real and quick cash up to $300 per hour. #sugarbabyneeded #sugardaddytwitter… https://t.co/IkrDjnlsiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @SenSchumer you are a BIG FAT LIAR! In years past you lobbied for BORDER SECURITY! TODAY YOU REFUSE TO… https://t.co/rQqYIlNXLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TasteOfCountry Gilligan's Island. .Hogan's Heroes ... Brady Bunch ... Petticoat Junction ... Johnny Quest... Dark Shadows]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to meet the incredible #MIEExpert folks coming to #Paris for #E2. Hello from Microsoft in Washington!… https://t.co/xtMC9LdZgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreneBrown Honesty &amp; Compassion (and curiosity if there was a 3rd)]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY MIN YOONGI💓😩 #MinYoongi #2ndbias https://t.co/rQOWhOTbkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morten @realDonaldTrump Should tell you something like what the world thinks of him. Maybe if he was in Russia or… https://t.co/MwjupeT6pp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatWokeAuntie @tenacious_O @magi_jay @ShimonPro Smh tenacious you intentionally twisted my words and omitted the… https://t.co/j1RdSxPb8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc what the articles say, Winnie the Pooh will always be male to me. @ElvisDuranShow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scot23 ... or at least you are both insinuating that Black voters are too ignorant to use paper ballots or that we… https://t.co/hNPlYOYZB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love my bff so much, i’m so blessed to have such an amazing friend like Kam and i feel like i don’t say that enough 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wrist hurts because the fucking smith machine was so hard to turn last night]]></document><document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once... https://t.co/D1VT4xEA7V via @BrainyQuote]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always forget to dance 😭 https://t.co/lcfw744b3E https://t.co/K9mKgAOYxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of y’all bitches out here hiding y’all kids from the world and not the world from ya kids smh 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isolated in open space, athleticism beats skill as surely as rock beats scissors. The question becomes how to devel… https://t.co/NsaSaTlHm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrFilmkritik @CiCi77 Don't those naked pictures of her modeling with other women prove she had "extraordinary abilities"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahcalverley To be fair, it’s from 2016, but I only just found out about this cool wall yesterday! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but if you don’t take your huge ass backpack off during rush hour on the subway, you shouldn’t be allowed… https://t.co/3rLw5VmpbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YerkDiff @ChrisRGun I was attacked by the truth of a knight and it is a knight of a good night. ...what]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianwest210 @shallah1164 @chiquibon2 @ChuckCallesto @tedcruz Call him I just did! I’m his constituent!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously just dropped $$$ from two stores 😅😔 one store was an impulse too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh GW, go back to your premise of the “weapons of mass destruction” BS that you used to get us into a still currren… https://t.co/z64kqxfMjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK. So.. It is looking gloomy in Jacksonville at the moment. Anything to do that doesn't involve me getting my tan on?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters No. My. God. I’m not even going to repeat what I think McCain would say. Although, I think that barber is… https://t.co/RXEgCgfOcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when "Siri Suggestions" suggests that you send a text to someone who wants nothing to do with you anymore 😆😛😚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Docsociology4 I don't think she's the sharpest pencil in the box.  I think she rides daddy's shirttails without th… https://t.co/3aLby4aWyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is clever. senior pictures for boys | have been fun to shoot. Sis came along on her big... #humor #tee-hee… https://t.co/W8AUtxuJeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you check out Lauren DeMaio on Spotify, you will find that she is an artist looking to “bridge the gap” that sep… https://t.co/lHbtVzgPta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPAIN I'm literally in tears 😭 please start putting music out with your natural voice, I cant get enough of it ❤❤❤… https://t.co/WmiYOdxIRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here comes the snow.  We are running out of places to put it.  I have a few suggestions where Mother Nature can "put" it.]]></document></documents></author>