<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Joe Rogan Experience #1258 - Jack Dorsey, Vijaya Gadde &amp; Tim Pool https://t.co/1hX0nPlrSQ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepBobGibbs Weak and foolish questions. You embarrassed yourself. It is obvious that you do not have the mental ca… https://t.co/gjDt4BWqFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[What kills me is when people get upset at the train for being a train. Like the train strategically learned your sc… https://t.co/Mj4KEXdWjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@In2theshadow @TheWave0079 @KayTravel @JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/lTbj00XtmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a busy time in the Bay Area. My review of #Monet show at @deYoungMuseum. https://t.co/1dGh2kLGmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteaknShake @jpvogt How, exactly, will you "use" this? Will it be a catalyst to genuine reflection and recalibrati… https://t.co/P4gRoh6uup]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworkers:  Me: It really just comes back to capitalism being violent and exploitative, the boss is not your friend, you know real commu-]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SundayToday Thst Reporter Is Wrong I Was In Vail, Colorado In 2011 It’s A Vacation When You Were Away From Home]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DadFiction @JannaKilimnik @MommedRealHard @jaxwax04 @Beagz @KristinaNadia @TwinzerDad @MelissaBeagley @sah_bsn_rn… https://t.co/8lgSHUpOpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asolorz01 @driversofnyc I like this simple install and design. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher Is your needle stuck on that record? What is wrong with you and attacking religion? Sounds pretty juveni… https://t.co/VifjDDW4Uw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Batusi_Hero @StarTrek I was ecstatic when Crystal Pepsi came back.  I loved it in the 90’s and was glad I was I wa… https://t.co/ek1yhVgiAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Referee sure spoiled an exciting finish @ManUtd @Arsenal with a very very soft #Arsenal penalty. .#tiredofdivers  2-0]]></document><document><![CDATA[10C District Tournament 3rd place GBB.  End of 3.  GF Central 46, Cascade 13.  #mtscores @406mtsports… https://t.co/XIpDtce08Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cammy Recovery Update: Started calling her "Pumpkin" lately on account of the orange/black romper, and she seems to… https://t.co/L3Kxv2pYQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the rock versions of “Without me” by Halsey are amazing. I can’t pick between them all. That’s my favorite thin… https://t.co/n8tFcsDUKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeltzVegas paid watch parties or wandering with a betting app the better way to experience #marchmadness ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is how I was before but roy made me try tomatoes and now I like them 🥵😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGreatStorm @mmpadellan @LCNM99 @realDonaldTrump @GovIvey I'm one o'the fuckers DummyDummy2x4 warns you about-I… https://t.co/CcOr7Sfv6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Christ’s teachings. Too bad evangelicals don’t. American politics and society would be better if they did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is dancing while 29,000 plus are without jobs. If I was one of her constituents I would be busy pointing out he… https://t.co/jF5zpfRdnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had my one useable hand full. Kicked a door open to go through it. Wind blew it back shut as I was going through in… https://t.co/BUCRji1RPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kozmiccc @DatGuyAris Lmao bro how are you in our conversation ? You have 6 followers go outside and stop being weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Colossus Festival Kick Off at Piano’s: HNRY FLWR #newcolossusfestival #newcolossusfestivalkickoff #pianos… https://t.co/Hr0puATRPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go follow my dog REACE YUNG,he’s a very influential rapper from the STL and he be spitting that 🔥 @ St. Louis https://t.co/jGmrusI6jh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm a huge fan of SciFi movie's @ Chicago metropolitan area https://t.co/RngeX9EptT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarryLHouser @IlliniMBB @wdws1400 @whms975 @Learfield Ready to bring one home from a true road game. Go @IlliniMBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Seperate but Equal,” “Finish the Wall,” “Manifest Destiny,” and other efforts in America’s history have always tur… https://t.co/msdddtkWkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SurfinjJoel @afireinside35 What the Lakers and @KingJames will look like the rest of the @NBA season. Next year th… https://t.co/IIRvIX8J0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be signing my union card next week and will be the newest member of Local70. Happy to work for an organizati… https://t.co/RFJh8t9cLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una cerveza bien fría para las mujeres por ser la perfección. ❤️🤠 #LaCervezaMásFina]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraRedgate @Lrihendry @JoeBiden Joe Biden, is a anti American SOB. He should never be allowed to hold office in America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminiscing them nights in the Beamer💔 #longlivegohtenks https://t.co/pA9rpg1x8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling ALL AZ women’s AAU teams... this is one of the best events in the nation - come showcase your talents in fr… https://t.co/CPxeHm872Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@virginia_garret I read that book and liked it. https://t.co/8TNppxdR9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[By clearing out the overgrowth of underbrush and smaller trees, the landscape will return to a state closer to the… https://t.co/AfuvgsUcbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[R.I.P To The People Who Died In The Station Nightclub Fire 🔥 Back In February Of 2003. Real Talk 123.… https://t.co/qWT2WAYPqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Responses exactly what you expect.  “What if...IF Brock Boeser isn’t a cornerstone franchise player but just a real… https://t.co/i5iH0xm4G8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@welcomet0nature Absolutely a beautiful video! A nice change from the trumpers attacking me! Sorry trumpers, but I’… https://t.co/4fS3QN7owy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#impayingit4ward “Friends who slay together, stay together💍😌” Thank you for being awesome and posting this great pi… https://t.co/n3ZDZ0WKpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome stuff Pastor. We need this out in the MSM so the brainwashed can hear the TRUTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pbump 10 term congress members don't need to make political splashes. Their inability to question well is because… https://t.co/5Bg6G8mq2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praise be to the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ! In his great mercy he has given us new birth into a livin… https://t.co/k7dpD1ioMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#skillednursinglife Watching the final days of Mike Trout as an Angel. #angelsbaseball #rebuild #tradetrout #OC… https://t.co/5Q7sUK0iUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[He needs to trademark "Spread Love" and "The Brooklyn Way" while he's at it...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandsmartin WHO DA HELL IS DIS...All that hand slappin she know she fucked up]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happened to that little elf?  I thought he went back to work for Keebler.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted to personally that the First Lady of Florida! Ms. Casey was engaging and really cared about not just the c… https://t.co/6SaywM3ful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickydirtyjames @nhlbecca Stay Strong? Isn’t professional sports a business? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimkerr1961 @KT_thomps @chrislhayes Who has that thought after a still born death?  Oh, right, the pro life party!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joerogan Alex needs to be the next agent in the next transformers movie thats what he reminds me of but he's hilar… https://t.co/rnAjL4tBJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a stunner! Amazing views from @killingtonmtn today. #killington #skisunday #skiing #snowtime @ Killington, Ver… https://t.co/1HZvOkugXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The idols of the nations are silver and gold, made by human hands. They have mouths, but cannot speak, eyes, but ca… https://t.co/ncnZEnNJ8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[As @PHXStartupWeek winds down, #entrepreneurs have been integral to @CityofPhoenixAZ's growth to the fifth-largest… https://t.co/yVTosDx2LU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evening service with my family at Midtowne Church. Continuing the series: Without. #Midtowne #Without @MidtowneChurch @dougpruitt @crollpoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muni bus strikes, injures pedestrian near Balboa Park BART - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/LzMW1TUD15 💭🔁♥️ @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescurtin @ufc Agree, but it won’t happen unless it’s a PPV.  This card is going to stream on ESPN +.  So it won… https://t.co/bBv6TvpPX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course I would be out of town for #NationalPetDay yesterday   Miss this guy but I know he is in good hands https://t.co/9w1DA4Zt2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsBreak You should follow their lead. Hint, hint.🤷🏻‍♂️ #UK #Labour #JeremyCorbyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arivium1 @WrestleCade They're under WWE contract and won't be in Winston Salem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Felix_Sicard It's really curious that Buffalo was so anxious to trade Guhle and a war round pick for Montour, and… https://t.co/r46gVWp5WT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevin_harold01 Tim Tebow: 14.   Therefore: Tim Tebow &gt; MJ and Lebron combined.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was today years old when I realized I was 23 when this song came out. 😐 #fakefan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnottah @9975Ts Pelosi your days are numbered! https://t.co/875N1kSFrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one bet with @Legend_X_today , @LT_Picks he's not paying the bets he owes. Pathetic calls himself a bookie/cappe… https://t.co/fU0jgGcOJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s some more Art Deco in downtown Tulsa! #becomeanarchitect #alanrphotography #soyoywanttobeanarchitect… https://t.co/TUpPfIzHXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogelioSierraD @marti160patria Sigue creyendo que el hambre y la miseria toca a menos , imbecil !]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Fighting tyrranical regimes,” @Morning_Joe ? Really? Like Chile, Guatemala, and Iran? I think the #Palestinian peo… https://t.co/wE7fZAtOs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iceland is going to kill 2,000 whales. Stop them. - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/ac3iFHNh23 via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drew_Davis32 Why do I continue to end up at Aldean’s on a Saturday night when I can afford to go to LA Jackson? The world may never know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattymcclelland Splinters gained in defense or your kingdom are justified]]></document><document><![CDATA[“So now faith, hope, and love abide, these three; but the greatest of these is love.” 1 Corinthians 13:13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AneezaBilal @ChuckModi1 The Washington Post is BS? I read her statement questioning the loyalty of Israel supporti… https://t.co/wHy1fHNJpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made it a point to tell her she was the best &amp; to keep modeling. She almost hugged me 😢😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si están los Madridistas que madrugaron para ver el papelón de su equipo😂🤣😂😂🤣😂🤣Atención @oleimi1 👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼 https://t.co/Cxs8TPamk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#foofighters #walkingafteryou #acceptsurrender #guitar #gibsonj45 #gibson #acoustic @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/VCVGcF2nP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @mikethemiz @shanemcmahon @WWEUsos @WWEUniverse After #EliminationChamber ends Tune in w/ OVER 5K+ #WWE FANS r… https://t.co/Tpl837bmPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@godsonjreid @ZuluPanther @Fanonian @son_of_malcolm Same way Jews do it. They identify with a homeland. Build that… https://t.co/3HJamm8x9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you..bitch.. I’m never gonna stop loving you.. BITCH  #dejavoom https://t.co/hsgoHRwixK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheldonAYS @HarrisonKM @michaelmcarver @DirtySouth1982 @gregolsen88 @antwanstaley @BarackObama @dukebasketball… https://t.co/m4IUTeojOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I turned 22 when he was born. This guy has the greatest disposition And one hell of a voice. Something tells me he’… https://t.co/szUsY1mNNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[OBTW did I happen to mention that she is @AmericanAir #ExecutivePlatinum? #DYKWIA 🙄🙄🙄 #FirstClass #DL5246]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somos tan pequeños y nos creemos los dueños de todo el mundo... "Si la vida total de la tierra se comprimiera en un… https://t.co/ttDuts3ZTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Walmart Neighborhood Market in Kissimmee, FL https://t.co/ibzUWUAhal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump That tub of excrement made you stop using your maiden name because he doesn’t like… https://t.co/FCz9Lv3CHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Businesswoman beheaded after husband 'wouldn't pay' ransom |  https://t.co/P9gnHki7zG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricaBrecher Great story on Cuomo and North Carolina-the NYS students should not be inconvenience-and genetically… https://t.co/BnIrNeP3t1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 20th annual @981WKDD "HAVE A HEART DO YOUR PART" Radiothon benefiting @AkronChildrens starts at 6a and goes unt… https://t.co/Q3mNHokNTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tem dois dias que o cesto sumiu! A becha ainda mandou msg pra todos dizendo que agora não tem como esquecer mais. O… https://t.co/Qz7Tm4gUL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panic at the disco was actually so good. I can’t believe I’m tweeting about it but I had to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterbakernyt We can only hope he keeps eating those healthy hamburgers with a large order of fries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday morning... #cumberlandstreet #verticalcityscape #cityscape #verticallandscape #landscape… https://t.co/ybn59exbOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connor Hellebuyck and Sergei Bobrovsky lead their respective teams out the ice for the pre-game warm-up. So that's… https://t.co/b9zmcIJ4TK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PNemiroff I’m so glad you liked @captainmarvel! I thought @brielarson, @SamuelLJackson, and @BenMendelsohn_ did in… https://t.co/oZImZS6kmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're on the elliptical and lose track of time with your favorite playlist  . . . . #unintentional10k… https://t.co/JpEkglUUjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris @Clancy_1 ain't nearly enough lady.  Is that how you would have reacted to the Nazi regime? You fail… https://t.co/naIzBUfEdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchPotterf advances to the semis with a quarter final pin!! @WNHS_Wrestling #WeAreWarriors 🤼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching republicans post on social media about the snow in Arizona is just fucking hilarious because they are stil… https://t.co/fgqR5AyDbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Problem is, we have had peace since mid-1950 and now Kim will be able to negotiate… https://t.co/LjGnoL3jvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoDucks @OregonWBB @KDTrey5 @nikebasketball #Cancer we crush your power in the name of Jesus and we commanded you… https://t.co/yA3v7N2ec7]]></document></documents></author>