<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What the actual F is Katie wearing on #WWHL right now ?! https://t.co/Tj3R9UlskE]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOR JEN: Results show that for APAP-S the recovery was 70-78% (Mother to Fetus), while for APAP-G the recovery was… https://t.co/1yqLiKP8mS]]></document><document><![CDATA[CAN WE GET THIS TO GO VIRAL?! Bet we won’t 😭Photographers where you at?! 📷 @Brandonwoelfel #photography… https://t.co/b0IBBVyV6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNC_Lineberger @angiesmith_uro @UNC @UNC_Health_Care Congratulations @angiesmith_uro!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueLionBlog @EmmaGPaley @ShopSmartResist @Narcolepsy_me @chrisvcsefalvay @ChrisJohnsonMD @doritmi @kidoctr… https://t.co/mZXTxVDJvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish there was a velnrines day card that said “I love when you talk that nerdy shit” @finneas I think you should… https://t.co/Y7zTLTaSmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump NOW THIS IS INFANTICIDE!! You should be held accountable for this child’s death!!… https://t.co/v88fP2XQfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Auburn’s Sylvia has a pair of shorts with foam padding on the crotch that she’s wearing for warmups, so if you ever… https://t.co/PQp3WdRDI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 year old or maybe 9 year old Kaylse’s double layer flounce skirt, a true labor of love and she persevered through… https://t.co/fnO7Bna16g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog @wenzitend Because that’s really going to happen! Meanwhile #LiarInChief  Donnie continues his assault… https://t.co/OoDtvlcAeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapehartJ If you aren't kicked out of the Governor's mansion, you won't get a second term.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DJohnsonPGA And this is relevant to the governance of the country, how?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy how you can feel such a profound connection to someone you’ve never actually physically met in this life. Hum… https://t.co/3BErh8OYpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@domlamberton @halihamilton I  said it looked like the interiors of Bar Raval]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Hickory, NC? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/mIvBoO8O6b #SupplyChain]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I have to hold something with my teeth, I have a small window of time before my body rejects this action… https://t.co/QVm2VRocNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is wild.@BlogChurchWork @DearAuntCrabby @DanRather @amvetsupport @B52Malmet @Headerop1 @tribelaw @JustaSlob… https://t.co/HUKCxTlAKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[But what got me was that whenever Ron denied his feelings for Kim my dad would be like “He’s a liar” 😂  It probably… https://t.co/r74e2oKjJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ningún proceso que carezca de progreso puede sostenerse por sí solo por mucho tiempo.  Mi ventana aquí con lo difíc… https://t.co/eF8qtARA5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jameelajamil Blocked him a few hours ago after this mess kept appearing on my feed, because all he really wants ar… https://t.co/Nokj53onuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw The Favourite &amp; it was super entertaining. The acting and the costumes were stellar.👌🏽 https://t.co/EXJxzM3q9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[people are really allowed to just log in and tweet anything they want huh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldretrieverUS  Who said carrots are just for rabbits? #Goldenretrievers #GRC #goldenretrieveruniversity… https://t.co/AH0wfs4Tap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lexi_r97 When we eventually go to Vegas they have these premade at one of their Taco Bell’s 😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesseleesoffer Love watching all Chicago Med, Chicago Fire, Chicago P.D.!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️💙💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lemonsteaa I love the way Scott immediately felt Tessa’s discomfort... his face changed and he prepared to try and… https://t.co/t4AGeI4RbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cahoho1 @ItsMeCathi @mayflower862 Hanging with the guy who had an American journalist chopped up...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all my niece won’t stop saying cat... it you know me at all you know this is very worrisome for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frostgirl11 @tweetNorvena @SourceRobert @AlliCamAllison @Danielle21A @OncerHardy @hjhollis93 @NGDAverk… https://t.co/eQdjOgFmCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Netflix is going to make a live action Babysitters Club based on the book series and my young heart is aflutter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E16_giacobone It’s tough being blonde when you’re naturally ash brown :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sluggishgotty @KPoopfeathers @SoufianYakoubi @realDonaldTrump Don’t get your hopes up! You will be disappointed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are getting more snow tomorrow! Many school districts will likely close or open late. We'll have the latest fore… https://t.co/vh917AJoGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[‼️GAMEDAY‼️  It’s your Lady Texans last home game tonight! Come out and show your love and support!🏀  🆚: Clarendon… https://t.co/epIQeqDpns]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m sorry to say it but Midnight Memories (Deluxe) was really One Direction’s best album based on “Diana” alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stan_sdcollins Prayers, love and support to you and your family, Stan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olgaNYC1211 @MalcolmNance The Russians pay a lot of politicians to go along with their agenda.  Some of these poli… https://t.co/XK0IA5CAAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 56% Off from Jody Steinmann at Mira Bella Salon and Spa https://t.co/U6mWVnkF8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greatersafety Thanks! It really makes sense from a whole lot of perspectives. It's not the dream house I was hopin… https://t.co/uJpPmq3eoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally back in the gym after 2 weeks of letting this ankle heal, feels good to be home!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dhinchcliffe @nyike @MosconeCenter @MylesSuer @waynesadin @jayferro @psalvitti @kyleejohnson @jcycio @S_dF @mzyw… https://t.co/vBs06fmSI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive even wondered if I’m ace/aromantic I’ve always been independent and never felt strongly about finding a partner… https://t.co/hPIbivLQQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliverEsFeliz @osofronio Claro! Esta formando a su criminal base electoral!!! Que terrible!  En lugar de protegern… https://t.co/nJdHlBu9oA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latest commercial for Maji Designs! #voiceactor https://t.co/3H3n0ZOrMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotTheChuckD Dope match. Furthers the Kofi vs Bryan at Mania story too]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may have gone in to work on my day off because the sausage is that good. #keto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyAlicea @snk_onlineshop Haha same. But if I win the lotto, all fgc homies are getting one 😹😹😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s apparent that some of the high end brands have marketed themselves in a way to discourage black customers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOR EVERYONE ASKING HOW: sarah drew is a family friend and surprised me with this for my 16th birthday!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommyrankin83 @PearlJam #GivenToFly #InsideJob  And baseball is right around the corner my friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Linkara19 Is that the one with the guy who gives himself the super evolution nanobots? That one ROCKS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessieJPyle Jessie I absolutely love connecting with you!  Grateful you had a take away from the session! #Nan3EDU… https://t.co/8ayGB6Uk1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GShapiro9News @9NEWS My dogs shorty on left and Danny on right showing support for my team and my orange tabby luc… https://t.co/w6i3UlwRtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen! Hire, pay, promote, and invest in women. ⚡⚡⚡   #allraise #IWD2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think all weekends should be 3 day weekends because #SundayFundays are the best. Thanks @icarus for the pretty ye… https://t.co/OdlTWg4Nkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[But my God shall supply all your need according to his riches in glory by Christ Jesus. https://t.co/bBYZiNjJUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida. 🥰 @ Orlando International Airport (MCO) https://t.co/Y0JHlttIiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ty_in_TX @SallyMayweather Me too - and people should be if they’re pro-death penalty as well. What a ridiculous argument.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So current, so historic. #TrumpCrimeFamily #GOPComplicit https://t.co/p8EY73FPNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me and start your day with Morning Brew, the email covering the latest news from Wall St. to Silicon Valley.… https://t.co/uKJik4HJlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @atticascott4ky for being an unapologetically allied with women, kids, teachers, public education, and co… https://t.co/guluxTLyrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[*is genuinely excited to see a cactus in the wild* @ Tempe, Arizona https://t.co/zuhXcRKFXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brothers imitating @SebastianComedy has to be the funniest thing I have ever witnessed 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FearlessRecords @WageWar Thank you so much! ❤️❤️❤️  Shoutout to you for having such amazing bands on your roster 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Starbucks for my #birthday drink!  And while it might seem like a “6 shot venti iced soy latte hold the… https://t.co/hdtxfsx5Gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funwithfielding @kaitlinwhitten @MsB_thechange This is so great! You’re 6th graders will love this!!! 👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showcase of how stupid leftists are.  Debunked and still continues to be pushed 👇👇👇]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unreysincorona_ @SpookySiku You havent MET met Siku. This is normal.   Last week she said "close your butt and shut your mouth"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister It’s not an easy thing to be dealing with severe mental illness in the public eye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lbrown05_laurie @mike_mnolan @GabiNolan Wish you were going to be there this weekend, I’d take your crazy a** with me😂😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brunch with some lovely ladies 🥂 @ Public House Food + Drink https://t.co/LMub0fUiu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want some CBD with your pizza? Check out my latest @statepress story to find out where you can get it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you want to just stay in on a snowy day, sit on the couch and watch @hallmarkchannel movies for hours.  But th… https://t.co/mF1vfnRAHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllKnightEmpire Thank god! Now I have to try to remember what size they are to get a portfolio to store them in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump thats great but her could have been the money for the wall and would not been a sweat off the DEMS… https://t.co/f9E4SrRePe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have very few thoughts on Lords of Chaos but all of of them are about the wigs and the varying degrees to which they work]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hurA0IJh9A👈👈👈 #BleachBattalion One inch #pins/#badges/#buttons are now available!!!! Show your… https://t.co/f3BeFHlC3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA, perdón quise decir, SIGUIENTE CLÁSICO POR FAVOR!!!! https://t.co/1WxqlOuWjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I’m trusting God to the fullest right now. Because I know my heart is to pure and my love to strong for my life… https://t.co/2pHfgptKOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m low on Vitamin Bruce today, and I wanted to share my supplement with anyone else who might need a Bruce Boost.… https://t.co/6a1iwWob1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo @DineshDSouza @SenBooker That's a change in his thinking.  What happened to guilty until proven innocent.  Hypocrite!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been following iamginabianca on Instagram for years and I was over the moon excited / anxious that she was b… https://t.co/16E0gWqmAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RSaulisbury @xoJillianJanson @thomaselliott19 You’re gorgeous @xoJillianJanson https://t.co/VX6asiEDLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpaceFartsOne @JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump Especially now since "his holiness" is signing bible's 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MiamiOHAccepted students, employers visit Miami looking for #QualityQualityQuality  students to hire.  Join… https://t.co/bdNEevZy8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was an honour to be included Jon.  This is such a great initiative you’ve created.   Best of luck on your broadc… https://t.co/ezJ44l7LtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ButNotTheCity There's nothing wrong with it being an ideal. It's my ideal. Its how the most accurate and perfect i… https://t.co/i7sWd8n77k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heroin. @Badflower #badflower #elrey #elreytheatre #okimsick #heroin #losangeles #la @ El Rey https://t.co/qcIbhtpx6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlwallen @KamalaHarris No.. stop that lie it does not fly. I pay my own insurance and with BCBSGA, try 160.00 a mo… https://t.co/CChzFFM5yQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to the @Starbucks on 66th &amp; 3rd playing Burnin Up by the Jonas Brothers. Made my bad day better 👌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wore my new glasses to school today and one of my kids was very concerned. At circle time, he raised his hand and… https://t.co/cqckFHESaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a friend to everyone who fears you, to anyone who obeys your orders. Psalm 119:63]]></document><document><![CDATA[These words&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; https://t.co/QLzSXThpTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should be the only way to solve disagreements.   @univisionsports ¡Qué duelo se vivió en las gradas! 👊 • • ¿Qu… https://t.co/UrkzDlPwH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It is ok. Don't feel sorry for us, feel sorry for them. More of us than them anyway]]></document><document><![CDATA[tell me i’m not the only one who really wanted them to say “live from LA, it’s the #AcademyAwards!”… https://t.co/UgoV1AyepC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be one of the good ones. @ True North Mediation https://t.co/9jxJ31LB8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had friends, but they all had such toxic personalities so i had to drop them from my life. now there’s no chance… https://t.co/VLFyDTvDkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heppoco01 my eye wanders to one boy... for some reason he seems... really nice... "Um... how about him?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[i move to idaho and now pub subs are on sale and brat brot announces its return smdh]]></document></documents></author>