<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@yosoypeligro_ @kenzibethh @OmniPhillips That's going to leave a mark...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMARIANOMD @CSAHQ @ASRA_Society @NarouzeMD @nelkassabany @NZ_ASM @andreanicolmd @DrJeniMD @NavSidhu08 @drchadb… https://t.co/E2qol8Uusw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @RobbieTheFire you should check out these guys... found them on my last trip if you will. Enjoy.  https://t.co/JlStr4GBgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Complete the comeback in 3 sets 15-10. 2-0 on the day. https://t.co/1MWwIMS6ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found some new fun little trails at Swan Creek MTB Trails near Tacoma, Wa. Also with a single track loop around the… https://t.co/FemkZNWDYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thread of you're not really a gun person but would like to understand why 2A supporters are so resistant to mo… https://t.co/HAEnvFGnfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me chuckle. #hilarity #snicker #smile #ludicrous https://t.co/BCNQwa5zfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lastly, they should consider moving the title games to the Pepsi Center…better venue all the way around and we live in an NBA city why not?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Retos Que Debes Superar en Tu Negocio https://t.co/XqwFgeaD2m vía @YouTube.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Orange jumpsuit boy is running scared! The wheels of justice are closing in you’re next! #NoWall #RussianAsset]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty cool! @FastCompany ranks Remitly third on its 2019 list of World's Most Innovative Companies for the Finance… https://t.co/RY0wujOkzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well said.  The god of the #Democrats is #Satan.  Amazing how far this nation has fallen in my lifetime.  Never wou… https://t.co/3Sp08b69bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Sticky's Finger Joint - @sfjnyc in New York, NY https://t.co/YQLO1leuPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been one of those weeks for sure! And it's snowing again! Daggum! At least I'm home, it's Friday and I have th… https://t.co/XVmuCDhIvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, that’s a darn shame about the further train delay! I’d love to know exactly WHO chose the train sets. WHAT CR… https://t.co/1aT8vlOUt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Lp8Nt86ZLq SO THE DETARD ANIMALS WATERED DOWN THEIR ANTI-HATE BILL TO AN #ALLLIVESMATTER TYPE DEAL NOW… https://t.co/dUyTO2AvZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a BCTweaked Session IPA by @beancurdturtle @ Beancurdturtle Brewing — https://t.co/LpHVru7L43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndiansRadio Listening while at the game, in town from CLE. Any chance on stopping by the booth? No worries either way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattJonesRadio I agree totally with your premise. One difference will be if a Democrat President does it it will b… https://t.co/UqRf5pUmL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louisthunter @MarvelNewsPTN @ThatZachWilson @ChristianDMZ @Xia_Land The one we all expected would be there but not… https://t.co/um6XyzkzRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why I love twitter. I’m sitting in Attleboro, Massachusetts in an all day engineering review (on the DFMEA now for… https://t.co/A53yMMqj6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgebing @CallieField @JKalena123 Awesome! Jason is a true rockstar. So well deserved !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing some black and white training for SW — swipe to see the final drawing #timelapse #monkey #inkdrawing… https://t.co/Von8S16guX]]></document><document><![CDATA[His real name was Jorge Garcia, but I always called him ‘Chiquilin.’ He was one of the more nicer people I first me… https://t.co/Q9sybdU9s7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolTenn @CoachJPruitt This  class will understand the importance carry the fight to our opponent keep it ther… https://t.co/HIbhy47jgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TroeUwaii @BassNicoh Sad part is I’m dead serious. Nicoh and I aren’t joking on the tl smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Santa Monica Bike Center in Santa Monica, CA https://t.co/dllZexLHPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to see @Ryan_Truex have a good run in @NASCAR_Xfinity series today really impressed with @MichaelAnnett and… https://t.co/pt7hlBuc6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[The great Travis Lulay retires. Seems like yesterday Bobcat coach Mike Kramer told me his freshman QB was going to… https://t.co/vhW0mWZYrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maklelan @timesandseasons I was mostly interrupting her Old Navy Online shopping. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smokingmusket Multiple times. Reset the router too. Shut it off and try again Saturday might be our best option at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There hath no temptation taken you but such as is common to man: but God is faithful, who will not … https://t.co/6z5jnKGe5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yearsandyears @MNEK this collab is such a bop! 🔥 #Valentino https://t.co/hpR9dVbf7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reminds me of them dudes in nap that hit a lick for a whole bunch of designer clothes in hang time smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For yourselves know perfectly that the day of the Lord so cometh as a thief in the night.” 1 Thessalonians 5:2 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@primegundam Considering their distribution model, it makes more sense for them to give us great figures of 6th Ran… https://t.co/gOIuhpP0D3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@o_tricky. Tricky : i been thinking that you are very lucky you are not a lost souls like Us !! Sincerely me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to advise the #Outliers community, founded by @Poseidon_Ho, at the inaugural boot camp this weekend in Seat… https://t.co/FsHW3WgZUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drayzze I see something here that just does not add up or make any logical sense! A naked slightly overweight man… https://t.co/9S9w2GlFmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leftyginger82 @_kingtrashy I only like men in their men in their 30's+. But I'm over men right now. Want to be alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Pay attention.  Republicans pretend to be about the law and say they oppose "judici… https://t.co/4f8Y1t2gET]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a surreal and beautiful weekend.  Emily and I spoke at our first Time Out For Women. Neither of us had ever at… https://t.co/G14BZedp1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyBobBobo1 @1776Stonewall @borntoraisehogs @BreitbartNews Mueller has done great work! Seven guilty pleas and c… https://t.co/2MdpJoNugL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sort of feel like a fraud because I didn’t get to see all the nominees this year like I did last year but if you… https://t.co/p5TfxmZt3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek Making fun of decent quality food now? Wow are you liberals out of touch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And young John is turning in his badge to be an actor.  “When you’re making your mark on the stage, just remember o… https://t.co/LgnVHT2A1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FreightGoals - Trucking’s billionaires: Forbes annual list includes those who made their fortune in trucking… https://t.co/46SNYVlU8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im at the dr.s appointment for my pain meds these mofo's act like they are paying for my meds they dont want to inc… https://t.co/DIffC9JbvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chazelena I do hope Macy can stay in the line up. I found her pretty impressive considering she never competes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Ass Clown No Matter What BS Lie You Spew To Your Cult Followers We The People That Are HONEST And Didn’t Cheat… https://t.co/Tz5BJOOzI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part 1 of a superset Weighted dips with a 20lb dumbbell between my feet Love how it feels with the extra weight… https://t.co/QYWiV1NgNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterLe29857073 @AOC So Pete what qualifications does the grabber have to sit abd speak to Chairman Kim about nucl… https://t.co/2jg21Qe4DO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone just took so long to answer my question that I blacked out and forgot where I was https://t.co/J8N9FaHyt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mog7546 Did you see the one where a judge got 28 years for selling black prisoners to private prison in America.th… https://t.co/EJXaXjPi6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatreeseBarnes You would be an excellent interview in my company journal of culture called the Blue Mountain Review.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Dells Boys Basketball on the impressive Regional Final Championship win at home over our conference… https://t.co/J64dgMlQnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[perfect math. good reading. ok writing. perfect math 2 subject test. near perfect french subject test. p good us hi… https://t.co/7ktQLH9YKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarabozich It’s almost like Untappd is being run by the PLCB. #thingsgovernmentshouldntdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProLifeTexanUSA @maxxx__power @MenaKyle @Zigurd @FifeTx @will10459 @raymysterio305 @edwood_not @Marc751e2f95… https://t.co/cxctlm6mUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[New project coming soon! Stay tuned on spotify.  omo_motorsports  @TheeBiggMellow   #biggmellow #mellow… https://t.co/edmG1bwOX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeffery4Pi @G33K01345 @AiG @BillNye It's a nickname for a child molester. In your case someone who lies to childre… https://t.co/far01G62BV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s Raiders Report will be Boomin. Believe it Baby!  https://t.co/TeRvjQXpOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls will hit you with their car and be like “sorry I’m on my fucking period”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cptnrwrpnts @mason4922 @Msmariablack Me too. It was wine for a while. Now it’s wine and working out 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at American Airlines in Fort Lauderdale, FL https://t.co/1IjPjbBWFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting #45… https://t.co/FOZYzwO0Cw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCMBB alums Pat Duquette @CoachLouis_H @CoachBikoParis have @RiverHawkMBB up 37-31 at the half over @HartfordHawks https://t.co/UmvzsaNXA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkHerbstreit Haha remember that well. Going over all the @HawaiiFootball player names for you the day before and #SandyBeach]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShimonPro @evanperez @LauraAJarrett Barr announcing the completion of the Mueller investigation=Barr effectively e… https://t.co/1gZt2TJpwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great advice that should be followed as frequently as we “edit” our profiles!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drewbueno Neat! I might try to steer 'em toward Cloudy, though they have reached the Age of Having Their Own Opinions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why "agree to return their device at the end of their term or pay a predetermined fee to keep the handset" if it's… https://t.co/Kmr0Wlqt3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karma: A billionaire, who can afford to enjoy the highest of the high-end ladies as often as he pleases, gets buste… https://t.co/mcrqBXYnjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmac1043 @Shapalicious @AllbrightNFL From fan’s view, and also former journalist, most annoying aspect of this pla… https://t.co/a2jsxvFIjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[You made it to Wednesday,  come give yourself a treat #downtownsd with some authentic #redbeansandrice  . . .… https://t.co/VlwSgqm1X1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dianpre Nunca digas tengo que hacer algo, tienes el poder de elegir.Pueden elegir sus acciones más no las consecuencias]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleMcGee @davidgourlay @playfoodandwine Thanks so much for helping us celebrate @DanielleMcGee @davidgourlay… https://t.co/yCTdIEeGiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Another historic monument being removed. This will not change history, just hide the reality. Some people… https://t.co/f1TMn41H4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noahpinion The truth is that I've hardly had much of anything to say about MMT in the 10 years I've been on here b… https://t.co/bDvPQU1sSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay Wok3, a song by Greg Gjerde on Spotify https://t.co/25poW3ASxS @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Believe It" https://t.co/m1d3liqN6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[It may be Transfiguration Sunday... but bc of #gc2019, Lent is starting earlier to a call to kneel and repent https://t.co/HHS4zPAPYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Glittermepink22 The gutter isn't a bad place, really, for a mind to be 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whats4GFdinner Here is a review. If you think she’d like it, DM or email your new address and I’ll send it to her. https://t.co/nTg9AcbPY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@svveetdee @poorlycatdraw When he’s getting pet and he’s in a good mood the drool flows]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atlanta is tough. Slick. Zero grip. You race the track. Not the competition. Awesome to watch. Even better behind t… https://t.co/volA04MqDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[One world-class chef. Hundreds of guests. @AnupamPKher stars as Chef Oberoi, a real life culinary expert who found… https://t.co/p9ZgKGJcdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder: My car accident was over 3 weeks ago. But unfortunately I had to deal with a drunken useless adjuster tha… https://t.co/Tkalebf5Di]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always responded to negative reinforcement. I grew up in a time when coaches were drill sergeants and you were… https://t.co/ddz3osJ72i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was all set to watch the #Brewers game, but then #LoveUnderTheRainbow came on. I'm sober and ditching baseball fo… https://t.co/j2trdpFTI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manfaland You’re too dope to be comparing yourself to anyone, you got my prayers but don’t forget who you are! https://t.co/gTv7WUNs40]]></document><document><![CDATA[If capitalism doesn’t become more inclusive on its own (lol), it will need to be made inclusive through taxation an… https://t.co/oFXXTSLwLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Uh, I told niggas stop askin' me where niggas at If you don't see 'em in the pictures with me, that mean they fade… https://t.co/F75bqBwmq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[kicked out of his Court of St James ambassadorship by FDR until AFTER Citizen Kane had been released. Herman Mankie… https://t.co/pQapuvqees]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ResistanceRises💙🇺🇸 @ Canyon Springs Post-Acute Care https://t.co/WQFV5nbdKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adams_lk_kruger @HammerAndRails Our shot selection sucks...D looks soft. Somebody needs to step up of Minny gonna… https://t.co/4H6oYfP4fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_salmonsjames_ Doubts, Tom said he’s working on getting this “cancer cell” cut from their locker room. Sad to say… https://t.co/OGv0Chweiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got pets? Would you like a doggy shower and large utility and mud room for all their beds? 🐶 Yeah, #FocusHomes can… https://t.co/rRKBAPaKtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@belamiboi1276 @AnthonyOrozco20 @ReadingPA @ReadingEagle Agreed, Denny! I think Donna would be great for Reading in… https://t.co/9vMFRr2auR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silkride @BackwoodsLife You’ve seen these zombie deer or know someone that’s been exposed to or contracted CWD?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paigeissunny Our booming agent is working right now on a national tour to support Remedy. Hopefully Atlanta is a p… https://t.co/c3RNl8k6ta]]></document></documents></author>