<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LaurenCohan And goodnight!!! That was a real treat... Can't wait for more!!! You Rock ✌✌✌ #WhiskeyCavalier… https://t.co/anm20eZPVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamKeithFL I'm grateful for the EPA and regulations on things like asbestos, which ~ contrary to new talking point… https://t.co/O5Y33bkbW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kebuenaoficial me complacen con #CuandoTeAme lo mas nuevo de @julionalvarez Gracias! #EsteSoyYo #GraciasPorCreer… https://t.co/tnsTA6dfPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The song in my head tonight There’s a tear in my beer. Telling my daughter about the awesome collab with @HankJr &amp; Sr.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eileenleftnotri @TedNesi @RISpeaker Because we believe a Virgin gave birth to the Son of God, but you don’t have t… https://t.co/LCA2AAEHpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating the legacy of the great Franklin Hall Williams! A graduate of  @FordhamLawNYC @LincolnUofPA!… https://t.co/viGa3MSEpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c4trends @ATTBusiness @magicleap @Brainlab @ZGJR @evankirstel @eViRaHealth @dez_blanchfield @Kevin_Jackson… https://t.co/2AP6JRDepc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think when we love some we make them out to be invinsable in our heads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women overcoming every barrier to reach each other. We are all who we are because of someone else. My platform of R… https://t.co/wSPcaa24JO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tabulacandida seems 30 years out of date??? monthly planners? only for us old folks, I think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar hi how are ya?? I need to go buy everything you use in your video today 🤩😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading... “For homeless people, the lack of stability is not only one of the biggest barriers to moving out of… https://t.co/6HJKLj8k19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone talk me out of gluing rhinestones to my ceiling,  quick!   #art #artistsoninstagram]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday leahcheyenne_ ❤️ #15yearsandcounting #birthdaygirl #aboutlastnight #goodtimes @ TAO Los Angeles https://t.co/nEuHrOAUfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@braxtonlit @gopchairwoman really cute dog, but name calling doesn't promote honest discussion about issues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl I was into back in the day never wanted to listen to my music because it was too experimental. I swore it… https://t.co/5iOgmQtK4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[More confirmation that Simpson lied to Congress when he said he didn’t meet with any DOJ/FBI officials before the e… https://t.co/mjulEKuBQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadiesAngel208 @HenseThomas @kentlee47 @SarahMundy15 @40kin3weeks @EricEatsBananas @Shelthecaper @ZellnerCrimeLaw… https://t.co/l7aORWEuwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gah. I really want a coffee but the puppy is in deep snoring sleep mode and if I wake him at 2:20 he will never chi… https://t.co/pKHiXcBqbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamjumpingin @dbongino Netflix just gave her 10 million dollars, will she spread that wealth around?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SystemsandTech @StevenDickens3 @tinatarq @apmcfadden @priyadoty @Maemalynn Likewise!!! Hope all it well...it’s been a minute!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity Please Mr President where is our AG ? This is enough, we don’t even turn the news on… https://t.co/Lca72YUkSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luzeternapr @jools6691 @TertiusIII @HaircutSpock @PeterWa33915152 @Denbar64 @geraldpayne25 @MaryVMos1 @orna_verum… https://t.co/rvyD142Aor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out our new creative community built playground! #buildcedarhill    #cedarhilltx   Still time to purchase a p… https://t.co/edyPEb5Kfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Designing a fashion line in art for our 8th grade population🎨   #creatinglogos#inventingcompanynames#sketchingoutcl… https://t.co/7KH1H52aA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m literally not kidding when I say this is the kind of weather that makes me happy https://t.co/NF7C8zn2UY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTL50 @maydaymindy9 @GmaG54499212 Ha ha ha! I hadn’t heard Marge Schott’s name in years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kid could seriously stand there all day and watch this movie. #happyfeet2 #mustbenumber2 #adorable https://t.co/vmgjlwFVK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ahhh Hello Deplorables! THIS project and many more NASA projects were underway during and at the e… https://t.co/6AQCErEjOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super cool #growwithgoogle stuff happening at work today! #roanoke @ Roanoke Public Libraries https://t.co/Xf9yTalnHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laurel Leverrier and Jannine Miller from @USDA provide #SBLN2019 state broadband leaders with update on RUS grant a… https://t.co/oHf8bPGbIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to working together on more great campaigns @CelerityLimited @MBautembach @craiga0273]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate that I have to sit in my cold ass car and wait like 5 minutes for my windshield to unfrost when I get off work at 2:30 am 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m waiting to see how long it takes my kids to realize @Indians baseball is in tv. They’ve been asking me nonstop… https://t.co/yZjHaM6F3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standby for a message from Cranky Dani...   Dear local #arwx folks, I understand the LR Marathon weather is a big d… https://t.co/uuhDM0Lrzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[So awesome @ON_EcoSchools will be sharing this with our school families! @stjwecdsb @WECDSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[He just keeps saying his dad is fake. Which I've never used that saying around him ever. So I'm in shock right now.… https://t.co/KFa8qB1g7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi mamá está comiendo en el restaurante de @GordonRamsay y yo un Subway. https://t.co/5rPEGkG8Gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeNeLeakes Caring for someone with cancer is hard! Not only do you have to deal with their illness and emotions, y… https://t.co/7uSif3LSeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I supported my local animal shelter just by walking my dog 1.38 miles using #WalkforADog app. Get the app at https://t.co/GkMAizAEhl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FemaleEros @biencalmex @libidorush1 @KristenKobandt @AdultBrazil @desires_unknown @rick702a @4669beaches… https://t.co/mw3EiRxztR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@softghc happy birthday ! hope it’s a good one 💘🎉 https://t.co/4QjHVYKfnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[only took like seven hours, but we’re here and we’re ready to party with @Badflower 🖤 https://t.co/hW86dvXVAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy afternoon at the playground with @CherryRebecca today! I can’t wait for spring! We had so much fun hanging ou… https://t.co/gRZZBQYbha]]></document><document><![CDATA[When in Rome..... #roadtrip #philadelphia #numnumnum @ Pat's King of Steaks https://t.co/XBDgE9WtRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevehowey Can you flex 💪🏻 your muscles for me and show me some of your tattoos? I am covered from head to toe. I’… https://t.co/gLvHv5gDab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated There is NO WAY that is an accurate description of his health. Wtf is wrong with people they will lie for him???😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is definitely a Trump puppet. Who else are they going to try to make pay for a ridiculous wall. Stop the insanit… https://t.co/LU87t4H6nF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jjpatt92 @JohnAnzo Unchecked? I’d like to see others it the facts and actions behind their words and get to the pint like she does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eye problem (@ Enchanted Oaks Animal Hospital in Spring, TX) https://t.co/EpRvv7zJjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And let the peace of God rule in your hearts, to the which also ye are called in one body; and be ye thankful.” Colossians 3:15]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MSNBC If Mark Meadows is any example the GOP plans on having a kangaroo court and  guess try to impeach Cohen. Wha… https://t.co/03yuSei4XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to announce that Christopher and Kent will be premiering there movie in the famous Chinese Theater in LA at t… https://t.co/MKNmyDMgH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol honestly as long as I know you care I’m gonna be straight but when I feel like you’re slipping or don’t care an… https://t.co/Np3uGsqNvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a layover so I splurged and got a chair massage.  The sweet old man said I’m a hot mess.  Lol.  What’s new?  🤷🏼‍♀️💆🏼‍♀️ #tension]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_Wes44 @KyleJamal4 You keep going kid. DONT STOP fighting! @WVLTDonovan testament even!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toddalio We're doing that next weekend! Enough with this 4yo stuff, right?? #upgrade]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings' sincerity and love for this nation is not in dispute, at least not in my book. #CohenHearing #respect]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social media sucks sometimes lol I look at people’s IG stories and posts and I instantly feel like I’m inadequate b… https://t.co/mlfzICh1kS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrTomMartinPhD #LastWord Have no doubt I will vote democratic. I just want those with baggage to either be able to… https://t.co/DU0HvhNnBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi. @StellaMaeve14 I love you. So excited about everything. https://t.co/WhlQLs6L1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just one of the reasons leaving my house is tough leg alone leaving it on time! #momofboys https://t.co/2paT4jRcma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@defenestrator19 Thanks ! It’s because my son had it set on 60 degrees 🤦‍♀️ https://t.co/wbr4HeTtAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lingerie_addict FWIW, when a brand/manufacturer/retailer does that, it’s illegal. You can cut, sew and finish garm… https://t.co/YYEbpPztGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of us are far better at this than others. #watercolor #watercolorpainting #kmcelwaine #art #s2s #cedarpark @ K… https://t.co/NaRJsnaeT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just really liked this photo. #seattleladieschoir @ Fremont Abbey Arts Center https://t.co/uXdJP6tMNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Read about our latest job opening here: Pharmacy Technician II -Evening/Night Schedule 2:00 pm - 10:3… https://t.co/a0q16Av0Yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhereAnnFlies @amydejohnson @CaltransDist3 I think the parents of this toddler might be with us in Tahoe now. 24 h… https://t.co/KynKTEj55r]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little snow won't stop us! Melrose and our schools are worth it.   Thank you, @smithgalvin, for canvassing with m… https://t.co/RLv2c0HqTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdvardHviding Vinaka vakalevu Edvard my ocean colleague. We may have 7 seas but only 1 ocean!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled about the 3-0 victory for @WL_Soccer tonight. Way to start the season!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loltyler1 pls stream on the weekends sometime i miss u dad 🤧 PepeHands]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sierra “you never tell me you love me before you hangup”  *says it every time now* bitch hangs up half the time 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fixed Upper drinking game, drink every time they say:  Shiplap  Tear down that wall/ open up this space Hardwood fl… https://t.co/RqIQ0TEYXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[So blessed to have these amazing women in my life! Love a girls’ trip!♥️🏇🏼👯‍♀️ @ Hot Springs, Arkansas https://t.co/1ZVxvgb1Hf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaireHMajor I feel like I had to prepare myself - I could have done a doctorate without ever having taught a clas… https://t.co/yDf7AYMsXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Varsity Stats are up on @MaxPreps - 3 game weekend leaders: Josie Ward: 21 Goals, 11 DCs Caden Pace: 6 Goals Ashley… https://t.co/a3eNc84puM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really pleased that my incessant praise and adoration of my gf in my tumblr tags finally propelled certain people t… https://t.co/PNlTCb5Ce6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Citibank I’ve been on hold for 29 mins and this is my fourth call to you. Why us this so hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is quite unbelievable that ANYONE would let a baby, very much alive,be murdered!If this is passed an amendment r… https://t.co/77D9Fn4mvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitrebox @DavidAFrench I always pick my son in a tie.  He’s a better passenger than his sister who questions everything I do...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys call girls out for wearing too much makeup when they’re out here covering up hair their face with a beard🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[*silence*   Him: it’s nice seeing you.   Me in my head: 🙃🙂🙃🙂🙃  Me in reality: 🙃🙂😍🙂🙃🥰😍🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jserena4 At least you listened and it didn’t happen much. Strikeouts that is😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwsmith_056 @ShuttleCDRKelly I second that! Actually thinking about retiring and heading that way to join my broth… https://t.co/aOMGHUZbRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #ZombieDeer disease is real and it’s spreading, so what #celebrity y’all think going to be a #Zombi ? I could s… https://t.co/GALvVX3XfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2DqfBKddZt  #iceclimbing #ClimateCrisis #ClimateChangeIsReal #ClimateActionNow #diving]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dumper_trump @ENBrown @swin24 I don't understand why Jacob Wohl just can't take a hint and stfu!    After commenti… https://t.co/Io9fiiuMjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imcorinnemec @SydChicky2013 @CatsoNemec Catso peeing on u again really catso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy happy Valentine's Day!! Different types of Love for everyone! 💛🧡❤️💚💙💜🖤#ValentinesDay #iseearat #ILoveNY #love… https://t.co/goIPGwBIuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SemperPatriota @reagan_kristin @GOP @realDonaldTrump So you have no idea of trumps family history...look it up and… https://t.co/dDDTR7YbeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no problem being faithful I loved you so much I hate you, cause you left me when I needed you tha most so now… https://t.co/dGA2fajyUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting until 9pm to check out the sights of New York from above...meanwhile...Chewbacca is in NYC! #chewbacca @ Em… https://t.co/l5MK24Yzk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an awesome night celebrating Miss Jeannie's belated birthday!!! @ Gyu-Kaku Japanese BBQ https://t.co/ruoH6B1vsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha OMG that's hysterical!! 😂 That figure being mapped out is TRIPPY!! #GhostAdventures #spirits]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMarkPantano @TuckerCarlson Tucker Carlson is fighting for Truth, not a bunch of lies. They better watch themsel… https://t.co/lOoV0IlRWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsEmilySmith23 has a true ❤️ for serving our #KleinGT learners! So grateful for her service on the #KleinGTGC !]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang comic. Stiles Stilinski - "The last time I saw him? Definitely the time I saw him last"... #humor #tee-hee… https://t.co/HrLxtpRoks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five Ways to Improve the Culture of Your Business - No Bean Bags Needed  https://t.co/fIZgQ7Dar9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turned over in bed and the world started spinning. Fucking vertigo?!?? I travel tomorrow. Uggghhhhhhh]]></document></documents></author>