<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Lively discussion by law students Andrea Garcia and Brian Trujillo about how to apply #AI and #MachineLearning to t… https://t.co/g6sxLhfipi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beinlibertarian @RonPaul  @whiskeynrebel @adamkokesh @AP4Liberty @ArtofNBG @EricDJuly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatbadwitch I’m down, but that’s a big jump from the first two to season 3😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[And under the National Emergencies Act of 1976, Congress can repudiate said emergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Reader, I married him.”-Jane Eyre  Pc: kwonphoto @ McCoy Equestrian Center https://t.co/uFjsVDuUdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAFromBK @DragonMom98 @SabreKevin1639 @rtadter @audsabres @JeremyGregoret1 @716hockeydadZ @MikeFButler @G_Ray34… https://t.co/NqVyWH19MZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus, nurture the faith of local and home churches. https://t.co/OVtYVbvnPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KXnOFanatics Barta is just saying words.  I want to scream.  He blames ignorance and procedure for his silence.  B… https://t.co/A8Us9PeXgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lynn was also there just before 10pm still grinding. Thanks to all the staff of @TCVolleyballNIT for taking great c… https://t.co/YcHFC0H87a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even on Sunday. #legday (@ Westchase Fitness in Tampa, FL) https://t.co/X3EVBpdTmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAvaArmstrong Not only that,those old white men are smarter,richer, and mostly run everything. Oh yea, they're a… https://t.co/m1LmR3PFvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dynarski You always manage to cheer us up with your tweets, Susan. (Dr. Dynarski)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleyfeinberg When I pressed publish I knew it was just a matter of time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hells_gazelles HO-LEE Shit what a sound! Just found you! Crunchy and hard and mixed so tight get your asses to the… https://t.co/3IFc8cATcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Baystate Health? We're hiring in #Springfield, MA! Click for details: https://t.co/YE52iestnv #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiness is a warm gun, yes it is... #TheBeatles #undertheinfluence #acrosstheuniverse #JulieTaymor #SalmaHayek… https://t.co/rPzUFPPkLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in South Lake Tahoe, CA, check out this job: https://t.co/xe3aIuUvHD #hospitaljobs #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealAFlanny Yeah I would say giannis, but even then.. what PG is doing right now is crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying a smooth #kpop channel on Apple Music. https://t.co/W65eSa4jjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexSpaethPhoto Does this mean that on your death bed you’ll receive total consciousness?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarxBarl @solehdad @kennaraew Finish my bachelors degree, finish my military contract, and start a business. One thing at a time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterjhasson @MeghanMcCain You are twisting and mis-categorizing the words]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wordwulf #bubonic #instagood #tweetgram #photooftheday #instamood #writer #philosophy #music #books #memes… https://t.co/oypMHr5xmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Rep. Omar voted to condemn hate in that resolution today*  As for Meghan McCain:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisBurdis @OSTXshow I was laugh-crying, the Judge and @mdotrayAJ were a lot of fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RattlerGator J.B.,  We hope you're right, but after two years, we don't believe it until the hammer sounds.  Now t… https://t.co/bfrjpYrbIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EnoughIsEnough with this ignorant term "Presidential Harassment."  Then again, they are NOT SPEAKING TO US!  (This… https://t.co/I0JcVQ6eXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Rui Hachimura for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/RfbS8D4vhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Avalangelist @AvsPodcast Day late and a dollar short here! If I would have known this... 😉😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[consensual sex activities with women that have consented gets me rock hard 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t start charity miles at the beginning but had a great 6 miles on a surprisingly quiet DTLA morning @ Downtown… https://t.co/vj1yJCaedT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PM_Johann Hey “FEMA” I need you to take care of Alabama. Give them the A plus treatment, this is the President. Abusing power?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lady shows up 5 minutes late, no ticket. We tell her she has to wait for the first piece to end before we let… https://t.co/L08v7LjgTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not mad you’re you. I’m disappointed you inconvenienced me to do so!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t be mad at him 😔 regardless of what he has done to me I’d still forgive him....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey if you feel like you had a missed connection today DM me your story and I’ll get it out on the @TheSAClubPod th… https://t.co/AvD2oEi0rU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bust down Barbiana 👑 @ 800 Live Bar and Nightclub https://t.co/3hiOCfwHS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KittyAndPitty @JussieSmollett @realDonaldTrump you realize they kicked the doors in and are holding two black Nige… https://t.co/uPeMp8yKwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DBleezy91 Barack was doing weed then graduated to coke according to his own book...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also- and UNBELIEVABLY SO, the only #1 song by @Aerosmith (on the charts, there's tons of #1s in my head)]]></document><document><![CDATA[just installed my stripes but i dont think it looks right and i ripped it like 3 times but its okay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juakogallardo @reciprocante Como harto para un país pobre con ganas de ayudar a un país jodido, ¿no?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Doc are you dipping into the meds? That was known as Jerry's crazy train to nowhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rdandamber @JimCarrey Yes, you'll burn his movies just because Jim Carrey hates  Trump, he's not the only one that… https://t.co/EgHIEPRUnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouTern Good evening! Hope your week has started out well!! #InternPro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s an example of what happens in most organizations when you try to cascade a message from the top down to your… https://t.co/9iP1m0SOJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DenPublicWorks @DenverCPD Paint some bus lanes so buses aren’t caught in snow traffic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZekeJMiller Donald Trump is like the Sean McVay of political staffing.  Except, instead of NFL head coaching gigs, they get indictments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_HeyitsmeAllie Aren’t they bots? Or outsourced people? I’ve had like 4 girls message me (all with obvious fake pic… https://t.co/XpkcG85VAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last thing she said was, “Lean back. This won’t hurt a bit.” Then, a voice from the corner said, “Is it safe?”… https://t.co/9Cd5Zwwhs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[True Detective season 3 was better than 1 until the end. Such an overwhelming finale. Why did they do that to us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @Rubberbandits, you've broke America. Sitting in a bar in New York here and my visiting mate was ch… https://t.co/6I92DuxQgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stand tall my man. I got ya back. Don’t let them tell u it’s something wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KierstenWarren Well they both are amazing looking pieces, hopefully they're in Your future.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiefitzpat @a_h_reaume Just finished it for comps a few weeks ago. SO great. I wish I had read it during coursew… https://t.co/IvRhiDhlUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ambitious. - Drinking an Organic Ambitious Lager by Wildwood Brewing @ Wildwood  — https://t.co/SPKNfNUCKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Blacks stepping in mud to get a gd scene 🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/aynHehSLR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep Your P💣WDER🚬DRY  Don’t V🔥TE til U C   Whites of Their Lies  11/3/2020 Default DEM Again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Per reports, Le’Veon Bell’s weight blew up to 260-pounds during his time away from football.   Does/ should this al… https://t.co/V3HrRSvXD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[God damn!! My truck needs a detail! It Frosted with mud ! Thanks  bipolar weather 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CLAU_LA_COLO EXTINCIÓN DE DOMINIO: En comisión en el Congreso todos los peronistas de cualquier denominación están… https://t.co/ek2mnt6XrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want to go back to strictly PC gaming, but most of my friends play on console. 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to clean my circle up cause no one was with me when I was behind bars!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot to tweet this earlier, but we had our weekly media luncheon at Pizza Ranch today, where @NWBearcatMBB coac… https://t.co/YRFOSXACut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treswritesstuff @BrenttHarshman Personally, I think we would BOTH crush that particular song’s vibe and subject matter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Lol... Nice try... How does it feel knowing your dad thinks you are #4 in the smarts department... Of his kids]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Nope. Not one shred. Likely hundreds or thousands of shreds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday is coming up. Can’t wait for that @lukecombs concert. 🇺🇸🍻 @J_Steww6 @jesssasmithhh @RachaelSondrini]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Chiefs already had a horrible defense, then they release Justin Houston. That makes sense. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity I hope you are buried in it never to see the light at of day again. #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LtGovPinnell A few of my favorites that I believe truly capture the Oklahoma Standard. #OkTravelTakeover https://t.co/pXN1tvcQIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to sleep in my own bed again. Florida was incredible, but 8 hours and I'm on the road again. This weekend it's Pittsburgh for work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza Robin couldn’t have asked any tough questions or she would be blackballed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help my AL students finish off their lists of 300 things that make them happy.  It’s due Tuesday.  Tweet what makes… https://t.co/NsEYYiwjDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xdabluesfan @MrBluesHat His stick is off the ice. Goes under his stick 5 hole...lol https://t.co/sXametEKB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPACT over INCOME ⚖️  | I am so happy to be apart of such a great company! I have been with the @RockwellTime fami… https://t.co/pWTpICUKlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW LISTING IN CHAPIN, SC 377 FOXPORT DR 4 BEDROOM 2 BATH only $164900  https://t.co/6owvo7CY16 @ Chapin,… https://t.co/Tf2iGn2EpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[He woke up a grown man. Maybe should of watched some film instead of taunting]]></document><document><![CDATA[House readies vote to block Trump's emergency declaration: “The president’s act is lawless and does violence to our… https://t.co/3qZCNVaoaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColliderVideo I would cast @MichaelKeaton with #timburton directing and do it all with CG and digital de-aging lik… https://t.co/ctU8M0MsKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well Mike it’s a holiday so a little bit of a late start for me this morning I started off strong but seemed to pet… https://t.co/UYN4pXCL4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mags at #BeerChurch2019 - Drinking a Lord Whangdoodle by @TheVeilBrewing @ Beer Church  — https://t.co/draS85LT6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[My PI: The map has been brained. The map has been —  the BRAIN HAS BEEN MAPPED.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarkinsWealth @CommonwealthFN @HarkinsWealth Glad to have you as part of the family!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thayesnet stopping by to speak with the leaders for @VergeMobileTPR @TMobile https://t.co/t0dKQCcMeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #Screenplay "MERCURY" is now available! Check out the script download and synopsis!  Longline: In the late 19th … https://t.co/CwuwDFo4dW]]></document><document><![CDATA[just flew back from a transformers convention and boy are my arms tires]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm on the PATH to Hoboken and want to get some work done so I fire up my laptop and NOPE   😣 https://t.co/LmWn7bfI7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@howardeskin @SportsRadioWIP Great interview/conversation yesterday with the GM. It’s why you’re #TheKing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Produced @Goldberg  for Shark Fights MMA for Fuel back in the day.  Warm, funny, and a total gentleman to everyon… https://t.co/fVhHitM8SB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@x808beats that's something my chimp.never told me https://t.co/OuvSjuBB2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rstewart2091 @BruhReport Bro go back to renegades practice, we’re trying to ball]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really like my 2014 Mercedes GL 450, it’s been a great car until last week. I figured @MercedesBenzUSA may won’t… https://t.co/adWO2fDLJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cluadiacano @deniseramosm @AlvaradoVMarce @bettyparedon @dulceesquerv @Denissenavarr0 @GrisEspinoza7 @ilyagarmar… https://t.co/cDfkHNyUfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LemonnLimee I want this! Even if I prefer other candidates, this philosophy is what I want!]]></document><document><![CDATA[shout out to all my ladies with irritable bowel syndrome. i see you baby! ❤️💩❤️💩❤️💩❤️💩❤️💩❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Riverboatjack Nice! I assume it’s on Steam? Would love to revisit it and a lot of PS1 classics, time permitting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #NorthwestRaleigh on Glenwood Ave and Lumley Rd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evansilva And I thought being a Giants fan sucked.  Imagine cheering on this dumpster fire.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for your reporting today! Invaluable insight for DPS parents.]]></document></documents></author>