<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@FortMillRaye is a SC civil asset #forfeiture reform superstar! Rep Felder has sponsored the bill that protects pro… https://t.co/cEKlvtuVmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FHA #FairwayNation #mortgage #firsttimehomebuyer #realestate #florida #StayPassionate #RayCombs @ Ray Combs Homes,… https://t.co/CtLh2PMAkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuySuFrida No te pases de lista.  Dijo las ternas que yo “proponía”.  Por favor no distorsione la nota.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse This is the MORON and THIEF RUSSIAN AGENT TRAITOR “RAT”, NEVER MY PRESIDENT. FU Cult Followers https://t.co/cPjKYkQknB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the weekend already... @ Raceway Park Englishtown NJ https://t.co/2vzHPAW34z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CornerPubRon @VouxCroux You’re probably right..I’m just doing the math and I’m like.. https://t.co/0Ox3Z2McWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And people still don’t like @nevin_lawson   I understand he draws a lot of penalties, but he shut down Thielen, who… https://t.co/Q360ISi9oj]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One 💙! ! Impeach Trump &amp; prosecute, now! 😎😄✌️👁️💚💣💥! https://t.co/i8r1Yp1O1Q https://t.co/DTkvkhLz7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Does it make a difference?,  every one knows who he is, the issue is he's promising a free ride and way too many believe him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonideepa @Barbie Because even in India there's a huge social stigma around skin tones?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing @djpaulyd tonight harrahspoolac  Until then, 🍷🍷🥂🥂 #saturday #saturdaynight #drinks #cocktails #photooftheday… https://t.co/4BCEUEVa3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it. I would love to watch animals all the time. Forget the political republican bull sh—.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaleighHoffman @jbillinson This convo has kept me entertained. 😂 https://t.co/oM9N906cO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@S_Padival @enn_nafnlaus @PlugInFUD @CGrantWSJ @markbspiegel @WallStCynic Did you even read the fucking thread?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My most favorite tweet of the year!!!  State Bound!!! https://t.co/tjCwnLRZ7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google RankBrain: Clearing up the myths and misconceptions https://t.co/6zrtcqz13S https://t.co/dZ9FxUTL2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madonna - What It Feels Like For A Girl (Official Music Video) https://t.co/iY6s9ejr1p via @YouTube. Classic Madonn… https://t.co/6fEScnoIPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot what it feels like to stay up all night to catch an early flight. #whatatimetobealive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanHays77 @chrimattbabylon I'm the hero Guatemala deserves, but not the one it needs https://t.co/pOlZoTnrsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TRDFan1 Need another @SNICKERS @ToyotaRacing @JoeGibbsRacing #Camry in #VictoryLane on @KyleBusch 500th Cup start.… https://t.co/BIGiJjVFT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nzgrant17 @GaylynnJohnson @RhinoluvsUSA @kdrose0718 @LoveBling6 @Josiegirlz5 @jkkc40 @WhitestoneArt @fglaus… https://t.co/5gPGOoVAVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto @mhanham Kim had his own brother and uncle murdered but sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheQuartering Well they will make some money, but this will be Last Jedi style bad 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows From the guy who was complicit to the point of guilt.  Jim delivers what we expect, low… https://t.co/OQ0lhhPEja]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many Kre8 Bacon Crisps and only one mouth. So sad. I need more mouths for more bacon crisps: proof that God exis… https://t.co/xHbzleB5M7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to work from the @invinst. We can see that Supt. Eddie Johnson justified the killing of Rekia Boyd by off-du… https://t.co/iPOojhPdm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laostarxo @OLNband I really wanted to go to see State Champs again too but the Chicago date was the first one sold… https://t.co/P9dJaYrZqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We live in a society of romantic and social constructs that create false hope and outrageous expectations that lead… https://t.co/Tr1XySo2iO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psalm//55:22 -  Cast your cares on the LORD  and He will sustain you; he will never  let the righteous be shaken.  https://t.co/VZtspdpmyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wraithyn1 @HiRezAjax @TitanIsiah Why take out my fav when Skadi, kuang, bakasura, and erlang shen still exist?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@COsoccerpod @joshsargent Sounds like a lot of excuses for Sargent to me man. https://t.co/ZrNoZB2IYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @seanhannity @FoxNews Sir, convenient that you interview exclusively on Trump State News where har… https://t.co/BB8BOb1b8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me know if it's a good read.. 🦅Batman: Nightwalker https://t.co/7C5QIuArrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mesa Mall GM Paul Peterson says CMU brings a lot tot the table and that a lot of students shop and work at the mall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trumpeter or tundra?  No color to the bills. @ Maplewood Water Park https://t.co/IGYkverKQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d @angelaisms President Pence will pardon him, if he doesn’t President Haley will!😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedRobinRacing @RyanSmithRacing @dannydietrich @ssspeedways Count me in! 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the budget proposal is Trump going to listen to Fox News commentators or the representatives of the citizens of America ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess paying off a pornstar, using foul language, bullying people, bankruptcy, lying is necessary to be come a ro… https://t.co/FiAP0wuMpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tweets4MAGA CAIR👎🏿🤮 George Soros 👎🏿🤮 David Brock👎🏿🤮 Media Matters👎🏿🤮  Keith Ellison👎🏿🤮 Nancy Pelosi👎🏿🤮 Bill Maher👎🏿🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your 2019 North South Travelers Cup winners, Team Chicago!  “We put in Werk so u don’t have to !😏 #golfaddict… https://t.co/dSumlWJkgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is your favorite #sport ? at @vivalivetvofficial we have them all, live. Call now and sign up 833 848-2888 or… https://t.co/t3gZ2hKqV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I feel like I lose friends because of my strict schedule and it’s like wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keaglemd @lipoproteinaFDN @MyTrainerBob  we need therapies.  Niacin, vitamin ,, lysine, PCSK9?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ringham7 @TennisChannel @Naomi_Osaka_ I was thinking the same thing. What a refreshing personality. Not just good… https://t.co/IgnQO5nDa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @washingtonpost @ericawerner @damianpaletta @WaPoSean If u can't get yur govt to work then how do… https://t.co/T27V1ZBASM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bungarsargon How is pointing out the obvious re @AIPAC doing wrong by Jews? It's a lobbying group influences Congr… https://t.co/ZE8oTKiGBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[One week out until our first @blvdia social team meeting. Expect plenty of pics and vids to come when the event hap… https://t.co/PvgEyazVnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The firetruck is loaded up and ready to go.  #rodeo #parade https://t.co/DQKya2d2Hn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericaNewsroom @washingtonpost Sue me then because I think you are a f*cking little MAGA pussy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GM Brian MacLellan weighed in on #ALLCAPS⁠ ⁠ inconsistent defensive play. #Caps had best GAA in East from March1 on… https://t.co/rgM36W3YK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Oh please, Obama played golf while in office at he tax payers expense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mountain Meadows by Judy Geller @judy_jgeller Exhibited by Norman Felix Gallery @normanfelixart normanfelixart… https://t.co/3TV4z6kkBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Course #1 @bjsrestaurants Meatballs paired with @GuinnessIreland Extra Stout @BeerInFlorida https://t.co/tldNtjmzgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[We found little to no effects, which is in keeping with the literature on spoilers (small effects in both direction… https://t.co/m573zoEBi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love having lunch with my mentor and my first mentee. https://t.co/ZMSxJFXt4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMO A MI ESPOSA, A MI NIETA, A MI HERMANA, A MI MAMA´QUE EN EL CIELO ESTÁ, A MIS ABUELAS, A MI NUERAS, A MIS TÍAS,… https://t.co/I5YBtA1IWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[coaching change is coming. Maybe it all works out. I dunno. But this is kinda what I thought would happen if he wen… https://t.co/unyunJy7Nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Italnangel @TheJennyMShow @RunningMan215 @molaikowski @NicoleZarzecki @JennyMcCarthy No. Hot dog is a sandwich, the dictionary told me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ltd_To_Two When you’re young and all’s aglow, there’s a smile for every hour  .  .  .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Belated birthday bingsoo 📸 rubenluong @ Sul &amp; Beans https://t.co/qavJU8O10X]]></document><document><![CDATA[The serenity of a pair of Swan as they glide by.  This at the Seney Wildlife Refuge in the UP.… https://t.co/7CRgQbrB5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHuynhArts just run away from or block out, and that led me to crying for seemingly no reason in class on multiple… https://t.co/L4ZLeJYMBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Success! It might have been 50 minutes in line but Orange Bird got to meet himself! Cheers to another year of… https://t.co/BsFxjXlOkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s up in Western Oregon this weekend?? Find out right here&gt;&gt;&gt; https://t.co/ZDT3ErqGXA #EugeneOregon @KMTR #WeekendReady]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1i7Yh0Hvx4 #in #breach #cybersecurity #CyberAttack #cybercrime]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wrote about DST and @jack yesterday and said that I'd probably get restricted. Not only did I get restricted, but… https://t.co/SzhaFVZjEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[He sounds more like an enemy combatant than a presidential candidate. People need to be aware of this. Somebody sen… https://t.co/C7blKPQNHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjenwbitches I mean, it's not exactly a unique sentiment. She used different words. it's just a funny parallel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Try To Keep Up - Episode 2  Knowledge Goes Nuclear https://t.co/DRK5FeDWhG via @YouTube. A must to view.  How do we… https://t.co/eALLedMweU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t Michigan and Michigan State just play each other today in hoops?? Too jacked for tomorrow’s contest! #64Miles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko @szwest1 Everyone except the GOP. Without them it can never happen. If the GOP was a real party th… https://t.co/JRTlEswGJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yumyumfish I want to see this although wouldn't the bad acid trip be Enter the Void?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somethings in life will move fast.. don’t get left behind.. learn to increase ya pace bc when the clock spinning th… https://t.co/kfvsphmygC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump YOU'RE THE ENEMY OF THE PEOPLE AND THE TRUTH, GOEBBELS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace @pgammo Wait, Cohen met and hung out with Democrats before his meeting today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @digitallearnudl to post covers of 7 books I have read and love: no explanations,… https://t.co/ys4RbJUtDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheltieman3 So sorry brother... I will certainly pray for Brent, and you...😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drive 12,000 miles a year. My car averages between 15 and 20 MPG since most of my driving is city.   45¢ per gall… https://t.co/i1Hv2N7zHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy tuve el placer de acompañar a @juankguerrerog y @pabloagarciae en su programa #GlobalSports, por @vdm_radio, pa… https://t.co/9rH5CJRisn]]></document><document><![CDATA[While I don't fully agree with @FFStompy on these rankings he presents well thought out assessments in this article https://t.co/FlJTQmXHgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to add another store in OHPA!  Expect this store to hit the ground running!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByMHarrington @JMattSmith29 I don’t hate you. I enjoy your work. Might not agree all the time but like the debate… https://t.co/LyM2zn977N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to all our sponsors for making the @HEF270 gala happen! https://t.co/IAsYh7uegQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop by GNC in the Winona Mall - Winona, MN TODAY for the HUGE BOGO 50% OFF SALE!!!! BANG Drink Cases, One Protein… https://t.co/OeiIK9WgaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 Opening Day on deck!!!! Good luck this season boys. https://t.co/mDPLcarV1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indfnsofplnts Agree C3 will maintain dominance. Palmer would have to learn some cold tolerance. Maybe miscanthus c… https://t.co/FG9RgHdTcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoviePass the app has been completely useless for at least  the last two months.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamBaldwin No, it’s a bullshit time-waster. I’d only miss the trolling and shit posting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good weekend with the Squad in Austin. #Biff #SLIDE @ Westlake Highlands, Austin, Texas https://t.co/YoNWySmNVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaniaKhalek @AOC .@aoc we luv ya, but you need to get as on point, savvy and effective on #venezuela as you are on… https://t.co/yihEv1rnT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emailtimw @sturdyAlex @Rykalski @RemainResistant What would the Tories even be able to campaign on in a general el… https://t.co/hbMHT1erQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter Recall why our Founders wanted virtuous people as leaders in the nation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this protein and lifting I’ve been doing got my muscles super pumped. My shit feels asf! 💪🏿🦵🏿#imonregular]]></document><document><![CDATA[@socal_chi @mtracey I think the video of him literally running to his connection in an airport is also good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/sVWbinpByT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Ah, @SpeakerPelosi has lost control of @TheDemocrats in the House--not a pretty sight to behold. 😱🤢🤨😑🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[How bout the guy decked out in WVU gear right under the UNC basket front row.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brokeymcpoverty Watching it now and had to come and make sure I wasnt crazy while watching this.  Why the heck wou… https://t.co/Y2l6yLZ3IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My job is so predictable.   I can almost always expect, especially on my days off, a call asking to cover someone’s… https://t.co/l16QNJkWdN]]></document></documents></author>