<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Notice his Garbage track race of late..buying champagne to get ready for the idiot to join Roger "big mouth" Stone… https://t.co/lnxAxKQa0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Erykah Badu ever get an award for “Best Video” for Honey🤔 #DopeVideo #CreativeGenius #HappyBirthday #ErykahBadu #BetHer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodnewsmag Did you WATCH your leader’s speech at the confessing movement lunch last year?  Slow to anger?  Ha, that’s really funny🙁🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heARTISTatWORK @MaireCervenak @LindaEdwardsi @tamaraletter @Bill_Huber_ @thewrightleader @teacherasleader… https://t.co/M6JTfBIux1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5SOS @Michael5SOS @Calum5SOS @Ashton5SOS @Luke5SOS can y’all bring wrapped around your finger back for this tour or]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personal Growth has become one of my obsessions. I spent a good chunk of my lifetime wondering why people did the t… https://t.co/8FUgannCuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like magic ✨  Day 16: 16 students visit for lunch and sketching ✨ On day 1, you extend an invite, open your doors,… https://t.co/o7LzR4d2J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleRichards @sarawat00267144 @dcstorm123 @doritkemsley1 @TeddiMellencamp @lisarinna @Andy @BravoTV Only responding to Kyle R!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sophia and Jason-Angelo at Falls Incline Railway...😀👍🏼❤️👧🏻👦🏻🇨🇦 #sophiaandjasonangelo #magpinsan #cousins… https://t.co/weWpCZ8PKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[A word about...  #YouTube and de monetization of videos over stray comments?  Done in the #StevensUniverse world?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost @maggieNYT He is a disgusting individual and so is the judge]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a renter on 115 OAK RIDGE LN #Milford #CT  #realestate https://t.co/kyoHhUiC4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Tonight is about keeping up the intensity. It’s going to be a playoff type atmosphere with two teams fighting for… https://t.co/JFlosdAm0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beatrizbecerrab @jguaido @FedericaMog Nadie entiende la desesperación d muchísimos venezolanos. ¿cuál o como sería… https://t.co/YyCq0pWBxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[really in a “put my hot dog suit on and run around campus” kinda mood ya feel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though my heart is hurting, I am also happy that you’re no longer in pain! You were the sweetest soul I ever m… https://t.co/pNJwsxPpxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s safe to say many drivers got their license years ago and have developed some bad habits between then a… https://t.co/tAcDVpsMR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[What am I doing at 1am on a sat night?  Ordering...  - 1000 thread count sheets/pillowcases - 3 inch gel memory foa… https://t.co/mnz2R0027P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be wise, my son, and bring joy to my heart; then I can answer anyone who treats me with contempt. https://t.co/EGOfBUoslg]]></document><document><![CDATA[We at Kingdom Provision Connection care about you and are praying for you! https://t.co/LsviXGTo0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[First session available on Apple Podcast let’s celebrate that https://t.co/VA01wryXCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must have just missed this incident. I’m glad the only disruption on our trip around Rivers of America was the g… https://t.co/5ZHNUl8Y0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timhinds4 @GoBearcatsMBB @700wlw Of all players to put on there and they put a miss by Fredricks! Who was the PR g… https://t.co/hur0V9Swi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean every person you encounter isn’t gonna be your boyfriend so yeah ima fuck and keep it moving]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emily_Stains413 @BNChesterfield @CCPSFACE1 A book for my students, a book for my kids, and a door prize which adde… https://t.co/hRQ7Beg1oa]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my newest #listing 9704 Tallahassee Drive #Knoxville #TN  https://t.co/mc3JiRfvn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see you nephew #0!  He’s @Jay__GetBuckets in the last shot in the team circle! 😃  Sorry, not sorry if auntie is e… https://t.co/UPNpHi1zfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlosarprietoc Tú también @Carlos saludos a distancia👋👋👋👋👋 #FelizJueves#]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to annoy my family by sending 200000 txts in the group txt this morning and it’s only working on the ISFJs🤔😂… https://t.co/HmluuXz4JR]]></document><document><![CDATA[freshly tatted and it feels so good 💉 lol jk rib tattoos are a fucking bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[As expected, Gerald Butts will testify before the Justice Committee. #CDNpoli #pnpcbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidde87284971 @Zebrafarm2000 @DZhou108 @RBReich All my in-laws are in the UK. I’ve had a medical emergency there… https://t.co/ToUrxX8PX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat Why is he not banned? What is his purpose but to be mean?]]></document><document><![CDATA[SXSW Day 1 - Featured Session .  The Universe aligned and I worked a Staff support shift yesterday on International… https://t.co/iL4xr93dxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to get out of town with my two favorite people🥰 @bradymcdonald3  @1Rayn_]]></document><document><![CDATA[hilarity coming your way. Im happy to say I watched Dakota Fanning from kid to young adult and of course... #comedy… https://t.co/UkVUnATITd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LinkedInHelp First of all ... I HATE change! I’m frantically trying to get up to speed with the damn WordPress cha… https://t.co/OZq8kA99JN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *drinks some of moms drink* Lexi: Kamron, don’t drink your moms shit!” Me: “wanna drink?” Lexi: “oh yeah!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jen14221 @dkelley5 Eataly in the Westfield WTC and Hudson Eats/Le District are some of my fave places to eat when I’m working down there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep dreaming, Jr. This is the beginning of the end for you &amp; the rest of your crime family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@battleofever @IWasHrren @Jali_Cat @politico @POLITICOPress @POLITICOPro @Barnes_Law @tedcruz @natashakorecki Done]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone in this town is seeing somebody else. Everybody's tired of someone. Our eyes wander for help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catherinemccoin @kilonova_gold @MarineWithMoxie @Advil @talkinaway Vinegar can eliminate the mold smell too. I wash mine every use.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliVelshi What he did was despicable. Gaetz deserves reprimand.  The Congress does NOT need nor should it tolerate… https://t.co/w5EYFZ6CTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get on our books now for your 2019 events!  -Need Event Draping? -Need a Venue with In-House Decor options? -Need B… https://t.co/ebHmrcrHZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hail in Ocilla tonight. (📸: Chance Pridgen) @irwinsheriff @NathanWFXL @WFXL @NWSTallahassee #gawx https://t.co/0fpq9oOgju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EluTranscendent @EluSadscendent It’s okay!! I’m happy you’re working on yourself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please welcome @RocketStarSpace to the "It will launch when ready and no sooner." Club. We'll be ready when you are… https://t.co/0SiNI5LPwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Is truth dying in darkness at your paper? The senate voted down legislation, this week which would… https://t.co/ysLuaVdX16]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok on second thought there is hail and wow did Indiana weather have some swings this week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juice WRLD &amp; 24 kt gold face masques. I love our nights in together💗 @DMTK_Plocc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitter. Have a great Thursday 😄❤️ https://t.co/42k7Enx0kA]]></document><document><![CDATA[i haven’t been to the gym in a month but my competitive nature got the best of me so i didn’t let myself stop runni… https://t.co/2uAtPGmDm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bojangles gave me 5 chicken tenders instead of 4 - Look at God looking out for me 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Measurment stations! #3rdgrademath #3rdgradescience #Collaboration https://t.co/mlFA8EejCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The greatest thing I’ve ever learned from Dr. Tim Richard - be relentless, every day, every lesson, every opportuni… https://t.co/9HqioKbYoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein It’s better than a woman who’s husband is a piece of trash and she has committed multiple killings an… https://t.co/1pSHwrOHwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes Proof that Trump doesn't care one bit about what is best for the country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROTBre @atheist_punk1 @ChristianDefORG 1. Why have there been zero limbs reattached by Jesus, no one cared of cere… https://t.co/QvpuFv8aP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @ccholleytrainer celebrating a milestone today....5 years with AT&amp;T. #TUProud #LifeAtATT @quntut13… https://t.co/0ZL3JuFChq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andreaw62290297 @CNN My point was that CNN is known for it's daily barage of anti-Trump stories, many of which are… https://t.co/E3Arll8wDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dracodonniedash @joethunderstorm @DOMLEAFY @Aeid_5 lmfaooooo he said “ the seasoning “😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PacBlue @DamnItLynn @amishbonnet Morning happy Wednesday! Good news it’s Wednesday bad news it’s only Wednesday… https://t.co/8GnBAp8Yuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Jude Heroes are more than runners. They are helping find cures and save children battling cancer and other dead… https://t.co/GB4BYxIaAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Females: do you ever start to say something but then think that you don’t want to sound “too smart” ??  Was respond… https://t.co/zdBhJ0rbh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes, I wonder about people who seem to just find the negative in any situations, even beautiful ones. It must… https://t.co/9cLSRuXa1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allilapoint SCREAMING HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO MY BESTIE!!!! I hope today was absolutely amazing, Al! Love and miss you s… https://t.co/fjdssVBOGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Experimenting with colors and textures is one of my favorite things to do when creating 💙 . Day 5 of… https://t.co/pgLBlG0Tbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sky Kraken by @fremontbrewing @ Founders Ale House — https://t.co/1nNRv1di1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny he didn’t have any jokes to make about people who use nooses and bleach while staging a fake hate crime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_squwa I should have! My other coworkers were to busy to go with me though 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mymynags @lilibellmia Justin Fairfax claims he is innocent. His accuser needs to go to court and present her evide… https://t.co/GLZvICEfVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iouisavontrapp This just reminds that I have a lot of junk to unpack in therapy regarding the exact same problem.… https://t.co/npkoQYCZNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @CelebratingTCM &amp; @ThePoppity! This Is All About The Great Kenneth Tobey!📖📖📺📺 https://t.co/tEiWILgmC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a helpful tip, please check your car for critters before starting your car. This winter is starting to get col… https://t.co/AJq9E1wOgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re gifted this for #InternationalWomensDay!!! Thanks so much @MrUtica!!! Get at him Luvz! He got skillz! https://t.co/mjA4rBvdmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeopardy’s biggest fan, @mitcham_23, is heartbroken. As we all are 💔 Thinking of you and your family during this ti… https://t.co/hSZm2yyCdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized me and adrian dead ass the only ones from the house who WORKS tf lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @shauntfitness tells you to go faster, you go faster 😅 you also say potty words and make a lot of grunting noi… https://t.co/4vxQAKpACm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty pictures in the rochester_mn winter wonderland. #latergram #rochestermn #wintervibes #itsneverending… https://t.co/On7yNGxt2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vikeologist He cane up short in a lot of situations. Just didn’t show his full potential]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending out a HUGE “Thank You” to all who have purchased “Butterflies and Blossoms”.  You will never know how much… https://t.co/Lp4wDj4yqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking @BernieSanders Principled? Please release more than one year of tax returns. The only other 2020 candida… https://t.co/chhyDa58dX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cindyb23263 @HuffPost And you probably waste your time playing Video Games...LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodbye #ScottsdaleSnow Hello #SpringTraining2019. . . . #mcdowellmountains #thewestsmostwesterntown… https://t.co/NzOJKjvReC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although the 2-day hangovers are becoming more and more real, I’m thankful for everyone in my life who make each pa… https://t.co/2xkg5Dmy6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ashton5SOS @lietomeashxx @httpAshton5S0S both of which are beautiful btw, you just mean a lot to us and we wanna m… https://t.co/bHcSMrQhW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of February 25th #dool #days  Victor drops a bomb on Marlena.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this kid. With his depth perception issues he has to work harder than the rest of his team to get a hit… https://t.co/Cc0ymEMCrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join me in congratulating the Pre-AP World History team and their Special Education counterparts for being c… https://t.co/0yyc7XNRwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 Movie Theater Chains With Great Senior Discounts https://t.co/mO66D0VFya via @moneytalksnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being fabulous💁🏻‍♀️ eating a pizza 🍕 isn't all it's cracked up to be. #pizzalife #lasvegas @ Flour &amp; Barley https://t.co/Vgy2InVUGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahdiane78 I have the twilight soundtrack in my car right now, no shame]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday Morning Blessings Worldwide!!! #GodUp Do Have An Amazing Day On Purpose #DC #Amen.       #SleekDaSongtress @… https://t.co/evLlHg7he7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had one of the biggest wake up calls of my life and it tore me apart. College sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taro latte was very fragrant. The Tiramisu snowflake shaved ice melted in the mouth. Had to squeeze out a space in… https://t.co/DPPySip3ps]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grateful that my husband got me a gratitude journal so I can write about what I’m grateful for!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lítla Dímun, Faroe Islands' Cloud-Capped Beauty: @atlasobscura https://t.co/TtnCgL5Cq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone wanna get married? It doesn’t need to be legal. I just want to throw a big party for all my friends and make out]]></document><document><![CDATA[The week in Cohen hearings. Last pic of me with my trusty chair by @SarahMMimms. Ready to sleep forever now. @ Capi… https://t.co/UmUzPsuEBh]]></document></documents></author>