<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Riley wasn't kidding about the food at the arena tho lol https://t.co/1w1hb5kA40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestlingSheet Interesting thing to say, but she was not saying that when she came into the business after being dРђд https://t.co/WOWimaVPgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay then. Cheering for BYU is like having a punch card for a restaurant with a bland menu. Tonight the food was raРђд https://t.co/qQ0UFgpXKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retirement of skilled trades people outpaces other areas.https://t.co/7fLcDIIFtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayer en el the_met_museum_of_art   metropolitanmuseum disfrutando esta obra maestra de #claudemonet laРђд https://t.co/fHUmk9erOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great show last night with @PWILLIE1 &amp; @keetwit at @Norfolkstate. Blessings to @DJMERCY_ as well.  #musicРђд https://t.co/wNVDkpseG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andreas_Hopf Fwiw , todayРђЎs action really shows how much reliance was placed on Musk really delivering stellar newРђд https://t.co/FSXK9Jhu52]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliyanett ThatРђЎs how they give interviews, Tecatito does the same thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[7:00AM РђюHey bro you good, you still alive?РђЮ 7:02AM РђюIРђЎm fucked up at the bar with a stripperРђЮ   My friends always hРђд https://t.co/A8UARSlZYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT #NikePosters #Collection #GeorgeGervin #Iceman #Ballin ­ЪЈђ­ЪЈђ­ЪЈђ#classicmaterial #Ilovethisgame #NikeblazerРђд https://t.co/sqGt1vgkTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @SpeakerPelosi Oh, how nice. I bet the crowd was checked very closely. She expects the rest of us to be tРђд https://t.co/1bHJKWkCHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is absurd....an entire city this size needs a much larger budget. @41actionnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanteAtkins Policing the label doesn't mean much. But he's accomplished more in terms of progressive policy than aРђд https://t.co/YkPJDteme8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wild lose. The #Oilers slim hopes may well swing on these next 20 minutes. CanРђЎt miss the opportunity to climb to within 5.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Knight Crew rocking Crazy Jake's. #myfridaynight #wnymusic #supportlocalmusic #northtonawanda @ Crazy Jake's https://t.co/IIYWOGx4Id]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knight nation tell @VoteRandyFine How you feel about his threats to our great University, 2539 Palm Bay Rd NE, PalmРђд https://t.co/g81zIBukae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Unvato28 @Sneakkfreakk @bansky @DragonflyJonez What are you being paid to constantly put and Keep Your mouth on Lebron James?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ted. - Drinking a Great White Buffalo by @Buffbrew at @budsbarbq  Рђћ https://t.co/nblamZlO84]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update. IРђЎm down to boxers and a T-shirt. Already lost 10lbs. #HotHotHot]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ADOS is being used as another ploy to distract and dissuade black folks from voting in the 2020 presidential primaРђд https://t.co/dBkr4c6XsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartyBassWJZ Is Nicole going to a high school prom after the show today? #WhatUhDress]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbarro Trump didn't start a nuclear war. I suppose he'll brag about that. https://t.co/VazgFBMrSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@huronschools @huronsuper @PrincipalLamb @adscamella @Huron_Athletics @huron_cheer Congratulations to the HHS FR BoРђд https://t.co/iFdVYEpIUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcardib All that and Cheat... Still donРђЎt understand that move playa!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep...So True! If you feel IT, show IT! #live #long and #love #life #Believe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Eubank Body Slams James Degale.    Stay tuned. #TerenceCrawford #BeatYoAss #travisgotti  #blacyoungstaРђд https://t.co/AvcwwoF4sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CARLOSEES @elrenecito2 @Polobson @JavierEnrikez @nhaiper @Luperciote @arielvmachado @MenyArq @levantamiento1Рђд https://t.co/K2pnjXZJFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah umm... I hate to be the bearer of bad news but the Venezuelan situation is a bit more analytically complicatedРђд https://t.co/IYBSr85IMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScarlettxMae @GreatestFanEver @NSDSxxx @ZTentertainment That would be lovely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisEvans Thought the radio signals broke down over insane distances? I wonder if these sounds were once a conversation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olahungerhero https://t.co/mP5NOkjSU5 explains how to solve world hunger without huge investments. Allowing peopleРђд https://t.co/BQyd0Ldr7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealBenCarson Of course your not going anywhere. Your A Man of integrity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Safe or out you decide #canon80d #canon_photos #canon #chuypatabionica #instagram #baseball #stolenbase #stealhomeРђд https://t.co/ZBfgPnBzyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsMarlena Yeah he doesnРђЎt look like a great guy at all, but tweets from past isnРђЎt proof he said that tonight.Рђд https://t.co/bt5yM93lUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[IРђЎll never forget my 10 years Pastoring here !!! #GreatPeople#GreatTimes#Painful#40minDrive#247SomersetSt @ The SafРђд https://t.co/JIJdXhRrue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer                            Now you donРђЎt stand up for Israel and Jewish people all over Ilan Omar, TaliРђд https://t.co/9hn3965G10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodgers_randi That being said good on them, their fans deserve to see good baseball in that park]]></document><document><![CDATA[GameStop told me retrofest hacksaw Jim Duggan should be available at their warehouse March 10 and should be distributed soon after.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anniekarni Usually cult leaders like Trump pray on old people with no support systems -after @LindseyGrahamSC lostРђд https://t.co/vDyKneg56q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreggDoyelStar If I'm looking for some good Indiana HS bball in central Indy, which games should I check out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steelmusician @RealSaavedra I didn't say I smoke it. What I have said is our drug problem in politics isn't pot. IРђд https://t.co/sPhw6svcDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergioSarmiento Lo que me asombra es lo delgada que tienen la piel TODOS los cercanos a L├│pez incluido ├Еl. ┬┐Qu├Е noРђд https://t.co/MdP5UOyBse]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheFutureBelongsToYou #DoGreatThings #FridaysForFuture #FridayWisdom #westwoodhighschoolscience IG@mroshields https://t.co/1w1mgNPRWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieLRutter I forgot what I was going to reply. How embarrassing.­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatSeabass @NuclearAnthro @SwiftOnSecurity Massive attacks of ICBM silos in North Dakota]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IncredCanemian @b6sgt @GOPChairwoman Granted, but with downturns. The opposite of faith is presumption. So, you saРђд https://t.co/krKgeHRJLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slwein These people wouldn't know (or care about) an actual conflict of interest if it was a rat biting their tiny penis off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @TempleChurch and @dadrumwright for the warm welcome today. Also, thanks to @girlscouts Troop 318 forРђд https://t.co/UEeHsOod1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there a lot of scalpers at basketball games in Tuscaloosa like there is football? Asking for myself. @AaronSuttles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scivs505 @gribblekz Yeah JimРђЎll throw the coke in one direction as a diversion, while you run the opposite way]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- what do you plan to repair? C- old consoles, every time I start I get all sorts of people wanting me to fix therРђд https://t.co/ze1ByxtUTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was just on the #radio, sharing insight about how we should be supporting entrepreneurs in the USA. Shared about soРђд https://t.co/uoy3e6LVtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz d├Гa del amor y la amistad! En especial al amor de mi vida ­ЪўЇ mi esposa, compa├▒era, amiga, mi todo, gracias porРђд https://t.co/KKUBxp3iCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow Akbar Cook, Well deserved!! I'm glad that your story has a national audience! Keep doing what youРђЎreРђд https://t.co/sAl0qfLxhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[And tell me how they got that pretty little face on that pretty little frame, girl ­ЪЌБ­ЪјХ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennieFinch Inviting you to U of MD to attend Bohemia Manor High School going for itРђЎs 3rd State title! Pitcher MaРђд https://t.co/kDYm19UKHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor Corris started the Princess Half Marathon! https://t.co/6L3qCBSrTC #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[A family of ducks greets us in our backyard at Boatmeadow, Eastham, Cape Cod, Massachusetts on a cold February mornРђд https://t.co/dJNANOPsr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moving day... After 3 and a half years living in Hollywood we are moving back to the valley and I get to drive thisРђд https://t.co/BIx9XYxB4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES! Saturday with Live Football on TV! Thank you @TheAAF and #TNT and @nflnetwork for the games today! #AAF #Football]]></document><document><![CDATA[JamminРђЎ Chef Dale #chipndale #jamminchefs #disneycharacter #foodandwinefestival #disneycaliforniafoodandwineРђд https://t.co/XnzeAFTT1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metsandnesfan Damn... the thumbnail made it look like a new contra game with that c in the logo lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsanders_3 I kept saying last night does somebody not think they should guard Luke]]></document><document><![CDATA[SB250 passes through committee 10-6, with one pass vote. Now heads to full House. @WHAS11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lately IРђЎve been sleeping through my first two alarms so I set atleast 4!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have some good feelings about @Raiders this season! Welcome@to #RaiderNation @AB84]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey look, everybody! ItРђЎs preliminary takeaways from the Class A girls state tournament field! #ArgusPreps #SDPrepsРђд https://t.co/lfOuhgURUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm I see a familiar face ­ЪЉђ­ЪЉђ   РђЮ5 Cards prospects to watch in Spring TrainingРђЮ https://t.co/3Tz1wzhh00 via @MLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolaus I bet thatРђЎs great in the spring with the garage door open and a nice breeze]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro what the fuck are you doing dying your mustache??? Have some self respect @AB84]]></document><document><![CDATA[My partner (on the ambulance) has just informed me, we drove 133 miles yesterday without leaving town.  GРђЎmorning!  #MyEMSday]]></document><document><![CDATA[To see or reprort power outages in oue region, click here. Stay safe tonight! РЏѕ https://t.co/udY4Gq2HNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Wernick is going IN: #JUST #cdnpoli @Clerk_GC : "Anyone who's following American politics these days, if you can stand it... "]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick tour of the new National Aquarium animal rescue center #connectingthedots https://t.co/aG6sUP6rFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT #2 De Mi Bella ├Їdola @anettemicheltv Durante Su ├Ѕpoca De Modelo (Parte 1) @AnetteMFans https://t.co/Kg5BYnLWUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It would be nice if the #POTUS would do his job, not attack an individual citizen with irrelevantРђд https://t.co/6f2szGjWkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more video of Screaming Orphans. Find this band of sisters on the inter-webs. ­ЪЉЇ­Ъца #screamingorphansliveРђд https://t.co/HWeoS15MUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OhioState &amp; @cwru are partnering to advance LED lighting efficiency  research. Collaboration! https://t.co/b03kbz49D4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExpertComedy @trackie81 @riordainn @thejtlewis @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews @idgeorgio What a clown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alissa914 @business @AOC That's what is meant by "The price of liberty is eternal vigilance." Not all enemies of oРђд https://t.co/kINb70jzjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eghsbrock @alicekeeler Grades are where you are, not what you are. Grades with personalized feedback is more impacРђд https://t.co/jT5FumdcOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenrryCastro1 @IcaroRD @javierrosa03 @LeonelFernandez @VinicioSenador Un cristiano mediocre y envidioso que quiereРђд https://t.co/dzGSe61biV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gift shop at the Greensboro airport has a section for college sports, with dedicated shelf space for Duke, NC SРђд https://t.co/o694u9SpWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@storyheadjillmc What really bothers me here is the underlying implication that UU World is publishing to a cisgendРђд https://t.co/JOucE7k77v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wilson leads Theodore Roosevelt 30-8 after one quarter of the DCIAA Championship game. #DMVhoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mickeys10thdag @kimguilfoyle What about tv? Radio?phones?  I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on EРђд https://t.co/S3jtypfLX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One ! !    https://t.co/92qDM8wrwo https://t.co/eMI136QUhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @ArkadiuszKula @RickandMorty We knew you would, as much as people were pestering you about it lmao...  What's next on the agenda??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods This woman has made a career of being stupid. She comes across as childish. Don't be fooled. She isРђд https://t.co/jkasHmHz7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last event I was apart of was a successful partnership with Troy Johnson at BreaudРђЎs Restaurant in downtown NatРђд https://t.co/PjkVgpLWQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday February 13 - Axios AM: Mike's Top 10:    House plans vast Russia probe;     New street name;     2 goodРђд https://t.co/mWNruQ1lQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardWebbNY @Akld_DHB Glad we turned the weather on for you! Hope the talk went well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends: This doesn't represent me or the Jesus that loves me....but what do I know, I'm a dummy...luckily Jesus loРђд https://t.co/yNxa9eoc0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColinCowherd Awesome take Colin. So the MVP of the league isnРђЎt РђюeliteРђЮ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsteph88 @thistallawkgirl @TomiLahren Who is the hypocrite here sir? Posting pictures of you and your rabbit briРђд https://t.co/OhfM68qaGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh!!! I just noticed. 300 followers. Thank you! Time to celebrate with a cup of coffee while IРђЎm staring at one spoРђд https://t.co/V1NNGnLCDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlosvecchio @EP_President Que tonada de pelo les han dado...practiquen el Guaran├Г pues van para Paraguay]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIRLS BASKETBALL: End of the third quarter - Republic 34, Rock Bridge 33. Turnovers hurting the Bruins still, but wРђд https://t.co/Wyse3uV3r7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bacon Mac &amp; cheese cone Mmmmm @ Disney California Adventure Park https://t.co/0AgXNsPpyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllsBellsInPA @AOC @jasoncabinda I asked the same question and just like you, I got NO ANSWER.  Typical divisiveness.]]></document></documents></author>