<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thank you Miss Jackie for always going the extra step and being kind to others all the time! #afterhours #RAKday… https://t.co/qLfF80hRdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashaBanksWWE &amp;@itsBayleyWWE You both are amazing &amp; you deserve it! Love You both!!💜💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching what matters for us all! A prepared workforce fuels our economy. #CTEWorks #BPCCProud @Gayle5Flowers… https://t.co/EDNXGNuv0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SanDiegoSummit @MarkMilliganDPT @SandyHiltonPT @fyzio4u @CoherenceMed @IrmaRaste @ShereesePubHlth @EMRAnswers… https://t.co/WuxXaGSni2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spoutsmith The ashes are from the palms burned on Palm Sunday. Ash Wednesday is a Holy Day of Obligation for Catho… https://t.co/7lUYaJSXNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacoTimeNW Gooey beans and cheese Wrapped in a beanie blanket Want all the hot sauce  #haiku #burritos 🌯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaireCervenak @DisruptedTv @WorldProfessor @brewerhm @loudlearning @DavidGeurin @SteeleThoughts Try having student… https://t.co/kLhHzr0ds8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand why someone would fake getting attacked. Very disturbing indeed, eh Bob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisQuinn64 @MaireCervenak @SteeleThoughts @deem_ellen @DavidGeurin @DrJStephensVP @MathDenisNJ @dene_gainey… https://t.co/zcHgvQ7MEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything turns out how it’s supposed to in the end. We don’t call it out — it calls itself out, we solidify &amp; God provides.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo unas ganas de ir a desconectarle la bocina al vecino que ni se imaginan !]]></document><document><![CDATA[My voice came back for 11 hours of my shift and decided to leave me again at the end of it hmmmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been saying I’m tired for the last hour but you best bet my booty was boppin’ for LIT90s on Seth Meyers. Kille… https://t.co/gboAIR0BUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TillysTower Cool beans...💜 (Maybe not THE Tower, but her Boxcar)😉 https://t.co/Z5lpgIj3uO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GloryFitness  Don't Get Upset, Get Healthy.... #gotthatgodjuice praisefittour #love #fitness #fitnessmodel radiope… https://t.co/P1JTmXb5pD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop begging unimportant people for their time or convincing them to choose you ! You got wayyyy too much to offer… https://t.co/IjB6L1ZDxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEPTA_SOCIAL The reason I asked was the app shows the Saturday schedule inbound. But outbound still shows regular schedule.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHeartTheaterNY please pick me for the speed dating with the boys @CNCOmusic  always try so hard to see them and n… https://t.co/jf2BemckiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to wake up in 6 hours and I'm still not asleep this is going to be really rough tomorrow 💣]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: won’t go to mcdonald’s w my friends bc i’m trying to be healthy  also me: eats 10lbs of snacks directly when i get home]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobdickeywx I have not emptied my gauge since it started Thursday night. At 7 tonight 2.25”. Not gonna empty it… https://t.co/mIoMC7KWI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi rutina de las mañanas que no me deja dormir hasta tarde https://t.co/fz4tTCFaTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brynn’s first NHL game. 🏒🏒 Fun was had. @ Pepsi Center https://t.co/JC9MfS7trK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My shoulders are sore sometimes trying to keep my hopes up” - @TheoVon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling sad? Poor your unhealthy emotions into obsessing over the Jonas Bros like you did when you were 13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntaresVazAla @ElFinanciero_Mx @MorenaSenadores @Pajaropolitico @MorenaEnGto @morenagtova @kuali_noticias… https://t.co/UYO9mVMjcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimksavesworld @AmericanAntiFed @realDonaldTrump free join.... :  https://t.co/C6Ym4uzxbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you get a Christmas present from me, this will be it. These are too funny.... https://t.co/HB88CigoU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally cannot even breathe without my residents thinking I'm being a bitch 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TO_WinterOps @680NEWS Need salt ar renforth and rathburn..sidewalks are impossible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @ccatmpt @SLBriscoe @thatsVeryKari @Cbp8Cindy @joneill55 @suziday123 @cowineco @AkronWineGuru… https://t.co/oPj9S7Ikbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeep I  just purchased a Jeep for the first time . I am a business owner and always buy new vehicles. This purple… https://t.co/HbiC498Amn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could not get someone’s name tatted on me, even a marriage certificate isn’t enough stability for me 😭✌🏽. You got… https://t.co/GPJeJBQBE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[me jamming to  #HIGH1X on my way to class this morning https://t.co/1E8dAFbMW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a privilege to chat with these two forces of nature in the utility sector! Thank you to them and to… https://t.co/UQlwkx20ur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash When will Schiff be investigated for his activities we need to declassify what senators and Congressme… https://t.co/pm3FPzvEqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚜️These lovely talented Men! With Ronald and David at the KW luxury event 🌎#KellerWilliams #realestate… https://t.co/25xGqKd0ZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[One can hope people will be disgusted by the artcle. My fear is that they will think it’s no big deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimberr9 @giannamarchese1 She did this to me today while she was in the drive thru and I was in Starbucks https://t.co/KhjiNHpbgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[House Democrats are working #ForThePeople to restore honesty, fairness, and integrity to our elections after report… https://t.co/R6koAk9NNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialSPGB @VP Um wut...Maduro is a socialist pos what kind of bullshit you trying to float here how the do is t… https://t.co/IrS2szalRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcbridemelissa @wwwbigbaldhead I think you guys should play a little bit for us the next time your at a convention… https://t.co/7CCgQxNxwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok being home in the rain+ sick + postmates is v dangerous! I wanna keep ordering food 🙃😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK miss CAROL!!! captain marvel was all that and more. I think she can just flick Thanos out of existence tbh, if n… https://t.co/lgV9necxaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wisdomwednesday always wear safety gear whilst changing springs 😂  #truth #osha #safety #safetyfirst #springs https://t.co/7mzL0iSLjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CiaraCKnight @danawanzer And the church said amen! We definitely need more scholarship in this area!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little glass art to brighten your day💥🌈  And a lil bling!✨ @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/Z4aHCTsMTc… https://t.co/XLKtApFivC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodo 🗺️📍??? Set them/it free.!!!!  🌻🌱🕷️🌎🙏    Do you really want to 🐝the ones who shattered the lives of children o… https://t.co/S1qOsOVkXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will never understand why people stand in front of the gate as soon as boarding begins, only to stand there and wai… https://t.co/Z0oofxSLk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wordopposite @DED1960 @AOC There are even post it notes that are made out of recycled paper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re up and live on @WPGC 95.5!   https://t.co/dOV7IgZvqt https://t.co/idgU3jFxzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m already following you,  but I do love a great patriot train. All aboard!! 🙏🇺🇸💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRamkey: *puts on In The Air Tonight by Phil Collins*  @DomLiuzzo: “oh come on, you’re gonna make me shit”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr trump I support what you are trying to do for this country but what about all is little guys just out there tryi… https://t.co/oFyBwglyaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. to leave 200 American peacekeepers in Syria after pullout https://t.co/SO503HtKbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to one of my favorite women! Love you Barbara! I bet you don’t remember the time we met at the airpo… https://t.co/m72ilEqe4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pencil sketch...needs inking @ Ithaca, New York https://t.co/v6ldylwvUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mchooyah @MailOnline Is this the one who went to Yale? I know he has a lot of kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[introspective showers late at night when you’re high as fuck https://t.co/YtkqOPhzNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did the senate Intel committee ever think that #RealityWinner should be thanked instead of jailed? @NancyPelosi… https://t.co/fWJVYXd3g6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cant get enough of  spectacular display of nature. Everything is iced over. Iced branches, up close and mesmerizing… https://t.co/ix2BsxhTfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely correct! Something tells me he is using his money along with other financial backers to build this wall.… https://t.co/uBbR4sFUKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbmk7 @lmlTN @djrothkopf Disagree. Panic is no answer. There are 20,000,000 Veterans in this country. None of us t… https://t.co/0vPKstMIp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[To amend my previous Tweet.... Yes, I know the  @fccincinnati game is in Seattle. I was printing off parking passes… https://t.co/DtwkrEQ5B4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Mail arrived today. Thanks, Teri @teriborchers, and yes I love them!! https://t.co/YMyPmLf6LI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy here is amazing! Check him out his name is Chris Cole! Doing big things. Follow him on FB! He is going pla… https://t.co/vA3TAMwSXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve realized that it’s not everyone else.. that I’m the one that’s unrelatable]]></document><document><![CDATA[*in Music and form analysis class* Me and Paloma humming the main song of Phantom of the opera *seconds later* The… https://t.co/TYyPLsadbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vayesfan @AstridWinegar @ericcron @pam_brundige @goldeemxtra1 @HollieWolfen @XDaneelOlivaw @AMHotFlash… https://t.co/Q71OI77h6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AralynnsMomma We keep shouting it!  Everyone thinks it will not happen to them ... Until it does.  #9PMRoutine #BeepBeep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dragging myself into work a little early at the end of a long, long, discouraging week, I flip on the lights and am… https://t.co/1v5z1s52vZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister Here is the visual @ProudResister https://t.co/UTs0VlHVi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I chose to vote versus a manicure 💅🏼 (@ PS 13Q The Clement C Moore School in Elmhurst, NY) https://t.co/bjf0QnGXN4 https://t.co/HHwFlMVUun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@millerslite Ok so is this u saying u cheat on me with girls you meet on flat earth fb pages?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Hormones are so messed up. I was off HRT for 5 weeks before my surgery and then prescribed a higher dose after s… https://t.co/erluiMQgQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[4/20 of 2017 was probably the best 420 I ever had lol my stomach was hurtin the next day from laughin so fuckin hard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halsey Catching a cold too. Hope you get to feeling better H. Hugs from H-town. Love you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you didn’t take the extra time to let your car warm up this morning and it shows.!]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy valentine's day my love. two years down... many more to go.❤️🥂 @ Disneyland https://t.co/i4kqgnp0RD]]></document><document><![CDATA[ROLL OVER | Such an incredible exercise for stretching out the muscles of the back...this felt amazing to stretch o… https://t.co/ZdPA1pfhyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDebateHitman @StephenAtHome @SenSanders @SenWarren @AOC Well, I did that before GOP started voting as a block r… https://t.co/Cv4KOvDn3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@egoldie80 I remember you talking about @budlight orange a while back and finally got around to trying it. It is de… https://t.co/h6GBo57Vnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[A PRIVILEGED, BLACK and GAY man tried to not ONLY blame our @POTUS , but cause a race war, when there was no need!… https://t.co/D55ofOg9rL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surrprise, surprise. Jr makes the same hand gesture as Trump and white supremacists make.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monbebes let's help our boys get to the rope. They work so hard, let's make Alligator #1 https://t.co/tuEaGmFnaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta be skeptical about shooting your shot based off someone’s social media. A lot of y’all don’t live up to what… https://t.co/SCBb0Zf4nl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pearl the Wonder Dog, quite possibly the cutest farm dog you will ever meet. @ Unity Farm Sanctuary https://t.co/4vibcv4Njl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets I disagree, Ivanka has created nothing for Americans. She has stolen the designs of other shoe man… https://t.co/F1QYWZRpWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTA @TheMTASucks I have been waiting 15 minutes for the Q23 bus to Ditmars while four Q23s to East Elmhurst have p… https://t.co/AS3yQ0Y8Lg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoodRDKD I was thinking that @KiaWellCoach (my NTR 351 student) meant that the cost of a food item included the he… https://t.co/SepheKlwXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I hate this Gavino guy ! He is destroying California! I thought Brown was bad but Gavino is by far… https://t.co/PmYW8h6TkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If everything is a "bombshell" or constitutional crisis, then nothing is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 Hi Max! I'm Little Bit! Sending you lots of huggies and kissies and cuddles too!!!!😻😸😽❤❤❤💋💋💋 https://t.co/Nap3o3a6lY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may have restocked my @zipfizz bowl. #energyfordays #zipfizz #everydamnedday @ Paper Street Soap Company https://t.co/Niv6bcCFIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone stole my nice ass Kate spade blanket out of the dries at school.... I’m fucking transferring]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #IdeaSlam was an amazing experience! The #Neuroscience materials that we purchased from #MIbased… https://t.co/IvRrROsnnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a difference in being a Christian who wants so shove religion down people’s throats to share the love of Je… https://t.co/8i9jPWEr1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venus always shines bright in the early morning! #stargazing https://t.co/jPVIjPWnAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimHalterman @BerlinStation @TVInsider @LelandOrser @EPIXHD ROBERT WILL NOT DIE, UNDERSTAND! @EPIXHD EPIXHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/TQhrlx1MCn]]></document></documents></author>