<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the heads-up pal!!!  So appropriate for sooooo many drivers.    #winning #drivesafe #coffeeplease l @ Gi… https://t.co/sFu2GT84gE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frequentbeef Are you running the City of Lies box set? Or just setting your game in Ryokō Owari Toshi?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wolf course we are playing is 7,604 yards haha longest course in Nevada]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAS LEGALLY TURNED 180° TO THE NORTH. YOU HAVE CONFIRMED THE JEWISH ANTI¬AMERICAN REACTION SECURITY LIE ABSOLUTE CR… https://t.co/0ukgZot04Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nprpolitics @NPR @NCConservation how scary is this?  #ClimateChangeIsReal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_keim @SouthBeachDad @Redskins So are they just going to sacrifice the season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatboydantee I like comparing women to breakfast foods. Telling a girl she smells like a homemade buttermilk waff… https://t.co/ZnVyU5xajq]]></document><document><![CDATA[chicago @igerschicago @chi_bucketlist visit.chicago @choosechicago visitchicagoforeigner ivisitchicago… https://t.co/TY2WRTyp0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AUnderfoot @silver53warrior @TheRalphRetort Probably nothing will happen to this puke.   That’s not the American way.  MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessinthenorth No idea, I've only been there once (with @paciorettys on her last day here). I hope so, though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidFo20074049 😂😂😂.  Dans ce cas honte aux autres de ne pas le faire 😉😉😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I witnessed some real bullshit, not one club I went to played box Chevy by Rick Ross. Where have the times gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Word of the day @ Syracuse DAV Volunteer Transportation Network https://t.co/FtTJrHPqxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re not playing Bill Withers and Al Green for your Valentine tonight, do you even love them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[are you excited for i can't get enough?   i'll be honest... i'm not that excited just cause it seems like another g… https://t.co/jT0v864qrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BumfOnline @secupp Baseless? You’re an idiot. Where’s Reports of record jobs, record low unemployment? Disease inf… https://t.co/aq5MY0jWs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erogers @kclightrail @RuKCMO @WesKCMO @polycitywander Leave it to an engineer to get lost in semantics but if we c… https://t.co/HAnFMhsFgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fun time on the air today with my friends from @Star1055 🤩.  Thanks so much for having me.  Happy Valentine’… https://t.co/hxcMfkn29d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think anyone will truly know the full story of how she entered my life. I’m okay with that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tequila Barrel Lime Gose by @Boulevard_Beer @ Oakview — https://t.co/0aKVUaxNCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inthefade @suedeHQ I’d go with Dog Man Star. Their s/t debut is stellar as well. But Dog Man Star is their masterp… https://t.co/tCZIkTig3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris97953402 @TreasonHappens @Barkforlove1 @DavMicRot Socialism does not work it never has and it never will and t… https://t.co/EuZqi2I9h6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard the Emoji Love Song for the first time... https://t.co/apDrq5rKqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[bridesmaidmepretty Getting ready for her big day!!! #blackoutboxing #cardioboxfit #aesthetic #aestheticsarmy… https://t.co/fkw3q03iZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AzarelDc @orgas2090 @Gerardotigre1 @TenochHuerta Que gran hombre ese sr pasaporteao']]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter Let’s compromise to@include veterans, active and reserve members of the military, and taxpayers...😆😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Linden Yard Fleet Operations in Brooklyn, NY https://t.co/ctzH4iv56t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m seeing it would have been Chris Farley’s 55th today. Here’s a clip I’ve always been a fan of. Check up on your… https://t.co/axsGw6v562]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful to have received this in the mail today. In the midst of a crazy week, this is the perfect balm. Sunday mo… https://t.co/todDDgY5PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[TROPICANA FIELD Fenway Wrigley Miller Citi Shea Old Yankee Camden old Nationals Marlins Park SunTrust]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con la memorable atajada de @yosoy8a, que arrojó comparativos con la mítica tapada de Gordon Banks, también a Brasi… https://t.co/cWdbBLUGQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to bed early, woke up late and now I’m trying to make it to work on time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christianity: Making Your Faith in God Stronger https://t.co/gogt6hncIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was searching for something I had done many years ago and came across a call out from @evanokelly and then anothe… https://t.co/5sJmXICfwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My tempo run today was a very challenging but rewarding run! And I'm really starting to love these lightweight new… https://t.co/52mDD9CdyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[FATAL ACCIDENT -on I-10WB all lanes blocked at Hammond Blvd - it seems to be a single vehicle on its side @FCN2go https://t.co/AzLxEAuEkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinrmcclure Not all region have orgs but some do. So, well resourced institutions have reps across the US. For e… https://t.co/95PuVuouiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteOlson @bradyfortexas @Steve_Riggle @joepaulo Gdamn! We sure do need prayers at this point! That idiot in chief is killing us!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎖️The FitLife 30🎖️ Day 1  It's the FIRST DAY!🤣🤣 • • • • • #thefitlife30 #day1 #noprocessedfood  #lchfmealplan… https://t.co/Y6uHTT4gE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[A star is born 🍿 Our Grand Baie Juice Box now available in Pool Colorblock 💦 @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/cOwXF4K4kc]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could throw a rock into a lake and be the last person to ever touch that rock until the end of time]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's hard to contain my excitement with hearing we still have nuclear tensions with the North Korean government.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We’re trying to make it easier on (our players) so we can play at a certain physical level that we didn’t play at last year.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting off this spa weekend for kellyymoon bday bash! Thanks for my homie allen.wong.39 for letting me carpool to… https://t.co/ARVQRbok1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do get noticed in all the noise in the marketplace?🤭🤭#customeracquisition #LeadGeneration #leads #SocialMedia… https://t.co/wd62qKHp3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFordSUPERfan @Senators @FordCanada F150 Ford Pickup.  But of course. Darcy.    Have a good day @SensOfficeRalph]]></document><document><![CDATA[nobody at all: my brain cells after 1am:   👈🤪👉                                                 🦵🦵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united An hour wait to get to the gate and then no groundcrew there to take care of the ramp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Dude leave this. This will make or brake you- laugh. Stop calling names. You’re better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trader Joe’s doesn’t have anything on this place. #mexicanmarket #cbus @ Las Michoacanas Market https://t.co/OIJZdneE0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cluck_25 Are you referring to thre person who tweeted this thinking or the way she’s saying people think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pray he is a good and moral man, the people of Venezuela deserve someone good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edubutbroke @thedebtshrink1 .@EveryDollar is an excellent app! It helps you crush those baby steps 💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Hardbassjunkie Heard so many bad stories with spirit 🤣.  3 hour flight turns into 10 hours 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d have a whiskey n coke split on a 2 gram sack of ❄️ n bring the bong wit @G_Eazy 😂❄️ we’re the same]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vuelvo a repetir la pregunta; Cuál se ve mejorado ahora...Brando Ingram o Kyle Kuzma 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mas5665 @HeroSnowden @EmmaVigeland He got the most democratic votes from texas. Higher than Obama. TEXAS. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zeiger_selma @BernieSanders Oh so you’re not worried about Bernie’s lack of tax paying?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've always only thought of myself as American but left demands I view myself as white male So b it We Founded it Fought 4 it Died 4 it Cont]]></document><document><![CDATA[No idea what’s going on or what this says but I want nothing more than to be this man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraJaneGrace Is it April yet? I cannot wait to see your shows in Wisconsin next month!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GroveCityAD @professorbriggs @GCC_WaterPolo @GCC_bsb @GCC_MLax @GCC_XCTF Giving him Monday off? Would be a great way to say thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in Middle-earth History Yr: 3019 - Entmoot begins. | Of all the 'moots, this one is my favorite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Bramble Blackberry Sour Ale by @Maltmaster1 @ Aspetuck Brew Lab — https://t.co/AkmUkfoxEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[In edu, we too often stress about scores... I wonder what would happen if we instead empowered students by helping… https://t.co/YssIIUmanA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WickedVfl @kvmidd85 You don’t think Trump supporters routinely cruise the sub-freezing streets of Chicago at 2 a.m… https://t.co/pWdbhEG2AG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjb_plm @parrischariz Waiting on that “DC’s Legends of Tomorrow” reference then 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetTipNet @JEttiP And I didn’t know they had more then 1 till last night when this alert went out.... I hope they… https://t.co/RKCUgOh9Q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kodak Black - Testimony https://t.co/RuYGoEavxk via @YouTube #MostInspiringandrelatablemusic… https://t.co/T3AJ46v3k1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls OMG the hate speech coming from Trump, Steve King for years and Republicans are quiet, This woman i… https://t.co/6J4p2Kkv9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnoopDogg 🐩 the easy  bake oven is boring you..Your passed smoke and don't choke 🍆 now you want French fried poodl… https://t.co/5NztMVQNBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[4.  So, much like the health of our oceans, rain patterns in cities are a litmus test for our survival.]]></document><document><![CDATA[👙😎🌊 POOL SEASON IS HERE!! So TODAY, come out to @taobeach and enjoy DJ CLA as she headlines!! 👙😎🍾 LADIES OPEN BAR O… https://t.co/KWyyW7suAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It all started with a “Good morning 😍😍😍” text... I knew she was up to something.. children #staywoke These parents… https://t.co/bOZH74dojs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super Congratulations to all of our Mountie DECA winners.  By competing in the States, you were already WINNERS.  M… https://t.co/3gGwnSOiMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ccMOqOQwgm well now we have dog park Debbie calling the cops on a black man because his dog humped her… https://t.co/RhL2sx3cAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbystrobelt @TurboGooch3000 I gave up, stacy is gonna be tucking this boy in and cutting the crust off of his san… https://t.co/FXXFA6Vv8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nevaevapressed @khaliqrodriquez Definitely not. Repetitively saying it, low key a sign of insecurity about it too]]></document><document><![CDATA[No bake Vegan Carrot Cake?? 🧁🧁 👨🏽‍🍳 @Chef_CB1978 👨🏽‍🍳 🍽 @Chef_CB1978 🍽 #eat #fresh #catering #chef @ North Carolina https://t.co/0sSscqSFSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellySchukart That’s incredible. I never even imagined that as a thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you listened to Recco Hoopscast yet? Check it out here: https://t.co/TkUL9bXuJ1  Yay!  I’m famous!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so proud of the art we’ve created together! Our premiere of THE LADDER at Boston Conservatory’s Winterworks las… https://t.co/Yfs5YbATNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally saw a basketball ref call steps on a Eurostep. Unfortunate turn of events for Holy Cross.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at J. No Lounge at Kensington Court in Jersey City, NJ https://t.co/aeuhaBTtvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s also worth noting that I first found out about this nearly a month ago, after being super sick with pneumonia,… https://t.co/36KwpA6FTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing up #Catholic, you are taught early on about God's unconditional love. It didn't take long for me to learn t… https://t.co/hEMsWa4MeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast today, in Dallas, shooting some @realwomenofjoy and @gridironmen promos w/ all these awesome friends ch… https://t.co/JXEj6JOehi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor Miller lob to Kate Orazen for layup. @CFBlackTigers 21, @hudwbb 13 #RCNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soniachocron Lo peor de todo, es que es un resentimiento de la boca para afuera, por demás hipócrita, que raya más… https://t.co/KLUHBELYfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gracietpt New York doesn't have to step it. They have goods on Trump, and are just waiting to strike.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile Real speeds, on the I-170 Hollywood Freeway. Avoiding megabits so it's more understandable. 14 MEGABYTES a… https://t.co/0MvqQdJ8ca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inside #Manufactory, #Tartine’s massive bakery restaurant. What is it?  Noun. A manufacturing process; a particular… https://t.co/NVNhwqZzpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3HL4LIFE Hey @CoachJCrosby , a whiskey fueled coach Boom should win this hands down right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome movie. I'm old enough to remember the public warnings about this film]]></document><document><![CDATA[@engineco16 @ServingChalk @ai6yrham Never !!!!    Hahaha  where has all the drought and global warming gone? So muc… https://t.co/K1tiakfxgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funtimeseddie @SheilaBx2 @music4peeps @hockeybtch71 @zerogspot @kitawny24 @Mukund_M27 @Hashtagger_007 @stamishinc… https://t.co/Owh7moNFkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more reminder: Hononegah welcome home party at 11 AM in the gym!! Be there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about having a few this weekend if I don’t work anybody wanna join]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardbranson ..continue with the disgrace (songs...) #LaceyRock (migration problems, surplus housing/enforcement… https://t.co/stN3hkLHtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bocasummers @NWS_MountHolly Good thing is...people were already "depressed" and broke in 1932, so it would have ju… https://t.co/uy8YnKdhJl]]></document></documents></author>