<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I am literally looking at furniture for my guest bedroom when 1) I haven’t even found a house yet and 2) I am going… https://t.co/UFKX0DuTzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @GabbyGiffords @lucymcbath @SpeakerPelosi That is great!   Ow we have to enforce it. We need to hav… https://t.co/vi3ejJjewD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maddie takes her 'stinky medicine' once a day. She says it doesn't make her giggly or hungry but it helps her with… https://t.co/GheQTdIMCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS  Hopefully kim jumg un will wake up before you leave and come to his senses!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is that quote?  Not bad peopke doing things, but good people saying nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if I could stop having dreams about pete davidson who will never love me, that would be fine 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ok117363638 @erikajayne But then they lack experience. Harris is being blasted for being a prosecutor. People evol… https://t.co/auenk61RLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe this lady parked by me just hit my door with her car door and gave ME a dirty look when I went to g… https://t.co/QLoOo3DQvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grownish I love the show bc it explores so much more than the party life while in college. I have two in college a… https://t.co/HV0IqKXNya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe Judge read my piece? 😬👍  Wilken: “post-eligibility scholarships to complete undergrad or graduate degrees at… https://t.co/ubWMmmcbLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicolas Cage is the white Samuel L. Jackson yo. Homie is in every Netflix &amp; low budget movie ever made.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@my2gr8girls @Chrisconsrv1776 @smoore1966 she said Obama was guilty of murder. (probably due to military in Afghanistan, etc. is my thought)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imactuallyashhh I was obsessed with the fact that we have the same birthday 😂😂😂 Nick Jonas, forever my first love]]></document><document><![CDATA[Americans being Americans @ Beacon (Metro-North station) https://t.co/uw6AXhHIPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Later night lights brings out all the neighborhood kids.... tag, bike riding, hide and go seek, swimming.   Oh to b… https://t.co/hBxyqLRgmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProtectAllLife I'm not sure I said all. I don't know what all of anything does. What I do know is what I've experienced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WuChangMo @GreenTop1947 @MelissaCBS6 @jonburkettcbs6 @CBS6 @8NEWS @NBC12 @jeffkatzshow Beyond newsworthy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosentic_xo @TheRightMelissa @JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump Read John 3:16. It will bring your heart peace for eternity.🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't understand why why WHY celebrities HAVE to post their problems, or whatever on social media. They don't kno… https://t.co/iLDjiaU5Vf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really bothered me when AB said he put his life on the line.  Really???? Such disrespect for all the men and wom… https://t.co/EMk8A4KPIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to accept the challenge from @goheels1984 to post 7 professional book covers in 7 days. No excerpts or review… https://t.co/RwSNP5hr4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harsh_Voice @Zells26 If you can stay home, I would advise it. Ice in Dallas used to shut down the whole darn state… https://t.co/5rqnuwsVMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melindas4u2 @RyanAFournier I guess ALL blacks, African-American or “Negroes” should “go back” to Africa, as well...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu No I think trump is resting just fine.  He just keeps on winning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i neither had a flannel nor nike’s. am i even american? https://t.co/Gwb7g3pSl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@princesstiamia OMG, not Patti! She’s doing a concert here. 😂😂 I was just looking at tix on line! 🙄 It was Tommy Chong!! #brainfart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The4RealStevo I don’t know. If I ask they never stop talking about it. We can’t have that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itz_mizdee # aww happy birthday hoped you had a wonderful day.💕🎂🍨 https://t.co/7fgbOCa3DY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The risks to protected areas... and sensitive habitats are predominantly low with some temporary, short-term impac… https://t.co/AFRIRBnBcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I had the honor of being the emcee for the @CrohnsColitisFn Indiana Chapter Great Gutsby Gala. It was so… https://t.co/L663duD6VA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Death penalty for Trophy Hunters, too... #BanTrophyHunting #StopSafariClubInternational #StopPoachers]]></document><document><![CDATA[I havent seen or touched my cats in two weeks. im in desperate need of a cat...please,,....it’s life or death]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Italian ingredient du jour was AMORE. Chocolate was in every dish because, just like love, it is bittersweet. O… https://t.co/PUEGrgvSF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I straight up grabbed the six and told my Uber driver “ sorry ima play some girly shit” and started bumping Ariana… https://t.co/72DI0VKeBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t gone on a trip in a while... thinking about just booking a weekend trip soon. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyyMeade And it’s obviously a fake account cause they were only following me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunterBros @HIGHVALLEY I am digging the branded bus ... so very inconspicuous 😉 and I’m pretty sure you missed a s… https://t.co/ihLZnL0LqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am really just running on maybe 1-2 hours of sleep a night lately and this morning, it. is. kicking. me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiarioTalCual @jorgeramosnews @MBMartinezR @Diego_Arria @miguelhotero @NTN24ve @FreeVenezuela6 @VenezuelaAnons… https://t.co/uLYkOwBwm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian This is exactly how my Valentine’s Day was last year! Crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babyname_maven @drfixus Again, I was born with a Primary Immune Deficiency (PID). #Vaccines do not cause autoimmun… https://t.co/T9VGIIptf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn’t already know, I AM the man. 💪🏻 @ Wwe Raw https://t.co/TZXHLKR4vK]]></document><document><![CDATA[We finally were able to visit Toy Story Land at night. We LOVE it! How adorable is it?! #disney #hollywoodstudios… https://t.co/6s9ZEQwyr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished Parks and Rec, and I def cried a little. 😭😭😭 Thank goodness @maleaman put it on, but there’s no way t… https://t.co/lYJftcDfow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @JetBlue am I gonna get to Tampa today?! Flight 1973 just got deplaned because of a computer system issue and s… https://t.co/qf7FVisghg]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great project I got to photograph for #bulleyandandrews #bulleyandrews1891 #klimenthalsbandarchitects… https://t.co/2IEykeuVgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life has me mentally exhausted, and oh so tired. . . . #Tired #Exhausted #Sleepy #Fighter #Struggle #Struggling… https://t.co/IgJ7XcJyOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My only question is: if this was resolved last night around midnight, why did I receive several alerts again this m… https://t.co/3WjoPSvd1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennedyamara1 @yikesitspam @PayneYasmine @PalayeRoyale Probably gonna have to speak for me. Am 6'0ft tall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAcademy #Oscars2019 Here’s wishing all the fabulous women nominated a fabulous day and evening ahead... #March… https://t.co/azsYpAC3qA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HellaMedusa @alyssalimp I was born in the wrong state i’ll tell you that much...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WHurensohn @paulpuckett911 @kneadinghands @KLinduff @Jacklynnbj @Tango__Juliette @ColleenKenney11 @ksplanet… https://t.co/vWmy9E97xC]]></document><document><![CDATA[im hoping that @norvina1 just forgot to follow me but actually added me... wishful thinking 💭]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a level of 1-Hermione Granger, how geeky is it that organizing my sheet music is the highlight of my day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to Chicago @convene 😎 we're glad you're here!! #meeting #meetings #meetingsmeanbusiness #eventplanner… https://t.co/kKtGPpcZ6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @LindseyGrahamSC He has morally compromised himself into a fool. He has nothing more to offer. All of hi… https://t.co/VwdpylwE10]]></document><document><![CDATA[emma chamberbitch is dressed like the one armed mannequin child in kohls and shes at paris fashion week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattnathanson and @aarontap brought the fashion and the fun tonight in #NYC #singshissadhearttour #irvingplaza… https://t.co/zH6kr8wDwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vontade de comer uma caixa de chocolate inteira nesse dia que só chove!!!! https://t.co/AMlL5ih3Ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello. You have just entered the single zone. This is where sad, depressed singles find love. Just kidding. If ur here ur prob bored asf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronasia13_ @WildGues @Aaron58477074 @isaachoward_ @vyatikram188 @KhaledBeydoun @NatGeo Exactly! The wanted somethi… https://t.co/Uo7y0na2Ek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nada amiga/os ☹️ vimos mil millones de estrellas, la luna divina, Mercurio, The Milky Way pero nada de las auroras 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[goodnight to everyone except the lady on the wonder women machine next to me who hit the bonus of 5k.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ohioboyryan I have a gym in my neighborhood and a membership lol so it works for meeeee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dayamourr Yeah I just feel like my college experience has been mostly shitty with some good times sprinkled in 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we don't get is how all the #TreasonWeasels can eat, drink, sleep, or function at all with what is hanging ove… https://t.co/7aR0nqWu9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Suntimes says social media monitoring by CPS should happen BUT police should only be brought in with an imminent… https://t.co/lq5q7gJmPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmmccormick19 PSA: if you are a white female and you god forbid don’t like white men you are TRASH 👏🏼 RACIST 👏🏼 CUNTY 👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh cool. It’s the beat boxing phase of not napping. https://t.co/28GRDfM7EV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bruce_arthur What are you doing to help people what stand are you taking  to help people? How do you help in this… https://t.co/Z5I1vwCweM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XXMIERSXX1 Same I fell asleep right when I got home at 5 pm woke up at 10 pm and thought it was the the next day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 26th birthday to me!!! Well, I don’t officially turn another year older until 7:11pm, but I already feel anot… https://t.co/CQF91w6x1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been one incredible 14-hour whirlwind of a #Disney experience that I will remember, always. Happily Ever After ❤️… https://t.co/cjpcxhe6C0]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a woman who often has “witty” and “hilarious” in her annual reviews, can confirm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“An attitude of adoring trust in the LORD will make an amazing difference in your life”💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanurai @EskiBrew @BadDogDesigns_ This is from about 1910. https://t.co/ho4B2yQLhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anaaaa3023 @LeJuan__James Blessings and more success you bring pure joy to this mundo loco and for that am gratefu… https://t.co/7gZTQNSh6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think a bird just flew by inside the terminal. At least someone is flying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only way my curls look good if I sleep like this lol #goodnight  I gotta be up at 4am for work 🤪 https://t.co/zpGtq5kHSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning kids. Car is warming up, banana has been demolished and it’s gym time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop posting the picture you just posted, on your story with a sticker saying new post]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KylePallo It's Okay...No Matter How Long, Or Short You Want To Make Them...!!!! We Will Watch Them...!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#turmericlatte mug by lyonclay @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/zyhKi1nekn]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh god am i supposed to be watching  a town hall? im busy fighting people who are trying to tell me that a photogra… https://t.co/t31EUcR9Tx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Thursday Eo 🌻 #ThrowbackThursday #Outlander  Credit to @Camilla68521063 @ Richland Center, Wisconsin https://t.co/VnxLE18twY]]></document><document><![CDATA[realistically i Should be air, though i Would be fire, but i Want to be earth. sorry katara]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hop back on the app for a few mins and see it turn back to 2012 Twitter in a heartbeat LMFAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @MikeBloomberg You lost the election for a reason Go Away. You’re harming the Democratic Party with… https://t.co/t3khOjZDyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyitsCarolyn @nancy_hamm1 Congulations Nancy!! On Reaching 45k!! Way To Go!!🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[In #meditation yesterday, we read a passage from @TaraBrach: True Refuge. "The more we look through the eyes of… https://t.co/x8GlC5R68r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhop77 @insideuniversal @UniversalORL @lorenlale @JimmyBrimble So soon!!! 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get a load of this guy... McCue is running for you!! My good friend Zach McCue is running for Off-Campus Senator. I… https://t.co/UZe8OUSAJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast with friends (@ Hamilton Family Restaurant in Allentown, PA) https://t.co/FgXNtGn94V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaBelcamino tRump’s Presidency is the real National Emergency... #25thAmendment]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️Realtor Love ....  #Malarkey #MalarkeyHomes #RealtorLove https://t.co/5Hl4DZ14BR]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my neighbors would stop playing their music as loud as possible that would be wonderful]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just ready for some sun so I can do yoga on the beach instead of in my living room]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy I finally met Alex and Mikeee !!!!!❤️❤️❤️🌈🌈🌈🌈 #lovethem #HappyValentinesDay https://t.co/WJrEfbGrHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrightMoments @fellowinameadow I'll cut you a little slack.  It's gravity's fault.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our big carved park entrance sign is gone. Like, we have no idea where it went gone. https://t.co/4A6K2DpffB]]></document></documents></author>