<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Americans made the biggest mistake in 2016 voting.They should have taken the GOP seats that was open.The Justice de… https://t.co/c8fJpxZQi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a dated movie for sure, but it still manages to have a pretty good message about bonding, especially between a… https://t.co/mdmTgAoytd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe this. One of the greatest visionary’s in the fashion world. #icon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IonlycarryLV @ProudNanaK @SabrinaTalksGH @louisemullin But I look at both point of views I mean dang everyone has great points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyrieIrving is Like a beta fish. Just let him live by himself in his own bowl @celtics @NBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithPowersNYC Thank you for your response Keith...I will think about that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten I think service time should be a major issue in the next CBA negotiations, but I dunno if it will be… https://t.co/DBQxvtJdgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll be at @hackwithtrees🌳 this weekend if you wanna come build React Native apps 📱 with me and the @expo crewww 💙🔥😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein What a sad life you have when you’re happiness is tied to hoping for the destruction of another person!]]></document><document><![CDATA[even if you dont have a #boxing gym to go to, or the time, shadow boxing (properly) with these for about 20 or so m… https://t.co/jGGcm7rYu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inglewood Southside Christian Church: Cherished Friends: https://t.co/xqlgLaxi8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Thank you, yes.  We do have some folks like that, but the changes in the last 25 years alone prove your point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chloeg_13 Lebron always got a good supporting cast to live in South Beach for a year or 2. If he stayed I’m sure t… https://t.co/3iMwQAjD5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hammetjohn She is a treasonous cxxx and should never be allowed into the USA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnydollar01 @BretBaier @MZHemingway DNC is punishing FOX. DNC thinks it’s a winning strategy to campaign Democr… https://t.co/3onYUP99lS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen testifies Trump is a 'conman' who knew of WikiLeaks email dump  #WorstPresidentinHistory… https://t.co/37ItxTYP0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was at this game, my first NBA game since the sonics left Seattle. What a finish!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dad #daughters #BlackTwitter So now the original loud ramble from a couple rooms away is riled up and screaming a… https://t.co/2DS07zOcpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimHeathTV CBS has not had credibility since the early 1970's. However, oddly enough, they do have my single favor… https://t.co/eufDnzM0pF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The City of Seattle Technology Matching Fund provides funds for digital equity projects up to $50,000. City dollars… https://t.co/f7H8BchrIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficeMonkey I feel like you are using call in a different way - I have been called to deploy on a Friday, and thus must]]></document><document><![CDATA[A 3rd grade teacher convinced me to read The NYT it had news about Trump enough for us to drive 3hrs to AC to see t… https://t.co/rEMua4AUUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackAftaThis I wish this account existed back in 2004 when I first started listening to mike]]></document><document><![CDATA[Devon Achane has dropped 55 spots in the recruiting rankings since December. How?  He’s scored 65 TD’s in two years… https://t.co/QbiHXdXMdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex_richards21 you know me sir i was tweeting this as i was pouring a drink]]></document><document><![CDATA[You thought it was a game but It’s tatted on my chest.  #ForeverDream #Fitness #Miami #training 👉🏾 @ Miami Beach-75… https://t.co/GoWTvtWeXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jconroysd @ChrisJZullo @KamalaHarris Facts, colder is worse. That’s not the question, sorry. The question is how c… https://t.co/4zfNKGG8ec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ebtesam00369622 @PatGrant7777 @Efrain99620830 @Hiqutipie @Marg1010 @TlrWorldWidellc @twizmwhytepiece… https://t.co/hbzcNzAfAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Takeaway from the week: over-index on communication. Don't make an assumption. Seek explicit acknowledgments and fe… https://t.co/eb03DX2wIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karen Arnold made a moving and inspiring speech at today’s #NoEmergency protest in South Side Birmingham. 45 is the… https://t.co/yeT3nX54Zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TenthAmendment Yup the welfare clause, like the commander in chief clause is constantly bastardized to grow gov and executive power.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newhavengooners @arseblog This is also the first time that our arguably most talented player who also wants to be… https://t.co/djcWWWJAqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[(In case you’re confused: Elway, Jones, and other anonymous competition committee members have been vocal that ther… https://t.co/wZCJGa1E4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDBank_US I wanted to let you know the pleasant experience I had with one of your employees in Colesville Road Sil… https://t.co/8nD1lFKWWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriJacobus @highbrow_nobrow If the Republicans could do it that would happen here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColMorrisDavis @RepMarkMeadows @realDonaldTrump Time for the folks there to make a change. The country is embarrassed for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metrolosangeles So the eta went up to 12 minutes and then the bus showed up. Glad it arrived but I waited about 30… https://t.co/uv0RQWkpEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Because Mexico was supposed to pay for it? Because it’s a waste of money?]]></document><document><![CDATA[God Will Carry You  #americana #altcountry  #music #itunes #amazonmusic #country #reverbnationartist #rockandroll… https://t.co/kbeUqRUozB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/h0bCFOVmn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onebadxo @MayoCenter @jackieevancho @The_Cabot https://t.co/aIv1qyMReV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EcoHeliGuy Here is the Glovis ship in San Francisco that I just took last week. How many of these ships do they ha… https://t.co/uv9kb4KVOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I realized during this interview that @BrianWFoster is the high school/college friend I wish I’d had. #wotcstaff… https://t.co/rJCCeZfHyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom accused of faking 5-year-old son's illness for disability checks  https://t.co/w0q6fcNCLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Student-centered “make it a snap word” with Brady. #WiltonWayCT #TCRWP #puos @TCRWP @Liz_Dunford https://t.co/MbKtKHlmUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really, really, really wish that instead of sponsoring a free fare day for everyone in Utah, @IntermtnMedCtr… https://t.co/U8sfh4wxj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I just ate it for the first time. I’ve come to the conclusion that @HolyHogBBQ is in fact #good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillRiley @BrianOake @TheCurrent For the love of gawd... I don’t care if that’s Beck but please refrain from playi… https://t.co/HF35xLH2en]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alice in Chains- Nutshell (lyrics) https://t.co/BMmzuW6r7M via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥21 Minute Aerobic EMOM 🔥   3 movements in this EMOM (every minute on the minute) aerobic session will get some ser… https://t.co/NQw9ZCo9FA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top-seeded Sheldon Huskies beat Oak Ridge 64-54 in @cifsjs Division 1 semifinals. Will take on defending champion M… https://t.co/lfvgS4RT7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rgaventures @marspetcare @FoundAnimalsOrg @Barkibu @jiminysforpets @petreleaf @smallsforsmalls @sniffspot Congratu… https://t.co/OoDIiAt3ct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waterloo933 Although I'm away from home right now and I miss him so much 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCfromPerth @JesseRikart @djenvy Those voters who flipped to McCain were the same white libertarian leaners who flocked to Bernie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeParker1964 @MsCharlotteWWE @AlexaBliss_WWE @NaomiWWE @RheaRipley_WWE @QoSBaszler @BeckyLynchWWE Yep]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️ Still No plans yet for ❤️#valentinesday2019❣🎁🍫 @funtimeamerica3 Dinner for 2 for $39.99 make your #Rsvp call 732… https://t.co/hdQGZFxMRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedNationRising @Cook4USHouse Cali-land of the fruits and nuts. Perhaps they will come back from the socialist hell they are in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last photo wasn't good enough. Here is @PeopleMoverCone in hi def and close up! https://t.co/hrGzWaA8da]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC The U.S.A. Emits only 14% of the worlds carbon.  Your reticules, Wildly inaccurate ideas are pointless!  You s… https://t.co/bNZJ5jAOlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[we can be BESTFRIENDS and im still not going to want talk to you everyday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well this Saturday just got a hell of a lot more exciting. Go Gopher Victory!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newark Catholic starters  Dow Jones Slater Evans  Ian Stacey Granger Evans  Htjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s a cold hardened SOB.  See how MSM has spent the last week showing her being “human”? Big smiles, pearly white… https://t.co/OMpn3srt65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoePisapia17 #BlackBook draft all end way. ROTO. OF is Harper Ozuna Cain Winker Hamilton. IF is Rizzo Cano Donalds… https://t.co/9HLt35RmCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of the great work that NEW does to move women out of homelessness!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LetsGetAshterIt‼️ #HowAboutGivingUpTerribleCatchPhrasesForLent❓ #ChrisCuomo https://t.co/PIoHe1wkqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cashman said he’s “closing the chapter” on questions about Machado and Harper.   “We’re up and running with what we… https://t.co/wv7Rfz8KrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have treated the biggest crisis in our province (aside from climate change) with total, willful disregard for t… https://t.co/ko4DzMKQer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Few things are as satisfying as an ice-cold glass of water on a hot day. ⚡️But, it’s a lot more difficult to get th… https://t.co/S9FKhfgKEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daveweigel Voting for Republican political ploy amendments that help fuel anti-immigrant stances and NRA attacks o… https://t.co/InG2ZwC6H7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffBullerman @dvanklomp Can the rest of the state secede from the twin cities?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMoldenFineArt I’ve been playing Tetris 99, Spyro 2, and Replaying Assassin’s Creed 4 Black Flag, and I just picke… https://t.co/XQpO9PCpca]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lightthelion #challenge #protectwhatyouveearned #royalup #royalspride congratulations @QueensTrack1 @ DSM Internat… https://t.co/0eFMwdoQVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElderSammy Nice man! I moved back to boca from tampa so just finishing my bachelors and chillin. miss the old @ClubAnalytics squad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 18th bday @raeganbartee stay woke out there !! https://t.co/A502J9U1GY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the wall murals of Denton. This is a city of the arts.  #wallmural #wallmuralsindenton #wallmurals @ Studio On… https://t.co/Xo25fxO9nD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson Lock the traitors up. Elections have consequences]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edgarrmcgregor @realwxforecast @NWSSanDiego I found a personal weather station in my neighborhood on wunderground… https://t.co/hnYPsCcyYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I disagree with the "Public Ownership" and "Guaranteed Job, etc" planks - they are nice but #UnAmerican; the rest l… https://t.co/LUDhXbpSXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[CODE ENFORCEMENT OFFICER.           SaCRIMEnto, Calif.          HIRES SUCH PEOPLE.          I DEMAND California Aut… https://t.co/HA4YL1gdRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TNgolf @K_m_Mitchell And NBC gave a shout out to The Honors Course and Miss Betty Probasco! I just love her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There isn’t a better ending to a television show than @PersonInterest Season 1 Episode 4.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy se conmemora el día de la mujer, así que no sean ordinarios y anden felicitando a las mujeres solo x serlo.  Se… https://t.co/vvKUVCa6UG]]></document><document><![CDATA[How late is the famous liquor store in the airport open in Nola on a Sunday?  Here’s my shopping list Margarita Mix… https://t.co/KODrWwEcVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PedroFerriz @lopezobrador_ @ClaudiaPavlovic @arteaganoticias El comentario puede tener valor, pero en política sab… https://t.co/ljjIG9rrCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[man this guy only a junior too, the things he does on the track... sheeeessh can’t wait to finish my last season wi… https://t.co/JzZLBzdo7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faith must not be conceited but it must be confident. No one is attracted to wishy washy faith.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great!! Take the 2 minutes and watch.                      #NationalAnthemDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Thread: Look, i know this is unpopular right now. There are definitely players in college who could make millions… https://t.co/YXyuoSOLIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haskell @therealkilp @_Jolly_ @_WEEXIAO @eSportsBSU @ESPN_Esports @MWEsportsSeries @floridastate @UNMEsports… https://t.co/n2hjjI2Auw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derridalicious I can't imagine Aussies can make good pizza. Am I wrong?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incluso con esto...  Rico no es el que más tiene, rico es a quien más le sobra al final de una quincena... he visto… https://t.co/o403hJWgYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickShielsPGA Yes, Srixon ZStar XV...although it was only 7-10 yards, that is a big difference for a mid-handicapper like myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimberlasskick @FinnBalor You can seemingly always count on Finn to be excited to perform.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Completely agree with this 100%.. unless you don’t have AirPods then you’re just a piece of shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then a year later my dad hopped on another bus and tried to fight the driver 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3: Loved this idea from @StealBasesCom - teach your guys to think positive thoughts while stealing. “I will be saf… https://t.co/1YoKtpeg0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[The band is shown as breaking up for a while because Freddie had recorded a solo album. In real life, all the membe… https://t.co/4eLUfMppOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emp3playa I don’t understand this reference but I’m faving it cause I’m Jewish]]></document><document><![CDATA[Libro 📚: Una Vida Sin Obstáculos  Autor: Erick Torres Disponible ya 😊😃💯👍🏻🇺🇸🇵🇷🇩🇴🇨🇴🇲🇽… https://t.co/ugUauksg4w]]></document></documents></author>