<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[And you still finna leave with no pussy lined up for the foreseeable future smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsAhmir @Afgunning   me: can we please not go on the fast highway you:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get to leave work 45 minutes early because I got all my work done ☺️ that's how it's done boys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justlikewater17 It absolutely applies to career and I have been there too! Do not give up. I’m finally somewhere I… https://t.co/VE9wfGhLwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck today. BEST PART IS I had 6 shots of espresso and I'm not even sleepy enough to end the day with deep slumber.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Channeling my inner @AOC with the hoops + lipstick out here advocating for school psychologists as school-based men… https://t.co/uODI5sPD2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation, help the Sheriff get his chair back! @SheriffChody @BeverlyChody @OfficialLivePD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I REALLY HOPE I GET TO SEE @the1975 me and my wife are trying to be cool for a day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever this unknown person is straight up blames #Trump for #JussieSmollett #Pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[This!!! Please vaccinate,these diseases are eradicated because of vaccines!!! Please dont believe that you shouldn'… https://t.co/iN3c6LQVDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[but yknow spikes just a sore loser for dunking on it left and right, definitely no other reason hes not happy it won]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ain’t put in, don’t ask! #SundayBlackFilmTwitter #BlackFilmTwitter https://t.co/UMD24e84Q5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy how Irvine can’t take my insurance anywhere looks like I’ll just d!e 😊 peace out Girl Scouts 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing he honestly knows about me as a person is that I draw and I'm weird, and strangers can look at me an… https://t.co/7JmgH8GBoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[💗 💗💗 ..   #justbelieve  #happythoughts #livelife. #laurelseye #stronger @ Utah https://t.co/dJ6ArqwFPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am grateful to my parents for scooping me up and getting me back in the City and to my Dad for making me workout… https://t.co/QoDLCIPxAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iownjd Kindness first and always. And learn something from everyone you meet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HC_Richardson @DeGolierThomas That's really neat. And a sign that the truisms in one region may not apply to other… https://t.co/GPsOyKuJjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Lance Byhre. My friend from the Esquimalt Eagles. @ Esquimalt, British Columbia https://t.co/cry8GkJevU]]></document><document><![CDATA[EVERYONE around me is talking at the same time in our open office space. How can anyone think this actually works?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FireGoddessB @spiritmoon7 @eddsmitty @jhgurf @ProfessorAMuse @fenrir_71 @MrsRabbitResist @escapedmatrix… https://t.co/3X2gDNmQPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so blessed to have amazing friends like @Ruthie_1214 in my life. #BlessedBeyondMeasures 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveDd15  I'd be honored to have your follow !!   #ArmyStrong #MAGA #VIP on #TEAMMAGA IFB #KAG2020 #BackTheBlue #MAGAVETERAN ✡️✝️🇺🇸🦅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Unprecedent is the way you lie abt EVERYTHING! Your tax bill did nothing for the middle class; you… https://t.co/NNNhdgfBPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red, I hope you are well, the mitochondira is the powerhouse of the cell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I grew up getting lost in the forest and coming back muddy and dirty. That’s when I fell in love with running. I w… https://t.co/eyepwD8AyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[IFHE XXIV World Congress Atlanta GA 2020 Call for abstracts,  submit June 1, 2019 to August 31, 2019   Don’t miss t… https://t.co/FnInsOycRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[because the LORD disciplines those he loves, as a father the son he delights in. https://t.co/Aorz2DiAdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @JudicialWatch @realDonaldTrump Welcome Ramona, Let's get to work girl! https://t.co/9KCSoGvjRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viva Las Vegas! It’s about to go down.  #winning #striplife #gambling #blackjack #holla @ The Cosmopolitan of Las V… https://t.co/sVZarH6z6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[...speech regression, inability to speak, speaking in an abnormal tone of voice, repeating words and phrases over a… https://t.co/J0J71YzW8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Commando074 @BianchiWrites @aafAPOLLOS You can watch it live on the app]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am definitely 1 of the very few with an extensive resumé as I have and the network, that is the most unorthodox i… https://t.co/GqlHObyDzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_benaf_ can u drop the name of those shit pills u was talking about today i am interested in shitting like my life depended on it pls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day, here’s my butt at @springawakefest 🥰💓🍑  Only TWO weeks left of being able to use code “LOVEK… https://t.co/h8M6dSKrkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_X_Classified Sorry love... vote earlier next time it’s safer and less crowded]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful #deer! 🦌 #FairHarbor #FireIsland #winter #PresidentsDay weekend https://t.co/DTlbGTx0Uu]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐾 Thank goodness for the kindness of this man,he saved adorable ☺️ Louie 🐕 for his meant to be furever/forever home… https://t.co/Gy2pFEfxsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashPost files somewhat March 1st SNEAKY editorial apology. #CovingtonBoys, contnue lawsuit,  own a newspaper.  Co… https://t.co/geIoiy57yK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry but what @SenatorRounds just spewed is a bunch of malarkey. What the hell is wrong with these people? What is… https://t.co/0oIU0FWaA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BizsHusband  This is a big leap for me. If I don’t see Miss State somewhere in the bio I rarely give a follow. Goo… https://t.co/aLjiIOaMMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MDeskaTTU @Landan_Kuhlmann @RoundRockTim @KingBobbyWdlnds @dkdeberry Altuve was worse in twice as many AB in 2015.… https://t.co/AVSGaXBJva]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcharlesworth7 Im getting confused with this thread lol I think now am answering myself Ok Michelle this is a long… https://t.co/NYnQZub72W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougmeehan Wish I Could Have Been There...!!!!  Rami's Dream Came True...!!!! ❤🍾❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you ignore the obvious signs but still decide to try and workout— that inner thigh cramp I got this past Satur… https://t.co/VCHfqJ9hwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cali_Tracii So happy about this nugget of good news for the babies.  We need more!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder - Meet Jonathan Cahn at @Mardel_Inc this Monday, March 11th at I-240 &amp; Penn in OKC at 6:00pm.… https://t.co/E25bhdkomp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's start off Monday morning with the things people don't want to talk about😳. Face it head on then He will show… https://t.co/0TOpLQCZND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DalaiLama Like always you’re holiness we are honored to receive your wise words.  thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to reddit, stopping Earth's rotation in one second requires 6.98E33 joules of energy applied on the earth… https://t.co/PlOgtQsdVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBates Who does that?  That right there was a great sign that something was / is hugely wrong with Trump.  It boggles the mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! Don’t forget to wrap it up! 💘💘#iwrapitlikethat  https://t.co/BtZmuvs6B6 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[on my way to my fitness center... wearing my nike sport's bra and leggings i'm freezing.😨 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rodlugox3 @kenji_marie @boxycharm @CoverFX @BECCAcosmetics Did you ever hear of Tribe beauty box or Tribe box- I j… https://t.co/ymV5UYUnLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m watching #worldofdance from last night and where the hell is @jennadewan at?? Tell me you just was sick that… https://t.co/77MJlsauwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking a hot shower, putting on flannel pajamas, and then laying in bed after a long few weeks of being a full-time… https://t.co/tJ2ZahMvrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t I sleep ugh.. I just wanna get up early and I know now I won’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo que mas me impresiona son algunos medios de comunicación propiciando las burlas con los memes🤦🏻‍♀️😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow, this showed up on my Facebook feed...I loathe @BernieSanders and wish he'd just disappear back into the Ve… https://t.co/tnUrfM5MHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrNesper @elonmusk Haha! That is a problem! But the invention for that is the automatic car-starter. Start your ca… https://t.co/OVtav7ByXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinbliss @ewarren Typical Dem, not a comment re: all the other positive things @realDonaldTrump has done.  The ta… https://t.co/zJtgfPGnu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetbtstea @msbeatrice_81 I know kookaburra song... I think... in don’t know I haven’t watched Barney since 1996]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lunar_Luster @Leon_Helmink Ummm about to be 44?! Leon drew them!! 😂❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraLeeNews8 @AbbieNews8 @News8 I don’t think it will happen for me cause I always have my family checking in o… https://t.co/onFbg3wcbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s never too early to get to work! #HappyMonday https://t.co/tqrDsP2mAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to I Love It by Cheat Codes &amp; DVBBS on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/Ve317x8lqu https://t.co/stOWyMsamF]]></document><document><![CDATA[jaycie is such an empowering person in my life. i’ve been so blessed with this perfect person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caldo del mercado (@ Pico de Gallo in San Antonio, TX) https://t.co/GZZX7GSmpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oreminsteluspl1 Write a book that won’t give us any greater insight.  At least he will have time to think, while in there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VuduSupport sorry wrong issue, each time I would select UHD it would default back to HDX.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As state testing season is looming... “Sometimes, the most brilliant and intelligent minds do not shine in standard… https://t.co/McKh5NR6zD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I thought I would go to college and do okay but I haven’t been able to make anything work and it feels lik… https://t.co/yOnN91nZnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump @nbcsnl There is a lot of reality missing in this man’s mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlumniGCU Ricci Johnson, still working past 90, is just Ah-mazing. Why? Read the story in the latest edition of GC… https://t.co/XCsbkY2AhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pray for my dad to get donated a new heart and for all his surgery’s to go well❤️🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gop @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @SenatorRomney @BenSasse @lisamurkowski @LamarAlexander @SenatorCollins… https://t.co/QXoWYi3Itv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoNickk clopen!!!!!!!!! @LuluMSchneider @michaela_kerr10 @C_Debrowski @kellyxo96 @deewesss @jamie_sand614 @_paigegrace_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilieTaman Evidently Wernick sees his time before the committee as a chance to editorialize on policy issues he c… https://t.co/4s6AVKMBHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep dreaming about this blue beach house with lots of cute stuff and I hope that’s a sign that i’ll get one one day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear god. All day I have thought I was getting 3 Facebook friend request at a time. I have now realized it was actu… https://t.co/gKPqKGJul9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Orlando International Airport - @mco in Orlando, FL https://t.co/a51xxIMVnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caelynn or Tayshia will be the next Bachelorette @TheBachelorTV you heard it first here 🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Word. #CaptainMarvel #internationalwomensday #thefutureisfemale #aHERo @brielarson @ Grand Rapids, Michigan https://t.co/EAlUvPWeCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickconfessore Not gonna cut it these days. No more normal niceties...this is political war.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryceeMcNabbers 🤔🤔🤔 this seems less than ideal kid...take care of yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He Will Give the Weary Strength by Ellie Holcomb (Lyrics) https://t.co/OydHKA0OZU via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish @Costco sold @PapaJohns special garlic butter dipping sauce. I would buy tubs of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenaguilar0408 @MrsAbingColeGT I would've loved to have gone to a game!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldenKnights I just wanted to say HAPPY VALENTINES DAY TO THE AMAZING KNIGHTS AND THE ORGANIZATION. Keep up the g… https://t.co/MxZEbEFRLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THindermeier @westernuEdu @Westmount_ps What a great idea! Practical and deepening understanding!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to them and to all who tell the stories that deserve to be told in our community and beyond,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to utilizing LA County’s Measure W as a funding source that increases aquifer recharge and removes… https://t.co/M0CYgrIBWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kbrown1742 @dallasmavs @Chiefs @PatrickMahomes Tell him hi! https://t.co/zsOo94rlg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samtwomilton I’d say yes to apple care 100% but I don’t think extra storage is that needed but I guess that really… https://t.co/yeCfuioht0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pneprincess @Mark_99nc @kath_gunn @TatumTotThePug @ScribblePug I also was lucky enough to receive a #ValentinesDay… https://t.co/yQ7jWGEXuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting my challenge all over. 21 clean eats. I really effed up this weekend. Here we go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok ... and I really hate that it is .. but 💀💀💀.. I really been over here like I’m horrible for feeling like song ca… https://t.co/ykVmN5E0AB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My parents put me on a pedestal and I’m so afraid that I’m gonna let them down. Failure isn’t an option. I can’t an… https://t.co/GRjzt9bWRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else trippin on the girls from pen15 and how they can pull off being 7th graders.. kinda? ..sorta? Or this just me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[7:04 remains in the 2nd, @DuqMBB has a 4-point deficit to go against. #PutEmUp/#DukeTheProcess #BelieveInTheBluff #ThankYouPalumbo]]></document></documents></author>