<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SunAngelsMusic iРђЎm sure all of them arenРђЎt settling for spotify and buying only retail !]]></document><document><![CDATA[this spring break, i learned how to (badly) photoshop! enjoy ­Ъїъ­Ъје https://t.co/7UKvcQFNwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTaylorSkinner @SenFeinstein I read it and it doesnРђЎt work to get us where we need to be nearly fast enough. ClearРђд https://t.co/OP5R7jFQow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday breakfast with the fam jam! 2/3 of The Littles are heading out of town tonight so we thought weРђЎd celebratРђд https://t.co/IbkI1nz6oo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorthHerSalt That's an interesting question. I definitely didn't notice any texture issues. Perhaps the bacon is mРђд https://t.co/2YNBPwWjLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with this statement. Ap on freeways is better than your avg la driver who texts, talks on phone, puts on maРђд https://t.co/xheShAzevw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyHallowell Respect has more than one definition, which some people fail to understand. Words are important!  "Рђд https://t.co/79ZIvLtZtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilbaby4PF discovered this like me and made a song about it itРђЎs called pure cocaine https://t.co/Q2rNEKkHN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boom! @TaneshaCWhittle and the team from store #1515 was the #1 store in sales vs. plan in 2018 for the PMD, congraРђд https://t.co/2Ezy20b5iW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MufasaEvey I have no idea why MLB dont go higher than they do every year. Both those guys are studs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanADeSimone 3.) We also heard talk from KS  in 2018 about keeping the door open with then FA Eric Reid as if SFРђд https://t.co/VuUge8FrkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[BIBLE SAYS IF YOU LET HIM GOD WILL TAKE YOUR HAND THEN WISELY AND TENDERLY LEAD YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюThe way I see it, every life is a pile of good things and bad things. The good things don't always soften the badРђд https://t.co/zNqEEiG6jZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THESUGARDAD_1 Gotta be a record especially for this time of the morning and on a Saturday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity The only thing I want to know is Where is AG William Barr?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kiss the monkey team  make a noise in tv to the DUCKS OF ANHEIM LAST NIGHT  fun nightVIP ROOM   Al harris you are aРђд https://t.co/edKKhEabGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@masnKolko How about any chance the Nats sign one of the remaining FA pitchers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@medicalaxioms This feels like an easy choice.  Give me Рђюthe fieldРђЮ when it includes everything but those three.  HРђд https://t.co/tRsPZeKl4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Restaurant Delivery Driver Part-Time"? What did you like most about that job? #FastCasual #Plano, TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Randle did everything @lakers asked him to do. HeРђЎs collateral damage in the transition in the front office. This iРђд https://t.co/COxQyeToV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then El Gos Vell is coming in!!! Moltes gr├аcies, Josep (and thanks for the added grace note of Catalan humor. ­ЪљЙ­ЪљЙ­ЪљЙ)Рђд https://t.co/03rsp0i8az]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Partisangirl @marcorubio @SecPompeo Puppet Rubio Posts Pic of Gaddafi's Murder as Puppet Pompeo Says Maduro's DaysРђд https://t.co/JrqR9rEkR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alfonso Cuar├│n gana Oscar c├│mo mejor director por Roma #Oscars https://t.co/fJLKrA2dOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InuyashaSan87 @PaulPescrillo The English dub of OPM became available on Hulu once it's contract expired with AdultРђд https://t.co/PXEaaw79g2]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on Omlid DR 17 #Springfield #OR  #realestate https://t.co/YH34g5yvoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the inspiration of Scripture - РђюThe religion of the Bible thus announces itself, not as the product of menРђЎs seaРђд https://t.co/e44aBEwFN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@consbyname @Himel55 @DeficitOwls @NcojoD @StephanieKelton Conversation*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendship.     #fortunatefearlessforty @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/0PSSCPgr7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey hey , hope everything &amp; everyone is ok , from what I can piece together my best  to @StvFrdRck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FerCevallosF @ClubDeCuervos @pepecardozo249 @peladoalmeyda Yo dije ­Ъци­ЪЈ╗РђЇРЎѓ№ИЈ jajaja se mamo!@LuisGerardoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZackSlater54 @TMrealityczech @HaveWeAllGoneM1 @nationalpost STILL GIGGLING THANKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[IРђЎve never understood why basketball attendance has not been higher, especially with a team like they have this yeaРђд https://t.co/GICLwtEHe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyRRQuaid 1/2 brother? ...I thought you two had the same mom and dad...]]></document><document><![CDATA[i bartend with this lady and she told me, almost entirely out of the blue, that i seek the approval of others, butРђд https://t.co/oZycMgW4ks]]></document><document><![CDATA[There should be a retired NBA player league from 35-50yo and millions of people would watch it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker your thoughts on Declan Rice , opting for England , and is he good enough to get a chance soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GAPtelevision @KamalaHarris Is not true you are a lie, a bot, i am from Venezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[While everyone is out celebrating ValentineРђЎs Day.... IРђЎm having Tacos and ice cream while watching college basketball: Get on my level.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fun night yesterday for some #SuperMarioParty. hyperxesalv hosted their weekly tournament duringРђд https://t.co/jYRJ8hm6CR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was being sick and staying home from school with my Grandma in the 00s. Definitely The Price Is Right and thenРђд https://t.co/bFbtNJPq9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Few yrs back, 50 and Jadakiss traded a couple diss songs  Jada had a killer line  This is a true fact/ since when hРђд https://t.co/EBZ3udJTMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's just funny that you literally played the lions and lost by 20 then tweeted that ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ]]></document><document><![CDATA[mohawkcollege  Home @MoMountaineers mohawkmountaineers #MohawkMountaineers  Open House Days Info linkРђд https://t.co/n5a5cr426P]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюA typical Saturday as the CEO of  @OpGratitude: 900 volunteers - 15.5K Care Packages - 400K items - all in less thРђд https://t.co/zlkDbJtWYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[mas gostaria de dizer que alguns de n├│s (infelizmente ainda n├Бo s├Бo todos), estamos do mesmo lado dessa batalha porРђд https://t.co/FsRWfxkjcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burning Man CEO bans campsite costing up to $100k https://t.co/ehEBgEI7xv]]></document><document><![CDATA[IРђЎve arrived in DC for some @nasfaa leadership conference enrollment management discussions in the financial aid world. #fachat #emchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever heard of the game of hint? No, this is not a game of throne reference. You could say that it is a social gameРђд https://t.co/JlDKBGEM26]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sigh.....no one even believes the lies from MSM anymore....(already proven FALSE!)...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevespaleta @SPACEdotcom @Astro_DavidS @SpaceX From Soyuz to Crew Dragon. Looks like going from a Lada to an ExplРђд https://t.co/Sogy8Y4lsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time being in MA and the people here are some of the coolest people I've ever met. #boston #patroits #newengland]]></document><document><![CDATA[DonРђЎt understand golf ruling body. They banned belly putters, changed the way you drop a ball, changed hazards to pРђд https://t.co/fuDTwkaPjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettEwing Need LEI, starts and other indicators to fade together. 3 of my 6 recession flags are up but can't whisРђд https://t.co/mNMln6prx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Book Spotlight February 28, 2019  Tom's Featured Books For February 28, 2019  Lili Anolik - HolРђд https://t.co/xjZEfNdNBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HunterXHunter Top 3 with Black Clover in Top 10 of trending tonight. https://t.co/CL7s9fJluc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un and Trump meeting is a joke. Neither can or will achieve anything substantive or lasting. For both its a chanceРђд https://t.co/8q9rBzwnC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[TodayРђЎs #RecordOfTheDay is Mezzanine by massiveattackofficial Words donРђЎt describe my love for this album. #VinylРђд https://t.co/4F8YWHJFqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[De #BHP20 11/Mar/19  N├║meros 33  En cada paso del camino, Dios est├А con nosotros. Obedecerle es la mejor indicaci├│n de ruta.  #rpsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders I herd give nukes to those that would use them against us and wreck our economy blah blah blah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDonahue_2 @maxarothschild @BenjaminSimon05 @thefeatphilly Tremendous article.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @BanjoBarb @realDonaldTrump No new fence has been put up just repaired]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarroRodwell I hear you. Stupid Americans shoot first ask questions later.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LincolnwoodPD Thank you for todayРђЎs training session at Lincolnwood SD74 https://t.co/BO7ZLdRAcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving the rain and snow...only to go to more rain and snow. See you soon Sweden!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't want another Black President because I can't stand to see the sight of a Black person using ICE to deport BРђд https://t.co/MxZhoGueMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliteSportsAdv @SouthernMissBSB @och_ryan @Matt_Wallner @Cfisch_11 @ChadCaillet Great article!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the smell of brick and mortar in the morning!!! Smells like... VICTORY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Under Obama, America was heading for war against North Korea. Under Obama Iran was getting the NuclearРђд https://t.co/qxgtfd3wHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would have been returned to sender in Concur for improper receipt ­Ъў│­ЪўФ­Ъўѓ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProWriters005 You think I had time to wait for you to respond until the next day? The clownery wheeeew. https://t.co/hmz14fMWEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buford_vernon @TheWantedEmcees And what will you, a РђюChristianРђЮ and Рђюall-around good guyРђЮ do to him when you catch him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amarinecorpsvet @migrantsaid its economic many staying and working in Mexico it's not immigrations are becoming an Americans its work]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/BNtUJda4X3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard on the radio that #taxes were a part of the decision for @Bharper3407 #Phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please read this and let it sink in.Its not a phobia,its a fact that we have three muslim women in our political syРђд https://t.co/wHTSVmQkqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanFergusonOH @universityofky @McDonalds @DaytonFlyers @wrightstate @OhioState @GoBEARCATS @XavierUniv You had to say it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jonathan-Ismael Diaby - Elite Prospects https://t.co/SeqZ8BTSXq via @eliteprospects]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SomosAmerica Tienes razon, sin embargo, ahorita, el clasico Regio es entre el 1 y el 2. Los dos mejores equipos deРђд https://t.co/4F9bqb6sFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bharper3407 gonna be like Рђюhold my beerРђЮ and sign with the @Phillies ­Ъњђ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matteocollina @wesleytodd @nodejs IРђЎd suggest focusing on the *cause* of leaks - IРђЎm pretty sure itРђЎs not unhandleРђд https://t.co/0GteNrKPUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 This should be illegal! I canРђЎt imagine African countries being OK with this!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timmyham heard this, tasted that, seen there, heard then, touched that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Batman no es un h├Еroe.  El es solo un hombre.  Falible, vulnerable y enojado. "En una ciudad g├│tica donde el amigoРђд https://t.co/gjsNTfyCxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @madsverdin and @PenalozaYulissa for showing me your homework assignment so jealous lol ­Ъўѓ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisgustedPatri1 @SidneyPowell1 I agree with Sidney Powell about not funding "nonprofits". The name says  it all -Рђд https://t.co/ooNdonPrvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias Best picture of the fifties:  High Noon Best picture of the sixties: Dr. Strangelove]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelScarn770 I hear you. ItРђЎs possible they donРђЎt make it. But LeBron in the first round is a nightmare.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VibeHi Honestly if theyРђЎre using that expletive in a tweet to describe you, the comment is null and void from therРђд https://t.co/lduEnaEnYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatMoranTweets Ugh. That is my worst nightmare in these types of storms. We have a huge old tree in front of my hoРђд https://t.co/eXzwOorqqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is my Source: Messiah-my Savior-my Sovereign-my Song-my Sun and Shield-my Solace-my Strength-my Serenity-my Salvation! #Slamism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbanyCanCode Upload it to @UnitedWay_GCR Рђўs United to Volunteer site.   https://t.co/PFmGPeVKbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only the people with primate level of intelligence which is roughly half of the population but growing at an alarmiРђд https://t.co/NFyawh94oX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustAGurLnSwedn @KathyKro722 Why is this loons mouth always open and why is he always yelling. https://t.co/ifByoD3PyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBrennan Are you kidding me?  Only elected officials consider themselves as servants. The general population seРђд https://t.co/ksCuXEg0rl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hsedi205 @MashiRafael Yo no me enojo xq no hay raz├│n. Simplemente dejo a tu criterio personal tus creencias. TengoРђд https://t.co/MJzoDA2bPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanwdesigns Dude! YouРђЎre like a creative Hercules.   Flex what yo momma gave yah, son!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @AOC is a textbook Marxist minion using Obama tactics to weaponize resentment and encourage division.Рђд https://t.co/W63W2Jliso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that all you know how to say? Fascist party what bullshit dam iam glad iam not a democrat anymore you couldnРђЎt pРђд https://t.co/FiA1bTxqQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[come see the wennie slingers. good food and friendly people https://t.co/DYUomymXtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody in Valdosta trying to get some work during spring break??? ­ЪЉђ ­ЪЈѕ ­Ъјњ]]></document></documents></author>