<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[“Try to get guys to go to their strengths.”  🗣@coachbrucepearl after road win vs. Vandy  @AuburnMBB returns to Aubu… https://t.co/HJqrL6Xk91]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liked that one a lot. TY @billyrunaway for so often being my sole supporter. Next week another one I haven't seen..… https://t.co/VlvCXgBVvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Every step feels like I’m walking on coals.”  Send a prayer up for @alai2016. HE JUST WONT STOP. 5.5 miles to go!… https://t.co/o8MDqnC5Dp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump Ya, it's plain crazy... the FBI worried about a President that discounts their inte… https://t.co/gDdVIKomWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Big12Refs I’ve seen middle school refs do a better job!!  White hair guy calling Tech game is terrible!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ClydesRides @Halmic1 @larrygoolsby4 @my3monkees @GraceLempka  @Aug1405 @crazytas62 @misspunk63 @Trumpydata… https://t.co/R1aoPyWcRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChampagneLabUSI Did you vote “no” ? One of these times I’m going to start voting against the grain just so there’s a bit of excitement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is Basketball Christmas 🎄, and the Sanford POWER Basketball Academy got a new toy, a new Dr. Dish CT shooting… https://t.co/hrXS4jmqf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful sunset and weather and full river! @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/49FfaiAxyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corrie_mae @tedlieu @hardball @HardballChris @LDSchurch @RepPaulCook @SecWilkie @DeptVetAffairs @mjgranger1 Anothe… https://t.co/xyL9HkZjE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThrillJosh93 Southern California isn’t a hospitable place and you act like it’s so bad. Move if you feel a type of way 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julianaleonf Buenos días Juliana. Feliz inicio de semana 😀🌷🌹. Abrazos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you have got to check out the @JREpodcast. @Timcast @jack]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @Annie_OUFB for talking shop with me this morning about recruiting! Love bouncing ideas off you! #OUDNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The call for volunteers to fly into LA begins again early this morning! 😂✈️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@72TraThomas @PPCherryHill @975Mornings @975TheFanatic https://t.co/h4BofXiC4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[يا ربّ: علمني كيف أحبك حبّاً خالصا  لا شريك لك فيه ولا مثيل..  حبّاً أعيش به لأجلك وأموت عليه لأجلك وألقاك به وأنت… https://t.co/u9iBV6HpZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#batfleckforever @BenAffleck please return to the Dark Knight! You were the absolute best #batman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClassicRockerz_ Sweet child in time - deep purple  Inagaddadavida - iron butterfly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo I feel bad for getting mad at the people working at bk, cause they hooked me up with their chicken fries! Lol mybad @BurgerKing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care about any gifts I’m just happy I have family and friends that actually care about me I’m so blessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breacher__UP @I_am_not_dense @TheChunkyD @RuFiOooooh @JackPosobiec I don’t think you understand. The 153M figure i… https://t.co/h64q7ZVHla]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wanna go out. I’m in the mood to just door dash and chill at home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Healthy Habits You Should Steal From the Pros @SparkPeople https://t.co/Tg6TPn86Y8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HernandoDeSot11 @CaliRN619 @misspunk63 @RevKeithBritt @KathaleenHarpe9 @BobBrinson1 @sc08960854 @youlosenordys… https://t.co/iVbZNuaMQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starters for @DHSVikings118: Miles, Smith, Hoskins, Stroud, Houpt. For @CHAR_GERS: Cowper, Flowers, Coleman, Williams, Laby #NGMedia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@st_halvard @SwixWax @BjornDaehlie Sweden and Germany are different but I get what you're saying]]></document><document><![CDATA[niggas ain’t got no choice but to be faithful if his ole lady can’t fight 🤦🏾‍♂️😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dumb hick motherfucker Arkansas legislature obviously doesn't understand the Maslow Hierarchy of Needs. Yes, I… https://t.co/0oENf37f2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mo Isom speaking to a sellout crowd at the Inspire Women’s Conference today at @elmbrookchurch #moisom… https://t.co/9943wZf9FQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AChandler1944 @nema Thank you for sharing this! Let’s talk more about it. Please send more about your ideas - emai… https://t.co/pPdlC9ILUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wcruz73 Yeah, I called bullshit on those sites rumors from day 1.  Look who has a season 3 now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_spinmd One is one too many if while dicing you forget and rub your eye 🔥😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[some people are just unhealthy. no matter how much you might care about them, if they aren’t willing to change then… https://t.co/iU4ImvlcmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ll be sharing additional tidbits of data from our new report on auto lending in the next few days. And don’t for… https://t.co/z6syBoz3PE]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALF: @alabamambb 34, Auburn 23. AU had 48 points in the first half of this year’s first meeting at AU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RotoGut Love the Cahill call. That ⬇️conract% and ↗️swstr% the past two or 3 seasons shows he’s adjusted and may b… https://t.co/KqNGGmjVbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big Ten bowl destinations could be changing https://t.co/gYyAFdQugM via @qctimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@appNove @AbkaFitzHenley So what longer-term strategies would you recommend regarding violent crimes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richeisen @RichEisenShow @chrisbrockman @MichaelDelTufo  https://t.co/2lbGx8JOqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The father of a toddler killed in July/2017 is #suing the #DCFS of LA County. They blame it for not taking their co… https://t.co/zgBirlz2QG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Human Torch @TFlight31 is heating up!! #PureMagic https://t.co/Sj5kR6MP2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Based upon your actions and erratic behavior over the past year, I’d wager that’s your coke straw.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Theron on the mic. #karaokenights @ The Robusto Room https://t.co/N3VvwZUY3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeCurkov @WhitneyMartin58 Lol, no. I was too busy drinking actual wine]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Lingering showers expected in the Bay Area this weekend - San Francisco Chronicle: Lingering showe… https://t.co/2cUK1RzCHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun day today with the second year #medicalstudent doing the #ophthalmology #jeopardy !   No there wasn’t any… https://t.co/cZ5K0ARZeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad to hear Peter Tork has passed. R.I.P.  I love the MONKEES. #DAYDREAMBELIEVER. @krassenstein @ProudResister… https://t.co/9wwC61OvLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LasVegas hotels make me laugh! @ North Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/0teHPlaudi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaylaniLive AWESOME!!! CANT WAIT TO BUY THAT!!! #PayForYourPorn #BonerInspiring #Goddess #Perfection #DreamCumTrue #DreamWoman #MyFantasy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sldeskins @sahluwal moment.  I would rather evaluate it based on what they were trying to accomplish and what the… https://t.co/KQ2tn9FyOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday February 20 - Evening Update:      Jared Kushner privately working on reshaping legal immigration;      R… https://t.co/fqYSxcCnoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT HAPPENED ONE NIGHT CASABLANCA THE APARTMENT ORDINARY PEOPLE THE RETURN OF THE KING]]></document><document><![CDATA[This snow today has me thinking about this great winter hike back home❄️  . . . . #hike #hiker #hiking #waterfall… https://t.co/fN1ZY7r5b9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gabigiovannis @JoeyMikez @daveoreoz2 @TonyJJs1 @darlacostello15 This shit crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sethzaremba Which personal lines carrier is at least in the stratosphere of @sethzaremba 's preferred behavior?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never made it to Arch Madness while I was a student at Drake, so I have decided that’s gonna be one of my post-law school goals. 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kady All these conversations were meant to be private and confidential. Unless something illegal had taken place w… https://t.co/oc34Yiwhcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I thought while I listened to this weeks @Gastropodcast: I need to grow a pawpaw (indigenous American tropical… https://t.co/e4NlBqB3gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember a girl told me I only look fine when the brightness is turned all the way down. That shit hurt my feelings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson Trying to use “State of Emergency” to try and circumvent Congress appropriation of… https://t.co/y12kz5XMwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t sleep in hotel sheets, with hotel air, and hotel sounds. I’ve tried. Lord knows I’ve tried.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No se... pero mirando el video de @CarmenYulinCruz en cnn me hace pensar que en realidad @Jenniffer2012 ha perdido… https://t.co/JF8CipWL9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFPD about two mins ago I witnessed a police officer harassing a homeless person at Turk and Hyde. This person was… https://t.co/U6pjuxrZbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VINCE_RUGGIERO @BTB_MikeII To those that liked the “PAYSON!” tweet aka @joey2900 and @RFL630 just want to direct y… https://t.co/MLAQhdtjVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrestling's Most Fire (character agnostic) Entrance Themes; A thread of absolute bangers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone want to go to Walmart? Got my grandmas handicap pass. Prime parking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll take any of these over the current occupant. All in favor, signify with “aye.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone @ another Lexi girl so i can fit in with my homies.  She's gotta be solid w the crew though.  Thx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterVecsey1 Who is your favorite NBA writer of the current bunch? I like Windy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I asked Abe a question, and he was honest all right... 🏛 https://t.co/z1RDNuMJBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @lsarsour I guess we can revisit our position on Palestine.  As long as they denounce anti semitism.  And offi… https://t.co/kGmriPu9XJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The final debate before the Public Advocate Special Election is tonight at 7 pm on @ny1. See for yourself why… https://t.co/stedpmZeBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Garrett_Love I also blame McConnell for holding this vote on a Monday when at least one Aye vote was delayed returning to DC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeartofNHL It's like underwear. Hockey players wear their gloves until they are thread-bare.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarmaBrooks76 @buzztard @FireGoddessB @RuleChicago @Cdubey_Texas @BlindMelon1967 @BakerBitchBakes @CandyisDandy100… https://t.co/zd9zKOYfEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorCollins I’m shocked you can even spell constitution much less understand it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeighHelberg @wearetavonni @Camouflage_Don @RainierDaVinci @SSGSaintLyric You look fab, Ms. Leigh!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewSellonNY  my username sake  Dr. Evil but with my name in the middle https://t.co/DZ78WALXHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[But when Obama wasn't your president y'all gladly took the day off so 🤫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems about right. Hard to argue against Florida in the “Lean R” category. The question for Ds is: spend big in FL… https://t.co/bBogD449lA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 11 highlights in Salesforce #Spring19 by Linda Johnson #Salesforce https://t.co/djBEMzS77G]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realdonaldtrump, you have no right to control my body or my decisions. Your gag rule keeps patients who get care… https://t.co/8DcuLWMYXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoredStiff415 @bryconmusic All it takes, is one wrong glance! And savages'll be pullin' money out yer pockets! Like a Cash-day- advance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love getting a $3200 bonus from work but losing 1k of it to taxes. #TaxationIsTheft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislongview @MarcACaputo He’s not running for president. He just signed a cable TV contract. And man, running fo… https://t.co/fEy6igvRkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Cohen is a known liar, asking him to go in front of Congress and tell the truth is a waste of time,… https://t.co/bFBJmhDkf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Week8Assignment #Environment #We #Somos @ Broward County, Florida https://t.co/VG3S6abwNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like I’m going to Nashville tomorrow for @kgumbs5 championship game 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJiffyGriffy Plus 118 more games, plus like 5000 more minutes as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re on the plane, next stop Disney 🛫🛫 😎😎😎 @ Nashville International Airport https://t.co/drZOEN8c7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annakayerogers @BookwormBlues Thats... both sad and fair. I never dealt with a lot of that in HS, beyond "WHY AREN… https://t.co/I8MHyy3yrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! On this day in history in 1980 #IWillSurvive by @gloriagaynor wins the first &amp; LAST Best Disco Song award.… https://t.co/LkU8HGr0EG]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing more special than Senior Day and everyone singing the chorus of My Old Kentucky Home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canada has turned into a shit hole thanks to #Trudeau #cdnpoli  https://t.co/tfM8NB8crb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This match is already 🔥 on an 🥶 night in the desert.  Both players are already into it, and so are the fans. Quiete… https://t.co/PhQ71xztR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Is this an official invite to the event? And can I bring my vlogging camera?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cooorius Thank you so much for your support for @CSBDBook. As I recount in the pages, I had to learn through losin… https://t.co/M9ecq2ik3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cole explaining this at the end of a song or on a Lil interlude gone be hard as hell @almightyzuwop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trip_elix @EinsteinMaga @duckusa @7proudamerican @tagruber @Rightwingmadman @heyitsCarolyn @tweets4poppy… https://t.co/Fcipqnft78]]></document></documents></author>