<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@blackwidow07 Thank you Veronica! Some days the pain is just so hard to deal with..... all I can do is cry and pray🙏🏼⚜️🙏🏼⚜️🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I TOLD her she's my mentor and she replied, "I got you!" 😊Mrs. Melanie Sithole, I love you, I admire you, and I app… https://t.co/n16iyfidRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mis palabras tienen que armonizar con mis acciones, si no como pretendo que me crean?.]]></document><document><![CDATA[somebody please teach me how to be more disciplined with money. please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FIRST @JeffreeStar PURCHASE EVER AND SECURED THE LAST SET 😭💕  @MorpheBrushes https://t.co/f4YmmfnsxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HATE greedy ass people that ain’t down to help the homies and the fam. Money comes and goes, I’ll ALWAYS show up for the real ones idc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NearpodTransform Countdown is on!  ⏰Just a few hours away! ❤️☕ @nearpod https://t.co/cJR91f6jmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Continental Pastries &amp; Deli in Battle Creek, MI https://t.co/MK5g7zXxKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrcrom1 I subscribed tp BotSentinel.  I'll let you know what it's like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamPaulaLM @Benmoak @RealJamesWoods I live in McAllen, Texas where Hispanics are the majority.  Everyone is friend… https://t.co/n16RpOkJSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djrothkopf @jonathanchait @davidfrum I think it’s because he can’t get anybody else to do it for him well simultaneously  taking credit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think this is technically complaining but.... i can’t stand ppl who constantly complain lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acosta Meeting for what? North Korea will never give up their nuclear weapons!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankLuntz Yes, she is an irresponsible liar that is trying to get attention and support from this class of people… https://t.co/B0m7RZXfDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checkin' out the offense!   @TorontoArgos @IAm_Wilder32 #doubleblue https://t.co/WZPoQfBJKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauvsongs @troyesivan @Spotify this song is toooooo good so i’m not surprised❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekends, wine, and Momma J. These are a few of my favorite things.  💕 @ Mallow Run Winery https://t.co/clzKWP9qaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing old friends and partners to celebrate @OSSEDC  birthday- I remember when we started in 2007!  @AJEInc… https://t.co/WlDkqikiMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisguysnuts195 @cpizme @AndrewPollackFL @realDonaldTrump No one wants to take your fucking Gunn’s away!  Time to stop pretending.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was that #YouCouldBeMine @DieterRuehle? #GoKingsGo  I think that should be Kovalchuk’s new song #AfterThatHit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[this why i could never date a white man, smh they family be racist af sometimes 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fawkesphoenix3 @KeltWitch @Fact_Check_Er @pollsofpolitics @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Genuine ( if you were asking me… https://t.co/bBDogYw8kd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shudder announces fuzzy new Critters series (via @CreepyDDCrowley) https://t.co/G2bYK7dmU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united Really United? Here I am in Medford Oregon waiting to pick up a very important world renowned pianist and I… https://t.co/5Mi3JfdhHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lucidi Duro viu? O bosta do entregador trouxe a pizza debaixo do braço! Mais idiota impossível! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackJ Sometimes I wish people would respect our rights to be secure in our homes, bodies, and papers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Harrison what are you doing asking that foolish question???  #TheBachelor https://t.co/RUsfsOAdk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[no entiendo porque me puse tan mal ayer, bueno si pero no manches Melina no aguantas nada 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just really confused why couples do “couples therapy” when they’re only dating?   You have no legal obligation.… https://t.co/6PqO2SWiIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@btaylor AGREED. @netflix please give us an option to turn this off asap 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the things (@ PCC Community Markets in Burien, WA) https://t.co/98fwkQlSpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm really that person that will decorate her own house for her birthday 🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg @joncoopertweets Not right - should not have happened - my heart breaks for you and all the other… https://t.co/BwQ4Xrie1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlbykarlsmith he was just tweeting in his sleep.  don't try to analyze it...  @Noahpinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve loved this song my whole life! My mom had the single on CD and I bumped it HEAVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to my 3:30am Pacific alarm to see if Louis, Kevin Na, or Si Woo has withdrawn #APInv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on with Lori &amp; Julia on My Talk 107 at 3:30 to talk about my Barbra Streisand Tribute this weekend at… https://t.co/MgLBI4fE7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[zakia_sherice 300du 1.jsl king.dayy njl0_o @blizzytrill @Ms_SmoothLoco  @ always humble ??? Zakia, you feel me? Put… https://t.co/3IQb5hXfTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laura24fan @ToddTPrice24 @chevychevelle48 @JLee418 @JudyJ31830202 @Chrisracefan1 @jonesbrent570 @43324FAN… https://t.co/eeH75wzlJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[...I need more followers who will call me out on accidental typos...*their...crickets...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilagrosLeivaG tiene el derecho de defenderse pero no con golpe bajo. Eso si que no!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne Quincy if I could get out of my own driveway I would be more than happy to help you. We are snowed in too it's horrible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recall &amp; jail time. Unless she’s NWO Deep State protected. Then, nada. It’ll be swept under the carpet &amp; forgotten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allahs_SonOfMan @SirDougunefheir @supremekimun @XiJingpingReal @narendramodi Agree. That’s #REALITY? #UNIVERSALITY #TAMFOUR #TaraAnnMoons]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro if you taking a whole hour of my sleep away why would you not expect me to come in an hour late]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, the legislature does need to vote to exclude hemp derived CBD from Minnesota's controlled substances act.  Thi… https://t.co/XuCVaQcAKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellenmcoyne @All4Choice Awful sorry you guys are dealing w:that. As I learned after the #TwitterQandA I did w/… https://t.co/IBHTj8WwHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best part of these pictures is the pirate ship photobomb #FloridasWeird @ Clearwater Beach Island https://t.co/LOhwWJtRcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously how is Hannah G not our next @BacheloretteABC ???? #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning with the bear. Roman Holiday seems to have made the cut. #desertlodge #edie #morning #movies #dvd… https://t.co/ZlsOriZche]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michele5411 Although to be fair, not really a Biden fan, for reasons I have stated b4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BentleyAudrey @InfoSecHotSpot @zippytrippy @barbarannott @AlaricAloor @archonsec @DrJDrooghaag @MiaD… https://t.co/DlUWa52gvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i see one (1) more liberal acting like joe biden of all people is the epitome of wokeness—]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @MrsAllard_ODS and @CoachVedder_HPE to post covers of 7 books I love. No explanation… https://t.co/EYLi2uK3NY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help the kids. If you have anything to donate I will gladly pick up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimothyBitolas I'm okay my son I was trying to change the wax candle with a pocket knife and it slipped and cut my… https://t.co/w001BcpZm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This makes me happy and sad Glee star Lea Michele ties the knot with fiancé Zandy Reich 💍  https://t.co/PNIs9VLMzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He wasn’t thrown out asswipe! You’re a despicable liar! Shame on you. Nevada loves Harry Reid. He… https://t.co/AyOJORdu8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is NOBODY able to board the path train like a competent human being!?!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big news! Excited to see what the future of @RUFNational holds and grateful to be part of this team as our organiza… https://t.co/sQwYFX0DkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump That’s rich coming from Ivanka considering her dad handed her a job and a fortune.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of hearing non educators opinions on as to if they should or shouldn’t go on strike. I know it sucks that… https://t.co/vKHQCALgtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unconditional love for my beautiful mom, she truly is one of a kind🙏🏼 we will be okay mom❤️ #family #love… https://t.co/KiqhvvX4cI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Medicine &amp; the Arts exhibit at Health Sciences Library @HonorsCollege https://t.co/qN14WVM9vX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @roknrolzombie Curious though on how many White people are prosecuted and jailed for the equivalent of wh… https://t.co/lK6Mvs09rL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have lost 42 pounds in 2 years. I have a long ways to go, but I thank God for the outcome of this stage of my lif… https://t.co/6IGGIlDJ10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEllaAyeAye Maggie just said “what the crap Sarah Eller retweeted for Hannah over Cassie!!?!?”😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tristan Maddox, 18, was found dead in a ditch Sunday. He had been shot to death. Investigators need your help figur… https://t.co/8dtvLmziFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Masculine but oh so sleek and sexy celebration for a 40th Birthday! Full Design/Decor/Balloon Wall/ Rentals/Draping… https://t.co/Za5jAyFA8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t fucking know what’s worse, the fact that i can’t put my lid on my water bottle or that i’ve been crying for 3 hours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Cigar City Brewing - @cigarcitybeer in Tampa, FL https://t.co/KH3HhUAFra]]></document><document><![CDATA[While the city sleeps these characters walk the streets 🌚🕷#🎬 #femalespirit @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/nIDtnj1vcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaintCharlie If he settled for any amount, he’s selling out everything he kneels for...IMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Omar was emboldened by the spineless inaction of the House &amp; is attacking every American now - even Democrats &amp; RINOs 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh well and since you just liked this @dearneele you are also coming even if you have NOTHING planned yet. Ok great😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamcbest Yea, the Dems don’t need any help either. Can we all agree everyone sucks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[the jonas brothers are dropping an album tonight &amp; i’m reliving the fuck out of my childhood rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule The boy will WIN the suit. Count on justice being served. The full videos proved his/their innocence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Serenade for Alternative America: John Mellencamp in Peoria, IL https://t.co/mQAiWctXUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worst kids punishment  @superherosrock @SharonG40210896  @Valac666 @JaneColes2 @Kitty_Goncalves  @TeamSalBrian… https://t.co/sdQH71fknu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StasyiBarth @RealJamesWoods Thank you Stasyi. I've tried to tell co-workers that it's rude and to go home. Great t… https://t.co/SuJ8WprYNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My filter on my comments to my cubicle neighbor has definitely started fraying. He just said something about Cheeto… https://t.co/2AcUX4eG0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HT_GIRLS @KyleParmley @jbeanpoll @DennisVictory Smiley!  Love that kid and how much she has grown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikel_Jollett @isa97 It’s beyond ridiculous, isn’t it?  Yes, he’s a liar.  He’s admitting he lied.  He lied for Trump and the GOP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled with the number of @DE_Nonprofit members and partners engaging with the Joint Finance Committee for the ne… https://t.co/F3VdzDy00H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prwolverine Licenciado, no sea malo, tenemos que ser mas inclusivos. Digamos algo asi como  PO PU IN DE PEN DE JIS TAS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to turn those clocks forward one hour my friends! ⏰🔃  Who else is on the struggle bus this morning fro… https://t.co/jfh03OYFP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ruthless_Regg He is for sure. I would have already killed him. Just in jail trying to start my 25 year sentence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gotthehelllout Totally agree! When I was in middle/high school my parents never monitored my internet or phone the… https://t.co/dQc0gYQZLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@femalesrule89 @beatsandlife @WoodardAlyson @VictoriaECM @thejtlewis @realDonaldTrump You’re a communist]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Think big. Start small. Seek impact.” @annmei at @sxsw #SWSW2019 https://t.co/pJF4SGN9N6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinB77 @aafAPOLLOS Yes! Watch the games, help get the word out. It’s all helps and we appreciate you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live show idea I have no energy to produce: “This Didn’t Age Well” staged readings of movies you loved as a kid tha… https://t.co/5DqrpzVhFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Soon as this gets to a point where we can I wish we could turn this around on their ass prosecute… https://t.co/C0VyPdVtmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interview: Suellen Gargantini, founder of SugarLab and travelholic   https://t.co/cpyl0DFCbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished watching the Japanese horror movie "Over My Dead Body", which is based off a rather old ghost story,… https://t.co/XvcRUiazGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing pulls on the heart strings like driving through your hometown listening to High School Musical 3: Senior Ye… https://t.co/c60zrjHsw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite person and my favorite food? Sign me up #DBBwithMyBetterHalf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realtor!!! Looking for more leads?  Join me as I rub elbows with these Mega Agents!!! Be sure to… https://t.co/XW6K55aV1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andrew McCabe says the Justice Department discussed removing Trump from office  https://t.co/pOUUg6C4Xr]]></document></documents></author>