<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@UCFONEBIGOHANA @UCF_Football @UCF_MBB @milton6teresa @tackofall99 @JulieJuliemilk @sarahboudro @cjasinski65… https://t.co/JgPDcS0tKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mudduhchris @rbnearthesea @PattyMurray Hi Chris  I was reading in the news there were around 76,000 entering last… https://t.co/vuoOUs6A6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshMankiewicz They obviously don’t need my cold , hard cash. Shame. Really.]]></document><document><![CDATA[scott has a new song done and is working on more new music https://t.co/zQiBh5UA1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lizard_Eyes Same!! But I’m finally starting to like being in one lol. Only took 83 years ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently there’s a Surf Ranch in Lemoore, CA! Crazy! @VisitCA #california]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido, @liliantintori , @realDonaldTrump  ,@Almagro_OEA2015 @marcorubio debemos a través de… https://t.co/SoVmchYJPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let the Bernie Bros and Sister Bros attacks on me commence. I will only vote for a registered Democrat for presiden… https://t.co/A77oAuQBE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[LET'S GO MANOGUE!!! 💚💛⚾️〽️ #manoguebaseball#minernation #20ismyfavoriteplayer #boymom #ilovemyboys @ Centennial Hig… https://t.co/1nSFjLRAWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating 23 years of Pokémon on Pokémon Day   💙💀💙 https://t.co/KlNFkCpU2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is Chacoman day! Hard to believe that my first love is 6 today... between loving old pizza and snuggling with as… https://t.co/epRMAo4eHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you’re ever wondering, “i wonder what music meg is listening to,” the answer is almost always “shamelessly blast… https://t.co/fMBv8KLv6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AprilDRyan @realDonaldTrump Just makes you feel good about the world, doesn’t it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally having a workout where I feel strong and can lift heavy SO NEEDED THANK YOU JESUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand stress, disillusionment, futility. I see ppl get ahead on the backs of others less advantaged. But not… https://t.co/BsLCKIbvzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gig is up! You are a fake, nothing but an actress playing a part! The Justice Democrat’s are pulling your strin… https://t.co/LrOwPHSoHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[They blastin thank u next n I know everything gonna be alright(hopefully)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, you piece of shit, for making it THAT much harder for real victims to come forward]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your relationship with a murderous thug is very good. Yay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMBlanchard @CahnEmily @IdahoStatesman I just had to literally pick her up/drag her from the car. Something must h… https://t.co/GyiIEFMGVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to be sleep but I can't stop watching Monogamy on @WatchUMC. This is deep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On The Street Where You Live installed in its new home #thanks #ilovewhatido #happycustomers #eleanorlowden… https://t.co/dil8irH7Io]]></document><document><![CDATA[The spark to depict my surroundings started as a child. I loved visiting my grandmother in Jefferson City, Missouri… https://t.co/c6F20QblQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Zeets A thread called “Nutmegs as philosophical arguments” was too subtle for them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope people are listening ... not only does the book have good strong messages, I believe it also shares the heart… https://t.co/75Gz7fmrrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope yall find someone who treats you amazing &amp; knows the difference between there, their &amp; they’re. 🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw that we are in pre retrograde on @amrezy IG story... and now it all makes sense.. 🙃🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have very few best friends   And the ones I have are like family....I'm just putting it out there if anyone trys… https://t.co/zbMkyS23N8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Social Work Month!!!! Happy Social Work Month to my friends and colleagues!!!! #socialworkmonth @jtrammell75 https://t.co/JxvKa0l6MP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump You’re nuts thinking God would stand for a wall... God sent Joshua to march around… https://t.co/XSeOiLtsS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[ExploreJapanWith KathNiel  #KathNielLovesJapan  #VoteKathrynBernardo #KCA @bernardokath https://t.co/5uNMUGaJs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karaoke from bed! 🎶🎙 #IggyAzalea 💁‍♀️🙆‍♀️ #ArianaGrande 💃🎹🎷 #ThursdayMotivation 💅💋 https://t.co/VHwEIPQzRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[See the 2019 Optimists issue, guest-edited by Ava DuVernay https://t.co/aSZHgqvzyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ What else can be expected from Cortex,  a politically immature, non objective inexperienced new Congress woman… https://t.co/YNDpbEsXKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork @KamVTV Nadler needs to be investigated! https://t.co/3JSqW1F7Vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on getting the channel back up and running :) #BossMomma #MakingMoves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was fun to read this article today. We loved our trip with @cmh_heli #BobbieBurns last summer. Amazing experience!  https://t.co/vGrJOavVzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s #TheBachelor date was totally at @wingsmuseum so throwing it back (on a Monday whatever) to the best dadd… https://t.co/HjU8kon2vX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a dream I cut my hair to my shoulders then I cried for the remainder of the dream and woke up in a panic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bwahahahahhahahaah my client said Ms Weathers, the most romantic shit this nigga said to me was, hey you wanna take… https://t.co/aXU4SKCsEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Hell On Wheels by @BrantleyGilbert on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/BFEYyuJUVT https://t.co/zNyEeE0zE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I  talked to God we made a deal and so he made a prophet.” I believe he is a prophet. Amazing how he didn’t write… https://t.co/WuyYtVT2tI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xcarson_Lacavax I’m coming to see you in like a month https://t.co/79qzp2vPPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am in deep admiration of Elijah Cummings. He’s a new member of “people I would enjoy sitting around with talking… https://t.co/H1M741xK6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rasmus "Captain Material" Sandin knows how to cook and lives on his own! #Marlies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 @Chrisbdg34Smith I wont vote Sanders. I won't vote Kamala (unless its as VP)  TO BIDEN👍😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NytoSports Otra cosa (valga la redundancia), una cosa es “entretenimiento” y otra muyyyyyy diferente es AMARILLISM… https://t.co/dFT0beLd50]]></document><document><![CDATA[when god or whoever made me it was that video of the guy throwing the french fries into the pot and it exploding an… https://t.co/Qa2dy4cAQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brwneyebooknerd Wishlist consists of anything Red Rising, Cruel Prince/Wicked King BN editions or merch, Laini Tay… https://t.co/4oqqxEr8zV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I start my back piece once I finish my arms or do I save some money 💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[i dont get why some people think you NEED to be ina relationship, i remember a while ago some guy was talking shit… https://t.co/CeejrOhOhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[De Blasio hasn’t decided whether he will run but says regardless he will travel the country and offer evidence of p… https://t.co/FWJcWfawIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to send me a soy vanilla latte and food, I’ll marry you. Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s ready for the album?? 👀 Lemme know. 👅😉🤘🏽 Side note: I’m doing features RIGHT NOW, HMU for yours!❗️❗️ @ United… https://t.co/u8jgaeGqJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just priceless. When I grow up I want to have this historian’s courage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexaNerDervish @VirtualCapitol Let’s hope Texas fixes its “glitchy” voting machines soon..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa @shareesewillia1 @RealCandaceO That’s what the Crooked Clinton’s do. Chelsea Clinton is no different...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#almondlatte (at @Bru_Coffeebar in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/dBuBe5ETE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m lucky to be with someone who really takes care of me. You can’t believe the dumb shit I’ve asked him to do for… https://t.co/a0jFR2wzii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Neena119 Props to the black dude, the pastor expert dude-least he tried. 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jethrotull @ProgMagazineUK I still have my Jethro Tull T-shirt from the 70’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamconover @donttrythis @AdamRuins And when does this air? I need to watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[By himself ok, he doesn’t wanna hold my hand he wants to do it on his own 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch Why don’t you compete against your own gender. You do have a penis. Maybe someone should kick you in the balls before competing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VarshPrakash @SenFeinstein @sunrisemvmt Time to listen to experts —@SenFeinstein plan is far superior… https://t.co/jflGbTeCOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AnnCoulter likes to straddle the fence so she can remain relevant to both parties..she sways with the wind..gotta… https://t.co/D22sKFeLaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SenLisaBaker for acknowledging @PAVictimsOffice and importance of balancing victims rights with those of… https://t.co/VUCPLG8gPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go Pens!! Game 2 for us this weekend!!@penguins 💛🖤🏒 https://t.co/oPwfDhkVUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna know what’s absolutely exhausting? Reaching out for help numerous times only to be shot down over and over again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CantonRepdotcom @mpopovichREP @SammyB1590 @Jerry_Snodgrass @1480whbc @btsohio @eowlspotlight @LouisvilleLeps Pleas… https://t.co/v0XrpfXvul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FinleyRhea2 @LissaLove123 @Plastik_Bama @hotblondtrouble @formerbondgirl @oftheangels3 @DatoFreddy… https://t.co/ZRBrsZ483T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aug1405 @grannyanon1969 @billiefischer13 @NewsMassCentral @Jscroggins5515 @EvonDesign @kricklys @jlpowellp… https://t.co/Wr1U6S5q1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why These Alabama Voters Are Sticking By Roy Moore (HBO) https://t.co/VryRghSqij via @YouTube. Please share this fr… https://t.co/yvBPXYdgck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been receiving a whole lot of LOVE for this “Sabotage” track. I even see a few ppl that I never thought were listen… https://t.co/EVownp7w0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teacherasleader @inspirecitizen1 @fablefy @BiscottiNicole @ThirstyBeesNY @ThingsMSKidsSay @lportnoy… https://t.co/8vo6HVbGsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendanKLieb The wonderful coconut aroma made it all the way here to Los Angeles!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, @SRuhle, trump is a criminal. Full stop. You know that in your heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmithCliff999 @redsteeze @neontaster I did close to two dozen interviews with them (most were too incoherent to us… https://t.co/zwAcoG1rhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[moving here by myself 3 years ago has taught me so much, generally about life. i’m overwhelmed with emotions thinki… https://t.co/a6y1FKLyXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @GingerMaterni  to post covers of 7 books I love. No explanations, no reviews. Each… https://t.co/Qfo0WnycZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You can’t even tell the truth about your height and weight.  FAT LIAR  you are not 6’3” https://t.co/fDvVGxzig0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Internation Womens Day and various other misspellings, such as "Internatinal Womens Day," is trending #1 ahead of… https://t.co/KNb099im9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHAZDEAN Sending lots of love and healing prayers for both Bella and Riley! 💕💜💕💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @MikeSchreiner.  Tremendous achievement.  Thank you for demonstrating that politics done well does… https://t.co/l7XdQadC9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sing any Led Zeppelin chorus while u wearing that shirt. I’ll wait. https://t.co/IGSXMjEiCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans daaaaaaumn!!! Sh*t is so fancy, I’m gonna need a second monocle!!! 🧐🎩 https://t.co/4sd2WFEp3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilkellbell @carlmartin656 @SadiesAngel208 @lloydbassII @novias_info @ZellnerCrimeLaw @obibluraven @discreetsecure… https://t.co/4s974Zcb1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Why aren’t you scared of me? Why do you care for me?” 👽🧟‍♀️💫  _ • • • _ Song: wherearetheavocados #buryafriend 🎶 C… https://t.co/I3yXCW50Ud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet another SNOW DAY!!!  Classes are cancelled as it has been recommend to stay off the roads. Better SAFE than sor… https://t.co/4VNQR5Vg9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneaking kisses from Sergei every time my parents walk around the corner. When did I go back to high school? 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz día a una mujer chingona, hermosa, de gran corazón y de las más hermosas letras.  Feliz #DiaDeLaMujer @alixbauer 🌻❤️✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HealthyWayMag Well, tomorrow is my 2nd HIIT workout, I know I need to do it to: 1. help with the soreness 2. build… https://t.co/cEjybdUOiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyisFlyer The friendship between Talbot and Hart would give him an personal advantage over the game and defini… https://t.co/ARagzfdHLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Friday, a Louisville Fire official warned that the potential cuts would have "life or death" consequences:… https://t.co/0aY97QHeBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 2nd Birthday my baby 🎉 aunt nana loves you ❤️❤️ https://t.co/cMOctai5NE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nw: OF FATHERS AND SONS (2018) nominated for best documentary at this year’s academy awards  “Sundance-feted Syria… https://t.co/6e1dwt0bvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had the honor of meeting Travis and he instantly melted my heart with his incredible energy and excitement… https://t.co/kXo5uKcB4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KillyFanForever @KillyForever @vickiabc123 I don't think you have any idea how passionate we are about Kelly and B… https://t.co/mcAd2cd29c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hulk5mashed Honey My tickets were purchased by the gentleman that booked me for these trips. That’s why it wasn’t announced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[people who show absolutely zero effort while texting need to be taken out.. of my life.. for good..… https://t.co/ksvlOuPpXc]]></document></documents></author>