<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Anthony_MAFS The Passion she has and her voice to express herself is incredible. She is singing to everyone person… https://t.co/xnfIow6Mab]]></document><document><![CDATA[I picked the wrong day to be with kamerin. These niggas out here buying drinks]]></document><document><![CDATA[John W. Hickenlooper for President of the United States 🇺🇸 @Hickenlooper #hickenlooper2020 #coloRADoPOTUS https://t.co/gUHxCcRYL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Year 2016 at 47th GMMSF Box Office Entertainment Awards  @mainedcm  / Maine Mendoza won Most Promising Female Star… https://t.co/X6z4EJOQsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJBlakBoy Lmaoooo 🤣 ayeee you right about that ima use that next time 🤞🏾😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetingdears @eugedelviento @maria_tsolia @dimash_official @WorldsBestCBS #TWBDimash , #WorldsBest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steeper33 @G_ozzy @AndrewScheer @CPC_HQ You're kidding right? @AndrewScheer is a Liberal-aligned Crony Capitalist… https://t.co/7SfzPO9dXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burke_Supa A track meet was never held in barbado😂😂 yall dont even have a track thats up to standard to hold a wor… https://t.co/fvSXUuHQ8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[scariest part about letting people in is you never know someone’s true intentions with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnav_08 @PaigeChristieUK IDK.  My sister' bf of 50 years is just skinny.  I've seen her eat and she and my sister… https://t.co/T3h1mwpzM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyjanehubb We do, although fundamentally I look most like my Mom, and Jennifer is my Dad's sister.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLTOrg’s Fireside chat with @codepath Founder and CEO Michael Ellison! #sxsw2019 #mltrockssxsw https://t.co/iyacTs4SWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW @SandiPattyP - I’ve never been more happy that I didn’t just go home after work. You filled my heart in ways I… https://t.co/TvIgzTLdZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccourtknee_ @Abt77Thompson @BQQuinn @TellEmSteveDave I bought him a bottle of vanilla Jim Beam!! Lol. Last year I… https://t.co/ZIcRCXQ62M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator Elizabeth Warren talk about breaking up Facebook has to do with Facebook must reframe from selling informat… https://t.co/bBe1T7tIPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@for_pittys @Ann13Beer ESPERANZA. meaning hope. And sounds like Keila gave that 2 the dog. TKS 2 all helping. Sorry, ESPERANZA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgentMcNasty @WIBeetle @zaptrapped @FixesItself @Silvergirl1072 @CatLSiegel @VFlowingFineArt @tea_ryanny… https://t.co/AgxCG8p3aP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Integrity comes first in our law practice. https://t.co/QOaMMr31Uo @ Law Offices of Ginger B. Kelly https://t.co/TOBOb9LHAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cs00582scs @DGPurser That is horrible to read and to think their are citizens who are afraid in their own country… https://t.co/YCMFaWCvAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pelosi says she's opposed to impeaching Trump: 'He's just not worth it' LET ME TELL U WHO'S NOT  WORTH IT DEM -HEAD… https://t.co/abtQ1cd3K6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @Iluvinspireu @MelindaYoe @debratankersle1 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Peeperpea29 @JackConnie @karenslinn43… https://t.co/WxU7yzmWrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I showed this to my mom and she said “oh my goodness and he licked it again! Oh wow, that’s scary. Snakes have salm… https://t.co/vsUXqvJOTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Innocent? You’re the most crooked president! You are a traitor, a criminal, a bully, a con man and… https://t.co/7MNoiuRsae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being an Android user makes me feel like a flat earther on this website]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourServiceYW @tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Yes, I know.   Then Democratic-Republicans, then Democrats and Whigs, then… https://t.co/Eg6s1D0gFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawnRppl @CharlieFKNSheen There are lots of them, I've reported at least 5 of them so far.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lash Extensions, Lash Lift and Lash Tint... it’s all a necessity 🙋🏼‍♀️🥰😘 #lashextensions #lashlift #lashlove… https://t.co/1xABUjDgsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_naeeema_  told Chooop “Broke niggas always tryna find a scam, like, nigga get a job”😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[This needs to stop now. No human being should be put through this. They treat us like we don’t have rights or digni… https://t.co/L5IeCnp2S2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real world experience for Stus - creativity, innovation, and life lessons @Trevvett_Elem!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BRaeSunny No but he watched me hanging clothes every day .  We lived in London at the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like @MTV_AMANDAG plays a role. She would never get in anyone's face or talk to people like she does in real… https://t.co/5HxWBnXKVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulWhiteleyPhD Think they T absurdly over reaching. ASD kids develop GI problems they R not born this way. Real G… https://t.co/yLMWbBf9iB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How in God's name can you, of all people, talk about corrupt? You and your administration are the… https://t.co/YH6htgUuin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm...did this wall keep the people out that didn't need to be in at @Oscars2019? Yes? So, walls work? 😉 https://t.co/RD94axVevI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewYangVFA @williamlegate Why don't we have a thumbs down icon on Twitter?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA He’s been saying that for years now.  He’s yet to submit proof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VTDukefan Oh my gosh!!! I remember that game so well! I despised UNLV. 👇😂 https://t.co/nIAbfmXpLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐈 KAT FUR NEW LONDON 🐈 Great to be knocking doors this morning with Kat for New London to get out the vote for the… https://t.co/e7nOzptvIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump You wouldn't know the truth if it was spoken, anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro... why does my roommate always fucking turn the ac on when it’s cold as fuck outside. I want to be cozy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrKitMath @samjshah @cmmteach @MaryBourassa @calcdave @stoodle @NatBanting @carloliwitter You know, Ca-rl. My husb… https://t.co/CT2KVDYcDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this.  I wouldn’t be able to to fill my Instagram page with ANY film/tv placements if I didn’t keep trying aft… https://t.co/Hn7fb7TQVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bravo, Ella! “I Am the Future!” Yes, you are! Leadership, young talent voices, community connections matter!… https://t.co/P97m8KFODf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Turning Opposition into Opportunity” with @BikeWalkRVA. Louise Lockett Gordon says a guiding philosophy for their… https://t.co/CLGfQb9chV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who woke up at 4 a.m. to make sure their phone sprung ahead since it is your alarm? https://t.co/n83IsIEkuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where else can you get this huge bag, containing over 25 pounds of carefully prepared food for LESS THAN $100? (see… https://t.co/M3XjjI5r84]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_R_Berna @pjbowles4 @LadyNY4Ever @AnnThacker2 @CensoredC1 @cali_curmudgeon @JulieReichwein1 @Sissy4Trump… https://t.co/N8PqzeHbNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je continuerai à collaborer avec les utilisateurs du transport en commun dans le #quartierInnes ainsi que les utili… https://t.co/klM6RNSQB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought my mom her first iPhone today. Her first comment was “How do I take good selfies like you?” 🤦🏻‍♀️ My mom now has Snapchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spike Lee’s @40AcresBrooklyn movie “”Chi-raq”. #WalterMcKenzie saw man killed at point blank range at  bus stop 🚏 b… https://t.co/z07YVpiB8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[9th grade writing camp @HMLSrHighSchool getting our Trojans ready! @David_K_Moore @MDCPS @IzquierdoMarie… https://t.co/fcsoN0rxIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraB16901827 Good night Sandra. Thank you so much and for the adorable picture. Hope you have a most wonderful… https://t.co/nocCz05S4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[There has, for a long time, been a progressive energy in the Democratic Party. It is what gave us the 2018 midterms… https://t.co/QnoxEMmwdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my best friends just told me, through the walkie talkie app on my watch, that my cough sounds like a car try… https://t.co/yRc4wsS40K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shedding light on something important that usually gets swept under the rug? Congrats to @Louis_Tomlinson for dropp… https://t.co/LklBmOEcQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone could please be my sugar daddy and pay my bills until I graduate from school that would be great. #sugardaddy 😂😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kohls #LoveKohls 🙌 #sweepstakes I love shopping in Kohl’s! I never leave empty handed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen I was just looking at this like why does she look like she's ten years younger LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear these are human ...or at least partially. If I ever had a farm, I would definitely have alpacas  . . .… https://t.co/vsufxuyEW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gondos, come out to @CicLAvia  to take the Great Streets Scavenger Hunt and enjoy the games! #GondoPride… https://t.co/kjaxLpuNLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prayingmedic Stress will do that to you though and this is a man who is ridiculed, threatened, etc, 24/7.  If it's true that is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[fuck um so I forgot about this song &amp; now I’m sitting here at work actually crying thanks https://t.co/F8OiCkE1BQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BraveTube @shawnwlewis @LndOntRetweets @MeganatLFPress @jacklayton Okay, so instead of making this a war of party… https://t.co/xP2b8VpB55]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm probably going to be one of those people that die by ignoring a serious illness because I think it's something… https://t.co/VfjPrzmR1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets @GOP They became so corrupt that it never occurred to any of them that this is TREASON!  Watch the h… https://t.co/Brmph52o25]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess its National Love your pet day. This big guy was protecting Dad and Liam yesterday morning as the woke up a… https://t.co/8w3PHGYWGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rglfm5 @debit_mullins @pjbowles4 @TheSteveKon @kaci150 @WC25828091 @timfisher836 @rod_brandt @PatriotRanger… https://t.co/H1FYUmRXP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyft PLEASE make the nope, yup commercial go away.  It’s obnoxious, rude, and annoying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bouchareb05 @NBCChicagoFire @karakillmer @NBCChicagoPD @JonSeda Cant wait to see them together again in the series !]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the Hollywood A-listers that jumped to his defense and called the doubters racist must feel like idiots. He's d… https://t.co/FaBmrgb24U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw this last fall in Athens, Greece while I was roaming the city with my family. This was when I was still vegetar… https://t.co/BLrjlz85SL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beccaboo_22 I’m still crying at the fact that the dog looked back at it 😂😂😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 @Docziggy @podlodka150 @AKiel42308269 @rene_toledano @crumpeteerer https://t.co/vIhTKGrkHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was and am in awe of Auric's business plan, which is primarily oriented to making regional flights in Tanzania ac… https://t.co/3nna7EiMVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack @LizizFine Lord Oh Mitty there are times when we ask for you're help in everything,  but YOU DEAR GOD bet… https://t.co/b0m0dR3iNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[she must be suffering from some type of brain injury if she really believes jordyn is the reason her family is now… https://t.co/4D9fTQgyvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad to hear some friends don’t want what’s best for me meanwhile I’m always wishing them the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost mindsetofgreatness ・・・ Usually I post only very uplifting stuff, but I needed this extra push and reminder… https://t.co/KJ1QlCv7ps]]></document><document><![CDATA[But when you fast, comb your hair and wash your face. Matthew 6:17 NLT https://t.co/OFZ9EDPieB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jugheadbabie @superfastmar I like a specific look and it’s been very like “do I just think you’re hot or do I wann… https://t.co/o8lBipTNWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EDeMarche @FoxNews funny how much you can pull out of your ass for views. Thanks the assumptions and even making u… https://t.co/xyNeDLBDmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg I was asked by a member why I thought they were a hate group. I guess this is my proof.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritWind16 @Mr_JSheffield @DonaldJTrumpJr @MailOnline This is some mind bending stupidity. It’s his signature. I… https://t.co/jSDuBPhl1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeG91203 They haven’t - I check everyday for updates. Please share his picture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think my #HelloFresh box was a little TOO fresh... 😂 #Cricket #catsofinstagram #cats #haha @ Lisbon, Maine https://t.co/J3SBmv0z58]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman I congratulate this man telling the truth and Tucker couldn’t handle it. 👍🏻👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner @deez_grapes So give proof of all the things you accuse Trump of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyberfly8 Republic is the real clue. And to the Republic for which it stands, one nation....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I let myself get comfortable enough to ask someone to do something for me. I quickly got reminded h… https://t.co/EVJRxgXmP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we really not going to talk about the fact that it was a nekked (faced) Landy who got his scoring touch back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was so worth leaving the monsters game for. 🤤🤤🤤 https://t.co/GWHh5CCsrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaraRanger @DarthContinent @BrokenBridgeGXB @HamillHimself @mosaiccanyon @_Cristian_Vlad_ @LeeLeeskeewee… https://t.co/YlU8th2FEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Who coached your dad into having sex with a PORN STAR????  NOBODY!  HE's a LIAR on his own.  Does h… https://t.co/BwsgsF76Rr]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 22233 SCOTT CIR #LexingtonPark #MD  #realestate https://t.co/RUwWC2iNHM  [For sale]]]></document><document><![CDATA[DePauls women’s tennis team are live on PlaySight against Michigan State!]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️What a way to start a school morning!  Thank you @Donuts_Delite for donating your world-class donuts to benefit… https://t.co/urXuqpU2eZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“All truly great thoughts are conceived while walking.” – Friedrich Nietzsche]]></document><document><![CDATA[My day has been made. Organizing (really overhauling 😆) my home office  and I just found a brand new @mallybeauty l… https://t.co/qcltBcNX4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorgeous day to be outside... what are you doing? #loveyou @ Woodinville, Washington https://t.co/BgfuAMbXGP]]></document></documents></author>