<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BET @BankzO @JDenelle @JustineSkye What?  Is she trying to look like a robot or something?  It's eerie looking in my opinion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCM @KaylaAndersonTV @LaceyCrisp @KelseaBallerini @MollyBrewerTV @KarinaNova10TV @AshleeBaracy @sam_ponder… https://t.co/jpkY4lKIAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one position at Clemson that was trailing the other positions in recruiting was OL. Not anymore....... https://t.co/bXPWrPk5Jb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HBCUfessions Leave , but try and keep a healthy relationship with her for the sake of the child]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CBJ MeNMyBestBuddy WatchiN the Columbus Blue Jackets https://t.co/4Vpd6qBTRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aubietiger1928 Just downloaded it! I think I’m gonna try to play it some tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPWallace @ToddFuhrman @BetOnlineBurns @LocalRoyaltyMH3 Bama has a weak schedule too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayleighf317 Concentrate on the good in your life and the great times to come. (There will be plenty) Hang in there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got sisters and brothers to feed, I ain’t going out like an Idiot I’m an OG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really tired of having these guy problems. I think I really just need to focus on myself for awhile]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aerostorms @k_yo_media C'mon man. At least credit @StuOstro who created the image]]></document><document><![CDATA[A co-worker brought #snoogles from Sheri’s Coffee House to work this morning for #FatTuesday. They were almost as l… https://t.co/E4d0T2spCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justaballer_ KJ you are an absolute class act. Congrats on a great career at KF and best of luck to you in the future.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to tonight's #WintersaBeachTour . Really excited about seeing @JadeEagleson and… https://t.co/CNHiRw0LHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting great public radio! Commercial free is the way to be!. https://t.co/GgQ6eUmkNf via @wfmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun, fast day. Got the car up on two wheels around this corner all day, so much fun 😂 https://t.co/NBlaBrY0Ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[One benefit of this industry is you make so many friends across the world that you share support and success with.… https://t.co/NCKxHre8CK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fitbit #sundaymorning #morningwalk @ Orange Park, Florida https://t.co/o6jA7CtyDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t write much on social platform, but there are some interesting things happening in science that can’t be ign… https://t.co/FZmawwh5xs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acnewsitics @MarenHofstad Why are you shocked? This is exactly what Trumps staff was afraid he was going to do Vie… https://t.co/0UWtocoPE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo why tell me why have I listened to this new 45sec snippet of the new @PIRATEKNOWLEDGE “Science Born” joint prod… https://t.co/9yzd7m0JOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Search for missing 19 year old Mallory Beach enters its second full day. Beach was lost when the boat she was ridin… https://t.co/sjLtL295nm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMWUSAnews Why is brake flush $109* in South Carolina and the same service is $197* in Southern California? Value… https://t.co/4QStKx5yBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SectatorGaming Not sure lol, but i plan to hibernate until it's time for work again!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toby_Christie Just tinkering on a couple cars... https://t.co/Xnt0OR8ZOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dog #Jack does not like posing for pictures. #dogsofinstagram #rescuedogsofinstagram #rescuedogs @ Elk Grove,… https://t.co/R805A0BvwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have wronged many. I will do my best to mend those that I have hurt. #fixingmeishardwork #fixingmyself @ West Woo… https://t.co/bRdSoBKutW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m surprised I haven’t made drinking tea a daily routine yet. I obvisiously haven’t hit my stride as a writer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Howard_Cole Loved Bill White as a kid. Run into him every now and again as he lives about 10 miles from me. Always… https://t.co/VMDktwqHuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golden Retrievers are honestly the best dogs to have, they show more love,affection and intelligence than some huma… https://t.co/syx46UednP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerChambless @EEDDDDYY96 @TacoSwaggerr and myself have an 818 day streak… we care]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:44.6°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JupiterBits @NASAJuno @SwRI MORE ABOUT JUPITER PLANET.. https://t.co/ACtaA1sdKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darth @Kris_Sacrebleu I watched today and WILL NEVER AGAIN VOTE REPUBLICAN ( after 50 years of voting ONLY republican )!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BatesPhysio @salsb @GeoEdResearch @drugmonkeyblog @mholder_conklin @Rick_Frausto @jenheemstra @sbarolo @dnatarheel… https://t.co/bmulKVSXad]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:30.7°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad sent me some money for food with an extra 5$ for what he said was beer inflation 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edeweysmith @OfficialGHSA @scoreatlanta @issuu SW Macon had some major battles with Douglass HS(Atlanta) back in late 70s-late 80s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn't it be great if the stupidity of the parents were to end, by not putting children in harm. The parents are… https://t.co/9UOrhT2ARD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@44ina4door Ah. That's what it was. You were using terminology I was too dumb to understand.  Whatever puts you to sleep at night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaBartiromo @kimguilfoyle @GOPLeader @SundayFutures @FoxNews @kevinomccarthy Shifty shiff resign!! Shifty is de… https://t.co/AW8vwIb2CF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two #GLVCchamps semifinals tomorrow. Both on Jock 98.7 FM.  12pm: @DruryMBB vs. Lewis 8:30pm: @DULadyPanthers vs. Truman State/Maryville]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s official, I’m gonna live in a cabin deep in the woods with my dogs. Complete solitude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck whoever don't like me, cause the streets love me, and I love the streets  back🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌 @ H… https://t.co/A0tvu5t5la]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Smiles As DDGI Celebrates It’s 15th Consecutive Year As Best Designers! Special Thanks To DHome For Hosting Suc… https://t.co/Wb0xSPrsHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My entire body hurts.   Someone bring me a rice crispy bar and and entire crock pot of mac and cheese.   #pasta… https://t.co/z2VnLgQZBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should have did Thanos or Darkseid because Bane is nothing without his venom]]></document><document><![CDATA[me and vivian bonding over being white men whores https://t.co/Fqi7Wg6NWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barton was asked about his defense tonight, which he told us he takes pride in.   “I hooped in the streets a lot. Y… https://t.co/uWXlZWlRGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @JackPosobiec @OANN He’s not a “former” Coast Guard LT.  Not until he gets due process of law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not even Lent, and I'm already seeing so much Easter candy. Do candy companies adjust production based on the… https://t.co/dukWt3hBZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wiccans wants you ... . Model: @andrea_perales1 . #aboutportraits #instawalkmx #portraitkiller #colectivetrend … https://t.co/9yI0I4P0Sj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Jobs report badly missed estimate, the U.S. economy added just 20,000 jobs in last month. Enough w… https://t.co/AgfVQT9hvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've wanted a staghorn fern for years, finally bought one yesterday.   #containergardening #staghornfern #fern… https://t.co/p0n7kGVAN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think if Dems ever get back all 3 branches, their next move will be to get rid of our flag (too offensive to them… https://t.co/worKQAEWfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jena4n @BullFro62410273 @DoeDRAKE2 @dq_420 @GrilledWith @MRC_C137 @1darioverde @good_ole_tay Thanks 4 the heads u… https://t.co/YRYYZ1HGIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miss_Allison_D Nurse gets tossed as refs giving the game to Spurs #Raptors #WeTheNorth https://t.co/1TJ1nGtBtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbiesawyer_ @RichardsonHS_FB All of our FB moms are so supportive and the best! 💕 this! Love @LoganSawyer_ and the fam! #StayPurple]]></document><document><![CDATA[@she_devours @Z0MBIE_PIE You gotta watch out for weirdos on here. You can't trust random folks on social media. Peo… https://t.co/hfVU17spFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTimpf I would love to talk to you on fox and friends about first responders PTSD, and the silent stigma, that t… https://t.co/qCNQq1qC8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidPriess DNI Coats dutifully serving when he could be enjoying retirement, reveling in his grandchildren and Indiana basketball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to Ms. Terri Butler and congratulations on receiving the LT High Five Award.  Ms. Butler is the Administr… https://t.co/9Xffp9eOAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The callousness displayed in the rejection of the #BornAliveAct on the #USSenate floor today is entirely consistent… https://t.co/XIu4vODeNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QBsMVP Imagine now if they draft Bosa. This team will have some playmakers on D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MasriAhmadMD @purviparwani @onco_cardiology @PushpaShivaram @mariovar55 @almasthela @ChamsiPash @rajdoc2005… https://t.co/I52LrV8sPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tj_billups @davthegoat1 @DavianSanders5_ @ljakevan4 @Cutup_rome @DyriEmpy @CoachDjTruth Coach you did an awesome job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAtlantic @gcaw How many times is someone going to write the same article about an "adult in the room" before we… https://t.co/SlLLzjFaUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morehouse Summer Program SMASH Morehouse is looking for high achieving, African American, Latinx, Native American,… https://t.co/AEVJnPTb3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just throw the whole player away. Stays hurt and a bust. Wasted draft pick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #EU has adopted a new #medicaldevice regulation which, for the first time, specifically requires manufacturers… https://t.co/317GKiK0k8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyrieIrving (Obviously I don’t know these people at all I’m just being performative right now try to @Jeep up OLDS… https://t.co/wyym8lX2Ji]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, uh, a guided munition? The wind isn't very divine if a pilot isn't going down with the airframe. I'm sure there… https://t.co/0iw6jcfkAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well.... (@ International Space Station in Merritt Island, FL) https://t.co/TFtjwNyXa7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so done trying to navigate iTunes for my podcasts. @DuncanAndStuff and I were both impressed with @Spotify for… https://t.co/j73oSbV850]]></document><document><![CDATA[OKC Quick-Cast: Expect mostly cloudy to cloudy skies. Warmer. Highs 40 to 45.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our first Black History Month Trivia Contest at our Corporate Campus by our newest ERG celebratediversitystl was a… https://t.co/yp0o91T19H]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only real Gaetz to fear is Link Gaetz - as in “The Missing Link” Gaetz. Still wear his jersey to Sharks games.… https://t.co/FxCQHlXjBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp I haven’t seen a single tweet celebrating him, but I have seen them criticizing the so called “news” for th… https://t.co/A1sRkO2sH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Round Up Country Western Night Club &amp; Restaurant - @roundupdavie in Davie, FL https://t.co/JvWZs5uOgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[And all will turn To silver glass A light on the water All Souls pass  #tattoo done at moontattoostudio @ Moon Tatt… https://t.co/Tknht2xoDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[As someone diagnosed with ADHD, I know we all have our own things. But, Yashar’s thread in so many ways describes w… https://t.co/pOlQOvu1z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t. Gotta take the Tesla into the muffler shop.   #HappyMardiGras https://t.co/b4cJP6AQYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricLPark @CNN You saying the truth is not bad,  but them believing the fact is where everything is wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you feel like quitting, I pray your given the vision to see beyond today’s circumstances and allows you to keep pushing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to officially launch the 24/7 Treatment on Demand program @DenverHealthMed with @MayorHancock, Dr. Robin Witt… https://t.co/UvqzjqYqGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kristennetten @elonmusk @RPMTESLA @28delayslater Sounds good!!! I’m in]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IL0VEthe80s @NINaylor One of the best speeches in a sports movie ever. https://t.co/tFUvhn1PZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@txhsfbchat I’m want them frustrated pissy warriors that will trample your soul! #TXHSFBCHAT We have our ways of cr… https://t.co/Z4Qe6HCyfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulBIGMOOD Only reason I can see it would be Cardinals want to keep Golden opposite Jones and find someone solid for the DL]]></document><document><![CDATA[In your recent podcast you discussed options to reduce Manning’s cap number by extending another year..the the prob… https://t.co/WfUHvBfUOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonLemire Oh please. Rudy Giuliani was tougher on people who littered or broke windows when he was mayor of New Yo… https://t.co/Ey8nPyGb32]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandallRimJob @NoahVavra These are faxs. I bet they don’t even mark every one they see 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump They're reply to you would be, "We just want to see President Orangeman".]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Cucumber-infused Pilsner by @RockCutBrewing at @rockcutbrewing — https://t.co/minVRGT2Gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't watch award shows unless it's Christian based like the @GMADoveAwards or the @klovefanawards]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make it your goal to be so kind, so generous, so humble, so honest, so pure, so loving, so biblical, so much like C… https://t.co/umAILq0jqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t do this if the story was true he’d have our support. But his story don’t add up he took time to promote his m… https://t.co/Lh8EpaiPsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I tired? A little. But I'm tired in a good way. I know I did something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s focused man. #ClassicalTraining @Third_Street @ Third Street Music School Settlement https://t.co/MMA7wBZMRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Race Day! Ready to get this season started. #dadrabs #missrabs #rabsx4 #spartanrace #spartan #spartangreekpeak @ Gr… https://t.co/w6rOfXRKsN]]></document></documents></author>