<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Just watched every tape I could find of Antoine Wesley. Supremely talented, has a unique twitch that is rare for hi… https://t.co/gNBZnbsRtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfaooooo no it’s the fucking medieval times. Oh yea the King is a little fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday, day C. Check your FlexTime to see what you have for 🦅 Block.  Have a great day 🔵🦅!!! https://t.co/7eeAQy4Iyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luka7doncic This is everything. Name a better duo than @luka7doncic &amp; @swish41.   I'll wait.....   yeah.....   that's what I thought.]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL SERÁ EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Y… https://t.co/tSJLyUEX4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown when he finds out he’s getting traded to the Buffalo Bills. https://t.co/CAvB4Y0T7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[the best game you can name...  #ourtownourgame #gofrontsgo #ygk #HappyFriday @LeonsCentre @KingstonFronts https://t.co/cfp77ytHlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoseDC11 @JussieSmollett Bad karma now feel the burn, https://t.co/Q1yrTAVc69]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today marks 10 years of the Lion’s Eye. Happy Birthday (‘90’s theme party) to my favorite bar. Thanks for being a p… https://t.co/LFIVQ1TFaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a #scifi #indieauthor, lemme just take a minute to say:  1. I DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS ARTICLE.  2. INCLUDING LGBT… https://t.co/Lnp9kBwW4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodKingSolomon @FratShannon69 @mitchellvii There are plenty of reports that get ignored. Have a nice day. Keep up… https://t.co/Z9QuzZ7M6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan The caravans of asylum seekers that present at ports of entry? I’m ready for the videos of these hordes… https://t.co/JcywtEPhkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joecoscarelli @KidsGetMoney @melenar Hey it’s my payday @KidsGetMoney please send payment ASAP https://t.co/VNWPB7w4Qo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safeagain1 @realDonaldTrump @DevinNunes @FoxNews @GOP How much will Americans take?  The day after @Comey was fire… https://t.co/vozJVv9vxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joeingram1 @MattStaplesPKR Throwing it out for the people who don’t watch. Also, the multi layered sarcasm of your… https://t.co/mm2dOd2QQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeThornWrites I think current-day Roth tackling even that would bring something quite different (and more inquis… https://t.co/M877AzTCaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I imagine Orrin Hatch is going to be pretty disappointed when he loses this honour.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frankie Lee’s LP Cover. Not Blonde on Blonde...more like Hair and Nose. @ Upper West Side https://t.co/ueig0hqFf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful!!! @nomadgoods #adventureon #Titanium @ Douglasville, Georgia https://t.co/4w8ugaU0Kh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMasterGMarek08 @RBatSWNN @laceygilleran Haha but it’s NOT my name! Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought some chips and salsa at the store, and the woman ringing me up had the audacity to say, “this better not be your dinner tonight.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah. Ain't that some shit huh? Again, fuck it. I've been to the depths of hell and I "fought the fuck back" to mak… https://t.co/OdkebX0gCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @LintheLibrary and our guest author Matt Laney for an awesome Family Literacy Night.  #LovetoLeadHere https://t.co/Cv5zA24T6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read Chapter 7 of my book and my pieces in Wash U and Wake or about a dozen blog posts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Baddboyhunt812 BandCamp is gay; Kyle from Incantation still has a mustache]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve gotta stop meeting this way jr0ck85 #dumbopremiere #dumbo @ Ray Dolby Ballroom https://t.co/FbkvxLZXbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great appointment by @GovParsonMO. I look forward to sponsoring Mr. Orscheln for confirmation by the Missou… https://t.co/SN0xftcHMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[God’s purpose and plan include both judgment and salvation. -Thomas R. Schreiner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vartian Honestly impressed you’ve managed to not play one yet. As a longtime fan of the series I think it’ll be re… https://t.co/pDl5oHKATd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new book I'm listening to now. The follow up book to "Extreme Ownership". Both books are very help for for leader… https://t.co/qdOUBbQ7Qi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DSmithShow Any time you can get Andy on the radio, I, for one, welcome it. No offense to hacksaw, but I consider t… https://t.co/K6E4eOVOHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rudyfive Noooooo! I mean,... We’ve never met, but I bet the photos would have been fab. 👀 📷]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parking Ban in effect beginning at 10pm Sunday until further notice. No parking on main roads and no parking on the… https://t.co/zoGSjhrDB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevDrBarber I agree and I probably agree with most of what she means but communicating that one supports the two s… https://t.co/4ffN26QYc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bfrye26 Totally agreed! There’s plenty of things to love about the movie. But also a few things I found a bit underwhelming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook is becoming wack to me, everyone trying to be a comedian and posting the same memes 🗑]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have nothing to give...you can always give the LOVE of Jesus Christ. Please keep brother Richard and all t… https://t.co/8A7BMNJCqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[SWIPE ⬅️⬅️⬅️ and LOOK WHAT CAME IN TONIGHT!  S/O to @Beastcoastunltd and kyle_wehrhahn for getting these done for u… https://t.co/4b4rkVbUJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zoeealexaa Wtf I'm in the minority. I must be clearly missing something about being the little spoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlesadler His name should have precluded anybody from voting for him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyKadiK @dmewing47 Trump steaks? A scholarship to Trump University? Trump wine? I don’t know, but I’m guessing… https://t.co/GIL1MT8Vj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handitvnetwork Love The Greatest American Hero to Get The Green Hornet 60's &amp; Get Gunsmoke on Line to &amp; On  Demand ON Line to.  😎😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear, Twitter just unfollows my followers all willy nilly. Sorry for the abrasive language. I’ll try to tone it… https://t.co/aglGFJv1AJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spy with mylittle blue eye,the always spectacular,@jimmisimpson 🥰I would watch him watch paint dry!  For Realesie… https://t.co/7bzaBnDhqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeandersonsr @dawnb4618 It's outlandish allegations, just liberals wet dreams.. .....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sugamomma8a @HotSauceBottIe @thatcoolgirlsab Heat your lash curler with a blow dryer and use ANY waterproof mascara. Works wonders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, let me get this straight. The Dems invite a man to testify before Congress that is going to prison for lying to… https://t.co/TtenaXRe06]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyGilman @ladygaga Yet another example of why we love you @BillyGilman you are a shining beacon to the lgbt com… https://t.co/diYkjyXWvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronatheking @Willewillz31 @chicagobulls @ctsbulls @CinkciarzPL They actually aren’t run by incompetent morons though. Big difference]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markuscanada And “more accepting” doesn’t always mean “fewer hate crimes”. DC has the second highest LGBT populati… https://t.co/JExtmtFuhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like I’m running late for a staff meeting...yet, here I am scrolling and now posting on Twitter. #ThursdayWins… https://t.co/zPdJK64A2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinMeade @HLNTV U.S. airports this weekend will be deluged with 250K+ Canadians on the traditional annual March Break ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Polar Projection by @HeistBrewery at @heistbrewery — https://t.co/iP7N5DkFPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re soooo close to reaching our team goal for the ‘19 Tally #GreatStrides walk! Please help us hit our goal or pa… https://t.co/hnS01tehn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HailieDeegan just watched you on TV, you are awesome. Continue your great work in the sport and stay grounded, you are a great driver.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tridroidrecords So, looks like it's still on and will be the last event at the venue before it's changed into a retro arcade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[79 turned Chuck Norris today.  HBD to the legend.   🥳 https://t.co/u0eRVaI1U2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queensuPPS @GeneralFusion @IrelandEmbGB @KingsCollegeLon https://t.co/vyZ7WpfEVK @CERN_JOBS @ZurichInsUK https://t.co/SOZIghQkmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATLUTD Mmm. The shadows in the first picture are a bit much, dontcha think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachCAnderson Belated HB @CoachCAnderson ! Your spirit and #GreatAttitude brings so much joy to @LongwoodLancers… https://t.co/4eZNouEZtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how dark and cloudy and rainy your day may look, there will be a #rainbow after the storm. Same goes for… https://t.co/WM51fOrjIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaydenSummerall @Dumbo @HaydenSummerall. I wish u where @Dumbo i would ride u 27/7 where ever u wanted fly me to the moon baby!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JG_Nascar @NASCARPortOPoty @smokecarbon13 @ATH_1_5 @2CodeRed4U @The_SuperSquad_ @michael_mrucz @Malec586… https://t.co/cxEq8okSJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristieGolden Since we cried over @MarsRovers, wanted your thoughts on this. Everything... you, me, all we love,… https://t.co/MXsEgRZx27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here y'all go thinking people from the hood don't know how to read again]]></document><document><![CDATA[The episode I Happened to catch had @tonygoldmark talking about Silicon Valley while spraying down a walkway at Dis… https://t.co/7CPx97SXGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sabreena Wadhwani crossed 13.1M. Time 01:59:17, pace 09:35 min/mile, est. finish 11:04 am https://t.co/KgJln7c5kZ #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeardedOne23 @smockerson @JoseChavezJr @JimmyBuckets19 I figured it out. Big name NBA players are finally going to… https://t.co/ofzmIje2sS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnewing @Benaskren You think it’s over quick? Robbie is a great matchup for Ben]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isaacs snores rival that of avalanches and tsunami crashes. If you know you know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine allowing @GordonRamsay @24HoursFOX to come into your restaurant, help give the place life again, train your… https://t.co/ZCYpyGaxZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradfatherSpeak @TribTomWharton Yup some people take it too serious when you have an opinion 😂👊🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adaptation, for years human nature has adapted and reshaped for the given circumstances; for you will adapt and overcome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOSS. Overhangs right followed by the uppercut on the way down. This kid is true blue. @blemieux22 will be a fan fa… https://t.co/yjQBp0IPlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[my 18 year old ass still bopping to it knowing exactly what she meant now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisrha Por supuesto que tiene derecho, como toda persona, a decir lo que quiera y sienta. Ahora, que lo que diga… https://t.co/OPo1L1RXMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s more embarrassing is that this screenshot wasn’t even worth taking because this was such an easy message to… https://t.co/OzyBsg7fUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great shirt! #PrincessHalf #Princess10K #CoronadoSprings #CSR #BOGPLizards #BOGP #CignaRunTogether… https://t.co/TpUqEvPGyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Benifits of CBD OIL: ANXIETY- EPILEPSY- NAUSEA- SLEEP AID-  . If you deal with any listed above maybe if your time… https://t.co/y8KVac6zfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstiloDF @vegabiestro @CDLC_oficial @EdySmol Mucho éxito a Joanna en todos sus proyectos. #CuidateDeLaCamara]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In George Washington’s 1796 farewell address. . .the first president explicitly warned against foreign policy favo… https://t.co/ywKeYN8XhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill good she should pay for her stupidity and the people who elected her should also]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump More people than ever on history are 3 months behind on their car payments. Nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[They might want to know that some of us are following them so that we find out right away when they brag about hara… https://t.co/oDA45oT1Ho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vaughanessa @AngeloM15612751 @reec__ Tired of all these SUS and BOT fakes 😏😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiantInsider @jerrypacelli @tomlapp66 @Giants @TheMediaCaptain Then 1966 1-12-1 so long short I remember this hell… https://t.co/n0GkHh4yQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to be a good day watching @Nassau_MLAX and @AACCLax today on “The Island” #RDOP #JUCOtrail https://t.co/ECbNZ4oL92]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalSpice It’s Sunday why would u feel guilty for doing nothing? Getting soft in your old age Sal 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist It isn't funny. It takes a real man to say he loves a chicken. https://t.co/nXuVxPdE5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[#saturdayvibes #Repost @madonna ・・・ @ Hudson Yards New York https://t.co/4pG9pdG5Gy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My eyes are open on iPhone 11 , Apple Watch ⌚️ and AirPods 2 with AirPower . Let’s make it happen @Apple]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alphastream @sixhitpoints @ToHitAC0 Yup. The value of classic, iconic, shared adventures has definitely been demon… https://t.co/DiMyZmKRJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randycharb @Graham_Couch Another argument would be Ward is not Ben close to being an NBA talent on any level. Lol.  It’s not happening]]></document><document><![CDATA[the sweetest valentine 💓 you are such a blessing &amp; I’m so thankful to be spending this year with you 🥰 https://t.co/N6z3Xg1E3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Guidelines this year: 1. Do the right thing.  2. See Number 1.  Seems pretty simple...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeodroseFikre @SteveScalise @SteveKingIA How about this F the naacp is that not racist too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[While walking through the #ProspectPark I found this great shot • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • • •… https://t.co/VfOeeOKR5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_strix You occasionally remind me of a younger morena baccarin.  Like you could play Annara at companion academy]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing time and experience I had at Duke University this week! 🔷 #DukeGang https://t.co/6ReJ7iHL6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please please please help us get this dirty asshole to resign. #StopALLformsOfRacism]]></document></documents></author>