<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m in a mood today and listening to the tax refund talk from those with children really grates on my nerves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s the day to come watch us hop and play! The Bunny Castle is @boyntonhealth today.  2:30 to 3:30 PAWS. 3:45 H… https://t.co/1Xd2zfqTlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Without reflection, we go blindly on our way, creating more unintended consequences, and failing to achieve anythi… https://t.co/9r4MHc2pim]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our @CA_RoyalCats team is the path to compete at World's. Follow them to track their journey. @CA_CharlotteNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great shot of #DavyJones &amp; @TorkTweet of the @TheMonkees . #RIP https://t.co/QrcOKvkanK]]></document><document><![CDATA[ROOM FOR EVERYONE! Wake Forest BASEMENT home on quiet culdesac with fenced yard - 6 Bedrooms/5 Full Baths… https://t.co/bPiQT54smx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbaschWTOP @WTOP @GovLarryHogan If only reporters had that option on snow days!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickmitch89 Right! And we don’t want to be on those watch lists. Tsk tsk tsk panda butts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing my @MamaEarthOrg basket... are deliveries late today? #DinnerPlanFail]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andando uma média de 6,5km por dia, será que chego no Brasil mais magra??? God blessed America]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenDialTV @HawleyMO @41actionnews Great pic of this spineless Trump puppet .]]></document><document><![CDATA[So true! The only thing they’re doing is try to trip him up, accuse him of everything he’s already been sentenced f… https://t.co/XN0YubwZI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's odd. Cuz I've been telling trumpy to fuck off for months. Since signing up, as a matter of fact. And never g… https://t.co/XnEZsrI1Ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[how to train your dragon 3 should be renamed “how to train yourself to not cry in a theatre full of 200 kids”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayGredder @NewJerseyDOE You rock, Mr. Gredder! Anyone who works with you is so lucky!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's Secretary of Labor Alexander Acosta helped billionaire Jeffrey Epstein go free after sexually abusing dozen… https://t.co/aH2K6XAJ8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy the day whatever you do #ralphlauren #Bodycon #BandageDress #bcbgmaxazria #Diva #Glamazon #Fantastic #Miami… https://t.co/M71qw8bGc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an awesome PD session with K-3 teachers! I can’t wait to see all of your awesome Clips projects! #redbud132… https://t.co/qWdrmr5J0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Folks really use Facebook for therapy. I’m on Facebook break until I need to promote the next event. Surviving.....… https://t.co/1gjRRiE3KL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule The pathological, lying,egotistical, narcissistic, racist,embesserler,money grabbing/0wing,profess… https://t.co/RJe6SegGsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Declared ? Nope. Accepted ? Nah. Earned ? Absolutely. 👊  #RAW #EliminationChamber #WomensTagTitles #ThankYouBayley… https://t.co/KkzEIzNKSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pH3point0 @cathylovestrump @ImmoralGOP @RayBurkhart1 @AOC Talk about bad karma!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier in the week, our team made posters for the @sonevada basketball tournament that was held today! 👀 Seeing ou… https://t.co/xlddgaCqvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I  just  dont get  this  immingen  I just  wish  to  let  go   of m y  humben   it  hard  on  me  and  more for  hi… https://t.co/EnyVIZJwys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrapped my last interview of the weekend with @DigitalTrends having a great convo w/ fellow engineer Pavi Dinamani.… https://t.co/HJxhBqQZkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few examples are the use of palestinian women and children as human shields on violent demonstrations by Hamas at… https://t.co/kZvW6xKUan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maximusupinNYc @NYC @NASAGoddardPix @NASAMoon @EmpireStateBldg @nycgo @JimCantore @JenCarfagno @weatherchannel Gre… https://t.co/HZeb37BpM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This red eye can go one of two ways and I really hope it’s the one that is me sleeping the whole time✈️ Buffalo bound!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏫 + 💦 = busy day for our staff as they crashed the #CareerTrek party at @aurorak12. Love being able to introduce st… https://t.co/ngHpFnVHvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can stare all you want, but one of you is still ending up on my plate. https://t.co/iCRtRLhu0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Us girls be out here settling for brad from alpha beta omega that can’t even give us a Happy Valentine’s Day text,… https://t.co/bmyEp7wLfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattcase31 @realDonaldTrump No Matt! Trump Is innocent!! The Only One who concluded with Russia was Obama and Hillary! Spygate!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to spending the day with a legend as we announce an awesome partnership. #choosefun #CarnivalMardiGras]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryB505 @IndivisibleNet Have you ever noticed that his wife is as tall as him?  Is she really 6’3” tall? https://t.co/Of8KjyE4sI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RT_com We should but we have already killed ourselves and the planet... to stupid to realize it 🤯💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GovCloud @Amazon @JeffBezos @AWS @awscloud @Washingtonpost @USSenate @USHouse @POTUS @TheJusticeDept @FBI @CIA… https://t.co/ck4FDavjzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I watched Game of Thrones, I gave scenes new songs. Please enjoy https://t.co/hFvnvxlQ9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[If supporting a president who is interested in helping Americans instead of wanting to rule us, then HELL YES I wil… https://t.co/ZtRCQzciCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My parents have done everything they possibly could to set me up for success and for that I am forever greatful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Lani Kai for a great week😘 @ Lani Kai Island Resort https://t.co/auUCD0zkZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sean Hicke Group performs at Rosie’s tonight! The guys in the band are regulars at our Monday night jazz jam, so co… https://t.co/gGjRydecIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiderPride1234 Yes Rick God has. God extended his grace/mercy then and...NOW WE have JESUS who gave us a system re… https://t.co/uJXFOZCn7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG I totally saw this taped to a light post downtown a few month agao and... #mirth #chuckle #smirk #farcical https://t.co/xOiJiaRSi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuneMyThang13 @ahardy316 @DelphiPriestess @PumpkinKingxxx @singingdoves13 @KuwaTakaSurfing @Memphis_Dre… https://t.co/6I8pym9S69]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddiemarshh @ONECampaign @ONECampus @ONE_UA @ONEinAmerica Proud of you dear Maddie 💞💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Alec is a hot mess!!  Call the wahmbulance for him. I feel threatened by the mere thought that I mi… https://t.co/3GR4KcNyLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow in the desert. #AZ #Tucson #saguaro @ Arizona-Sonora Desert Museum https://t.co/KgWkL4mqCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lazzzyeye the fact that this was 2012 in the oxford valley mall Hot Topic]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve followed both  @yashar and @Advil for a long time and this is exactly why 😂 https://t.co/SfXd1CXfQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Los Angeles Air Force Base https://t.co/5BNlvwqCY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeborahCuella11 @MaddowBlog Planned parenthood only cares about abortions. If you are not interested in that, you… https://t.co/qqRhh5z1kJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOY #CohenCongressionalTestimony @MichaelCohen212 has SURE GOT that oh poor pitiful me face down!!!! 🤮🤮🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@orrdavidx All my derivative rules worked out and I TRIPLE CHECKED and it still didn’t work on the graph I was devastated]]></document><document><![CDATA[Romantic facts of musketeers foundationed deep, somehow / Ah, but I was so much older then, I'm younger than that n… https://t.co/YPWB15dAzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ettyd @MamieLouJ @greta I paid off my med school loans at age 45, Thank you...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanMajdali My neither. Im off but I'm in sales and have to get caught up on outbound calls so I'm logging in from home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been seeing posts from all these females talking about how @ArianaGrande  and her new song Break Up With Your… https://t.co/gxoNhQvZ0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Texas #TexasSunrise I can live with the cold mornings when there is beautiful sunrise like this… https://t.co/scZgBWchUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Orangetheory Fitness - Ironworks in Indianapolis, IN https://t.co/9K9RINA70b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been nominated by     @MCA_Paris and @MarilynSewell4 to post covers of 7 books that I love: no explanations… https://t.co/cTPbX7CJR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[District #287 DS Team Build  @rebekahbunn5 @DHRM_mjackson @Edmond0485  #PMDPeopleFirst #D287BiggerStrongerFaster… https://t.co/xGca4tfpYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just received word that Daddy Maron will be at sxsw https://t.co/horqboFreS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost 2) And to make sure everybody believes me, since I know I am lying, I will keep the rope around my… https://t.co/lQe1dWfd0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[For #ancestry.com at #rootstech #Salt Lake City #SLC #genealogy @ Downtown Salt Lake City https://t.co/0WoTNpzJrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@satanisfemale @JeffersonCtyPDC @sissypuckett3 @sushdiaz @lesleyabravanel @MichaelCohen212 @POTUS @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/DL5bVWLqjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my work family ❤️ #55strong #teacherfriends #thebest #wv #WVTeacherStrike2019 #moncounty https://t.co/PLfdZhDqzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kudos @marty_walsh @CityOfBoston @BostonBTD for proposing more dedicated bus lanes. Their expansion,combined w/ oth… https://t.co/2ZqFecWERC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom told me I’m losing it and I need to step it up a notch and I felt that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gop @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @SenatorRomney @BenSasse @lisamurkowski @LamarAlexander @SenatorCollins… https://t.co/gy3ZfaD8TV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! Oo nga pala! Sobrang smooth ng running attack ni Kim G nung high school halos pareho nung kay Maddie!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a blast shooting for 13 hours today in the same sound stage that 20,000 Leagues Under The Sea (1954) was shot… https://t.co/cFYndKod2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[i stg nobody ever wanna play board games or cards with me 😤 when i have kids we gonna have a family game night EVER… https://t.co/kP2Kcrrq4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle Well what an ignorant inbesil, we are not a Democrasy, or worst he knows dam well but his talking to… https://t.co/XL7keki1u3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fort Cheer applicants, we will NOT hold live tryouts today! Instead, email me a video of you practicing for 1 bonus… https://t.co/oJcxXfdPNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hands down, best ice cream, ever.  Thank you @TubbyRobot! #IScream4IceCream #BadAsianOmbre]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the introverts like Keats: “solitude opens the channels to truth and beauty”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#21Savage released from immigration detention, immediately flies to metro Atlanta on private plane with his mother… https://t.co/ZGLz6jpZRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say, “you’re a little much for me, you’re a liability, you’re a little much for me”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I supported my local animal shelter just by walking my dog 0.46 miles using #WalkforADog app. Get the app at https://t.co/Fw8mS2N1mA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nuevo apagón masivo afecta a Venezuela  https://t.co/VZTkGN7a5e vía @elnacionalweb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatABaby @MrFerndogg me tooo! i been telling fernie but he scared and dont speak spanish 😬😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimberlyLCampb3 People lost their minds all over social media last night. Erin Napier shut down comments on her In… https://t.co/Q5wz2Jb8hg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelleywimberley @mchastain81 The power of voodoo! Who Do? You do Do what? Remind me of the babe...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_wheeler18 hey Julie.😊How are you doing today? I miss you girl.I miss seeing you.are you being silly lol,😂I am al… https://t.co/MhOFNhtPyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you see me partying one night and calling in the next day, you better shut your whore mouth up susan, mind ya bidness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJWesttt @rustyrockets How was a convo done when relationships were done?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 5 a.m. workout done at JC Health and Fitness ✔ My baseball team there at 6 a.m.✔ Let's get it! #bobcats432… https://t.co/PGoGKQNZ17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PPact #Dems better prepare because this will be the lie  GOP uses to keep control of the Senate and pack the courts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Spoken by the face of racism! I’m sure he hates me, and he hasn’t even met me! Just stop with the hypocrisy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a strong person but every now and then I need someone to hold my hand and tell me everything will be alright.… https://t.co/YIEex03gGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATTENTION, beautiful babies!!! Make way for the GRAND RETURN of TRUDY CARMICHAEL'S CHARACTER CABARET this Wednesday… https://t.co/4z8NvY5YuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing all these tiny homes makes me just wanna live in one of them at a campground]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC I miss this Lindsey who made sense. https://t.co/H0dtvef5IK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who said #embroidery is for #abuelas? We're bringing it back! It's #nationalembroiderymonth! Here's our fave abuela… https://t.co/jnRUMSKYBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interviewer: Tell me a bit about yourself Me: Ok so, basically I'm baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since @RamboDonkeyKong is a real life dog trainer per his @WalkingDead_AMC Instagram takeover... is Dog actually un… https://t.co/MVgUXFuEvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Constitutional Amendment Ends Abortion in Pro-Life States - Christian News Headlines https://t.co/LSL7mtLqXf via @christianhlines]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw this BCBG gown today at Macy's ... I feel in love with it!!!! Wish I had a Fancy Party to go too ... Bet you… https://t.co/LVPYinfOOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[✌🏼 (@ Aeropuerto Internacional de Monterrey - @aeropuertodemty in Apodaca, NL) https://t.co/DoZkbXRVf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kevin has been my favorite since day fucking one and that will never change]]></document></documents></author>