<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The week of @mattnathanson is here!!! 5 days til I get to see him for the 8th time! To celebrate the week, I’ll be… https://t.co/SLqjxywpg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like @BlacKkKlansman is the most underrated #nominee for #bestpicture at the #Oscars tonight. Such a good fi… https://t.co/QjolXPsRBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonicaLeeAlvar1 @GobAbiertoBOL @realDonaldTrump I don’t hate anyone. And, I am fully aware that corruption is ramp… https://t.co/hjSh8SzIfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone is happy I can't fill up the bird feeder without spilling everywhere. #BulkingUp #Spring @ Walnut Creek, Ca… https://t.co/B5UbBTyaon]]></document><document><![CDATA[people say they love my finsta because it’s so funny but deep down a bitch is rlly going thru it lmfao like help]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love hanging with friends in the #greatsmokymountains #happybirthdayjen #weloveyou @ Downtown Gatlinburg https://t.co/iIhW7NFe5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChickfilA y’all messed up my work lunch order pretty bad and no one at Southcenter WA is answering the phone. Can… https://t.co/r1K94VkK2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all thought Jordyn was down and destitute without Kylie and sis went and called her Auntie Jada and got a seat at… https://t.co/zbnaiL7Qqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Too bad but she chose to leave.  We don’t need traitors coming into our country- already have enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree 💯@ananavarro this is despicable! I hope the next judge and sentencing is more appropriate for said crimes and… https://t.co/Fim8xzRflt]]></document><document><![CDATA[DOWN GOES THE 200 FREE RELAY RECORD! Killin’ the game! #wdtsiatb #createthehype  #h2p #h2op https://t.co/ByxN575fof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wes_chu I find old dongles in the weirdest if places. I think they have sinygle orgies at night and make more litt… https://t.co/fvZtqk2VFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it too soon to call the ticket office to inquire how season ticket holders purchasing of seats will be handled?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel Why would he get any applause. Trump is not only destroying US but he’s also destroying the world.… https://t.co/ZzOPHIpmfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@besitos_liz Its the worst girl and after pregnancy if you breast feed oh jeez]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at West Orange - Pleasantdale Section in West Orange, NJ https://t.co/Cj0x0Y0rgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be part of such an amazing institution that sees men and #women as equals and works hard every day to clos… https://t.co/WxMa9Wu36P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerome_barry_tx @Igneous_ntruson @adamhousley @60Minutes They know more and that is they will just stay quiet unti… https://t.co/yS728bgefZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimberlyAmato Oh WOW this is taking me back. I started this game two months ago and barely remember these opening scenes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made a super yummy dinner today’s. This recipe is based off of one from @marleyspoon from over a year ago. I lost t… https://t.co/g4ptRtVc1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited @seandaustin will be my guest!! Y’all better set your calendars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuitYourselfToo @MrFudgey @blue_check_mark @FantomaSpirit @RealMissSteam @ProSouth_ @TheCognificent1 @Andywarski I… https://t.co/2570fUYnGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alabama legislators propose bill to require drug testing for food stamp recipients. Do you agree?… https://t.co/C1TtMgmsMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all see me move in a cute Mexican boy that speaks no English mind ya business]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beachy. #california #travel #adventure #beach #waves #photography #nature #californialife #californialove… https://t.co/AkxMFMCqg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first student loan payment is due about 2 weeks before the wedding. Lord have mercy on my bank account 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine how much it would be for the rest of us? We don't get the cheaper prices Members of Congress do- your insur… https://t.co/cIqE0szcyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to say "Yes to Your DREAM WEDDING DRESS"! 💍 at @AlesiaCChicago full service wedding salon, where your imaginat… https://t.co/TXJnhU36ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[California bloom 🌸🌸🌸  . #spring #flowers #bloom #nature #beauty #trails #outdoor #love #hiking #California #ilovela… https://t.co/8aWuRq2AQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doncatt @armandodkos Has he ever won a primary in his 2(?) previous runs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radiopendy @TrueFactsStated Ugh....why Jimmy Johns....thanks for letting me know!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keith_pearson There's on ice stuff in there. Also, the point isn't hockey vs basketball. By your argument, no one… https://t.co/WZdGUMayCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Live like there’s no tomorrow Live as if all your Love  can heal all your sorrow”  The Part That Sets us Free  by… https://t.co/2zzP0fWr8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definition of hard work and dedication!!! Super proud to be a part of this team!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #ChineseNewYear celebrations coming to an end means my @TheVIPKIDLife schedule is back to being pretty much ful… https://t.co/haPdL14GeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sun_shine712 @AngeleStar11 SHE is an EFFIN MUSLIM and was  BORN in in a FOREIGN  COUNTRY .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do believe him I think he's trying to redeem himself I hope truthfully he gives up everything The Good The Bad an… https://t.co/RmOZ1owQ01]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillPower715 Don't stare directly at it or your eyeballs will melt. Ha! #iamup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell , no they don’t want to. Traitors believe in their wannabe Dictator!! SAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @MicheleAtTriad to post covers of 7 books I love. No explanations or reviews, just t… https://t.co/C5PvfF2ZYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[After watching how long he rehearsed this, im so happy it looked this good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abstract City by Jennifer Godshalk, Oil on Canvas https://t.co/ShgxKrEpxo #abstract #cityscape #nycgallery]]></document><document><![CDATA[As an autoimmune disease sufferer with degrees from two very expensive schools, these last two weeks of @patriotact… https://t.co/52KSk4pmnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Dr Palombi! You’re doing great work, so glad you’ll get to expand and explore more opportunities! T… https://t.co/o5w86BjfKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[*UPDATE* I haven’t started drinking yet ... just been in YouTube the entire time]]></document><document><![CDATA[bruh crying in ur car on the way home blasting billie is a different kind of hurt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bloody_Chamber @NPR @NPRinvisibilia If you take the idea that physical and mental pain can't exist equally.... int… https://t.co/Mem2dt3rAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the words of Johnny Mac’ “You can’t be serious” @SenSchumer You have had no plan for decades. @POTUS has opened… https://t.co/AhCPm92f0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few of the strong, independent, hilarious and beautiful women I get the pleasure to work with everyday.… https://t.co/OzWIavKQJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiding in plain sight 🙈.  . . . . . Wearing @blackstoneus  📷: @onlyBrentWitt #actress #model #hustle #workhard… https://t.co/1C4nQXqcoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning gifts ❤️ @ Lake Morton Historic District, Lakeland https://t.co/pSdnOvVSbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sheriff warns "lock your doors, load your guns’" as he suspends services - https://t.co/RfEGx6IGvB https://t.co/npzwk1V2Yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@titiismael72 Good luck in that class and im rooting for you to pass! I had to take animal anatomy and it was the w… https://t.co/EWrBQ1LKRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final beer in my st Patrick’s day mini tour! - Drinking a Guinness Draught by @GuinnessIreland at @oldchicago1976  — https://t.co/MlBPEGvIwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyroneTracy @KennyTracy3 @beasley0814 @MrsLavernaTracy and many more not on Twitter 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BesottedGeekPod @BrookReadingPod @FOP_Network @StephenKing Lots! https://t.co/12c8OiOzK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Justin start our liver cleanse tomorrow and im def not excited lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[No words. Don’t really think curly fry and loaf should go together, but hey, to each his own #curlyfryloaf @ NRG St… https://t.co/mGKSAaWgbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There’s nothing restricting kids from praying in schools,” Desetti notes.  #ksleg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Education4Libs @Figgitaboutit Oprah is a fraud who thinks she has "street cred" but she doesn't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For as long as I can remember, and I still do this, I refuse to eat food not in stages.   Like if I have a side sal… https://t.co/uEPMuVoKZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimMissWorld Tipping really helps them! Not only do they have the high cost of gas, they have the car insurance… https://t.co/SyH9UelAlv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me too!  It’s totally ridiculous to refer to his wealth when he’s declared bankruptcy soooo many times!  So Stop It… https://t.co/X9MzPwkgzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning all.  It is so nice to be able to sleep 😴 ALL NIGHT 🌙🌙. I haven’t slept all night since the 25th.  Bee… https://t.co/4NyfMKjHFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bhuang2012 The outage map has just a few so far, mostly contained to one or two homes from tripped breakers. But w… https://t.co/v2QAo1LRlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @EGPrinciPaul to post covers of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews. I’ll challeng… https://t.co/uJsmv0GXUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omigodtrina @hjwcarroll @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump My bad.  Actually thought this was a person.  Should have known… https://t.co/1F7jThnQTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@throwupthehornz Omg I didn't know this was you. Ha! You crack me up. Hope all is well with you. Is it snowing there?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetsyHindman Thank you. I tried using Todoist but the recurring tasks didn't display quite the way I needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiggaSaaac You’re wack wtf!!!! No I couldn’t turn him he’s still a good child]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyJShaffer @instagram Yeah definitely seems super not antisemitic at all!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave_Stein @HashtagGriswold @benshapiro It’s more of a disgrace to actively work to delegitimize a nation because… https://t.co/KWAXsVsAEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t heard my father in law sing in a while.. when he joined in on the manianitas I balled 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[The plaque says it all.   “Success is a peace of mind which is a direct result of self-satisfaction in knowing you… https://t.co/2miZFAClbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The line for the #Hamilton Go bus after the @arkellsmusic show. #ArkellsRallyCry https://t.co/0ctDLbbTsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DakotaMoyer02 @cam_wallaceee It’s a Cabot Phillips Sonicare DiamondClean]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivitoon Hi Viviana, we have vast experience in Native iOS and Android app development and would be happy to assis… https://t.co/231iPonyPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all know the little scenarios you have in your head that you think will never happen, well, mine just happened and i don’t know how to act]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarvemupJames Ugh...my son rides (a Harley fanatic).  Scares the shit out of me with all the distracted drivers.… https://t.co/3fhk7SanS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdDrantch @WKBW @ABC @CNN The man from Buffalo should have been answering those questions right away why do you have to wait]]></document><document><![CDATA[@candwalsh Absolutamente tudo nela é perfeito, a voz parece música, e o sorriso cara... acho que eu morri e ressuscitei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OPDOfcZipay I swear if you can’t figure that out on your own you shouldn’t be driving....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YvonneN_KVUE Thank YOU for being the real MVP and letting me borrow it!! ☺️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @MalcolmNance @MaddowBlog Wait...safeguarding the right to vote is socialism? Or is the @GOP afraid if every… https://t.co/yDfmoOvePA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WindsorMann @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews I’d forgotten that!  What a snake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally fulfilling a dream. Seeing @bocelliandrea in person has been a dream of mine for years. @ Amway Center https://t.co/6JVwTa7kyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gratitude Party ! What 3 things are you most grateful for right now ? I am most grateful for the warmth of my firep… https://t.co/GimJJPhfbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is the day my upstate family has been waiting for !! Final day to register to Slinky Academy @ ‘Da Cuse !!! https://t.co/UxpIgovycp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kittenladykc OHHHH. Okay. I get it. Never mind lol. I thought he was like “super casual about it no homo whatever”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question: why is Tide detergent locked away at Walmart... like top shelf alcohol or razor blades?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grim but super interesting research using #Chromatography #GCMS   #AnalyticalChemistry #MassSpectrometry   https://t.co/P5oanGkQxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain I LOVE YOU but PLEASE SHUT UP, I can’t hear what @sunny is trying to say over your RUDELY INTERJECTED… https://t.co/vyuQR0urZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @EITnd (get_repost) ・・・ It's sunday, ya know! 😉 This is freaking amazing, isn't it? Love this so much!… https://t.co/GfWhSdSCA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[DJing now on @CHIRPRadio until 8pm Tune in at https://t.co/kYeMlTrQvu or via our iPhone and Android apps! #chicago #music #communityradio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonKirkSBN Barbra Streisand and I think I could at least hold my own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stand4flag @MonteDCantu @America1Make @CharismaMolotov @Always04177875 @EcgoLC @Kegan545 @OdysseusOfWinds… https://t.co/w9179CPLqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did some major adulting today. Got the oil and headlight changed in the car today...anytime I take care of car th… https://t.co/QHVsFutpKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m really obsessed with the possibility of aimee getting to meet a british lulu and living vicariously through her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though it is still the start of the year.. I made a goal to be in my bible everyday. I would miss a day and wo… https://t.co/DLU1DhBlrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Covered in black dog. #myhappyplace #blackdogsrock #dogsofinstagram #adopt510izzy #510sam #510jimmy @ Berkeley, Cal… https://t.co/hmxnftSwjT]]></document></documents></author>