<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Charles Spurgeon evening devotional teaching  Evening by Evening Devotional for February 22 https://t.co/Jvtf3c5atF #arcamax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made my first chicken crust pizza,  its pretty good too..... @ Plantation, Florida https://t.co/oWNDYSqcLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Asian Fly by Scubba, from #SoundHound https://t.co/z5KAMZdi1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[How we learn to count to 100. To no one's surprise...the only thing we had 100 of was Goldfish. @ Salem, Oregon https://t.co/3HG7ydwLL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @diegoantoniosp ‼️ hope you have a good day bro, party hard!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopCrave @Disney Disney is coming with heat for Gay Christmas! https://t.co/8Q0kgVGdBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the best thing that Josh has written. And yes that’s saying something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our fans did an amazing job yesterday. 🔥🔥Loudest in the arena. Hope y’all can make the drive to NoVa on Tuesday nig… https://t.co/bbuxNq5lpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usyacht @USATODAY Do you believe Rupert Murdock is actually the messiah?]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are no heros in the military. But they know a few here and there. I know a few heros. Some have past and gone… https://t.co/BbxKqGdpqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peggyperez @9975Ts @RepAOC @SpeakerPelosi @BreitbartNews Talk about a cat fight better have some water handy.😂😂😂😢… https://t.co/fBwyc7IUQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BariAWilliams @HBODocs @FastCompany Well written, a great piece! Thank you for restating this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@screencuisine Looks cool!  A little steep at $30 for my early access budget.   Will wishlist it to keep an eye on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSugarLily @1RealLori @Bmw2163Heart @Boyd_2650 @tillmantweets @ukwildcatfan191 @busylizzie48 @WhatSquinkyEye… https://t.co/j7EguhTm1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fox43 You never ever ever leave a kid alone with any dog! How stupid are you people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudreyHolidayxx Just went to freeones n rated u 5 stars baby ur a true big star⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyCSports Salio 3-1? No me digas, pero que casualidad, en el 2012 Riber Belgrano tambien salio 3-1. Pero que casua… https://t.co/OaFF2XtmWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LocalTVSPXPrbs Been looking for my check since I lost it when I moved. https://t.co/1NkMpACLXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPayneDigital @GcCraft @babbleaxe @apocalypsebiker @notwokieleaks @AOC A mixed economy is what ALL economies are.… https://t.co/ahSmFyeHs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelSideB @Bill_Huber_ @DrP_Principal @SherriElliott82 @NowakRo @mafost @_on11 @RACzyz @USD_SUP @SJSaragusa… https://t.co/0RuowB7Dm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrisAlvaradoMD @mtracey To say Wikileaks, contacts w Russians, obvious lying abt Russian contacts and Russian inte… https://t.co/G3IHOFCdcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clifton Powell is one of my favorite actors of all time... it was a blessing to meet him at the BET Awards last year 🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CiroGomezL @lopezobrador_ @NicolasMaduro Es obvio que el Mesías le debe a Maduro financiamiento a su campaña, que vergüenza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@orangebiased @chrisrobinson00 Nah she”ll block me again &amp; only unblock me if Kentucky wins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Larry_Bishop_ @drabtshirt @JunkiesQuotes @matt_valdez @JunksRadio @daverichard @moneymetalcakes Cakes.... https://t.co/uwblhpijVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sure, but does it spark joy?” What I just overheard a guy ask another guy in a clothing store about a pair of sweatpants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteButtigieg As a South Bend resident, I ask that you PLEASE go onto the @dobyfriday podcast]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know true fans can relate to what I am saying about @PostMalone. #PostMalone Always has that energy and he never… https://t.co/ARVeqruw03]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to all the Big Pharmas getting matched with their Little Pharmas😘🥰 let’s make this the best reveal day ever 🌈]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told Sierra about my retro set up idea that involved a Sony trinitron and bean bag chairs and she was all for it. I found a keeper 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am Starting to Think as a Baby Grows up it's Brain Develops and it can more going on Around it. At Fifty Years ol… https://t.co/ghYn3Je1U3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone’s talking about Harper and Machado, but nobody’s picking up Bartolo. Give that man a contract! #bigsexy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a short write up and interview with @ginarox1234 about our new single streaming now 🗣 https://t.co/b1TipewGjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  thanks to @AnnCoulter  the @POTUS own far rt nut bar coz they have no ideas wing r on the loose from the bubb… https://t.co/JLIy3v2wQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMAnderson247 Do you think we look for another QB in this class since we are low on numbers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the ultimate question I have about Kingdom Hearts after all of these years is, Where is Sora’s poor mother? Does he even care?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great interview by @AndrewYangVFA on @joerogan podcast. I encourage everyone to watch this interview in whole. He a… https://t.co/BIm6bBX2lZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier I mean when a group of bigots supports one....? The maga people deserve all this shit😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Another republican enabler, there is more than enough smoke to think there could also be a fire 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeachESL @Cameron_Gray @SpeakerPelosi @Ilhan I think we're on the same page- I just saw the irony of it all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the worst parts of living in a post-apocalyptic wasteland must be running out of Omeprazole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haleymossart Yeah- there are parts of me feeling the itch of doing that activity again. Like in recent weeks when… https://t.co/ZLGscm9XN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously??? 🙄 @ESPN gives Kentucky a 59.2% chance to beat Tennessee in their Feb. 16 matchup. 🧐 Agree or disagree? Go Vols!!! @Vol_Hoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I lost one of my Polaroid pics at crush over the weekend and the guy who found it mailed it back with kandi 😭💗 P… https://t.co/0iwt8ohlHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayer tuve el placer de estar desde @noxostudios "Conectados" con @LuisChataing junto a  jenlybouzon. Gracias angela… https://t.co/WW3oogZyVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anastacia back in 2015 I had a commercial assignment with a sober living behavioral health company that had just le… https://t.co/8roy561UJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danicamckellar @hallmarkchannel Love your pi song. It’s still in my head. 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aholdy12 Lucky to get it, would’ve bumped duke off the 1 line no doubt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[James White Jr., who's lived in Smiths Station all his life, is cutting a fallen tree off his home today after torn… https://t.co/Xaqgo4mxmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrCraigManifold Wow. Ask Holly what you can do with white wine.  See ya in Dallas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy week! Got Martel Automotive all sparkly new again. 4' X 10' logo, painted on concrete block wall. 🏁 @ Bellevie… https://t.co/JaZnF7GS6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sólo en Venezuela se puede llamar a un acto de negligencia algo tan tierno como “arropar”]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy your my Valentine! Happy Valentines Day! #valentine @ Rochester, New York https://t.co/mmC8f8gCHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Folks be careful I'm warning you, AK-47 and large knives could very well be hidden under that black cloth, along wi… https://t.co/S0Pnxi1L2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiagnosticChick @IanColdwater @jamieschmid @DarrenPMeyer Oh I use the gnome pomodoro extension, which blocks the e… https://t.co/JgACpCFXnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer Listening to a traitor of our country speak about Justice is a joke. I'm sure we could make his sentence fit his crime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Jussie! You’re getting “Mueller’d” - Imagine this is your life for the next 2 years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave @AOC Nope, nothing will happen and this story will disappear tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yurt walk to the falls revisited... @ Cloudland Canyon State Park https://t.co/8bW67R8NSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TearsOfLightnin @KTNV your estimate on a hard surface like block wall, car, etc? closer to 3"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PupTitan404 @artieotterpup But there weren’t any horcruxes in Frozen 1...,]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I lived in NEBRaska not ALaska! Hahahahahahahahaha 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣😀😀😕😕😕😕😕😞😞😞😥😥😥😥😭😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raidermike5569 @cherylcarter @Howard_Cole Sorry to challenge your Mensa status]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @crosspens  I’ve had 2 of these pens and loved them. This is my 3rd try at a new one. Has there been a change… https://t.co/oUW9TO9fWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisarmedToaster @system76 Distro hopping is half the fun! But yeah pop has been a very productive enviornment for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatalieRacing Glad you are ok.  Terrible scary way to start the Truck season.  Go get them in Atlanta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBigCat Subway PR members googling articles in case they missed a story https://t.co/UpvdcRrF3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[This school made us .... literally the best decision I’ve ever made ✊🏾.. Aggie Pride till the day i die ... it’s sh… https://t.co/A01rZtbPuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leodelo2 Both. It is actually quite simple. Just because #Catholic #universities have given up on their mandate doesn't change the mandate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RomanAtwood @_little_britt_ @SmileMoreStore got my smile more blank in the mail today my dog and I love it https://t.co/9kTlrXfN3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time my nose is stopped up I’m going to think I got a leech up it instead 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prepping for today’s @kcrw set. Hope you might join me from 3-6pm as we sit and listen to some timeless favorites x… https://t.co/KIQSNcO5Eb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plz ask colleges to start brokering our health insurance premiums directly. The universities might as well be the m… https://t.co/HiTdIgiULn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryandawidjan Just read your post on being on Twitter on Medium.  Fantastic!  Just sent to a founder CEO friend who… https://t.co/CQL3Hj7yJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mynameisrel Dude is a Packers fan from Chicago, we should have seen this coming]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FleeceRodgers @judgesbaker You said just cuz like it ain’t the best shooter in the NBA standing right beside him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicholls women attempt to defend their tournament crown in Katy, starting at 1:30pm on Friday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @xmagicmomentsx How is this possible ?  What happened to common decency ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[☠🖤LONE STAR🖤☠ DROPPING SOON 🤘🏼🎶 TILL THEN CHECK THE LINK IN NY BIO SUICIDE 🤘🏼 PROD BY @tmighty_beatz  . . . . . . .… https://t.co/4DIAUkefGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachDP32 @ChanceDickmanTV @slopocsports @JessicaVoSports @JBaileySMSports I enjoyed every minutes of calling the… https://t.co/Gu4P1Jaw80]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve Stricker appointed U.S. captain for 2020 Ryder Cup: Steve Stricker is going to his seventh straight Ryder Cup… https://t.co/bFJQUed3Pl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecachockey @CornellSports @PWIH @PUTIGERS @ColgateWIH @ColgateAthletic Congrats, James!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuffaloSports84 @rbenny43 @LedyardNFLDraft Irv is my biggest draft crush next to McLaurin. Hard as a rock for Irv, personally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murdo_fraser @MspLiz But in January you praised the BBC for their “Motherwell” audience.  Calm down Stroppy McStro… https://t.co/aC8PoLUxQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barracuda_Bella @gaye_gallops @FoxNews  3 months and the F-ING BOSS  NANCY GET YOUR LITTLE SHIT UNDER CONTROL DO BE STUPID U WILL LOSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NW_Horadam @SafeSelfDrive Yea I wonder how those scooters I picked up at the metro station to charge got there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The strategy of the Socialist is to make fake news. In this way they keep the people attentive to what they are goi… https://t.co/TGTqK9DM3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los venezolanos odian tanto una continuación del gobierno de .@nicolasmaduro que serían capaces de destruir Guri si… https://t.co/Z6hRoHJDsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should never happen in a civilized society, but we’ve convinced people that it’s either put up with heartless… https://t.co/0wJRWW1vfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas told me I was going to college I was like...... https://t.co/6xBHTtVklQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight bud, until someone can supply me a cart that won’t kill me down the line. 💀🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malcotheatres Will the new Powerhouse Cinema have reserved/assigned seating?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nothercupacafe I believe the degrees of that adjective are Bat$#!+, Super bat$#!+, Gorka.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WritersofColor ...applicable. Stories come from a mix of assignments and writer pitches. Must be available during… https://t.co/DQTuhmFjFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@womeninblockch3 @WomanBlockchain @PamelaDraper14 @satoshiswife @TheBinaryRunner @codeyvargas_ @mysticaloaks… https://t.co/ey8mOFNexF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phat old A🕳‼️Just another racist🐷 #RushLimbaughWho #racist #AsinineMOFOs #RussianRush]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinmarieeg @DanJFederico @JulianGuilarte1 It’s amazing and frustrating as hell the Yankees aren’t even considerin… https://t.co/Mda3iS8pnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The phone I have is a “tool”.  tool:  device or implement, especially one held in the hand, used to carry out a par… https://t.co/BWWSmjdOM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I realized this is just where I share my random thoughts. Fun fact: kiwis *the bird kind* have whiskers. https://t.co/nfyiPqM8Eu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyJKoch @mad_gonzo2 Dems don't care how many voters they lose. They are replacing them with illegals.]]></document></documents></author>