<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@smacneil13 tell me why i walked in there today and was traumatically thrown back to junior high when my brother discovered axe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell you're a wonderful man @RepSwalwell ..thanks for sharing..]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is a wondrous month. It's the month of Spring, and thus renewal. This year I can't get out much, but we have… https://t.co/TkgnpUkmgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let ado this, Monday!! @ West Pelzer, South Carolina https://t.co/oBm6VLVljh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tamar Braxton won Celebrity #BigBrother tonight and I have something to say!! 🗣🗣🗣@TamarBraxtonHer @CBSBigBrother… https://t.co/TE6zlyt5k4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShSherrer @misspunk63 @PaulieD55 @jimeh5 @hdorenew241 @jmarker1612 @MoosePatriot1 @LadyNY4Ever @Aug1405… https://t.co/tEtMGuFM8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveDelzer1 @Lowcountry1Girl @AOC Rumor has it she is another Soros puppet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They love you so much @Stana_Katic - excited you will be talking with #HFPA soon - oops I just spilt the beans! And… https://t.co/MoTvM7RbDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharpEndurance Could not have said it better myself. For the record, Moana &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; frozen (1?).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreBernier @Fox8news and the Weather Team--"DAWN WAS A STAINED-GLASS WINDOW IN THE SKY THIS MORNING ... A motion… https://t.co/rdiXZIEnIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DiamondandSilk Now lock up the liars and traitors to our country’s Constitution]]></document><document><![CDATA[Precious moments "all done" for today... Thursdays are Bode &amp; Gigi time. @ Atwater Village, Los Angeles https://t.co/6vN31qLzwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BullisKari @iowaahperd @GHSaysRockChalk @CoachPirillo @momoneybeet @tall_kelly @ScottAmpersand @MSMS_PE… https://t.co/u7mhKBTKtx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArthurG74385202 Arthur ... Happy Valentines 😃❤️🌹😃❤️🌹😃❤️🌹😃❤️🌹😃❤️ https://t.co/5bGtbl7E5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[#playback #tenfeet #film #auditionday #actingclass #bestactingcoach #oncameraclasses #funlife #funfacts hashtagbles… https://t.co/30Yh3cyqCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monie724 Why we are here! Snowed in.. NO fire falls 😥 Try again in 2 weeks ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoeSargi this is from the Tom episode 4 comes from the front room. I left the time stamp in the utube comments https://t.co/tqRx0Uu5Cu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boozychef @EatingBeagles @_drazzari People like that have differently wired brains. They don't care what they say… https://t.co/zTQcL7nnEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of you didn’t go up watching early 2000s disney channel and it shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're going to obtain someone to masquerade as someone else, it's usually good to be certain the FAKE LOOKS REM… https://t.co/7EGbAJGuqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my best guy friend has a gf and I’m so happy for him that mf deserves happiness .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marisha? More like My-risha. It's always a good day when I see the beautiful @Marisha_Ray ♥️♥️♥️… https://t.co/W6v2YwwYZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my baby @MiemsGurl having fun, not sure why we’re on the steps though! Lol! @ Camp Arnoldi https://t.co/XuGoPeVTVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this look for “What to Wear for March” by @styleblueprintnville featuring our pleated romper, pale pink leathe… https://t.co/1nJ5qiHOfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar @RepMarkMeadows I watched all of the clips you posted in this thread. My head hurts. https://t.co/BAOFdX2x41]]></document><document><![CDATA[#theonlymayhem #djbrynntaylor #jasonkingphoto #MickysWeHo https://t.co/fQG72z22Ah https://t.co/j6vxuXl3Oj]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need more of this in the world. Way to go @JFBKnights @Kings_Schools showing up to support @MasonSchools by serv… https://t.co/CaUORF8Ut7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyKinLA Eeewwweww. The assumption that you want or need his opinion is gross and shows a lack of social awareness… https://t.co/i1XZCH4Yat]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Netflix Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  C… https://t.co/RguPZSSm1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[bald men + exploding water balloons + perfect timing = priceless #hilarity #snicker #grin #hilarious https://t.co/peBsp68ESk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gelato! I don't know if it is weird to people from other places that #JoePattis a #seafoodmarket has some of the be… https://t.co/4ilUX7yddA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting a little help from our friends with studio lighting in Photo 1! @ArtsFcps1 #youthartmonth19 #fcps1ARTSyam… https://t.co/sjjFbFxm8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Active and Original Program !!! Congratulations Mrs. Paine!!! #Toschpride https://t.co/24CRT68OtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eloquentgemini @AppSame @AOC When it walks like a bartender and talks like a bartender, it just might be a bartender.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump @KimStrassel Why, so you can lie to them some more?  Lol, you are another narciss… https://t.co/0VaHlusmqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu just saw the tweet you made.  You might have removed but undoubtedly you don’t watch the news.  We lost 23… https://t.co/6BbJhNRlFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retraction?  Racist? Homophobic? Attack?  This is a carefully planned production to destroy the fabric of our melti… https://t.co/j2K2E87uP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me WHY my weird ass was bombarding this poor man at the bar with pictures of my baby and dog and moms new hair… https://t.co/E270RKzt9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ERyuqkL7Ak #Churchmadness #Andre3000 @shootn3zz 😂😂😂😂 #youhavegottobekiddinme @BigBoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad said they’re gonna get married so it’s confirmed. I don’t make the rules.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @HelloCrandil Two word for you you @DonaldJTrumpJr  #CrayCray #GetHelp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaceyMusgraves LMFOAOA I LITERALLY SCREENSHOTTED THIS EXACT MOMENT IM CRYING ILY https://t.co/iWaFGEGpwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom and Kevin went to New York to slaughter a pig.... what do your parents do for fun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Who is buying this “retweets” over  78k— come on -this is pure bull shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_F_Kennnedy @FuctupMike Precious baby at just 12 weeks. 100% whole. Abortion is MURDER &amp; needs to be a FELONY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@minjjongie IK I wanna just give in and get the $40 one but I've been spending way too much on pcs and stuff  recently....]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/gmcLMHlrGN  I KNEEEW THIS SOOONG WAS GOING TO BE A HITTA @ellamai   Since you gotta have it your way...   #ShotClock]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when I graduate cosmetology school and try to practice cutting on bae lmao 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews @PrincessBravato I suspect our knowing he’s not a billionaire will bother him more than anything else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I‘ve sometimes just ordered club soda with lime, but bartenders often serve it to me in a ridiculous large red tumb… https://t.co/Uf1Z4sudLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maseeh4alum That is a great question! I am on the fence about what I think they will do, but I certainly HOPE that… https://t.co/IGSMkhICyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meemfe حیف از میرحسین و زهرا رهنورد که پیر یک مشت ایرانی بی فرهنگ و بی ثبات شدند. همانهایی که الان برای دوزار نفع… https://t.co/JXBsmlJSKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newspeg @HardballChris Who says that families fleeing communism, oppression, violence, and oppression are falsely… https://t.co/mbLOKpTjtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samuel Fosso as Muhammad Ali as Saint Sebastian in Encore: Reenactment in Contemporary Photography now on view at t… https://t.co/w6yh4Wgchq]]></document><document><![CDATA[A need is a goal. What the potential client actually needs to have done. https://t.co/ZHpVUqB4NG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raquel Welch,   Saint-Tropez, France, July 1966. @ Saint Petersburg, Florida https://t.co/5CwQJcKXHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmclymer Great news! Congratulations on making it “passport official.”  I know the paperwork/bureaucracy can be da… https://t.co/wPSwbiF7Nn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this is not insanity I don't know what is... I mean this is supposedly the person in charge #TrumpIsMentallyIll]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so humbled and honored to have been invited to the #WomeninPower dinner this evening - I sat with women leaders… https://t.co/celUaEBDlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wackyvorlon @Heterocatalytic thanks. That helped me figure out the radio station. It's Guadalupe Radio at 87.7 MHz… https://t.co/fW8Dae9Sgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[11:11 Mucho éxito en la gira de Shawn ❤️ #ShawnMendesTheTour https://t.co/Z2RuiR0WfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all. I’m officially an Auntie. Lincoln William Smithson has made his entrance into the world today. 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[These gals ROCK! Great presentation today about optimizing content to get found better on Google! @HOFunkDesign… https://t.co/FBbEb2AFxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet new state rep for Warren/Bristol @profjune @myrwu is fiercely proud.  #HawksSoar https://t.co/uMjdxWizy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissy40697285 @funder Epstein is a particular type of creep that needs to be in prison. The victims didn’t recei… https://t.co/OvyjvRAGF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@browneyed_nuna @Lilajev @BTS_twt @RoseBowlStadium @KookieBae26 @laintrepida Oh hell Cali ain’t flipping ready!! https://t.co/kmCrmrlgi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganKIRO7 @PhotogGriff @ClaireKIRO7 @KIRO7Seattle My kids have been to school a whole two days this month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Читала "Людей, которые играют в игры" и "Игры, в которые играют люди" Ирвина Ялома 7 и 5 лет назад. Основную информ… https://t.co/acdr0IAI4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tesla @elonmusk: this video is incredible. Your #modelx is amazing in testing. All the world should see this video… https://t.co/Z9AHjFMKIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can anyone help out @NewburghUnified? See @Michael28710212 video I'm retweeting. @NBA @WNBA @SHAPE_America… https://t.co/zlQnINRWzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy release day to Tesla! Loving everything I am hearing! Well done! #tesla #shock #troyluccketta #jeffkeith… https://t.co/lRnYBGmwVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s valentine’s day so show some ❤️ to our public schools. They give us the gift of a lifetime- an education!]]></document><document><![CDATA[People ask me this all the time!  First name: Brittany  Last name: Evans  Started off as B.Evans (in HS my cheerlea… https://t.co/lLZyr9gq4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima always have love for Angela😭😭🙄😭we both foodies and we just click fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whiteconfettius THANK YOU, THANK YOU for helping me “Pop the Question” to my Bridal Party!! Everyone LOVED their b… https://t.co/M2sIsPfU7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morgain21567853 @Midgespeaks @Mik5171 That is correct. When caravans were arriving illegal immigrants were carryin… https://t.co/TtQTwtT1fT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LP_Ani_Morales @maikenoda @BroodingAnanas @mikeshinoda I was waiting for the pineapple love you guys 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NinaNighting I am thinking you are right. I am trusting the writers to do the right thing and turn this into something epic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chloecmorse HAHA omg me too, love that for us. next stop: marriageville]]></document><document><![CDATA[But to lose all my senses That is just so typically me Oh baby, baby  Oops,I did it again 🎼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaRecruiter @Adam_Karpiak @KatrinaKibben @highonhr Oh ewww! I was raised on well done steak and A-1 also. Grew up in WI.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Julienicole03 @OliviaOletzo Cotton candy is my fav flavor of everything do you not know me]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Gnf2yIRpY4   A TRUE DEMOCRAT: KAMALA HARRIS DIRECT DESCENDANT OF SLAVE OWNERS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmdavis0997 hi how are you I listen to Mike song over again and it keeps taking back to why this happen and I know… https://t.co/qD8VrAVrAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read her autobiography, and some of her essays from when she was a newspaper columnist.  There was a real hidden… https://t.co/8Vl5xTLiYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg Subbing 4th grade today and THATS THE PLAN 😉 and they’ll love it since they remember you guys from… https://t.co/laMir8x8CC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyjeeper65 @sunnyright That’s actually really funny! It also makes me wonder if Twitter is using some sort of auto… https://t.co/LpMRssgfqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!!! Appreciate ME!!! lol to all my friends TODAY is OUR day.  JK everyday is OUR day!!!… https://t.co/G9EBQ7GSHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: and I feel problematic using AAVE adjectives to describe deep-dish pizza but it felt so right in the moment, it… https://t.co/mAteFk2GbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregNorberg Welllllllll, they don't have guns, so don't we win by default? There will be no shots fired by their side, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so happy we rescued Bella from going to a shelter or god knows what would have happened to her she's the sweet… https://t.co/BbSms0Shqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still stand with @CollinKapernick #Kapernick Let the haters hate! #standforsomething https://t.co/vZFZ8GeR1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only we could be in 3 #IAASE sessions at once ... seriously the speakers here are all incredible and dedicated t… https://t.co/ZFTvNGtqqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobOldisTowel @JDaniel2033 @achs_fred @wthballs @SID402SID @JoeDeCamara @irockphilly @WhiteyinHeaven @Phillies Tho… https://t.co/tVFV0A9Cdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going through TSA pre-check trying to get to Texas for a meeting and bump into the voice of St Louis sports @Buck a… https://t.co/Vjgd2BlUxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm in the running to win the Ultimate Kitchen Giveaway from @Gourmia! https://t.co/dcYWlhhEpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulHunter11 @WorldRugby @vpschoollife this is what I was talking about... we should totally do this at practice one day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tpcowgurl @ruthlesswench @strom_annette @Blabla79021362 @CunningSq16 @GayleellisLydia @MisleaderC @esadah… https://t.co/swTVs9vObr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when people try to converse with me in the gym, men specifically... leave me alone. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #FacilitiesMgmt job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Environmental… https://t.co/jQP7gDW7k2]]></document></documents></author>