<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JLozanoA @TorrucoTurismo @SECTUR_mx @DesireeNavarro @juliopatan09 @LeonardoCurzio @beltrandelrio @PabloHiriart… https://t.co/WL0CX3b236]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The thing that was new [with the IPCC report on climate change] was the message: It is O.K., finally, to freak out… https://t.co/lrgtzAlSvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pedro Borbon! The guy had a rubber arm. He could pitch all day, every day. They don’t make ‘em like him anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Einstein Bros. Bagels? We're hiring in #Denver, CO! Click for details: https://t.co/ut1amu0V2K #Hospitality]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom Crack baby!!  I have seen many like this. We need to get him into treatment. 8 to 10 years in "treatment" should help him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Austin! #Texas #Austin #SXSW #KeepingItWeird @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/XtXjhSgCNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched a discussion on @TheLeadCNN w/ @jaketapper about this apparent socialism / capitalism dichotomy that w… https://t.co/tVDXAVZHY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1ChristWarrior @realDonaldTrump @MjrCitiesChiefs @MCSheriffs I love it when you always wave that flag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CocoaGoddess @NMAAHC I came all the way from New York City, followed the instructions on the site and had no true… https://t.co/9nEFX2s9Qj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Middle School World Languages teacher Maria Picado meets with prospective parents and students who have completed t… https://t.co/G4Jso0LcZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey hey what's up guys and girls haven't gotten back to anyting and to answer to I've been in the hospital for a co… https://t.co/mjC5cFdKEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give me Dragon Lee Vs Ishimori and give it to me NOW. My body is ready!  #NJPWWorld #njpw47th]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CobraAlert @ParklandMBB hosts their final home game of the season tomorrow. It’s sophomore recognition day! Come o… https://t.co/hZc1JzWxXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameOfThrones trailer just dropped and now my days ruined cause it’s all I’m gunna think about]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RP_Quigs @cubs4wsn2012 @GoldenKnights @NHL @LasVegasLocally @J15Emerson @JesseGranger_ @reavo7five LINDBERG FOR LINDBERG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phoneguy24 @OllypopZA @HillaryClinton @GabbyGiffords @lucymcbath @SpeakerPelosi And one ruling (Heller) is that Congess CAN regulate guns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart hurts for the people of East Alabama. At least 22 dead after tornadoes hit the area. An 8-yr-old girl among the dead per @WTVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I unlocked $20 Rush tickets for #SeaWall/ALife at #ThePublicTheater on @TodayTix! Unlock here: https://t.co/8Ty2ClLyAR #TodayTixRush]]></document><document><![CDATA[There it is, as described by @NaomiAKlein, “Wealthy people think that they are going to be OK, that they will be ta… https://t.co/72jcLy7MR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Briteeye777 @mam65mam66 Sue baby I know you have supported the Republicans two times with Trump and made all Democ… https://t.co/5l66Kr1yze]]></document><document><![CDATA[You would think the #courtevangelicals might lay low on a week like this. Nope.  https://t.co/TBsCq7YICj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm the type of person that will buy you 10 nuggets, knowing that the 20  nuggets are cheaper ($ per nugget) becaus… https://t.co/jH7NsatZFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cezarykrysztopa @AndrzejDuda Moim zdaniem zyje Pan mrzonkami i powinien zapoznac sie z tekstami doradcow Dudy pokr… https://t.co/9Lb2Dz0Y2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[❣️ Elegance isn't defined by what you wear. @ Dude's Positive World https://t.co/O5gXuyxCw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It isnt heping young women in detention centers.That is where the clear and present danger is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreakUrChains Evaluate probable outcomes before you leap or rely on imagined outcomes which are less likely to occur.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, he can read. Next question? @NichollsState https://t.co/2eNb5fdLff]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% of what I post is for me God does over an abundantly more then I could ever ask for so...I know sharing is car… https://t.co/Ppl2d4qoKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day#4 #Wordfast challenge  Never again will I confess defeat, for “Greater is He that is in me, than he that is in… https://t.co/I3gnquu4dw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericnakagawa Possibly the most slept on travel accessory: https://t.co/Q0gUdK0UIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to keep the @Fan4RacingSite Fantasy points in the @NASCAR_Xfinity series, @sam_bornhorst picked up 4 at… https://t.co/lee5mdRTO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ivan_Drago87 @Lilscreech @trewuno @beefymon9 @JLA_SBH @elreylee33 @theolainez I say we end at San Fernando]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KySportsRadio Matt, you should check out this great interview I heard on NPR yesterday. https://t.co/75csxw3Jso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Community Care Day in #Denver gives us a chance to give our neighborhoods a bit of extra love. This weekend, our… https://t.co/8AzCCDda8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiltonHotels @DoubletreeSNADC I'm trying to follow the process, but calling the Diamond Desk to then call the hote… https://t.co/HuuziiotPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadBourgeoisie @DoddsDC There's a cat at the bottom of my cat's water bowl.  He doesn't bother to try saving the "drowning" cat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalvesForDays @Padres DMing the Pad Squad a list of my favorite edibles and KY jelly brands]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Graceful Strength by @highlandbrews at @HighlandBrews — https://t.co/MfbicNxmLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Belgian Blonde by @TwistedCypress at @TwistedCypress — https://t.co/J4EkRnQ2dy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYGovCuomo If it hurts the butchers in your state  im all for it The real America prays for your people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@becausewecare1 @therealgynomite @wyo_advocate Allow? I don't own them. We do however work with local non-segregate… https://t.co/hzvinS3Bq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sad when a company you have bought from makes things impossible to order from right @TSRStore]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he didn’t criticize the $12 million that President Obama earmarked through @HHSGov to the @jfederations for Hol… https://t.co/5MhtxtzBSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Anyone ever run for POTUS pledging to serve one term only?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Union_Sports_ @Braves If he opted out after 3 years then the @ braves could use that $ to sign the big 2 when thei… https://t.co/F8FC2x3bcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUNIORS This is a reminder to complete your registration for the ACT by Wednesday, March 6.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FutureMoncada Guys it’s all going to be good. Baseball season is soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMan_1776 @Trashchristmas1 @JacobAWohl @OfficeOfMike https://t.co/UAKpL0IZ5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @KamalaHarris @JussieSmollett Fits the agenda truth is a distant 3rd behind agenda and lie]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson I feel insane talking about the voices in my head, but most of the people I say that to admit they h… https://t.co/yifTgXuE1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Bad Leaders Put Their Own Needs  Before Others https://t.co/4Qb6Moj0F1 ⁦@bigtime_76⁩ ⁦@campdaddy36⁩]]></document><document><![CDATA[My old favorite picture of my lock screen when I was still looking for the right of in the back days this picture n… https://t.co/YjVqEIRfyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So your telling me a joke caused a rift in the consciousness of man resulting in eternal damnatoon? @OSHA_DOL   #TURNTHEANIMAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePoniExpress #Truth They may have been talented, but they weren’t #Winners! There’s a difference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter You know this is untrue. There’s no new wall. They are repairing fence that’s been there for years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenryMartinM, @OribePeralta, @EdsonAlvarez19 le pueden decir algo a su colega? 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@365DaysOfDisney My family just got back from a 2 BR at BLT. It was amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe If you’re real, then if I get up to talk to this guy and he is kind I’ll know what to do. He said he… https://t.co/IUhh30HRqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump Maybe he should have 😂😂😂 cause guess which one of the two is going to jail]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to know how to buy and sell online? https://t.co/yL7sNxyb4W https://t.co/CiuedxCw1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[But she still “screwed” #21NY by gathering VOTES to limit@Middle-Class-income deductions! My taxes has DOUBLE! Note… https://t.co/mTCMIkSfVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec @realDonaldTrump Who are you kidding? Are you off your meds? #Trump loves on thing, #DonaldTrump https://t.co/XFHjxaUKeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiderofWolves Start with good thoughts and when you get a bad one smoke some pot you will forget the bad and think of the good again]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Outnumbered  Hey @KamalaHarris If  you have to deny you're a Democrata Socialist....  You really are a Democrat Socialist]]></document><document><![CDATA[WB I70 has reopened at US 6/Loveland Pass. Chain/Traction laws from Bakerville to Silverthorne. #cotraffic… https://t.co/oqPlVgAPk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s nice to know that as bad as things have been for the Celtics, they are still better than the Sixers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Kass You know spring is in air by the mounds of dog poop slowly exposed as winter’s snow recedes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bodydouble @RealCandaceO @HawkofNewYork @prageru Everything costs money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a good 30 minutes of your time - not everyday you get to hear from one of 32 head NFL physicians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing quite owns the Trumpsters like public defecation. That’ll win tons of people to your cause.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonKirkSBN Derek Jeter would definitely destroy me. Maybe Derek Carr and Derek Fisher too. I might be able to take Derek Holland though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Week’s Work. Some of my work is available on https://t.co/bo67fHYDel   #thedailysketch #drawing #sketch… https://t.co/429HMiS2mL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man with special needs is missing and his mother is on the run. Police say Yvonne Longmire brought a man (right)… https://t.co/BoTtG8owvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easy call for the pinball wizard. Oh I mean deaf dumb and blind refs #kubball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that a Taylor made bill dolan there Erica or a distracted district judges floor pearsalle sisterdale lil hores d… https://t.co/UcpIUVauu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/f5yt9Syi0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SStormCoach12 @82nd13 @butchbaccala @_JeremyBooth @JasonMcCuistion @mactiner @SBetkey @CedrickHarris11 @TGGCB… https://t.co/L7Y997G0KB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @tedcruz... it is time for #TERMLIMITSNOW Join the fight and support Ted's constitutional amendment --… https://t.co/R1VuWzYUXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when my students and friends meet at the gun range unexpectedly. They always have an good experince when sho… https://t.co/A2iyJl2zLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAcademy @BarbraStreisand Great movie. Both funny and informative. Loved it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ali70049534 @TheRightMelissa @JenniferBurt @Anubis1412 @realDonaldTrump You're smart?? https://t.co/8M657gBrKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Socialist/communist /liberal/democrat... you have to do as I say,you don’t get to do as I do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marissa_Creekkk You’re an absolute angel and your fits were just FIREEE hope u had an amazing weekend!! it was an honor meeting YOU❤️💜❤️💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gas V8's with a big cam and nitrous are way cooler than diesel trucks that most owners dont even know anything about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Seth_man I think it’s just that the main story of trying to defeat the invasion and his redemption took a backseat… https://t.co/ri2JQ5CdiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@6abcadamjoseph @6abc Hey Adam Likes it He Really Like it!! See @chris_sowers he loves winter lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveRubens @jack @Calnewport What? @benshapiro's tweet on DEM leadership?]]></document><document><![CDATA[People it’s all Talk,Nothing will change until some of Hillary’s ass wipes are loclked Up. The Clinton’s will go do… https://t.co/p2uuUDtppd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CJSullivan_ The only thing better was watching you wile e coyote down @bigheadpaul stairs in full Ricky Fowler regalia]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to the jumah Muslim service tomorrow at 1301 e. Las tunas dr. San Gabriel.  On March 1, I should be leavi… https://t.co/hO5HPlq6Tm]]></document><document><![CDATA[AB how’s it feel to not be wanted ... prove you don’t need football and retire ... what a piece o crap !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have spent hours watching Dax Shepard and Kristin Bell videos and it really gives me life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw Beirut tonight. Talented, but nothing special to see live. Listening to their albums would have the same experi… https://t.co/pBraxgtn5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/TY4KsiYI17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like the textures of Big Bend for Black &amp; White! #bigbendnationalpark #bigbendnps #visitbigbend… https://t.co/jfRkl09C6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA You have to play guessing games to keep your narrative relevant to the zombies clueless enough to hang onto your nonsense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenjones_BU @bradleyumbb @BradleyBraves I cannot believe it.  That first half was awful.  Couldn’t believe they ca… https://t.co/qJtk31YRXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@LionUpBaseball OPENING DAY IS TOMORROW!!!! I REPEAT, OPENING DAY IS TOMORROW! I’ve gotta prepare my mind so I can… https://t.co/qvXihxVEvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it's just me because I don't like to spend #money if it's not that important but it seems like #mens… https://t.co/Yj3ccKAf4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bucktailes @panekbill @LauraMcOutdoors Thank You so much!!👊👍🐾🐾 We have a ton of work to do, but we will work it out!!🐾👍🐾👊🐾🥃🐾👊]]></document></documents></author>