<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@bradleydevlin @RealWendyBelle Ever notice they always size up and take on/harass those that are either much older… https://t.co/3ysiWQcuDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had two hours of the wall forced at me on news shows last night. Not the first word on the amazon/nyc breakup. Do… https://t.co/n28bMfZaLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch out with this cforcewater ...it makes you do things like Chuck Norris. I finished a bottle earlier, got into… https://t.co/1KWGaY9ovw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYinLA2121 I'm with you,  New York City. My city. Los Angeles the runner up...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8Wankmaggot45 I want to come out and denounce this as it puts a negative connotation on oral, I mean, if you don’… https://t.co/mNZEp2q3hs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Formula One AUSTRALIAN GRAND PRIX PRACTICE 1 Mar 14 https://t.co/uXjgsIxqrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again Mr. Lincoln bowed and sat down. The efforts to obtain a speech failed, as was only proper it should, under th… https://t.co/33fdZXrJws]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marsh check in @ Smithsonian Environmental Research Center https://t.co/n841phzMrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[K small business owners time to exodus the communist state. Burn your properties to the ground on your way out. Rid… https://t.co/tS2z9dTX2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFCBarstool @FeitsBarstool TOUGH look for White Sox Dave. Just hate to see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heyyyyy St. Louis, Chicago, Boston. @BenRosario1 and I are coming to see you and talk some @insideamarathon. You ca… https://t.co/CJdFRkMtTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoyolaMLAX @LoyolaHounds @SportsCenter there’s a cursor in the middle of your screen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wedding vibes. (With Joe Bishara.) Video: @EvanDickson https://t.co/1csOieKrWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose I just dosed up w/ 50 mg of ritalin and it made perfect sense to me.  Open up your mind people, ca… https://t.co/okg2dBFBsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarryRSmith Drilling down on the numbers reveals some very positive info. The U6 number dropped from 8.1% to 7.3%,… https://t.co/Gdqd5p31xV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr It's funny to see leftists run down one rabbit hole after another. Then they have to try to cover t… https://t.co/vPi1tsDTcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Draylen_Ellis5, GOD GOTCHA, LET’S GO. I GOT MY🍿READY! @CoachFlowers, U R A 1ST CLASS COACH AND I THANK YOU! COACH… https://t.co/QVnU7vy8ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few more photos - Thanks@again to @stulaperle and @collegemedia https://t.co/gCMNewdGui]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@OldDominion so yall really went home off the road to record “Song For Another Time” not knowing what come from it… https://t.co/rWPLe33IdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephanieQuayle @1065WYRK @tenilletownes @abbya_music Lol they play none of them. Fact check the adds on each. I l… https://t.co/AGXvBQc64q]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY 👏🏼 DRYWALL 👏🏼 WORK 👏🏼 REQUIRES 👏🏼 A 👏🏼 LOT 👏🏼 OF 👏🏼 TIME 👏🏼 AND 👏🏼 SANDING 👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateDunlevy Never heard of it.  But Fred Glass seems to be doing a bang up job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brickwallblitz Raiders got rid of Mack and got AB and they don’t have faith in Carr idk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unrelated. He moved to Marsh Landing during the season. Had plans to sell this house for awhile. Wanted to get away… https://t.co/MMcPFMBkRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Media timeout at 3:45, Prep up, 23-10, O'Boyle 4 for 4 FG, 2 reb, 2 asst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AWholeSnek Must be because of my huge cocking balls and devilishly good looks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotVandyOC Because were the only private institution in the conference and no one likes us]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could watch this all night. My little angel  growing up.   #happy #happiness #life #pursuitofhappiness #motivate… https://t.co/4Kwnlnpp0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DakotaHansen13 @justme2andu @rfmmoran @nancylees @Ehukai411 @KirstenPowers @LLinWood No. As children in a confront… https://t.co/sndzjZaClS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robostop10 @toxicxmo I think Conno is pricing himself out of here. I like the player a lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expulsado el Idekel, por lo cual no juega el próximo y forzosamente tendrá que entrar el colombiano. Se celebra, po… https://t.co/m0ugcRzTzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaDP4S @capthlr When you have no job and want to blame a system that has helped millions succeed but you can’t everything offends you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:37.6°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annanainys I don’t like it! Just drove the ‘English way’ around a roundabout in whiteout conditions trying to find… https://t.co/pOWc7FxiGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FraFont The characters really grow on you. And four seasons is the perfect length for it. It's a comedy but there… https://t.co/ijgrATry7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[we made it @BTSsmash #UltimateSummit @BeyondTheSummit https://t.co/cLtJf7US8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[New: All the updates to Information Protection in Microsoft 365 with @gagangulati  https://t.co/3tJn5VNRpg https://t.co/CHxUUrRPz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you know your tweet is gonna go viral and it only gets 4 likes. https://t.co/TrqRQTf97n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo digo qué lo más pendejo es contar los tecates que te tomas jajajajaja tu tómale prro 🤘🏻🤘🏻🤘🏻🤘🏻🗣🗣👽👽👽👽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OSUmommaDOC @RiderofWolves @SweetArpeggio @nerdo5 @BrienneTarth6 @topher_crux @DivinaDeeMe @Aflgirl126… https://t.co/DOxBKodvyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fattuesday #mardigras #bock #untappd #craftbrewjunkies #craft #beer #craftbeer #craftbrew - Drinking a Mardi Gras… https://t.co/DeTRjjwiGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[im gonna draw like. lanque w the whole mother mary thing from that one jean paul gaultier runway show since yall r… https://t.co/eQG292jsKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LGB @jetblue flight delayed for 3 hours, jump in a @lyft to SNA and @JetSuiteX saves my day. Thanks!✌🏼❤️ #SNA &gt;… https://t.co/KkzdTdjqke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rashadlawrencee Today your name is being spoken in places that you never deemed possible. #favor #Goddidit #WordOfTheDay #faith]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesus_solis @ednuvi Me esperaré cuando vendas el portafolio de bodas y el smokin de tu historia con la señorita Solís 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready player one shouldn't even be nominated for anything.  Im more upset about its nomination than Infinity war not winning best VFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck @Wyatt_Jordan17 and @N_Keimm CVILLE we be cheering you on from the state fairgrounds!!#CardFam]]></document><document><![CDATA[I plan to up North in March. Before the ice is out and with plenty of snow in the woods.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @KimStrassel @WSJ @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong… https://t.co/tLT6NBlwS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceEbanks @trnrtips @ProdigiesNation I’m up almost 2500 pics and still nothing 😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susanhall_EdD Thank you for the amazing opportunities to learn the past two days during your presentations!… https://t.co/akKoGH9hX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring athletes: If your practice is outside today, you must wear a hat that covers your ears (hoods are acceptable… https://t.co/1Zlx9vHiah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just unbelievable from start to finish. I would do this every day if I could. Phenomenal broadcast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @ALL4HNW with get_repost ・・・ Feeling that Monday morning burn 🔥 Daylight Savings didn’t stop this crew from… https://t.co/Iuesa9oWUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FresnoStateMBB continues with the records as they set a new @savemartcenter record by scoring 121 against SJSU on… https://t.co/pX7mvKXNmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@former_usMarine @JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews You pass the ASVAB???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justadadinKC @iamAtheistGirl Summarise for me how a creator would not, itself, need to be created.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iflabeast @KFerrugia @JuddApatow @lowkell @FoxNews https://t.co/lB7GONHjc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cover brought me to life and I just wanted you all to know. https://t.co/y9x2cbGtM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming up at 10AM on Face the Facts with Max Reiss: Melissa McCaw discusses the state budget and why @GovNedLamont’… https://t.co/xU8b4Pv0EL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman I do not like any of them in the running, they are all liars and crooks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fletcher Magee is the most how does he do that shooter since Jimmer Fredette but I think he’ll actually have an NBA career]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks so much again to Chasing Your Dream Radio on Twitter for all the incredible spins of my single and title tra… https://t.co/ro8uTidlZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would like to see him avg around 26-28 a game . He’s that type of scorer]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now you have an unhappy long term @netflix subscriber evaluating whether to remain. A 15min conversation has ove… https://t.co/qeSVrdVL0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCrongeyer Our  avatar was not programmed to respond to real human disgust https://t.co/lAbzwUBjpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Southbound 620 rolls into Cochrane Yard February 10, 2011 with GP38-2 1805 leading, GP38-2 1800 trailing, and a 39… https://t.co/iK5T40cO0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[So... I got three pairs of shorts for 75 bucks... well... five bucks because I had 70 in gift cards...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtsport2 haha can’t believe how good/bad that show was, had me hooked tho 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBA @kostakoufos @SacramentoKings @LandonLynch4 wishes the happiest of birthdays to his favorite player KK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re playing Could Get A Top 3 Pick And Also Beat The Lakers Bingo...you’ve had bingo for weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has been a goal of Jaylen’s even before he entered the league. Pretty impressive feat at just 22-years-old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders @proxy_man Sorry Bernie, you are too old and too liberal for me. You run, Trump wins again.🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final after overtime: Terrors 3, Cougars 3. Goals scored by Branden Herd, Joe VanDyk, and Dane Smith!… https://t.co/ilfS65slEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The inventor of the laser, famed Cambridge physics professor, Dr Alan Parsons, is coming to Fort Lauderdale.… https://t.co/vXUHNrYW9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLeksander @cleared37Joseph @WitmerCarl @godrockin @Jr1Pittman @Cannoli_Joe @CB618444 @jjauthor @FriendlyJMC… https://t.co/a0bhG3nxck]]></document><document><![CDATA[see i knew youd say something LMAO bro you gonna gave to keep that Bell hate to yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have officially hit the age in life where staying home is better than going out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ApexLegends had a short time in the spotlight (obviously my tweet is a joke but also I really downloaded #Tetris99… https://t.co/f7w0vT8QdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking you're entitled to someone else's labor for free is how you got racist, my guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her win — plus Hannah Beachler’s win for production design — was a real highlight of last night’s ceremony for me.… https://t.co/bn0l3R7K2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[La gente sigue consumiendo y comprando, dijeron algunos propietarios de negocios en Flagstaff. Les contamos cómo… https://t.co/w7brWN54kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little light w3rk to finish the week.  #RUNwithGOD #KikiStrong @ Tappan, New York https://t.co/I1Ki71Vq6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sleep (@ The Timbers All Suite Hotel in Denver, CO) https://t.co/WGfmawiR0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pres Trump has given us a safer more powerful and  great financial boost, lowered taxes and cut regulations and kep… https://t.co/AYO6N3v9vY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carrieanninaba thank you Carrie. U seemed to be the only one that got it that this was a very difficult discussion for @sherylunderwood]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love sharing the word of God!! And letting everyone know about His free gift of salvation.  God is my light and m… https://t.co/2pPbFtfy7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petalipari @connor_oneill20 The B.C. faithful became biiiig Connor O'Neil fans yesterday! 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this isn’t the most accurate thing I’ve ever seen... Y’all want to be entertained? Catch @natesperling1 on some… https://t.co/eC1K0dx7W6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1014lacookie That sucks I use to be able to sleep thru the night but lately if I go to bed before 2 I won’t sleep right]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Betty but waiting in the car listening to @JackTrackItDown pregame for the @UNDwbasketball #LetsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MurphyandToby @DesmoDog3 @maeveydog I agree. I don’t even want a bed (I like sleeping under their bed) but they ke… https://t.co/7H6qkmO6PQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NazWrestling DaShawn Farber wins 9-3 to advance!!! 🔵🦅🤼‍♀️💪🏻 https://t.co/jsFWCmCPJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m finally watching Duncan Jones’ MOON. Love the robot. https://t.co/fzOgqMqDxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pet Blessing - I bless all pets for the love and companionship they provide. #DailyWord https://t.co/PTDPjGwE1i @DailyWordMag]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care who you are. If you want the same respect than give them the same respect that you want. Keep giving p… https://t.co/gHxbQ1zOln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoffordMBB wins this game there probably a 10 seed.   UNCG wins and the @SoConSports might be a 2 team league bid.… https://t.co/jTEk6MTzyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesTully02 @AnnCoulter Dumbocrats would never ditch on a fellow Dumball. They go after the innocent and protect the guilty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and it could always be different. I’ll take a 2”-5” forecast over this any day of the week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LEGENDBETS I’m hoping BigM is racing. Snow has stopped and should be fine. I was surprised Yonkers canceled.]]></document></documents></author>