<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MittereMary Yeah I miss tweeting on the reality shows! I just have been going through it with my health. So hopefu… https://t.co/wLjSpQc3vh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCiniglio @LAVarsity @ashchevalier16 @lexidababy @amandaolinger33 Congrats girls!! 🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonFinleyHQ @inclusionchick @JTspartz @BetteMidler @EllenBarkin @RobynOBrienUSA @rosariodawson I love this shirt so much, @RonFinleyHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter You’ve been the number one person saying “update still no wall” and now your criticizing his tactics? W… https://t.co/uqpVDFufBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always been told if your hands are always freezing cold that I was cold hearted 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever feel like no one ever misses you? Like you’re not as important to others as they are to you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today Tea Dance with Betty Who! #DJ #EDM #vocalhouse #deephouse #gayDJ #soldoutclothing #denlapresents #weho #ladj… https://t.co/thqniUPgJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I once had my bedroom door taken off the hinges because i slammed it one too many times]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeopleValues Missing out the the relational nature of how we build resilience is hugely problematic but unsurprisi… https://t.co/YF1PnHM1Cs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rania_tn If you wanna feel better just look at my dislexic, spelling mistake ridden abstract and bio in the Frankf… https://t.co/ikwnt1GyQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reschcenter what’s up with these lines? We are going to miss tip-off?!?? #wiaastate]]></document><document><![CDATA[dearly beloved, we are gathered here today to get through this thing called life https://t.co/bQeNtSySVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakaktaSouth @Barbara102006 It didn’t hurt that her dad was a multimillionaire...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougRipleyODU Wrong, and AT&amp;T Center is not downtown. Northwest San Antonio is where the growth is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pabloalboran @RoyalAlbertHall Estoy tan feliz de verte cumplir cada uno de tus sueños. Todo por lo q has trabajado… https://t.co/TJ9hynJu8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone need a waitressing job in the Waterford/ Keego Harbor area?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 @VP @HouseGOP @SenateGOP @GOP @DevinNunes @VP is going down with the DIRTY SCUM that he aligned with!… https://t.co/l8NqeVlrfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[of course right after i tweet bohemian rhapsody starts winning... fuck that i hope that's all they win but im prepa… https://t.co/OBw5lNR6tp]]></document><document><![CDATA[i see myself doing this to @_Brisssaxo7 and us laughing exactly like that afterwards 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, flight is delayed about an hour. Low visibility in Vegas.   This is fine. I bought myself a fancy pair of ear… https://t.co/emC8g5mYkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck you Jim! Russia is biting us in the ass and you are looking the other way! Your complicity is sickening]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @GOP is a party of projection. They accuse Dems of their own ill acts. It's historic and pathological! Case in… https://t.co/LkMncTtunS]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUPER successful @prideatworkcan Women’s Networking Breakfast this morning! 🙌 Fantastic turn-out that even included… https://t.co/tQfnTWc54d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Candidate. Donald wasn't  elected legitimately and isn't acting like a preident so I feel no qualms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FLASH BACK FRIDAY..Me in the  early 80s 24 years old... Starter wear all Day... @ Queen Creek, Arizona https://t.co/UEFmnvWybI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teelittle0608 Congrats love that it’s a senior and freshman says a lot about#tarheelnation]]></document><document><![CDATA[good gosh ppl will do anything to get attention, &amp; to throw petty parties for themselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows maybe check your email for important work communication. Your outrage is fake! #MichaelCohenDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now an accident has been reported along your WB lanes of 290 right at FM 973, the left lane is blocked with this on… https://t.co/8FTvIX8Jtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DevinNunes @FoxNews “There is Collusion! All of these investigations are in search of the truth.… https://t.co/rkHYqV1GKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“have you been to 1025?” “Yeah I’ve been awake way before then” - my dad]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope everyone is ready to watch the premier and show freeform that we are still here and fighting #Shadowhunters #saveshadowhunters]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Lab Support Technician II/I - https://t.co/7NdRIktMXo #Healthcare #Springfield, MO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@junedarville Sounds interesting and looks good!  I lived in France over 5 years and never came across it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t front, I had a great weekend. Spent time with beautiful women with great energy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really sub-par check in experience at @HiltonOhare   Just saying... Especially for a diamond member]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you get a girl for her 21st birthday?  A trip to Paris sounds right.  Happy birthday to my beautiful brilliant daughter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlashFudd Only thing I have against Ash is that he should have caught way more Pokémon than he has. I mean we know… https://t.co/YRTDWW5izI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every single time foods ready and we’re about to eat at work that’s when the most customers come]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was saying how I’d never work for the government bc I don’t want to know the secrets  And my family said “yeah we… https://t.co/t1ITfWMgXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’ve been a good doggo and get spoiled with yummy ice cream 🍬🍦🐶😋 https://t.co/4K2JevKyxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sucreyoongi Of course any language person wants other people to speak theirs. It makes it easier to communicate.… https://t.co/h1wSb4vePM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #jonasbrothers are BACK!!! I’ve waited 10 years for this ahhhhdhsjaksksksmms]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm on the bus and it's hailing outside. Someone is on the phone saying "I don't know what's happening out here. It… https://t.co/lfHsOruveC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really really wish i could knock out, when my alarm rings I’m deff going into instant depression 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks vintage.pop.up.613 for making us your March beneficiary! We can't wait to buy some gently used clothes and g… https://t.co/67hvXHfHEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooper would run to his crate if heard the word “bed” so we made up a code word to talk about getting ready for bed… https://t.co/HvKvT0kyWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diana’s Two Months | History | National Geographic AU https://t.co/jHr7NjArYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schouten17 @nazliesoeker1 @funder Don't try to shame us for telling the truth, BOT! Report this troll as suspiciou… https://t.co/HHnEUvyig6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Lindsay graham is a paid off Russian plant like so many of the GOP. Check ties to RUSSIAN NRA and oil indust… https://t.co/yDsmXcww6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alwaysvitia @TheRyanHenry @charmainej_tv Yes but on this show she’s only around black people so not sure that’s a fair assumption you made.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can. Not. Wait. To see the girls bragging it up tomorrow!!! #HardWorkPaysOff]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m jealous as fuck of people who actually have good relationships with their siblings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@knflkkollective 😂😂😂😂😂  Elephant: get up White folks: huh? Elephant: fuck y'all sitting here for? White folks: huh?… https://t.co/kRT3zM9NXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so fucking excited for tonight 🥳🥳🥳🥳 I’m behind the bar and yes it’s my actual birthday !!! 🍾🍾  🚨🚨4TH QUARTER SP… https://t.co/IYbM5eQMJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo no se que voy a hacer pero voy a sacar todo adelante cueste lo que me cueste!]]></document><document><![CDATA[4- 6-hour repair time frames. I feel like tech should have helped us be able to say “we’ll be there to repair your… https://t.co/iBDMXHRvnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamelaR3y1990 @kathygriffin @GavinNewsom @toni You got to stand next to our handsome governor? Now, my claws are out. Meeeooowww!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Honestly, he hit it out of park in crystallizing how he could win again in 2020. Dens better wake up fast...#scared.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey NYC! Tomorrow is (special) Election Day for Public Advocate. There are 17 candidates running.   First, what doe… https://t.co/VVata95k1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessBravato Distraction. Even the National Emergency is a distraction!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hgudenkauf @hooksnbooks @wendydheard I still have this on my shelf. Must read!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2:40 in the morning so does that mean it’s the perfect time to tweet all my drafts? I think yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are lying about this, and it’s dangerous.   It’s already murder under the law to kill a new born.   You are try… https://t.co/tBn9bPBZpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[GAME DAY LETS GO @trailblazers AND @oregonwbb #ripcity #goducks @ Tualatin, Oregon https://t.co/ftOgsZcnIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@london3673 @maddow Exactly. A felony was committed, now what? Shouldn't he be arrested? If I were to threaten a wi… https://t.co/OlsgwdIIgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattGertz And you posted this, why?? To reconfirm that you’re a bigger and dumber asshole than Trump? I didn’t even know that was possible]]></document><document><![CDATA[im mad y’all said she look like thomas the train, cause thats all i see now when i look at her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylemartino @The2RobbiesNBC Özil (yes I named my pup Özil 🐶😂) and I are up and ready... 430am is early but we gott… https://t.co/ueCdGgDXAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because once again it's all about him and his and f*** everybody else. What an a******]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbastats @NBA I think 🤔 James Harden is the craftiest player of all time! Even when having an off night shooting h… https://t.co/LfsV4Vt0O0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign is up!!! Please start purging your closets and pack it up for Got You In Mind - all proceeds of sales will go… https://t.co/Sw3JphTWub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoLuchsinger O STF e uma mafia a servico dos gringos. Eles tinham era de serem presos e jogados por traicao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are a lying piece of crap traitor. See you in jail....soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The results of my first attempt at diy alcohol ink. I think I need more actual ink in the mix. The tutorial I follo… https://t.co/aLuDEAPgPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna be in high school and getting excited to go sit at sonic again but no now I’m excited to get off work 3 minutes early]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Wednesday @krisscottxxx @MsAbigailMac @KatieKushxx @misslee_x @LexiLore @JillKassidyy @KenzieMadisonxX… https://t.co/Uw2O0s3n6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[PETA literally kills animals &amp; now apparently disrespects dead people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated Don Don Don you just don’t get it do you ? https://t.co/pgwkgBQw0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tyler2ONeil @roddreher @JenKernsUSA @PJMedia_com @facebook Hi Tyler. Don't think every yr, but definitely before b… https://t.co/BR49SFAyVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got $100 of drybar products for $20 s/o to Nordstrom rack allowing a girl to have bomb hair on a budget🤙🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes education is put on a back burner. A lot of these kids are from broken homes. Shouldn’t schools focus on… https://t.co/43K0Tq2ZvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kjboies @trish_regan @nedryun @POTUS Who said anything about Venezuela? And I’m not pro socialism. And. I’m sure y… https://t.co/7jQdyYA8S5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also the premium snacks are all the rage. I felt like I was on JetBlue with the fun options. Nuts or a banana or th… https://t.co/1HAt0dRXCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Cheyenne: clear sky, 41°F 55% humidity, wind 14mph, pressure 1021mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJay008 @emory999 @CNN It wasn't a come back.  Simple question, trying to prove a point, which you so eloquently d… https://t.co/x48TIhftb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Well he could reasonably blame his BFF Putin, since that appears to be the only one he listens to. @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nominated for Best of Wake County.  Super honored and would appreciate a vote.   https://t.co/Nrtbp94ONB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anntensity @AnnCoulter Donald J. Trump is a huge hoax, Ann fell for that rather swiftly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xXxCore54xXxmlg @EricTrump @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr It is Not about the video posted by @dcexaminer . It’s… https://t.co/pCtG53kdCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuzanneSomers My husband got me chocolate covered strawberries.  Yum Yum]]></document><document><![CDATA[hilarity is good medicine. reason #766 why I WISH Pinterest was around when I got married!! Our groomsmen would hav… https://t.co/mSyYP7SuoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@llow091215 @SenJohnMcCain More funding and more education and appreciation for scientific research !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdBouchette Martin Luther King, Jr. would be embarrassed by Le’Veon Bell’s misappropriation of his signature civil… https://t.co/DIBDCh3600]]></document><document><![CDATA[The surcharge I just paid for not being 25 is more than the cost of the rental car I’m MAD 🤬😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckennanielsen Even on my best days I never feel like I deserve him. He’s a literal angel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Downtowns are the image of the community #rmlui #downtown #community https://t.co/BNGj3cSW9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWERomanReigns my friend from work Rehana loves u she’s a big fan and is so happy ur better and going back to work… https://t.co/TfrAr4ebVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[We go DB we don’t get tired!!! - Big love to my sheafs for staying on their feet with me for 24 hours, I can’t imag… https://t.co/TsyBN0mVgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @mrsyakafluss: Honey did you go home? Think they just canceled the show and nobody got a refund? Plse explain… https://t.co/Igi2pwckn1]]></document></documents></author>