<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Tensions flare at Venezuela-Colombia border amid aid row (WATCH LIVE) — RT World News https://t.co/Is9VdYpcLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HOVAAA Stay home hovaa. Our stores suck when it comes to hunting figs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petit voyage ce matin au Canada 🇨🇦 à Toronto. Admirez ce magnifique panorama. #canada #toronto #skyline #horizon… https://t.co/dHSjyePFYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomMcLellan24 The actors perform the film live AS the movie is playing and they say lines that are in direct respo… https://t.co/90Py2H37N0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patmahomes @Bhonecker Wait a sec I already have one of those locked up long term]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/HZOoRAgvtx]]></document><document><![CDATA[40 hour work week 5 hours and 45 min worth of meetings.   I guess this is growing up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJWatt Honey Nut Cheerios is off the list?  Going to have to start calling you #98, because you are one short!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. I got out of bed just before 5am. As for writing, the follow-up to "Sevanport Remembered" goes ok. I… https://t.co/zWNEYpFubg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MovieNut14 This is definitely less wholesome than I was expecting. It’s a Western!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willhampton @kowyatt @novalsi @GovernmentSM @GovGoneDigital @NinthCircuitFL @GovLovePodcast @Gimletmedia @NPR… https://t.co/Wy0mZTxtXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WJRickman We don’t seem to have gators in Florence. I’ve heard an occasional story, but I guess we’re just a little too far inland.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year it was a new vehicle, this year a house. Never ever stay stagnant. Always progress yourself and make goals 🙏🏻🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dale play! Disponible en todas las plataformas digitales. #MeBorre #DanielSimo #bachata #music #newrelease… https://t.co/Z39Rw4tDCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get ready to start seeing alot more green text messages the future is here now! @IsaiahHodgins @JackSeelye… https://t.co/t2Pkog9RbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂...Grab your 🍿Patriots...the #ShillWhores useful idiots will be thrown under the Cabal Bus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind the scenes moment. Go for the gold today. #JeffRogersCoach #IBetYouCan https://t.co/eWR7Ay0ha8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@udubdawgs1 Isn't that the Truth. Thank you for your Kind words. Gus was our family dog. Loved by All. I have a 4 yr old golden doodle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So...people are actually mad that @JohnFetterman dresses like a normal person? What a time to be alive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching De La Hoya vs Pacquiao boxing match on this Friday night. #oldschool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5 of a week long #ExitSlip assignment for the #QuoteoftheWeek in #Room210BlackHole #BetterTogetherWPS… https://t.co/AYranFUSXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re all smiles on Good Morning Tri-State! We’re on from 4:30am-7:00am. I’ll see you around 6. #mood… https://t.co/fyvWSN0W4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HolmesJosh You might want to check the Twitter feed of the current President of the United States.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brewerhm Are you ever going to be speaking in the Chicago area?  #relentless]]></document><document><![CDATA[My momma asl me how it feel to be in this position, to be honest momma, this just the beginning.... 📍🖤 @ Fayettevil… https://t.co/A4cInfTBUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib What about food? Do we all deserve EQUAL access to food? Housing? EQUAL access to housing? Clothes? Same question]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annamaria1word I suspect that the post doesn’t want to contribute to healthcare for all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RampCapitalLLC @dollarsanddata 😂😂Ramp's burner accounts are like a hydra, cut one off and two grow back. https://t.co/F7Gec4IT4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I chipped my tooth today Texted my mom 5 hours later when I knew she’d be asleep Called and woke her up Just to remind her it hurts :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost all of my fingerpicks without even using them. That’s some sort of talent or something, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This truck is beautiful!! #masculinemonday #truckdriver #truckerlife @ Fort Hood, Texas https://t.co/YUsU1OMg0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#friday #blessed #lifestyle #musictime #video #scruff #scruffapp #venezolanosenelexterior @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/pgqNoXkxnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN YOU SHOULD BE TALKING ABOUT! THAT WHITE LADY, THROWING CHAIRS OUT INTO THE PUBLIC STREETS WHERE SHE CAN CAUSE… https://t.co/4SCRDdx30I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RitaWirtz I guess you can't take a snow day, Rita! Drive safe, I hate Winter!❄️🌨️🌨️☃️☃️⛷️🤗☕️☕️☕️☕️☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lobster bisque for lunch today at caffe.capri Oh boy this is fantastic!! Nice and @ralphfajack for sure!! #love… https://t.co/zX89Cb3ZPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[✖️February 14th a Hero was born ✖️ . . . Fredrick Douglass. A man who escaped slavery and went on to become one of… https://t.co/0cmkCUyVdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Muddawg @CouRageJD What’ll really bake your noodle is realizing that’s not a gif of @CouRageJD https://t.co/Io9gaoyd13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristophPatano @SenTedCruz @realDonaldTrump @HoustonChron https://t.co/oFBMQPn3jx watch it old fool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@go_rox_ @denverpost Yes, absolutely it’s news. This guy got harassed in his own yard, then the officer blatantly t… https://t.co/QzJ1U8g9ew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MST3UK @jonahray "Back home in Hawaii we call this an aloha shirt. And what's in my wine glass? You might know it… https://t.co/msAjUTDPYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MirrorGlaze #Mouse de #YogurtGriego con #mermelada  #FoodPorn #Food #Tijuana  #PorSiAlguienPreguntaba en Vitro https://t.co/SBpsTq2rHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two cool things I got in the mail today, courtesy of @cinephile24 and @silentfilmmusic. Looking forward to diving i… https://t.co/0PWSo3AdpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[STOP DEFENDING SOOO DEEP your not playing Liverpool your playing Lyon. We inviting them onto us @FCBarcelona #Barca]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big #tcsprops to the @TCSBears swim team and coaches. Great day 1 at OFSAA. Can’t wait to cheer them on tomorrow. https://t.co/uXkd5cmkZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalOrgy Frank all Justice is social. It is giving to others which is rightly due to them. No. The loud mouth… https://t.co/YN6OUQO7L0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it! That’s my girl! What accomplishments. @AustinPeayWBB got a steal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BitBottom @BernieSanders Ok gloves off, you have no idea of what you are talking about :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚾️ La Joya 13 RH 4 - Pitchers vs. Coyotes: Christian Garza 1.1 IP 5ER 5Hits and Ivan Juarez 2.2 IP 2ER 2Ks 2Hits… https://t.co/owGsVFufCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshjarnagin19 @SiriusXMNASCAR @PPistone @LVMotorSpeedway @NASCAR If nascar needs to issue a stat book saying look… https://t.co/EG2MfjUNpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xspaceyx @nodqdotcom IDK how you confuse bring black and being a Samoan nigga]]></document><document><![CDATA[You buy a piece of someone,they don’t send pictures of receipts before mtt and want to meet to show you  reicepts a… https://t.co/gATYa6zPwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandraoverdose @TogosSandwiches Hell yeah fucked up! Employees deserve more respect than that!!! Getting yelled at… https://t.co/GKjIcgh3x8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers. (at @TopPot Doughnuts in Seattle, WA) https://t.co/Dz1YYHk6BS https://t.co/fkT78WlRic]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost doworkcompany (get_repost) ・・・ It hurts your soul . . #doworkco #fitlife #workout #workoutmotivation… https://t.co/a6NlOZ8cgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright @krollteri Cost of living in DC is crazy, I hear. 52k might not be as much as you think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlMacLeod66 @CupersLee They wanted 2 average prospects and a 1st rounder? Or is Dorion a fucking moron that has ab… https://t.co/QtlvWR69kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudyE2018 @RedTRaccoon @MomsDemand The scariest...luckily, I work in the same district as my children and we have… https://t.co/9fZFT8C31x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to be political, but how is 2019 and we still aren’t using metric? Who do we talk to about changing our subscription?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hkvn61Jeffrey @Trump454545 @QForaustria Best way to deal with lunatics like them radical Islamist !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuck regards my shoes as his toys. @ Waxahachie, Texas https://t.co/k5L32uy2gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurameehan04 @susanresnickco1 Very true. Right or wrong is irrelevant if the reason why is unknown!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so AWESOME and improves city life at a cellular level. Happiness is riding a bike. Let’s get those protecte… https://t.co/adRRrVnMug]]></document><document><![CDATA[To those of you starting your own sites. I book people one time. The way we determine whether this person gets book… https://t.co/iIKf1o0OuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important read about English language learners and retention. Decades of research suggest retention be used sparing… https://t.co/uMbhJr5ttr]]></document><document><![CDATA[A cool thing! About to guest present in @SarahEMcBride’s class at the @UDelaware’s Biden Institute. https://t.co/wloo80FsEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Dem Party has an army of millions where everyone wants to be a general.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Bangkok Bistro In The Alley https://t.co/MaUEUTUcki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our seasonal cannoli flavor is now Shamrock de Menthe! Delicious! #basil #basilpizza #basilpizzaandwinebar… https://t.co/cQcuax0fZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My writer brain is all over the place. I’m currently working on 3 stories one each for different collections - 1900… https://t.co/RzdHGSQDRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suggswriter @journalgsports @nbagleague @TheMadAnts Gotta show the Mad Ants love after they put them in the MyCareer mode in NBA 2k19 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Michigan #PureMichigan #MidMichigan #US https://t.co/S6MMjjEl56 https://t.co/S6MMjjEl56]]></document><document><![CDATA[I met @bam__margera tonight with my bro @alexjamieson925 and yes I also got ashes beforehand @ Bijou Theatre CT https://t.co/k4hCJRwOJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofyoule @Dentheluck @Dandelorme @IzyLaRousse @LeFrancoisCoutu @radiant_path Me demande si l'autre que j'ai vu va pogner 👺]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love METAL UP YOUR PODCAST - All Things Metallica | Episode 72 - 1984: A Year In The Life of Metallica, let's pla… https://t.co/ER5ENeChBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@draggabeats That’s interesting and I kind of assumed. Is the x word also pre-recorded?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GreatSunMass #FrMike #EddieV #JoeP #GoodCatholicJrzBoys 😇 https://t.co/oMjgKzjlh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn it’s like deja vu foreal. Like damn near exactly the same events unfolded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s Go Tribe! Day3 of WEED PRO Indians Radio Week presented by ECOTREE Services ready to go on @AM930WEOL Nice li… https://t.co/u4Nf2D7MyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 You forgot one important fact: of the people live then Republicans now long dead: 100% Democrats now… https://t.co/lqQJAb5fKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉😎🕺 TONIGHT enjoy a LIVE performance by @migos @draislv Nightclub!! ONLY VIP TABLES AVAILABLE, NO GUESTLIST!! 😎🍾🕺 F… https://t.co/06Jij4ariF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobRFC @AndyWillett5 @Readingfanman Willett pay for parking? I’m sorting petrol and Holdstocks are sorting my ticket...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly get goosebumps looking at wedding photography and videography.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course the heat are destroying the warriors at home on a game i did not watch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyways Uiehl parties puiehlb Uiehl stone henge fbi doodle lee auiiehll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimthejam @MHSBullpups @jacekinnamon1 @sportsinkansas @VarsityKansas @KansasPxPSounds @VypeKS Let’s…go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goodbye_Jesus Probably. But you must realize that there are points that can not be agreed upon..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDanZak A lot of comments focus on “sirloin.” Wasn’t it Zippy the Pinhead who observed, “Life is a blur of Republicans and meat” ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @TonyKornrumpf @LZJ879 @kaci150 @jonz970 @SpurFan @Edsterko @kmfisher1 @rpggamer1 @Cleanman0 @sunshinette… https://t.co/GM51NVNNLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first ever dog selfie: | The 35 Most Powerful Snapchats Of 2013 https://t.co/9z1Q3nsy2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeAngelina Told Les that Tommy wouldn't be ready for St John's talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Positions (2): @Interior Bureau of Indian Affairs (Billings, MT) - Civil Engineers/Ag Engineers. Closes: 27 March… https://t.co/2gzzHkGAUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xiocon320 @DrLeanaWen @realDonaldTrump What about the rights of these unborn babies being burned to death while in… https://t.co/IdzXHRP09b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnyDeutsch   Hey folks, here's another Liberal idiot who thinks he's smarter than 60+ million Americans simply b… https://t.co/XJIfttmWuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbbyMixer Hope you feel better soon @AbbbyMixer https://t.co/cMz5wab80z]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is a complete embarrassment that she was elected by the people of my district.   #wecandobetter #MUCHBETTER… https://t.co/61h1pXQXhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just trying to be a good Dad here, folks. #GoHawks https://t.co/UYKTiAhxge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in will co jury room with 3 TVs on cc MSNBC, Fox and CNN. I think they should turn volume up on all 3. Woul… https://t.co/GiuifrM6OZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobDarbyCanberr @Harpers Ancient stories, fairy tales, religious myths and writings should all be held dear as imp… https://t.co/TwyiI7LHWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[DRC: UNT special teams outlook for 2019 -- Replacing kicker Cole Hedlund will be a key challenge for the Mean Green… https://t.co/S2EgQfw9WA]]></document><document><![CDATA[LABEL AND ROAD MANAGEMENT!!! #ATLANTA WE HERE!! NEW CHEDDA CHIXS THOTIANA REMIX BlueFacebleedem I SEE YOU MY G… https://t.co/BNJMCeyg1c]]></document></documents></author>