<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else #Alexa talk without being asked anything.... or just mine?]]></document><document><![CDATA[who wants to go grab coffee and make art while listening to music  hmu 👋🏽👋🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we just gonna act like her being ugly is not an option?? I mean we all can’t always look our best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @TMobile &amp; @JohnLegere for #TMobileTuesdays! 💗 You guys always bring it! (Thinking of FREE @MLBTV,… https://t.co/tUjv1pi2Lr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edxnlouise how in the world did you get mcdonald’s  to tweet back at you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melt ice, please.  NOT immune to MEASLES. Drive back to doctor for shot, then 10 days to 2 weeks to grow some immunity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Montrose neighbourhood in South Orange, NJ https://t.co/cQIF4qgIGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@smerconish Not true; they talked about HRC's weight during her campaign]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one’s gonna drag you up to get into the light where you belong ✨ #aceofbase  . . . . . . . . #songoftheday… https://t.co/AIPmWPVgrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been trying everything for my dry skin on my face and everything is just causing me to breakout. The winter is so bad 2 me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinche_felix No it was the last night!!! The first night Danny and I were dancing in papas @ 5 am when everyone wa… https://t.co/RqsO0K6tKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t she start dating rob to piss off kim, Kylie and tyga ? You guys act like this isn’t her MO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from #FultonStreet in #BedStuy 😍☀️ https://t.co/NqcOCKdONd]]></document><document><![CDATA[After everything you’ve done, I can thank you for how strong I have become, cause you brought the flames and you put me through hell🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanMaloneAl @DavesCoffeeCo beautiful morning for a run. I did the #oceans4miler and husband is doing the… https://t.co/FrAgT0P3oO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpockResists @ybbkaren @Twitter @jack @TwitterSupport @porpentina2017 @meg_Y12 @ladyhawkerfinds @LunaLuvgood2017… https://t.co/KhuHILHQlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loccdawgg Thank you cause I’m at work and I was bout to press it in front of coworkers 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngieRRowan Thanks!  Looks better in person!!! They are ready to battle! #neiatough]]></document><document><![CDATA[The old @AmericanIdol was way better. Bring back the original judges! #wewantsimon]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girl placed 3rd at girls state!!!!! so thankful I could watch @FloWrestling since I couldn’t make it. 💓🥉 https://t.co/Mp0VEAi5B1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop talking bad about President Trump! He is trying hard to make us safe! My sister in my heart was murdered by a… https://t.co/uwKwlcMCte]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all thought it was a game huh!!!! I’m da Trending Topic I’m who they speak about when it come to this Torchin shi… https://t.co/KQjfw1097w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited about this! Pre-order at https://t.co/rZTgPpXp0L...I know I am! #LetLoveHaveTheLastWord]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dried aronia berries - a new superfood to brighten our breakfast: The high-antioxidant berries were a tasty additio… https://t.co/zv9XGlVtwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#winterscene #spartanj #sussexcountynj #newjerseyvegan #winterwonderland #beautifulsnow @ Sparta, New Jersey https://t.co/zK2u2M3KLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[3x3 Magic Square detail by Gina Dominique Hersey. Come check out the cool, new configuration at Firebox Art Studios… https://t.co/Jb1QgFzbMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[important: god cant read minds; make sure you speak when you pray   you can’t have a conversation without words]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NKOTB @SonySquareNYC Sorry won't be able to make that trip but will be there in spirit. #HANGINTOUGH30 ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmbKennedy_ret @LauraSHHolgate @laura_rockwood Wherever the 3 Lauras get together, it means business😉🙋🏻‍♀️So nice… https://t.co/JoXDY1c6o6]]></document><document><![CDATA[👀on the weekend!!! ⚾️#gigem #aggiebaseball #familyf1rst https://t.co/pSBuhz6Akx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got day driunk and fell asleep at 7, it’s now almost 1am and I can’t sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No me se los nombres de mi familia y quiere que me aprenda la bibliografía de porfiria diaz no mame profe]]></document><document><![CDATA[there is no irrelevancy. every situation in your life has the potential to liberate you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She has a Pascal Skull pirate hat omg I LOVE THIS SERIES SO MUCH *bawls*]]></document><document><![CDATA[i honestly and truly feel like billie is the only person who cares about me]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is where the older generation doesn't compare. The younger one got game! And HE can have it any way he wants.… https://t.co/rtdxk8DgyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YSCBuzz @The3Day 60 miles. It’s hard but not as hard as breast cancer. Come see me at booth 319 at the Summit in A… https://t.co/2qyVKxI7Q0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Happy Bday Tyson!!!! We love you so much..... #bestdogever #mybff❤️ @ Medina, Ohio https://t.co/vBKnciNjxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exists do something but snow on other's sidewalk. #entrepreneur #digitalmarketing #SocialMedia #Business #snowday #Oscars #SingerSongwriter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@birdman8272 @bethlahem16 He should, i think he was trying to insight riots.  Just to dumb to know folks rather sta… https://t.co/hY5m0H0eXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX29philly Why did Japan switch to all single shots? Google it for the answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE HYACINTHS ARE IN FULL BLOOM NOW  IM DYING  I HAVE TO GET THESE THINGS OUT OF MY HOUSE THEYRE CHOKING ME  Once t… https://t.co/hstfWwtBd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKay_not_Ashlay i have never related to something as much as this before]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting thread. Politics suck. Found out I’m not FAKE enough last November. No spin - no win 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MellieBikowski @aCreativeDC Surround yourself with #femmefatales for a night of #healing, #love, and #community!… https://t.co/BbIYgyZSSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamenluka6 @oreina_MAR @muyevil Jajajajajaja así es. O unos zancos. https://t.co/TeZLMgChS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me estoy ahogando! En serio? Seamos serios @UnivisionSports!! No se unan a la fábrica de humo 💨 https://t.co/eKx4KkRTbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are just "Highlighting" Shari's studio. @ Studio Hair By Shari https://t.co/CeMBocsKXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boygeorge I just love this your performance your singing is just awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alternatively if that stuff is whats important to you then do it yourself. Have your party donate to a common pot f… https://t.co/ugKKHJym0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[#autism Never forget the non-verbal folks have messages too and need a voice! https://t.co/8zZAt8f530]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paaigegraaves Hey, I’m ALWAYS a text away. You ever need to vent- I’m there for you, babes. ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re in New York &amp; haven’t seen Adair perform. Now you can...#54below @ New York, New York https://t.co/QD0OGH4TEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my dope ass cousins @crashdoyen love you mucho ❤️ come drink mimosas with me this weekend :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashaDistan I wanted to make a new chocolate cranberry sourdough but didn’t plan ahead with the starter. Consoling… https://t.co/SbuH6wf42h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect snow day! 🏂❄️⚡️ . . . #bigbear #bigbearlake #bigbearcity #snowboarding #snow #snowdays #weekend #happiness… https://t.co/1kWy0WvXDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy to say that in the 28 years that i’ve spent Valentine’s Day alone, I have never celebrated “Galentine’s Day”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackjonesbabe @decaro_nick ...in last election but many people are disappointed.  #60Minutes #traitortrump #EnoughIsEnough #Mar-a-sh*thole]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait do people actually care about Valentine's day I thought we all agreed it was a meme holiday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning to make powder cartridges  #moorescreekbattlefield @ Moores Creek National Battlefield https://t.co/63SybQm5I7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell Environment Minister @Melissa4Durack to list the spectacled flying-fox as Endangered! https://t.co/dj08SnfpUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noshoesradio Just thought the same thing!! This time next month you will be in Louisville!! Woo Hoo!! 🎶🍹🎤🎸🍹💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ex just texted me out of the blue to say he’s going to a bar back home and why am I sad when I haven’t thought of him in months? 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[And being in denial about being a Miranda, followed by a blanket rejection of the whole premise for being stupid, b… https://t.co/qvaVjiZp6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GovIvey Hope you do better than you did with Puerto Rico...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear this use to be me when my friends would take care of me when I was drunk 😂😂😂😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know my feelings are valid and I’m not gonna change for anyone and if someone can’t respect that,,,then they’re j… https://t.co/oOe4memMaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BGR316 Thank you me too. This is now fun it hurts to swallow or cough.  Poor little hunny I'm glad she's feeling b… https://t.co/sPdUHB0fYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another close game here at Golden 1 @SacramentoKings trail 103-101 with 1:45 in regulation. #SacramentoProud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a WinterBock by @GBBrewingCo at @gordon_biersch — https://t.co/vTN1ypY2Wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, thinking back... I drank the equivalent of a whole pitcher of tea. I’m so reckless omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “have you ever met a man who was worth your time?” My friend: “the black eyed peas”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles Can you do my makeup like that totally remind me of an 80s cartoon I loved Jem https://t.co/TIdM9A9fhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know that nightlight’s on when you sleep you’re not so tough yeah you watch Eat Love Pray on repeat  Like why, ar… https://t.co/8TjHVAWOy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Key states are providing useful roadmaps for the #GreenNewDeal to follow. #climatechange https://t.co/s8v2TQoSmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEBrightbill I was the the only kid in my kindergarten who could read and I read all of the teacher’s lesson plans… https://t.co/qkApBJftDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The "#Teacher to do list" seems neverending. How about changing the list to 1 thing - Promote the long-term flouris… https://t.co/9O6uuJzkHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you have plans for Valentine’s Day? How about saving 3 lives. That’s what one pint of donated blood can do. Stop… https://t.co/Jv0XZqnOi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Muslims and socialist are going to impeach our duly elected President??? We the People will not stand for it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Aramark? We're hiring in #LockHaven, PA! Click the link in our bio for details on this job and more… https://t.co/yJby8e1BrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a weird ass dream that I was chewing gum and it got nasty so I went and got another one and it was an endless cycle it was nasty]]></document><document><![CDATA[I a m novung all by myself again I could use somehelp HELP https://t.co/PRitVvUczt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Mexico Will Pay When All The Drugs And Sex Trafficking is STOPED !!! #TRUMP2020 #BUILDTHEWALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning I effing mobile ordered my Dunkin’ from the wrong place and had a nice stroll around manhattan to find… https://t.co/GgxmXckZ1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extraordinary funerary portraits of the humans and divine #duraeuropos @ Yale University Art Gallery https://t.co/GyWKqSxGTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RedWings Helm 2 tripping at 3:28 and #TBLightning Stamkos 2 hooking at 4:10 of the 1st. 4 on 4 for now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrisroach777 Today has bothered me so much, I can't shake it. Love you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@villianarts #tattoo #newink (@ AmericasMart Building 3 - @atlantaapparel in Atlanta, GA) https://t.co/AxNKh8Bh2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[tonight, me and angel are going to party because it’s the WEEKEND binch https://t.co/QvuLk4zPXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Postmates my screen’s been stuck on this for the past 20 min even after multiple app and phone reboots. What’s up? https://t.co/qltn9HOMvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when you try to go to sleep but end up chewing a gash into the side of your and only realizing… https://t.co/avknjP1J96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder Words won't do! These political hacks are bottom feeder's..Scumbag's one and all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see the beauty, what do you see? . .  It’s taken me a year to try and unlearn the fatphobia behaviour I was taugh… https://t.co/Qg0zxFTXDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the R Kelly interview from last night taught me one thing - everyone from Chicago argues the same way 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBeatWithAri @AriMelber @cthagod @AriMelber was my virtual tv journalist boyfriend that I never met. 😉.I must sa… https://t.co/eqafOPgpjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please me, baby Turn around and just tease me, baby You know what I want and what I need, baby🎧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmeraldRobinson Twitter isn't letting us see the list of Senators who voted no.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgallowaycbc Some people need to move to a gated community where they can really keep "outsiders" out of their neighbourhood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Q1:One of my guidance lessons was The Gratitude Tree. It is a story that teaches students that the secret to happin… https://t.co/EDbTop2Ai0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alerte risques sanitaires : Faites-vous confiance aux médicaments vendus en Pharmacie ? https://t.co/5SA0YZeEgH]]></document></documents></author>