<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I got big bills phone calls to make dealz, play ya cards right just wait til I deal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Roberts is now 0-37 in the Nacho Challenge. Last night’s defeat stung as it occurred in front of our idol and… https://t.co/jacqBeJTD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuickyBaby I may be a little late spent all night keeping a drunken munchkin from flashing her boobs on stream I'm a little tired]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday February 20 - Morning Report:      How the winners of New York Lottery’s biggest jackpot were able to sta… https://t.co/B7H35ZRkQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[How often do you type a tweet, proofread it, then delete that whole tweet and start again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It almost seems as though there are factions nascent in the GOP intent on rejecting the old tropes of the party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh shit i messed it up oh no oh mother fuck I have to do it all again for my best friend 🎀 https://t.co/nFe3b9x4qo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeHenning Dion’s “Abraham, Martin and John”  https://t.co/iSAbo3sMR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump and Ocasio-Cortez are both symptoms of the same disease that is going to result in America turning authoritar… https://t.co/pl19PvrlUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day for a tennis tournament! But when I picked up a racket, I was instructed to “gently put the racket do… https://t.co/IpVU7C2p8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m hella greatful for all my friends that I’m getting to see this week in Lubbock]]></document><document><![CDATA[More frequent and significant precipitation events in the U.S. 2014-18 warmest five years on record. @BAndersonDTN… https://t.co/9H66ih358I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDCEU Stop. Just stop. Please. Who even thinks about sex and the Joker?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpaceX Congrats @SpaceX engineering team ! I'm sure there is a ton of data captured - https://t.co/EOihkBjXw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worst genre of tweet:  “I’ve been predicting this” [Quote tweet of an article about something that person *definitely* never predicted.]]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brennandunn Those motherfuckers send me socks and other dumb gifts I didn’t want, never asked for, and I didn’t gi… https://t.co/KJ5ajbd5qh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats , Geneva! Bronze winner, Overall Child Talent! #talentincmarch2019 #dantalentgroup #singer #actor #model @… https://t.co/scT8IXLb7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@17LadyLiberty76 My dad used to HATE movies that basically took place on one set.  He didn't know how to say it but… https://t.co/NpCR6pLUEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh look. Palmer cites himself for huge breaking news story. Well done, Sherlock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mincanada @MAGAMOE22 @ChuckRossDC @realDonaldTrump @DailyCaller This coming from the person making this tweet? Oh… https://t.co/1B6UCiZxIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amadcartoonist Riverdale is trash, but it is such delightfully silly “I can’t look away from this disaster”/“i sho… https://t.co/UeKhJenCLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The GOP should start thinking about what's good for the country and not what's good for partisan politics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: SpaceX to Launch Falcon 9 Rocket #CrewDragon (DM-1) @2:49am EST https://t.co/QiPAwCAW7R via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeDeWine is now pro-raising taxes (an 18 cent PER GALLON gas tax) and anti-death penalty. It’s not why any of vo… https://t.co/DVI06ECPI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my kids can’t complete the paperwork in the bathroom &amp; call me up from the bullpen. #TheCloser #parenting… https://t.co/MAifZYtknq]]></document><document><![CDATA[6-4 MBA with 6:02 in the 2nd. MBA’s defense has been on lockdown this quarter. Transition opportunities create goals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKing Come on Stephen, as an author, use of words and meaning should have import. Not having health insuranc… https://t.co/XN1uQJGNMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work in progress, “blue heron” Rooted Ground series cigar box. #blue #blueheron #bird #floridabirds… https://t.co/I7YWNrnrCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have seen multiple posts to that effect but have not been able to verify- doubt it or it would increase the media… https://t.co/gVZujjIxqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mulaney 👏🏽😂💯 it’s always a great time watching you perform @mulaney can’t wait till Mar 2nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y TODO GRACIAS A LEO DAN, TE HE PROMETIDOOOOO QUE TE VOYY A OLVIDARRRRRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krtexxx In the other 50% they attend an academic program that roughly correlates with the Japanese curriculum, and… https://t.co/HiWljKuMUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dralysalucas @achastain1535 @nattynatwiesty Thanks for having me. Had a great time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders will be a good president for United states of America..his thoughts are similar to Andres Manuel Lop… https://t.co/T7FFU1KXeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScotsFyre @AllianceDefends @ValRichardson17 @WashTimes He doesn’t have to refuse service in his business to freely… https://t.co/XMyNkEJUh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, either Karl Marx and I are going to overthrow our oppressors or Adele is going to disarm our attackers with h… https://t.co/AV13RT8bEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take this W right on back to Charlottesville.. #GoHoos https://t.co/9z7oqwMpOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mediaite @brianstelter This is the funniest thing the @TheBabylonBee has ever tweeted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP Ok! We got it! There is a "crisis!" Why were "you people" for it once and against it now? Why was it our Repub… https://t.co/eR2NvlhTHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kevin's enthusiastic delivery of every single one of his jokes was absolutely hilarious! Incredibly charming. 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMarshNHL @FlyersAlumni @DannyBriere48 @Hartsy43 @BrianBoucher33 @NHLFlyers @SniderHockey Damn man I thought I… https://t.co/nJoQRbrUAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @dbongino @RealCandaceO @realDonaldTrump  maybe if you had spent the same amount of time that you did producin… https://t.co/xPJ5ZFIoIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliasme1602 Looks are just veneer. It's what's in the heart and mind that counts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KintzelSteve Thanks so much amigo! You are a really good player and a fine human being. It was great fun spending… https://t.co/zbsRu7hKGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtussell1 @minakimes As for making it about me, I wrote thousands of stories in the dozen years guys were going ou… https://t.co/wmpmP9GnBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lordmahammer L'affaire Tapie a très, très fortement contribué à me faire quitter le pays. Bien sur qu'il apparaît… https://t.co/jJSm753o18]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amahdy What narrative? Isn't it the Steelers job to understand who they're doing business with?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Algunas foticos del partido de este viernes entre #México y #Uruguay  #FIBA #WorldCup #China2019 #Qualifers… https://t.co/fst50MMnAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good move by @dcexaminer if they did in fact cancel their sponsorship. https://t.co/xM7VU6aRQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[19’ so far this month. A new record for feb - 1/2 way through! @ Squaw Valley, Lake Tahoe https://t.co/SC3dj0xPY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snapshot of last night's Shenanigans Main Event Fun times in the Five-O!!#gofastturnleft #racing @ Havasu 95 Speedw… https://t.co/Zu3gRJXqAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gym is no place for judging...BUTTTT, dudes who go super fast on the elliptical, ya’ll look stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chicago_Scanner How the fuck do you rob the subway across the street from the police station ? Lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we please get a coach in here that can land this SMU legacy? Please. Pretty please. https://t.co/C2hH7D7Bsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yea and it’s sad that mafia government still trying to hold on to it! #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNewsIive He can’t win period, maybe a woman will help wipe his nose when reality strikes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kevin Davis crossed 10K. Time 01:00:33, pace 09:38 min/mile, est. finish 9:18 am https://t.co/1LpAU74tVu #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quig53 @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump they didn't just give it to her, She got  voted in, by stupid anti Americans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Act your age What does that mean, anyway? @ The Vault San Marcos https://t.co/PNZJFArJBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hey mike, wanna go to the super cross next weekend?” Is that a real question, fucking a right I wanna go to the super cross]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boredom of Winter... conducting official Taste Test of @TillamookCheese aged cheddar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that @jackieevancho didn't even make the #AGTChampions finals is a crime against music, talent competition… https://t.co/iWz0upIZTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you decided to not watch the hearing and think Michael Cohen is a lowlife scumbag I get it. But you choose to wa… https://t.co/KQ7VjkT0dM]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I project potential #Eagles compensatory picks for 2020 if these guys leave (Note: Teams only get four comp pic… https://t.co/P2h2QOPtze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennaLaineESPN @vxmcclure23 This should be the BIGGEST NO BRAINER in free agency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be sorry this is so sexy and Hot I love it 🥰 would love see more with you and me support you be my sexy woman… https://t.co/x41HNnJOP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianferrara @TysonApostol I don't think you want to let them see each other. Let them all think the production forgot about them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The number of people in the replies who can have a one-hand follow through be a 375 ft double: 0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys i have my very first YouTube video "first time doing makeup" go check it out i know it will b fun for many of… https://t.co/8rqgWlK1BF]]></document><document><![CDATA[One final share from Night at the Museum. The T-Rex! Rawr! 🦖 @amnh #latergram @ David H. Koch Dinosaur Wing, AMNH https://t.co/mXwm1ZMSvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inezrussell @haussamen @RepTorresSmall @AOC I also recall that Teague had a few issues with his business and the f… https://t.co/cWqB58MECG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Oh you weren't misinterpreted at all. We heard you loud and clear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh I would say psychiatrically incapacitated defines this President perfectly! Invoke the 25th before our country is destroyed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squidster18 @TH_snuggs @B_Stones1 @TPHaupt @dstones77 @CShankOfficial https://t.co/PvbgE5TO2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[😎 #Trump #Trump2020 #TrumpMemes #TonyLeeHamilton #DigitalMarketingVeteran #Crushingit10X @ Washington, District of… https://t.co/stwvvIlma2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legit stop wasting good food #rhobh all that arguing and now you are all starving and hangry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexbradwayy That’s a commitment I could never make, honestly Chinese food is to important]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giantswfan @NECsports @espn As usual, terrific job again this season Paul! Go Knights!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CoachNelly_ Great staff,, 1st class individuals that love the game...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Answers: - Malakoplakia - Michaelis-Guttman bodies - all of the above - Abnormal lysosomes - Phosphate - Von Hansemann]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dick_nixon Have their constituents really been disenfranchised any more than they were before?  That being said, i… https://t.co/hpAaeF5qrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was a very moving experience for me. I’ve been wanting to come and pay my respects ever since the night of the… https://t.co/VSlJ3sQtZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today @roseygirlx109 told me if she was ever murdered, she hoped that could be murdered together, because she thoug… https://t.co/o31gWPdiZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2Sally @KPRC2 Very sad day people who work in the aviation industry]]></document><document><![CDATA[6  state titles for Wenonah HS(AL) Boys  (1990, 1993, 2011, 2012, 2013, 2019). … 1 – in-state loss for the Dragons… https://t.co/ROxu3xTnOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netsfan3 @hardball @JulianCastro No, you are just antiquated and out of touch… A.k.a. old fart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbnauman @DilaraEsengil @libbytard @1Liberty_Lady @davidf4444 @traybishop @england498 @bluridg4 @m_stewart_paine… https://t.co/yphEcfJihN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Ever wonder why they are always at the top of the Greatest President of all times fees… https://t.co/n1QF5x6Hl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Wage Growth Hits Highest Level in Over a Decade https://t.co/rsv5507wkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LanaWWE @LanaWWE , you have every right to speak in your own Salty way. Say what you want and Say FU to the rest w… https://t.co/8NqdHSYuFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HSN  There is nothing flexible or affordable about a filter that costs 70.00 to replace,seriously now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilibellmia @BigBrotherGOD1 Citizens need to be able to challenge the fitness of judges to sit on the bench withou… https://t.co/VdIbicTLEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Santa Monica's continual descent into a haven for tech bros saddens you as much as it does me, I hope you'll sto… https://t.co/0icwaL2Z2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[occasionally i get the urge to use curiouscat again, but i haven’t used it in like 2 years and the last stuff i rem… https://t.co/ApHvyVtFTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished running 3.10 miles in 27m:35s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/6oH3L85N3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamuelTracy This is one of the nicest things anyone has ever said to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods First sentence from a cheater, "He/she is just a friend."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spectrum quietly tries a la carte TV streaming, but restrictions apply | TechHive https://t.co/HG5Aj4djEL via @TechHive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 Well there is that sinkhole in the south lawn. Have you looked there?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tired of politicians campaigning 2 or 3 years before an election When they should be working]]></document></documents></author>