<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DavidAFrench In the wretched DC hole from Hell it climbed out.   Marvel rules.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @garymdouglas @accessConscious @dr_dainheer https://t.co/4NKCWHkGKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StoriesByEli @HarvestPM @rameshraliya @WUSTL I'm trying to find something concise and am probably going to fail on… https://t.co/m0CPbO6zqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @beINSPORTS PLEASE stop giving and $$ to Allardyce. The man is the very definition of a dinosaur. No clue on h… https://t.co/EmwIvwhLbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_pinales @Javier44130014 @daviddscotty @TwitterSupport @Twitterhelp Bitch ass nigga Sam always snitching on gang]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serena williams let a spoiler slip for #EndGame (spoiler warning) https://t.co/8lfi1574d3]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you could let me know I have went on the website but I have trouble being able to contact anyone I don't know wh… https://t.co/WYc1omBvR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cellmavin @Stef_Pellerin @cedarflats @OkiTimes @JonMontag @DaveK72 @zappafaye @lhtetrick @Just4BeerLovers… https://t.co/Biz0sn2KF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifesafeast @ForecasterEnten @neeratanden White evangelicals have spent over a century developing biblical interpr… https://t.co/3VFFWb2w33]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bea73 "Happy to help! Can we see how we fit into your 3 year plan? Maybe give us your current version and the vers… https://t.co/eT8q9F0VhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNTDrew The EA forms are broken and unusable on mobile.  I’m not going to have access to a computer while playing console.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNMcGee I heard that and Wayne's World Reunion were definitely the highlights..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Text FuSioN to 545454 for VIP. For a Free Bday Table 404.576.8471  We are different..PERIOD!  The Vibe is Crazy… https://t.co/HN1aEizp2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young hoopers if you see the “guard hand” up APPLY PRESSURE immediately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CuyahogaRiver #WaterFalls at @Metro_Parks’ Gorge #MetroPark. 💦   https://t.co/4JjeWDDefV https://t.co/tYmSYWd4Nv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveWAFB June 25–LSU wins its seventh CWS finishing a two-game sweep of UCLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/2 what makes it funny is the RP has many lower middle old people who have very little but fear they will lose it… https://t.co/sfzAT2t7nq]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're new to the Dave Matthes Literary Train, that's very, very okay. We're taking on new passengers every day,… https://t.co/Dha3VeWKbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger You sure sons and act Guilty, those little palms all sweaty, RESIGN NOw and maybe stay out of jail!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I probably shouldn't say it What I'm about to say..  We could make a comeback if you come back We were on top of th… https://t.co/3hx1WADDgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Phx Sky Harbor Airport on our way to LA.  My wife won a contest on NewsChannel 12 (NBC) to go to Hollywood and g… https://t.co/yxcErmYzAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning lift complete. Emphasis on heavy arms. Got in 130 push-ups and 300 sit-ups also. #OutWorkYesterday...… https://t.co/2f3ANEcnvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @accrosbie to post pictures of my 7 favorite books, no reviews needed. Each day, I’ll chall… https://t.co/ZEK9PQ8Xio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sulfer Creek Footbridge #reddingcalifornia  #blackandwhite #photography  #lightandshadow  #patterns  #shadows… https://t.co/U8rYi9ZEk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wedding hashtag would be#itslarreanow but who’s  gonna be the lucky one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BonsaiBroz @FortniteGame @PlayOverwatch @PlayApex Well now I have no choice but to stream.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Graduate Tempe Biannual Award featuring Ulises Heredia https://t.co/KPQzFCbjPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolmassar Ha ha ha ha Their Batteries have been accepted as a proving storage source in all the wind farms in Au… https://t.co/Wrq87AKB9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hangin with the @CMS_Braves Jazz Band this afternoon... so much exciting talent in this room!! #MIOSM… https://t.co/2vzVMek4Ts]]></document><document><![CDATA[My lil brother and i are still up cause we was playing pub g da whole time and he air dropped me the aqua man movie… https://t.co/uJVupnT9DB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at the number of people still clinging to the bullshit lie that those boys were not mocking Nathan Phillips. L… https://t.co/B9QwABYKYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have been following us awhile you will remember Chansey. She was the matriarch to the Pack 29 we rescued las… https://t.co/MnkddxQn90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NPR It starts with wanting the big boy toys because they don’t feel safe. Then it is use the big boy toys because… https://t.co/qpcGBrWUQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump These people are not citizens and they don't have a citizens right to due process. There… https://t.co/1InRhgWIWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you fail today... Do your best to succeed tomorrow. #rinse and #repeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Fake up the Jakeup” was one my bro and i used to say growing up for some reason, idk i think we heard “*akeup the… https://t.co/XnJomfOM1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soir-Jour.... il faut ce qu’il faut.... pour avoir des soirs de congé!!! #Soupirs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m here, Pittsburgh. We’ll see if years of living in Raven country gives me an allergic reaction to all the Steelers gear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Naming my kid after my favorite athletes is gonna be easy since they both Russell. @DangeRussWilson @russwest44]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a firm believer that the issue with children nowadays is that they didn’t grow up watching Fantasy Factory on MTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly that D Wade shot was pretty dope...anyone else and I'm hot...but that's what happens when you go down 24 t… https://t.co/U3VojLzdpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MLSisBack and better than ever! Well done @mls. Atmospheres were 💯, entertaining games all weekend long 👏👏 Excited for what's next!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made a timeseries chart of multiple sensors strain data. Colored by sensor ID, which is character. Is it better to… https://t.co/6DJnAED83n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeMelrose01 @SPWTalessia @JussieSmollett Black Israelites were saying a BUNCH of what BS, stupid adult chaperone… https://t.co/uYPqg6nCml]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah dude, superb advice!  For someone who gives a shit.  The Convo is not for you.  Now go back to never tweeting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will win indeed because we are going to fight with you and as you said you have a 3 years contract.  ❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Lexi Fleming, District 16 Player of the Year and Jenna Schoster District 16 second team!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was awesome to present alongside some awesome innovators and operators today at #IFA2019 https://t.co/QtKCqu9oKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tfausnaugh I thought we had equality in America? Why is this holiday only for the women? Why are ya men expected to do all the “work”?]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% of what I post is for me God does over an abundantly more then I could ever ask for so...I know sharing is car… https://t.co/dp4bbAiUiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow, March 10, 2019, is the 85th Huntington St. Patrick's Day parade. The weather might be a factor, but I'm s… https://t.co/XDiKTtbvhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBradCurrie A3: As a SPED Teacher Aide (way back) I fixed several computers, installed gaming ROMs (8 bit games)… https://t.co/SUL8KTUaQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SanCadilla Si anangono cabeceara mejor, le pegara mejor, se desmarcara mejor, fuera mejor en todos los aspectos ju… https://t.co/VXqlxqHo4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@presserofOZ85 Love it but should have had a 19 pressed on it for the year! 🏒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mongogolf You don’t read people very well. I’m pretty much in a fantastic mood. You can’t do what I do and be angr… https://t.co/7x0kior8kK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out Malibu beach on our way to lunch. Divers were exiting and said the water temp was in the 50s. @ Malibu… https://t.co/pKR55tKA1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colin Miller returns to the #GoldenKnights lineup tonight after being scratched in back-to-back games #VegasBorn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great date! With this lovely lady even thought she can’t bowl❤️can’t wait for the next one!😊 @ Clearview Lanes https://t.co/MmCm4IBlvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Videos you often see peeta use. And ever since then I’ve been making strides to change my diet (which is hard due t… https://t.co/OKUKkRAyNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lorain's Daniel Findley is pinned in :34 by St. Edward's Bryce Andonian, ranked No. 1 in the state, in his 145 semifinal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come Support as Pike Takes on Sig Ep in BasketBall At 10PM in the Rec Center Today !!! https://t.co/2E3QXEjekX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BornFreeTweets @z0mbiraptor @SpookyMeylani   🤔🤔🤔🤔  https://t.co/nvWga8rlIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every disgruntled Trump staffer got a book deal and glowing media coverage but if conservative activists try to mar… https://t.co/iba5Bgp4dJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine getting an Oscar for playing someone else (who was queer/died of AIDS) and just talking about yourself for… https://t.co/6RnKf9SHhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post Malone, Swae Lee - Sunflower (Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse) https://t.co/htm73Dy0G5 via @YouTube  Such a catchy song!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jr_portela Pero las estrellas harían las mismas clavadas o incluso peores. Creo que es un tema técnico más que de nombres.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suaa__ age is just a number, jail is just a room https://t.co/YmjdjKii5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to watch @ManUtd win this game  then head to work later this evening for an extremely busy Mardi Gras crowd!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did Bring Me The Horizon "sell out"? 1. Lee is strongly influenced by Metallica.. 2. Only a real musician would… https://t.co/vsYax0X1Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dollyfarms2 u know ur a fan! 😝ironically I muted an ad for their new album today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaPennyworth @GGraphicsinc You two are making me ... ummm, never mind 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is humidity in Louisiana might as well be a fish! https://t.co/XAAJANbLWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to work for a place that recognizes the amazing women who help others every day. #InternationalWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @RepAOC how will we pay for your green new disaster. I guarantee you will not answer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoldyMagnet @OriginInsider Ive had the same problem with origin but was able to successfully move my game install… https://t.co/hDh2ICf09D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimberlasskick I just finished posting a Becky tribute video that I thought you might enjoy  https://t.co/YsgH3zi1pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keltkainenkukka @greysonchance And you told me that you couldn’t dance... you did just fine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about how cute it was when @adambain had one bobcat in his backyard. Think these two might be living under… https://t.co/VdGvYoGZyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuffRumblings The Kelly family should quietly fade into the background and leave the team alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 Great Eddie Murphy Quotes Yes he curses but as a teenager we were allowed to watch... https://t.co/DOKqXCCs3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always remember that a dog is still an animal you may call it family but even family can snap be cautious around yo… https://t.co/VyEETmuzs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Draisnumber2R Right? Isn't it all residential, too? No industrial or commercial. Just a mayor. Don't they know they're surrounded?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get the best deals on some items. (at @BJsWholesale Club in Pineville, NC) https://t.co/E0g9V6KI7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeymourSnott @HallidayDoug @JZ_Flair @JeffCapo @manielse @imthathoop @officialturbo @edmalik17 @MaddyABoulton… https://t.co/pn2khzTHpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smittey10 Homeboy got straight one pumped to the noggin in the final circle I already know]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the Mister Rogers Documentary. Fred Rogers was a gem and a radical person. His Christianity was genuine an… https://t.co/Qav202HqVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinWRDW @MadDogRadio Nah. Missing the playoffs is an embarrassment for Magic/Bron/Lakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe how into the @MaskedSingerFOX i got. Didn’t think it was Joey Fatone or Rumor Willis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAY THE BRIDGES YOU BURN LIGHT THE WAY. (I would have done the same thing, @monetxchange.)  To quote Robbie William… https://t.co/1KlYLi6QAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rapid application development with minimal staff in high-pressure multi-billion dollars heavily regulated industrie… https://t.co/VVcLsmR996]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@AOC but this shows you didn’t understand the deal. Because the $300 coupon you are referring to is as-of-right. N… https://t.co/vZwpWEoKet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como que el selfie, afortunadamente, está perdiendo su sentido. Poco a poco se está volviendo un verdadero retrato… https://t.co/qjaZirvo7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visualization   #bikelife #bikersofinstagram #rideordie #motorcyclemafia #motorbike #dieliving #truetothis… https://t.co/mBhK2DMQjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to send my MacBook Pro in for repair. Now I get to use a PC for the next week.  Yay me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily💭: “I once was sad that I had no shoes; then I met a man who had no feet” Unknown  #BeGrateful  #IAmBlessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner (@ Zapatas Mexican Kitchen - @zapatasmexkitch in Pickerington, OH) https://t.co/1FEIi1MHgW https://t.co/zJO8WbiB6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer Are people really going to spend the next twenty months retweeting obscure twitter criticism of oth… https://t.co/NJO8G1aZQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asajcampbell @DeejDrake Can you not retweet your weird fetishes on my feed D-junk??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECHOtheCALL @Kat_truthseeker 2020 is being composed as we speak. https://t.co/Mw7Zl15ZFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Iowa State team I watched today played with effort and a purpose. We fell short, but the team I watched today i… https://t.co/GVfgxs6gwn]]></document></documents></author>