<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jbwsgirl @tammierobbins59 @TravisAllen02 To me self made is when you aren’t born into a famous or rich family that… https://t.co/SzRZnwWbNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Massage Envy - Matthews-Mint Hill in Matthews, NC https://t.co/isCw7s5cbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Canadian friends would  not agree with you A healthcare system for those that can’t afford is responsible   Tota… https://t.co/2zPV1DSoIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennzzzzdall @brookiehansen6 @___cloda___ @Dexriah @ShelbyGrosboll @maisie_mousey I try to explain it all the time and their jaws drop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicenews Wow. Looks like Stone will be in jail sooner rather than later]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WriteRonni Hillary “loyalists”, establishment democrat supporters basically.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mythousandfaces @conrad1on @Equality_Ninja @CharlesKhanTV Not with THAT attitude you aren't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dictating a quote from @BCDreyer ‘s book into my phone to save for later, and Siri gives me this:  “There’s a certa… https://t.co/BlwtEzjWbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer After a few confusing minutes, the manager called my cellphone and directed me to a building entran… https://t.co/eVGYgYCS4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHIZMAGA Right?  Ugggg... especially coming after the beautiful Melania... good luck with that one lady.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eentertainment @BellaTwins They are certainly strong in many different ways!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @IlhanMN @isupportisrael_  @aoc @AJCongress @SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer  Quit treating @Ilhan like a child.… https://t.co/jYBhy1CO4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@W_W_G_1_W_G_A @RobChristie11 @comic_boss Rob? Is that you, Rob? Oh now you’re just showing off 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@genesimmons Now. Now. LOL  Leave my friend Eric alone now. LOl Have a great show.  Knock'em dead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnkrausphotos @Mimikry_ Yes fun and if Jim was your pilot he is awesome esp when he circles to let you photograp… https://t.co/e6VkYkHoea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowayjeff And I will.  I do hope its soon.  I can take pain but this never really stops.  I'm about to graduate, a… https://t.co/d7VK5PQGMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phil70279335 @MyChickenDinner @realDonaldTrump @HillaryClinton well get over it, it is called electoral votes, bee… https://t.co/ERkQ12DgQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Lilies and #Roses 14x17 #ink #pastels #graphite  #illustration #flowers #sketching #inkandpaper… https://t.co/c8JpvuxHkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbraclamLincoln @revwadegriffith So does this mean you put the LGBQT community in the same bucket as felons? Becau… https://t.co/AjGRXq8DXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slick_vic9 @_whoisashley it was my SECOND DAY at my FIRST job stfuuuuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[are you really upset with cardi for getting back with offset or you projecting because you’re angry at yourself cuz… https://t.co/trH0VtRREm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother is such a PC that trying to help her with anything Apple related is INFURIATING.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitivamente creo que marzo es el mes más triste desde hace casi 3 años 🥺💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePennIUP Seth, thanks for believing in me! Kyle, I'm out to prove you wrong, brother! Was texting with a Stephen… https://t.co/rAA8bl8Vbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[update: he spent a majority of the 75 minute class explaining how to set a table for a 6 course meal?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldiesWithRudy We lost a great talent with the passing of Hall Blaine. "Be My Baby" by the Ronettes and most of my… https://t.co/QxJxeEtQ2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[💚 mom’s cocktail table!  welcomebeads remain.rustic downtownpawleys #succulents lachicottecompany pawleys_life pawl… https://t.co/16zxONc2Ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever grateful for your words, Paul Kalanithi. Thank you. I look forward to the biggest hug when I see you in hea… https://t.co/KxjqSicKWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 year +, no bragging. Just thankful for friends that turned into family]]></document><document><![CDATA[When You Balance Your Life, Everything Becomes Beautiful 🌺🌼🌻🌺🌼🌻 #EnjoyLife #SeeTheSmallThings #NaturalEarth… https://t.co/gbyp7X1Aed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there any better feeling than putting on a brand new hoodie... the answer is no]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrBobbyBones @bobbybonesshow Just over here figuring out how quickly I can become a flight attendant so I can try… https://t.co/R1DakypjeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[one time when I was very depressed I ordered 1,000 googly eyes off of amazon to help me feel better]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wrote a post about my journey from training to be a cop to finding my passion in writing, photography, and travel… https://t.co/90l0cldyPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturdays are for self-care and drunkelephant skincare! @ Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania https://t.co/9y3XvvDzX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey reports say something different.  Hope ya work it out and u bring your best to Buffalo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really enjoyed meeting @SenGillibrand last night. She’s smart, a good listener, she was on time, and she was drin… https://t.co/Bq4GdqBEP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of 8 hours it only took me 4 hours to do all my stats homework #hellyeah 🎉 #smolvictories it is like I'm le… https://t.co/NhQEpAGvZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Assistant Principals Guide to Restorative Conversations https://t.co/dShn1tAEfF via @karaknollmeyer]]></document><document><![CDATA[birth control makes u fucking insanebro like fucking crazy dawg tahat shit is dangerous as fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I watched the bachelor so I wasn’t so confused with all these posts 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh, wtf is going on? Only on Twitter niggas ready to fight after they came in your mentions being disrespectful.… https://t.co/lO5guIfOeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also can we talk about how FRICKIN ADORABLE goose is?!?  #MarvelCat 😻 https://t.co/5bbjIOyVa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find the husband, vacation edition. @ The Neon Museum https://t.co/OgbPsLTMP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieDiedrich1 @JFKEagles @kolleensdancers @jeffjaguars Just incredible! Congrats to @AmyDiedrich and all Kolleens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giles_whitaker @MbQueenbee3 @army_bc @DKNE4Sure @EmmadeeH @Susanne09248043 @TerryannScott @blondedolphin17… https://t.co/cENxmP32Xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanaJonessss 👀👀👀 Let's Goooo  #NewHeightsNYC #GUAA Under Armour Girls AAU League!  @Zacchio_LoHud @lohudsports… https://t.co/ck0LOhLXBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoleeMockler How sweet!  Fits right in!  Those Mockler Bassets are the best...❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessestew28 hey just wanted to let you know that the format of this tweet is kinda off, maybe you wanna delete it… https://t.co/NhHtMQmkUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just saw a man in a wheelchair walking his dog and i’m really trying not to cry after i got a spray tan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannamariee_ @beautifulsinn__ @IRSnews Have you checked the transcript?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quote of the Day https://t.co/9QidgdK49u via @@Realtytimes. DaleHomesAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge winning effort in R8 for REMEMBERING RITA @OaklawnRacing!! A stake disguised as an allowance! Congrats to trai… https://t.co/4gBNfNkdHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[white people are the ONLY ones who say this and it’s cause they can’t make racist jokes without being called out 🤪… https://t.co/bXLySOVj9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIT. #insidejoke #thegirls #getinside #getoutofmyway #dcistoocrowded #lovetheseladies #spastic #greatfriends 💕😸 @ M… https://t.co/ItmDK6OYMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some personal news: I broke up with my trusted paper planner in an attempt to transition to digital, on the same da… https://t.co/FCZRWMYni9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resurfacing this for the kid’s Senior Day...  You’ve come a long way @NateSestina23. Proud of you on and off the co… https://t.co/3DwaWBBK0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really do smile and laugh a lot for all of these photos to be so serious :-) https://t.co/0eozoy0yhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ParentsLife: Planning the summer in February so you don't miss camp deadlines and best travel rates. These simple… https://t.co/K54LJzTKsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cops GALOIRE ON LA ROADS!! HEADS UP!! But they don't see the weed smokers 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@koshiz Boots, jeans, fringe, guitar, EP anddddd me. #Nashvilleboundanddown]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hseidner6 Cause his other Cassie (Cass) might get jealous so it’s on the downlow ya know]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz día del Amor y la Amistad ❤️ aunque lo celebro todos los días, es bueno recordar que Dios me a dado la bendic… https://t.co/rBDnl6FL9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a rainy day in old New York;  Traffic lights  Burning - steam  Drifting, shifting through gutters,  Electrifie… https://t.co/pgm8YAAWOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evidence Proves Obama Used Kenya as Birthplace Until 2007 https://t.co/GXXw5twowv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharlesPreston I'm 31, and not counting high school, I've had 21 jobs, 5 of those were full time. I currently am… https://t.co/q4xGGe9eJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@castingcallclub The picture attached was what I started out with, but you can check out my video to see my current… https://t.co/O1wKAfk2xV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoAnnDwyer5 @emily_rj Sometimes EMS, it seems. Sometimes police. Facebook is vague on specifics, which is what thi… https://t.co/9yvY2qVztb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iWILLbeatheodds @Jrue_Holiday11 @J30_RANDLE @PelicansNBA As fans, that’s what we need and deserve: a team with som… https://t.co/xJjrWO938y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Payless ShoeSource is closing all of its stores. Sad to see another retailer close. Really sad for those of us who… https://t.co/5SSm62T8UY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr And YOU can’t protect CHILDREN from getting RAPED in USA detention centers!! Hypocrisy at its best! Grow a neck!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My beautiful brides! L❤️VE Pics to finish off February! I❤️ 👰 photo by Lupita Ramorez #azweddings #azflorist… https://t.co/YsNSIAQcmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 But we cant keep them from migrating to conservative areas and destroying them.  Why are they so stupid!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the only one who thinks this to be a bit on the emotionally abusive side? You’re basically teaching him he’s go… https://t.co/v9cUt60Ui4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waitwait Dr Ben Carson because he certainly isn’t doing what he went to school for. Sen. Ben Sasse because he’s a walking dad joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[A reminder we all need that when you are striving🔭 to be a creative teacher 👩🏻‍🏫 that engages students by constantl… https://t.co/VDcTJEZ2pV]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever miss someone but know how toxic it’d be to let them back in your life?? 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first thing I tell Alyssa is to not spell her medicine and the FIRST thing she does is spell her medicine on my… https://t.co/BHf06WAgTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always been a meat eater but my favorite soups are tomato and vegetarian vegetable. I make no sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @TXCivilRights Maybe we could send a few to your house?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#beforeandafter #beforeandafterhaircut I did, I also did a #brazilianblowout on her #texturedbob #razoredbob •… https://t.co/JLPBM8pZd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Part of learning to write well is accepting mistakes are signs of growth,” #PatternsofPower]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo, fulano de tal, te entrego a ti, sultanita, este anillo, como símbolo de mi amor y de mi filedidad...   Yo aún… https://t.co/f7t1etnJli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Queeen_Aleeex Always wondering if I’m the only one still bumpin this shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dmack1215 @IsimaOdeh @alxfergg 👏🏼👏🏼 yesss we love to see it. Rwanda is on track]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing compares to seeing the excitement on your kids face at one of these events! Well, maybe when I embarrassed… https://t.co/21BNOVxRuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryplane I think you just summed up the American problem in this tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desert Wolf | 📷 @lujo18 . . . #joshuatree #desert #sigma #fs7 #sony #california #travelshoot #docseries #dplife… https://t.co/ukWtw56JwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌸Those days are all gone now but, one thing is still true when I look and I find, I still love you.🌸]]></document><document><![CDATA[They need to see #jurrassicpark or read it.  Otherwise we got climate change to deal with, let alone death by T rex.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @NRA Why would anyone invade? They installed one Jackass, popped some corn and sat back to watch. Vlad is… https://t.co/IVPhRsvtIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[$1200 won't get us even close to #1, they need to work towards something closer to $5k, increase COLA for retired T… https://t.co/b5fcl2cP03]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wyattamandaj Awesomeness! How empowering for students!! Kudos to y’all!! 🤗✨💕 #languageMatters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PPTeamCamila11 @PPTeamRafa @PPTeamItzel10 @polinesiosxlove @PPTeamCataSk @PPTeamCarolina_ @PPTeamAlejand0r… https://t.co/W24OhnemY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you can put ketchup on french fries, why can’t you put ketchup on baked potatoes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of West Virginia's 55 counties have called off public school classes today as teachers protest the controversial education reform bill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Lord, That You for all the blessings You have given me. I know I don’t act grateful. I whine and complain abou… https://t.co/2RpPYUAL9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I always lived with someone, whether it was roommates in university, with the guys in the dojo, or with YOH while… https://t.co/PpYjGmxxRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[What can I say, I love it when he fucks my ass #bbw #bbwassworship #monsterass #gstring #strokeitandpokeit #retweet… https://t.co/dOgtFANWKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh like he avoided questions about his sexual conduct with boys he coached]]></document></documents></author>