<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Had a nail in my tire, slow leak! Turns out I need new tires, CRAP! I was trying to wait alittle more!! Oh well got… https://t.co/wVjZp5rlcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadgerMBB #UWMadison win for the brothers you love win your heart love wins when we do something that is right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricedaddy7   Regarding your "love" for Gabbard:  "On November 21, 2016, Gabbard became the second Democrat (after… https://t.co/ZBhGkJeBF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtbauer WHEW thanks for the response. I was worried there we cord cutters were losing that amazing and generous… https://t.co/uY5SHm8OXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xeniadidthat @almondmilkhunni “You okay baby?” hell yeah keep going 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Sailer Will be working with y’all in the upcoming weeks. Thank you for the invitation!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelloAndrew @whydyouhave2BOO @DonCheadle @nbcsnl A group of individual businesses  that are grouped together to fo… https://t.co/5mIsSszLTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[normal #Christianity https://t.co/k85vD0hwsQ #Jesus #Christ #God #Spirit #Faith #love #grace #poem #prayer #hope… https://t.co/2Nke553Wl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wpschaub howdy, I have some time to go over act 1 with you to understand flow and provide my text, let know what t… https://t.co/W5DFgtZPwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normalmente leo diariamente la columna de @SancadillaNorte  pero esta vez siento que es algo tendencioso a no habla… https://t.co/TF3NgN39s0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essentialmindz @sflcat @LeeDoughertyIII @AOC I'm from hialeah too. HHS class of 06' 🤣😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hopslam Ale (2018) by @BellsBrewery @ Barnegat, NJ — https://t.co/yQrn7tdE4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, look what you doing, look what you done, but in this jungle you can't run...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a dream when the Pope of Financial Columnists, @matt_levine, references @TheBlock__]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's ok to call in sick to spend the day at home with your cat, right?  Asking for a friend...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best way to spend my Saturday night was watching @PanicAtTheDisco live in San Diego ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever shed #RedTears ? - Stay tuned for @richmutts  #Documentary 🎥: #DirectorEscobar myexecutiveroom  .....… https://t.co/lHMzAGjXrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tulowitski hits homer in first at-bat as a Yankee against the Blue Jays  https://t.co/kLnmlCkThD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psykter14 @nKeph @KurtSchlichter actually, when you have the superintendent of police (bases on his cohorts statements) saying his motives]]></document><document><![CDATA[I taught myself to switch bat because of @PeteRose_14 my god. #LetPeteIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kgilstrap13 Gonna read this already knowing I’m going to have very STRONG feelings about the topic]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Blind Prince #TheLiarPrincessAndTheBlindPrince https://t.co/qo7hQhU9uc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The audits show that the same systemic issues have been around for over twenty years. Our most vulnerable deserve a… https://t.co/HfWuCA9IOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@King_Ponder Lmfaoooooo there's this one girl there I hate I should offer to pick up her trip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHSchwartz @NYCTSubway Yeah... I've had shit like that happen too. Sucks so terribly to be waiting and waiting for… https://t.co/26HPOlAyOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LDashti7 @ShelbyProbably @kallispolis @Sw0rd0fjustice 🧛🏻‍♂️🖤 #hellyas #hateyouguys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tan123 @FriendsOScience And just before Copernicus and Darwin, how many scientists do you think could be found que… https://t.co/vKGJ85MsGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me coming back to my friends after a puke and rally like nothing happened:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanRichards Thought I would, but it’s working well &amp; quicker paced]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're reading this, you have helped me reach 300 followers and counting! I know, I know......still just a Twitt… https://t.co/I8LquyBrWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to announce that Lux now serves 25 states and DC. We’re just getting started.  #gogreen #gosolar… https://t.co/pbGW4hWnIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of luck to all the candidates in @TweetWorcester that will pull papers to run for office this year.  You will… https://t.co/pZryJ7iohS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This—is inspiring.  I’m on my way to Olan Mills right now to take some portraits with my cat Qi’ra—and some lasers—… https://t.co/JmPYYtCPoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willy2625 I know I get in the way sometimes (all the times!) but I hope it’s worth it for the coverage]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate doing my laundry because when I have WAY too many clothes and literally have nowhere to put them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thistallawkgirl It's true.  The War on Christmas taught us all not to underestimate a "culture that rewards victim… https://t.co/zHFUpCKPWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm now going to write a nice little epic - stream of thought, no word or autocorrect or check spell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone has human heads in their closet. And I’m finally finally listening to @TheBloggess read Furiously Happy @audible_com]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisterRedlegs Fair point. A week of camp has felt like a month already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mitch_Terrell I understand your perspective, and I truly do appreciate your detailed perspective/response, but we… https://t.co/N4urhLFIRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hawryluk_Hive @N6rthern https://t.co/6hGWQRhQEs 38 seconds is all I thought of]]></document><document><![CDATA[dianne told me I look like the ‘crack child’ from beautiful boy today ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_Katzman83 Considering that it's only 3 people and they're probably basing it on that, I'm not surprised. True th… https://t.co/K5xp8ObnPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stlpcs @elagrew @roddy202620 @rosered2020 @garway95 @ctanner3 @DaleRobin_ @Josearoni10 @jujube1027 @BerryTessie… https://t.co/QDi0dmEqZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick breakfast and social time with friends in Durham. Almost time to take @amtrak back to Raleigh! . #dkb2019… https://t.co/wc9ujlCQmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t help but feel horrible for everyone involved in last nights crash with Coach Boeheim. #tragic #OrangeNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@limanichris @joe_gutowski Let’s just say I’m not upset if these are my options. All of these have a special place in bat heaven.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are you Alabama??? @AlabamaSenate @AGSteveMarshall @GovernorKayIvey  #saveindependentpharmacy #stopPBMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[STATE GIRLS’ BASKETBALL RANKINGS  Palmyra girls (16-10) receive honorable mention votes in 5A. First-round opponent… https://t.co/zifVrc41yP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tshillings @underwoodgtm Thanks. She's bummed. She tried, but got sick again on the way. Back in bed now. We'll ro… https://t.co/rGg5ZqnSE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, I didn't plan on it but I went to a smash tournament today at @SaloonDoor and it was really fun! Didn't bring… https://t.co/TqfmiYH5CQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful to have a pro with @andyaustinmaine’s talent on the mic for our inaugural events! #BullringBash]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodzillaMindset this is so insanely fucked up I don't even know where to begin. What constitutes being a "Criminal… https://t.co/iobp6nwwlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danaemadeleine8 SAME! Netflix dropped an announcement trailer so it’s already in production and Anthony Mackie is… https://t.co/b9oalDWtaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FridayThoughts 350 million ppl in the #USA and the average #income is around 50gs so taxes come out to about 6 tri… https://t.co/uTaPADok3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[KaeperPOS done played y’all. 😂😂😂you thought he really cared. He wants paid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MELROSE100krs Idk Zach had that in him, he was always so chill at school 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyGuad @MarkMcLain @tymmoss @LeftofStr8 @MichaelVaccaro @sudirick @GaydarGun @GarrettsHot @VPCOWBOY1… https://t.co/EoRclG4PRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dope song tho🤷🏽‍♀️ 6ix9ine Gifts Dj Akademiks A Song For his Birthday - 6ix9ine Lanes https://t.co/YteDBKRfqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#painting. @procreate #MaxU #chunky #wet #acrylic. @maxulichney  #art #color #ipadpro #applepencil @ Atelier Crashc… https://t.co/RpnHQpLv7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foticos de la acción en el juego entre @rayados y @alianzafc_sv  #Rayados #Monterrey #LaPandilla #Alianza #Concacaf… https://t.co/24iqgoJO0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B2BSeth @PBTaxAccounting @davidleary @joewoodard You won’t hear much. Rumor has it that Intuit told the Top 75 Pro… https://t.co/1n6m5MtkcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌷🍄🌷Will a lion roar in the forest, when he hath no prey? will a young lion cry out of his den, if he have taken nothing? Amos 3:4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spookymeaghan @FredCStresing Pshhhhhh. They know they have to bring out the big guns to get people to go to that park.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve wanted to live in LA for as long as I can remember. Two years ago I was at one of the lowest points of my life… https://t.co/MP55iMDqSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskTSA @DENAirport @WhoaItsJoel How are the lines?  Should I use the alternate security route?  Thoughts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Dark Lord - Marshmallow Handjee (2018) by @3floyds @ Hunahpu’s Day 2019 — https://t.co/znCTjfDU89]]></document><document><![CDATA[Americans should consider insisting that Conflict of Interests become an Olympics event.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evonne28 @BrianDunseth @AricaKress @ColumbusCrewSC @kylemartino Yes!  Give me the whistle, cards and VAR😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithpape Love this!! Would make a great slideshow on the Echo Show in our kitchen. Going to try it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattMackowiak He should not have insulted Brooklyn like that. Queens would be a different story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joined American business leaders at the @USChamber for a roundtable discussion on opportunities and challenges to i… https://t.co/wjywa2j7BO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss storm chasing. I miss working.  Yesterday I couldn't even lift a pencil w/out tearing up (side effects of ch… https://t.co/jegamdJAJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful mellow hike last night. Fun to see it staying light later; a harbinger of Spring. // @bitsonbits https://t.co/CuRtaJWKJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could watch all day L O N G James! Tks 4 gettin my ☔️ rainy/cold 🥶 Monday started off right! She wifey material 4… https://t.co/qvgssVXTG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@knowroaming Sim switch before I get on the plane 🛫 @ Toronto Pearson International Airport https://t.co/QmsKI1kJyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys night out consists of models mikes hard and singing hey there Delilah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jzanier468 If we're going to get fried chicken for lunch, I want everyone to be happy. They have some really good… https://t.co/0XwZf3Zls0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweets for swine: Does chocolate have nutritional value for pigs? https://t.co/SxnDzNOjTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Is that some sort of constitutional requirement to run or is that just plain illegal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllEyesOnMe212 Morning DT.  Glad to have baseball back and some positive vibes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenergy__ And this doesn’t have to do anything with the event I told you about]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vmute25 @Connor_J_Hughes @tym2g3thi From college he was 3-4 olb. Vikings still drafted him and used him as 4-3 pretty versatile guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[100 bad days made a hundred good stories, 100 good stories make me interesting at parties 🎵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhoenixRane Sometimes I think it is even worse when one always plays the roll of devils advocate without announcin… https://t.co/1o1YSRnSTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, $10 Gets you our famous There Burger, fries and a draft Monday Night All Y’All brew. @MondayNight… https://t.co/8crW70Acnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CohibaCacique @zdiddy182 @UfoSunday @Chuckthefreak @Keithmayoh @JeremyCorbell @UfoJoe11 @SilvaRecord… https://t.co/B7RUKcBaoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[That level between kinda there to there when you start liking &amp; sharing shit of fb to annoy people #happytrumpyday]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a tough loss last night but the dawgs looked great! @ugaathletics #godawgs #basketball #ugavsmissst @ Stegem… https://t.co/k5ArJ17QZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stem_em @MrRyneAnthony Thank you very much!  We're a big-time Lego and k'nex family!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaynaeBishop @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump And #GOPTaxScam is ballooning the deficit so you got that going for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me listening to So Far Gone like I haven’t already heard these songs 1000 times https://t.co/O5AxznRQEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Get an Appointment With Anyone in 3 Simple Steps https://t.co/5hy7hM5QM9 via @HubSpot @emmajs24]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can a picture with a dead rhino in front of you be more beautiful than the memory of seeing this?  #Rhinos]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW HAMSHIRE. Très "pittoresque" et très conservateur au niveau de leur environnement. Peut-être ne le savez-vous p… https://t.co/69oiBdY27B]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a great article, @JHWeissmann Why is childcare so expensive? I don’t understand. Their  employees are not p… https://t.co/tdfNHxP4dQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just sat in my hotel room in Palm Springs watching Norm Duke defeat @JBelmo because I didn’t see it live. Great cal… https://t.co/iL9VRQ2BOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shirl032_DFS @FantasyGolfers Yup. It was something else. That fourth shot had enough speed to roll off too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spike lee is the most racist person I have ever truly made.#RacismMustFall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TristonMarez Hey man it seems to result in some damn good music so I’ll take it]]></document></documents></author>