<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Came home from work to carlos putting our new bed frame together, chocolate covered strawberries, a giraffe and ice cream 🥺😭💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I guess that is something. @ Hagerstown, Maryland https://t.co/hcTNrDQpvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moneymon228 @therealqueen_p I don’t know if I can make it through another week 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s treason and he should be put on trial for it!!!  These morons need to be taught a lesson...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimFleischer7 Butter biscuits topped with pulled pork, eggs, bbq sauce and jalapeños!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@El_Universal_Mx @Nor97442184 Poniendo la muestra nuestro incansable presidente tiene todo el valor moral y actitud… https://t.co/awz3qJ8g9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 77 year old making another bid for the White House https://t.co/uHSI1qhrb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jensteer They know it's news.  They don't want to admit it, or they say it's not as a way to hide their guilty pleasure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the man @reaganschommer hope 18 treats you well buddy! https://t.co/D1jlON7oKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lock them up.  Emails reveal coordination between Chao, McConnell offices https://t.co/DObDywZdog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KremlinKrypton @CNBC @AndrewYangVFA @CNBCMakeIt You can't guarantee jobs when robotic automation replaces the vast… https://t.co/WUmaESoMW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedraftsmanFB Or how bout this crazy concept... Jeudy’s fast too? I know crazy right!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: avoid the 101 west from cavecreek to 7th ave. There are 2 major accidents and lots off traffic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Malmquist!  From Chorske!  5-2 Edina!  Pretty play!  #TheTourney19  Wow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what our President is talkin about, Horrible. Absolutely abomination the worst you've ever seen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 (@ Epcot - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL) https://t.co/VqzWUdzV39]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKINGNEWS Reading indictment against #Empire actor Jussie Smollett.  Charged w/16 counts of making false report… https://t.co/doQfSCw8dy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are just plain stupid and mentally I'll.Must be removed from the office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[JAYARSON - Get To The Money (Produced By Loski On The Track) Reaction https://t.co/hTONFpLZwh @nolaraplife @_JAYARSON]]></document><document><![CDATA[ladies…………..I drank a lot of red wine last night and am now quite hungover]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmcin9 @ClementYChow @brandonscooper Felt the need for a long sleeved t-shirt tonight...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vern_Down4what @SportsRadioWIP Everyone seemed to miss that part of the quote lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@najeperdomo_  and I are having 3 different conversation on Twitter, I Instagram, and text messages it’s great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamBagni @RealJamesWoods But no comment on Victor David Hansens whole piece yesterday, she harmonizes with everything he wrote]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShhAssyriansSay Short study of anyone’s ancestry quickly proves we’re all one big happy family. I am proud of all… https://t.co/wbyNM6oWuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexfenton @FaizaMan42 @UptonCC Gents how we doing? Thanks for kind words Alex. What is it that you’re looking for? Cheers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CovenantHouse hi folks. I’ve been emailing and calling trying to get a hold of someone there who can give me more… https://t.co/7AWoxbcJi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganLHewitt and Sports teams usually do give players a second chance (unless you are kaepernick) but the media an… https://t.co/OskaTDVucz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicSerritella @NFLDraftBible @DraftScout But you don’t take a guy in the 2nd to be depth. You take him to compete… https://t.co/vhYbIfcni4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radiocoringao bola aérea nessa zaga é meio gol. Grande abraço aqui de Point Richmond, California.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happened to the great turf? @TargetSpecProd @TurfFuel https://t.co/SETACoqkTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[True story: My wife and I were bawling by the end of #Bao.   Really set the mood for The Incredibles 2. 😂   But ser… https://t.co/YnnOaNMJGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beware of &amp;quot;Yahoo, AOL and Gmail Award Promotion&amp;quot; Lottery Scam... https://t.co/yE25BXjQ06]]></document><document><![CDATA[“With newsrooms across the country facing declining revenues and significant staff reductions,  @knightfdn will inv… https://t.co/LWOKRZAEau]]></document><document><![CDATA[It'd be so punk rock if likes didn't show up on the feed or on our profiles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The .@realDonaldTrump Crime Family goes to Prison #impeachTheMotherFcker #MuellerIsComing .… https://t.co/ZLDoCsZ2Uv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conservmillen "The most terrifying words in the English language are: I'm from the government and I'm here to help."  -Ronald Reagan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO @realDonaldTrump Because calling somebody a moron amongst your like-minded friends makes them smil… https://t.co/LeuyJQcpQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is a brother to me.  I look forward to his redemption and comeback.  You haven’t heard the last from him.… https://t.co/diXdjmnOB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kay_suigeneris Oh dude don’t go all feminists on me please don’t 🤦🏾‍♂️ cause that little boy probably could say so… https://t.co/DaVsUsZzkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The squad, @asvp_banana and @bufe00 qualified for the next pop up cup on trios 💪🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Lil something for everybody up here.  I never tried old lady gang but I heard @kandi nem was on point. @ Atlanta,… https://t.co/VbkDKGRcWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ACLU100 at #SXSW is really bumpin y'all who aren't here are missing out on @oliviakruda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mainwashed 😡🧞‍♀️😡what are you people thinking to elect a person that hates America!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blacksmithing 101 - second class (@ Antique Gas &amp; Steam Engine Museum - @vistamuseum in Vista, CA) https://t.co/Bl4hFu8mkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck this breathing app that makes me feel like people wanna talk to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go!! @GamecockBasebll fired up to be in Founders for opening day! https://t.co/YCK5JEDMug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HDdoubletrouble @SomeFrancisco Wey! Ya no eres nadie, ni para burla llamas la atención ya. https://t.co/sJJnSJEB24]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbm422 @Jaberuski That’s a rip off the 23 yo should retail for $300. It’s a scam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al Sharpton is a racist. Why is MSNBC allowing this racist to discuss racism??? The individuals accusing others of… https://t.co/p1c6qU4Ewj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orphan Lake detail oil on masonite. Still have more to paint... @ Wawa, Ontario https://t.co/jgkAkbVQml]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to EP#32 The Scumstache of Masculinity w/ ANTHONY A @anthonya400 on the BarbacoaCore Podcast barbacoacorepod… https://t.co/AZJYmvJskl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpartanAvenueFS and the difference between him and ward. #splittinghairs #justsayin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway @MTA still no update on A/C trains?! Why are they delayed? Why are you not updating?]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy internAtional women’s day i’m gonna watch a star is born with my mom and grandma.. stole my grandmas  drip...… https://t.co/EJuwmQOMBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ask Bradley why he didn’t score those goals against Belgium,” a fan just yelled at me.   I get being annoyed with… https://t.co/LGZlPykz8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MajorLeagueFish Strike King cranks with Trokar hooks did they say?   Hmmmm...good golly...maybe Shaw Grigsby?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendOfMataNui @PRAISENerzhul @makutran Here's the image I'm referring to. https://t.co/snoB6DULWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought on price of Hololens 2: For accessibility reasons I'm normally a fan of cheaper. However Microsoft framing… https://t.co/eWVkubbZQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@royalpratt Every editor and publisher in the country -newspaper, magazine, online- should print out this tweet and… https://t.co/FLkc1nna96]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight slept like a dead person yesterday. I’m off the next couple days. Fuck it. Roll up it’s terminator 2 time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to hear @michiganstateu alumnus @brettkopf share his @RemindHQ story on this platform.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe &amp; Mika are simply jealous they no longer associated with President Trump socially...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bookishbelle I can always rely on you for bringing Shades https://t.co/MDcY70pn70]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mediotiempo Real Madrid!! Real Madrid!! Ra!! Ra!! Ra!!  (Medio Tiempo)  Así es el "periodismo" deportivo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley @pnjaban I agree with you comments but I believe the media helped catapult this rediculus attempt at hate crime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna go on record that the world’s fate does not rest on anything the Kardashians do or if the Lakers miss the playoffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPost_Brazille @Chris_J_Rod @triplesss1123 @nyfanin2ndcity @dfends_com @Men2Red Totally agree]]></document><document><![CDATA[#usa #ocean #nature  #perspective #composition  #instagood  #nationalgeographic #world_shotz #photograph… https://t.co/s4ei8qVJJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 men put in some work this morning at #TheClydesdales. A B.O.M.B. was defused! Great work men! @F3ENC https://t.co/bKaoyOHQaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking like Arsenal plan fi lose the way dem plan fi start lol. Towel done fling in already]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MondayMorning😉Learn Spanish at your own pace by studying Dialogs translated side-by-side with memorizing exercises… https://t.co/p8oAgektVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fsubones I tell myself that when I do Mania, I’m going all out. Then when ya put it on paper... whew. Lol. TakeOve… https://t.co/ktj0gz9fmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Great Florida Reef, 3rd Largest Reef in the World https://t.co/7rKhbkDOt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was my absolute pleasure @alpharettafumc. I am so grateful for the work you’re doing here in #BayCounty after… https://t.co/s9jcpoFuJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concrete jungle where dreams are made of 🚕 #tb en Times Square, New York City https://t.co/R3xvEjxEYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Lindsborg tonight for Bethany-Saint Mary in KCAC action.   The Swede women look to win their fourth straight gam… https://t.co/wtdL3t8eNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieDHondtJr My thoughts and prayers are with you and your family may God give you peace in this hard time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whiteboyJW82 @Gasman8523 @Dakexcuses @Marcus_Mosher No he had Antonio Bryant, Joey Galloway, and Terry Glenn .. no… https://t.co/YXR8KYiuOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quill_monger @boyroshima @BloopinDoober @ButtBoob And of course that is on a medical journal, right? Not an anti-vaxxer lunatic blog.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@feraulia Salam kenal juga ya... 😊  Tetap semangat dan semoga lancar kuliahnya 💪🏻💪🏻💪🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alguitademar Mejor ir al gimnasio y comer una chimichanga, que no ir al gimnasio y comer una chimichanga. Al menos… https://t.co/F4xC7L9ANr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikNak722 I packed a bag on a flight last month. Female friend shamed me so badly I promised I’d never do it again… https://t.co/DbhBbrNGD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Americans who are on the right side of history have already spoken Brian! The GOP needs to decide if… https://t.co/Bcy4g5Zlma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, Katherine. This feels so very good....what you've done with me. I hope you feel good as well and that your… https://t.co/hmfHxfWcwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not shocked but at the same time.... what a ki. https://t.co/Lh8M0qbO6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[can you restock your air force 1 07’s online already i’ve been waiting since christmas and they’ve literally been o… https://t.co/KtPxrXA6mW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bonnie_bella_FE @I_habsgirl @JLo Exactly plus be multi millionaire to have your personal trainer personal diet che… https://t.co/Qn844tHa4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[The flt attendants like our guys. Or maybe it's just me they like. Either way, I'm set for a while.#AAMU #Bulldogs https://t.co/nSc4VfgBdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ None of those examples apply because they are not members of Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love being with my people! @ Greenville, South Carolina https://t.co/D5nfdfXStH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randommusings89 Haha well glad to see you’re right about this and can see through BS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenRhondaFields @ShellsBells1861 Oh. The irony of a Democrat lawmaker, sponsor of the magazine ban, whining about… https://t.co/P4VUEILRzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @epetro52 on winning 3 straight State Championships !! Amazing accomplishment Coach! Well deserved]]></document><document><![CDATA[If European countries pull out, everyone knows Iran will  get nukes and wasn't it Israel's leader that said before… https://t.co/ph0ld1v9AX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excuses are lies that we tell ourselves in order to justify avoiding discomfort. Strength is built in the discomfor… https://t.co/uDiOBJeeml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Krystal96618560 @Angrypops2016 @BetoORourke Remove the wall we have now? This idiot says yes. How about you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@echriqui  good evening. I am trying to raise $4700 for 2 homeless veterans here in Columbus Ohio. I am also trying… https://t.co/hAZ0elCu0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateySagal Sadly not a thing. My only day off which means laundry hell. https://t.co/zHEmywh1k2]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK, do they do movies what are their names what is their Twitter what’s their address what’s their phone number wha… https://t.co/r8z2AAPYi3]]></document></documents></author>