<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[And we’re on the road again, can’t wait to get on the road again... Early congratulations to the @njchamber for wha… https://t.co/ZLYOcJUe3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out at the @chooseATL house at #SXSW. #atlanta https://t.co/RovcVzUzK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition Impeaching trump won't get him out of office. The courts can get him out of office, if he is indic… https://t.co/q4dyTbVBii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jerry_Jordan @DavidNakamura Or maybe you have no idea like David Nakamura what the hell you talking about so sad !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our first stop was Niagara Square were it became very apparent I have 0 skill. At 6 we will be on the steps of city… https://t.co/izsx2FU3ZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is pretty exciting for the mighty reading Cardinals!!  @ClarkCountySch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not complaining but are people that bad at driving in snow @ccps thought it was necessary for a delay?  It’s not th… https://t.co/IyhJvqUNKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@landonromano How upset would you be if you found out that muscle knots can be removed immediately anywhere in the… https://t.co/42e1BYQhBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/X3bXiT1EfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE’RE JUST HOURS AWAY! Calling All Women! You’re invited to Join Us TONIGHT at New Jerusalem Temple of the Living G… https://t.co/upSn7lCX98]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also don’t have to be to work early today for the first day all week..🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karinejours Deixa eu te dizer sobre as baixas: fica pior ainda pq a bermuda encurta a perna q já é curta e vc vira uma criança.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just wanna be rich af and support my spending habits. &amp; if a man wanna come around and buy me shit too. that’ll be cool💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Highest #Deficit in history way to go!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I oddly really love how consumed I am with work 65 hours a week is amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ❤️ whoever invented DVD players in cars!!!!  #GreatWolfLodgeHereWeCome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump @SpeakerPelosi ur so worried abt the taxpayers money how abt taking aborted babies… https://t.co/J7oQ6WIxfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super smooth results 💇🏼 Brazilian Blowout for Jenny.  • • • For appointments please call and book with our salon… https://t.co/gXwgr5YVOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoanneDriscoll6 @DaRefScottGrady Now I’m in freaking prison baby I can’t go out in the sun]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only thing i’m good at is letting go that’s why i couldn’t love u and i couldn’t let u know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamuelJComroe What the fuck is he trying to say.  😂😂😁.  Good grief. I he doesn’t breed. Also, why block his name ?  He posted it publicly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bindy_417 This has been a depressing season. A few bright moments but knowing what the future holds; I feel like I can’t enjoy those crumbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I laugh so hard when my boyfriend tells me someone from Yulee or Dina follows him and I literally don’t fw them or… https://t.co/JZUbkS4uCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all. This Khloe/Jordyn situation is so messy. I feel for Khloe. And yes Jordyn is shady af for her part. But Khlo… https://t.co/CzQ8rBL73t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarTribune Anytime we have received or ordered flowers from @ShopBachmans, including those for our #wedding, they… https://t.co/oyekyBPsO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[i looooove when u speak spanish n ppl talk about u...in spanish...and they don’t know u speak spanish.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was on the horizon for the past Council as well,@Town_Blue_Mtns unfortunately the funds didn’t come from Grey… https://t.co/5UU6t3jlPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelbypevans I do this, too! “Hermalicious” has been a staple in my house for years. Thanks, Fergie! 😹 https://t.co/jy9y0JWehY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/5x286TMdX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @MSNBC Oh look.  The judge ruled Manafort did lie about . . .the meeting with Russian intelligence… https://t.co/pMmO0UjP6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[jenny shot on portra 160 makeup by bb @gracesnookk 🍒 https://t.co/yPihlroVPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crap. It’s totally a kill list. #matildamaeve #gameofthrones #listofnames @ Casa del Dingo https://t.co/JQbGmVr8S9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @hprhs_tyra and John Kappelmeier for being selected as the 2018-2019 scholar-athletes!!! 🏀⛷📚 #soproud… https://t.co/UoQpGhuAw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s now demand for reform. And many actors in the system, like good mayors, long caught in a prisoners dilemma,… https://t.co/EzqhmFGwA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait for someone who makes you feel the way you do when you hear Superhuman by SLANDER. That’s all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally started Game of Thrones and I absolutely love it...but! Every now and then trying to keep all the people st… https://t.co/k6exiE2gG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[No se si es bonito o estresante estar escuhando a niños decirme: maestra, maestra, maestra, maestra mi papa..., mae… https://t.co/1ONtuFujJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astralbodies @carolynsonnek I'd never leave you off the invitation, Aaron! You have such excellent taste in caffei… https://t.co/XSzeHkKcnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alsadvocacy @AnswerALS looked at these and looking at other options..some are worked into clothing. The technology… https://t.co/UnHwm54luH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TuesdayThoughts  #KarenCarpenter  My TRIBUTE for KC #OnceInALifetime Voice Love &amp; Miss You Karen ⭐️💗🎤 https://t.co/XYsl20Pf2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Memory lane. What a time! @TorontoArgos @MattDuniganTSN @pinball @iamrocketismail @TSNChrisSchultz @brazley]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's no one else I'd rather walk....  Or ride... Through this life with than you, babu 😘😍❤ i love you! Happy Val… https://t.co/6U6QxoZNWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yes Democrats agree with border security—- does not equate with a wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cstegmaier It is full OS asbestoes it is like Naval Hosp in N. Charleston.  Can't be upgraded to current codes.  N… https://t.co/vSU90DkalI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dsquintana Prism should have never become a subscription a few years ago💰 📈📊. @GraphPad Prism is an awesome progra… https://t.co/OPJBufpb5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[This why everybody got the fucking flu. What in the hell dows Tennessee weather be doing? The most. https://t.co/fWKRsqrl8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@123Mitora Glad to hear your feeling better,god bless you!!🥰🤗Hugs to you and yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[east coast or west coast girl?💋 #california @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/5jbKZDhcg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good half from Weber State! Keep it up, ladies! 💜🏀 #WeAreWeber #BigSkyWBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terminal Breakfast. . . @flyknoxville  #Knoxville  #Breakfast  @trumoomilk  #TruMoo  cinnabon  #Cinnabon… https://t.co/hpwEmsjIn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting facts 👍🏾on how International Women’s Day came to be celebrated 👩🏾👩🏻👩👩🏾‍🦱👩🏻‍🦰👱🏾‍♀️👩🏼‍🦳👵🏽… https://t.co/QHjg2RV8w2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnastasiaSMihai @ShelleyZieroth @hvanspall @HeartDocSharon @ChangeAtHeart @jackie_ratz @mizzeyheart13 @doreen_rabi… https://t.co/Pa0tGNeL6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siendo de Boca, tengo que admitir que el NOB del Tata fue el mejor equipo que me toco ver jugar en mi vida. Verlo e… https://t.co/trjiBAPg0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go Algebra 1 Super Saturday team! 🎉  Loved getting back into the classroom for some engaging remediation act… https://t.co/yZZ7mWPxal]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶 we know we’re classic together like Egyptian gold 🎶 #5sosFansAreBeautiful https://t.co/skCMm2wO8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cillabeeboston @realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger Many people want him in the Oval Office and believe that he has is doing good for USA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Providing new options of care for our patients #clinicaltrial #gyncsm #endcancer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hippyplace @jaimec729 @bigredwavenow I'm telling you both that you need to take a look at both video's and see wha… https://t.co/deYswRNspa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachaelray @MichelleObama Tell me about riding in the deuce and the quarter!! Lol!  I drove one to school!! Loving the interview!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today didn’t go as well as I’d hoped, but I’m going to come back even stronger next week! @TCHSTandF did amazing to… https://t.co/ypKBEHxKVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go girls ! Sarah had the WHOLE CROWD on their feet when she hit that DINGER BABY !!!! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HCscoreboard Okay. Y’all have a 2B in the stats for him. Just checking. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mexican parents just be like “diles que se vayan a su puta chingada madre”]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s that time of year! @boulderfilmfest is in full swing! SO many amazing films and wonderful returning filmmakers… https://t.co/dU6uB9MNKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adorkablymandy @CrazyAF_ButCute Is your boyfriend 5’7”? Short guys get all the tall women...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words can’t describe how much fun we all had tonight! This little girl, especially! She even caught a doubloon!… https://t.co/atZ9Ui9mCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH MY GOSH! This girl could not have said I DONT WANT TO BE WITH HIM any clearer! Ajfjgjsjgjcjgjfk  #TheBachelor https://t.co/wxdJrdhXk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me in reading The Priestly Prayer Of The Blessing: https://t.co/rc3dFXhpyl https://t.co/OlrWpQDm2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #LasVegas, NV job and click to apply: Training Coordinator - https://t.co/sAIdwLVPa5 #Education]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to where my glasses upside down to see thing right side up.  My life is like a soap opera! https://t.co/4RsCeNs39Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished walking 1.55 miles in 33m:42s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/tgKWZMajZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adult quotes of the day...”there’s donuts in the lounge and I have to say no” “You guys have your jackets? PE is ou… https://t.co/e5M6b53b8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve just got a new #fan! Get access to my unseen and exclusive content at   https://t.co/oXFBcl6ZHd https://t.co/Mx8yUlHVlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jabu1ani You seem to like snuff films for both humans and animals. Enough already. Blocking you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmieJohnson @NASCAR The MAN. The GOAT.  #Chasing8 starts today!!! #DoItRight  @allyracing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rasheed72 @BreakingBrown Wouldn’t that tweet imply that her discontent for the person casting the roles? No?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoapFanForLife Yep. And I'm happy cause you got honey and your furbabies and your surrounded by love. And thats an awesome thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting: the House is now taking up SB 8, the teacher tribunal reform bill.   This is the bill that @BamCarney… https://t.co/XsIeeBgyNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi principal hobby es siempre dar todo de mi a personas que no lo merecen y luego sentirme vacía culpando a los dem… https://t.co/dohTqzbZE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at WKU L.D. Brown Ag Expo Center in Bowling Green, KY https://t.co/AVqQnUh9p1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I love @Natalia11 even more....she like the @DodgerA &amp;&amp; #OnMyBlock 🤘🤘❤😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[we all know i say the weirdest things and i wanna hear em 😂 https://t.co/gt2meebUUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely!  The Real National Emergency that would be addressed if we had a real president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just unfollowed so many people on IG and already feel 1000 percent better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelMiller49 Major hitting up of the gift store!!! Luggage now overweight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The four-day training session moved to the ice on Saturday in Scarborough, honing ice rescue skills through an inte… https://t.co/F20MzTV2tH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveTVShow I have over 224k miles so I talk to it every time I start it up and thank God. I also lay hands on it too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their should be disclaimers or some sort of heads Up before they randomly air those scary movies trailors. I get terrified everytime😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be still my heart, be dry my eyes.   This team has earned all the smiles, many more to come! #AllEyesNorth]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate short ass dry convos, like just don’t even talk to me if you’re not interested in anything i’m saying lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[On another note, #TheWalkingDead is literally a show about the betas or the world surviving the modern day alphas..… https://t.co/FV093rzXzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Morris Museum 6 Normandy Heights Rd, Morristown, NJ in Whippany, NJ https://t.co/mTftGE8LHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico I’m not saying it’s perfect, I’m just saying we have to address climate control ASAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate @Unalienable76 @realDonaldTrump Tough talking Michael Richardson uses his prison ID photo as his twi… https://t.co/Opn8PF0rag]]></document><document><![CDATA[the unspoken role of the president is to kill people constantly but we never talk about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy plenamente convencida de que duermo demasiado rico; nadie debería ser capaz de disfrutar tanto algo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just going to keep listening to "Say Aah" by Trey Songz on repeat. Bringing 2010 back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[guys are so bold until I see them in person .. they don’t say shit .. and then they text me after like “ wow u ain’… https://t.co/YgnN8Chpqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GradyJuddSenate  We luuuve @PolkCoSheriff  Don't we @mamabearwelde? 💙🇺🇸🌴👮🌴🇺🇸💙 https://t.co/zfKTb71MoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I walked 5 @CharityMiles for @TeamForKids. Thx @BrooksRunning for sponsoring me! #fitreaders #everystepcounts… https://t.co/FGpsJblTUL]]></document></documents></author>