<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Shame on you. You are a racist piece of shit. You are a disgusting man with your fake emotional outburst at the Coh… https://t.co/iGxIhJefgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lookin’ back on our Texas 🤠 photoshoot last week trying to pick my “hero product” 🤩 As makeup artist we depend on a… https://t.co/BQtQMoMO7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful South Florida winter day at the dog 🐶 park with our doggies: Susy, Milu and Hershey. Missing you… https://t.co/nKxz7YUzsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Security Officers - $1,000 Hiring Bonus - Ventura County"? What did you like most ab… https://t.co/b72gCGeZNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soyousay44 @WorldTrekker18 Via twitter bitch!...... via twitter remember that https://t.co/85qzOcyDKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’d like to say that BMW doing donuts in the middle of western wasn’t me, but ya girl can’t drive on ice so RIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MumsMovieClub Yay! Captain Marvel was sold out at most of the theaters for the showtimes we wanted... we saw HTTYD 3 🐉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RUDYINT45 @Police_SGT_205 My brother loves you!  Can you send him an autograph?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered for the chance to fish with Chris Zaldain and win a Skeeter ZX190 and more. You should too! https://t.co/waqGtoppFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you my love for teaching me about selflessness, community and the OCCASIONAL value of Radio Disney. My Basher… https://t.co/unkYNq2Ksg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahilkapur @PilledDem @GOPChairwoman Would be nice to have more GOP CONGRESS like them too]]></document><document><![CDATA[#insomniaproblems @ Eagleton Village, Tennessee https://t.co/Xd89IOhnud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamshatwo YES!! Sooo...Majestic without a doubt!!💓🤗💬Sooo...Beautiful to watch in flight!!😘💕💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFNYC1 😂Watching this w/o sound, it looks like she’s conducting an orchestra.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TarpeoDesiree @feebs1907 @NydiaRaquel25 @Mandalyn3183 @Glenda68336051 @Laulauthelau]]></document><document><![CDATA[#losangeles #friendsthatarefamily #vanderpumprestauranttour #villablanca @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/7jviPfkBS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished a guidance lesson on the importance of keeping our hands to ourselves with Mrs Garcia’s class. The sa… https://t.co/M1X8ND7B1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌲 We chased a lot of waterfalls in Oregon (January 28)🏔 #portland #columbiarivergorge @ Portland, Oregon https://t.co/M8DL1bUJ7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RutherfordRocks None of trumps three kids would be considered Einsteins. Like there father they also lack honor, c… https://t.co/nNslxVnq18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday Fuckers! Fuck some shit up today 🤗😘 https://t.co/j2bNvX84eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gnash00 @PredsNHL @BaileyLAKings @PredsNHLPup Get one of those dolls for each team we play and let him tear it up… https://t.co/gQIx7q6L3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guy at lunch: My body's telling me to eat but my brain's telling to go Jump Off a Cliff.   Well I guess that's one typa mood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yes make daylight saving a must we here in AZ LOVES IT * all states will 2 just think it won't tur… https://t.co/xrrqYeeAtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fortune cookie told me to challenge myself... so I’m challenging my lactose intolerance with some Graeter’s Ice Cream 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of @tompetty #thebestofeverything 💙🎶 Here I am doing “I Need To Know” with The Long Players in Nashville… https://t.co/Z24rYrMdpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so incredibly invested in The Resident  Logan can get it  Theo... like he too can get it too  Amy is the same gal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoxHelp Messaged you guys again because you had again my Wi-Fi isn’t working somebody better be coming out to fix… https://t.co/atKcSqnpIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHSBOOCREW I love these kids. Our kids are spirited &amp; fun to be around every day. 😊 💙💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinos and Dunes in the Colorado Desert: Travel Opportunity @atlasobscura ... https://t.co/9Jc1zcogHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we need to do isn't complicated... Stop the human traffickers. Stop the drug traffickers. And #BuildTheWall!… https://t.co/9G45Pbl6CN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRE_Go_Fish @BellsBrewery @badhopper @ephoustonbill @JonMontag @JohanBBT @OkiTimes @Paul_TheBeerGuy @wolv54b1… https://t.co/F5uPFDTiNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Praying for you Terrence!  Get well. We need you! We miss you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @israhirsi She can leave the US. She can go elsewhere for a better life. You PUKE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephisham12 @spinningliketay @isntshedelicate @marleyharper hello i need more taylor friends in orlando can we ma… https://t.co/GCGhXOwIaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrimRutherford @JMackeyPG What about water?  Will he also pick up water?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKsDay @katherinesergi Nothing makes me happier than the twitter revival we are all committed to making.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richlalove Jessie Nail on Clybourn in LP.   It’s $35 for that hot stone/sea salt scrub but they rub your feet/legs even longer doing that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t these fools know there are videos? It is astounding they think ppl outside their base will fall for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@firstwefeast I would. Especially if I had my camera handy.   https://t.co/1vy5yrOD6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gone are the days of casual Friday - now, it's M-F for some companies. How do you feel about this more relaxed life… https://t.co/QvqwzFxo5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reuters India: Pakistan to lodge U.N. complaint against India for 'eco-terrorism' forest bombing. https://t.co/2O0T8yft06  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[😱that moment when you find out @AlaskaAir serves @saltandstraw  in first class! 🎉 #iFlyAlaska]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mypeakchallenge @SamHeughan @jordana_brown LOOK WHAT FINALLY CAME!!  So excited to finally workout in my mojo shir… https://t.co/DLS5J5gIKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't that so pretty? What Bsp B writes... 'like is known by like' makes you think about it and want to know more.… https://t.co/OC1oDb4peG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JNRutherford If you are in the health science library, I'll be back to my office (room 228) in about an hour and t… https://t.co/aFHg84WUw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwilightZoneism @John_F_Kennnedy Okay, Bill has very nasty woman thighs🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you like to see the updates from the Photographer on last Dynasty here is his Instagram of his experience. https://t.co/Iydbqg4Jec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Galex5_7 WOW I LOVE YOU SO MUCH🥺 I’m so grateful to have such an amazing man, eres todo para mi bebe❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganOrtagus @MunSecConf @Lagarde @IvankaTrump @LindseyGrahamSC @IMFNews @WhiteHouse What a wonderful event!  As… https://t.co/W6NKLNlE31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drp29chev @barstoolsports @HardFactorNews I was informed yesterday dogs are capable of rape.  I'm not joking. Some… https://t.co/gvEvyWhWNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: @SparkmanHoops wins 59-35 over Tuscaloosa County! Congrats girls]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never forget that crab that my dad rescued, then my grandma accidentally murdered. I love u. rip]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a FFA fundraiser, students can bring $1 and wear their hats tomorrow. All proceeds go to benefit the Open House… https://t.co/zCxPLAVNCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was the old skinny , bent over, short black man wearing the purple pimp suit and purple rimmed glasses! You coul… https://t.co/mTDvzT8um8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump Did you ask Jared if you should use that fake Jackie voice when you are called to testify in front of… https://t.co/dUTOFYAQQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[What ever happened to #CriticalThinking ?   It shouldn’t be this hard for people to tell right from wrong.  And to… https://t.co/NNLub5f8pk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marimolina385 Exactly. I won’t name names but there are people we know who were SHOCKED to learn I have never done… https://t.co/qZgCUKCKJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APGiarratano @FlemRarSchools @klemerich @DrDeMarco75 @RFIShuskies Best of luck!  We will miss you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fucking hate the way one of my family members treats my brother 🤦🏽‍♀️ I’m livid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElleEmBoogie They were technically already broken up but it’s still against friendship code to date your homegirl’s ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptivatingCory @carmenstarrxoxo @TSRachelSmithe @supergirlstorm @AdultModelProm1 @Mistress__Kitty @lexi_cat28… https://t.co/1ifPGR4ztW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gogi house &gt;  Trying to get the smell of gogi out of your hair/clothes &lt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home sick, trying to sleep, and have received 10 fake calls in 3 hours. Make it stop!]]></document><document><![CDATA[To those who work on a university campus, there would be no greater gesture of love. Happy Valentine’s Day to all—M… https://t.co/aSAlW94GUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealityTV_Guru @chris07841 Me too! Erika needs to take a step back. She's as rude a.f. LVP didn't deserve that treatment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who ever in Milwaukee by the Fiserv Forum slide we got an extra ticket 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of Right to Read week, ”beware” of Daniel the fun-loving dinosaur as he roams the halls for Three Rivers’s… https://t.co/FNiBkjRM1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[We hit a few Southside hot spots last night and tbh, it was a fucking blast. 10/10. Would do again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm just tuning in now.  Looks as if the tables are turning @VPBorrero!  Miles to go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have two new favorite apps- One is @duolingo, where I’m reconnecting with the Spanish language that I partially l… https://t.co/n5YGV2TLAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[dreamt not sure if about flooding water rising house was underwater and saw a garage. when I came up you didn't see anything. 🤔🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[We KNOW what a freakin cage is! And it’s not acceptable for children, regardless of the color of their skin! This T… https://t.co/6dqNzpyIhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping to share more mrsubofficial love with #Repost mrsubofficial with get_repost ・・・ Sub? ✔️Cookies? ✔️Delicious… https://t.co/pXYm1NtCiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t mind me if you catch me listening to so far gone with my windows down and I’m dancing and rapping/singing n shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TinaInTheSun Same. I'm the awkward single friend in a room full of couples and now couples with babies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is the first day in weeks that I can sleep in but I’m pretty sure I’ll still wake up at 7😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pwallinga Amazing. I will never forget the dean at Juilliard saying that life has a funny way of working out. So true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's 2:30 on the clock after Sanogo swats a Northampton shot back. Taconic up 56-37]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Nan were talking about Tyler Herro and found out hes from Wisconsin and has the same birthday as my uncle wh… https://t.co/qY2JbggJjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenryCris77 Opino lo mismo sobre las segundas partes. Yo lo que hago es reírme de la prensa deportiva y sus exclusivas...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anthony Kim live in the house! The New School Rules  #MakeItMatter #educatorfirst @edmentum https://t.co/DHaoG7onYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mileysm61740767 @hipcated @thvgcess @khloekardashian well good thing you can’t relate because we didn’t ask if you… https://t.co/8T7SiRmWEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I found out @WillieGeist has never seen The Notebook https://t.co/TfRreN8QLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@actinginthelib @TLJamesA @JenGilbert42 @KASL_Librarians @TASLTN @TxASL @sherryngick @NancyJoLambert @lmsjanlan… https://t.co/fLxT0vgTaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeriLOC @MeetThePress @IlhanMN Unrelated subjects and you know it. Tsk tsk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the hospital that didn’t give derek a head CT is the equivalent to dburg hospital]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just made my day 😂🤪 the whole horseback riding thing is going to happen... you just wait!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kawaiinat94 @bcuz135 @TheBlackSledge @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @nytimes Because by shutting down the WH AIDS… https://t.co/FvamuGnZh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley @ThatConservati5 Our country needs to Pray   Satan is playing hard  and his puppets are many]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dan_Stereo @Sifuentes Soy Sateluca. See ya Sunday to settle this once and for all. &gt;_&gt; https://t.co/zDUNwP0s8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/TtQPC6JF5w I tried, but Molly Weasley won. #cheesechallenge #dogs #pets #rescuedog]]></document><document><![CDATA[been up for the past two and a half hours for no reason. I’m completely exhausted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best time to be up creating and planning is when most of the world is sleep 🕰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Camila y mi hermana están juntas en la misma escuela, hay algo más triste que eso? 💔☹️ https://t.co/fuUKTy6vzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sup @JuiceWorlddd your album dropping Friday is getting me thruuuu this week ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader not a conspiracy person, but theres lots of docs in from various sources on this. Im sending to you to i… https://t.co/kWJbVbWDqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Technology is wonderful, but can it mentally handle a Sun Flare EMP..? We shall see, that is why the development of… https://t.co/WK6jiCl7f7]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙 my Mom!  #mymomgetsmyideaofnoms #lunchnomswithmymom @ El Azteca https://t.co/xL9vITUb2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re the kind of person that gets an aisle seat then takes both armrests so the middle seat has one, please do… https://t.co/5HkhK2mVJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wbny Congrats Wiley! How exciting. I hope it’s another book or literacy related.]]></document></documents></author>