<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan next they'll spoof all the students you failed to protect at @OhioState]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #WWFNoMercyRules on @tyltsports. Championship Mode was awesome! https://t.co/NyPs8rVF3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got prints of @BethesdaStudios @ElderScrolls #Azura and #Talos today i gotta get frames for them along with amulets… https://t.co/nAcCtT45co]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody wants or needs permission from YOU! We can honk even if we are Horny! https://t.co/Brpah2sK7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all you must understand this, that no prophecy of scripture is a matter of one’s own interpretation, becau… https://t.co/mG0nM5oBXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tront213 @GemmaIsAFatCunt Me &amp; @GemmaIsAFatCunt https://t.co/Ldrf2ovATC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Strangers In The Night - Remastered by Wayne Newton https://t.co/LdFQqnPB18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Bolton - When A Man Loves A Woman (Memoji Style) by juancano71 @ Long Beach, California https://t.co/R3ZP4sPwsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericgitter @WayneCGolf Wayne is a man of many talents! And his wife is nice too!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScotPollard31 In today's NBA they'd probably give them a double technical]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSolobay @loc8ingoil @DogGilmour @EvrybdyLvsSteve He’s relevant for tormenting homeless people]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Their Own Words   #Leadership #Diversity #Wisdom   https://t.co/bxlFg7ax1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some might say money changes people, but I believe money just exploits what a person already was and they feel alth… https://t.co/le7qiyo725]]></document><document><![CDATA[What should we call this?   @SuedeThompson  @GroundZeroSD  @EliEverfly https://t.co/avAd1qZu9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kiley favorite crawlers are the red and blue ones. I ate all of the other flavors and saved her these. I may have e… https://t.co/uuS7Kiqipr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebelYelliex I've been following you for like a year , you're awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a delight to hear Dr. Andrea Achi speak on the MSS from the monastic library of St. Michael in Egypt (ca. 82… https://t.co/C931lBjA1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rileyanntoine @trishapaytas They were never her friends and she knew it. Hell everyone knew it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomcliffordcfc @premierleague @HKane Indeed the idiot could have sold him to us for 1O mil more than Real paid , I… https://t.co/Qs35ojb3P0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Saturday we are back at thejuicyboxbar  More comedy, dope comedians It's a free show, name a more 🔥 combo than… https://t.co/g0gtwlOhmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[There it is. Jason Johnson brought up her husband. That didn't take long. #AMJoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry, @muckbro16!  I just can’t heckle you...You did too much for us as a Star and our Captain...  #AlwaysOneOfUs #GoStars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@transitharmony @capntransit @sandypsj Correct but a one a day train isn’t justice for these critical pairs. There… https://t.co/fLAgZJaIR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fully support this. Go solar. Alternative energy from California. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarPanels STAR… https://t.co/nxGsauTwR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The parents should be held responsible.  No way would I ever allow this to happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mickeypg @NRWO15 @chebroadnax @TheAmz2017 @TrevorSamaha @AOC Yes I am glad. Would you expect me not to be. Also that was white on white so…]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍😍 @YosephMachado @Zuleyka_Rivera que guapas visitantes! #missuniverse #venezuela #puertorico @rickborjas… https://t.co/1fVoBgCRI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mel Kiper On quarterbacks, wide receivers and Drew Lock next #Jaguars   https://t.co/6Lbrhm9AVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman @Nurselaurel21 We could gold plate it for that and still be saving money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @L_Bell26  @AntonioBrown just sayin,  you'd look real good in a @nyjets uniform. Just sayin!   broadwayjoenamat… https://t.co/9zi849GM0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[The second best thing about having pizza for dinner? Pizza for breakfast the next day! 🍕☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least 3 managers and multiple other cast out near the Coco show. They’re taking it seriously]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahRa03053401 Heavenly Father Bless Sister Sarah with your grace and wisdom, in Jesus’ name. AMEN! #GodBless]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Big_Gross_94 @Ashuntag27 Good deal. Thanks Isaac. I really didn’t mean anything personal toward her. “Leghumping”… https://t.co/Xe3d5A2Fup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you everyone who voted and made this possible for the  H12Sports Academy #hulafrog https://t.co/USzAHezviI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cried a couple weeks ago watching Instant Family on my flight home and bawled like a god damn baby. No shame in c… https://t.co/zF6EiRdVMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/Mnj6lxql9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WHSBarronPride @JFKMHSKeyClub @ColniaHigh @Cranfordweb @SPFPE @ParkMiddleSPF @middleTerrill @JHSZone @JMHS_Jaguars… https://t.co/hRnchZ23QB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Climate change is a big joke democrats can't make money off of season change]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are off to Fresno for the regionals.  @AGHSEagles robotics https://t.co/zj3B9QHoy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casey_grey16 I had no idea. I know I speak for Brett too when I say we're so sorry for your parents loss, and your… https://t.co/f0eROdjnsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Side note: I had literally never heard of Jussie Smollet before this whole race hoax incident. The only tv shows I… https://t.co/knAJ8ogGxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In Full Bloom” The Anza-Borrego Desert is now in full bloom. With the additional sun and heat this week. This week… https://t.co/0YRqI4sHp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[im so impressed by the massive number of ppl that legitimately travel from the across country for @MLB… https://t.co/1a7CDZyNXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone know what essential oil to use to get rich?! Asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottAZSKOL @MatthewColler This is my point exactly. If Rosen waited to come out til this year he absolutely is a top 10 pick!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wake up and feel connected to everyone and everything and it’s a moment of peace until you feel the col… https://t.co/fAxx64CRhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattowanHP Agreed.  You just need to argue on Trump behalf.  It's a sickness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PetreRaleigh @mattzollerseitz @Nymphidel @sepinwall It's comical to me that the alivers all ignore the chorus in f… https://t.co/WUFHRmjlBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Pusch Ridge Porter by @AZWildernessCo @ Arizona Wilderness DTPHX — https://t.co/6qNqWZOFxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[New video out about Lebron and the disappointing season the Lakers have had https://t.co/9l57D8HpGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh man, looks like the Nats might need another outfielder as insurance.. any decent corner outfielders still on the… https://t.co/IIfcRZOgAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeRizzo22 @HammerNation19 @ChrisOldach @ESPNCleveland Great Job @MikeRizzo22 I thought you did great. Held your… https://t.co/S8gt847QK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@datcrayburg @fSANDMAN The lived experience is valid and true; however, its the reality of the reactions that I think needs to be criticized]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sink Or Swim 🤷🏾‍♂️  @TemptationTV  #TemptationIsland2019 https://t.co/REfqGJybtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier At least the younglady with $226,000 in student loan debt is trying to make the world and herself be… https://t.co/jicvlQCb9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game 2 of the Dodger Stadium College Baseball Classic... #ncaabaseball #baseball #dodgerstadium #uscbaseball… https://t.co/3Fieu4zqCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at La Casa Horne for the night. Feels good to relax.   Anyone here with me? https://t.co/9UgoSQOez1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's currently 44° in Oak Grove, KY.  It was 60° when we checked in last night.  Had to turn the air on in the room… https://t.co/z1FugV6Z2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Fake says the guy with the spray tan and cotton candy hair]]></document><document><![CDATA[No se ustedes, pero que maravilla es conocer la #CulturaMaya #Uxmal  Yucatán. #FelizDomingo @INAHmx https://t.co/D34P6005Qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the @Padres snagging #MannyMachado early Tuesday, with reports of them still having interest in #BryceHarper I… https://t.co/uCwEgc1I0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone should have socks with shuttlecocks on them. Best looking socks ever #sockgame #sockswag]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol this is just funny #laughter #tee-hee #smirk #amusing https://t.co/cwv4n7oKtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A luta diária que elas travam contra uma sociedade, que aos poucos está mudando mas ainda é patriarcal, é algo que… https://t.co/2GBrQKBoCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously @ash_brew can do it all, sports, entertainment and more. You’re awesome Ashley!  #ashleybrewer #abc… https://t.co/CcI9MpD9fs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rshifty lol yeah I felt like I was exaggerating the number.   Let me know I’ll meet up with you that day but I’m n… https://t.co/I0joMi5WDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettKollmann I watched about 5 guys in a row running 4.6’s at 265-280. They’re used to be a handful that did that… https://t.co/tAXlT0hnlH]]></document><document><![CDATA[religion is so fucking stupid. there is no need to violently dip a baby in liquid like over and over like that. smh… https://t.co/wr8JHHCXPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncprevo Also very stupid from an economic standpoint. The US needs more workers, in every fashion, especially wh… https://t.co/6j0CpK453j]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fav music has always been the product of other people’s demons. Mount Eerie, Cohen, Townes. That music speaks to… https://t.co/zEWyWDzqLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AniaBurnosN1 Gilbert Becaud, Marie Laforet, Mireille Mathieu,Mort Shuman Nana Mouskouri,Pierre Bachelet Sacha Dist… https://t.co/7hNUVkjLr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Not everyone can serve, i.e. 4F, and it is not shameful. Weaseling out of the Draft with… https://t.co/4s5YHAovRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merilywefall_l @M_SHIN3 @Brandoon__ It be the struggle! I be preparing whole speeches when I’m fucked up but then… https://t.co/IdEWUczogG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnhancockusa put that work in last night #office #corporatetraining #bootcamp #bootcampworkout #bootcampfitness… https://t.co/pEHyFZ2hn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoundingComics Well, it is. The way you phrased it in your headline is that it’s the only film showing in theaters… https://t.co/y9QDpNRSq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s kinda hard to eat clean though when fish tastes like metal now and sometimes I can’t even chew enough to eat a salad 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stocked up on my car wash stuff and I don’t think cstat is gonna let me wash my car until i graduate probably]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaTrillStak5 Aye stak keep doing your thing always showing love to the people with is more than any NBA players do… https://t.co/dpUVSYHcpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News How to Outwit Blockchain Analysis and Conceal Your Coins https://t.co/MSDYcWCHvT https://t.co/D3kn37TKtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theauntysharon It's all about the teeth ...and breath.Breath is definitely a part of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oregon official: texts show 🐷extremist collusion #Portland #Portlandia #PDX #HellHole 😈 https://t.co/gC3JOM9YVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bilthy_ @Scottyr12 @ntretts Martin isn’t bad. If it wasn’t for that unfortunate situation last season, he would’ve… https://t.co/NxzVvPvMNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ollie just hanging with Benjamin #dog #puppy #envywear #cute #instagood #petstagram #ilovemydog #instagramdogs… https://t.co/TRsUgzrvHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @AEARetired (Ms. Sommer and Ms. Nichols) for visiting with Sen. @LelaAlstonAZ and I. Your advocacy for sc… https://t.co/fZzhMK3dBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rt @LeadToday Most people work to acquire but the most successful people work to become. https://t.co/neED1Yb4de]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clement Nwankwo is just pushing the IPOB agenda,he is obviously the IPOB contact person in @OfficialPDPNig,he can l… https://t.co/gtZ7Ofymnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally finished season two of Making a Murderer. Is there a worse state out there than Wisconsin?? 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was one hell of a good turnout for our first PowerHIIT class!! First time for myself as far as group training goes… https://t.co/PYgxWTGtX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 hall no he is a criminal himself and needed to do this to try to protect the crimes of other democrats it’… https://t.co/QWCONp7Xx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericfosterius Yeah, bit regular meaning: an object or feature which imitates the design of a similar artifact made… https://t.co/ojnZr25CcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thuhJeneral @Rosie you should go hide from him in your closet until 2024. Bye!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soft_b0y Oh for sure! Who wasn’t in those days? Half the Bible is drama about fucking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kollauf @jessica_mattes @ryne_o_mite @lmehrler Watch one a day and then triple up on Friday Saturday Sunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lhomarramos @realDonaldTrump WTF r u talking about an unedited video? Please go kneel in front of your shrine to Herr Trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scali_gianna I’m so worried that Jesse Smollett thinks I’m a 🤡.  I’m waiting to see if he gets charged with fraud… https://t.co/UeRMFgOgy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle Amen Kimberly, Sounds like he’s playing from the Obama’s apology tour.   I say if America is such an… https://t.co/UAokSRI1gw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaneDennis34, They have MLB Network at the time share... https://t.co/3l8xOFYxCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎤 Happy #NationalAnthemDay. This is @KnightsSM’s Maddie Rowe singing the Star Spangled Banner at last night’s game.… https://t.co/gnyy6zYb87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Outlaws Showing support for tonight’s match from Central Park, NY #UpTheAnte https://t.co/RIYeC75K3p]]></document></documents></author>