<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This is all I can think of when I see a progressive commercial... https://t.co/kCTwUO7yJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicCervantes3 @TruthResponder @Tonya23622442 @g3man43 @whiteguy3275 @wellsh40 @barkhaat @sunflowermoon14… https://t.co/lvHCIYtZYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nightshift10000 For true comfort regarding future and escape from a world gone mad try this.    https://t.co/aTWpBZaoBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bellajane127 @Albybound @phillip_beaver @LisaMarieBoothe @CBSNews Or commit a terrorist act in USA for ISIS! Keep her out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuddApatow @carlreiner all his many flaws and being an idiot why is nothing ever written about how much Pres orang… https://t.co/HdIhQXQAhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[And in that moment she realized she has a stream schedule to follow.  https://t.co/UCq19EBAnQ https://t.co/1ORtQrjatx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backstreet’s Back 🤫🔥 @backstreetboys @ZapposTheater https://t.co/QYWenxEDch]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @Memphis_MBB open as a 17.5pt favorite over Tulane for tomorrow night’s contest. https://t.co/pHwVPZbzrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it passes it will insure his re-election. Lets see where it goes in the Senate. People want the wall. Everyone I… https://t.co/zr60H94IMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRS4bama @PRBrimFyshin @WarOnDumb It has everything to do with the vile hatred that comes out of his mouth on a da… https://t.co/bOicJlRrsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benedictevans Rip them all to lossless or high nitrate mp3, then get rid of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talladega Superspeedway, formerly named Alabama International Motor Speedway (AIMS) #Car2Can #BuschContest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plainoldname @RickCarpiniello I’m a fan 1st!! Bleed Rangers blue.  Regarding my season tickets , sorry pal, it’s n… https://t.co/PXxxtffC28]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're doing favorite Pokemon, huh?  I haven't played since gen 1. https://t.co/VqiBrriJrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMB_KY41 @SLessard People attending DMB concerts aren't doing so out of desperation in order to flee violence, pov… https://t.co/mJZeQ62X4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. Predident this is no longer about you but the elites in Washington sending a message that we w… https://t.co/439vMRXn1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KennedyNation @jasoninthehouse @guypbenson @GordonGChang @jimmyfailla @lh_carter @MDuppler @ScottyMarkets @FoxBusiness We’re on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskCiti I’m good. On my way to a branch to close my account right now. Since you don’t even allow me to get my my… https://t.co/HEOUYyRqNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanBixter @kwilli1046 Which is witch or bait switch Never once did the new gov say hay hay I'm gay on his skip to… https://t.co/N7j3Kxb7it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo im bored asf and have done everything on my phone 4 times now. Wtf do I do now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBI hello. I’m looking for a banker my account was stolen. I have to put money in my new account. My number is upd… https://t.co/pan6kChF36]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giadamatelli2 @Keith1029 @trishayearwood @KarynRochelle @matracaberg It’s too different skill sets dumb dumb. When… https://t.co/md4EwPa8BN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scorpions @RushFamTourneys Hanover is my Fathers home town.. Scorps Rock...!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if it is evil in your eyes to serve the Lord, choose this day whom you will serve, whether the gods your father… https://t.co/jLXGsOZwiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopChassid @brianbeutler Elad here blames Trump for liberal shooting up synagogue. Don’t be an idiot like Elad. Think for yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travistritt Have you herd about Cory Sorensen PBR Rider ? He came home to Oakdale California and some guy walked u… https://t.co/K1JBMY6Onn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the honor of being interviewed by the lovely @BHookedCrochet 😍🥳 She let me spill my heart about Yarn Punk and… https://t.co/vwj4YREgUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Chicago show was amazing!!!  @EllaMai, @KianaLede &amp; @iamLuckyDaye put on a good show. #TheDebutTour 📸 https://t.co/SKsPF2Xzzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7Chicago Gonna be a bigger hit in prison than he was in front of the camera lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steele makes both. Tie game.   Tyler Powell with the huge three on the other end.  Marshals up 45-42 with 1:45 left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So...kissing Kim's fat ass is somehow a major historic event????just don't sell us down the river… https://t.co/YLJz7vk9Wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join my team in @MayorBowser's executive office! I'm recruiting for a Correspondence Management Specialist in the M… https://t.co/N5XtAHejoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goodtweet_man @atMeghaAsdoodzo I think fraud continues to be a problem, it's just that the locus of fraud is not a… https://t.co/CU4LOYZdeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Richmond hosted the 2015 World Championships of Cycling, an unbelievably complex event from a logistics and securit… https://t.co/4rWu5ie8Eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kilmeade i was in Wembley stadium for the live aid concert... It was a pretty good saturday...and wet #BohemianRhapsody]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha. I have no idea how they got this boxer dog to stay in this.... #funniness #tee-hee #grin #clever https://t.co/WkMAvX3Z3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avon's Jack Roesch wins 3-1 over St. Edward's Brian Kilbane to advance to the 285 final. #LoCoMats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Romans58 @gatewaypundit It won't be long before they're snitching on each other on a daily basis via Twitter. The… https://t.co/yp7mgIsNJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[After P2📍@SAPCenter: @SanJoseSharks 🦈 1, @Capitals ⭐️ 4. 📊: @Str8ToTheBanc 🚨 (2:06/P1) 🦈  @TJOshie77 🚨 (3:38/P1); 🚨… https://t.co/vjsq9p02ek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join us for 2 #MiamiOpenHouses this weekend in #CoralGables! 📍 We are opening 1549 San Rafael Ave 🔗… https://t.co/JpC8QRZujU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impiri @BossMoz Hard work pays off, dreams come true Bad times don't last but  X FACTOR  do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenklippenstein A reminder that eating healthy is always more expensive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRogne @IngrahamAngle @CraigSBPA She's not on drugs she referring to Conservative White People say'n the nation… https://t.co/YdAwKt3COq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve determined my preferences on the first partner Pokémon. Fire-types have often been my favorite, and Scorbunny… https://t.co/4Jb8rwznN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y ayer leí un tweet "que raro que no han saqueado todavía" eres tú profeta?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does ANYONE think @AOC is smart enough to not be a part of this?   ANYONE?  Strangely quiet about it.   She’s not q… https://t.co/4V29DplenL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have purchased at least seven neck pillows, because I never remember to bring my neck pillow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the @AugustaRnchGolf @PGAjrLeague team!  Sign up today at https://t.co/lsyrdDkcRz. https://t.co/kaz2MPm0Br]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angcould @TaylorREIGNXXX I cut my all facial hair off for the first time in two years. Haha I’m in a idk this person phase]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RediTlhabi Indeed @pierredevos, twitter (properly used) is a 21st century salon of infinite size where one’s nurtu… https://t.co/VBZz8oHFui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do we travel in a Blizzard to watch the  @HuskerHoops tomorrow afternoon! You know I love watching  Husker Hoops! https://t.co/87TgBhmWNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Anti-Christ is a projected image. He’s got a voice to talk. To blaspheme God. What does blaspheme God mean...To… https://t.co/LxOXijfzfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get comments like you have received, you are directly over the target.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BelleriaCanfld @BelleriaItalia #cornersburg #canfield savings for your #Valentine https://t.co/sF0shJhZeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @CBS12 just letting you know I’m not watching your station anymore, I don’t think Boris  is what I want to see… https://t.co/348iEVS2CS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve come to the conclusion that I’m now immune to the guilt trip. Ty mother, youve taught me well 😂🥴🤘🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DSmithShow @MartyCaswell loved DJ comments about Flacco!!! Glad was able to get out of work early to hear it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very blessed 🙏 and happy Saturday campers! Thank you God for another day 🌞 and for herbal tea  with honey 🐝  List… https://t.co/R4F3BRO3N6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@volsbaby y’all might not have to worry about being co-champs... @LSUBasketball might be vacating some W’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cool thing about having a dog is that your leftovers never go to waste]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rabid Anglophobia and hatred of ‘traitor’ Scots to be found deeply embedded throughout the Nationalist movement… https://t.co/jY7CSnfXJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day for a hike 💪 @ Dry Comal Nature Trail https://t.co/nGqkNdafDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notthefakeSVP you need to bust out the Jacks hat again!  @WorldStarDave breaking the Bison with this 1/2 court gem… https://t.co/VWBRHPvTGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertoSmithP La memética de la cultura: teorizar y dejar que el lado narrativo del cerebro domine al lado que exp… https://t.co/Stj2yvJONJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[💀 it was the first thing i saw off the highway and needed a quick snack. it was my first time ever having it and i’… https://t.co/8zTQ241miB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acnewsitics I wish the Dems hadn't given him anything. There are so many areas along the Rio Grande that the wall… https://t.co/6de032JzRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lowest thing anyone can do, is speak down on someone who they used to fuck with heavy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialPJNorth @CMThot20 @CMT @CountryMusic @NashvilleCMT @billboard @harland_william]]></document><document><![CDATA[2,000 plastic bottles are used every second. See how you can be a part of the change and reduce your single-use pla… https://t.co/3unC015doy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dbetras @OHDems I'd like to see some stats, but I feel like the #MainStreetInitiave had been one of @OHDems bigges… https://t.co/B7Px0Y8wlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My (very rare) #FF post: You should be following the Northern Spanking Sweethearts: @CupcakeSinclair… https://t.co/wLISMJ2NAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Players don’t care how much you know, until they know how much you care...#CR_Softball]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Coach skips the play you made, then says the whole position group needs to do better...  https://t.co/stzGGB34Tv]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The person who doesn’t read is no better off than the person who can’t “ #ThinkBIGSundayWithMarsha #leadership #booklovers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madfriarskevin @marcusSDTX If you offered me $50k right this second I couldn't tell you with 100% confidence what sport they even play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcACaputo @armandodkos Bernie lost all four large states in the last primary, and it’s tough to envision him win… https://t.co/BO0OYd41tH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me:  FA: “Oh hey you’re the guy me and the other flight attendant were comparing pros and cons of the way you pull your hair back.”   Me:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elegant Marble &amp; Bling Nail Look @itsjustmiaya 💎✨🤩🤩.. Tag and share with your bestie @ Nail Studio By Tom https://t.co/KCUQCknJrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I ran the @runrocknroll half marathon in DC today. I had been stuck in a rut and was a little stagnant with my t… https://t.co/yfkHytIunV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annecsteelerfan If love was simple, there would be no breakups or divorce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesbeal @TimoOlkkonen @euinzim @UKinZimbabwe @HMAMelanieR @usembassyharare He has hit the reset button. The system… https://t.co/5OMasu01vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matute_yo_Peres @MrMaxican @e23martinez @HoustonDynamo @MLS @MDAndersonNews @Hincha_FC @adidasUS Niiiiice!!! Too b… https://t.co/MjEhoSF4Vq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachaelRayShow @JoyVBehar @TheView Joy is a disgrace and should have been fired 20 years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ski___10 We have to give Amare props at some point. He never even attempted a layup hebfirdt 7 years in the league… https://t.co/fsueDdbUHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KUKAI369 @gatewaypundit Extraordinary efforts were made to savor every second. Which was followed by days of walki… https://t.co/DST2hOTq6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *standing in kitchen*  Toddler in the bathroom: *grunts* “Big poop”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sundayfunday #snowstorm2019 egg is doing its thing... ready for some #hotandfast #blackangus #filets &amp; #hanger… https://t.co/VnEdUsEEWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t emphasize enough how great it is to have good friend like @NYPost_Lewis on the road. Wide-ranging discussion… https://t.co/geFflLf4S8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@motel6 this doesn’t even do it justice. Roaches, bed bugs, old Chinese food, dirt, stains, etc. I’m disgusted. https://t.co/3cRAXGEGZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell no, this is honestly incredible.... I don’t even wanna know the odds of this happening is]]></document><document><![CDATA[People on Facebook are always asking for @netflix recommendations as if that isn't literally their entire feed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nexton9news And let us never forget she passed away because her insurance company denied paying for an antibiotic… https://t.co/RSm64aHnhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[So GOP, are you tired of winning yet. Wake up. You are driving our standing in the world into the ground.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DumbCerb @complete_eediot I like to think Galactus has Hank Hill's voice now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maraschinox @THC_blondie @kushcoffee1 It’s not a joke but I mean 💁🏼‍♂️ it’s not funny. It’s not cute. I guess some… https://t.co/wFn5uMiSlb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ducks #floridaphotographer #florida #swfl #swflphotographer #waterbirds #birds #photography #wildlife… https://t.co/QF2muNyxbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra So here is Joy's Body Double  @TheView https://t.co/TvH9J7ua2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox reboots Beverly Hills, 90210 this summer!  This is going to be good!  Can’t wait!  Congrats to the original cas… https://t.co/kMvk8lU4vl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity #Traitortot45  #ImpeachTheMFTraitor  #TrumpCrimeFamily  #TrumpRussianAgent https://t.co/PlFuiHFVBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllieMargolis @CBHessick @lawprofblawg Academic partners are the real VIPs.]]></document></documents></author>