<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Doug Jones is a closet Republican. He won on the Democratic ticket but votes with the Republicans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are putting our village together ...teamwork!!!  Where We Are In Place and Time!!! https://t.co/hK99jsMSmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t sit there and watch game of thrones I feel way to behind niggas been watching that weak ass show]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laying in bed listening to @samsmith has to be the most peaceful thing ever. https://t.co/Qry5z5sabo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t even wait for @festivaltortuga 2019!  Bringing my buddy @Jason_Aldean with me!!   Get your tickets today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chanceperez Life is so confusing and can throw a curveball out of no where. I’ve often questioned if I’m a bad per… https://t.co/IkJiPMg2WQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when older people genuinely support me and my dreams. I am excited for my life to become something that really fulfills me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh... really don’t want to work out but my watch just told me @HelloRo_ closed all of her activity rings so now I… https://t.co/6FvUVbDsl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[T2406 #see_and_beseen #newarrivals #new #ootd #wholesale #fashiongo #denim #day  #contemporary #Outfit #Style… https://t.co/1FmjjAGZPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanna be the best possible person I can be and I want to do well by others and remain thankful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then he says, A reading from the holy Gospel, making the Sign of the Cross with his thumb on the book and on his fo… https://t.co/fyvzWZX58y]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay but i’m lowkey excited to go to ashlynn’s class party tomorrow. that’s the side of parenting i haven’t done, o… https://t.co/hfP52kaQ0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl I follow on Insta works out all hardcore and her hair is never sweaty/ messed up 🤔🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s the last show you saw at @DPAC ? Do you get up dressed for the theater? #whatwouldaprilwear @ Durham, North… https://t.co/n7yqeQ0bJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#privateparking #whopays #barbarakruger #geffencontemporary @ The Geffen Contemporary at MOCA https://t.co/Nh500rZpby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaytbug0700 @DavidlambEX @AlyMichStevens Honestly, I don’t really know where they do their business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@todmassa Absolutely. Makes me think of the calls every single person in my office got for Whos Who a few years ago… https://t.co/5TwF81wagw]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all had that one annoying ass girl in one of our high school classes that would always tell everyone to shut up… https://t.co/kUk6FooeJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I legitimately had Olivia Colman as LEAST likely to win Best Actress, but she is incredible and I am NOT mad about… https://t.co/Xk4bjT4Aao]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a hat, we have free speech, the hat stands for Make America Great Again....!  I wear mine with pride.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luvnewinfo @my3monkees @gakagtrumptrain @DeepStateExpose @Laurarode2 @Spring_Harbinge @enzorcapo @Bud_Doggin… https://t.co/EMV1QlTxmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ajaytuque Pues es lo de menos, que parezca o no, no quiere decir que de verdad está ejecutando cosas que le están… https://t.co/ZITWXj0fgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's almost 5am &amp; I've been watching a thread on crackheads for the least hour]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could know everything ever, like that would be my wish – that’s what I hope heaven is, that they tell you… https://t.co/WZaMYU6LMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad to announce that my trouble with self is unrelated to my comorbidity and just has everything to do with my… https://t.co/7iDBE0Brje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clarke10Rich thx for the follow ! I had to follow you with “patriot pet” #NationalPetDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost everyone I know has a cold and are happy to share. So I’m spending Saturday night at home with a book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been less than 2 months and he’s already gotten so big :( https://t.co/dmEbRVnFy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patharveynews hi there Happy Valentines Day! Hope you had an awesome day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner Trump so happy trump can do crimes and absolutely nothing happens to TRUMP.EVERYONE ELSE GETS JAIL SENTE… https://t.co/A8iiU3YI6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need help from natural girls who put shit in their hair. I got this smoothie I put in my beard and the white residu… https://t.co/E2ZF1wFpHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaseyChris Try runnning at 9k ft like I did this week. I nearly died! 😂✨🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel @VP You seemed to have missed the part about not bearing false witness. Maybe mother will spank you. Oooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tfw you’re hosting a reading &amp; you sit down after doing the intro &amp; realize your shirt is on inside out https://t.co/KRD3d6HnfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realize miss Honey from Matilda is Derricks sister on greys anatomy I can not believe this. #mindblown]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShimonPro @evanperez @LauraAJarrett Good. That was a monumental waste of time &amp; money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JettScottNow @triszhermogenes @robynkonichiwa Live life to the fullest. Why not?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachWallace30 @Allison_Kruger Three kids around Allison all have phones up. Was there a game going on?]]></document><document><![CDATA[På plats på NABE-konferensen i Washington. Sitter alltså 2 meter bakom Paul Krugman. Känns som stabil start. https://t.co/80yZrd9pTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobProvince One smokes weed while incarcerating small drug offenders while the other rumor has it snorts Adderall… https://t.co/HBF4S7ZQJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevenhornjr @Shaun_Gains @senatemajldr @JohnCornyn I think what it could do is require the child to be transferre… https://t.co/QctF5M5Bje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I have a date with my four husbands, boyfriends and lovers😜❣️Andrea bocelli, Charles Aznovour, Roberto Carlo… https://t.co/Di9WLFR6x2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piesaac I met a bass-baritone the other day who took great joy from the fact that, by singing the shit out of Wota… https://t.co/bMnpEQ2IES]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this snowy day we decided to take in a movie and are @AMCTheatres to see #GreenBook]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chirpsbysarah We need a channel for climate changes with augmented reality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino has gone from patriot to propagandist in three short years. Sad!  I’m praying for you this morning Dan- b… https://t.co/Pbx1mjs5VF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My great grandmother Nelli bagby died on Valentine's day.  My 13th bday.   We will never forget her 💗 https://t.co/C2HUxAsO65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gisselleivzla31 Me acorde de hace rato que se la aplique a tu mama con un chiste 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m looking at the old videos on my phone from 2016-2017 and my Snapchat zooming skills were IMPECCABLE lmao I need… https://t.co/rBtFLvYEPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dr_K_Kelly I totally would’ve taken credit for planning that attire. Panache runs in your family!]]></document><document><![CDATA[sin is deceitful and this is why many of us are tempted to sin. This is what the letter of Hebrews tells us. 'Take… https://t.co/D62vI816WF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots to talk about during the #dailyscoop - movies, tv, @Jason_Aldean and more! #ScottAndSarah @949WQMX https://t.co/OJaZuQPHOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve decided to title my autobiography “You’re Never Really as Cool as You Thought You Were as a Senior in High Sch… https://t.co/gPIom2TGFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taniapsuv @PartidoPSUV FEA TANIA DONDE ESTAN LOS TRILLONES ROBADOS A LOS VENEZOLANOS Y DEPOSITADOS EN BANCOS EXTR SEGUN EL FMI  ?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Chase has the largest active mobile banking customer base among US banks. $JPM Investor Day https://t.co/h0AZAkRwyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[That time I got a shitty omega tattoo but fixed it with #Kratos. #GodOfWar #Playstation https://t.co/VC4wz2pjrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TandyRayes that just seems repetitive if u gotta mention it a bunch of times]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Who gave Rodrigo Duterte that wonderful Zero Tolerance "Drug War" concept?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Proofreading Day, fellow #wordnerds and #editors! #nationalproofreadingday #editor #amediting https://t.co/1wRFEWbgnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you mean to tell me @khloekardashian  baby daddy cheated on her with the same ( yet different spelling) name of… https://t.co/ltcwwpExoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can get down on this! - Drinking a Manson Lamps by @CigarCityBeer at @CigarCityBeer  — https://t.co/zHvfddWe5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_Legend1976 Are you serious? Well don’t I feel dumb https://t.co/pZUCVfPTS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philipnolan1 @AC360 @cnni Haha, Wow, what a difference in environments. I'm in the South in the US and we are pred… https://t.co/WI97hIQQm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josefacp71 @AlfredoJalifeR_ @MohsenAlmohade @josseder Gracias. Lo leeré más tarde camino al trabajo 😃👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything… https://t.co/Mm6k912XQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@worldsofwork is finally here! Follow @EastALWorks for live video Tuesday as Jacki Lowry with @alabamapower and I s… https://t.co/XOSvGaaTFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepGwenMoore @pdacosta With the aid of MCConnell and McCarthy...and many GOP who seem to be compromised!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope i survive when global warming kills off majority of the population. I feel like it’ll be a great story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[La verdad que cada vez que veo y escucho a esta mujer me surgen serias dudas sobre sus capacidades.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen on Trump: He is a racist, he is a con man, and he is a cheat https://t.co/2MhHsHZHQh via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reesetheone1 Yes, I too have gleaned some substantial nuggets just from what was said on Thom's show.  This is a g… https://t.co/wXrWzGcmSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today! Taught, connected @NCS_PFAA with an amazing #creativitysummit for the kids of #sacramento next month, did an… https://t.co/cXqpmxwFYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will you also vote against a man jumps putting in charge of The Endangered Species Act he's a coal lobbyist Trump's… https://t.co/xUM5HDxA42]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join MAYA for lunch Today (2/26) from 12pm-2pm. Visit us at our New York City @mayaromanoff showroom at the… https://t.co/b9QLEC7iah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to my hubs for the surprise reservations at Elizabeth’s American Bistro. Here’s my Valentine’s day latergram… https://t.co/ylSdQI3lmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Authoritarian #governments enforce strict #obedience to #authority at the expense of #personal #freedom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColeTheBlackCat Oh yea I would!! And @calicopaisley88 would as well!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePdFans That poor puppy in that cage is like: https://t.co/CJq3mmiJ7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[$VYST Anyone that shorted it got scrweed this am $1M dollar vol coming up-  Make em cover on the ask!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FullForceElimination8 #LastWomanStanding vanityvixsin vs @MistressBelmont #AtlanticProWrestling @ Newburyport Elks https://t.co/IvT0z3IKMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roommate: where have you been all afternoon? Me: I went to Trails Cafe in Griffith Park and sat on a hay bale in th… https://t.co/LOtqEXtD5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McResistor @ninaturner @TulsiGabbard And look what happened when McCain chose Palin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know something I find really interesting: there is no mention of US involvement in this summit thread from DPRK… https://t.co/l7jJkYmspQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when your grandmother asks if you're still seeing that "nice young man" who came to Christmas o… https://t.co/RtuZq5SFqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadLeistikow If I were the coach of this team they would be running Gene Hackman Hoosier defensive sprints until they couldn’t stand]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, so I stayed up catching up with the @GoldenKnights and just like @FeinbergFOX5 said, tomorrow morning is gonna… https://t.co/v9RgJB7U2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddSantos4 Late afternoon in #Youngstown, NY. https://t.co/NAOZfc5UOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GovRonDeSantis issues an executive order today, aimed at making Florida’s schools safer.  He is once again keepin… https://t.co/zwbx8bbwrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Children don't need to see parents fighting physically, they become the next generation of victims and abusers! It'… https://t.co/AOJ8Hnpcej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another game, another disappointing loss...Latest @HockeyBuzz blog: https://t.co/2e4xGx72Tu #Canadiens #goHabsGo #habs #CH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_ankrom @lovewrenching36 What does she care? She won the lottery when she got elected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VINayot @kitkatrebolos @PanjST @novabellss HAHAHAHAHAHAHA shufa naman waks karon it's the new you, that was the old vinbegz lmao 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IWD2019 #ricohcares @RicohTweets @TeamHendrick https://t.co/SRmGKMYvh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude is now comparing me to TERFs, radical evangelicals, and “literal Nazis”. https://t.co/CUI9YZeld3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw an ad for a new movie. Looks like machines take over. The key ad starts with,  "it started 10 yrs ago. They p… https://t.co/ZURvETaG6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[I reread this tweet every once and a while to boost my self confidence.   I wasn’t raised bilingual, and that’s wha… https://t.co/ByFJFiYt5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RueNahcMohr @wackyvorlon But doesnt RF like to travel via skin effect?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like SVU and a full glass of wine. I truly understand what it’s like to be a mom]]></document><document><![CDATA[The boys say my boarding pass and I have a lot in common.. #Basic 💀🤣 https://t.co/kTzBqrVCf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbyfuller Cosign. The ONE thing I like about being on them is that it sometimes gives me new cool folks to follow.]]></document></documents></author>