<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My Spotify just went from “I don’t mind” by defeater to “my world” by code orange 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump Don’t forget the hundreds of successful businesses he owns. Has over 9% success rate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfDiamantaki @Tsag_An I believe that it may have already slipped into a death spiral...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikschlitt @thelionswire I was huge on Marquis last year that's why I noticed right away lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO thank you for standing up and being heard. Please run for President. I’m in Iowa. We can make a state… https://t.co/M1Bqa8VhEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conférence de presse avec @elonmusk et @JimBridenstine, dans quelques minutes https://t.co/0HQXfg5U7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all have that one song that you used to love so much but now you don’t because it brings you so much sad nostalgi… https://t.co/ALTZayOFDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strontiumtom This did happen about a year and a half after my first (and hopefully only) case of DTs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incase your wondering what a pinball machine  looks like in the inside.  Lol @ Pacific Pinball Museum https://t.co/t3K0ZgirY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulapoundstone He should have done it with 6 costume &amp; character changes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xxxleander @JoshMooreXXX @blake_hunterxxx @BallsBruno Oh wow amazing 😍❤️❣️💕 😘💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[The good days was when you cleaned ya room in 3 mins cuz you got a chick on her way over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re here for a second night of War &amp; Peace, parts three and four.   🔥 The War of 1812 gonna be lit. 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Lockhart shredded Ken Starr's arguments that his investigation was not politically motivated. Mueller's investi… https://t.co/qHBQP3c0GA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shakeywade @NHLonNBCSports @strome18 @stromer19 @Mstrome16 @TSNHockey @HockeyCanada @usahockey No shit huh 👍… https://t.co/u9CK25kEKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ayren_Coleman @RANK10YGO Lol Jaden was late to the school entry exams and they didn’t wanna let him do an exam (wh… https://t.co/7LC2hkrkrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skyscraper6394 Closest street is Sahara. Right behind the freeway and about 5 mins from the strip or less.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericfisher "Can I have me a reprisal of February, 1969, Eric?"  LOL!  Sorry, that play and variation on a phrase t… https://t.co/sV9JkmPEJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melgibsonsmrsme @Jossfjh @Bornabrit1 @ellievan65 @BSmithTweet We didn't have cable television and Watergate disrup… https://t.co/fL4ru12IVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥🔥 I know right! Happy Friday Fam!!! We made it through another great week! Enjoy the time with loved ones and fam… https://t.co/uuQjm9AZWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the #Oscar for Best Costume goes to... Melissa McCarthy for whatever the heck she's wearing! https://t.co/OGv5VZL3PZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tyler_Babin Eddies Sweet Shop - Forest Hills, Queens   Also the best ice cream in NYC   plz @me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DbDant @maddow Ask Michelle Alexander what she thinks of Manafort's sentence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He stared down at ibaka. Are you really that upset over him looking at you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does it feel to be a member of a political segment selected as most gullible by Trump?  If you’re in his base t… https://t.co/fQ07dEAlA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[i get ariana's album is killin it right now but why is no one talking about the song she's featured on my boi 2 CHAINZ ALBUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WHEC_RSPETA @PARKERzack Awesome! Thank you for your service, Robert! 🇺🇸🎖 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[The defense Craig is playing tonight (like always) is why Russ wanted him in OKC this past offseason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We would seriously like our parents and supporters and the make up artists that spent 3 hours everyday to cover my… https://t.co/NZNDRc2wyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK — final three photo posts for the @surlybrewing boot soccer tournament incoming! #MNUFC https://t.co/W7LH5677vC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @IAMMGraham Yes, as is the campaign of the  Senator from NY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brunch with one of my school Investors.. . #blessed #investors #mentor #friend #dad #impact #love #mlmpipa… https://t.co/a8X8jx7UuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lannadelgrey @AOC Women are not as powerful women are definitely more powerful then men women have all the power]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not fear  Pastor Robert Jeffress morning devotional teaching  Pathway to Victory Daily Devotion for 02/20/2019 - https://t.co/6QtHV3rgqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[New music video for ‘Madness’ with the help of @southern_souls! Milles Merci Mitch!  Join us March 22nd at the… https://t.co/DlhhoqS6DJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LukePerry in one of my favorites, “Buffy The Vampire Slayer”. Dreamboat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the showdown we’ve all been waiting for. @RapSheet vs @AdamSchefter in a trial by combat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proper #MerseysideDerby today  -All 4 CB’s excellent -Salah maybe feeling the schedule a little  -Fabinho is growing on me #EVELIV 🔵🔴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycjim Ttump want have to worry one bit about impeachment. His MAGA like 1932 will get him drug out of the White H… https://t.co/je5libexrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyHomeStore Took a coupon I received in an email to store in Jeffersontown, KY.  74th anniversary coupons.  12… https://t.co/LKW9Srpsno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RitaPanahi Give me a freaking break. Is there anybody in the free world who doesnt understand jihad?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Fostech Fighter Lite Rifle w/ Echo Trigger from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $1200!… https://t.co/zLfsB11BxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@palerider321 @Dougs1978 Are you f...... kidding me? This is hysterically ridiculous!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleGallner What if you just thought the movie was over all kind of crappy? The cast felt off.... the script was o… https://t.co/u32RWGmxjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMDb Was priness Diana but that's England so I. not to up to date on current affairs especially in United Kindom I… https://t.co/OTxcz6x4Hq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeeBrookshire @shanpalus But how much snot can a defleshed skull even have...? 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[The PS Vita was dead after 2013, lack of games killed it. Retailers discontinue it in 2015. The Vita could’ve been… https://t.co/JbgEhJeodR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/K5oWSyhFTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bryan700 @kimguilfoyle @JoeBiden has never been the brightest bulb in the room.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me:*feeling nostalgic, listens to Talk dirty to me by poison once*  Spotify: I noticed you listened to poison once.… https://t.co/PcTt17EYm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Kraft Heinz shares plummet after revelation of SEC probe and $15 billion write-down”  https://t.co/tvols4VxJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 #ComradeKimJongWon https://t.co/NBg0HSOHSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look what was trending the other day, BUT no longer is. Why isn’t the media covering a hate crime, oh wait. Because… https://t.co/TqUsStGEty]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sad part is that I wrote this warning in 1978. https://t.co/RhfFoy5dN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s reception for #PublicDomainDay and kicking off #fairuseweek was a blast! Huge props to @shebam and… https://t.co/bGHEbaaZDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rehab Mogul. When Amanda went to the Motel with the gross and bad smelling Mogul, was she thinking of some kind bri… https://t.co/xp4mSI6WGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKylerMurray See Samardzija career. You can make a fortune with much less wear and tear. Please reconsider and p… https://t.co/Ct04P35uj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[BYU down by 40 to San Diego in the WCC semi finals...March can be cruel like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why @maryalioliver and I are soupsnakes (soulmates) https://t.co/buBM1PGpKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffzeleny To be honest and fair to ms Klobuchar I was a no on her b4 her town hall.   There’s nothing she could say to get my vote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hotmacandsleaze Those cats ain’t got nothin on my beautiful GODDESSES OF THE ARTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new tatted strongman shirt💪🏻. We just dropped these last Friday along with 2 ladies items #ironandinkfitness  S… https://t.co/PVjoRoQmPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ginnyhogan_ I wasn’t sure which it was, so I went with the one that looked stupider.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobGMacfarlane Is there a particular reference guide or dictionary you use for your etymology or do you gradually… https://t.co/WHxgV2Itqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Build that WALL along with an electric fence.🔥that should stop the trash getting in!!!   I totally support I.C.E...… https://t.co/KQgzDQSUJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NEWLEVEL1331 Yeah Magic might have made a mistake on this one, all because of Swaggy P. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Holy sh@t!!! Can you get your lips off trumps ass! WHAT DO YOU THINK MR. John McCain say about  your kiss… https://t.co/oRY2itcyn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[after 1 at Mead: Mavericks can’t miss and lead @HF_Basketball 22-11. @BoCoPreps @hf_lamppost #copreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad thing is I couldn't really tell the difference between the NBA All Star game and a regular season game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfAEDixon I heard about this last year from some small trade business owners.  They were working to find Black Youth in PBC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadFemPirate @theatregirl5264 @NorthForBritain @VeniVidiVicki @Martina @sharrond62 Agreedes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro do y’all see the dudes these females be settling wit? Don’t ever think somebody out of yo league lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are any of the #Democrats running for President calling for increased penalties for parents who let their children… https://t.co/fpry7lP3VF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calonghurst @Apple Does this mean that my #EHR notes will make more sense?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YalixaAparicio @thalia 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 "sueñaaaa con un mundo distinto, donde las almas de unen al fin y la bondad renacerá..."]]></document><document><![CDATA[With respect Molly, I disagree. I believe one of the big mistakes we as modern Americans make is not judging people… https://t.co/cBmC80AzWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhatiFRacing @JimmyBroadbent I hope you are watching the Daytona 500, it’s pack racing and Matt Debiddto is leadin… https://t.co/i5RjRZP2mZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a nightmare I had this morning. I’d moved and left my @Sonos speakers behind. 😱😤  luckily it was only a dream.… https://t.co/CrN2svP8hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dailybriefing @DanaPerino @SenatorBennet Hey @SenatorBennet you are in the Senate!  If you hate the EC so much--PR… https://t.co/0AgT7IRTnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pra mim, escrever aqui é quase um exercício esquizofrênico, praticamente falar com as paredes. É quase um diário ué ninguém nunca vai ler.]]></document><document><![CDATA[7th graders applying decision making skills to real life situations... with the help of the 90's sitcom Full House!… https://t.co/UHtqPHVFzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 Ah, the “rubber/glue” strategy, works quite well in the sixth grade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gasca The second half of a silent meeting feels like we just read the questions in the comments, and then read the… https://t.co/cEU2weI27z]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing about Milk Bar in Cambridge (and the one I remember visiting in DC) is that it has room for about 5 peopl… https://t.co/OjaPY60BcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seafood and scallion pancake #foodporn @ Midori Restaurant https://t.co/wy7q3xyJQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only did I annoy my girlfriend and make here fall asleep because I’m a fucking loser. My internet won’t work. #livingthedream #roundtwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qualcomm again calls for US import ban on iPhones, cites #Apple’s own statement as justification… https://t.co/eAsJW0OzJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh uh we uh are continuing to work hard for Canadians uh uh and working toward a more uh uh transparent government.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They've had plenty of time to cut a mutually good deal for both sides, instead of which they, pushed a less than ad… https://t.co/80KIAxMeeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to have the opportunity to wake up today and be grateful for all the blessings in my life and the ones comi… https://t.co/LmGTcLeJwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherC91 @ActuallyNPH @Hughes11Amber That’s exactly what the peacock would say!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teaps @GarlavaBJJ Yeah just go after the dude with all the gear and helmet on instead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bihh get pregnant think she bouta blow my phone up to vent aht aht call yo baby daddy Bihh 🤦🏾‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @sloanwilliams10 for your accomplishments and signing with @LCUVolleyball go represent Dumas we are proud… https://t.co/H5YzOdJ1VH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait just a damn second lol did @ahrensjustin12 just shush @notthefakeSVP lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity It’s a shame, that people who are still upset that Hillary lost, the anti-trumpers, and the people who… https://t.co/BusVh09wM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theNatoPotato I always knew that complaining on Twitter was the way to get things done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debbiecakesky Congrats Coach Dameron. You treated me an my family with the upmost class and professionalism. It wa… https://t.co/LCkeSJnamE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best fast food 🍟, according to @JalenandJacoby   @JalenRose: McD @djacoby: Five Guys  Me: In n Out fries are bomb!… https://t.co/6541KwVTKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a great game.  Maddy was on 🔥🔥 And as usual, Chippewa fans out numbered Eagle fans in their house 😀😀]]></document></documents></author>