<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@rogina47 So far, not happy they killed the wolf/dog.. lol 😂😂😂 Hate when animals die! Love the scenery... only 2 episodes in]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsskinnyg @ayeavs @yerrrrrrugly97 @LIBGyal I called and had a phone consultation I’m so down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Chupacabra! Sadly, I’m too old now to yell, run and jump off tables. Still a favorite lesson though 😊#almost40… https://t.co/oLyLN6uAq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone really needs to stop bringing their unvaccinated ass kids into my store when they’re obviously sick. I can… https://t.co/dvXvSqA0HJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCBua WTF? Does Fixed News Propaganda  for Right Wing 🥜 have to do with a Russian Dictator? JR’s met up at Dump To… https://t.co/PstZ4cOYDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[But you are ok with aborting, killing legal citizens that are infants!  https://t.co/VJHdlHneWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao some people are so clueless when it comes to personal space... GTFO😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming from the city it’s always a surprise to see deer! These little were just wandering around as we were driving… https://t.co/bNoL1yBItq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it possible to talk about the game that is on without mentioning Zion or other teams 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best thread on the Jackson’s accusers from the @HBODocs n I can’t believe this was even aired. MJ had a troubled li… https://t.co/vdaqudtrQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Because you had such bad morning sickness you’re totally gonna deliver early”- um where’s THAT nonsense in a medical journal idiot?! 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBA you’re refs are awful if you’re going to pay them rig the games tell them to make it less obvious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kvortexvg1 Did I give you the impression there aren’t a team of licensed attorneys on this?  Agree Paycheck Fairne… https://t.co/IIGZr6RYq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[No animals were harmed in this photoshoot   Thank you daddy macjericksantos  for the badass shots and… https://t.co/vtzAZ8NSsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mconnelly816 @Madafak06774732 @JoshMRadio @steven_seibel @PhilliesNewsnow @DannyTstout @SotehPR @KenCageRepo… https://t.co/O9Z3MI0Xva]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naked_phantom @TWPundit Yes I think so. Don jr or Jarad. Not sure which is next -but soon I hope!!  🤣. Just like F… https://t.co/qCoaVZPGst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@48hours Uh, you can’t have it both ways. Did you have illegal contact with minors or not?]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Este sábado! #bienesraices #impuestosdepropiedad #escobarhomesteam #kellerwilliams @ Emmanuel Presbyterian Church https://t.co/83BGgVEFJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz seems threatening. Could have watched it ( everywhere but @FoxNews ) like the rest of us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW today is gonna be good because my professor rescheduled our quiz 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning moons.  - #sólisdefloresluna @ Cuyahoga Valley National Park https://t.co/b2morHlvgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting my cats stoned on the Nip is the highlight of my evening... 😻 https://t.co/eQ0F2tXEwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhparks @Paul91701736 But I'm sure the truthers will be unconvinced. That's fine. Just know that not all the data… https://t.co/0HEqs48SUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WendyWall_Math @theresawills @GMUMathEd Can be arranged- you have an “in”!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets People on my street drive too slow!!!!!  #nationalemergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBraeden Extreamly grateful that @malyoung  is gone! Thank you for supporting @DougDavidsonYR and may the show mov… https://t.co/nzvihSRfvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomtomandtom I’m super down!!! But FYI, there’s a helium shortage. #truestory]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s #TwoMinuteTakeAway is:  It is wonderful to define your goals and push toward your ‘I wants’.   Write them d… https://t.co/jwX9V2tjxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still after three years my girlfriend sends me the cutest goodmorning texts 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me waiting for Kristina to tell me if she wants to eat nuggets together https://t.co/L29rLboNe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clownejd this was such a special moment throughout this journey for my son, @KyleFelix18.  Thank you so much for h… https://t.co/lJuwtBMh5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends make up for the love I don’t receive in other places of my life &amp; im deadass so thankful for it💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sokolowskia Tried it a few times and ain't work in just over it at this point]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bee_emjay @SrikanthANair @RealJamesWoods Yes, parents should be teaching their child to be respectful them, their… https://t.co/F1h853Fa3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is wrong.  If the idiot can't pass, he shouldn't get top secret clearance.  Matter of fact the guy should NOT… https://t.co/YzAssVYvR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tayari I hope your previous books, especially Leaving Atlanta are getting recognized and reviewed again.  Genius. There is a movie there!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martyswant Dinner (avoiding crowds) Roaring Fork at Stephen F. Austin hotel delicious/takes reservations; Manuel's… https://t.co/CcL4tUGpKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big fat anxiety storm right now, complete with headache, racing pulse, sweaty palms and just feeling horrible....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllVape3 @james_bong13 @stonervswrld @Godzmazter @808KushBoys @xStonerGirls @HiHappyHungry @420moongirls… https://t.co/WeQawCV0Pz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flourishing Friendships club presenting their Autism Awareness posters. #autismawareness #bccbarons https://t.co/COqSS9asbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a whole ass car on fire in the middle of the highway. Welcome to Houston.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know beavers, wolves, and bats practice Monogamy. The more you know]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish someone baked for me like this. Lucky kids ✨ https://t.co/hz7xd8GO3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigR50792436 @omfcctw @BigwavesOrris @CTFletcherISYMF @simon_maybury @KimberlyISYMFS @Mr1MoreRound… https://t.co/FmOQVTcOFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ @sbn1780 The whole family is sinister. They have been caught in the act of being themselves. Not a p… https://t.co/QOoPCJlcdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love to chuckle. #comedy #giggle #smile #cute https://t.co/rc8yrCO6yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hahahahaha I love this. You are right you are my favorite President]]></document><document><![CDATA[my pluto is exactly on someone’s south node/uranus conjunction in their 5th house. i just had a dream last night of… https://t.co/boVr2o3aAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we get Harper and Machado signed somewhere soon please? At this point I don’t even care where they go, I’m just… https://t.co/G293ElvVNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlysuepickens No, I’m saying trauma in the moment means you don’t necessarily remember accurately. I work in an… https://t.co/mXn2CV9M4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people have the most fun ideas as well as the time to actually do them.... https://t.co/eEMFg9TyV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catclawzzz @Tinkkz Ok. Good. 😑 I can’t have imposters summoning tacos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remembering Jason, loving you, dear Leesa!  #StrongArmSelfie #FightCRC #rememberingjasonwaite https://t.co/5qDhhuDCLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics Sick of old, white, rich men robbing this country blind to line their pockets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I AM SO PROUD @toribelcher24 FOR GETTING ACCEPTED INTO MED SCHOOL, that’s my MF BISH! Love you so much and I’m so proud :,) 🤘🏽😭🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[JCPS is excited to be hosting the JCPS HS Aspen Challenge Louisville! #AspenChallenge https://t.co/bxRuRoXAck]]></document><document><![CDATA[guess who's a national merit finalist ?!! big thank you to @KellerISD for the yard sign !!😂❤️ https://t.co/rwp5aAwgYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Analytical-learner response to learning opportunities vs reflection on teaching #ettacollins @AssocTeacherEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her determination to become better and drive to conquer new skills always amazes me! The dedication that these coac… https://t.co/iKrsxFNgc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ar00ster @leon1961lee @thehill @IlhanMN You may wish to look up the fraud that allowed Franken to get initially el… https://t.co/GeYb8s825j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@confessions_cup @linds4fins @TheAngelOrsini @JackConnie @hmgivingsoul @suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy @ja2cook @Jay_Rombach… https://t.co/fzAFeyzLFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Karl Lagerfeld, your illustrations are iconic and you will not be forgotten! https://t.co/H7VKOJipf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlierShME @Betterw05759703 @amccrack3 @kylegriffin1 @RosemaryMscott We would be in jail bc they would enforce the perjury clause on SF86.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But Jesus does not ask us to do the impossible unless He supplies us the grace. The basis for love of enemy is a de… https://t.co/SiG0BqZlmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 20 years of teaching I have never had to testify in court for or against a kid. A first!  #TeacherLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler Really, if someone doesn’t know what it is they can look it up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBaier That is because a man cannot become a women.  The female race needs to wake up ! They R trying to do away w our gender.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I watch Bohemian Rhapsody for the fifth time in three days or do I go to bed #lifequestions]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he answered and spake unto those that stood before him, saying, Take away the filthy garments from him. And unt… https://t.co/86aVSdM6Zg]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I see people having their 2 and 3 year olds in a booster seat. 😢 do some car seat safety research people!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real talk: There are times still, after years of being a #spininstructor that I doubt myself. Is the music good, am… https://t.co/DmSKCk39Wj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson Who is the “fake news”. Seriously are we not a free society... free of a dictator,… https://t.co/4tUJ4pQZg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squinn1769 I hardly know what to say to this... No more cacti for you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatHeverin @Charapoo That’s fantastic! I demand tails and tie the next time I see you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fired Up &amp; Ready to Go by Pastor Jackie L Jackson  https://t.co/yV6vWc7uGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely beautiful duet.....And I’m the 2nd person in singing this popular awesome song! Listen to me sing "My He… https://t.co/A7tZ0x9Xjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abbas asks African Union to monitor Palestinian elections https://t.co/zl4GZDjg3v via @MiddleEastMnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes I do things spontaneously and i’m like mmm maybe shouldn’t have done that but 🤷🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe some supporters of FFP believe that, and some don’t, obviously better to keep the policy coalition cohesive.… https://t.co/sb5Cq90cMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where's Bugs Bunny to run the outboard motor on the boat for the president?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you want to join me today ? 😜#shooting @21sextury #brunette #tatoo #lingery #pornlife #picoftheday #LosAngeles https://t.co/GLNHshTpbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need closed captions on because I can’t pay attention to movies without them. I love to discuss and analyze movie… https://t.co/pZ9WV35DGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@montielbkdv @PadreJosePalmar Pero esta bien que pienses asi. Montale un altar y le rezas el rosario diariamente a… https://t.co/jy8OxjfT5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[My only comment on the Oscars is that they better DO THE RIGHT THING in the best director category cc @LegsFrank]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Landslide1973 @Magimare She should be allowed back to the UK for one reason. To be shot as an enemy combatant the… https://t.co/S1JmrjgUZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wouldn’t love a coffee that has #DrSuess Thing 1 and Thing 2 on it?!? Thankful for those who participated today… https://t.co/kav1AHORnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willtangclan36 Is anyone REALLY that naive?!?! Or were they just hiding reality to cover their own sick secrets?!… https://t.co/BE0kW9VvbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aquariuspussy I am so glad that that this resonates. You are so beautiful and there is something that has just com… https://t.co/LGVly8C0pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rolling through the desert on the way to #SpringTraining and listening to my 5th @EdMylett podcast. #MaxOut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corrupt Democrats!  Liars and cheaters!  Can do nothing without cheating!  Nunez did nothing but bring out what lyi… https://t.co/WDJV5MBTj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TGDsquad @GoodDoctorABC @gooddrwriters @danieldaekim @todavidkim @SLfrom @freddiehighmore I told you I’m off my meds 😢🤧😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I only wanna have sex with a trans person cause I’ve never done it.” So you’re fetishizing trans people? First bod… https://t.co/K8xFuKh1d0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the 2019 Lift Jesus Higher Rally where youth and adults gather to evangelize through uplifting music, test… https://t.co/QugTKedILz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Received a favorable vote today in Senate Judiciary! Onward to the Senate floor.  Thank you Sen. Westerfield for yo… https://t.co/FQQ9pZ2IBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBAonTNT please get better announcers for your late night game. I don’t care about there opinions or stories I wan… https://t.co/fxZL4YyM64]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this was ALL you knew about this administration it would be enough. #impeach45 #reuniteFamilies]]></document><document><![CDATA[my sister has had my phone for the past hour and there’s no idea the damage she’s done lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the state trooper that pulled me over... thank you for not giving me a $500 ticket https://t.co/KsYgAN9Jpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayah_a Get a 2! I’m a 4 which I think would be big on you. I tried to go a size up one time cause I was scared it… https://t.co/6lbzJ0yhtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b_f_r_a_n @DeuceGotti__ @josh_valles1 And btw that has nothing to do with anything cause they had the best record… https://t.co/g6LuzifJ41]]></document></documents></author>