<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Adopt SPECIAL rescued by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from Chestnut #DogMeat #Farm #SouthKorea  She was tied to a pole with no… https://t.co/hsxOozlRwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am available now in Atlanta, Georgia, United States! To contact me, visit https://t.co/4Z2kXmMPil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning Frost #socalwinter #grateful #lifeisgood #notcomplaining #coldforme #nofilter @ Pomona, California https://t.co/laTca68P3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley People are saying it’s ok because the gNg of 8 didn’t say anything.  Wrong is wrong. No vote necessary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always “wyd” and never “wana move to Napa and open a winery?”  :-/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @FoxNews @AmericaNewsroom I think he is probably going to "come out" finally!!!  on @FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[This misty morning, @laurenfturek and I (aka the Hotfooting Historians) fought to the finish of the Run the #Alamo… https://t.co/TshnXqbYcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I can say is im shook an thank god we finally got to see him jump the damn fence #BachelorNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birds at the house in Florida🙂#parrots #birds #florida #parrothouse @ The Parrot House https://t.co/LQYHB2yXUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Synphamy @Jenerator72 @flowerreflects @HarveyWeinstein Not everything on TV....I’m not going to argue with an idiot either]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeff_Jacoby @ofsevit @reillyadam It’s not just about bikes. It’s about transit. Especially buses. @MassINCPolling… https://t.co/fSUjiIoRAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[fucking darian being this perfect ass boy. good looks, good grades, loads of friends, could have any girl that he w… https://t.co/ip2qNGjtln]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found it odd, too, that Elliott only spoke about home care/hospital discharge follow up and very little else.  Sh… https://t.co/KerKs858eJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilKCCeleb Right, not like they can run after you?! But as someone who has been a caregiver you get into a mindset… https://t.co/hpppWA6M4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[#proudcoach doesn’t even begin to cover it!!! #morethanbasketball ❤️🧡💛💚💙💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mary60053440 @Valac666 @NYmitton @TeamSalBrian @SharonG40210896 @JaneColes2 @Kitty_Goncalves @735BlackSheep… https://t.co/JZPPIcwTDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#victoriagottimovie guess what! @MauriceBenard will blow you away well done sir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toi_potts @JSOPIO @BlueWalkPoconos @propacop @FLSheriffs @NatPoliceAssoc @NationalSheriff @PolicingNews… https://t.co/yBxMRh77dQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#d4d19 Brad Frost opens the 5th(!) designing for digital https://t.co/x7QOEw04Rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stage is like home. #LoveSG 💌 • Follow my poetry page: lovesg_poetry  • #HopeDealer #SGThePoeticLifter #poetry… https://t.co/l8H5MY40zE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you made your appointment for your mammogram yet? Beast Cancer don’t care what race or gender you are!! Many d… https://t.co/Ay6zF4l729]]></document><document><![CDATA[handbag go-backs in personal styling #nordstromstylists #lovehandbags @ Seattle, Washington https://t.co/jyEJSe8ZfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am an Aries and that’s why I am going to be so grateful for you and your mom]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OleMiss y’all got basketball players kneelin before the game starts😖Who down there needs to handle it😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep telling myself that it’s just a phase and that it’ll go away eventually... But, what if it doesn’t?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ken_Rosenthal @FOX29philly @JeffPassan Congratulations @Phillies but what about #hungerinourcity #clubsforkids… https://t.co/cYvOglBIMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CartoonHeroGuy @JimB_85 Yeah, good idea. Cheeky and if I ever imagined Kazooie having an accent different from Ban… https://t.co/0K1TYiPfpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying for God’s Guidance and Direction  of Georgia Legislators - HB757  SB 221, Thank You  Marty Harbin, and CoSp… https://t.co/pXIoYagI2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[to the sweetest little boy who told me happy valentine’s day this morning, i hope you grow up to be a lady killer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @FirstLadyNJ for speaking truth about #MaternalJustice. #NURTURENJ understands the true social determinan… https://t.co/MH0mLRNqfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch me in my hotel room listening to @schnitt_talk for the whole week]]></document><document><![CDATA[I earned cash back pretty quickly. Ty it! Join Ibotta to earn cash back rewards on everyday purchases. Sign up and… https://t.co/0WIO8XlOFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sean_C_Larkin I can’t believe Mr. Ageless just capped a story about a “middle aged” 40 year old!  😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PadmaLakshmi @tomcolicchio why was there an auction where they spent 80$ on radishes when they just went to Whole… https://t.co/7Weu55iXK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aiello_luke @Ro12Two @Twitter I'd say we'd be better off without Twitter as it was revolutionary in increasing the… https://t.co/2QQx4mbX8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[#joycemeyer #prayer #amen       When Good Things Happen to People Who Have Hurt You   Have you ever seen someone re… https://t.co/USJhxgkjSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙋🏽‍♀️When all seems #cloudy and #unclear to me, I have to have the #faith in knowing that #God will always be there… https://t.co/PMbRvaELfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a heads up twitter world, I’m having surgery tomorrow! Nothing too major, just getting my wisdom teeth removed… https://t.co/BbIONw42WF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resisters yes we must not let history repeat itself #VoteBlueNoMatterWho2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pos Scumbags..how can someone do this to an animal!? That dog would have died an extremely painful death..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinBond1 @_DishinDays Yes. But he told Ciara that he wanted to kill his own sister yesterday. He still has that literal killer instinct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DefenseBaron Okay, don't see Jesus Christ. Do see a flying saucer with a mushroom on top.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an incredible show!  So proud of every #WeAreDGN Trojan who was part of the show.  Every detail was perfection… https://t.co/Nb3MBHuaGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dumb @DevinNunes  Just shows the desperation of #Republicans to trash Dems. Now they're literally grasping at straw… https://t.co/7uksEOcHIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do all my friends live so far away. 😭 Well not the ones in Calhoun, but the otherssss 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obianuju God Bless this couple for giving Albi the opportunity be born and loved for the time he survived.  So hea… https://t.co/r4QcWGjKe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grammysue67 I'm a truck drive I tune in to Fox News sometimes because I'm bored. The things they say on that chann… https://t.co/E6SnEA051Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[who lives in Austin and is looking for a roommate I’m deadass thinking of just leaving EP no questions asked ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_anaacabrera19 @byanneyt1 @abigailaranda_ Wait hold up bitch since we putting her out like that. She will go to VS… https://t.co/RIz0NQcr80]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnHookfox10 @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama The result of this pool pointing that Obama would be chosen for Presid… https://t.co/K7WjMgSFIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas brothers getting back together is the best thing that’s happened in my life since fried Oreos 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Japanese Ambassador Shinsuke J. Sugiyama in the house!! https://t.co/wBOCMXijsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Library wine tasting lenzwine #nofo #liwines #winestagram #librarywines @ The Lenz Winery https://t.co/kYPBn1e1v7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @GabbyGiffords @lucymcbath @SpeakerPelosi Now how are all the clintonsides gonna happen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grant helped momma sort alphabet tub items last night! https://t.co/5kVd0qmZx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @Bakari_Sellers Joe Biden is writing $30M book. Sure he will run to sell it well 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm reduced to flipping off the tv when Johnny comes on to challenges us to stand for policies that drive positive change in the workplace]]></document><document><![CDATA[my headphones died while walking to class &amp; my music started blasting out loud, rip 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCazter @NicolaTSLI @anne_theriault So true. How many kids out there have stunted potential because they’re cons… https://t.co/st0NrGenIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sad I’m not with my chiquita but I’m glad I was able to still give her her gifts. What I’m more excited about i… https://t.co/enXSCYrmOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicatNY @mferrell6741 I have to watch it tonight. I got caught up watching a Turkish TV series on Netflix over the weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adammc123 Maybe just offer to pay for it and see if Biden &amp; Bernie argue over whose gonna pay the check for about 10 years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in the back seat with your baby making sure he breaths every minute #justmomthings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday! The office I work at is really slow today it almost feels like the weekend will never be here 😭 What… https://t.co/YG8uCkRhTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Bet THAT won’t make his day.  The twit has been hiding out for days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never judge someone by how dirty OR clean their hands are. Build respect, not pedestals. #farmlove https://t.co/MHtb0cv0Gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @USDA bioengineered label vs @NonGMOProject label. Can’t say I think @foodscibabe’s #agdaily article is wrong.… https://t.co/MpBWmm099K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 467 Route 35 #Mantoloking #NJ  #realestate https://t.co/MhcXawnnkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lifetime fan of @brookeshields 👏👏👏 amazing seeing her host the forbestravelguide 2019 awards gala at @beverlyhilton… https://t.co/ohvb1Urqjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hangtenstories 826   Don’t write #credos in stone, If composed in dry-erase]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud to represent the @AdCouncil throughout this creatively inspiring partnership with @YouTube. When creativit… https://t.co/fiIQztJuFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 How about ALL of them considering honor, dignity, truth, and respect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#boglewinery #marvelousmonday #boglevineyards #vintagewine #vintage #merlot #merlotwine #california #californiawine… https://t.co/JoM6nR3Jnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProtectaPet @KatzenworldBlog @ShelleyGj @sarahlcrowley @GoodVetGuide @ISFMcats @Completely_Cats Wow that’s nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReeseNeedsAHug Just  wanted to give you an update https://t.co/CPZqLAWWNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[all my friends are soo nice, they always remind me how good of a mom i am 😩💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite slide from the Cave Fest talks with Nerd Nite at Alamo - Slaughter Lane yesterday.  . .… https://t.co/DGPbQpVSPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[you gotta later to say fuck them just like they say fuck you &amp; keep it moving . ✌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why students (and their teachers) love spoken word poetry... happy to be interviewed for this. Our students need mo… https://t.co/62PhhRY6Pt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judgealexferrer Every presidential candidate since 1968 (when Nixon was caught cheating on his taxes) has been pre… https://t.co/hSLcrBDjDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vankapro @HuffPostPol I say bravo. Not a legitimate news network and should not be treated as one. Can you imagine… https://t.co/8K8dVLCxT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[That jacket is tight son..now run that sh*t nah mean 😭😁😂😂🤣🤣🤣🤣💯👏👏👏👏 #slay #runit @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/pxmwiHkN9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chipotle Mexican Grill in Glen Ellyn, IL https://t.co/DUEJjikPBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[pueden creer que estoy preocupada por algo que va a pasar en septiembre ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnypauling Yeah, actually. It's about 10-20%. But critique gets the most retweets so it seems like more. Check out my TL for yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Know exactly where you are at all times with Rino 530HCx and the precision of high-sensitivity GPS. Th… https://t.co/EFmVRokNwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow assassination classroom really got me all up in my feels right now damn https://t.co/RwFII8nJMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_David_Edward Yea, was going for the breakneck and wanted to rank up faster. Solo queue sucks. We ended up with a 12 game winning streak]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy #InternatioalWomensDay  to some of the strongest women I know + many many more💘💜💓 https://t.co/bpgMAD7lHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re an adult when you spend $20 on six pairs of socks 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dream sequence that begins “Our Lips Are Sealed” boldly asserts that, due to their popularity, the Olsen twins’… https://t.co/MgXP50HvpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Send @AOC to jail TODAY.   She is so wrong but is wielding power and arrogance and self aggrandizeme… https://t.co/Uw4CE9qOPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get shade from everyone when I say this but like let’s be real it’s not good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheVandals  @musink_tatfest @ The Hangar at the OC Fair https://t.co/u335EvucXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh I could eat tomatoes slices all day as if they were potato chips ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when I wake up from a good ass dream &amp; realize it wasn’t real]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/krhiS142EF  Hi Everybody! It’s Sahara Herschtein here playing #roblox #theincredibles wearing my… https://t.co/NRoX2HUABF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great crowds, amazing bikes and epic people watching all day long.  #daytonabikeweek2019 #pp405 #harleyfatboy… https://t.co/XAPrjz0uef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bellathorne And I can smoke weed in every room??? Will I get to pet the animals these are things I need to know]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's #warnkychallengewednesday is trying to walk across a balance item of some sort (low to the ground for safet… https://t.co/pnwMuiSNer]]></document></documents></author>