<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheKidIrv24 @UnkhanciousAmir @SmokinYungBruno @SibbieBoxing @Yogi_CapAlot @avondale_cincy @TyiFalls @The1stWright… https://t.co/AKiOh8DSRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew! Seek the truth, tell the truth. One💚 ! ☯️☮️👹 Trichome Thursday! https://t.co/y7l8Op8A1E… https://t.co/4PsP1JfKGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I support any fan who has enough guts and determination to meet their favorite wrestler. Yes I was called crazy and… https://t.co/gkQ3tVdrOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cernovich It's the violent white MAGA man, vote for me routine. https://t.co/4qwznoTJdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good read. Like it or not, it’s a new era that requires change —Asia’s leaders have a more hard-nosed assessment… https://t.co/Ra8dqAxOLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[my nhl picks were great last night 8 right 3 wrong i am getting better with age]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #TeamFlash on @TheTylt—’The Flash’ is my favorite CW superhero show https://t.co/QRYnnycsWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando tu novio te da un masaje de cuello // uterino. https://t.co/MD0M4m7NAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[4\ [here it comes...] THE COURT: Randomly does not involve the application of human intelligence. You looked at mul… https://t.co/0SMgvKBUHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[S Fairfax Ave &amp; W 3rd St Los Angeles, CA 90048 https://t.co/4x6y7hRVsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nilegirl @Refinery29 Yes! For all their forced ubiquity, they are incredibly boring. I be]]></document><document><![CDATA[i bought a shower curtain with jeff goldblums face on it as a joke have used it for over a year and now jeff goldbl… https://t.co/zZ5wngUJeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[yeah its only been 8 hours since ive smoked, yes my anxiety is already through the roof, we exist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flawless execution of the Cote HNO from long distance @Stugotz790 @LeBatardShow @gregcote]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Machete Kills” #machetekills #austintexas #moviestills #ricotorresphoto #troublemakerstudios #sofiavergara… https://t.co/hWXVhQAeGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait Cohen just said that he was contacted to "fix" the harm that the leaked video was going to do. WAIT there were… https://t.co/JBnshN2tBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse coming through ports of entry where the administration refuses to allocate resources and staff. misguid… https://t.co/xuFHERg4kg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBonvoyAssist I am not a Bonvoy member and certainly do not want to become one after this situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody want FREE tickets today?  @BBNcrew @Real923LA  #LouieInYourNeighborhood 🚗🏘🎟 @ Big Boy's Neighborhood https://t.co/o6Kwir5nld]]></document><document><![CDATA[[lpfan2017] sings Lying From You by Linkin Park, what an incredible voice on The Voice! #music #karaoke #sing  https://t.co/SxmO7mYrdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MongoGoesInsane @martinonyc Yes, but they don't want to bid against themselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren praises Patty Murray for ‘fighting for our youngest kids’ — well, not the youngest https://t.co/aiJ7TVVDgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaambeats Have u used them??? Milwaukee has improved tremendously in the last few years. Have you SEEN all the fuel line?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoustacheClubUS That’s what I’m aspiring to be. We should try to turn me into a fitness influencer and chronicle it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won’t be buying one.  However,...If she reads Atlas Shrugged first(or any book without pictures over 200 pages),… https://t.co/RlRgBfv2ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny that us has the same top as the bitter, only a little bigger.  But the label fits the bottle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Police charged a 12-year-old boy this evening for allegedly making a threatening Facebook post referencin… https://t.co/WnufgyjnlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning #pittsburgh !!! ☀️🌈. . It’s DAY 2 of #warehousesale - thank you everyone yesterday for cleaning us out… https://t.co/KTxYMqKnlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino TheAOC GREEN PLAN is another fraud being perpetrated on the American public.A completely idiotic proposal… https://t.co/9ZPzKKOPIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone else having issues with CCH Prosystm fx Tax crashing when it kicks you out after inactivity? It's a pain… https://t.co/ew7YyqLmQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro Freezing buns off this winter.  Would appreciate some other hoax to shake me down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Higher Further Faster Baby! Here we go! #movienight captainmarvelofficial @marvel marvelentertainment @brielarson… https://t.co/DvqLkJcgXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee Huck, you’re an idiot. What if instead of progressives not reproducing, we get right wing radicals… https://t.co/IsMQNQBcBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@docncsu @HornetsOnFSSE @SwarmnSting @hornets Couldn’t agree more with you ^ to see that shows where he’s at mental… https://t.co/T9B84cGRO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when I drive a normal car then drive my shelby can feel the power difference]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TroyStradford Can you please tag the @MiamiDolphins in this tweet please]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Lee with the Billy Garza 4  entertained a room full of dance enthusiasts at the Mercer Street Dance Hall, Sat… https://t.co/LvMCYyNsf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @SpaceCorpsUS What's with calling people names why can't you act like a President? You're a total jerk off for doing that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidNbreslauer @eighteenb You guys are making new stuff every week! What's next hummingbird inspired jet-packs (I hope)?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevOnStage 1 Doritos red mixed with cheetos  2 BBQ lays  3 cool ranch  4 lays  ....... 5 carrots  6 fritos  @ Me]]></document><document><![CDATA[this good samaritan at the dealership pulled out his nintendo switch and offered to play mario kart with me while w… https://t.co/g5Mb4WkWtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CJHoytABC27 With the right link this time: Philly has had the highest murder rate among large US cities (+1M pop)… https://t.co/h5sTPIwzj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will toxic masculinity stop people from listening to the Jonas Brothers tonight?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Braised octopus and fresh made ricotta appetizers here at @molinarimangia A great way to refuel after a long biz tr… https://t.co/HFfpR0xRVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#A1ponyparty #rainbowunicorn #ponyride #ponyparty @ A One of a Kind Pony Party https://t.co/MxSABbTFyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[💗With My Princess💗 @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/GH7xsjsZlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[need this week to go good! Sending positive energy out into the universe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Daylight savings time for Fucking me, out of an hour of my life; that I can never get back Lol.… https://t.co/KRR6WlHyzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emily Pfalzer makes its 2-0. Spin o Rama pass from one circle to the other by Scamurra sets it up. Goes down as a l… https://t.co/7Id6bF8iED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1wayblick_ They say 229 go so hard for it cause they really hurt that they from there but they don’t want nobody to know]]></document><document><![CDATA[Engel &amp; Völkers Exchange 2019  International panel-Germany, Italy, France &amp; Dubai  #milliondollarlisting… https://t.co/4LwaoPhk8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockTom84 You realize you’re going to miss out on all of the great tweets about Bernie Kosar, Bernie Madoff, and t… https://t.co/vMMeRgKcn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder what’ll feel like if I dated someone out of my reach? You know, someone popular, but you’re just a normal hu… https://t.co/Q2dL8fJTiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack How come the new socialist Democratic Party has the same goals as our enemies,we have more evidence that… https://t.co/HRhj3nxQbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HIMSS19 about to give my #bluebutton 2.0 presentation on #4849 @hl7 #Fhir booth https://t.co/wQGFwOA7cl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Countdown to @GOP calling him unamerican over support for gun safety: 5...4...3...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1JBoogie_ @roachyroach23 Deff can be on that tho mfs git some good rest last night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying @FloridaBaptists pastors and churches, Habakkuk 3:2 O LORD, I have heard Your speech and was afraid; O LORD… https://t.co/2RUAZsPbVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pugsfran @TUSidelines He single handedly beats every team.  I have to see this one on 5 game he plays.  Have to as… https://t.co/be5ltQrRSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two summits. Two photo ops. Two strikeouts. With a leader who served his uncle to dogs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PresidencialVen @CORPOELECinfo @vladimirpadrino No necesitan patruyar nada. Váyanse ustedes y listo. ¡NO LOS QUEREMOS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cornandcalves @ben_fritz_ @jrow9670 @the_meat_lady @corbittwall We’ve got a seed customer, built a state of the ar… https://t.co/DspST3RnBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay had to re-do this, gotta be specific                          🕯               🕯              🕯         🕯… https://t.co/9pGrN0YEkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a Michigan fan I fully support Twitter banning App State’s account 😪 #neverforget]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s difficult to fathom the rationale. And remember the 4 principles of mitigating light pollution. 1. Shield outd… https://t.co/7HoIrrEoiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEED TO READ!!!  Apparently it is not just the Elected people we need concern ourselves with in our Governments.  https://t.co/wjKbv8LQmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Susan_Loaiza believe me, if that horse is sniffing anywhere near 10-1 I will bet the living hell out of him. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benholden28 @Neill52Cameron @CFB_Overtime @bgjccc Oregon has cool Jerseys, the best looking cheerleaders, better w… https://t.co/xbivRm7jUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulTheDaly Exactly. Role model the behavior we want to see, don’t ask or tell.💁🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Crucial Mass by @BrewingWeight @ Dorothy Waring's Vista — https://t.co/vcWcPSpgT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join us for the Ghost Bike ceremony for Paula Sharaga on Sunday Feb. 24 at 2pm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember my first time in LA. I went to the Santa Monica Pier which is on Ocean Avenue and the whole time I rode… https://t.co/Ofh3dhgDsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Monday Our Revolution sends out mass email message from Michael Bennett urging people to donate to Bernie Sander… https://t.co/OSnEWSn4KE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@93XRT The Futures So Bright I Gotta Wear Shades, Blinded by The Light, Mr. Brightside]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dadbaddy @Global_Occupant @zypisfy @debbiepalm44 @Glad2bAtheist @PolyRhuagh @yrysbryd @JordivisionD @horusrage… https://t.co/apkj9Cvgfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristenNolting Glad to help! Next time you see a duct, I hope you hear: https://t.co/EcOLoNg5Nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This show was so funny, will it stay out of politics and just be about life or will it force feed is liberal propag… https://t.co/IZEdiKLIvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like trump ripping off people attending trump u.... getting his charity to bribe the Florida AG...]]></document><document><![CDATA[In replacing Nacho Piatti in 84th min, Zachary Brault-Guillard definitively becomes the 102nd player to appear for… https://t.co/lBsitzXafa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MOI2I2OW @ZeeMatic1 @Braxtonlit @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Yes remember what tick's of politician's. Rich peo… https://t.co/9PaYHiNg0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion Williamson se acaba de lesionar la rodilla.   Duke anuncia que NO regresará al partido de hoy ante North Carol… https://t.co/IPouFdZKrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Briteeye777 @cheriseguilfoil @ritasue2264 @pajacobs78 @trumpinator_the @ezbreezi @g3man43 @uninstaalled… https://t.co/OwYBY6PTfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnvarlas Bearden is really good, 2 D1 guards and a 6'10 going to UT, they look like a Memphis team]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muchas felicidades por tu @P_TvyNovelas la mejor Villana @claudia3martin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandlestickWill They are the only team without a banner in Staples, guessing they won’t overtake the Lakers as LA’… https://t.co/tsyJgWHRYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a valid word...yet. #sextremely #wordswithfriends @WordsWFriends #scrabuloso #words #spelling #language #app… https://t.co/xduXPFK1Br]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro this man Hami hit the honey dip....AFTER jumping over Shaq. To pull off the honey dip alone, ya realize how high u gotta get up ? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guerrillacrypto @RealJamesWoods Something is in the colleges/school systems, the media, the big tech companies, like what’s going on??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenKamalaHarris just curious, what exact day was it, when you sold your soul? Was it when u failed to stand up for… https://t.co/MilysaOiJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiredGuns @JeremyDyson Yeah now it’s Jackson’s Social Club &amp; BrewHouse]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Always Sunny In Feltonville in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/AIi5nOTiUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hogs_All_Day It was good once the excitement settled in it looked better, I hope today is a sign of aggression fro… https://t.co/cYHo1jSpPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being at Shepherd's Conference has confirmed one thing. Christianity has a celebrity problem, as evident with the p… https://t.co/P3ZYpd6p9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when I text somebody and I'm like, "Wyd tonight?" But for some reason my phone says, "STD tonight?" No wonde… https://t.co/hVMOfV8G0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% correct remember the Democrats The Party of the KKK and slavery, they weren't too fond of Catholics or Jews ei… https://t.co/q2R4guTHfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone know what brand has #corgi diapers? #parenting #help #babies https://t.co/JgxO4s4FR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un emploi d’été ça vous tente? ☺️https://t.co/jUp9sGITed #PolQc #PolLvl #Laval https://t.co/OiPaR6ARCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[OFICIAL, HIPÓLITO MEJÍA EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Yo… https://t.co/3GHcSltEQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who tells me Luna isn’t the cutest is a liar and a fake. https://t.co/wFfQGmMR9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a week so far. Met new friends, updated on latest in politics, shared with our representatives, and finally to… https://t.co/91FzsF3nTe]]></document></documents></author>