<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JessCottoo Okay I drank oat milk for the first time today and sis🙌🏽❤️ so I stan for this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolewagner667 Really??? Envíame su información. En abril regreso a PR. Tengo varias personas que dan la orientac… https://t.co/eKgPuPQ11N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eck43 @PeteAbe @NESN @RedSox We are certainly looking forward to having you. Your style of announcing is second to none.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah water is DEFINITELY not as good as wine 😅 #fdiets https://t.co/B2QDxolzqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thechloebird Thought of you and the pep talk you gave me before my last sociology test! 🙌🏼😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillAFox29 @KarenFox29 @thomasdrayton @SueSerioFox29 @BobKellyFOX29 That's the 3rd decompose body found in Philade… https://t.co/xEuiVmlMOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honoured to receive the From Mentee to Mentor Award @TRIEC #TRIECmentoring #FutureofMentoring https://t.co/dr4FKkuiND]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally I can go to another @rascalflatts  @JayDeMarcus  show! https://t.co/3i6u0V5E6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need RTS to hurry up and announce who sings what night.  Cause I need to know if I need to leave work early 2 Friday’s in a row.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey everyone: could you do me a hige favor and vote for my aunt? She’s 80 and in poor health  and would just be tic… https://t.co/f7xsr8CvKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter @mizj626n Mcconnell could rain him in and doesn’t. GOP enables. I wonder why....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted a challenge from @CGurskyj to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, just covers. (I’ve done th… https://t.co/fPEf7njlvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poniss_CHET i love cloudy/gloomy weather so much 😤 cali is rarely like that tho smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frozen: let it go  Disney on ice!!! @ Vivint Smart Home Arena https://t.co/TouhuWUSjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[How has nobody ever used the term “calmomille” when referring to chamomile tea?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday absolutely gorgeous (and F*ing cold!) #PNWwonderland #Snow #Evergreens #Winter #NWwashington @ Arlington, Wa… https://t.co/eJ2q8i7TIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Earpapalooza Happy Birthday!  Hope you had a god one! https://t.co/qfoDZ1We9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved watching my girl dance during halftime of tonight's game! @ Middlebury Community Schools https://t.co/tIB5nXdMnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshgroban thank you so much for the awesome concert/movie. We are huge fans, but you didn't stop in our area, wit… https://t.co/BrREdrQyQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna drink and have a game night. And not have to go back to work for about 2 months.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerronJordan @amnewsboy What’s wrong with you?! They look amazing! https://t.co/f8L6gJqnP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilJSpinksART @JerryFalwellJr @ArkEncounter I am sorry you see it that way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carlos_Can_Do @CunningSq16 @Barb81146 @chefrocky413 @strom_annette @MisleaderC @tpcowgurl @thesaucyliberal… https://t.co/aIFmVo3GAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d pay off all my debt, pay off my college degrees, and go from there. After putting half of the money into savings]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty happy thinking about how pissed off and miserable Trump is, pouting and shouting in AF1, about how every… https://t.co/t3Or0EGdrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may have to watch the ep this morning...ya know, for the...plot. Yep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaAdlerr Working 2 jobs?? Yuck.  I barely handle the 45 hours I do at my current job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFLOK2Ask A5: Empower, facilitate, and model instruction that is inclusive and integrated with the arts. #OK2Ask]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun day with my Functional Skills valentines @LBSharks @ISDMsTaylor They make my heart smile 😍 #isdstrong… https://t.co/yDsVLOFN1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BojorquezMarce @madresdlaPatria Y entonces esto que significa? https://t.co/mHzcDd24Yv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished grading student presentations from my General Music Class. The progress being made is phenomenal. I’m… https://t.co/SXeT6zRO7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[“from now on” is one of the most underrated songs on the greatest showman soundtrack😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWToday Trying to score FOP for my wife. It’s her favorite ride! Also trying to score Slinky Dog Dash for her sin… https://t.co/njdorYeGlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Women’s Day! A special thank you to all the women in the #VixenArmy that bring out the best version of me, ev… https://t.co/lSicV0xvpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to be teaching Reiki Level 1 today! Changing the world one soul at a time, with love 💕 @ Namaste Healthy… https://t.co/p8sVjKoPsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[New UN report warns about #biodiversity loss threat to global food supply. https://t.co/ESFXxv8Cwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarcroftEagles registration for Spring 2019 Intersession starts this Monday!!! #TeamBarcroft https://t.co/YyHMnPoJmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MontanaLives first birds, now dolphins... smh. wake UP america https://t.co/GL6vXtGAiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[first day, I was in my bra and board shorts, so I then showed Father. Then I told him how Fr copied it and sent it… https://t.co/ZahFCAcWha]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally finished the front and am moving along on the back #jangankal2019 #oliveknits #leadingmenfiberarts… https://t.co/Y7OhWnQySn]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 of my little cousins posted tweets back to back on my feed roasting khloe kardashian and it just made my whole day 😂 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[That one Day a year we work on a Saturday!! #challengerthatsmyschool #ilovemyjob so I dont mind 💕 Open House starts… https://t.co/jWrPkDwVzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because AS A VICTIM i’m tired of seeing people accuse others of r*pe simply because their significant other isn’t d… https://t.co/6PWtnqYW8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you God for another day and for the weekend please watch over andruw today help Shelby give my husband streng… https://t.co/ApSkEgnMeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rain or shine Today is the Trunk Show not to be missed#@GiseleClothing #trunkshow #rocknroll #tees #jacketstyle… https://t.co/ujdyHLwOpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Guess Me &amp;Shawty Not Going Talk Either Cause  I'm Not Hitting Her Up Period]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand how it’s possible to lose your big ass makeup bag but I did that. It has been lost for a week an… https://t.co/OtxTtLwURy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dans la vie il faut rester humble ne cherche pas a te jeter des fleurs mais laisse les gens parler de tes bienfaits]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smitty_1911 So fucking bad! I swear if this was a white actor there wouldn’t be this much push back in the story.… https://t.co/jU2siTfNEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[In today’s #HealthAlert-Why you should just say NO even to E-cigs. They may not be as benign as many believe accord… https://t.co/SLkQU1Gdrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Larger Than Life by @backstreetboys on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/npDdO5sUo5 https://t.co/eYUD1qSbUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MewllerRawr @TechWriter2015 I've had to start over [followers], changed my handle a few times, hacked/changed pass… https://t.co/GFjbHR6yfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews This is crazy I can't believe both parties are screaming for these traitors… https://t.co/myB8tLOaPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucky_im_irish @LacedUpBreezy I love angry orchards too though don’t rule them out🗣🗣🗣🗣 add a shot of fireball to a… https://t.co/PqleZegL5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rscottpenrod I donno. I think I might have gone with bat shit crazy. 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the real reason I am in Austin is this! Space Traffic Management Conference - Progress Through Collaboration. It… https://t.co/SrcufMLeDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CCPS_LibertyHS leads @CenturyGirlsBa1 42-40 with 1:31 left to play. #CVHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be brave, be humble 😏 Still reeling from last night,but I'm so satisfied! Thank you @privenyofficial and baekhyunee… https://t.co/GN1IqCKrek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hickenlooper (updates his Twitter handle) and officially runs for president. Here’s the release: Stand Tall… https://t.co/fqfPSgwN3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s gone. Seasonal depression back (or just depression? Idk) Was a nice few hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentines day fun in first grade! @MrsQuanaCurtis https://t.co/0wVuYOOcYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo much that I love.  My favorites that I’m constantly going back to are Breaking In by @SomewhereApart SSD by… https://t.co/PPFoXlfKS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmaooo one time this girl told me she was a dancer and I was like oh no way!! where do you strip at???? and she say… https://t.co/zUqXAkhOJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone tried to disrespect me and I’m not going to let anyone treat me like that so I robbed and left because I respect myself!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy GUSaversary ally_dunham 💞💪🐎!  Wow times does fly by - just 365 days ago you began a new adventure with Gus Gu… https://t.co/hg8JAHLUW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans Yes..It's a very sad day. 😔      R.I.P  LUKE PERRY AND KEITH FLINT 🙏❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scotbot @AOCpress True, there are a few parody accounts around that sound so close to the person, I have to check… https://t.co/vTVCEy5eAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[A si es nada más ni nada menos con el presidente de la primera Potencia del mundo que tal]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨Dead mayor in Oklahoma headed to runoff in general election: report  https://t.co/rQIEoBqnjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OkayCharisse It’s all good in the hood! Miss seeing you in person, but VERY proud to say “Ay, I know her,” when it… https://t.co/ZICWu54ywW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when I'm sitting nice and still in a room and then the lights turn off bc I'm sitting nice and still.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trickster1966 @WiHmonth @NOFSpodcast The whole scene in the bar is magic to me. https://t.co/uJOPnCZcYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[new kids on the block... i like what you’re doing.   backstreet boys... i like what you’re doing.   jonas brothers.… https://t.co/g7yJwK6zOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your weekend wear!!! Check out @ADopeStore  for a DOPE T-shirt!!! #weekendvibes #weekend #tshirt… https://t.co/VPrjg3aEy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WithGregOrth there are #climbers and #campers in organizations. Which one are you?! #sales #business https://t.co/O2QkMsDlM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaFKenney1 As one who was in the performing arts for decades, its nice to create something permanent for a change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yvresse69 @sylvainreynard I just saw it myself it was a wonderful tribute to Freddie and the band.  Bohemian Raspo… https://t.co/dS8mSaGBsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[6am is dark again... #StillSpringHopeful 9 days and counting..plus temps on the way! 🌷🤞🏻❤️ #spring #daylightsavings… https://t.co/JRrQbArQZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone in vampire diaries dresses like they’re from an old navy catalog ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[here's some entertainment. WTF grumpy cat? Why so rude? Click through for more WTF Wednesday pics! https://t.co/HIQEEEPr5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christomlin My husband- who rises daily to pray with me and seek the Lord]]></document><document><![CDATA[15 years ain’t enough, she survived the fucking Holocaust only to get killed by some fucking crack head. THIS shit… https://t.co/fD1yf2zSdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[117 años de historia. Hay muchas noches negras, quizás ninguna semana como está que acabamos de terminar, pero tamb… https://t.co/8QYISIi3tj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I doubt that people will ever forget the disrespect she has shown this president. I know that I never will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews The greatest scandal in American history is that a corrupt, con man was placed in office… https://t.co/uFx1ovhklO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leona_Clevenger @AgbaGbolly @Lahoneyy @TheMedicalShots Rarely,it is general knowledge the our animal children carr… https://t.co/WT8YbPndhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Apple Pie J.R.E.A.M. by @burleyoak at @dainep — https://t.co/YwTkJm0btz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frosty_shoulder @Pharmdoll5 Does your school have a counseling center? When I was in college, the counselors at th… https://t.co/99ls5w7Wxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a lot of people that owes him and big thank you. He was so generous and kind. That's what he should be hono… https://t.co/VODQWeIHF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackyyJack @Chupacaubrey @LifeboatNetwork I’m not sure what we can do about this. While obviously this worries me… https://t.co/u66aLJRe37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanGratz Wow, you’re awesome! I’m sure you made many, many kids very happy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrNDisis Dr. Vogelzang just highlighted some promising data for this combo in endothelial ca.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring practice starts today which means football season is basically here 🤩🤩🤩🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[I felt cute today but probably look ugly. Paid $400+ for a new tooth  Paid $100+ for the doctor to tell me that mid… https://t.co/ihHg94MQ8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a five day old egg, cheese and croissant sandwich for breakfast, so let’s see if I survive the day. Gambling my literal life away...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only 2 reasons I hate Florida: 1.) old, rich, white conservatives  2.) no Dubia roaches]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_real_LAFord You are so right. I just love him. He is so hireal. No bull. And he is very warm and loving. I jus… https://t.co/g1c1w5bTXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anton47492193 @Bozesgirl66 @sheri_lynn95252 @social_stars Aww thank you Anton! If it's in God's plan, we will see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giving up Mexican food for #lent ...it’s gonna be a long 40 days!!! I’m already thinking of what I’m gonna have for… https://t.co/D1xconKkDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rustytin #galvanizedmetal #storagesolutions #vintagewicker #livingstonmanor @ Livingston Manor, New York https://t.co/lk4JNZpqzn]]></document></documents></author>