<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Harlem Globetrotters are so much fun.  Great, great entertainment that never misses!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little snug yet  #teamogre #theogrecompound #nutrishopmtjuliet #shr #superhumanradio #beverlyinternational… https://t.co/ocgPLt82Oi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deanondraft Not having a good season until he played is a great take - Kyler had an 85.7% completion percentage an… https://t.co/ohbsqNQln3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Dave &amp; Buster's - @daveandbusters in Myrtle Beach, SC https://t.co/HyEYxD4yLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s like three stages of female existence in my sphere: “Daddy’s Gone”, “Mommy’s Home” and “whats good fam?”  C… https://t.co/QGZW4f4nM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude had to go live on Periscope to defend himself from @AOC and her “attack” on him. 😂 What a baby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gretchenho I knew how to make all those kinds of coconut leaves weavings. https://t.co/N3GSYecGh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The scholarships, the athletic gear, the existing living stipend, the direct marketing ans opportunity to showcase… https://t.co/vPs2f5zOdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthanVanSciver Get your cwp you do important work and you have a right to feel safe and not be stalked by idiots]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Bring your own reusable bags you idiot.  That’s what concerned Americans do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[People don’t know you / don’t wanna get to know you and still got stupid shit to say / do in your life. GETRIDOFDEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Michael Cohen testimony is beyond petty. Talking about POTUS grades in high school? This is pathetic!… https://t.co/2elkfcnNzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s an epidemic man...   It perpetuates a cycle of “excuse making” and passes on through the generations.  It’s al… https://t.co/zgxNsD6Ex6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pelotrain So many hashtags to choose from...... https://t.co/1EZiMbiygq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jil_slander Whenever I see that signage in real life it makes me feel like I did a bump of ket ......]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should be, but the independent institution charged with being salt and light has abdicated its responsibility th… https://t.co/48nXxVJbe7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SKCmatchday @MLS @TheChampions @CAIPanama @PhilaUnion @cmpark The boys just looked destroyed out there at the end.… https://t.co/fzX4Ucynnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Really Gone by CHVRCHES. https://t.co/Q4beGCAoGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow...  loser teachers huh?  This entire family has no filter at all.  Like listening to a child under 5 years old… https://t.co/hBV1unAemd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well damn bryce that was a classy move honoring doc https://t.co/xVo0HHBD9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Love 🙏🏾💛  @atticuspoetry   #positivequotes #lovequotes love #poetrycommunity #goodvibes #newlove @ Los Angeles,… https://t.co/wFWbUqnOkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toridcprw Yes my sister Tori D! amen!  The “Lover” of it is indeed the root of all evil!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch Wow such bluster and stupidity! We must fight back and pray for their souls!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone with a speech disorder is struggling to talk, completing their sentence for them is not helpful, it's actually crummy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baugh now makes the 5th player who has worn a Team Thad jersey in the past 5 classes (2015-19): Martin, Marshall, H… https://t.co/3vtnLUuu2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNotriousBob @Crazy4OReilly90 @LakeEffectXJ @DragonMom98 @MsAFromBK @SandiMarie79 @Jack_WanderS @lno09281978… https://t.co/1I1qE4i2xz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Pliny the Elder by Russian River Brewing Company @ Russian River Brewing Company — https://t.co/AY3VVnf71h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jef_poskanzer I’m not loving all the rain, but at least it’s not so freaking cold any more!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandyAnd37080 @realDonaldTrump For real 🤨🤨🤨? Naaaa.. wait, You for real 🤨😶🤨? You have to be a fcvking bot. Or not… https://t.co/j4Ork4JcCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you think the going rate is for videos of me on @BookCameo wishing people Happy Birthday while my kids scre… https://t.co/oxOwbLJrOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib You shoulda told that MoFo to “Stop crying. We all have to look in the mirror sometimes.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad to see the season end this way, but what a historical year for @NMUMensBBALL - it was a pleasure covering you a… https://t.co/lSJV98LJDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Otis said “We can’t choose who we’re attracted to. Sometimes the people we like don’t like us back, and there’… https://t.co/8KUeB0lBDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Funday Spring Forward Jerky and Turkey Smoke. Nice to have the extra daylight. Bring on spring!  greenmounta… https://t.co/3P4sQq51TV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscars from last night to tonight. #california #losangeles #pic #picoftheday #instagram #academyawards #oscars2019… https://t.co/JKj3C33BQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macondoneando Ugh I thought that was you but I’m only wearing 1 contact so I wasn’t sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stoked! Shout out to manolitonola for their support! Rum Fiyah in NOLA!!! 🙏🏼 #rumfire #manolitonola #puresinglerum… https://t.co/nBXmnwRABI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattLibman @El_Binario @jdavidgoodman @lachlan You seem confused. We don't want them here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seem to remember OMD having 4 or 5 singles about Joan Of Arc back in the 80s. #Forgotten80s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayadoDeNegro @r9carloss 1 Dudo q lo conozcas  2 Siempre busca incitar a la violencia en toda sus tuit  3 No hace… https://t.co/QFRV3EOjHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I remember hittin licks passed it to the homies, finished off the night grubbed down in the mornin” #TB 😂😂😂😂 old t… https://t.co/wYOe1suAeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[NICE TRY NANCY: Pelosi Says Omar ‘Has a Different Experience in the Use of Words’ | Sean Hannity https://t.co/g7S1JemGGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CroWarrior1978 @NHLReese @FanDuel @NHLNetwork I dropped Rakell for Johansson in one league to day actually]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff And how many #Antifa thugs did the same to MAGA supporters? Not bad for the thousands that come to l… https://t.co/IeYGt4vVlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanMorrow @PhxSaltyDog I think playing away from The ‘Skew will be a good challenge for the Aggies. They have t… https://t.co/ae4THjp6yt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katienotopoulos @deray Just wondering if it would help my little one potty train faster?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Salted Caramel Porter by @properbrewingco @ Proper Brewing Company — https://t.co/NAvNXlqv9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[My valentine ❤️ #tbt to our most recent trip, finding random things to do around San Antonio. She travels like I do… https://t.co/9XtLTczFwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aafstallions @TheAAF @KarterSchult #KarterSchult motor reminds me of #JustinSmith when he was with #49ers .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristenRN202 Seriously asking:  Isn't the point to win the contest with the person in your life, not for a person in your life?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found this in a drawer.  Thinking of you @JON_SNODGRASS 😂 https://t.co/vw19xeYR04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleChefcita Estrategias de Guerra...x desgracia existirán, Pedir x un solución pasifica 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Verse of the day 3.6.19 “Now, therefore,” says the Lord , “Turn to Me with all your heart, With fasting, with weepi… https://t.co/EbABkAjCiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix @UmbrellaAcad If there isn’t another season of the umbrella academy then I’m suing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richeisen @RichEisenShow @chrisbrockman @MichaelDelTufo  https://t.co/RNN13QnN2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Thats funny a Trump talking about Fetishizes.... Being the experts at many ! https://t.co/eKpx29O7by]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ten years on this. Found a baseball league out of it. Not a bad return. #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/YIyGk2Ms6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DOPEisBLUE @erinpyt @kianabeme Thank you for this iconic moment https://t.co/xXapvp58yX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The key to hiding the taste of cannabis butter in baked goods, is savory ingredients.   (And not to taste the batte… https://t.co/x82CCreJZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[To share faith u must own faith. To tell the Story u must know the Story. #It’s all about the Story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Amazon has canceled its plans to build a campus in Queens. I honestly thought this was a done deal. #shocked #Amazon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @OversightDems He needs to be reminded that he can receive additional  prison time for lying to  the committee]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Requirements: Microsoft Office, Word, and Excel”  Do people actually know how to use Excel?   I definitely don’t.… https://t.co/7MjeIzLoNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s was a great experience officiating the @soflinfo Special Olympics FHSAA Championship At the Lakeland Center. https://t.co/Q3fXhtlexy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since Pokémon Gen 8 is based off the UK I’m naming my starter Tom Holland]]></document><document><![CDATA[La distancia como que da nostalgia, porque llevo tiempo sin ver a mi raza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go Reds! @lfc ⚽️🔴⚽️🔴 @championsleague #lfc @fcbayern @ Rochester, New York https://t.co/SyVVa0Dxmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriciaHeaton Tell Raymond to get his butt over there and help you! (Back in the ELR character ha ha)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyk1967 @WeidnerRoger @gayle_gigiangel @maxxx__power @Marc751e2f95 @Bamafanaticfan1 @GaryDehart7 @NewEndsBegun… https://t.co/MfXqf3qwXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 13 Kansas tops Baylor 78-70, stays undefeated at home  https://t.co/mWeToY9vJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IreneNStokes Love it Irene. On same path too! Maybe ours will cross someday! 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crucialcalicars was the best part of my day. Everyone go follow him #losangeles #hollywood #beverlyhills… https://t.co/pooZIoK9FC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GackleReport What’s your assessment of what the #SJSharks should do with Erik Karlsson while he’s re-inured his gr… https://t.co/ZsXcqwOs9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @Twitter ...is it the algorithm that pushes more ads to my feed when I block at least 20-30 promoted tweets/day… https://t.co/qB0ju2vtI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading out tomorrow on the #ecstasy out of Charleston. #cheers package standing by😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[these Democrats are campaigning these Democrats are pissing in moaning about the Democrats listen to them they will not take credit]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO sick of these issues with our heat this winter!! New oil tank, new boiler...what the hell can it possibly be now… https://t.co/nofXE2CEru]]></document><document><![CDATA[@i_ivvy @Mullins14Kayla @ThePackFootball @LadyPackHoops But Wolfpack man is right.  If you're concerned about what… https://t.co/jHzuJCUdsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you miss yesterday’s post about the @TheAAF ? @aafhotshots @aafAPOLLOS @aafstallions @AafLegends  https://t.co/PsrrviyFxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_jgarland91 @JPinVA @kear20 @JCapGLJ Aside from Cizikas, Nelson leads all forwards on the team in blocked shot… https://t.co/5VQEubmyae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Islanders PA announcer needs to give Tavares the Chase Utley treatment tonight, during the starting lineups announc… https://t.co/EpiRp8QoJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidjohnson717 @sylasjp11 Lmfaoo he’s done done 🤣🤣🤣 he better hope the get AD this summer or he out next year too 🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UN I N T E R V E N T I O N M I LI T A R Venezuela 🇻🇪 LIBRE  Demasiada Educacion Demasiada Tolerancia  Demasiada Di… https://t.co/7ZmyIZaWjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being on missions knowing this thing is up there somewhere just waiting to protect my ass was always comforting]]></document><document><![CDATA[First matches of BHS men’s volleyball begin today at Chatard! GO DAWGS!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful March for Peace and program celebrating #MLKDay (makeup date) in @CliftonForge1 #Peace #Justice https://t.co/Y2WeaPvlh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jerry_Kramer_ @jnelson714 That’s the extra spray paint I brought home from work isn’t it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carmen38004447 @Ruben37889962 @BJ_Stew @FrankLangben @Franklin_Graham In your world, Satan wants fewer abortions,… https://t.co/o213UcHYGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wife just asked for me to put something more livelier on tv tonight at 1 A.M.   Six flags dance [10 hours]… https://t.co/9xJtXAZnWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Power Rangers Beast Morphers has been trending huge all morning! 👏 👏 I DVR'd the season premiere, can't wait to watch it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jake_Laubach @Fatmansoonerfan They wanted to give 20 billion before so now it's inhumane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CARLOSEES @epigmenioibarra @FelipeCalderon @lopezobrador_ Está bien rependejo ese amigo, lamehuevos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FritoDink @JohnDennisWEEI @AOC Can you show me the legitimate article that shows this to be the case. Because this… https://t.co/JL4r6sEZ0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helenium @mdtaylor @lynnevtaylor @andypiper @bincerli @yosub @lorimerstreet https://t.co/ZcT5srlkHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday cely starts now @ Lake Tahoe / Truckee https://t.co/zwRYPFSJUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[California professor reprimanded for saying police 'need to be killed,' reports say https://t.co/cJGcd0RlS2 #FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockChalkPhog25 Yeah undermanned, they replace injured guys with other McDonalds All Americans. The struggle is real “big boy”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveTorrence WAY TO GO BILLY!Heck yeaahh.Time to get those Capco pipeliners their first wally if the year. #Capco #ArizonaNats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmclymer who is being stupid in shaming her? damn people are just dumb. https://t.co/9sG3CrWFC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrBill_Slugo @NateHoot @EdKrassen He ordered one from Thornton Melon’s Tall and Fat catalogue.]]></document></documents></author>