<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I love that I can’t have my windows open in my apartment because the nasty ass people below us just sit outside and smoke all day 🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so sleep deprived that I literally swiped my drivers license in the vending machine instead of my credit card..… https://t.co/XmYWEAWqt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The practice of medicine has evolved because of the nimble people who choose to take up the job of doctoring- we ha… https://t.co/3L53evErB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My marriage has become one long game of “Who Has to Wait for Whom to Watch Which Movie” and I’m getting pretty tired of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC. You should WATCH! Why aren't you proud of German cars (BMW) making cars in SC??? WHY isn't U.S. f… https://t.co/3Qte6PXV9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully Timmy The Little Goat listened to me this morning when I told him to take cover INSIDE the shed. Cuz, if… https://t.co/e5gnkdPcVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDeanPhillips @TRantosaurus Because they’d lose ! Such a mealy mouthed chicken shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[ולכן היא נראית כמו שהיא נראית ! נזכרים בה פעם בארבע שנים וחוזרים לבועה !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ffolliet @ePOCUS @POCUS_Toronto @RogueClaire @DennisCho @eUSMD @82CharK @PhilipStasiak @romanoermd @laurenmcchaim @pemtweety 🤫]]></document><document><![CDATA[ACOG doesn’t specify how to screen. My preference is to screen for pregestational diabetes, with a Hgb A1C, and not… https://t.co/UKWxIIZdiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like running into one of your hinge dates at the doctors office!!!!! https://t.co/qIfP15TXDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m convinced the love of my life lives in NY so due to personal reasons i can’t go back to california.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell There are few things as relaxing and joyful as coming home every day to my sweetest puppy dog! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:45AM: Gov’t Center, Boston 7.0” measured across the street from previous measurement.  Wind starting to pick up a… https://t.co/xQDfFOi7iM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So fun to see @RMHSMUSTANGS Badminton practice in action! https://t.co/av7dzYlYeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngrierWHStaff I'm so sorry. The great joy they give us is the flip side of this terrible pain. So sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This case so confuses me. Just like every woman or man that claims they have been abused should be treated as they… https://t.co/TR1W9wbkzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you find someone who can make you actually laugh out loud, hold on to them for dear life. That shits so rare.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone else Bunny obsessed?  🐰 . . I can’t resist a cute bunny 🐰 this time of the year. They are literally poppi… https://t.co/tqkgfhuVc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to the amount of people in the supermarket, the end of the world must be coming #snowstorm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Securing our southern border which has been a problem for 40 years and congress refusing to do it's job!when are yo… https://t.co/TDKcwmixjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from @etobicokeroos  -  Are you, or someone you know, passionate about coaching? Well, you’re in luck!  Th… https://t.co/aJopZdrfFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teachers, this is what I do at The Florida Bar and it is essential in classrooms!!! https://t.co/zQpNX2pYN3… https://t.co/uVwocT448s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek How would @IvankaTrump know about "wanting to work for what they get"??? She never wanted or worked for anything!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is clever. #comedy #tee-hee #grin #merry https://t.co/uxEYGy90VO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 Whichever one u pick, can u please save it so I can watch later?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amvetsupport I doubt el Chao transported anything across the border. He brought drugs into this country w/boats, l… https://t.co/Cic0BhcxxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh we’re gonna have a problem in 12 years alright. It’s when these kids are allowed to vote. Lord help us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My date tonight told me he’d like it if I hit him up more often and that he’d like to be pampered too.   I didn’t k… https://t.co/AM2R8gNPzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@herreradja Pues sí, vi que les preguntaron conceptos técnicos y no contestaron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#spiderman #wedding @tomholland40 this is so sweet @ Central Center in Centennial Park https://t.co/iI8aNhwbPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[´*•.¸(*•.¸♥¸.•*´)¸.•*´ ♥«´¨`•°..i love my friends..°•´¨`»♥            .¸.•*(¸.•*´♥`*•.¸)`*•.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irshroz @pookienorris Botox Betty is a spiteful nasty woman. She should have never been put in that position. She… https://t.co/NUV79xIT9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m dropping a diy nail thread soon. I’m boycotting Ling-Ling!!!!!💅🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexi5983 There are how many people in Washington for 8 years that could have banned something together to fix it?… https://t.co/jhMXs3yvGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Who’s Who of racists caught on camera with the newest addition. #BlackLivesMatter #WhitePrivilege]]></document><document><![CDATA[i want to save everyone but i feel like in order to do that i’m going to bring myself down and not reach my own pot… https://t.co/JvgPw1PMcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh so now she's seen the light?! Nope she just started seeing everyone roasting her ass for blaming her family brea… https://t.co/DOD1eF6XSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, You Just Had a C-Section--Do You Need Opioids? https://t.co/eDSQ20WdAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyNarcisse @TeamHISD @FondrenMS_HISD You deserve it! Proud of you 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else was thrown off by day light savings? My partner and I ate around 8, which felt normal (I like to eat by 6:… https://t.co/B44aojMNrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolederong @mattnathanson @aarontap @hmbscully I was hoping, and it was incredible.   I'm still a little in disb… https://t.co/RXlU43lARB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll have you know I almost died via pickle at the ripe age of 6 so anyone who agrees with this can take that pickl… https://t.co/Qe1AMB1cVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd be okay with Fox News having @rea1jeffreyross host DNC primary candidates in a roast of Tomi Lahren, which woul… https://t.co/Krc8ctADHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMaryHoward @lindavhoyt @michaelsalinger @joanneduncanjo Can’t wait! We will be talking about strategies to jumps… https://t.co/XejRkqgm1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarrettAll @ATLairport Apparently Buffalo doesn’t want you either. This blizzard is even more blizzardy than last week’s blizzard.🌬💨❄️🙄😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signs that you’re in the midst of a transformation:  ✨Your days are fun and you don’t default to thinking it’s some… https://t.co/m70kks375k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga and #BradleyCooper just killed it on the #oscars stage. They performed #Shallow and it was perfect. I'm g… https://t.co/frBaqPppYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brantley can suck my left nut and bye Cody Allen but the other two got me sad. Chis don’t look right in that uni.]]></document><document><![CDATA[treating myself this vday 🤤🙅🏼‍♀️ @Excision can’t wait to see you in march 😍 https://t.co/x4i9eJBxo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmac57 Thanks, David. Change is usually something I look forward to, &amp; we are adaptable. Journey. 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mandala from Traveling Mandalas done with Colorit gel pens. #mycolorit @ Holt, Michigan https://t.co/qWLIny6MIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your rights are at risk. The real opioid Epidemic EXPOSED. https://t.co/mNNDX5HxE9 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the longest I’ve gone without caffeine &amp; alcohol, someone wants me to die fr fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHAWN Y LA GUITARRAAAAAAA KDJEIVHJTKRNBJVRGNB O YESSSSS  #ShawnMendesTheTourAmsterdam]]></document><document><![CDATA[When #MnCities officials stop by just in time to watch #mnleg floor session as the Senate debates elections securit… https://t.co/EIXnZbulzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrShikharMisra Thanks Shikhar; I didn't hear any rain overnight not sure we got any, but forecast still showing hi… https://t.co/3uk6RlWfc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make no mistake, he is not there to serve his country's intetests. He is there to serve his own interests.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You who say that one must not commit adultery, do you commit adultery? You who abhor idols, do you rob temples? https://t.co/9uSwdzWwA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody wanted to have company this weekend. And I wash my hair in the shower accompanied by a podcast. They bout… https://t.co/swlRAMAe15]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have arrived at the @MITSloan Hack for Inclusion Conference! Trying to look as fabulous as @tmo_knows (those 👠 a… https://t.co/Qwe02yXWmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[$151 Graduation shoot special for my Morgan students...  2 hour max on campus session, 2 outfits, unlimited photos,… https://t.co/vODgxCNlzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Devastating news. I deeply admired Jeff - and the public defender office he built.  He will be sorely missed .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WahooStrength @MarcKaminski2 @RMHATC She is amazing!!! So grateful for her dedication to our athletes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m not in a good place mentally rn, so please excuse me while i work on myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[READ ACROSS AMERICA: I had *so* much fun reading Dr.Suess to these little cuties at Plains Head Start. We let them… https://t.co/Pd8x09NSnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dogs annoy the shit out of me when my parents are gone. They act like they’re never coming back with how batshit… https://t.co/wA0tisq7fM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pick up my cap and gown for my undergrad on Wednesday. I can’t believe it’s almost over 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for over 4000 followers on Instagram!  During the next couple of days I will share about my passions and del… https://t.co/l4mbp6ghOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam’s ridiculous, stupid plan is so 🙄 worthy! Lord free Jason from it please! Let her ass get caught in her own stu… https://t.co/IY8z305bmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I was somebody's peanut butter @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/dAG0yeQIvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, we were able to hear from some of the @GovParsonMO amazing cabinet including @ChloraLM. True public servin… https://t.co/e0zAviBDqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you tomorrow? Ready to get your “Red Carpet” on? (No, Ygritte! Not that red carpet! Put your leathers back on,… https://t.co/ZOTSO4BmHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheetos are the new black!@flahertyrob discusses how news travels fast by showing us the ~cheesy~ @Cheetos campaign… https://t.co/Kh2sqCaFnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Human promises are often worthless, and many broken promises have left broken hearts.” L.B. Cowman #trustinGod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericakuhl @amcgriff87 My mom used to make us do a software typing program in the summer. Also the neighbor kids sh… https://t.co/9jItdo10h0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenMintonWSB  we’re going to miss you. Congratulations on your retirement]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had such a splendid Lupercalia with @radioSUZY1 and @GoddessPhoenix1! Great to share the teaser for Spider with… https://t.co/hk0AM9jK9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylangston @langernutrition @Shape_Magazine Ah I see. Yes, it’s easy to feel that way]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe I should’ve been more careful when I dyed my hair blue... #MyPinkNailsTurnedBluePurple https://t.co/LztIlD4Lkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I saw when Colton pointed out the bath #TheBachelor https://t.co/HbDLA7q2Bz]]></document><document><![CDATA[me looking to my horoscope for answers as soon as my day starts going bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[So so so excited for my friends @Robbi_Lynn and Kyle 👏🏼😍🤗 Can’t wait to celebrate with y’all 🥂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senate should’ve passed the bill before Christmas with  5.7  it. Mitch should’ve went nuclear!🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimenaINovaro I like your decision! Here’s my Monday: 👩🏻‍💻👩🏻‍💻👩🏻‍💻👩🏻‍💻👩🏻‍💻👩🏻‍💻👩🏻‍💻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you have never missed a race for Coach Chuck and gone from the B relay to the E relay and it shows!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cantguardmike yessss!  Very proud of how our team and City handled the whole mess of a season ending.  Next season they WILL get it right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight @SashaBanksWWE!! Hope you see this! #fanart #FanArtFriday https://t.co/G8E7jLctF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pep rally at school tomorrow which means I’ll be close to people https://t.co/tbHhMnAvjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elisabeth Yes, ma'am. I want to get that t-shirt that says, "Sorry, I'm late. I didn't want to come." haha #introvertlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holi_matos @huchilora @JBolivarDiaz @MartinezPozo Holi todo esto es mas sucio de lo que yo creìa.Desde hoy dejè de… https://t.co/9jHGG4w7Z6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you seen our spring line yet?! 👀⠀ ⠀ How about these beautiful Blush Lydias?! 🔥⠀ ⠀ In just the perfect shade of… https://t.co/5JcvCAuFpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Whatevah_Amy I buy the silken tofu to put in it then it also goes to waste. 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dahomes I had about 10 flats in high school...I’m grateful to have had any car in HS and a junker since it taught me how to change flats ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last snow of the season, I'm guessing... #kswx #ictwx https://t.co/zZwVOBsAjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@purbrooktony @rickygervais OMG!! I just hate some people. That poor baby. I hope this baby gets better soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting in that pre-season work. Awesome to see/hear how many have been working hard. Can’t wait to watch these guy… https://t.co/YAFiML9ri6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara He acts like a thug but at this point, what does he have to win or lose? They won't lower his sentenc… https://t.co/s368QTkvxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need some giggles? @StFrancisCCSD is defending their title for thinking fast on their feet in the improv Loose Moos… https://t.co/1QJTMFDYCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[i didn’t take the SAT today and i wish i did cause i want to understand the SAT memes]]></document></documents></author>