<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Gold Show Choir for helping spread the #love with the #NorrisTitans this #ValentinesDay! 🔴👏⚪💘🔵 https://t.co/NgDBbCnAMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamfelber @TheCoupDQ @StarTrekTNC @MattMira @PoundstoneInst @paulapoundstone Hey Adam!  Get ready for a lot of no… https://t.co/yNolzmrm8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what the hell was that in tx on ur show tackled that man was completely out of line]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richeisen is on fire with the quips this morning at the #NFLCombine @MoveTheSticks]]></document><document><![CDATA[WATSKY!  #watsky #concert #roadtrip #tampabay #florida #theorpheum #liveband #liveshow #rapshow #headliner… https://t.co/MMDHXZt4q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axios We now know how this kid became such a douche bag.   🤦‍♂️ He had great examples to learn from.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey North Dakota!! @DrJoeDeutsch and I are headed to Washington DC on Mar. 6th for #SPEAKOutDay to lobby for… https://t.co/2xbHufnYSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- I want to know everything C- the world is change.  To understand what makes it change and what it was leads us t… https://t.co/CZriv65g5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TxBornSooner I’d have less of a problem with someone saying “racism doesn’t exist because I said so” than “I haven’t experienced it”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talked with @StJohnsBBall junior star Mustapha Heron (@Kingheron5) after his season high 28-point performance lifte… https://t.co/CQWNR4ir6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenCarman @DaveThreed Gardner Minshew Late round or UFA Baker clone 👍🤞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is t link/page to change the registration ADDRESS of a car? I don’t see how to do it from the attached pages.… https://t.co/lZjLh0rpUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @WAalumni and former @WAWarEagles standout Mekenli Forrest on a tremendous @NCAATrackField Indoor Tourn… https://t.co/739z1N9Zpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you've forgotten women kick butt, Captain Marvel is here to provide a super reminder. https://t.co/mArnYtpzNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trintran A heart shaped hole in the ground... 🥺 https://t.co/COMthL82nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rico_Abreu @WorldofOutlaws @LVMotorSpeedway @NASCAR @SPFRacing @AraiAmericas @Lucas_Oil @alpinestars… https://t.co/fg9Z53aaCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimothyJMcL’s version of making cookies.  one handful of dough later: “maybe we could use a...spoon?” 😂 https://t.co/5qAIZ5uTV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southerndwaal @AOC Won’t gut my deductions. I live in Texas. I can still deduct my property taxes and have a highe… https://t.co/nfcupJL6Mc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#breakfast #breakfastofchampions at a #steamboatsprings #steamboat #colorado #restaurant #staple #bacon #crab… https://t.co/jFVfKSbfzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dnlnwmn @jasondingr @Kithygh @WoodWhisperer That being said I have seen framing carpenters do amazing work on spec… https://t.co/yE1RveH6zY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Bullshit Democrat control freak. Obviously a Maxine Waters flavor hater. What was there to overreact to?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alanalda One of the best MASH’s was with you and your Dad. I think he passed soon after. What a great moment. Did… https://t.co/S7oSkW1wmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalleeGolfman @lyallr Took me a couple of goes as well to catch on it was a wee gaffe and no a little boy!! Lol mu… https://t.co/s7RAlINTZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have liked the outward facing @amyklobuchar since I have seen her. But I have seen, have worked for two-faced peo… https://t.co/PshJoXvbIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook is going to zero like Myspace and there is no real value in facebook.  Facebook has become a quick chore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drivadeneiramd @me4_so @NorthwellHealth @juliomayol @SWexner @JohnRTMonsonMD @ZuckerSoM Agree @drivadeneiramd… https://t.co/1Pabl2Ei5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMcGrathKY Amy you should run against Mitch McConnell in 2020 and unseat him.  You have the support of every mem… https://t.co/jDkqedcmgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Merci @jfrobergeQc pour entretien riche sur tous sujets #éducation #universitaire au 💙 #CoopFrQc : maternelles,… https://t.co/x5G3BAzQDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is #SAMOA 🇼🇸🇦🇸 #Usa7s #GoDaManu #ManuSamoa #Rugby #LasVegas @ Fremont Street Experience https://t.co/n0R1O00PtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn’t hear already... Matt Duchene has likely played his last game with the Senators, they are holding him… https://t.co/lB1zvgxzr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many hoes claim to be wifey material but can't make a peanut butter and jelly samich]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not getting rid of Shrimp because it can go with so many things. I’ll never get rid of shrimp fried rice or fried shrimp. NEVER 🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey fans of @FWKomets, I recommend you pick up a @journalgsports on Thursday. I have a story on answering something… https://t.co/YRfmoc91lw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cocando @AlbertoRavell @jorgeramosnews @realDonaldTrump La ayuda de USA es politica de Estado. El gobierna de Trum… https://t.co/GOZmc5TieO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool things from work today: I had a blast in the caf learning to use the new sound system at lunch w the kids and… https://t.co/XIUPiUIB20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerperry I saw @MadeaFamFuneral last night. I love her. Please dont take her from us 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trash Talking Level : Expert @rmcpaladins queensgaels #trashtalk #volleyball #rivals @ Kingston Military Community… https://t.co/5z63dWI2mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend has extra passes to tent &amp; I’m balking at going so last minute lol @RODEOHOUSTON]]></document><document><![CDATA[The classic “tank and then move to a new city with all the draft picks you acquired” strategy. Works every time]]></document><document><![CDATA[INTO THE SPIDER-VERSE.  INTO THE SPIDER-VERSE.  INTO.   THE.  SPIDER-VERSE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelClayto15 @RichardZokol @55GACrowder Arnold marked if there was a 1% chance you’d hit his ball. He would say… https://t.co/kyyYcoTmEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plum Cool , Byron Ga will carry with honor , the numbers CN 007472 too ANGEL OF THE MORNING - Juice Newton (Lyrics)… https://t.co/j85kH3biJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @WhiteHouse @UPSIntegradAtl @UPS @GovKemp @UPSers @UPSPolicy @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and sup… https://t.co/1LoW9dNFFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part 2 of my CosPain Art Livestream starts tonight at 7 PM EDT! Be sure to tune in as I finish up the strip and tal… https://t.co/z10HIHhzes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of all the snow days we've had, today is clearly the #1 candidate. Main and back roads haven't been touched, ba… https://t.co/mRbR5shx0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zechariah 7 -for our nation, our city, and ourselves, Pray the Scriptures https://t.co/wDKyEgHaGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TamEdwards6abc Completely agree my friend! Thank you! Which reminds me the one next week will feature A'Lelia Walk… https://t.co/ZhDscO5LbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialJackM Whatever . . . as long as I get to look at your face . . . 💝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very proud of these Warriors! Tradition - Honor - Excellence - THE Fresno High]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GertieTheDino @OrangeGrove55 Dumbo was the first movie my mom ever took me to see.  Still makes an old man 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaitlancollins When do the #impeachment hearings start? 🤔asking for a friend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to bet  on no jail time ? This is Chicago Illinois . Sanctuary city and state . Most corrupt legal system… https://t.co/CJL5oBAf2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[rip to one of the greats and someone who inspired me to push my mindset forward, we will miss you Karl]]></document><document><![CDATA[This speaks to my heart 🙏🏼💙✊🚪 @ Hudson, Massachusetts https://t.co/650Zsj8sKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEVER GIVE UP! My dream is to lead an amazing team of drivers and attendants, whom are dedicated and passionate abo… https://t.co/bYTiBoLUx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tracks that @hissgldnmssr shared from his forthcoming release tonight @StandardDeluxe are some of the most beau… https://t.co/2tu3FNMFML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hospitalvespers I wouldn’t trust her. She will bite you and fart in your nightmares]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Insomniac228 Thanks! We’re very excited for it. Hoping to close mid-March 🤞🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack Goodbye Rand Paul to the support of millions of Americans who want to deal vigorously with the problem of illegal immigration.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmadoDiazSDE @LauraLebron12 @JLMendoza_ @orlandogildice @nieves_rd @hectorherrerac Tampoco existirían los teléfono… https://t.co/mvNgJOyEj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is more to the world than firearms... Still, Republicans seem to believe otherwise and still nothing by McCon… https://t.co/sd06iDfPds]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when I see my Ma and Nana, so many things I still have to learn and here they are to help me along the way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FarmingtonPower Benching itself won’t blow your shoulder out in the gym in most cases. Most baseball shoulder inju… https://t.co/1ef1Ob6mJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@copperbird7 @QuancyClayborne Bunch of grown men in tights ramming into each other.  Sigh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delegate Linville is back up to speak in support of the amendment he sponsored. "By eliminating this section of cod… https://t.co/2QxpMgidp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because... Barbells and Beer go together. I’m just bringing the Ice though. Keeping the #ArnoldClassic2019 Hydrated… https://t.co/MxJAlzisnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MUweather At least that should help their drought this summer. Unless they get rapid snow melt, then it will be a catastrophe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@16_Titles @DionApollo They are the DLo apologists who are still hurting from him getting dealt. If Clippers go on… https://t.co/rku8vUO9Br]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcusdavis904 @NickC_Castillo_ @AdamBoselli Texas football&gt;Florida football @trvisXX &gt; @KodakBlack1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny.  That is the same thing I think whenever I see one of your tweets or awful blog posts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want Bernie to win the Democratic nomination with his college-town silliness, but am wildly curious to see… https://t.co/CSHD0g6rjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGenoaofBoz @CBSLA It ended at 10pm. Right across from my home. He ended up surrendering. After about 5 hours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evel Knievel pinball machine at TNT Amusements! Call if interested  215-953-1188 or Email at tntquality@aol.com @ T… https://t.co/LRz6xgQU1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawnNeufeld I’m not saying to leave knives and lead paint everywhere, but the industry preys on scared first-time… https://t.co/HT8w0Jp4zN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyLuscombe Gridiron Dinner attendees’ response to Ivanka’s “jokes”: https://t.co/NLc2xyfh2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@faith_crist Yo dead ass I’m in the middle of doing legs and I literally lost my balance watching this lmao. Thanks !!!! 😂🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RuFan130 @BirdsNetsDevils @Jay2thePNY She did. And she filed before me so I basically got screwed. Apparently I wa… https://t.co/ITUBUmuy2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arca_10 @negrosantos13 @chapa281225 @MiguelHerreraDT @ClubAmerica @intelecto7 @andremarinpuig @Faitelson_ESPN… https://t.co/zBvP5bRRPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was watching the podcast and @GavinFree talking about time. @sorola @burnie  https://t.co/KQ4sweu1mJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ethan_iverson I guess in 1st bar of D you can arpeggiate the G and D on 1st beat, hold the D with RH, grab the A o… https://t.co/cIY6KcxKXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PantheonMMO Go get it.  Or get my Necromancer friend to summon it for me...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stlCupofJoe Jaden looks like a trooper.  I am praying for him, that he is strong through the surgery.  I am prayin… https://t.co/iH6hY69y7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[“God, I invite your searching gaze into my heart. Examine me through and through; find out everything that may be h… https://t.co/bgYMIp0Hyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeerEDUPod @jmartinez727 @creativeedtech @AndersonEdTech @BDicksonNV @misterwashburn @Mr_JVD @SJteaches… https://t.co/NqyFQ3ReUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the first round of consolation, Liberty Union still has 7 wrestlers alive!  Keep it up boys! #LUHSPride]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me in spite of everything that’s happened out here supporting Carmella https://t.co/lxJWt97oDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepTimRyan Why is it the GOP always says oh tax cuts will “trickle down” but then when you question why companies… https://t.co/Fnr7Had0h6]]></document><document><![CDATA[From my personal experience being around some white males whose dicks were average size. They did not have the stre… https://t.co/58gwQd2zDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It has been a nice 3 weeks off, but I'm glad to be back in the swing of things tonight. It feels good to be back in… https://t.co/rpCu7n8Sm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow @khloekardashian said some real words on her account. I mean at least she is smart enough to know to be mad at… https://t.co/gz1mzVuHa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[DEM @Thomas1Todd recognizing our amazing met safety captain Eva for driving the team with ZERO incidents all of 201… https://t.co/2ybrwMD3nY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gary Gensler (former CFTC Chairman) and Hester Pierce (current SEC Commissioner aka "Crypto Mom") talks about ways… https://t.co/ce9BuEq3Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris It’s a sad day when A father and mother each works a 40 hrs. A week job and can’t make ends meet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday February 20 - POLITICO Playbook PM:    Sustained and ongoing' disinformation assault targets Dem presiden… https://t.co/YqnKpOKaHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kbiz I’m torn between thanking you and feeling like we’ve really been missing out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TigerLetsRoll @Jamierodr14 @AOC @BreitbartNews @terryatthebeach https://t.co/IYcD3ElAmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kiwanis Club of Edinburg took first place “Fiesta Edinburg”. https://t.co/KRAddF7bKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brileeper23 Where the hell was this contest and why didn't I hear about it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or messing around in the woods behind campus now can bring their gun everywhere they go on campus.   Let me ask thi… https://t.co/V97anSLX1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianDMains @Mattel I saw a picture of the action figure a few days ago, and it's been stuck in my mind. I had to draw him.]]></document></documents></author>