<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Dan Hartman - I can dream about you (Ruas de Fogo) Tradução em PT-BR https://t.co/PB6xVt4Nzv via @YouTube happy valentines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if baggy pants or cargo shorts will ever come back in style. I’m getting tired of digging my wallet out of… https://t.co/3M3ke1DXd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Macys why do u guys pay your employees 💩💩 and avoid working with #unions?? Especially in #nyc? #MacysSucks #macys]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one time I actually get ready for school on time and my dog decides to run away https://t.co/WriI6YIVvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[So how much of this investigation was funded by Roger Goodell and the NFL?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A quién le gustaría ver a easymoneysniper / Durant en los celtics ??☘️☘️ . . Credits: celtics .....................… https://t.co/xIJ0Mgk4Wm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bae and I tearing it up at the putt putt course, yall ain't ready.... https://t.co/a934GG6Ves]]></document><document><![CDATA[As well, with that I have to commend @MarzGurl for sticking through this after being subjugated to a mere fraction… https://t.co/msZiYPEKlS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLAhuberdeaus @THR Maybe if the actress were hotter it wouldn’t be getting cancelled]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runningwolf1978 He did say something to me,  however I'll leave that out 🙂 That's when I was like wtf.  I almost f… https://t.co/fWRZMow3gv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LorenaSGonzalez @garydaranger @LorenaAD80 @CaliforniaDFW Thank you, I look forward to sharing with our readers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EversTurk Hopefully u have better luck then I do. A blowout to the islanders before Halloween. And that garbage of… https://t.co/HsAV2nuGJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chuckles152 If it’s legal then fucking it’s rich privilege. Guy made millionsNd a crazy ass daughter. Who cares what he spends it on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlessandroLai @AmbassadorAwsum @adamwathan Laravel has the best testing practices, tools, docs, and courses of any framework in PHP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[EVIL PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD😡😡😡 #UTAH man who #Killednewborn avoids #deathpenalty  with plea deal https://t.co/pvf7cJ7Moh via @MailOnline]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katebarbax @Cataldo98 Because people assume the worse, you have to think before you speak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newest listing 89 Dunfield.  2 bedroom plus den. With parking and locker. Amazing SW views wrap around balconies @… https://t.co/m74dyiBBpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LastStand2019 YET HIM AND ALL HIS SOCIALIST DEMOCRATIC CO-CONSPIRATORS, VOTED IN FAVOR OF A BILL TO MURDER BABIES!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Nina Lunde for having her artwork chosen to hang in the gallery at COSI in Columbus. https://t.co/ImaBcEIVq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MckinnonJaron @HardyMusic This is awesome can’t wait to meet u guys some day!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Faustman3 @RealJamesWoods 1) What color is Crispus Attucks? 2) Was he murdered? 3) Was it lied about? 4) Did Bosto… https://t.co/gghebLAvu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shouldn’t have laughed but.. anywho, my son and I are vaccinated and you can do whatever you please with your own… https://t.co/Qamqk7d6XG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KnightNation, @CFEArena arena better be WALL TO WALL PACKED for this team on Thursday #Knight!!!  How could you no… https://t.co/2cVYIzKFZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @dbongino Who’s going to investigate #SCHIFFTY? Maybe he should be presented with “liar of the year trophy!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Product Manager - https://t.co/3DPEA6a3Bd #ProductMgmt #Boise, ID]]></document><document><![CDATA[No lie, Partynextdoor music ages the best with time...  “Belong to the City” got me vibing on another level]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the situation heats up in #Venezuela over U.S. supplies crossing over the #Colombia border, I’m going to re-up m… https://t.co/1uhBHNKV0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas bound!! patgiacone #internationalpizzaexpo #vegas #randomvegasflight @ Cincinnati/Northern Kentucky Internati… https://t.co/rlaqLW75Xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@braddewhat The garbage was all over WhatsApp last year and now because some UK police department catches on months… https://t.co/Si22txIfWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo IN MY EMOTIONS that this is Countess’ (The Legend, The Great) last round at the Treasurer position! 😢 Wow wh… https://t.co/lo0vwpSAS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This could totally be... There is only one family who really knows and sadly that's the 1st family of the U.S.A.… https://t.co/4NXCUpsQZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbyRosinski Should have cut him the minute the season ended.  5 million for your fourth or fifth receiver?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_AKA_Becker @washingtonpost AREWE QUICKTO JUDGE Everyone cansee this is so stupid. Someplaying evil toget thei… https://t.co/77ftXw7Vtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BunkerGear_Gal That was an incredible morning. Yes indeed the Land of your home and your People  is beautiful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You know why crackers don’t sink? Because they float!” -Olive #olivequotes #toddlerlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Opening Day in Orem! @UVUBaseball and @SMC_Baseball are set to play game one of a double header. Catch both ga… https://t.co/oIQfqAojzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sherabphagmo @BABIDOLL301 @evesdadisbest @sweet___ash @Wardworkz @ValentinoAndy77 @PaulaAbdul @ghostlybeard… https://t.co/cargpKMAjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportslead1055 even if you look at Kraft from a football perspective and not life. The patriots have been the MOST… https://t.co/YxMak5R4LK]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get your guests laughing 🤣🤣🤣 #camaraderie #BekkerReady4Launch #younggaffers #CanPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jake E Lee.  Red Dragon Cartel.  #jakeelee #reddragoncartel #vintagemusicimages #photographybydavidplastik… https://t.co/B1HIQXX6hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe in the happenings with Plum Cool , I feel certain , I am with 2 registered Tin Soilders of the bay of Pig… https://t.co/ojNAvO7OcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poses. Honestly in this picture I was feeling myself and the feeling of a new hair cut is just awesome. I was actua… https://t.co/BFW6Z86Ntu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasJockin @LaRossa My point in all of this is that I believe that most clients, especially corporate ones, woul… https://t.co/I3GO3XwoU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soldado Venezolano ponte del lado de la democracia,  Tu y tu familia estan pasando el mismo trabajo para conseguir alimentos, medicinas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sitting in a movie theater with lounge seats (legs up, of course), a bag of kettle popcorn and a pint of Blue M… https://t.co/cKBwGoGCa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Line for coffee 100x shorter than Starbucks. Cheaper and pretty decent. (@ Camden Food Company in Boston, MA) https://t.co/nUSKZtEYB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Silver_Buck @tjfxh @TxEx @DeficitOwls @StephanieKelton @CNBC Natural Gas too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrRoderickPerry @WSURaiders @WSUBaseball @CoachLovelady23 @JustinDParker24 @JeffMercer54 It was windy and cold.  M… https://t.co/pmZoFmgust]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t usually take selfies but I felt cute so here I am ._. https://t.co/2mYdJfPkIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkraju F___king amazing. He needs to remove his head from tRUmp’s ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Bringing in #SDNY to investigate trump organization is a little like bringing in Sherlock Holmes to investigate Wh… https://t.co/oSIQQspHs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a fan of democracy right now. I think all seem to be focusing on self interests over collective.  If I had to p… https://t.co/hnWBmByKrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got yelled at last time for hiding the nipple this time I’m not!! Phase 2 complete https://t.co/YfbTIGVX5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rossladycom whatever we are going through our light will always shine if we truly belong to God… https://t.co/i9diQIwn16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crgl_3 @Paquemasyo Ya le explicamos al pana que muchos en venezuela no puede. Hablar porque los puede. Matar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh I am surprised the Amazon New York pullout is not getting more coverage on my feed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sammusmusic This song always helps me. I also Stan for Theremin solos, but I digress... https://t.co/ZI4MEukG7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeilMilliken @ericwbailey @callmevlad even w/in my own dev/design/product teams, I use both interchangeably (acces… https://t.co/ytgTCYLSnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tfp_podcast I agree on Star Wars being the best race weekend, but it's tough considering Princess weekend is prett… https://t.co/hTH9J31hMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoriSchmidt @SarahStoko Lori what have you done to help ease that feeling of loss over the years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @lexilayo @OfficialMiax @brittanyxshae @slutsaucekhloe @caseycalvertxxx @ChanelPreston @AndiRye… https://t.co/8IQjbLSU5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the update @mint but I can save ya some time. I did not stick to my budget https://t.co/27np4CjWa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random lock #photography #HamOnt #art #blackandwhite #urban #dslr https://t.co/qJuR4P8dW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamanthaPreis Have you visited Mevagissey and Porthluney Beach yet?  Lovely places!  Here's a link to my photos fr… https://t.co/RaDZMke8Qi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting day for Emma being inducted to @nhs_njhs and proud day for @tina_groff and I. #NJHS #MertonProud @mertonint https://t.co/MPvTBzomev]]></document><document><![CDATA[fui expulso de sala 3 vezes no mesmo tempo de aula por xingar a professora de francês . . . em francês]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m scared I’m at an age now (22) that I’m expected to give a ball I catch to a little kid... I’m gonna wanna keep… https://t.co/cTkK01v27u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen. Murray (D-WA) Takes Floor To Protect Infanticide https://t.co/XDJBE8XZJn via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a moot point now (1-1) but San Jose is 26-4-5 when they score 1st this season while Boston is 12-12-4 when the… https://t.co/izqdp4UaJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gran lugar para visitar en Oklahoma y llevar a sus niños... en Toy and Action Figure Museum https://t.co/LY8p9WjNLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thistallawkgirl Hanging onto our freedoms with all those trying to rip it from him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElenaWeinberg I'm going to be in Austin Texas on March 26th-30th. Where can I see it at,Elena  ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are Bennet and Hick really running for vice president? https://t.co/ReBc6fW7iJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenkePalm84 @lisa_luxe @SenTedCruz @realDonaldTrump @HoustonChron No record highs set in the last 23 years (1995).… https://t.co/T2x3ud7o4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Average recess time in NY...15 minutes. Some districts have ZERO recess! It’s child abuse. My district has 40 minut… https://t.co/PAvx0SaFWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever happen to doing things off the love as opposed to when it’s convenient for you? Cause that’s shits wack]]></document><document><![CDATA[West another miss outside. Gadson rebounds this one. West Rowan up 6 with 450 2nd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CreaseAndAssist Personally I think the Donato deal was fine, I’m super surprised we got as muh value for Coyle as… https://t.co/V56MA65H0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuaneGundrum @miro41411 @TheGameWiz77 @IGN @Marvel What she said was appropriate. Nothing stupid about it. It's am… https://t.co/piDXoSuLpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CornhuskingB @PredomOrange Not over Adrian Martinez though. Am I right? 👊🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert is 1-for-3 with a diving catch in center in his return today. Jimenez was 1-for-3 before exiting the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gateshoops2000 @NHSRattlers @NavasotaISD Pleasure and honor is mine Tommy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidenHatfield Hey  your doing a great job out here the least i can do is tweet it out since i'm in no way able to… https://t.co/P0adUQAnX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tired of pizza, rice n beans and burgers. Made an omelet with potatoes, tomatoes, onions n peppers.… https://t.co/4PD7OYsWJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fam I already put in 23 hours in the past 2 days.. but this new salary looking good 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should’ve had a poetry book published my sophomore year. I fell off, I’ll come back to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@money_bags222 @KeatonAlderman @KobeInDClutch23 Oh so 48 of them are on Twitter? Because the only ones saying he di… https://t.co/HV9q8k2f7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosieperezbklyn @MikeTyson He couldn't even knockout dude in his last fight. FOH!!! https://t.co/KhXFgrg4v9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsRwessels What is roi? And I want to buy a new sti. Something stock so I don’t have to worry about it blowing up… https://t.co/jmaIFD8JSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[During the week my Twitter is all violence prevention, public health and social justice. But on weekends, it’s all… https://t.co/ImiwFE6Jzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I wish I was doing this morning... 😴#DaylightSavingsTime https://t.co/vnFKOwYuSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenKalifornia Very sorry Karen. I've cried over the loss of a dog more than some people. I get it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff You sir are pushing lies on the American people.  Democrats had 2+ years to prove what you claim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOYS BASKETBALL: End of the first quarter - Rock Bridge 22, Kickapoo 8. Bruins starting to play their pace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gross.  Mac gives Donna Marie back some of the money she just whored herself says she should treat herself to something pretty.  #Hollyoaks]]></document><document><![CDATA[This what it feels like !! 2nd attempt ! Still in Charlotte NC 3 1/2 hour asleep!!  Well is not the #beauty… https://t.co/sNvqkiwwMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@backintimepod @paranormalpat64 and myself did two podcasts on wrestling so make sure you go to @backintimepod give… https://t.co/6ewWZdiVy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[So does anyone want to help break my new bed in?? 😈 and by break in, I do mean sleeping unconsciously for a period of 10-12 hours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This piece by @proseb4bros is fantastic: https://t.co/ijDouXKJdc (h/t @dkopf)]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’ve hiked Mt. Washington...in my car.” — @jayobtv https://t.co/AFtGBnFWvb]]></document></documents></author>