<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[También soñé que @ma_silvestre llegaba a una reunión con amigos chilangos e intentaba acariciarme la mano una y otra vez debajo de la mesa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does Connie keep finding markers for her notepad? Or new notepads? #TheWalkingDead]]></document><document><![CDATA[some girl got really close to me and put all her hair on me... and when i scooted up, she did it again... i felt the lice...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seemed like a good day for a hike. #GreatDismalSwamp #outearlybeforetherainstarts https://t.co/luxnYwM6w5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCPolitics I believe she’s confusing Science fiction with actual Science 🤦‍♀️!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yes, and so is a Present who can't fucking find the fucking truth if it slapped you upside your tiny dick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I late to the party or has there been a Pretty Woman/#StarIsBorn  breakfast scene comparison? https://t.co/IlzWSxITfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump So now Donnie Dementia is retweeting a tweet by another fool who makes his living c… https://t.co/qu7wZAEMIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing the Tod to my Copper a little more than usual lately... 9 years has flown by 😞💔 https://t.co/VqcnMxAmiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super blessed with a group of friends that always make my birthdays special. 🥰❤️   (Kasey didn’t want to be photogr… https://t.co/CtFZcPByJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Sailor Moon Super S movie viz media edition on dvd!! So cool!😊💖🌙 #sailormoon #anime #otaku #AnimeJapan2019… https://t.co/57qxZABnjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been a minute. Love these ladies!! . . . . .  #pinchme #thisiswork #rodanandfields  P.S. Yes I’m the weirdo taking… https://t.co/ZFF3TIUNxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I want to know is when Trump diverts the money, who has oversight? To whom will it actually go? Some of the st… https://t.co/0Qspi8bFOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetEvaine Third watch, 24, designated survivor - I didn’t like her either - lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun after Nicholas Megalis show in Las Vegas @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/xmq5ApxVvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Kinds of Prints You Could Get on Your Custom Sublimated Tee! https://t.co/ZEgaot4pkW #Sublimation #Shirts… https://t.co/YZUbqBFXLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RKELLY; 1CORINTHIANS 6:2; DO YE NOT KNOW THAT THE SAINTS SHALL JUDGE THE WORLD? AND IF THE WORLD SHALL BE JUDGED B… https://t.co/0WcmczzWSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenCBS3 You make your forecasting so interesting .... Even though I am not a snow person You keep it interesting 😜😂😂😜😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack Biden's looking for the next foreign collusion in a campaign for president, what an idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to all who have gave me inspiring words. Your the best https://t.co/frcR61jE2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quem sou eu conversando com pessoas aleatórias que estavam nas solicitações do ig p passar tempo 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatHerrity Why a Republican who co-sponsored the ERA resolution says she helped block its passage… https://t.co/dDlbhZul19]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to reschedule a haircut two weeks ago, and I’m still not getting in for another two weeks.  Couldn’t be happi… https://t.co/6gu2dZUWkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best Beer Festival https://t.co/AuflAbFwcI can you cast a vote for @Brewgaloo today? Let’s put #Raleigh as #1!! #ncbeer]]></document><document><![CDATA[International Children Cancer Awareness Day🎗 🙏🎗🙏🎗🙏🎗🙏🎗🙏🎗 @ White Plains Middle School https://t.co/HoqsCxU95n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edwin’s annoying for leaving me on read every time I send him memes or snaps 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had a fucking pit in my stomach since yesterday morning and it won’t go away #anxiety]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t handle this Jonas Brothers release, bringing back all the memories]]></document><document><![CDATA[😭😭😭 I haven’t cried yet today but I might from this. Thank you beautiful!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday my hero welcome home from Vietnam Chuck Taylor @JessWaltonYR  The message above is from your Gun Smo… https://t.co/mwoU8WHflh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrslancaster810 @_BostonRocks_ Joy and passion are contagious! So grateful to be invited to the dance! ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylviaObell Black Women: An Unbothered Nation   The calm. https://t.co/duv6bitQsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been remiss in sharing some pics from the work I found most compelling in #RenwickGallery’s #DisruptingCraft e… https://t.co/SaRShmqmAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The set list. #setlist #songlist #songs #thetrews #trews #civilianaires #vintagelove #junonoms #rockalbumoftheyear… https://t.co/Z2iLIDyubt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Good luck with that Individual 1. Thoughts and prayers anyone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[listen i know u all see me struggling to format this tweet but please just ignore it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most interesting store in New York City- Growing up, everything is fascinating, you create your own adventures… https://t.co/GxHf3tNCZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MedicareForAll WILL work right now, Cloudbutcher, you fucking moron. Look at EVERY OTHER INDUSTRIALIZED NATION ON… https://t.co/6f4XNaS36i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar @LouisVuitton Need that bag.... jaw dropping.  I’ve always wanted @LouisVuitton https://t.co/KDufLqdTTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY THREE SONS I AM PROUD OF YOU AND THE MEN YOU ARE AND BECOMING - "Never quit always learn to earn the knowledge i… https://t.co/CZHwryQPQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jerri_Gill @IamLaceyChabert @brennan_elliott @BarbaraNiven Oct. There will be 3 Sundays in a row.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Craving pasta &amp; bread sticks &amp; only one person comes to mind with that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Does Trump’s horrible antisemitism receive this kind of scrutiny? People on Squirrel Hill blame Trump for the synagogue massacre.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@txtually parents don’t have a problem loving more than 1 kid. Siblings don’t have a problem w/ loving all their si… https://t.co/7lzFFaV8JH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You know I didn’t fart the whole time I was with you, that shit hurt my stomach” 😭😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to go bungee jumping when @dreamchaser1990 and I go back to Costa Rica, but how cool with it will Ethan be? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lady is a true gem 🥰🤘🏼✊🏼💚from Katie “My second protest painting... I’m wanting to draw attention to the contin… https://t.co/ntro1OBuRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatTheBerner Can’t wait till they ask her what magazines or newspapers she reads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was very confused as to who sent me a package from Ukraine! Thanks for the Saturday morning treat @serpstat! I wi… https://t.co/ueV48Hu7g3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Underboob for the win. Here until 6 come say hi 👯💋#teambeans https://t.co/i4Fz4mnqKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickMolnar31 I personally would say the ones who wear super hero logos]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyway @QuinceMountain your UPS guy is glad to hear things are going well, and also I bought more of that amazing c… https://t.co/a9ddicePR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proverbs 15:3 (KJV)  The eyes of the LORD are in every place, beholding the evil and the good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched Infinity war because I get so geeked up about those kinds of things that i can literally only watch… https://t.co/bIsvep2qK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NKOTB @DonnieWahlberg @dannywood @JonathanRKnight @jordanknight @joeymcintyre @michaelstrahan 💜💜🎶🎶🎙️🎙️🎵🎵]]></document><document><![CDATA[The question I have gotten the most since moving to New York is usually accompanied by a pained face of a stranger,… https://t.co/Rbsi5TVG0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SayWhat?! #AbolishICE #AbolishCBP #ArrestAlexAzar #ArrestKirstjenNeilsen #ArrestJeffSessions #ArrestDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrazySciTeach I like the GC embedded in gclassroom. I need to get Ss to use it more. #CAedchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me deleting and blocking every boy on Facebook proudly declaring that they don’t tip ever https://t.co/8ECK3p56Z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is a very big sellout. Personally I hope he does get some fresh competition when election time rolls around. Oth… https://t.co/xMaa5fogWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HSf7SOlkg7 @ Terra Nova - Wellness SPA https://t.co/dvJGdfdkYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t believe this winter wonderland was right in my backyard this weekend💙❄️🏞 #flatiron #superstitionmountains… https://t.co/Dame8i6nTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tojulius I feel like I should stop tweeting this so I don’t get on some TSA blacklist 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: started laughing at a tweet and he stops and says “are you crying? please don’t start crying” lol ok I’ll try not to sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome along New Peeps with Meee! Closing down this #ThorsDay  Dropped the Hammer on this treatment day Y'all Peep… https://t.co/mfT27APLSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. Just got stung by a wasp. Yes at 4:30 am in February. I guess as warm as it's been. I dont know. Any… https://t.co/WvBFBqQPb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missdee716 @circleofsun Good morning Miss Dee!  Have a great Monday. 😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yessss !! Beavers For the W 🏀🙌🏻🏀🙌🏻💕🏀💕🏀 @BeaverWBB @oregonstatealum @MarvinBeaverman]]></document><document><![CDATA[BR - Junkie (noun) A driven busy person who strives to achieve goals in life while attaining a beautiful glow both… https://t.co/euZIzfdrbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveMustaine  LARA MUSTAINE  DAVE MUSTAINE  LOVE YOU. https://t.co/fQkGqYCiCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nunugoodform I’m literally a huge fan of Cardi. Stop hating on latinas!!!!! Boohoo cry me a fucking river]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two qualities that @jrstahl looks for in a prospective member of her podcast team: technical skill and passion abou… https://t.co/XqEsCmAnwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For many, many months, I had very limited mobility, so I am thankful to be walking at all. But.]]></document><document><![CDATA[heyya wanna see a live pic of me add me on kik seller// ill send previews.. KIK 20skylive https://t.co/E3EnwwRkMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[12 gins probably wasn’t the way to go at a meet and greet with the entire company.   But hey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diversity and equity: Being fair is not necessarily being equal. #EdcampVance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNCResearch @LucioQuincioC Si pensaron q Hilary era la peor candidata en la historia de los Demócratas, les presento a @BernieSanders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SFGZ wait I’m so sad I still haven’t seen it :(((( where did you watch it I NEED it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Keep the faith Mr Cohen give us back our greatest Country. Blessings to your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobRmhenry1 @LastStand2019 @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama That’s awesome!!!  This is all it would take to convince… https://t.co/MhN8634ORs]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you have a smart car and drive like an idiot??? @ChriispyPalmerr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loose boots Monica strikes again!!! @LilRel4 @AAndersenPhoto https://t.co/kJKM4y5esn]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Hombre Libre by La Adictiva Banda San José de Mesillas on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/uG6TXcVY2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @DrRLong3 to post pics of my 7 favorite books, no reviews needed. Each day, I’ll challenge… https://t.co/WOkRVzOxBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great day at work. @swalterpack I’ll take the late spring shift on the roof.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And so the countdown begins:  my very last Monday of work at old Olympic Indoor Swim Center. #WorkCountdown… https://t.co/Ckbpe07jqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Baloo_The_Bear @HireVesuvius Are you learning more or thinking more though?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Your Week to Save 50%! Best Selling Bibles $9.99-$12.99 + 7 different 50% Off offers! https://t.co/w2MgXkCVwd via @Mardel_Inc]]></document><document><![CDATA[almost 600 followers &amp; only 30 likes on my last post, im reporting all 570 of y’all smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Friday of the board period. #yourfavoritedriver #44KiplingSouth https://t.co/w5Y5nEwW7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid It’s disgusting and painful to watch how the Republicans are out to protect Trump no matter what. Shame… https://t.co/ajvgCmvIVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those interested in @caster800m v IAAF, follow @RogerPielkeJr, who is in Lausanne for hearing. He’s part of team th… https://t.co/0xgCu3C1G2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is sad but true that this does appear to have become #twitter #Colosseum. Appreciate @TopCyberNews for sharing t… https://t.co/T6njihcrXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @NPR @nprpolitics — impressed with the questioning of Adam Kennedy. If we’re truly having an emergency… https://t.co/YsxdPnyOOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is good for me when I trust and believe in my heart.  It is good for others when I trust and believe in my heart… https://t.co/BSbWKnibpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do y’all have 300 unread messages?? my OCD would never allow that 😅😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for a best friend who FaceTimes #TheBachelor for you when you don’t have power...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JR_24X @Mitch_T13 Right right. I thought you were comparing the whole punishment. Yeah I always thought Earl was h… https://t.co/Gl2pa2bAEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexnazaryan That's more than stupid if anyone believes that nonsense.   #traitortrump #EnoughIsEnough #ResignNow… https://t.co/JPaUj3gQ4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally getting around to #abductedinplainsight https://t.co/WxgOsQw8Th]]></document></documents></author>