<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Oscar46733450 @2394armando @GloriaAlvarez85 A ver si Amlo mantiene tu mujer...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportsology His game kind of dictates amplitudes in his production. It’s not like he has been abysmal. Fix the power play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[to the girl that makes my life complete 💙 #HappyInternationalWomensDay https://t.co/dHueeYxyuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible hubris from our “moral” leader. Let us do better, Mr. President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The logistics of making @Fleshlight videos are so damn easy. No negotiation, no scheduling, no cancellations lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jharwood14 @NBCNews The substitute teacher was unaware of the law, and made a number of offensive and provocative… https://t.co/OwxGIFxvox]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven't yet, be sure to checkout my latest podcast with Derek Duncan of @feedtheball  ...… https://t.co/90VgBm1NDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMicCheck @RekedFantasy @klabreck @JesseReevesFF @FFManBun @tacitassassin13 @TheOpenBarFP @JakeAndersonFF https://t.co/dviAq17CJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ChrisHixon51 BJHS student council remembers Chris and his Sister Natalie HAPPY BIRTHDAY CHRIS https://t.co/ASJcW47ckq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcusRicee Hahahahha panatiliin nating No.1 sa pornhub ang Pilipinas😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikees8802 Te lo huelo primero y después te agarro el bulto y luego lo chupo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sterling thought holding the umbrella higher up was more stable. We’re all learning here :) @ San Pedro, California https://t.co/4OQXTcu7Qj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msinsulindpndnt Definitely #insulin4all, but in the meantime you can get serviceable regular insulin at Walmart fo… https://t.co/CNHqVsoyei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@motarola123 @KDRVSports Your story actually put me on the lookout for any movement here]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch remains!! Gotta feed the troops on Saturdays!! @ Jarrett Scott Ford https://t.co/g0HlG3bMej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank You for the support on Episode 1 of Stack Sessions that just reached 700 hundred views. Since we got so much… https://t.co/37kU2T4nph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait to hair @JRsBBQ #RossReport this week find out what he thinks of this whole @MsCharlotteWWE vs… https://t.co/9sKE7mnG1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Timothée Chalamet, Oscar Isaac, Josh Brolin, and Jason Momoa formed a basketball team to compete against aliens… https://t.co/xMO5SGge7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oliviamccabe72 Suspense. Agitate and then drop it politely. It's like knowing when to go the bathroom in the middl… https://t.co/aMoQvaPn0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 24 Hour Fitness Super Sports in Walnut, CA https://t.co/Lmq3JVOnNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please age well, please age well, please age well, please age well 🤞🏽🤞🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it can’t / won’t happen but could you imagine @TheHumble_21 on the @Saints #WhoDat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickGiva @SantiagoAuFund @AOC @realDonaldTrump Also, the real America is Jesus plus football plus second amendment… https://t.co/HuvEkD411V]]></document><document><![CDATA[But Applebee’s will be coming out with a Naan flatbread soon. Where do these people think that these ideas come fro… https://t.co/qJ7Jhqb7EW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLynch49ers 2 of our division rivals added to their defense. What’s our response? @kwon is a start… https://t.co/eAiDRNU7bw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got his autograph in 1982, yesterday I got to meet Shep Messing again! He gave an amazing speech to my students w… https://t.co/3lJi7dntT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CANCHAELNORTE @coyoteelsol @Rayados @ClubPueblaMX @AlonsoDT @rogelio7funes Como cuando el editor es bien Rayado]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @ModernFam pilot was just shown on my local FOX station, @fox47madison, and it's like a trip back in time. The kids are so young!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are sooooooo right. Seems to go hand in hand, huh. I wonder if the “pedophile” question is in the membership ap… https://t.co/WtGZYpoewN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keselowski thank you for what you did for my pops last night! Means the world you have no idea!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@verge No 1 make reaction videos to this even if you properly make one that is fair use cause @verge @voxdotcom are… https://t.co/SfmgPM5wFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[To Anyone Having A Bad Day Today Remember Tomorrow Is A New Day So Stay Positive And Smile :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsForceBB @NorCalBaseball @jordan_vujovich @OU_Athletics @norcalbbgm @SportsForceBB your working with Jordan o… https://t.co/r1mhYzvJRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConstanceM2015 @ArmorocCA @Jenny2Hugs They love me so that won't work lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody likes Eli Drake but he does make a good point Eddie Edwards needs him so they can take care of Desi Hit Squa… https://t.co/UC9VKtDbvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_flora_bot_ It just seems like a truly gallant way to sell remastered Queen music if they WERENT GONNA SING IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryCrnobrnja so I'll leave you with my question : if you could deliver the club head to the ball at the same speed and all square, but -]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrunoRguezP Sacame@de@la dudanhiho de tu gran Puta madre https://t.co/WLukcd4rR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyJohnsonNews It was a combination of things at the end forgetting the poor shooting. Scott’s unnecessary foul, Si… https://t.co/BrD6Nb2xJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonTierney @stephenasmith @maxkellerman @DAonCBS @ZionW32 when I watch highlights of Zion I see a mixture of p… https://t.co/q1UCX03PbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptainMabel Guess it won't be as bad as Super Futaman! Or Lady Longstroke!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatgirlsbeauty Okay, I guess we’re promoting obesity now. It’s not that we don’t like “overweight” people. It’s ju… https://t.co/3ijf0RGbNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdoverkamp That’s more of a testament to Papa John’s than VGK. Pretty sure it’s the same deal the day after the Ca… https://t.co/RA2QJpfd9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brentalfloss @JeremyFuscaldo “Wait Uncle Scrooge, you need a suit out there! How are you alive? You need heat. Also air.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[This show was so much fun! Any time I get to talk to @adamhlavac about fiction it’s always an awesome time.   Give… https://t.co/VMLugxRVx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[anakin literally turned Darth Sidious in to the jedi council in the morning and then killed every kid in the jedi temple THAT NIGHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zypisfy @horusrage @debbiepalm44 @yourmumspants @dadbaddy @Cern_lXXl @BahdlerBen @coelleen @Wolfpak561… https://t.co/2m918as44O]]></document><document><![CDATA[With less than a week to go before Chicago's Mayoral election, 19% are still undecided. Is there anyone anybody rea… https://t.co/r34TThKecZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shard_man Being unveiled next month apparently - https://t.co/Fc5hXWMOKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lenarosepierce has started to film videos of her talking on snapchat about her life and I would like for us to jus… https://t.co/Y8fN0EDGUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awonderland 🙋🏽‍♂️🙋🏽‍♂️  But also when talking to my cat. Gotta keep him on his toes. https://t.co/kGddyAhrsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments I just can’t believe this was leaked. Call me surprised 😯]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of being made the bad guy. You know what you did. Stop acting like a victim. I’m not going to sit around… https://t.co/oKWz9zoBkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[edubbmusic knows how to throw down on a sunday night here en la philadelphia 🤙🏽 @ Silk City https://t.co/pobJZRu2xc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds like noe needs to get his ears checked! I mean the guy didn’t fall out his seat but he was pretty excited!… https://t.co/baKHb40lqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeagalSuriyel @AM800News Again. You do you. I’ll do me.   I’m not insulting you. I have repeatedly tried to end th… https://t.co/SDv1pYQvbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trackstarkelly @ltthompso @SaysSimonson @jenniferm_q @AOC https://t.co/o8EIXfANtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch ima choose the dirty over you, you know I aint scared to lose you]]></document><document><![CDATA[ONE of the last nails with mu ex girl was the hips last show ...she was at parents house. she called me and i told… https://t.co/YVuIthYl5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smile in the mirror. Do that every morning and you'll start to see a big difference in your life. #Happyweek… https://t.co/v6Bpvfr9Eo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place Music Label Spotlight March 5, 2019 Celebrating 15 Years of Cosmicleaf Records  Various Artists -… https://t.co/zAei7TA4uM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an awesome escort the rest of the way home!! Thank you cvfd❣️ https://t.co/z3sIUuZHn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theoldgreywolf It's soooo easy for entitled "fans" like yourself Mike to criticise fans on the outside..not everyb… https://t.co/GjJYGYSjfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not that she is Hispanic,  because that doesn't matter. What matters is the Democrats now have an IDIOT as a n… https://t.co/afDAuGRBjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doc_Durham @GardnerPhD @KevinH_PhD @priyafsingh @Stanford @latimes The above quote was from a study by Kevin Hall.… https://t.co/gTOzuIvpJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dowsonick @AFootballPod @torontofc The “Bloody Big Deal”, is known as one of TFC head office’s biggest PR disaster… https://t.co/wJu4cvbKbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grant_Blank_ Man now that I got going I realize there’s a ton—  Marietta v. May-retta  McCrae v. Mack-ray  Alma v.… https://t.co/zn7R9KA666]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited for my newest listing #comingsoon. Beautiful Columbia Heights row home with 7 bedrooms and 4.5 bathrooms. S… https://t.co/n8xqzQMgCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UmbrellaAcademy is a new @netflix series. Based on a @DarkHorseComics comic. On ep 3. So far fantastic. I love stu… https://t.co/p2sqp91OaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking some brett saison whilst reheating some quiche I made, how’s your Monday evening shaping up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamHillLVRJ He’s got that duckage down and pretty sure I would not want to win against him]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at NYCB Live in Hempstead, NY w/ @isleschick https://t.co/IkDzDaRiAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let nothing be done through strife or vainglory; but in lowliness of mind let each esteem other bette… https://t.co/EwkiTO1m4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s very easy folks. Confederate sympathizers have a constitutional right to march. Ole Miss players have a consti… https://t.co/pGpAWgRhJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four years ago to this day, we were traveling to hotel ballrooms in Philly with the dream of turning this game into… https://t.co/HeHYJYfOVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago Friends - Come Find me Tonight in The @GmanTavern ............. https://t.co/2GWPYWebpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LionOfKhyber @OfficialDGISPR @ImranKhanPTI Khan promised and khan delivered! Pashtun hameesha badla lay ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noahisreal2 Now i have one question where did you find a bag of original poo??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vwinstonv @TVesAlDia @NicolasMaduro @ConCiliaFlores @maduro_en @SputnikMundo @DrodriguezVen @TareckPSUV @dcabellor… https://t.co/is21XmhiCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[But that’ll never happen it seems like, so ima stay up forever it feels like]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ mind if i use the charger?”  i just plugged it in man  “well you’re at 62%” ok and? you don’t know where im going… https://t.co/JD68YLXn1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet @JadedCreative @Lady_Star_Gem @NWPinPDX @MatthewWolfff @StormResist @TrisResists @LunaLuvgood2020… https://t.co/yTwaTLrdP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenMank77 @tcm So proud he was inducted into our South Carolina Hall of Fame just 2 years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake, in it’s entirety... such a damn good performance.   https://t.co/U0mCICsnut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iBoldNews I disagree. I think it would be a colossal failure. A failure of epic proportions. A slap 👋 in the face… https://t.co/JhePHVr4bQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me after getting capped when I was 1 kill away from my first win on Apex 🤬 https://t.co/9NgvgxyjSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @Sue564 Kimberley, I wouldn't expect any better from democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫I'm A Long Gone Daddy by Hank Williams, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/KxIDoDY4S7]]></document><document><![CDATA[From to start to finish this was a solid #SDLive the gave a good final push to #WWEFastlane and gave us a NEW… https://t.co/EBaRapoY05]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roman surprised me with a promise ring &amp; it’s perfect i’m in luvvvv 🥺🥺💓 https://t.co/3xOJLHwB7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk or maybe their parents could do their duties and limit their kids to playing the game?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benFranklin2018 And those who want to move us to another planet (Mars) which we will undoubtedly screw up as well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPoversight @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows @RepCummings https://t.co/ZYKOy0LOdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goooooood morning #brooklyn  #williamsburg #eastrivercycles #eastriverbar #eastriverferry #eastriverpark #nyc… https://t.co/q6CmHtlAl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The post rave depression is so real. Might be a while til my next show happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DocRivers @Ohmeomy @LAClippers Super class move by Doc to honor Dirk before the end of game. You get a standing ov… https://t.co/shg7gdvJEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We actually made it through four days of school this week!!! Anyone else feeling totally spent and ready to crash??… https://t.co/LtHnOdpFIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz Read this, over and over and over until you understand what a real national emergency is, you putz! 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MannyM83 @settlemlCFB @sneakerseminole @Jmacfsu24 @DMFrank_ Yeah it was. I kinda expected something after Styles w… https://t.co/lApLf3nvc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Based on how things go tonight, the UW men will more than likely get to watch a majority of the UW women's game aft… https://t.co/X1uLtzyYSl]]></document></documents></author>