<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Made Reubens the other day. They were 🔥🔥🔥.  - . . . . #stpatricksday #pattys #happy #pattymelt #reubensandwich… https://t.co/2Wqg7EtVps]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best mentors I have in the business—about working, building and maintaining relationships, and he’s pret… https://t.co/Ou9F3DTJc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump is not a quitter He will get the wall built. And he got a down payment 1.37 billon from Cong… https://t.co/9WxszA2Tmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Begun the identity politics wars have. Lisa Tatge There’s no details of the issues. No real way to persuade people… https://t.co/UCdCZGno2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s really early but I am gonna go on and say I think JCPS will be easily closed again tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 miles bites the dust #trailrunning #trailgangstaz #aravaiparunning @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/3ISrSz4BrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Adelardus Tripel by Brouwerij Kerkom at @maxstaphouse — https://t.co/EHXdrULegv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Keefe21 @DORKpodcast Once you discover the Downeaster Alexa you listen to it two or tree times a day for a month or two. I’ve been there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este es el uso correcto de los baños en las gasolineras. https://t.co/zweOzjo267]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Shambhala Is on Fire by CULT OF DOM KELLER https://t.co/WMFNpCn6FN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day to the one who brings me joy on a daily basis. I love traveling through life with this incred… https://t.co/BRaqoorrVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me-“ I’m a lone wolf” Bartender- “oh I’ve noticed” https://t.co/qj4iydLEGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[the two assholes according to my brother's wife, barack Obama and cesar Chavez lmao https://t.co/kktQS2ABUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @DonaldJTrumpJr He is 10x’s the man Trump pretends to be! NO MORE looking the other way dude! Oversight i… https://t.co/bzuTaUP0rv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perhaps you’ve seen my comments on the #JussieSmullett situation a few weeks ago. If not, I invite you to see my “O… https://t.co/QmXMJYoind]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Evil Dead remake has a really good Frankenstein reference where Mia's brother sees a tree get struck by lightni… https://t.co/uIYG1ZAoEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the vault: I tied this 10 years ago for the Yakima River. #flytyingjunkie #flytyingporn #flytying #flyfishing… https://t.co/SEEjXfew3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[An anonymous account just sent me some sinister and vaguely threatening DMs regarding my dog, referencing my tweets… https://t.co/ZmLgyKnxBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Artist Connect @bigshowfamthick  ___________________________ #comeup #artistonthegram #thecreator #lightroom @edit… https://t.co/li5AeVhnZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twobarrels @jamesjaydrums @luckymee22 @BrizbyFinley @RevKeithBritt @shesup21 @pamelaggs @Ladyjana143 @JoanisMarvin… https://t.co/GqaUrsZ0SW]]></document><document><![CDATA[EDM songs can be deceiving sometimes it makes me dance my frustrations in life away]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tahani____5 مو بس كذا في عيد الفطر عطونا اجازه يوم كامل عشان عندنا عيد وهم ماهم ملزومين بذا الشيء]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was watching the concluding quarter of my high school Alma mater @afhsevents take on PGHS for the State's 6A title… https://t.co/zFfVyYHkQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder Dems went ballistic when Duke said nice about President Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @Potus lied 8,158 times during his two years in office. Shouldn’t we just assume tha… https://t.co/ZYI7d7teFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow we’ll get ISM Manufacturing survey results for February, which should give us a more timely glimpse at whe… https://t.co/9HVRi5ygIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[it starts with self luv #BWVS #PEACE IS #PRIMARY 💛❤️💙 #MADEINNYC #BWOODKNOWS #VINNIES #X @ New York, New York https://t.co/TiyZyp335V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beantownbroad I decided to follow you after seeing your beantown &amp; Boston references as I'm in Western Mass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kblack1Kyle @sellis1967 @usbnsports @MontCoach2 @dantheman1844 @UCCVBall @cheer_ucc Good luck Cougars!]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/q5jqCTcCcM  Substantial. What you say Mueller? Substantial? Because … i think the kid's getting the ha… https://t.co/joUcSQ5ODG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @sydyoung05 continue the grind of getting better. Going to be a great Senior Year for you and your Rocket… https://t.co/VyDtEEEMlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelGrid That’s crazy. Two people, constant costume changes that I heard were expensive, it was a living action… https://t.co/xcvwxHa21M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JU5T1C3_4_ALL90 @JanC60 @DrLeanaWen @realDonaldTrump Science and fact, readily verified by all reasonable people "in self evident truth"!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCenteredEgg Since the "having" part (ouch!) is true for all men, your other points are superfluous. You may hav… https://t.co/d4nideo7pI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer Maxine can’t make sense of anything, keyword being ‘sense.’]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMLO @thirdlieb What's the conversion of a metric funkton to an imperial funkton, and do I need an expensive travel adapter?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Minuteman223 @Tactical_review @JenniPrickett @Bearman1130 @pensfannc5 @44_rem_mag @teamregulators @AverageHunter… https://t.co/7wbcj9GX1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funnel Swag keeps rollin in #funnelhackinglive @ Gaylord Opryland Resort &amp; Convention Center https://t.co/GBZ6fhYeqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[On paper this guy should have nothing to do with any of his old companies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brhodes @davidmweissman Such a spineless tool. @johnmccain2016 passes (RIP) and Graham cracker transforms into Tru… https://t.co/0up43ZFwUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showtime! #Ratboy #MaskedIntruder #TheInterrupters !!! @ The Masquerade https://t.co/dlXeLu6Jo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Eagles Howie Roseman just said, "We've decided to let Nick become a free agent".  #flyEaglesfly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I will soon be running for my local HOA board I am sure I can count on BS to share his free money H… https://t.co/IpVIaiOatp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to my online home. I invite you to come in, learn more about me and my work, and stop to embrace the slow p… https://t.co/QJriFIotN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuyetPawz @canFURence Omg I had so much fun at both panels last year. I am so happy to hear you are doing both aga… https://t.co/HDgLnt8fGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[walking away from the governor of New York mean anything to you a baby killer he is your brother walking away from… https://t.co/W5aiGE3vZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima start a premium snap idc. Girls be making that money and so should I 😤😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davemeltzerWON Do you think he might ever be tempted to make the jump to pro wrestling. He always seemed like some… https://t.co/YfV83Y77pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final stint done, Cody is in the kart with 20 to go, https://t.co/nOwmYZbjeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmcdavid97 @drtwofive Was ur last memory sucking ?   Cuz as an oilers lifelong fan. Our team is a disgrace.   Go practice or sumpin. Wtf.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeCunninghamSC Please call out your democratic colleagues that have made anti Semitic statements. Please !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Savannah is a true @SacState student athlete. She was chosen to represent all student athletes in the @BigSkyConf… https://t.co/4KFvN8Xg6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life’s mysteries ... why do we drive on parkways and park on driveways?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your mind will give up before your body will so when ya think you can’t just remember you’re being a pussy and you CAN💛 k gn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nationalloveyourpetday everybody knows Yaya, Maci, and Ivy! 🐶🐶🐸 (2nd picture took me about 30 minutes to get...) @… https://t.co/6pzSJ06Occ]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the last 8 days I have been on two short films and edited another 3 out 4 it’s 1 am and I have not slept in like… https://t.co/l8FsUUwYF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank YOU to everyone for welcoming me into your homes for the last year. Can’t believe today is my one year annive… https://t.co/CFR5Hk4ehG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JavyBaez4MVP @jemelehill Is that what she tells you https://t.co/0s2nOezf2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkYoungTruth What kind of recovery would that be? Getting arrested and doing jail time for filing a false police… https://t.co/KN9e55WMc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Purple Rainbow Unicorn All Night Long #purplerainbowunicorn #allnightlong #grahambonnett #rainbow #neilturbin… https://t.co/MSef4LZU4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rach18K The last one about making things normal and then “come in and try the new dumplings” 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reporterjamie @tarseytarsey Great seeing you Jamie - did it get a bit toasty..;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to catching the @UMassHockey game this evening. Big crowd heading into @MullinsCenter tonight #HockeyTwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good fight. I scored it a draw. Good last two rounds for Castano, needed those two to earn a draw on my scorecard. #LaraCastano]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love it when games notice a player having a tough time and offer help. They're like "You may be garbage at this gam… https://t.co/rL5JLod5p0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crushed three shows last night in Miami!!! Catch me this Wednesday at the Miami Improv!! #Miami https://t.co/fw4gsDxaaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's the deal, kiddos. I'm not trying to climb any social network ladder or otherwise profit from anything here.… https://t.co/QDck20PxHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[4-3 Oshawa. Looked like a stop, but trickled through oh so slowly. Damn. #Steelheads #FearTheFish #FishFriday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Depending on how Brian Elliott feels after tonight’s game with Phantoms, he could be back with the #Flyers and be a… https://t.co/VbVQSTEtfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caroljsroth People get angry first and think later.  .#ohididntknowthatwaswhatyoumeant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBCompanyMan Make public servants walk everywhere, eat what is served for lunch in public schools, and wipe their asses with their hands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[being under 5’ 10” and wandering around barnes &amp; noble must be so disorienting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Danielle and I literally ordered the whole menu at Kona today and didn’t even put a dent in it lmao #leftoversfordays]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ethangpeck Your debut as my favorite Vulcan was both honorable and original to those before you in the Trekverse.… https://t.co/sMeJb7pyr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VancityReynolds @ChrisCandy4u @TheRealJenCandy He was my favorite... Uncle Buck is my favorite movie of his.. I in… https://t.co/jIEUHFKMda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some great views from inside the US Senate office building as we advocate for the profession of #architecture durin… https://t.co/EZXFDneYNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 11 Pipers Piping by @thebruery @ Big Betty’s Dump Station — https://t.co/wnGn6UPC1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this Zenith 18KT White Gold &amp; White Diamonds Watch. for $46,837 on OfferUp https://t.co/0en1Sowq8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fdlepio Thank God, law enforcement and all those who assisted in the search.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wolfejosh Beijing’s leverage is less in buying/investing in the producers, really about controlling access to prc… https://t.co/YY2HxWPYGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donaldgmcrae @Giannis_An34 I enjoyed this and glad you made the trip here.  Here's a profile I did in late 2017 of… https://t.co/DA5ShxDEIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @suptdrmccormick, your leadership means so much to the @EducateIN team and superintendents around the st… https://t.co/poh5jqMt8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MashiRafael QUIEN FUE EL ESTUPIDO QUE PUSO A MORENO EN LA PRESIDENCIA? ACASO NO FUE EL EN ESA ÉPOCA RVCD? https://t.co/1XObauYOUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[We just saved money on the bill from @DominionEnergy by adding @SigoraSolar #engery #solar #rvawx #vawx #weather https://t.co/Mn9CnfczRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoesNcherrios NYC :📸  #sonyalpha #sonya #sony #photography #a #ig #sonyimages #nature #portrait #iii… https://t.co/1pyNrldhFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pure fun tonight at @mattandkim concert😁😁 these guys know how to throw a party!! https://t.co/xoBBtgWezg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonDeSantisFL It is a shame what is happening at UCF with their President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AldReilly @_johnbyrne Never thought I would read, "The electric scooter industry has hired a band of lobbyists..."]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣🤣  TORONTO REAL ESTATE SALES  Unadjusted Feb:  5,025, -2.37%  Seasonally Adjusted Feb:  6,212, +3.77%  Doesn’t Fe… https://t.co/Dlgoohm5fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VolksartOnline @poppyministries Daisy has a soothing voice for sure....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible @aiww show at @marciano_olivia #mustsee @ Maurice and Paul Marciano Art Foundation https://t.co/Q8fgNvh5iz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Nailed it again. It is really pathetic. It's almost like they're trying to help President Trump get re-elected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the only person overrated here is you, @JacobAWohl. Have you ever heard of a balanced panel and the exchang… https://t.co/KXnHLzgmm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7Chicago @ESPNChiCubs @dmillerabc7 I guess Dionne didn’t share the dress code memo w Jesse ahead of time....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you will be remembered for being corrupt and a terrible POTUS. THE WORST EVER.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zuklin1 Correct. But take a look. The platform is far more robust and includes a ton of cool features.   FIVE crew… https://t.co/UYORYSOwVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is buying a home in 2019 one of your resolutions?  If you’re receiving a tax refund, add it to your down payment fu… https://t.co/20hXXVWcRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Allegedly, #RKelly isn't broke but he's hiding his money behind his 2 girlfriends. Full video in bio.… https://t.co/yThjANUv6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sadieeelongo You know I totally would but @tyler_beichner and I have plans at 3:14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedster19 You are responsible for all actions on the console, regardless of who it actually was. That's irrelevant.]]></document></documents></author>