<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Cheering on the O’Conner StarDusters. 🐾🐾🐾 @ Texas State University https://t.co/GB89fdWHZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamweart I totally would but have my son’s basketball game at 9:00. I still have to go out in public😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why oh why @theresa_may does GB need to leave the EU? Are you just following the right wing conservatives in US, an… https://t.co/FnNelowbUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome Wednesday! What will you do for you today? I plan on keeping my thoughts on gratefulness. #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/urkkIzWkoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bless the Lord , O my soul, and all that is within me, bless His holy name😇🎉❤️🎁🎂🎊❤️🎉😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to go back to LA I miss my siblings and my crackhead friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s rightsaidfredcat’s third birthday! Happy birthday to our fur child! 🎊🎁🎉🎂🎈😻 #furbaby #ohspets #rescuepets… https://t.co/7hVZkjviqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m leaving Daley HQ and heading to Preckwinkle HQ. Stay tuned for more @CrainsChicago coverage!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saint Patty’s Day at Silva Brewing  ☘️ 1. We are opening early, March 17th from 10am till 5pm 2. Live cask tapping… https://t.co/1tbUKKSgBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[But first- breakfast! 🥓🥞🍳 #sweethometdc #bellabearamazesme❤️ @ Sway https://t.co/rbAw7lZHzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bittersweet celebration of our dear friend khrispynuggets who is moving on to greener pastures. Glad to work with y… https://t.co/8oR3QMieYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Restaurant Hourly Team Member - https://t.co/wwwUhnNjKc #Franchise #Restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cceanv @ConnieSchultz @SenSherrodBrown we would love to have you join us, if you are in the neighborhood. #FundOurSchoolsNOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got kicked out of a bar after hours in Dubuque and had to wait for a cab #noubers and last Sunday I got kicked ou… https://t.co/O07by5MAb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do u ppl who sit on twitter do all day other than get offended by random shit? Lol go outside! U need some air! Hahaha 😂😘😘💗💗💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Goldberg Tax Services Satellite Office https://t.co/jFnGd7vhA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m very conflicted in the supporting actor category #oscars #oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekend breakfast time! Our flock only took a couple wks off from laying this winter. Very happy to have homegrown… https://t.co/KKp6SmGBdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ana, hugging in consensual. He is assaulting that flag. #FlagToo  #TYTLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[CRITICAL      S.O.S      CRITICAL     S.O.     Dear Majority of American People (because those of us who believe in… https://t.co/VyJPt1C9Pb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking Nintendogs got a trailer before animal crossing..... https://t.co/FsPDpKLWoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends are seeing Jake today and my heart hurts 😩😩😩 they’re so perfect and I’m so happy for them. Jakes so happ… https://t.co/aavOzTaK09]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not nothing to fucking play w. Don’t hml just to talk to me whenever you feel like just cause you’re bored and… https://t.co/dc3fXOPrff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preach baby girl! ❤️🙌🏽 #praizynhim #wordgirl @ Hilliard, Ohio https://t.co/hv3BiMb4XI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 Voting blue no matter who. I hope we can escape the clutches of GOP and their evil intentions...but if n… https://t.co/MoqRyKBkO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[my neighbors found a dog, Gallatin &amp; Lakewood area. Please shareeee @DowneyPatriot https://t.co/20jz8TvcMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a gorgeous day at Hood River! Give me all the mountain views! Orchards, good beer, great friends, breathtaking… https://t.co/Q1t2jo4739]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAAhh or WEE-oww? NYC considers less annoying sirens https://t.co/SC64dXfBpv via @torontostar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmagbeauchamp My entire hope is that they do what the books do and make BOTH characters strong in their own ways.… https://t.co/6rMd8ahOmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trigo_mar Una disculpa. Igual terminamos en una conversación con stickers. Fue hermoso. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want you to join me on MeWe, the Next-Gen Social Network. No Ads. No Spyware. No BS: https://t.co/hs4UXhSZnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we vote how many years this jerk will be in prison.  I say 20 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wildswan @ShawnDebMartin @AOC @RashidaTlaib Why should she stop playing the white privilege card when it’s so effe… https://t.co/mQQ5KVTjXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand what you were going for but that second picture funny as hell 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Maybe you might want to research that better! I don’t think you quite understand the garbage you spew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maconder71 I'm here cheering you on and will celebrate with you once you completely kick cancers ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love myself so much that I’m own Valentine this year, bought myself gifts and all lol 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrFitzPhD Just learned Douglas Co fire was doing tests on the sirens and accidently sent them off. No emergency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY DOES SHE FEEL THE URGE TO SAY IT. WHY IS IT SO HARD TO SKIP THE DAMN WORD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sinasabi mo yung “patay na binubuhay niyo pa” eh ikaw nga gumawa non with your substitution 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This program is excellent and I strong recommend it to anyone interested in an @abalel leadership opportunity. It p… https://t.co/rSuc2L4qAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m upset about my paycheck...days like this make me never wanna work at that mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never get over Luke Combs saying “and I ain’t gotta see my ex future other in law anymore”   I freakin love that man]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is gonna be my guy. I knew it last month when I saw a piece on him on some random Sunday morning news show. Ev… https://t.co/LDJ6yZzBs2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Home Design your own dream house in My Home! https://t.co/qTxjMheRTq https://t.co/SZVXlajH8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[The video documenting our last #StudyAbroad trip to #Nicaragua won an ADDY tonight from the American Advertising Fe… https://t.co/DLGsgyy3ud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your true friends are revealed during your time of grief... and that is a major fact]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not what I was hoping for, but at least I didn't gain. Goal this week is to have a blue dot every day, hit water go… https://t.co/GdeZHPjolP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OPDOfcBossman @OPDOfcAustin @I80Speedway @omaha_scanner Lol, sorry.  Team Blue was @JimCahi45960065's department.… https://t.co/950NIMLCFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esses três foram tipo um caminhão desgovernado que a gente não consegue parar de olhar, né? #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naturenohurry91 @jennyraej1979 @Sheila413Sheila @JaimeRKOFan @Ruth_A_Day @DDUBGIRL69 @CncBhDdubminion @Asure76… https://t.co/19r8g9xg1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you ever just see stuff and already know what it’s about lmfaoooo so stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[you have to look over some people and realize that they dont have all their marbles 🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennapieper Yes! Send me your dates—I hope we are here! And I’ll be in Lincoln for CARMA in March—see you then?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OyvindStrang @CascadiaCoffee @angelicblack24 @STL_Blonde @AnnCoulter Funny, not what rethugs were saying when Clinton got a blow job🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madisen Clemensen crossed Lake Hayward. Time 01:39:48, pace 03:41 min/km, est. finish 12:46 pm https://t.co/HSO1DigdCA #Birkie2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was also a sketchy online romance with an executive from a Fortune 500. He was married and when his wife foun… https://t.co/HS0vzwfulf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HDarthPancakes @seegreenfairys He is beautiful and so is your son!  Maine Coon's are awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesscole @Seamless 47 minutes now of being on hold!!! best part was when i gave him my order number and he couldn'… https://t.co/FG0PS8Ltu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversaryI do not remember https://t.co/IhtmcF87ho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michigan Math @MichiganAdvance +@Eclectablog = the easiest way to know what's going on in Michigan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OCEARCH @Scientits @GeorgeProbst @OCEARCH have you ever spotted sharks in any kind of formation? Don’t sharks 🦈 tr… https://t.co/oIpm8f5ORJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeldenSharon  Hi Sharon, Thanks for the follow! I'm following you right back. 💙💦🌊💙💦🌊💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine growing up listening to 6ix9ine instead of the Jonas Brothers 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day!!! Don’t hate on the day... you don’t have to buy a greeting card and eat chocolate, not eat… https://t.co/M7ixFgScqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump "Regardless of your overall opinion of President Trump, do you find his new call for 'record-high'… https://t.co/L3wAniCVFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexxcreed I know u retired party rock but still disappointed it’s not here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveDSM @StarkDavid1462 @UnityPointDSM See you on the big board in two years 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza America is No Longer her Country! She gave up USA when she left for ISIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sappy moment for a sec, I do have to say, the PABers and advisors light up my life omg so supportive and fun and al… https://t.co/BOHNPZPd20]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pero me la pasé tragando la dvd y se me fue el pex de que ajustaron el vestido. Bai Bai Bai 🍕 🍜 🍞]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Beauty lies in the eyes of the camera-holder”. This post gives you 50 inspirational examples of... #humor #laugh… https://t.co/Kmx5r1G0hO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeltsleySteph @PEltzholtz @nicoleedeuter @FLOTUS @WhiteHouse No thank you! The so call "prayers" from a Trump supp… https://t.co/bMc6aU1a4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think it’s really what she thinks, it’s what she’s being told to think. She really isn’t smart enough to th… https://t.co/FNza9f7lyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Donald Trump is the biggest political scandal in U.S. history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Germ_the_Nobody Cause really what’s the point of a 100% useless drop...if you like useless drops...I don’t think y… https://t.co/tRFpsgqyCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a beautiful snowy morning❄️💙 #HatfieldKY @WYMT @AndrewWYMT @brobwx @KelliWYMT @PaigeWYMT @JimWKYT @JoshFitzWx… https://t.co/iPIZWzwuuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't miss this great contest from @wheretraveler https://t.co/nMogM6FYoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McConnellWendy Ahhhh!  Look at how pretty the capri’s are!  Peach seriously had the prettiest uniforms - both the skirt and the capri’s! 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson So thankful it can be found on Kindle. Just downloaded it and I think I’ll be up all night likely scared out of my mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcdiversity I’m so conflicted on appropriate next steps. While I find the language disgusting, I think it’s import… https://t.co/LBRyhcEXxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Votre attention, vendeurs!  Nous aimons l'enthousiasme général que suscite la participation à la Journée d'IA du GC… https://t.co/cPvKET3ixn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how many dreams has complacency killed? #Realestate #Realtor #RealEstateAgent  #10x #InspireOthers… https://t.co/gUMsm1HLaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump feeding soda and nuggets to college athletes............CMON 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoskipartaTiina I watch multiple times a day! It’s been my go too since I’m fighting a cold]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh. You're gunna go be a little whore now, huh?  Uhm... Sure🤨 https://t.co/QGEGAtVmpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I managed to get us the same Airbnb in LA we got last year. I’m still so geeked about it hehe 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy howdy do I love waking up to a flat tire. 🙃 Here's a baby pic to make this cold wintry day better https://t.co/grRrVWP7k1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never met a more terrible person than the man who owns the bar I work at 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My artwork is NOW available on coffee mugs, notecards / mini fine art prints on @etsy My ink drawings are made with… https://t.co/uZCxmo5ZYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlamTalk22 @FLOTUS @WhiteHouse She’s beautiful thanks to her husband’s money and a great plastic surgeon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud hubby Nate 💕 Reposted from @schramnate  -  I’m a lucky hubband @beccastevensbsb  @JCollierMusic  - #regrann @… https://t.co/i4Zqmbq3c7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laspositaslions I don’t know Grandma Judy but congratulations. As for the other lovely recipients, few are more de… https://t.co/Pk8GFKTMAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[GO DONATE TO TULSI GABBARD'S CAMPAIGN!!!!!!!!   We need her on the debate stage to speak truth to power. She needs… https://t.co/XCFtzmXutr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HawaiiDelilah @peterdaou Trump and his supporters little Marco Rubio are chewing more than they can actually swall… https://t.co/gmebKIU0vZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyRichter Agreed. He is also magnificent morphing into the elderly character.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you not tryna help me grow, have an amazing friendship or relationship or benefit me, or you not tryna get this… https://t.co/WH7Fg37slR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView What you THINK 🤔 is what you create.  What you SAY is what you  CREATE.  What you Do is what you create.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hPI4800ub9.   Pop-up Carryout lunch TODAY!  TODAY! TODAY!  11-1  Place your order with approximately w… https://t.co/XTjAOR3ime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollieOReilly Ha! Will stayed watching it one day and 1/2 way through I figured out why it was so weird]]></document></documents></author>