<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Texas mom claims teacher gave her son ‘Dumb and Dumber-‘style haircut  https://t.co/P2zsIHTuKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Bug eyes has been saying this forever but won't show you anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EugenioChicas @gportillo912 @nayibbukele Viejo lesbiana, disfruta el dinerito y después matate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone has been paying attention, it was about a year ago.                  Russian 💰= NRA= Republican Party… https://t.co/mKeO3Z6sIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohio State projected as a 9-seed in @ESPNLunardi’s latest Bracketology. They could get a possible rematch from last… https://t.co/CtN1h5g9pW]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one is saying that this is a racist hate crime so i will smollett is a racist hater and should be charged as suc… https://t.co/yCnkifZMNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liking this new Leisure Travel Van Wonder RTB  more and more every day! #rvleisurestyle #rvlifestyle @ Beach on Oka… https://t.co/MrSO1hZlKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ferrari- Consistanyly 2 years behind McLaren in technology. #F8Tributo #ferrari #mclaren https://t.co/EswU5wncjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTimpf No. Incorrect. Im certain you’ve received a blessing for that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consecutive steals in the backcourt by Morgan Smolen and Tyra Wingle give Hogh Point an 11-8 lead. #njhoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro liquor making my nigga a foo nigga said somebody bihhh getting f*cked tonight I'm dead dab man its wendsday nig… https://t.co/9cAOeKgMsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics https://t.co/pofj7W9Jqc Probably much more constitutionally sound than many of the previous so-called National Emergencies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Garner, NC? View our latest opening: https://t.co/RTqAVwubnZ #Marketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The only thing conflicted, illegal and rigged is you and your grifter family...you will be incarce… https://t.co/sFDAmzA3rx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimos_kosta Back when we only thought he was good at factoring........ https://t.co/8JKdxzqSHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinksThinks @Mattreiels like your Utah playlist name, I hate it so much that it’s awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about renewing my final fantasy XIV subscription but idk yet will I even play it tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Sunday Afternoon........ #NXTDETROIT @ Royal Oak Music Theatre https://t.co/9UMHqx5Rjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyAi @Nneka22821893 Isnt it a trip though? But you know the difference I am sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuminaFound @Jimmieka_Mills And trump pick to oversee education in America Devos is making things worse in America for students in America]]></document><document><![CDATA[2:35 in the game left and @vcvaliants playing strong up 55-34 #govaliants #roadwarriors #finish https://t.co/tbHEIllJYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know what I’m talking about add the snap and join the story @ jayswaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IVerboten @aimhumor @Imamofpeace The first time I heard about Peterson was when Seahawk fans were in a outrage bec… https://t.co/P7CT7HS4QU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The record doesn’t show it but @PennStateMBB is a dangerous team right now. Congratulations to @Coach_Chambers and… https://t.co/uX9u2FIOH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaomixSuicide @DaveStriDirk @sheerIock @FreckledIvey @jordokream @hashtagmorg @TeegesMagee @Ibelievthehype What? T… https://t.co/rf8a1H968o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backing track shenanigans on my #prs 594 @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/mqsCaaRZzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndyPressLive @LibsInAmerica @jaketapper Ken Starr doesn’t just hang around with creeps, he is a creep. And Bart O… https://t.co/gJMt0EcdnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyGraceByers   YOU PLAY THE PART WELL IN THE TV SHOW,&lt; GIFT&gt;  I WISH YOUR POWER  WHERE DIFFERENT,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pam_brundige @rikkibird @ringsforfun @sassy9374 @Jacquel78403333 @rebelalliance1 @LJak07 @AngusKerr9 @haysjr9… https://t.co/9hAf2GaZxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayStation @Konami @CapcomUSA @NetherRealm @UnrealEngine puhleeeze somone, hear us! 😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahbuckk The kids on the show are amazing. They’re out there cooking things I’ve never even heard of]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulsperry_ @DonaldJTrumpJr Adam Schiff wasn’t even in the meetings. He’s smarter then that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sirvizalot @ClemsonUniv Incredible.  Happy for you and look forward to reading your research.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladisylph @dreadful_damsel I’m cool with purple but this goes to a whole new level of purple awesomeness 💜🖤💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davezatz @verge Are you using a Withings scale? I find with mine I still need to open the Withings app for it to s… https://t.co/N0NzgUpwP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealWayneRoot @realDonaldTrump Why would a VICTIM of a MAGA hat wearing HATE CRIME , need to hire a defense crimin… https://t.co/jDEV0DJFe9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marketing_Skye Thanks for Following! Like a good spy thriller novel or know someone who does? Please check my auth… https://t.co/kOLSqWeJ53]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TGIF Good morning TGIF have a great day @paullyricjl love ❤️ you @ Markham, Ontario https://t.co/heb0ZUxPSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shelby_Lynn1105 No one person is better than another?  Better how?  In inherent worth, proven worth, percieved wor… https://t.co/p5xbxS7Zdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[definitely absurd. #humor #chuckle #grin #ludicrous https://t.co/niX8ZXazMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the greatest rivalries in global sports. Montreal Canadians v Toronto Maple Leafs. Seems like half the arena… https://t.co/0NDTQO3Yjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can see Donald Trump standing in front of a mirror naked with his penis tucked (or maybe it’s naturally inverted?… https://t.co/bjg7nwQfDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still confused how ppl just wake up one day and decide they don’t love you anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpamericanM @Jerrique57 @GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump Why did Manafort lie to the Special Counsel about his i… https://t.co/e0dQilSa4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEAsuka @VegasToyCon @WWE Okay, I'll be there @WWEAsuka ... but I must tell you, I AM ready for Asukaaaaa... :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open up before God , keep nothing back; he’ll do whatever needs to be done: He’ll validate your l…… https://t.co/gQ1mIbCE5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really like rodeos, and I really like carli... and she’s going to a rodeo today 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Braziilljolie Jordan, imma have to disagree the flavor in boneless gets lost i the breading of the chicken whereas… https://t.co/kMbn84laH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo can we get a zoom in on Bradley's Cooper's wife during that performance of Shallow? 👀 #Oscars #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCoSun That looks like he got paid for not helping when he said he would, but Cohen helped, and get three, Mueller… https://t.co/EEKmlxFG8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very rare to hear of 21 y/o stroke. My guess is ruptured cerebral AVM. RIP brother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DynastyGuruFF Been going back and watching old movies with my wife that she’s never seen. Watched 88 Minutes with Al Pacino the other night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only one of my favorite players ever to suit up in the New England Uniform, but just a real inspiration! Keep b… https://t.co/ymFCHsLLIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@owillis Pretty sure this is in the same universe as @SaraJBenincasa's Great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SetonHallTech How do I exit a badly maintained university tech ecosystem?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5: It’s all about lesson design. What is the content standard? Don’t neglect your TEKS for the sake of a fun game.  #gcisdchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[With no disrespect to the other five nominees but Ryan Coogler absolutely should have been nominated for Best Director.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@earlystart This would be more like what guys would make Valentine's Day interesting or fun   https://t.co/KTiJD1Ai0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[baby boomers were never taught to say please and thank you, only thoughts and prayers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blackisbeautyyy Idk i mean he pose to be Kobe Mj the goat he should make more of his shots lol they only lost by 8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fukk is this bullshited life I got granted going to be.on it's last run]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1TrueJasonKidd It's the one day they can fill the place. I dont blame them one bit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[03:50 Temperature 47.5°F, Humidity 96 %, Pressure 30.1 inHg, Rain Hour 0inch, Rain Day 0.1inch, Wind direction 213°… https://t.co/mldZAtW4u3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollyHolm  thanks for stopping in and spending some time w the @UNMLoboVB crew, what a special night it was cheeri… https://t.co/rqZ17zBWBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more time! Here is Aranxa killing it in our Logo Windbreaker 1. ☝️😈🔥 Limited sizes left at:… https://t.co/S0wEqHXNIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well @iamjohnoliver is a National Treasure! Take that @FCC!!! #StopRobocalls!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @SecNielsen No rational person would put a child in a mother fucking cage. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@douglasmack I took it as a nod to Kubrick but that may just be my fever dream https://t.co/LZxfKqHiIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always forget how SMALL the Mercury rockets/capsules were and how HUGE the Apollo Saturn V was.  This 1 of 5 (?!)… https://t.co/qm7ZvEwaqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikeybouchhhhh @TyJohnsonNews No Embiid is contributing to his poor play]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_osh_j Are you aware that your child has a nozzle coming out of his head?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RochieWBZ hey Dan look who’s celebrating her birthday today. https://t.co/5xbGQYyjzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍😍😍😍😍😍😍 mañana tenemos nuevo videooooooo de @calleypocheoffi OMG &amp; I can’t wait to see it!!!… https://t.co/8carNAPlfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live in SF, have an hour of free time on Saturday, and needs photos taken for their tinder/online dating? Hit me up… https://t.co/mZsMvfiqQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we are celebrating our 1 year since we opened our doors to the world. So many amazing memories are packed int… https://t.co/33cyKWAGIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ref stopped the fight, preferring to get back to a crossword puzzle. #JoyceStiverne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCTheVoice @adamlevine @IAMJHUD No no no Adam you are supposed to turn your back on them remember!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Your silence on this trump supporting freak is deafening! Judge refuses to free Co… https://t.co/wQEyQpIKlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ccs Comfort inn New York Department of Homeless services HRA US government Justice Department federal bureau of pri… https://t.co/IW6v5Xc7bw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irishhillsjoe @_Drew_McCoy_ I'm referring to the voter ID law passed by WIGOP which disenfranchised a non-trivial… https://t.co/HI8usMvHh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorCarper @SenWhitehouse you devils, do not know how to deal with THE G-D, you, have all angered with your idolatry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now for some Tough Enough graduates theme songs on our noontime mix Kicking off with @mikethemiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__MisterRager My bad, just saw this. Yeah I had the camera set on a tripod and then just stacked all the images together. Thanks man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizHealthEd @NIAIDNews The tools are there and if applied this could happen but the implementation gap and the… https://t.co/RzheOp1izz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drump is nothing but a power-crazed man-child who needs to be tucked away behind a large, beautiful wall of his own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newportliving Normal shirts are for normal sized people ...   That man is not normal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisKTLA @mrpotatojimmy @WestRanchXC @West_RanchPride @CalPolyTrack_XC He's a good one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kml4694 Amen, bravo, and co-sign. I was never above any job, and I learned so Much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me after I drink this Coffee and hit the gym!!! https://t.co/ZBTzmmEBLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @kkwm53 @realDonaldTrump Democrats must start impeachment proceeding now on Trump we can't afford to wait… https://t.co/rW2OSwaJas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then hold rat baby mommas gone always disappear aroun Income tax time 🤣🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has he suddenly regained feeling in his fingers? Bc he will never be 2013 Matt Harvey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XeniaWoodFAN @karlaclijster @janklaar2 @bigboobiesworld @JuggLuvr @STFPromo @number_kuusysi @schlupfwarzen… https://t.co/6Gl2P7k1fO]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is one person I hate giving feedback to because he always tells me I’m wrong.   Fortunately for me, I have a… https://t.co/bUMR1b9yOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greenhousenyt Raises the question of whether there is a real difference between welfare capitalism and social demo… https://t.co/Y3wv1xfqJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone been to a $10m startup party?  #sanfrancisco? #SiliconValley What venue? “Budgets for start-up parties, he s… https://t.co/G6ARlMDNfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veggie Chicken Cake.... "I'm sorry sweetie, could you repeat that?" 😂 Veggie Chicken Cake. Yep, ya read that right.… https://t.co/IzaX2V4sNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeerCounseling Soooooo.... I’m guess you bite off more than you can chew?]]></document><document><![CDATA[False - every congress person must vote as Pelosi and Schumer say - pure dictatorship by the few mega donators]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @smerconish Michael Cohen brought evidence of the president committing an election crime. A CRIME. But sure, it's the Biden thing.]]></document></documents></author>