<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump just said it's a big con game. It's all lies. We know that you are a the biggest liar in the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emoblackthot @ArianaGrande YALL BETTER STOP PUTTING COCONUT OIL ON YA FACE FOR THE LAST TIME !!! 🗣🗣🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard @MicheleBoss6971 She worked hard for scholarships, maintained standards as an honor student, held a par… https://t.co/05qKOXNyqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could take Jordan Belfort if he isn’t on coke and Jordan Speith can be dealt with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Music: It's Tammy Rivera (@MzFlame_86) With, "Sex With You." - #OnceInALifetime: https://t.co/nIXopJdVfD https://t.co/5251GVWdhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisfrRichmond Do you have to sign a waiver to use one? #fallintotheocean]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Borowitz Report:     Amazon Announces New HQ: Jeff Bezos Chooses Soon-to-Be Bankrupt Mar-a-Lago as New Amazon H… https://t.co/qOkMacvLBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to open restaurant/bar with a retro educational theme. Lit w/overhead projector lights, roll-down maps on wa… https://t.co/mJpETF4EIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth be told. Im Dope as fuck🤷🏾‍♂️ @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/lbTSkytkCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t need to defend your position. Trumps behavior and his rhetoric are openly@imflammatory in a way no Americ… https://t.co/H2gufqeRDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stand in solidarity with activists from across the African continent, fighting for gender equality. SIGN their lett… https://t.co/X254IOwpvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Student Voice!!  Making it a priority in Selah!!  RSVP training under way this morning.  @The_VikingWay https://t.co/lsSUoIkg1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eagerly looking forward to our new Editorial Team meetings here at Sage Publications  for the Canadian Journal of P… https://t.co/MQ2Hc2X0qm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got into this show. It’s so great. Rita is a national treasure. Watch it if you haven’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[#POTUS @realDonaldTrump never met a #superlative he didn’t like @ChrisCuomo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing home games in a stadium that is hard to hit a golf ball out at night in the heavy damp air.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahjeong Seriously? Abdicate your responsibilities under the constitution. Yes, Justice Thomas has no thoughts o… https://t.co/JX82yHR4UZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@singletrigrero1 @jguaido Por supuesto. Pero había que pedir una insurrección y no una intervención. Esa es la resp… https://t.co/vnRe00LMtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch us in your city performing records off our album   👿 'Madness 2 Magic'! 🔮  Song: @JilleeParker X @Draydel - M… https://t.co/GJZHhQF50a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to this podcast about poverty inequality. What I heard coming from the Progressive advocate made the poor… https://t.co/8OoCl0oLP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuniorBrokerBae I log on Twitter tonight and this what I see??? 👀 https://t.co/oLoTjmVG26]]></document><document><![CDATA[She still indulges me in an occasional  run every now and then. She keeps me company until the last half mile like… https://t.co/zAXEtzoufM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happybirthday #matukunzle #17thbirthday #soproudofyou @ Hallandale Beach, Florida https://t.co/SG2xKH0LSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funbuns_06 @chuzefitness That’s good to hear stay fit and healthy you guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s around one in the morning, and I’m binge watching ASMR videos. 🙃 https://t.co/FQVmDrlZNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyShirley1611 @MichaelClark_8 @melinda_clark23 @chris84webster @PastorHobbins To the casual onlookers... https://t.co/cl9I2yQZfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Oakland A's are starting to test out some of the graphics for the upcoming season... Can't wait to get it going! https://t.co/rmu1eGrId8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Candace Sue, SFMTA director of communications and marketing, presented an ad campaign honoring Rosa Parks inside… https://t.co/YYGIhqPTdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LunaLuvgood2020 @whatisaidis This is how a real president (person) should act. Thanks President Obama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidSpade Met him once in south beach. He was down to earth to a young navy guy at Nikki beach bathroom line 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐺 you came to world tour and.. 👩🏻 yessir  🐺 which? 👩🏻 Houston SF and LA  (Staff tells me to move it)  🐺 wait! did y… https://t.co/L7eW3f0u4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t really care about the things we used to share, but what did you do with my heart? (These are just lyrics fr… https://t.co/DhWwvfMFWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t post instagram screenshot memes from world star on your snapchat stories. ok thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[24 hours into the trip, and the body immediately begins to deteriorate.  Bad sleep.  Muscle atrophy.  Fuzzy head.… https://t.co/rD11V5aJke]]></document><document><![CDATA[We know Mr. Cohen quite well however most of us had never heard of you Mr. Higgins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rockies Wow! The @Rockies do love the @Indians ; they are advertising @Indians jobs on Twitter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cali_Tracii @RealErinCruz Heels Up Harris probably wants to sell her own v-jay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gridlore @Caltrain ! thanks for sharing, and cheers to you and all your hard work and (often invisible) discomfort!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one has the right to make you approve of something that you believe is wrong. #freedom #freedomofconscience… https://t.co/oeam4aSVpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessgartner @BoydKRutherford anyone still harping on this after the reporting last year is not acting in good faith.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grftn_ @chris_stearns @WhitneyTilson That’s because Chris is an idiot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t want to sing Count Belfiore in this amazing production! You can see me on Friday evening and Sunday afterno… https://t.co/ahffSz6fV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This tactical outplay is basically how I was able to beat Frew twice today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think it would be in bad form to ask 4-5 people to wait in a freezing car for 20mins as I splurge on a live animal… https://t.co/XpWAHlDtL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little taste of fun is always needed so you never feel like your missing out on anything...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Fashionisima @Rob_PR76 @CycloStorm @denisselebron @mjean2 @boinaverdeyulin @gladysbigio51 @EndColonial1sm… https://t.co/TFnYBN8CEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[As demand for time grows, the YouTube gen (#GenZ) is shifting from video to audio content consumption. @SplitLegend… https://t.co/Or3bX8uN57]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pookietooth @mitchellreports @realDonaldTrump It sounds like you just described an infection caused by an alien pa… https://t.co/BB1WXqVxVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timothy_de_Illy You are not alone! I was getting a lot until yesterday and now hardly any. I read some had been put in time out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adanger15 @Money23Green I'm 39....been a warriors fan since the days of @TimHardawayFDN @BamG_1 @mitchrichmond23… https://t.co/MGsJW6BEmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thoughts from journaling today: Outrage is a perspective distorter and will mislead me by inflating my ego. Best le… https://t.co/ylRx7jRbvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaRealGrizzle @TheRacemancan I wonder why we can’t use the money seized from El Chapo to help build the wall. It w… https://t.co/WyiNwJzIFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eileenwilk1 @wazzuer @chucktodd @Jim_Jordan You are suffering from collusion delusion.   It afflicts butt hurt Dem… https://t.co/DUTXToJjnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @LLC4USA The only embarrassment for the USA is people like Biden that become rich feeding at the publi… https://t.co/9llLU5mEzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sin duda un desconcierto con la temática y un gran vacío en el diseño de espacios públicos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rjballinbias Looks like we are smart...well at least about fist fights]]></document><document><![CDATA[#REPOST  @inspiredquests . TRAVEL FACT . #InspiredQuests | @KevinEssar specialises in… https://t.co/S2vLr6GhsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huron-Bruce from space. My friend @TomSpears1 tweeted this weekend about a picture of Huron-Bruce taken from space… https://t.co/MBEQRq9XoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come rain or shine we are back at Central Filling supporting our best food trucks https://t.co/ywX6Z4NW1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rubis32 В контексте: бля, никто интервью не даёт, о, давай, этот в костюме, давай хоть что-то запишем.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gregggyboy Everyone enjoys things differently, and crafty beers is one of those things I do enjoy. It tastes a lot… https://t.co/S5FT9UDw7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Pieces of Texas by @RealAleBrewing at @bighopsgrowlers — https://t.co/FLS90ImoMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyFlwsUNTCHBL @MLB @SFGiants @RaysBaseball @Orioles @astros @tigers 8 in Chicago for sure!  Just for the simple fa… https://t.co/9eQf430awY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Upstart_Brewer @Crystalann617 Isaac is from NH, you have to take his opinions on food with a grain of salt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing I can say. No good wishes I can give. No thoughts that I can offer. But I can thank the wonderful… https://t.co/TsBT2DsRFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope everyone has a blessed weekend full of nothing but positive vibes... Much Love 🤙🏽 https://t.co/jN5CZkEmoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally bought the Bigsky from @strymon after so many years of wanting it and these next 4 days are gonna go by like an eternity]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great night and a amazing shot.  #caughlin #familylife @ Scaddabush https://t.co/s5l8lUvwsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter when you try and watch a video  A̷̼̼̗͎̖͉̤̽̾̓̇̀́̓̀͝͠å̸̳̭̀͑̌̔̅̇͐ȁ̷͙̖̩̣̺̖͇͖̝̊̂͘ä̷̛̞̯͚̺̥̣́̏͐̀̚̚͘ȧ̵̹̺̱̿ͅ… https://t.co/AJ7eqzqwof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RusevBUL What will you do for work? Play Chewy in the next Star Wars? @TheRock]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ride-or-dies. #onelasttime #theshield @wwe @ Wells Fargo Center https://t.co/5TOB90Oa22]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a crazy dream my boy @BlakeIrvingg played at @OU_Football  and snapped on everyone! Why not? Somebody have to d… https://t.co/14szDq0oBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up at 6 am to start smoking pulled pork for my family that is visiting from out of town! https://t.co/WeaJGnvylx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GalvinSeriously @MrMikeCalta I thought I’d let you know. I tried listening to Galvin’s Open Letter in the app and… https://t.co/Siw8BP9UBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ringo Starr es un gran baterista y quien diga lo contrario ya sabe que hacer]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏟 Estadio Azteca. Copa MX. Martes 12 de marzo | Cuartos de final |  🏟 Estadio Akron. Liga MX. Sábado 16 de marzo | Jornada 11 |]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ironically, he’s actually only inside right now cause I heard him getting into a fight with some ginger butthole fr… https://t.co/wkQXE6iLhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GWU_MBK @BigSouthGameDay DE went off! But good thing he did ! Good win!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DxnielDimas @NieR_JPN Me faltaban 3 logros que en 1 hora podía conseguir 😂. En fin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Socialism_Kilz @AfroLibertarian @LibertyEricRI @LPMisesCaucus @ThomasEWoods Speaking of embarrassing... https://t.co/GSOWOeCJBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenseiJayyy happy birthday brother. these the only pics i got. But you know I love you Jefé 💙💙⚽️ https://t.co/r1jgOnjbun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AthulKAcharya @TheAtkinsFirm If at any point you feel like argument prep is overwhelming, just remember you’re bei… https://t.co/1tkQagRnGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can name 3 loyal #Apollos fans: @sheehan32 @Stephen_Shiller @Jeff_CMU #ORLvsSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonAmico @BNightengale It will not be an easy task to win 2 of 3 from the Orioles this year. Don’t undervalue th… https://t.co/4XaMuJQSzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Translation: Questioning the foreign policy of your ‘democratically’ elected federal government is unacceptable. Qu… https://t.co/c77iVUux5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[“No, Officer, this is powdered sugar all over my face, not cocaine.” is not a line I thought I’d have to use today, but here we are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Film Industry and #media #production sector in #Ontario  #Canada and #NorthAmerica. Many graduates from this progra… https://t.co/QeXocgQev0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good evening everyone!:) I just wanted to reach out and say Thank You to everyone who came the Celebration of Life… https://t.co/MWwKGAev5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easily the best thing to have come from an AAF game. Very, very good boy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsiderSubo This Gif isn’t great. I don’t think it really grasps the genius of Henning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got word that today’s baseball game between @ArcadiaBaseball and @Etiwandabasebll has been canceled and will b… https://t.co/5yKwvuSoUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunDoniB Why would anyone take it out on the messenger? We know where  the real problem is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lutecroy My Army commander is doing his at ACU too and likes it. If I can make the money happen Vanderbilt is what… https://t.co/IwCFxdLE0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw this clip before the movie came out and it's the only reason I didn't watch it. Y'all don't know good movies th… https://t.co/fWlUde11ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AETV I wonder why there isn't an #Obama dynasty 3 night special? Barry was president for 8 years. @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/Q1UD2gOXUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FarmChicJodi @IHboog @mommahenof3 @BootscootinGMaw @birdfarmerswife @dbatie @thebirdfarmer @JenSchweigert… https://t.co/WW8YLjwWub]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I know we have to kiss this goodbye, but one more time, kiss me goodnight.” 💙💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the #FridayFortyNYC for @HPPlayNYC on @TodayTix! Get tickets for performances next week at $40 ($20 per Part) #CursedChildNYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFLSTROUD Wouldn’t players get pissed to be released this late in the game?]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a couple of weeks of shock and muscle rebuilding... the scale finally noticed that I’ve been riding my bike...]]></document></documents></author>