<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Making chicken enchiladas for work today... got home from the store... ready to make the enchiladas... forgot the c… https://t.co/NfLPx2uABK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never know who you’ll run into in WeHo #akidwell87 Chapel https://t.co/OdeCyPykVz https://t.co/ptlhpoyyZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful ❤ Journey  I am grateful that I got to meet Coach Miller @DLouMiller almost 5years ago because she truly i… https://t.co/VwaYvS5De7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EuroYankeeBlog @politico There was much work that had to be done to make it look like HRC won CA. AP calling it th… https://t.co/RPSDgn0b3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halecetretheare A Gentleman’s Guide to Love and Murder #hctorg @ Hale Centre Theatre https://t.co/melLxAlOWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same Day Appointments Welcome! Starting at 2 Hrs 2 Maids $90 Professionally trained cleaners ready to help!🧹🧼🧽 No c… https://t.co/cxMtvPviu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity See! We don't need a wall. This shipment of illegal drugs was caught at one of the ports of entry, not… https://t.co/vPFnC6K2Ub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psyched - can't wait to see #TheProdigy in #Boston again soon!! #EDM #punk #tour #UK #liveband #crazyfan #dance ☠️ https://t.co/dwyYcG4Jyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to convince your coworkers to take barre instead of yoga is harder than it sounds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OKDOT @GovStitt @govstitt Your retweet makes it seem you’re concerned about people being safe...not calling an ear… https://t.co/SkYel1qdpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin The flu is horrible, and can be very dangerous. I’m so glad you’ve been to the doctor and are on the… https://t.co/y8FlXJyqjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TLT16 @ShadowHeartGlow Nice picks! I miss book mail now that my committee is done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is phenomenal! I'm so excited to see the various ways we engage using technology.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brasilmagic Historically, it's not looking good....he has successfully wiped out all accolades after 9/11]]></document><document><![CDATA[On our way to our favorite event of the year - Ketch’s Palette to Palate. @ Wichita, Kansas https://t.co/YdoOIFEK4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if we limit this to things that occurred in New York while he was in office, he was governor during Hurricane Sandy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Merci to all my colleagues at @HRH2030Program in #Mali for their #IWD2019 photos! #BalanceForBetter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bretmichaels I am sure it was an awesome show! I wish I could have been there. Love ya Bret❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Oh my apartments safe. Nothing will ever happen. It’s right behind a fire station” *multiple firefighters cars get broken into*]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the drag queens introduce theme selves to @nickb2z saying “oh you the boyfriend” 🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re gonna sit at Starbucks and just be on your phone that’s fine but I politely request that you please sit a… https://t.co/Nun7j6OX1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then January 21st 2017 right after Christmas I fell and paralyzed myself again. Lost 2/3s my income and enilated my… https://t.co/UVGCzJnn9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emily on the phone with her dad: “dad! Mom is as useless as a condom with a hole in it”]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/4Tn3wL1Ck4  Can’t stress enough what a powerful show @OneDayAtATime is, especially now, more than ever… https://t.co/gfHbnbsNWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree and remember #Diversity means #genderequity and other #diverse groups like #DisabilityInclusion #LGBT #Agism… https://t.co/Jd7tWtNHXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richiewrites @spookychan @alexeckmanlawn @Taxidermied @DarickR @neilhimself https://t.co/QpWoGQRuTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bizg33k @samanthagwolfe @MissDestructo @MarshaCollier @kerrymflynn Oh wow! What a nice surprise. Thanks, Neil!! 💕… https://t.co/EPQOPNxr9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weirdradopinons @kkelseeey_ @momof2dinosaurs @xoxoelley You keep questioning my intelligence but stay mum when I c… https://t.co/GzV1TVjnqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @JanetMaslin and @MarkHarrisNYC for (another) compelling Oscars conversation. The drive home was tough, b… https://t.co/kLLIUtF6oo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows If #Cohen has to amend that document he still has 99 more before he catches up with how many time… https://t.co/x5d27LFF8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlmaBona @JussieSmollett Your reply to a 2016 tweet is fascinating then....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs I am shocked to learn this I’ve been so naïve growing up. Our world was so diseased and I thank God He’s cleaning it up amen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Khole a fucking dumb ass she’s going to blame everybody but her baby daddy on why her relationship didn’t work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ulookgoodfor33 shared this with us! 😂😂 Too funny not to pass along! @ Charleston, South Carolina https://t.co/S9BpJlluVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TotumaStereo @itzhel_s @redhotmm77 why did @mah_ret_zah just say “girls night” 😂😂😂 I’m jumping out the car]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nel23x Do it! I was super scared for mine but honestly it wasn’t bad. The worst part is when they’re healing, be c… https://t.co/lWWD27ejOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Try a Billion Dollar Apple Whisky Cocktail recipe with @crownroyal  it will the perfect drink for your wedding rece… https://t.co/ov1hvvIwoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacBlythe @usmcdoordie @AOC I hope she knows it - I do as I’ve been quizzing her for the test all day! 😂 It’s pretty interesting tbh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andy B ha viajado en lo que va del año (3 meses) más de lo que yo he viajado en mi vida]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly Congress has become nothing more than a circus.  And the Dimms are the lead clowns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kc Cowell THIS so totally makes me shaking my butt at Stink acceptable!!! We'll get THE... https://t.co/Cn0VdjpIAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praise the Lord.. if WE TRULY trust GOD! Have FAITH!!! GOD WILL work IT out.. GOD IS MOVING]]></document><document><![CDATA[__goliath__  Wasss Popping??!!?😋 I couldn't help but SCREEN SHOT this moment!!! It was TOOOOO FUNNY!!!! @ Greenfiel… https://t.co/4jawBWeFz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nynfa711 @AstrosAtoZ @DollyDwyer10 @somosLosAstros @sillylilmom @WBaygents @astros @MadSadAstrosFan @HtownWiggy… https://t.co/PdjlNRptVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emolclause @IvankaTrump No, because she never actually does anything good that she says she is going to do.  This… https://t.co/TCJdy1UKnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tuffsies @AOC It’s all part of their need to feel superior.  Which tells you that they are very insecure people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deuteronomy 31:6-8 New International Version (NIV)  6 Be strong and courageous. Do not be afraid or terrified becau… https://t.co/HDPdv2OpVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Después de que me grito que era una tonta aquí andamos 💕 https://t.co/c2wfi9Gsyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carole_mercy @soyjoseyoutuber Un saludo a tus seguidores @carole_mercy toma tu like ☺️🖕🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 The hate-filled insanity of the Left is not going to wear out Trump supporters because our POTUS is a WINNER🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸 G B USA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rihanna - S&amp;M Remix (Audio) ft. Britney Spears https://t.co/pQcf1D4ol7 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[8th graders finish their morph drawings as an exercise to learn about texture and form using technical pen. https://t.co/s5av6orUNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[So peaceful and encouraging to watch members of my church praying over people, situations, and praises last night!… https://t.co/Jg5RzLvez8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha that's a good doing his popularity! Everyone hates him around the world with the exception of mental patient… https://t.co/O6b3EKvXSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reader's View: Re-election campaign for Commissioner of Finance City of Saratoga Springs https://t.co/fT13AskE6B via @saratogiannews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me showing this to my parents because they’re worried about my safety driving in Atlanta. Welp looks like now you h… https://t.co/iY0ofucF4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russman123_ I will argue another white person down about racism lol like bitch fuck you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yzest5121 @AZChiweenerPop @SpectatorUSA @realDonaldTrump @20committee @spectator It HAS beem professionally edited… https://t.co/hZYidNAUSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yo111481susan @YouTube Oh please...just stop! You can assassinate Cohen's character but the fact he brought dated… https://t.co/VCYL3cLJTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rebecca Smith crossed 15K. Time 02:07:46, pace 14:57 min/mile, est. finish 10:10 am https://t.co/8Xizm7S4Qv #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @MissRoth_cbsd to post covers of 7 YA books I LOVE: no explanations, no review - j… https://t.co/sMR1ODh7ZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun beach houses are my love language. ☀️ #seagrovebeach &lt;The Seaside Caftan in Boho Blue available on-line at… https://t.co/P9O8WgiOyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHE SLAYS!!!! 🎨🖼🖌 #ArnoldSportsFestival #Day4 #fitnessbeauty #npc #ifbb #ocb #ArnoldClassic #ArnoldClassicOhio… https://t.co/foFWzJyz1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep on TRUCKIN’! 🔥🙌🏼  #Silverado #GlendoraChevrolet #chevrolet https://t.co/NiKVObs6DY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodjobliz I guess it's just a shame that the majority happen to be white men that are in the industry and busines… https://t.co/cZZfwvxTle]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched the end of New Girl, but didn’t know it was the end of New Girl. I am now very sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you scroll through a girls insta you can see the phases of best friends she goes through]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dad: look it’s Quavo Me: yeah! Dad: like Jose Quavo?  Me: lol good one  (CC: @QuavoStuntin) https://t.co/EnicImIcMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[📍SAN ANTONIO  Today until Monday, BUY ONE VIP TICKET, GET ONE VIP TICKET FREE!   CLICK LINK AND BUY YOUR TICKET:… https://t.co/5BNtdoVKZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just won @hqtrivia for the 2nd time ever. This time on Sex And the City Night! Thanks @SJP @KristinDavis… https://t.co/Zl6W9qdxca]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Educators urgently need a national movement for professional learning about reading. We should declare a No Shame… https://t.co/RTZSBWldkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, @DiCiccoMethod, 99 days out from the World Cup. After last night’s performance, what has to change to actually make it to Lyon?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KapeKarl @disarmingfilms Why don't you go follow Sarah since you love her so much. Oh wait she doesn't have an acc… https://t.co/HK4rpDfXVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow I totally agree bcuz he was defamed even after they had the whole video]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s down to shoot on any  7/11 of  downtown Miami !??? #streetwear #streetfashion 🤳🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmoyeweirdnews @HowardSchultz Ok YES. Dangit now you just made me admit that I AM interested in what he has to say! Curse you! 🤣😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know I was excited for Swensons but this wins https://t.co/xm9Z6fzJOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savanafvinson Well the back side of my house is built into the ground so the roof is like 2 feet off the ground 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[...All things God works for the good... @ Iglesia Casa De Gracia https://t.co/nK17RRwQp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[ARTPEACEGURU  PEACE ☮️ WANDS  Designing this wand using the crystal🔮 Shiva Lingam. I just finished carving out the… https://t.co/YPyn6djHt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill We have a border, between both of the countries touching us. Also between every state. I’m in Idaho and do… https://t.co/AJPuX6j6A5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for Summer like... 😎 Help me celebrate the Springtime at Brennan’s this afternoon in Venice where I’ll be s… https://t.co/nD4NcpbKhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GretaThunberg @tveitdal Nothing is more educational than teaching students to protest peacefully to save the earth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye y’all include @Drerozay_4 in your prayers and send some good vibes his way! 👏🏼✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[|Switch| • • Couldn’t have had a better time with my best friends 👯‍♀️ {not all pictured} in the world. Soo sooo so… https://t.co/GRAQA5GyGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@old_osc @angus4819 @GOP @DNC @dccc What's WRONG W/ SOCIALISM? WE NEED A SYSTEM HALFWAY IN BETWEEN CAPITALISM n Soc… https://t.co/6dHgeZTtR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bivši francuski predsjednik Hollande  je održao opširno predavanje o izazovima koji se nalaze pred novom Europskom… https://t.co/6p6irM3yfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cannabisphotography #funstuff #cannaculturecollective #cannapost #mmj #mmjlife #mmjphotos #cannaweed #tokeitup… https://t.co/4msOotMiLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[😭 the way some girls try so hard to be petty towards other females is embarrassing BBYG! No]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebekahDenn I agree. I’ve been walking all over First Hill and Central District for work for the past 2+ months an… https://t.co/Lkm6Qpd5Hz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreatBonsai @ABHodgkins @4everNeverTrump @RepJuanVargas Goes both ways though. Neither side (I know the dreaded both sideism) is innocent!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a great night at McGrath’s for Mary’s first fundraiser in Harrisburg! Happy that so many people showed up de… https://t.co/VzMV8j4UJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@immigrationcom @RealDonalTrump That wall was there before Israel became a state]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherrynron @shannoneffects1 Also no proof that roger stone was involved with Wikileaks (no offense Wikileaks MY LOVE♥️😘)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ernie_plumley @MAGA_Engineer @POTUS @ILMFOrg This woman is mentally disabled to be part of our Government 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was the single most bizarre thing I’ve seen in professional soccer in years (well, discounting Suarez’s pencha… https://t.co/msqRZZoB8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GnarWin2 It’s a tragic problem for the addict and everyone who cares about him/her. I hope your person seeks help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[play date chaos in a nutshell... I knocked over my glass at lunch (and it shattered everywhere🙈)... one kid fell in… https://t.co/OnllRi5urp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Single lady just looking for a good guy to watch @BravoTopChef with on #ValentineDay... Any takers? Hello? Is this thing on? 🎤 #TopChef]]></document><document><![CDATA[i literally stayed home and cried, drove to bk to get chicken fries listening to 1d nonstop and just sobbing, SKIPPING CHEER PRACTICE IM]]></document></documents></author>