<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday! Here's some important upcoming @MBTA meetings on the proposed 6.3% fare hike that would start July 1s… https://t.co/1svZ0W2zga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harbor Freight Tools is hiring in #Madison, GA! Click the link in our bio to apply: Retail Stocking Associate #SupplyChain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraKAtkins I attended this session as well. There are so many opportunities for shared leadership with students a… https://t.co/HTtjJAUTQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely #Orlando @MomsDemand Cheers right along with you from CaLeg @MomsDemand Our election work and day to day… https://t.co/nHGYagPiVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#signsofspring #rain @WYMT @AndrewWYMT @brobwx @KelliWYMT @PaigeWYMT @SpectrumNews1KY @JoshFitzWx @JimWKYT… https://t.co/jFa7bvQBlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noahcent if you are trying to get my attention... it is not working. Keep trying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@esmeehdez_ @nath6niel Ohhhhh shit another guy not giving me credit for my shit 🙃🙃🙃 ohhhh great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecojsz I would be very interested in that if possible 0”:  I don’t have adhd/add but rather OCD which def causes… https://t.co/vCnMamFk6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[wait I may be real late to this but y’all ever notice that @KFC follows 11 people. 6 guys named HERB and the 5 SPIC… https://t.co/ZWCJxiZgCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USPSHelp I have tweet and DM few times without any luck. I keep using tracking for a package I believe sitting on a truck or you lost it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP #LukePerry man, life’s short and uncertain... tell your friends y familia you love them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to India Talk about her Keto Diet Journey   Let us design your next training 🏋🏽‍♀️ #greatness #trainer… https://t.co/oWkRyxXSR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_DrinksOnMe Bet you lost a few precious brain cells dreaming up that gem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ex. In a Mexican restaurant they will ask him questions in Spanish then turn to me in English .... am I tripping??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@introvert021 Hopefully they give you the book , they gave me then you take a picture of the receipt and show it to Dr.metofe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katienotopoulos Is there a chance that women are...wow I can hardly say it...more emotionally healthy in some ways… https://t.co/Yck2DC19q0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy TargAversary 30 years  Mrs. Karen Rocha signing specialist  #T-1805 https://t.co/1c2AT58w7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stuck in a classroom with no electricity or WiFi and 44 7th graders. Not a great way to start a Monday! #TeacherLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure sign of Spring, Daffodils in the garden. Weather is nice this morning with the sun shining but the forecast is… https://t.co/pSxCp4ya0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump seeks $4.7 trillion budget with domestic cuts, $8.6 billion in wall funding https://t.co/SvbAYQrPsk If defici… https://t.co/5EzuvQQMIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobvt1777 @maydaymindy9 Oh. I see. You live in Bernie Sanders state. Your arrogance now makes sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coral Springs FL Fri Feb 15th AM Forecast: TODAY Mostly Sunny Hi 79 TONIGHT Mostly Clear Lo 61]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarioLopezExtra @Esther188rod  MARIO I FIND IT DEPLORABLE WHAT YOU'RE DOING ESPECIALLY THE DAY WITH THOSE TWO BLAC… https://t.co/CcbNY0jmcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joy is... — #blackwomeninhollywood  captured by @mrowephoto @ Beverly Wilshire, Beverly Hills (A Four Seasons Hotel) https://t.co/RsrO0FFri4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got to check out Nauti Spirits Distillery. So great! @Ristagno_DMan #nautispirits #capemay… https://t.co/qrGoMJCNAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnMEllsworth1 VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥… https://t.co/4MkVdcT5Y4]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now what?🙅 😂 #blessed #modelandactress #housemusiclover #dogsofinstagram #edm #movementdetroit #edmfestivals… https://t.co/JqU6WCulWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-opening night ... One of the oldest surviving classical masterpieces and August Bournonville’s most lasting con… https://t.co/b8AH5z1g4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had tacos , beer &amp; they smoke me out, they where giving me free liquor but I said no lol ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrdannyglover what an stupid answer you gave to @JuanCarlosCNN, we all know that you liked Chavez’ revolution beca… https://t.co/DmPZXT08Xx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you a woman? 👩🏼 Do you own a business?  👩🏼‍🎨 Entrepreneur? 👩🏼‍🍳 We would love for you to join our Oak Cliff Wom… https://t.co/9df83YYLjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryFolley Apparently he thinks you can buy one of those too after all look at the position he’s got into with his money]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish every time @SonOfGodAndMan or @s8n or @DarkPrinceLucy decided to comment on @realDonaldTrump @Twitter that h… https://t.co/leQ8RiFW89]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 21: this album goes HARD and lyrically some of the best content i’ve listened to this month. i’m in LOVE with t… https://t.co/NloBCBvhVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a month I will be on a 3day mini vacation and I’m so excited 👏🏼👏🏼  And then in 3 month and 10 days I’ll be on my second vacation 🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[You've got to face the enemies of right NOW. Enemy #1 is indecision  #SPBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started binge watching @STARZ  counterpoint. ❤️ jk Simmons &amp; this spy show #spy #starz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acro_nm Lmao it’s just funny that it’s always in one of the first 3 things men ask.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stacie9853 @tnormandeau22 @birdtracs @BuckeyeCuti @lizheileman @Katie_Elaine012 @ddub_girl_69 @whitegirlsmooth… https://t.co/jLIlWxhluZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weegee56 @mccunecicki I’m 60 and live in Ohio and agree wholeheartedly with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marattin Era il passato in cui si viveva a debito. Non è male, se non te ne frega nulla del domani]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElleEmBoogie Ehhh some not all. I enjoyed both &amp; Zoey and I just watched it too.   Again...we are the same fuckin person 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just bought my own amazon prime account and I feel like this is adulting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 1st of March! This month's challenge is 31 days of #Abs! #JoinTheMovement to be #HealthyWealthyAndWise… https://t.co/LLPjL2OMo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget tonight is the night to turn the clocks ahead!!   Don’t think of it as losing an hour of sleep but rat… https://t.co/b5zSyzrql5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always so great chatting with @JessSpindler. She has such great energy and just an amazing human being.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How's my face glo today? Your face can glo too glospawashington.  Today Only $5!!!! @ Glo Spa &amp; Salon https://t.co/Cv7ueAnoTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever want to test my level of violence.... put me on a crowded ass bus in the Bronx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodwinlaw @reshmasaujani @GirlsWhoCode @EmilyWWeiss @glossier Such a nice surprise that the book was signed!! 😱 https://t.co/IGuxHadYZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TennesseeDonkey @TNMOONCHILD I check it a lot 🤣🤣 https://t.co/Ai6o8usd5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[A miserable 5 days in the hospital just to realize you have yet another fever and worse pain than before, that Twit… https://t.co/n9e1IhVrbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to use this gif. LMAO @sincerely_steff https://t.co/duMWuIjVWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliansRum Yes they were involved because he wantedIsrael to give up their nukes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gorgeous bathroom features our @mayaromanoff hand painted Weathered Walls™️ wallcovering. Thank you for sharin… https://t.co/aYcKr1IC9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenniferabrams @HBO Completely agree. The story of the creators is really cool too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunset and rain coming @ Carmel Valley, San Diego https://t.co/iNLCm86xJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wasn't able to make it into Bill's LGBTQ+ YA panel @ Tucson Festival of Books, but I did get to meet Bill Konigsb… https://t.co/sGAFLeBeI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoogMarshall @Mr_Domoooo Hands down she’s the best girl I’ve ever seen play in person bro, I had to go cover her f… https://t.co/lOWFUKM57W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuysBride @ckhowell1 @wessells_andrew @CaldwellElemen It so so exciting to watch @CaldwellElemen's @PCSBITV progra… https://t.co/FoeBpZMdWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VABVOX Yes it is going to be ugly again because we don't seem to learn a damn thing. Take a break. You try so hard… https://t.co/Q1m1Kwx4eo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #LoveJonas on @TyltEnt—Jonas Brothers will make a great comeback https://t.co/KPvyZhuX0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started my Monday off with Lift &amp; Blast then headed to the store to get food for work so I can stay on track.… https://t.co/5CVAJzNJNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine that! I didn’t see that it said the Dems caused this problem though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Have you seen this?!  The Mueller Report: The Final Report of the Special Counsel into Donald Trump,… https://t.co/Bwk8xc343C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crazycharisma @619sports @Bobbycressey @SanDiegoSockers @finbegin Awww es okay!  Next game!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmbJohnBolton pls address the fact that Maduro has raided &amp; arrested 2 American Reporters affiliated with @abcnews OUT OF Miami.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@millstreetbrew The #beer Hall @distilleryto en @seetorontonow #seetorontonow #cerveza #cerveceria #amolacerveza… https://t.co/CFJ936A8CE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last President that criticized America overseas turned to be undermining America. Let's not make the same mista… https://t.co/iZXpaqs5mY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinjosephkane @TheWrap Don't worry... they'll rob ya from a distance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the course of a month, it rains so much that the saplings grow into big trees. Bring it back; we're heading to… https://t.co/c7wRRdDwMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitch ima choose the dirty over you, you know I ain’t scared to lose you]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Qué pedo con la gente que cuando esta triste/enojad@ hace ejercicio del coraje? Wey yo lo único que se hacer en es… https://t.co/ouVvc7QGhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Those crazed Democrats are finally  holding you accountable for your dishonesty, perpetual lies, y… https://t.co/5DRFrGRBSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait. Northam restored voting rights to hella felons in Virginia? To say sorry for blackface?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#winner #smallchange #californialottery #monopoly #truckerjackie https://t.co/Au24s4k76y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YesICandice Wait are you talking about a ball gown or nightgown?? Lol, I respect either answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I already know I’m dying of lung cancer or a heart attack so my life expectancy is short😌💅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaylegoldin Ever wonder what your baby would have been like? What your life would have been like if you hadn’t killed her?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has Saudi Arabia forsaken the Rohingya for oil money? Published April 18th, 2013 - 10:49 GMT via… https://t.co/A2MTGm3qjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 31st anniversary to my best friend. No matter how hard life gets for me, I can always count on @bdamp17 havin… https://t.co/IbTFOHvxka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chefsymon Absolutely ! And a chicken broccoli bake (for example) is a casserole, IMO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m listening to frank ocean and my roommate really asked if I was okay 🤧 idk am I???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriciaCLee @escapedmatrix @rsmale @AOC She doesn't need people who think they have a right to tell her what to d… https://t.co/Gz94gGVqcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbt to like a week ago when i said only psychopaths go to the gym this early bc im at the gym right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[To more days just like this one 💕 @laureltheory @ The Blue Lot https://t.co/lgIswZkJA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well since it's late anyway... first time I tried drawing Aggretsgo... Gonna be a late valentines day cause of that… https://t.co/2gt7Ygk9kD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This 1 article outlines what we do: robos mostly help people invest money... #wealth managers’ core value added fun… https://t.co/veyQY1mnOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My only Valentine's today be my customers, who keep on surprising me with how nice they're being.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my newest print landing in my shop today, “Summer Dreams Floral” 😍✨💕 I went with some neon highlighter co… https://t.co/4TbluzI5zO]]></document><document><![CDATA[7) Now, I always give 100% of me to whatever I do - I don't know how to do moderation. This is both one of my great… https://t.co/IK1rsJmjkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DomoWilson1 @_DomoWilson1 in my first semester of college, studying criminal justice ! Anything would help me and… https://t.co/eBFp9Yrpdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iluvjunior88 @DaleJr @WhiskyRiverCLT I hate to say it but our Whisky River here in Myrtle Beach has been less than… https://t.co/cplbUDW2Bp]]></document><document><![CDATA[We hand selected each piece of wood that went into the basement from @my_wood_loft. It all came together beyond my… https://t.co/vE3F1IrHsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕️☕️☕️ Someone asked me why I‘ve never made coffee. 1) I don’t drink it and 2) Even as a young woman (20) in Journa… https://t.co/qeyiA75QbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[A BIG HAPPY 21st BIRTHDAY  TO THIS HANDSOME GUY!❤️ We are so proud of you and love you so much! Enjoy your big day!… https://t.co/QcvPV8XJhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are recording this or around this and not standing up for her before he got in her face and called her a bit… https://t.co/iPClLOzF8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[RDU has a specially-called meeting to talk about a possible lease with Wake Stone Corporation - and a lot of people… https://t.co/7f60V8g3mk]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you constantly talk negatively about single women on social media, don’t expect to be getting no good pussy out… https://t.co/FPo8LpYEZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do the black Lightning uniforms remind anyone else of CGI actors filming befire they add in the CGI characters over their movements?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoyed being on the interview panel tonight for @NDDECA state officer positions. These 14 young women and men ar… https://t.co/TnZNnLpQfy]]></document></documents></author>