<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@frothymouth there just needs to an incentive for teams to actually try. Watering down the playoffs even more isn't it, either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand your feelings. Went thru it last year. No over it yet. It was fun watching Zyler play all these years.… https://t.co/pKgB8XDHqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[ I bought a bottle of jack and Mexican coke, the bottle not the power kind  I'm fucking dead]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your going to back any film why not back a film that is empowering. A film that draws light on an issue that eve… https://t.co/vYti5HUUhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[On wwe espanol Twitter page  @reymysterio pick the #BossNHugConnection @SashaBanksWWE @itsBayleyWWE to win the wome… https://t.co/cTgjMdbdOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCCPSS_SS Yes I went to the Slavery in GWs World last year and it was amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickFaldo006 your welcome to comeover, soup is heating up on the burner. https://t.co/4dclKw6vc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cleflore23 @Alyssa_Milano Yo give life sentences for criminals who use guns in commission of crimes. Guarantee you… https://t.co/EN8tu9LEdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend @ScottJenningsKY absolutely nails it in this op-ed.   So for all you hand-wringers out there, read it and… https://t.co/9gN8aUYKW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's 3:16 in the morning, do you known where your Steve Austin is?! https://t.co/6B8XWG8cf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bintrim1 @jmarshfof I recall lot of articles on how Sid and geno felt great with reaves in the lineup. Also. If he… https://t.co/tsnurtkdwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael: "Erin, do we have the journal?" Erin: "Your 'Feelings' journal? You told me to put it in the time capsule."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I’m being ignored. Who’s tryna kiss me? *Serious inquires only* *homies only*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi Mike.  I have a great deal of difficulty with this line of argument. It isn't really possot to tackle, e.g., dis… https://t.co/OjuXIhCzk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Levy14Gillespie @ThadLibs Go on google n look up Charlie clips vs nu Jerzey twork ddotomen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_steller @jonbream @FirstAvenue Ah man, this is a sad story. Gang of Four would’ve been incredible I bet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaddukes calm down guys. Not really weird at all. Homeless guy sounds like to me just looking for something to tide him over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I realize that snow does not equal polar vortex but somewhat ironic that this event is postponed due to winter weat… https://t.co/o3jNe8xSkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iSkizm @XxXnUnEzXxX @AdamMKaufman And nobody to block or play defense and special teams. What a team]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing Work Different  I always thought it built on   Think Different  but   hey  thats me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TyAnderson I was surprised they traded Donato, but since he had 2G against Carolina he had 1G-1A in the 10 games… https://t.co/QWJVWemcTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reached a milestone in bridge-hunting this week.  Mailed the first Bridge coffee-table book outside the USA.  Signe… https://t.co/mhZT104ZOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@O__reckless__O @luciaaownzsonn Like a lightly salted yogurt drink lmaoo.   I grew to like it when I visited Turkey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanBakopoulos Yikes not a very sympathetic response but I loved Summerlong so I expect that relationship provided… https://t.co/uAwWyyuad6]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great article on focusing on your own goals and bring your best instead of focusing on stats @108_Performance https://t.co/b5I0WSQLap]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @nburrows7 to post 7 covers of books I love--no explanations--no review--just the co… https://t.co/OIwQqt5KAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still my favorite tattoo❤️ Thank you @jarpad for being one of my biggest inspirations, I love you❤️ https://t.co/r5mWl3Elkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those who wanted the high def video with audio of the steveaoki caking at the sacramentokings game..... Here it… https://t.co/JnPnYu4LCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelpeep @Patriot_Voices @RickSantorum I know I’m in PA too , he’s a disgrace]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your using the hand dryer in the wash room and its really powerful]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing I’ve never tried at @innoutburger is Animal Style fries. Am I missing out on the greatest thing or nah? https://t.co/JYSrJdaAU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanMMoore I CAN’T WAIT!  I couldn’t be more excited about the cover!]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Houston: haze, 74°F 88% humidity, wind 8mph, pressure 1012mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[An absolutely wonderful evening. Feeling so grateFULL! Thankyou so much Paul Roffman for this wonderful shot .. @ N… https://t.co/6O6oRgkP0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielsOfficer You’re welcome man. Love the message you’re bringing to people! Stay safe out there. P.S. I’m waiti… https://t.co/qWfVafibYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ EL MOMENTO, LLEGÓ PAPÁ EL PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/Amr3mOUMdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still boggles my mind how Bobby Hart gets a contract like this. Good athlete, yes! Good offensive tackle, no no no!… https://t.co/cVQnZcXMix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch yourself Issei. #HighSchoolDXD #anime #kiba #Cosplay #NewProfilePic https://t.co/2nzyltFyzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all mad at AB. Dude bet on himself and it worked out can’t hate on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another masterpiece from my growing criterioncollection @janusfilms #sullivanstravels #prestonsturges #joelmccrea… https://t.co/dlOGhTcQCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinSavidge can you believe 5 years later still mystery surrounding MH370.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mad_sters @JudyTungMD @WeillCornell @WCMGIM Yes, and when I decompress to #twitternist and #medtwitter most nights… https://t.co/0M5N3sQRG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Land O’Lakes prevails on rival’s home court. https://t.co/mtux4XUZUw @TBHomeTeam @LOLHSathletics @LOLHSPrincipal @SLHSseahawks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisBlender @CBCPolitics Yes, but it does focus attention appropriately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing left of that Ethiopian jet that crashed. What a violent and fatal impact.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe My Craigslist room rental ends this Friday and my first payday after release from hospital is 14th.… https://t.co/TyY4qhS3Jj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday! Choppy loves ya!  Keep being awesome... the world needs all it can get! https://t.co/0tJYpFnC0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omgchante Yeah I was almost done with it until the last episode before the mid season break. I’m interested again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you don’t look exactly like your dad and have farmers from a 500 mile radius strike up a Conversation with… https://t.co/dHjnbIAsgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember The Ann! This will be our mantra for the 2020 General Election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tearing Flesh From Bone DIPA, DDH with Mosaic and El Dorado 8.2% @burialbeer Thanks for the assist brewsandbourbons… https://t.co/7w7uikO2vW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is very easy to reach your @fitbit daily step goal when you have John Bonham in you life. I wonder how many step… https://t.co/EN7Ly2Y7Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Classics: McDonald’s Classics are, without a doubt, the best thing to happen to bacon. #TeamClassics FTW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is amusing. Playing With Shadows- make chalk expression, let your shadow show an emotion #mirth #chuckle… https://t.co/Ba0KFfrUA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Select Eagles picture make-up day to be announced soon for those that missed their picture day for the Year Book. https://t.co/2R1QhSYG0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigitalTrends No thanks. I’d rather have protected bike lanes, a cargo bike and baggers at the grocery store.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski @Alina__IV @AnnCoulter I am a liberal and I love sex I only have sex with my wife. It’s been that wa… https://t.co/VspPZl1EJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those involved in #humantrafficking need                 to be treated the same as #sexualpredators under the law.  #passstricterlawsnow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daisy_child https://t.co/l1zBSOgYiW  should have it on for free, Daisy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I love about 🇨🇦: how most people say thank you when they get off the bus. #littlethings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamCraggsCBC In order to get the investment correct is there $50 Million being spent to develop 44 new units?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KY_Clips But when duke loses without Zion “ehh doesn’t really count if you think about it”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSoltisAnderson After you find out where they live , leave a little bit of Wally's deposit on the door handle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smoss How could anyone hate someone with a face like that? I just love watching those lips move. I wouldn't kick h… https://t.co/z7pyzavpPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseRob80461260 or just excused themselves to go to the bathroom and heave. LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[beach cruisin’ #roc style #rochesterny #running #schwinn https://t.co/x6HvuZX2Gw]]></document><document><![CDATA[They don't care that Canada is sinking as a result of their mismanagement!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great story on @CBSThisMorning from Vladimir Duthiers called Monticello Roots - a beautiful story of two Thomas Hef… https://t.co/wneFivwfkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Da bees a whol lotta D licking. . .goin down. . .under the gown!!!  In CathLICK town!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[4am wake up for breakfast then on to the mission field in fla. going to be a long but great day in the Lord.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These steady cam moves through the audience searching for the winner reminds of a certain game show #ComeOnDown… https://t.co/YlGvt7xC76]]></document><document><![CDATA[El papa cuidando a su bebé 🥰  #franck #pepa #pug #puglife #puglove #dog https://t.co/6jJdd2ngPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s stream will be #DarkSouls after work until 7 and then back to it with #AnthemGame until 10! https://t.co/herQSLmdMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I MET HIM OH MY GOD!!!!!! @DeLongMusic is literally so fucking nice. Thank you for an amazing show. Thank you for y… https://t.co/IGpAYBipzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to The Closers leading Cerritos MSS with 14 AALs on Friday. Way to go @shekiamartin @N_Vega_Guadian… https://t.co/c1pGnyttuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was lightning and thunder inside El Baron last night too. Ritiche M. Angeles began his comeback with some new… https://t.co/wzE6eC5ajt]]></document><document><![CDATA[So dead tired, barely got sleep last night since I stayed up late drinking. I need a nap]]></document><document><![CDATA[No internet at my dads. So I’m literally watching all my movies I’ve had. So X-men last stand it is 👌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DICEY63 @xxdr_zombiexx @matthewamiller @foxandfriends ... despite the fact that conservatives fought tooth and nai… https://t.co/kINLC3JRGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I think about how lucky I really am.  I keep getting better and I have a job.  That is enough for now.  I had… https://t.co/gz4gjM5raP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro. Who the fuck thought that #Isles video about JT was a good idea? 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where does one find this menu of victim  excuses for all of life’s bad choices and actions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyRyanOnline @JANELABABY @GCWrestling_ It wouldn't be the first time someone faked their death to move onto anot… https://t.co/NygVLaD8bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#eltonjohnfarewelltour #❤️❤️❤️  #aviatorsunglasses by #stuartfreeman @ Barclays Center https://t.co/GHf8zbnC37]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Kushner is trading US secrets for favors.”  He is a traitor and should be waterboarded by Dick Cheney!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have seen the difference in people when they find work that they truly love. It can be powerful as the light come… https://t.co/V0CfkvRzM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Criminal Justice students @HudsonCCC were great today.  Thank you Professor Walker for this continued partnersh… https://t.co/dN2ks2wj7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NigelConstable_ It should be for almost $1100. Too big for conceal carry too. But yes, nice looking gun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cellmavin @innisandgunn @almostablaze @MIbeertaster @Essau1969 @wrayzors @madsen414 @tilbeerdouspart @cedarflats… https://t.co/mNhBUbvphV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention Doctors:  Outside the context of your discipline, no customer service personnel has ever cared that you a… https://t.co/04k1ZnebVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/ORs0tbqmmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BasvanKaam @WilkyIT @james_kindon @kevhowla @JGSpiers @LittleToyRobots @selgan @CitXen Done and done fellas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Gesaffelstein and The Weeknd ought to do a whole project together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But what happens when we live God’s way? He brings gifts into our lives, much the same way that …… https://t.co/15NMpWwGgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to skip the next two days so I can be off work and not have to deal with anyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexJMaggard @KDM1617 @MikeGarafolo He's missed 14 games in the last two seasons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunningNoleFan @alloutofforks He loves carbs. I can tell. #fatkidsunite]]></document><document><![CDATA[$10 for a #ValentinesDay2019 card? If @Target only knew how hard I had to work to earn ten bucks..... https://t.co/jTnPhLT07h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobyclapdick @TheDomainAustin Picking out panties dont text rn. Make sure they cant track delivery place]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sleepysteph_ @p1tatorres He could have just not wanted the publicity, that is a very low down trash thing to do, but nothing is certain.]]></document></documents></author>