<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Lebanon, MO job and click to apply: Registered Nurse-ICU - https://t.co/F9XNQHIiB4 #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arielangel1026 https://t.co/A3D96IQGtV This is, the Storm, the Qanon book with all the Q drops and still being wri… https://t.co/Oiy3TRCABB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMelMead @JerryFalwellJr @AOC @CPAC Sounds like you are being a bully to me.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to receive my first order of #pillows to sell at my #booksignings This is from one of my #watercolors A… https://t.co/O4pIR71HDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is ludicrous. Picture Me As Your Valentine! { Vintage Valentine Card / Heart / Retro Val… https://t.co/ObzKnaizy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you put your best foot forward there is no obstacle you can’t over come]]></document><document><![CDATA[had sooo much fun last night at the #pbrvelocitytour with @HnyBofOats!! 🍻 ——————— #100daysofhappiness day 50/100 @… https://t.co/5nEixrq8qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve intentionally stayed too long on the train twice in my travels to NYC to pass through the City Hall station. I… https://t.co/YXJTME2N5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ta_bun_yun @Calex61 @thetalent59 Is the hot scale like hotter people? Are we judging how we looked in 3rd grade bc I was pretty cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you been to Waco, Texas?  Pillows pretty in pink!  #designer #artsandcrafts #artsy https://t.co/sx8AbJcGzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol braden and I both hid sappy goodbye letters in each other’s stuff🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackieforIowa Thank you @JackieforIowa for your support of our program! Also, great to connect with you and Logan… https://t.co/jCLbWSsLLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking forward to this event &amp; meeting prospective RPA customers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[By all means, protest and do your thing. BUT if a four year old girl asks you what the pictures are on your pro lif… https://t.co/jnrU8456qH]]></document><document><![CDATA[massive Cinematography and Best Picture snubs right here https://t.co/uonLAfo6CJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett is victim of 'media gangbang,' defense lawyer says GERAGOS...DIDN'T YOU  BELIEVE SCOTT PETERSON  TO… https://t.co/Xbg0Ys3YUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sophyish @AbortionFunds @womensmedfund yes, and???????????  but also sometimes i'm really good at bowling and I al… https://t.co/XE5uu7Jfed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love when I am reaching for something on the ground from my bed, fall to far to a point where I cannot get myself b… https://t.co/QTUIUmzGX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blown away already and we are 3 hours into the IHS.  Go follow my Facebook page Dani Williamson Wellness.   I will… https://t.co/q6RhOAZIzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[But first, tonight, I'm gonna do this with the hubby and my bff. Prepare yourself @TweetsvilleUSA https://t.co/2kuzRyGLay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heymikey80 @jeffrygc @ADmomof3 Tech companies are predominantly leftists.  They apparently dont like anyone rainin… https://t.co/Z8Xc8daEBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessacogs @QuirkOfArtXD @vitzpatel Do y’all have bjs brewhouse up there?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fake news - always twisting what people say. Shame on journalism who twist everything. This is why we can’t believe… https://t.co/qR1TwZ85mj]]></document><document><![CDATA[People have places to go in the morning, and the people driving 10 under the speed limit in the left lane just make… https://t.co/0q6MWwcWpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynda3035 @SoxandD @Axolotl_2019 @BarbaraBpiwetz @BloomNight2 @vroberts9 @Marielincoln10 @GordonHarmony Wednesday… https://t.co/lK9Er59mVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t say enough about @LauraBenanti, Harry Hadden-Paton,  and the rest of the cast of @MyFairLadyBway!  What a phe… https://t.co/ZvOgYyyk3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you’re trying to listen to GOOD country and americana listen until 8pm https://t.co/uH2T04L0jF]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all the guys that voted for dinner with @pamfoundation ~this one’s for you❣️❣️ https://t.co/0P0hoY6TIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ❤️ concept- subjective experience is not objective reality @kimballscott #radicalcandor]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love spending my childs entire nap time on hold with @PineRestGR because they cant get their shit together 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop by the #Chamber535 for refreshments and networking at 5:35 p.m.! @TracieBHGFRG @WCACC @bhgfrgrichmond https://t.co/rf1cCt4iDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Women historically don't plan Genocides.  Men historically DO plan Genocides.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @challlass No one accused Obama of being anti-Semitic for criticizing Israel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeckToMe @Heck2you @mcfunny @urbanx_f @mc40_e @Rosewind2007 @Siubhan_H @EugeneBu @germeagher @Just4TheCause… https://t.co/kdicIGbySP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colombian Emeralds just stunning all sizes and shapes Fancy #GIA #diamond #ring by getacarat. Inbox us for pricing.… https://t.co/iuRx36D6mK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist @coyote_pastel @AOC I think he meant to say Matt G. is an unlawful weasel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of bonding I do with strangers about food is nothing short of ridiculous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good lord... fucking cry babies! Take a Midol you bunch of pussies! Jeez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomAutie @ellievan65 I don’t understand how trying to save the planet is a bad thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2francis2tancis NO, Don't boo the Canadian anthem ... Show respect for the Islanders who are Canadians, for starte… https://t.co/vb7hB4mrCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's @Honeypop_kisses wearing Ana Ljubinkovic hot pink dress with custom prints! PR i.deapr #AnaLjubinkovic… https://t.co/UzDukWDqid]]></document><document><![CDATA[thanks for bringing me and supplying the manishcewitz 🏉 @ Drexel University https://t.co/MvlTjJouK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sweet daughter @jackieeemoore spent many hours at Baum watching and supporting her future husband… https://t.co/HFjaYOsBsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Area One Leadership Conference was so much fun! #eptlod #elptxtlod #elpasotopladies #elpasotopteens #elpasochapter… https://t.co/aDgSS2hPOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok what is going on with this yeezy drop bc sizes keep selling out and then coming back. What is this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched season 1 and 2 of TVD then I jumped on to the finale episode. Ugly cying the entire time. Yes, I suck at watching series.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanFieldABC Personally I would pick you for quarterback, besides the uniform would look YUMMY 😋 😋  😎😍💙👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot tub afternoon @ Saint-Faustin–Lac-Carré, Quebec https://t.co/cudysgTBWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my god this is ridiculous they’re playing music over speakers loudly now. Oh my word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCSSuptRay CONGRATS TO THE ONE AND ONLY... DR. RAY!!!! I am over the moon excited for you! #superstar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make a argument that the Madden Curse isn’t real! I’ll wait! #AntonioBrown]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we are. #thisisus #hereweare #watsonwomen #bitchdontkillmyvibe @ Rockford, Illinois https://t.co/z2D86hFvHe]]></document><document><![CDATA[My annual pilgrimage to the Windy City has begun and then we’re off to the mountains!!!! 🥰❤️ https://t.co/gqVL8Fg6xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s here! The 🔥 new single from @thepaytontaylor #AmericanBorn is a high energy, pop culture name dropper that thi… https://t.co/BwKk3B61Ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TigersnTitans @tflaire34 @Dfresh924 @teaghanf12 @Lotbusyexec @RobertaOtoole Thank you Coach! You are the best and… https://t.co/j9oUzkFeLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justice. Finally nature gets even with hunters. Thank you lions. https://t.co/9EyL9oby4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating UWaterloo’s International Women’s Day Dinner. 350 strong.  In support of gender equality globally. This… https://t.co/lTvRIWe6w8]]></document><document><![CDATA[⬇️👇🏻⬇️ Sohrab Izad Macbook Pro Giveaway (*SCROLL DOWN*) https://t.co/D0qR49CjG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmanderino @Ebonyteach @amystorn “Instead, they are positioning themselves as always already the center of their l… https://t.co/AQSJvjxBQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ That’s cute.  I’d hug you.  What’s muslim got to do with it ? Terrorists are crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BIG 12 CHAMPS!!!! #KState #EMAW @timcottam  @bruce_ney https://t.co/2AAHnkhkRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allisonkundrik Americans are from America, Canadians are from Canada, Mexicans are from Mexico, Europe is a lot of… https://t.co/aWFZdlWAvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Democrats will argue semantics regarding this vote.  But there is no doubt that dems support 3rd t… https://t.co/4pdcOADBqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "shift supervisor - Store# 05244, WESTCHESTER"? What did you like most about that job? #Retail #LosAngeles, CA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janariess Please bring your bookmarks (and books!) to #MHA2019, @janariess !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotAricJohnson @hollysim @KentuckyMBB @PJWashington @DukeMBB Long long time ago!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every BODY dance now! Your visual dance mantra for the day. Sign up for all our weekly world dance classes at… https://t.co/eRNgj1COMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at the texture of this babe 😍 The love of #sourdoughbaking deepens ❤️First time adding stuff to the dough, and… https://t.co/eAaqgKvo78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overheard Big Guy to little guy: “Problem is, you’re bored. Problem is, you hate kids’ games. We’re playing chess from now on.” #blessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@salgovernale you are doing the right thing taking #tumeric #curcumin Don't listen to those guys. Also, DM me so I… https://t.co/kbVDupgP47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pilar_rod @pilar_rod Sabes cuanto cuesta el pasaje y para cuando planea viajar???]]></document><document><![CDATA[The perfect Valentine’s Day Ever enjoying what I love the most seeing my little boy becoming an amazing kid full of… https://t.co/FCYgNhvOdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most you all that dislike or hate President Trump have no valid reason for hating him. And if you have no knowledge… https://t.co/9dnPSfKCDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#winning #roma #yalitzaaparicio #oscars #academyawards #cleo #mexico #oaxaca #vintageislove #vintagelove #trophy… https://t.co/s6e3ir9giA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day with friends at the Beverly Hills Kennel Club. Picked up a select and a 2nd in Jrs.  with a large quality… https://t.co/NpWybW9EPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi if you live in Colorado and want to go to concerts all summer, please hit me up]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a lovely surprise from Ms. Reber’s Gentlemen. ❤️ Thank you! @reber_andrea @HollisAcad https://t.co/shPJGL89nG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solojoe @BillAicher Muy triste. Ay que corregir a los niños desde chiquitos para que aprenden la humildad y la vir… https://t.co/rLmpyFHubD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kbgolfsingapore @LPGA @EuropeanTour Loved its debut in Adelaide @WomensAusOpen !! 👍❤️ Thanks to all the @LPGA players who took part! 🙏🏻👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[So good!!! - Drinking an Orabelle by @greatdividebrew @ Duke's Upper Deck  — https://t.co/YQSpuYbY4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latelateshow @JKCorden Can you please tell @Harry_Styles it's my Birthday and I'm waiting for my Birthday Tweet fr… https://t.co/MaCLU2mIcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magnolias for days at @SFBGS 💜 @ San Francisco Botanical Garden https://t.co/IEeHU2ZoKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Night #wine #wines #winesofinstagram #wineoclock🍷 #wineoclock #wineonwineonwine #wineoftheday #instawine… https://t.co/Pnu6U9dICy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@threefivestep I love them, and I will forever visit them as long as they let me. And I miss you too! ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look ugly asf in the grocery store &amp; mfs still gonna approach me like can I help u SIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its official, I have nothing else worth living for. I'm leaving all social media for a while. Nice knowing everyone. Bye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Et le déneigement des trottoirs dans le Quartier du Musée @ville_gatineau ? Marcher dans la rue, c’est trop dangere… https://t.co/HSUraY66Wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@budweiserusa All of it stretched way past the limit with corn syrup. Your beer tastes like weak sugar water. King… https://t.co/MBe6JOY3bQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Hinesville, GA? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Associate Lo… https://t.co/BPlJUTAEzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Little Round Hop by @BigHillCider at @Stbonifacebrew — https://t.co/A1G3mCTMNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Debra Granik! ‘Leave No Trace,’ ‘A Very English Scandal’ Win USC Scripter Awards https://t.co/q7dwvWOiLB via @variety]]></document><document><![CDATA[So great reconnecting with @cathyharwick ! Great ldr, great heart! #c3conf @ C3 Conference https://t.co/Xff2Mfrctx]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd month ~~ Working on my face🌹I have #botox #lashes #brows #facials #lips ~~ message me your business, body is ne… https://t.co/HV4zAJaOwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This @Starbucks almond milk cappuccino is giving me life right now. #earlymorningflight #longweekendblues #florida #sunshinetosnow]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t realize how many dead dads there are in every form of media you love until you too have a dead dad. This… https://t.co/819MPA6T6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGLotz Thank you, Anne. And thank You, Jesus, for this powerful exposition of Your word.❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dgvreiman @lostandlovinit @aleeyun_nvaazun @dragonwookie420 @KodiaksPal2 @SwettmanF @Merry_Hippie @AynRand_is_Dead… https://t.co/sRVU7QVbMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hugoboom @HoarseWisperer The suspensions had nothing to do with the accounts doing anything to violate TOS. They p… https://t.co/sLpqDQr19a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should Kentucky’s struggling third graders be held back? Some educators urge caution. https://t.co/Ip05v6MDCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between the wind and the chilly temps today I’m wishing that I was all snuggled up and taking it easy... Sadly that… https://t.co/lhGMOd5AFl]]></document></documents></author>