<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I would have pulled out my gun and shot that liberal loser to defend myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fair warning to all. If you spell Sam Gagner as "Gagne" it will be an immediate flogging.]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.K. officials and companies have been bracing for potential trade disruption by stockpiling everything from ice cr… https://t.co/PwWmfDFAsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing with Carmen vandenberg is like being given the best birthday present you ever had over and over. I love you… https://t.co/N964LJr9st]]></document><document><![CDATA[@knappAP @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama Umm. Yes. He’s the commander in chief of our army. So, this is apples and or… https://t.co/QiPoPXs4o0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly and not to mention I’ve had my share of some of the bs that involves the music industry. All these so calle… https://t.co/QN7CGQDszQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When the child was a child, It was the time for these questions: Why am I me, and why not you? Why am I here, and… https://t.co/0di83dcIWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored and blessed to win the 2018 @KemperSports Golf Professional of the Year Award #kemperpride https://t.co/UEDLM6M3qw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank U @RalphCindrich for the LOVE!!.....The Listeners seem to really like the show on @WEEI ...ALWAYS FULL PHONE… https://t.co/kCUeLQZNkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickTallon81 If they miss playoffs, that hurts. They’ll be a middle round team, no playoff experience. Lose los… https://t.co/mBVBQdHqtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rondo cuts her promos like she has only one dime to make a call on a pay phone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Down not pass the smell test. There must be another underlying reason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSketchyPete Ayyayayyayyyyy!!! This is gonna be a fun one my dood 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selbst Iced Tea muss man in den USA in einem Verhältnis 1:1 mit Wasser mischen/verdünnen, damit es nicht mehr so süß schmeckt. 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orlando bound! Anticipating a visit to the Busy Bee!! Make it a great day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrancesWangTV @KatiePhang Thinking of-missing home ☹️@NaplesFloridaa https://t.co/gLQKqUnoZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks my step-brother! But for me everyday is #NationalDrinkWineDay .... Which explains my waist line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished day 63 of my  Bible Reading for this year. Ephesians 1-3; Numbers 6,7; Psalms 54. Jesus is still th… https://t.co/O1i2UbaJtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stastny and Backlund both go for a small cat fight in front of the benches.  4-on-4 hockey.   #VegasBorn  #Flames]]></document><document><![CDATA[#peoriaplanetarium #space #universe #espacio #universo @ Peoria, Illinois https://t.co/wGgLGiLcra]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the fuck was that vote? Like, for real! That made no sense! Ugh! #Survivor38]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nomoremao @JohnFugelsang @LibsInAmerica @AriFleischer Proof of what? Russian contacts? It’s all in the public reco… https://t.co/IejwAVwdTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF? #Indivisible #Democrats #Progressives #Independents #TheResistance #Resist #BlueWave2020 #IndividualNumber1… https://t.co/AwgAIrXogl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmckee14 Apparently cause there’s no one there shopping to make it dirty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetKingz0 Shit dude you Russians are starting to get real sensitive. Lighten up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the fuck did I just read? https://t.co/7030c1oZFY https://t.co/Yb9XsYIEh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarcyCarden @pitchfork Can you confirm.  Does @IMKristenBell smell like hope and skittles?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevin_Tuttle76 Dorit is practically admitted to be working with Merck psych ops.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sultry_Miss Yeah I spent ten years up north I found out I don't like digging my truck out of a snow drift]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Apple got rid of the headphone jack they got rid of me. I listen to headphones about a million times more than… https://t.co/W6MFKhkgLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sad that there’s gonna be a 30 for 30 one day about Bron and Kyrie splitting up just like Shaq and Penny and w… https://t.co/nF7XfMAObS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newlevel__ lmaooo dawg I stopped it before that part and I’m dying 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffRisdon It’s a competitive balance issue. If say the Lions have 5 guys injured and the Patriots have 0, if you… https://t.co/4Txf8IMXYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @RalphNortham Coming to Richmond VA Sunday @ the National!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Techy_Tech @MrNunesteach @CoachellaCUE @CentralCalifCUE @HollyClarkEdu @AdamShortShorts @GridPalGeorge… https://t.co/pbqQicVjHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAO fuck, perfect jokes only come around once in awhile. Heard my 2nd perfect one tonight 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theSamMad Maybe this was what Dorsey meant about ‘not going all in for a super bowl at the moment’.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This interview is well worth listening to. Comments welcome. // Dr McDougall interviews Dr Atkins: High Carb vs Low… https://t.co/VsX6pgkPaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[for those of y’all who said you were my friends then through me under the bus without a shred of evidence or explanation, thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I started watching @salomondrin's new GT 4 video, I wasn't sure about the new presentation style... By the end… https://t.co/nbzxnrnTbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can do 10 pushups in a row. Ladies, please try to control yourselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeslieSimone_ It cracks me up that my parents and never even Had this question on their radar. They were gone befo… https://t.co/i6wOOfuLa7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might regret posting a pic in my swimsuit in February. Might not. #feelinmyself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GIAmoorelove @ScarletBlueTour @ScarletBlue9 @PG_Australia @AvailableAngels @PunterPlanet Goodness I love this photo of you Gia 👏👏👏❤❤❤🌹🌹🌹❤❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all know Duke is about to lose in the first round too, LOL. JSNSKKZOSPSNZNSNSN. Middle Tennnesse College.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@72OH_M @8Rih9MSjCWjlYqn @malakmlaki Oh boy you’re so ugly because ur to much make up. Be natural]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that, all of a sudden I have an obsession with brussel sprouts 😳🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcushjohnson @Pstthomas @SenSanders Fine, that can be your opinion.  But Bernie’s assessment differs from that.… https://t.co/vMfr9UAoyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PnPCBC @VictorFedeli he likens it to goldilocks because it's a fairytale.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Comrade_Star @SilERabbit @IPM_HQ @bourgeoisalien @BethLynch2020 @PrettyBadLefty @LeftwardSwing @TweetingYarnie @philosophrob Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking: 6-month-old baby killed by pit bull in Salisbury today. Police say it happened on Wilson Rd.  Getting details.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The only disgrace is you and those who you associate with including people who have been indicted… https://t.co/6IXveRNbFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sirpeezy Meanwhile in Ohio, ya boy gets a $100+ ticket from a state trooper for not wearing his seatbelt on the highway 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Choose to LIVE... YOUR CHOICE... Another Great workout in the books. I definitely didn't want to, especially after… https://t.co/GVTnnZGUvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's OFFICIAL !!!  I now am a very proud owner of an SSL AWS ANALOG console. I can't wait to start working on her.… https://t.co/lNb0rAV7Yl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTadaaah Well prepared! :) I was able to get the set-times. Would you like them for tonight?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob Persichetti is one of the loveliest fellas we’ve ever worked with! Hooray for him and the Spiderversians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎭LIVE from Napoleon and Magazine: Uptown Parades delayed until 7 p.m. due to rain in NOLA metro. #yourlocalnews https://t.co/3dOLD8R9FB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badlands98 @Big_Man_Mahan @bostonxu18 @KirbyHoops Nobody in that conference would touch Houston. And Marquette has… https://t.co/UlFHNmvRSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why have I been awake since 3 am and can’t go back to sleep? What is up with this torture?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ejwessels Thanks for the note. Newscast items sometimes are unfortunately very brief.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanteAtkins He's idiotic to take this line of attack. Stuck in his own mud bath. Can't help himself. (Who cares ab… https://t.co/QwpNbOzDyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another marvelous day!!!  #carpediem #greatnessawaits #noobstaclesformedagainstusshallpropser #blessed… https://t.co/Uo8wR2113x]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can spot a looser right away when they use the word "tryhard"!!  Thanks for the compliment!!!!  #Generationweak]]></document><document><![CDATA[first spring training game! pirates v. red sox @ JetBlue Park at Fenway South https://t.co/YhKXvaiphO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaneMayerNYer @currycolleen What FOX is motivated by something other than the pursuit of truth I can scarcely believe it]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlashBackFriday “If my son ever ask me can humans fly”, i can show him that his dad use to be able to fly for a sp… https://t.co/CfhEGlPPd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lincoln 48 vs. Canton 30 4Q 1:17 Region II-4A Final girls   #txhshoops  @SportsDayHS @AustinTGCA @Tabchoops… https://t.co/8MdahSq2J1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC So apparently his motive for staging this crime was to boost his career? Get more $$?  How so?  Maybe I follow… https://t.co/1BJZ2a2BAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We are bound to thank God always for you, brethren, as it is meet, because that your faith groweth exceedingly, an… https://t.co/2TusO7UQjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The media should ask Pope Francis about this! Stop harassing @realDonaldTrump . Francis is making a totally ridicul… https://t.co/F5IcU8w6o9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@troyy915 He should be greatful it’s that and not lower. Every good play he had he had penalty or something so fuck em]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 Specialized #stumpjumper Comp 29er size Large $2300 OBO  . . . #mtb #sale #newbike #mountainbike #webuybikes… https://t.co/49AEFcNH67]]></document><document><![CDATA[The borough and UPMC may not get their say tonight. It's only supposed to run til 10 pm tonight and then reconvene… https://t.co/VBlsXQamoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Memes #memesdaily #progressive #dank #dankmemesdaily #dankmeme #crossovermedia #tampa #miami #orlando #capecoral… https://t.co/7ZDB9l8HzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA. Trump mentally unfit?! YOU are the one that's mentally unfit! Please get help. MAGA &amp; KAG!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got back to cabin about 1AM  and we chatted more about Boogie's Cat Cafe. Some went back to hot tub on enclosed… https://t.co/nVx3CjrtzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Drumpf I mean nitwit ! It’s too late you fckd up ! Trump first suggested North Korea wasn’t responsible for Ott… https://t.co/3u1ipiPzwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Icy_Kirby_ @bruisin4cruzin @NintendoAmerica I don’t have a 3DS...hence why I asked for it on Switch...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still the same, but i’m different. I don’t yet recognize myself, but I see ME.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valeriepenny @rogerbray22 @RosieTravers @ninsthewriter @TrishSuter @cathiedunn @AndrewRoberts66 @jessica_rachow… https://t.co/zfALpjzeZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out @WMTribeSwim at @CAASports championships! No dive team? No problem! #GoTribe https://t.co/kJGQneYEho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parents trying to everyone out of the house to go to Disney be like https://t.co/wygMQUfWBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYDNSports Everybody can't play Professional Sports in New York the bar is set high the Tradition and History espe… https://t.co/87qo3WOG9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g_marguglio @databoxHQ @parabolahq It is $150. @parabolahq doubled it up.   No one on your team who has time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not at all against owning a building. The first goal shouldn’t be buy a building and then we’ll grow into it. D… https://t.co/AMoz5dOIeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @spittinchiclets for releasing the episode at an ungodly hour. It kept me from murdering 49 other people on this greyhound bus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see #Fort Larned @AdenaSprings produce a first out winner with #Fort Ramsey in a MSW in race 2… https://t.co/n4I5kUkX4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sunrise Beach walk in #santabarbara. Rain on the way again. https://t.co/7i2V3OilwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking @LilSallyWaIker Trump world runnamok.  And the irony is that the modern @GOP is the party of the Confederacy reborn.  Sickening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This for all you Rustler Basketball Alumni!  @CMRRustlerHoops  https://t.co/HtYkfM77xX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courtesy of the brilliant @politicalkathy @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/WpcMJ3l4ed]]></document><document><![CDATA[There comes a time when Americans need to know their president is a low life mob boss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes @jennydeluxe A House To Paint SHED EVIL THIS ANoTE I vote for the legA-LiZATION oF: This note is LegA-LiZa… https://t.co/RGJ8CipjlS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reporte_Indigo NO ES fascista ES TAPETE Y LAMEHUEV... DE LA LOCA DESQUICIADA RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ckmaughan Sad thing is I was born In that city. (st. Mary’s hospital) Last 20 years or so it has had its fair shar… https://t.co/z8o2tTVioF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter tells me I gotta sleep on the couch because I sleep to wild 🤦🏿‍♂️🤦🏿‍♂️🤦🏿‍♂️🤦🏿‍♂️ Me: Ok that ain’t no p… https://t.co/dCtPThm7Pc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4YrsToday Answering yes to this should report you to Child Protective Services.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yvonne_frodo @mykneeguide @MoPeaches @linda_beesley @Lfeik12 @Jax On (MyKneeGuide), if there is a patient seeking… https://t.co/RBx0D7m4d5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMJKaiJones Hahahaha I can’t fix them but the little one at home knows all the old heads. All the way back to Kare… https://t.co/iiYWy0elTz]]></document></documents></author>