<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Muchas gracias por acompañarme hoy en el stream de Karaoke ♡! Me la pase muy bien :3!!! Que pasen buenas noches :B https://t.co/eJVTm5Kyv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um.... I think Martha Strwart went to jail for that... it’s called insider trading. So getting shares of stock for… https://t.co/tbslSvCpjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Total non-retention has kept my education from being a burden to me.” – Flannery O’Connor #education #learning #quote #creative #ideas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swimmerbr78 @catawu I am VERY much for getting rid of the electoral college.  At 66, I would like my vote for pres… https://t.co/VvjMYZGPXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebelYelliex @ldygamer I have to change my answer to 6 + 7. I was going by color.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for you caring and intelligent post.  Most have been vile and cruel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone traveled to Toronto and have recommendations on hotels/ flights??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord, thank you for allowing me to see another day! #Blessed #HighlyFavored]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honey Lavender Latte is my new favorite. Definitely. @muse @Westwood_Now @CincyFoodBuzz @explorecinci… https://t.co/ReSBk9MIBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And the convictions and guilty pleas all around you are just a coincidence?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 I hope you continue to keep quiet, you're already doing a good job of dropping your value. Steelers aren't go… https://t.co/1k5dcQzlPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfesserBird @TalbertSwan @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Most of them you moron.  The rest were school aged children.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJDinger @tickles_thecat @_TaraLea   Wishing you all the best!  Happy Valentine’s Day❤️  PS  NASCAR just isn’t the same without AJ!☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeding American is a hard job; yet so gratifying! @UMNExt is here to help Minnesota farmers with workshops like th… https://t.co/QiAaZ6nBZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @tedlieu @RepAdamSchiff what are you going to do about this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@getFANDOM @LuvsGoddess10 @RottenTomatoes Bull, this is stuff put out before the movie really came out. Everyone wh… https://t.co/MD7oII6eCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeganMarieMusic  You're a role model that teaches people to stay positive, keep fighting remain brave, stay ambiti… https://t.co/4RjclN9N53]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite people in the whole world.  #family #loveis @ Walnut Creek, California https://t.co/OIeHuFhGYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rammystar @sweetangelface @JeffreyGuterman @CNN more than one according to much testimony in court filings on #Epstein and other suits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clear skies + yummy food aren't too far away! Do you know some amazing food vendors that need to participate this y… https://t.co/Tx8mDducsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g8r_rich @maryrules @emilynussbaum I did the same thing. Super rage cried at the video comp at the end. Except not an empty theater.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time you see me catching feelings for someone punch me in my motherfucking neck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does everyone hate Valentine’s Day so much??? I love seeing everyone else’s cute shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 49.... namaste @ Greensboro, North Carolina https://t.co/VQV7w55AQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Oh oh oh... broken ribs maybe?  I have asthma and I know that breathing feeling... hope they can give y… https://t.co/YjxXDSNcmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peter_M_V @MalcolmNance Or a brain, or a heart. Just his tiny toadstool dick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my stepdad did that shit, and like even though he rescued her from being tied up by some scumbag in an empty lot he… https://t.co/lL1QyIpMDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobcesca_go He did get close and he can not just switch parties whenever he wants]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MomsDemand are in the house! Wash Leg we want you to pass SB 5174 and require training for concealed pistol licen… https://t.co/ndv3eY6dIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dixie State could sure show BYU a few things about how to run a REAL police department. 💪🏻🚨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being single makes me a much happier care free anxiety free person and i dig it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pallisondurfee @OneDayAtATime @Isabella_Gomez Totally agree! Fingers crossed @netflix]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got pulled over and was late to work on Monday and today I literally woke up to get ready for work and FELL BACK… https://t.co/e8UUiIKYEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJasonJohnson @karenhunter Nothing will come of this. His nasty appetite has been exposed however.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenwaldrup It's the fever talking. Lol  Still quite funny.  Rest for now and let it take its course. Feel better soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week’s detox/retox was yummy. 🍷 🥗 jellyn69 #latergram #yoga #afterhours @ Matt the Miller's Tavern https://t.co/2uZWwoDI3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy and I may not see eye to eye politically, but him and his lil babe are the cutest!! So happy for you. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The author I've been working with for over a year announced her cover today and the book is coming out this summer!… https://t.co/VdmnJn7nQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missbradleyyy You had to either get over it or get through it sis 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[A place that I’m actually gonna be able to feel and call Home has arrived 💕🙏🏼God works in mysterious ways]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BREAL412 @PGVarsityXtra Penalty?  You mean foul ? https://t.co/YLYgUFVphd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrookingsExecEd Thank you @BrookingsExecEd! Look forward to participating!]]></document><document><![CDATA[... I must be bored.  I’ll try not to wander too long though heh (@ San Francisco International Airport BART Statio… https://t.co/PzYCQBk6dK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xxo_aylin @boxycharm @Itcosmetics @BECCAcosmetics @MorpheBrushes @deborahlippmann @wander_beauty @modabrush… https://t.co/5IWsDvhwqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I don’t think that real history is taught in public schools anymore. That’s probably why she fails… https://t.co/zhKTk6SuNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepHarley the Saudis should not have anything like this.   Please keep fighting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My skin is not looking its healthiest because I’ve been eating meat. I’m drinking a gallon of water today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo @Airess They were complicit in her crimes because they failed to act. Charge them all with treason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked jody to not wake me up in the morning because i don’t work tomorrow so she can just take my car. Let’s see… https://t.co/XA8PdobBBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Become a DoorDash driver! Earn up to $25/hour and get a $50 bonus after 200 deliveries in 60 days for signing up he… https://t.co/M6j1urpSWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tamara_janowski @GrahamAllen_1 @realDonaldTrump At the top of the ladder...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wanderlust_mel @Diane_Keaton @WolfgangPuck @TheEllenShow Diane Keaton is so funny!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we went against the number one rule we made when we got Sasha and let her sleep in the bed all night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuentinMilesEva The one with the exclamation mark included? I looked into/tested it tonight and it seems to be whe… https://t.co/233IaY7Xso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make #art out of everything. Including yourself. https://t.co/f117yIwZTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your tickets now! Film Festival will be on Saturday, March 9th. @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/DzeuemYYlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎂Happy 15th birthday Caiden🎉🎈 Hope you had a great day..!! #PhillyTuesday #sixers 🏀 caiden_2k22  _kevin_019_  kkcal… https://t.co/fYcFhZ7K40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sydtherockjohn @hanxdar @ErinBrodersen Obviously our definition of punishment isn’t the same so I guess this is wh… https://t.co/wHQzY4iCbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dukeenergy #florida We ❤ STEM! Did u know Countryside HS is one of the ONLY high schools in FL equipped to do mamm… https://t.co/lDfniuZtE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was in a slump for a while but my last game I dropped 16pts and today I had 21. It feels so damn good to be back 😢 https://t.co/ZcYR32CBTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Happiness is a butterfly, which when pursued, is always just beyond your grasp, but which, if you will sit down qu… https://t.co/GFd6nZwBhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GriyoPikliz @ParissAthena The national convention is in Detroit this year. This event is diff.. I was a chapter prezzy too ❤️💛💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little, big. Very big.👩🏼‍🚀 #iHeartHsv #Moon2Mars #NASASocial @NASA_Marshall @NASA_SLS https://t.co/1dPeWH5Vmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been an amazing transformation thanks to @wtes_art Mrs. Cordle and Mrs. Henderly!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlogDoPim Ta chatinho demais! Parece uma criança mimada de 3 anos que não pode ser contrariada, um verdadeiro pentelho! Rsrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyond Thankful, Grateful and Appreciative of my AMAZING TEAM... WE are Truly BLESSED and NOW a team of 13!!!  Gott… https://t.co/EnLwaJNuZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It hurts seeing uneducated people who don’t know anything but how their era was raised.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg @NRATV @stinchfield1776 Once again Mr Gutenberg I am so sorry you are subjected to these horrific… https://t.co/v1U6WbtBJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[We #appreciate your efforts to assure #smartcities are #accessible for all @SmartCityA11y Thanks for the… https://t.co/FBAyZakR5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate my friends. They’re making me to go #ASTROWORLDTour 🌎 @trvisXX Ahhhh! #peerpressure I hope @Drake shows up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slip n Slide @ the patch 3:30.   Bring your own everything. Fenna have some fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@world_adorable @SafiMaasai A puppy( Heinz 57 - mix ) from no kill shelter. What I need!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halftime: Hutch 45 @Dunbar_HS 22   Let’s go Wildcats!!! @FWISDAthletics @dallasathletics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got the fuzzy socks and snacks. Time for Westminster Best in Show--ie the Crazy Dog Lady Superbowl. https://t.co/mvPe0Nig3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AMJoy I live in Texas, I talk to a lot of Fox News watchers. It isn't just Trump who thinks that what Fox conveys… https://t.co/i876EwWfIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Kids are banging on my office door*** I ask a student, “who is that?” Student: “Ms. Monto you’re crazy im here for sellin’ not tellin’”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flipgrid gotta share the L💚VE with @EdTechSpec @kmartintahoe and @TeachingTechNix ... they are ALWAYS there to sup… https://t.co/ErDdNrNtij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Soccer with Dad!! - @tjtar12 @ Morris Knolls High School https://t.co/wJ1r3wRF7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next on reading list is either Flights, by Olga Tokarczuk, or Record of a Spaceborn Few, by Becky Chambers. Flights… https://t.co/xOzkzPndMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sisisisimba23 Ojalá pase algo que te borre de pronto ,una luz cegadora un disparo de nieve........]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo único bueno de haber visto anoche al amor de mi vida es que por lo menos ya supo que existo 😌😌😌 paso a paso que la cagamos jajaja 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biden is the only true democratic candidate at this point. Biden would Knuck if u buck and not utter one apology. And that alone has my vote]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jamás pensé que me pasaría algo así pero un señor me empezó a tocar y bailar en un bar le dije que se quitara y me… https://t.co/jrq4qWxhkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does age &amp; gender have to do with tech or being a COO? Can’t believe people still write these ads. https://t.co/At8EHMGm0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night my friend from Germany talked to me for the first time in 3 years and even tho it was one conversation I… https://t.co/wggrMNAOBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: oh look life’s going great got a new job and I couldn’t be more content  Life: https://t.co/KHjUblFHbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calacuayoMX @DisidentesChile ¿Como que agarro y cambio Cuba por USA y Maduro por Guaidó? Aunque uno es conductor d… https://t.co/EvN1C3E8Rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[We sell the humanities and social sciences short when we devalue the knowledge − the historical perspective, the cr… https://t.co/7W0pEqGyR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re dealing with freezing rain this morning. Be careful as you head out for the morning commute!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisB_KVUE @KVUE @_JuanRodriguez_ Apparently Austin doesn’t love Selena 🌺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go B’s! Find out how #NHLBruins legend Patrice Bergeron had to #LiveMutual to get to where he is today:… https://t.co/kpYwz2XQsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gemma🐶♥️☃️🌎 #planetdoglife #snowmuchfun #snowdog #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy #lovethemback… https://t.co/lQEk4FRwcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Student Teaching, part 1 is complete! Good luck at Grassfield High! https://t.co/p9DoqW3EEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieBella86 @joe_tarski @highbrow_nobrow Another one bites the dust publicly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jill_magnussen @DansoyGomez @JackConnie @ChristiWalling @loveGoldenHeart @Sky13861654 @letgolifeflows… https://t.co/oXTgRYiAzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NurseMan33 @pastorlocke Dumbest comment on Twitter. https://t.co/kye2BhY5lL]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF, who calls at fucking 11:30 today to cancel a two o'clock appointment for this afternoon - Edward Jones you inc… https://t.co/LkOXoLQSPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_justinemariexo @JaclynBrohl_ My mom told me the dermatologist can prescribe a pill and that it worked wonders for… https://t.co/AWAGNi3YpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be better once 11:00 hits. Closer to the end of the day.  Then, everything will be ok again.😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Challenge: Ask your dog to "Sit" after they are already in the "Lay Down" position. #ChallengeAccepted… https://t.co/xqGGDkkxfV]]></document></documents></author>