<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@benscoalum1 @TuneZanotti_206 @SandyDarity @HiveMindMilitia @kzshabazz @BreakingBrown @tonetalks I wouldn't call it a misunderstanding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristineSelwa1 @jordanbpeterson We will pay for the sins of our church leaders. Reparation to those they have hur… https://t.co/W5WdloqLhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else ever randomly think about the office dog they got in the @HFA app? My phone won’t let me open the… https://t.co/WC1M0vLGnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more chance to see this fun, fun show. So very proud of nickpettit_ for giving the theater another chance... he… https://t.co/p5fuXJ5Qwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk where the remote to my emotions are but when I find that hoe I’m putting them on mute 🤐]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Patience is a virtue” I remind myself repeatedly as I stand behind a line of idiots at the Ramskeller]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronnlbaker @NWSLittleRock Yep. Stewart is out surveying the extent of our damage, so I'm sure he'll take care of that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benteka @AskeKammer @natschluter @netekristensen @stinelomborg @sarahsoutlook @nikkiusher @silvertje… https://t.co/Fums5Nf2Jy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Humphre79828990 .A 'good adult relationship' means different things to different people. There are many different… https://t.co/jkjtPRUUQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some hops.  Good and hazy. Hints of citrus.  Maybe just a tad sweet (if not malty).  Enjoyable. - Drinking an A Ter… https://t.co/QDWwDBgSY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best decisions I've ever made before a flight is to eat this amazing braised pork rice bowl @tecompany.… https://t.co/JQJygoAC3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Reasons Why You Need to Know Your Business Expenses!  https://t.co/EDlDZ4kxvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Where did all the premises come from about how terable Mex. Is? I guess they just want the free gov. Checks wh… https://t.co/LJhnJ9nIo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[OHHHHH, This makes me SO MAD!!! It is now out in the open!! They tried a coup!!!  Thank God they failed!!  Does McC… https://t.co/Y0RLMdj4To]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a great detailed breakdown on what’s happening from @shilohwalker. https://t.co/ftoznUxo8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahoraenunrato @canyonoflight @washingtonpost No bashing. It is beyond dehumanizing to let a child suffer this tragedy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all think this is funny? This was me 2 years ago with my appendectomy hahahahaha I finessed candy and flowers and… https://t.co/Qp50ULe965]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyOfCats @MICHELLEFAZIO9 @SassyCassyCat @catsrule0 @vroberts9 @lynda3035 @Tonithecat32 @fluffybasil @BloomNight2… https://t.co/dwWPSiZ5s4]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are some amusing tidbits of wisdom that my family received in our fortune cookies tonight.  All I can say is… https://t.co/MC66TiiHAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did it take for things to backlash on you for you to finally realize you’re a dumbass bitch and need to take accountability?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoHWFanClub And when can I ask , do you find time to be depressed? Prayers ❤️🙏❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome Arizona startup news apparently is breaking faster than I can tweet about it. 😂 @ClearVoice - an… https://t.co/u5euoLv4s8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a amazing show! @panicatthedisco you never disappoint #panicatthedisco #prayforthewicked #brendanurie… https://t.co/HFPSPk3WpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy de lado correcto, de lado mexicano 101% Si o si. Foto: Laura Noguera,  Mexicali BCN… https://t.co/XfGCyZo7K6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discussing the role of #HomeEconomics in the space mission. Artemis Westenberg is working to put humans on mars.… https://t.co/chDF8qVvgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got almost 12hrs of sleep and still feel tired something is not right https://t.co/RIHTImoN1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Claims Drug Use Caused His Woes, Just How Long Has He Been Doing Drugs? https://t.co/leG6rygecc]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom said she’s getting me a never full bag 😫 everytime she bouta get it I do dumb shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3-I accept the challenge of @ALambLHSTheatre to post the cover of books that I love- no explanations- for the n… https://t.co/c95VBDvutH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love winter ❄️ but I can’t wait for summertime ☀️ The day is longer get to take my son out to the park, you just… https://t.co/wfYEAqhySA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ehsleeta I can’t say what I’m working on bc NDA but, I have researched romance and sexuality in games and I agree… https://t.co/wZMu1szhei]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awwww when you blushed! 😍 You are so genuine Tarek! Logan is speaking facts (love her too 😘) you teach me something… https://t.co/ee9cDcWMqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance What more evidence do we need to realize that trump is beholden to the Russian Federation?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to see The All American Rejects for my first concert ever was the best decision of my life cause hearing this… https://t.co/VlaiI63V5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[At @HomeDepot picking up my online order and how fun it was to have a sales associate roll her eyes because I inter… https://t.co/K7v0qqEhXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m good on kids. Y’all be trying to start a family one week then the next week it’s “I need a break” 😂👋🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiyyahlong BASICALLY! Damn can I get 15 for gas for driving to see you everyday 30 mins away 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume No she is hateful and meant what she said . You are just trying to save face for the your party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreabarber Me too! Loved Davy before the Corey’s and then NKOTB and still do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hquirozn Al final vendrá o no, pero el nuevo ridículo de la prensa deportiva española está siendo de proporciones bíblicas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got off you ass Tell you President if he want vote Emergency Incidents.That may be 2bd stupid thing everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things You Didn’t Know About Margaret Hamilton, The Wicked Witch Who Could Never Shed Her Rep -  https://t.co/jfDAhLjtUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unintentionally drank what was probably a gallon of water at work today. No reason. Just for fun. #hydrationnation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaSmith4680 @gbroh10 Forgive my ignorance but what the heck is "fluid gender?" Seriously.   The only genders I k… https://t.co/kAzXEdQn79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahhollowell I have been trying all morning to put into words what you just wrote. If you are going to fat shame… https://t.co/JtWdH3NY2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or is his hair very different...?  #TheBachelor https://t.co/L6APHZVc86]]></document><document><![CDATA[Short term gain= huge. Long term... hmmmmm... but hey! His dancing w the stars appearance. Gold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joseliahughes 😂😂 my mom still won’t let me get in her bed with mi street clothes on dem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Jaci said we were going to bed and got off ft and as soon as we hung up we started texting 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pep_pep926 @kimmi37043 @kelly_clarkson Yep. Just passed 9 months clean on the 15th! 💙😊 #51518]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve come to the conclusion that my dad and stepmom spend their entire days man-spraining things to each other and every one around them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On display at Bay Hill - Arnold Palmer’s first and last Rolex watches...separated by more than 50 years https://t.co/7jCNA0oTIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally got around to watching You and here I am crying bc Joe just wants love and apparently I don’t care that h… https://t.co/itb8rWCmac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes its crazy how many ideas cross my mind on how to increase revenue at my job. Finally one of them is comin… https://t.co/7DdUY7Et9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boo thang 🥰🥰🥰🥰🥰😘😘😘😘😘😍😍😍😍❤️❤️❤️#Mi’ReilleLatriceMcCray @ Newport News, Virginia https://t.co/kNduPdVkKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Evening! Amy Larsen, Principal, ML King ES, PWCS #VAESPChat #VAPrinciPALS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so overwhelmed by Hugo that I never got to the concluding part of my appreciation, but you can read the first… https://t.co/MZdfKEbTpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bec_Shrader @jenniferwilkin Too true! We offer an evening study as well.  Women express mountains of gratitude tha… https://t.co/1gTfKdCTFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizHackett Now THAT gets a damned retreat. As mad as I am with Hillary it's impossible not to like you. Thanks for… https://t.co/z8pofBbpMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s coming along. Not quite finished but this will be perfect for a little boys room!! What do you think? . .… https://t.co/FCeJAvXO3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[currently working on the biggest project i’ve ever attempted and I’ve been thinking about this since junior year. f… https://t.co/gdTe5KR6zM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: The gym I’m going to on my work trip has a less-than-stellar selection of medicine balls.  Coworker: Then why d… https://t.co/J6ttBTDhgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chickgonebad @TheGodThief We’ve used that as the cover photo for tarot nights at AO :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Middle aged white men are true demons walking amongst us, I know because I just had an interaction with one on 95]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TobiasCarroll I'm revisiting one of my favorite books of 2018 and watching/listening to a mix of Spiritualized, Bo… https://t.co/Yq5CnvNI4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so used to shit not working out with ppl anymore that shits just funny . TYN🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MAGA Michael Cohen reveals Trump’s dark secret: He thinks Americans are suckers | Will Bunch… https://t.co/YX1g8AFH0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wholesale Luxury Beach Towel Manufacturers in USA 2019 https://t.co/rSX7Z3UAO1 #towelmanufacturers  #wholesale… https://t.co/f4BTEUsTDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPdevo @heathershore @SenToomey How about doing some reading  educate yourself . God people can be so ignorant]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at West Orange - Pleasantdale Section in West Orange, NJ https://t.co/EjVFqS8Ujc]]></document><document><![CDATA[today i found out one of my favorite people is in ICU on life support so instead of dealing with it normally i deci… https://t.co/KCPJisDwx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[With whose help have you uttered words, and whose breath has come out from you? https://t.co/ye1jcDAqJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kels_ohara I hope you sang and danced along with the fake Billy Joel! I am guilty for making a music video or two… https://t.co/NS1ombyG18]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFreeze7 what are my chances of a flight getting out of White Plains airport #HPN #Sunday at 7:47 pm?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread! 👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼Research success doesn’t come easily 🔬 #survivorshipbias]]></document><document><![CDATA[@len7weets Chief keef &amp; famous dex AKA Chief and dexter ❤️ my babies https://t.co/97jzzBYLac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganMiller994 I know!!!!!!! I see these kids everyday but I forget how little they all are. I had a sixth grader… https://t.co/26lTVTK8pw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EpicFilmGuys Step aside #Alita, the new waifu for 2019 is #CaptainMarvel https://t.co/JHs0fJxrQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every month before we upgraded to unlimited 😂 @JulGreisman @dannygreisman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya hay cuatro cepillos en mi baño 🐥🐻🐼🐰. Aunque sigo creyendo que falta uno...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifewithshar How do squats help the quality of dude in your life... asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[the people below that NPR post insisting about the blueness of ATX are totally missing the point. racism happens in… https://t.co/OvFZVbwYx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[listen,,, since I've been reading tarot for my friends at school a lot of people have been asking me to read their… https://t.co/5vl2acA5S0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofiamerajver Totally agree!! We can’t do enough to correct this imbalance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@___str3 Major problem... I was bored today.... so I went to “look” .... yeah well that didn’t end well https://t.co/UWoED0mxhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kaye89309845 @my2gr8girls @Chrisconsrv1776 yes saw Mitch on either fb or fox. He said was dead in water when it hi… https://t.co/wCMXqATQ96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump He trusts Putin. He believes Putin over our own best intelligence in the world. He… https://t.co/XJl9utj93u]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone at the seton hall vs. st. john’s game????? lmk! trying to get on the jumbotron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ross_milu @TgirlPromo1 @IloveShemale44 @TGAdmirer050 @TGirlsAddict Honey I want to 2 week long play-vacation with u 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING COWBOYS NATION @ Valley Ranch, Irving https://t.co/XMv8C36HBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetsFan_4_Life @sjoseph316 @LesWinkeler @RepAdamSchiff This line of thinking gives me hope... Until I remember tha… https://t.co/fBynYUfEST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rejectedjokes @GrayscaleGospel Okay, that made me lose my cookies. Soo funny!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My artwork is NOW available on notecards / mini fine art prints on @etsy My ink drawings are made with 💯micron ink… https://t.co/lsI577w1zH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trevor_Adams I tell you, I think he has dyslexia @realDonaldTrump   https://t.co/nKfSVbOj9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loveromantique4 @DougDavidsonYR @LauraleeB4real It's so good seeing you two together. 🤗❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have I really turned into the crazy cat lady who gets excited to come home to her cats 🐱 🐱]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, accounts like this help lift the spirit so much. Certainly works for me. Bow wow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smile because it happened #disneyafterdark #90snite #90snitedisneylandafterdark @ Disneyland - Theme Park https://t.co/9q0MI7gVyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oigan, estoy súper feliz por haber visto a mi comediante favorito en escenario, neta no dejaba de sonreír y reírme a carcajadas]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wont be tagging my gf on shit on ig because I dont need none of these bitches coming to her as a women cause she… https://t.co/thgqRyhkDU]]></document></documents></author>