<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@maximaxoo @sagansense Speaking of your wonderful wave video, it looks like the 8ft monster that I tried to get too… https://t.co/pAEa9aegVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa!  Wish I could move even a little bit like that. Of course, in my own mind, I’m qualified for a spotlight on S… https://t.co/Xf4J96yCx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tooooo earlyyyy lol🤑 🔹 Snapchat📲 "kingfrost30" 🔹 #ChillyThoughts 🤔❄️💭 #chilly #ChillyVybz ❄️🌀 #king 👑 #frost… https://t.co/RwoUQIa4ZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitchyTeam Booker only sees color in everything he does and everything he says.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@somadina_arthur Again my brother, just like I told you about his PU, Akpabio can never lose his senatorial seat in ikot ekpene]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XianJaneway Oh me too!! I’m not sure I’ve ever even know anyone else who knew about them. This is amazing!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A DUSTY STROLLER IS BLOCKING TRAFFIC BESIDE A FAMILY FRIENDLY RESTAURANT. OMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piotr_maty @MichaStepski @KsKneblewski @AzRoztocza Sytuacja na Wolyniu i w Malopolsce wschodniej jest nieporownywa… https://t.co/C4KCaaYhjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichiganDOT @COMTOMichigan @garlin The "future" of transportation? Now that I will retire soon, you FINALLY will f… https://t.co/64ZPCTAH9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lovethisnation_ @BillKristol @funkyburck I’m not a huge fan of O, though I would say he has more integrity in his… https://t.co/NSReY4AP55]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course my flight is delayed @pitairport #snowmageddon haha. So #shoeshine @ Pittsburgh International Airport https://t.co/0oyrt69KBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This team! The entire bench just mobbed Alexander after that dunk #Vols https://t.co/axhbxAjK65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@digby56 A lot of people don't know that Donnie Dotard hasn't had a unique or cogent thought in his head for years… https://t.co/gSEab4H7Gh]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC is a 3 month freshman not a Dem leader, front runner or even a viable policy maker. Need to really stop giving… https://t.co/3NE5RnAOol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poile on FS-TN re: Simmonds trade - email was time-stamped 1:58, two minutes before the deadline]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love deserts and i loving snow. why not loving both? My version of Horseshoe Bend in a winter sunrise.  Amo los d… https://t.co/CQWyg2yEoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trenzifromcali But he did and here we are I don’t find it sad or funny I just find it sick.. he hurt not one but t… https://t.co/0nE4gltnZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMasterPotato @ginkers Good to know I was going by transcript elsewhere, thanks so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent this morning documenting our relationship for the immigration process! Thank goodness we have lots of photos!… https://t.co/sewxO4k2D8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaSandunga7 @AOC @hugonopo Lo que pasa en USA es q las ganancias de los aumentos en productividad no van a los tra… https://t.co/Os9SnwsFnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday To the best person I know @cadej4686 . @cadej4686 @Badassgreaser @sodabitx @GreenLuffy26 https://t.co/U98TwSFS0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @realDonaldTrump Democrats “have their panties in a bunch”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 month from today until the @Indians open the regular season in Minnesota. And 32 days until I’m back in The Land… https://t.co/IjKmjO1MMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenDRakestraw @KamalaHarris My tweet was to CLEARLY point out the insanity of Kamala's policies.  The… https://t.co/tOeCoz31Jm]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then the #sun came out. #lovethesun and #lovetheSon and #lovemysons https://t.co/RdnmjU2gfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way you think and feel about yourself, including your beliefs and expectations about what is possible for you,… https://t.co/2SOrR3QU2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo can we get Hold On to 2.5k streams?? It's so close! 🤔 @astimefades https://t.co/L7Yuy7ZRin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buffer I need to talk to someone. Every other post is a failure. Either fix or refund money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is the same with my word. I send it out, and it always produces fruit. It will accomplish all I want it to. And… https://t.co/cmTqbHyYZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my hockey teams knows how to come back and finish in regulation!!! #TMLtalk #GLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EduardoJFloresF @PanAmPost_es @danielgalindez @ReporteYa @ChacaoToday @GiuseppeNoc La segunda imagen representa al… https://t.co/cbYzz9Y7UR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shuffcard @Sports1430AM @IndianaMBB @bigten Yes, barring catastrophe. So you're convinced Arch can't coach even th… https://t.co/6h2NuSoDLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul @SebGorka A line has been drawn in the sand: any attempt to take our buns and condiments will be met with h… https://t.co/ADZbRiJoQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Members of Congress “are not only Legislators but they possess inquisitorial powers. They must meet frequently to i… https://t.co/Kg3EQzi2LU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely weather for some #GPACTF Championships at @cunebulldogs fieldhouse!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesPFlannery @GeorgeStrait This is the correct way to listen to albums]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maritta_oh Oh!!!*** that is excellent, a Holy Ghost of God dropped is anointing on that⏫⏫🎶📖⏫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up, up and away! Said goodbye to my tree-hugging hummer yesterday.  ~sniff~ @ Welland, Ontario https://t.co/Nu3z2n0MQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might be bad at ping pong, but the #silverteam is good at cheering on our Knights! ⚔️ #swordsup]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re looking for the best Bloody Mary in Arizona head on out to Encanterra trilogybysheahomes   #Winning… https://t.co/npXkCQEOdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los rotulistas de MM Televisión son la neta! 😂😂 https://t.co/6bAwoTdxN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that #SxSW is a place that facilitates connection between people - and not just famous people. I’ve already… https://t.co/IIe6biil8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lenticular cloud time lapse west of Charlottesville, VA this morning! Forming off the Blue Ridge Mountains #vawx… https://t.co/F00g8zCks1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frankie_Jaay97 @GamerDyson @SaulG321 @David_Anzalduaa @trillLeo1 @AustinMG20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GAMECOCKFAN83 @donchambers821 @franklinnb @heathradio Washington seemed to travel well for the playoff game, but w… https://t.co/2a7bWNxVDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Picklesnova @RabbiShmuley @realDonaldTrump @SpeakerPelosi @POTUS Heh--now I know you're lying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Except for when Nate Parker needed some help w birth of a nation there was little to no support but aye Tyler for t… https://t.co/2HPHjW8bjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown to the @buffalobills Is this really happening?  WOW!  Would be shocked and excited at same time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating fabulous teachers @JosephCaseHS this month: grateful to adults who forge positive relationships with st… https://t.co/UPk2QM1fnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The humanitarian aid that Chile, the United States, Colombia and Brazil delivered to Venezuela is a blow to the Lat… https://t.co/VP9nZ0Sexe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogue_exposure StarWalker by Buffy Sainte-Marie: https://t.co/e3A6s85Z6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DezBryant When will make your @dallascowboys return announcement ? https://t.co/eWuhmOew5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ES_F lots of panic out there, but this is a better scenario IMO Immediately breaking above the Fall/2018 resistanc… https://t.co/SmKGUvdBOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeractoVita I think 🤔 that you are very nice 😀 and funny in your own way.. 🙄😳😁😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[more like "Packs of humans stealing mountain lion territory force lions into more urban areas then demonise them fo… https://t.co/I32821BR7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emma is texting pictures of Bentley to 10 lucky people this morning. Actually it’s the same picture of Benny, just… https://t.co/kZQFrNlQ7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @MikeTaylorShow @hutcheyesun Toronto closed the game with their closer and we had the guy who turned the ball ove… https://t.co/FXT7jvbwJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARtrackside @MattHagan_FC @KyleBusch @MW55 @CoreyLaJoie @LeahPritchettTF @HailieDeegan @Brendan62 @BradGillie… https://t.co/3VvA2FjETy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WORK_LLC Congratulations!! Looking forward to joining this group of “bookers” soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boozy AF - Drinking a Gravedigger Billy by @revbrewchicago @ Thompson Compound  — https://t.co/w36L1LUnLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @VP White collar criminals abound in GOP but point fingers at Dems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JewishWorker @LeftistWriter I don’t care about anything else. She’s a legislator and she ought to be judged exclus… https://t.co/6g3XtkbOYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my #writing porch and this beautiful #Bobcat walked by. https://t.co/FiHohDUoSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge crowd out this morning to canvass for Zandra Rice Hawkins in City Council Ward 10! #nhpolitics https://t.co/0DjX0Xy9dS]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your phone says "no internet connection" but you have wifi turned on https://t.co/QR3HuqIBCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who had United, Porto and Ajax in the accumulator.  No, you didn’t. You’re lying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This must have been somehow ironic, right? A sitting US Senator can not possibly be approvingly quoting a fascist,… https://t.co/llhUZ3NjDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Embargo #HipHopRepublicans #WASHINGTONDCTHEBESTREALITYSHOWONTV #THEROADTOTHEWHITEHOUSE #MaPoli #MASEN #nhpolitics… https://t.co/0WMEVFMHjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HisChildAlso @elguapo64 @gatewaypundit @BernieSanders @RepAOC Talcom is not black. He jus wanna be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday February 21 - Daily Yahoo!:     Andrew McCabe unleashes revenge on Donald Trump;       Alexandria Ocasio-C… https://t.co/Eqe59mCyie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Brutal13 yeah I have no idea what’s wrong either. just started being this way yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach Jerry Scheve to me, “You’re a fountain of worthless information.” 😂😂😂 #d3hoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made a playing card sized watercolor painting for my beloved wife this morning.  A nice freehand mountain scene.  T… https://t.co/AV4LR0hzYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BDawsonWrites I don’t give a fuck what anyone says, threatening to beat up a woman over words she might have said, is never acceptable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Medford You have a great family.. 💯💯  #Volnation is rooting for you bro. #VFL 🍊🏈  You have never let anything sto… https://t.co/qxJhajd2RR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelTrebony @CaraTHD1324 @HomeDepot How Do With Nothing But Respect For All ... https://t.co/3WpfShNP5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t want to stop ✋ the illegal entry of drugs that killing thousands of Americans in this country. Very si… https://t.co/wsxasr0Asp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthanFinlay13 @AllinaHealth @Migue10Ibarra @cgasper77 @_Nash10 Your Crew fans/friends will be happy to see you on… https://t.co/6IfuHSTHiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kadi Cole kicks off day 2 at #exponential2019 pre-conference session “How to maximize the female leadership in your… https://t.co/3cKzYFsc8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAlexHayden Ah, night races.  Back in the day, we’d nearly be in time checks about now.  Enjoy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShazamMovie @Capt_Marvel75 Lifelong fan of the character: after hearing Zachary Levi denounce fans who still refer… https://t.co/hQ9tw5tYAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yangthoughts Japan is under serious threat from aging demographics and climate change. They will desperately need… https://t.co/7L5B9MabOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettyBowers WHAT A BUNCH OF STUPID RED NECKS - yea just what i want a trump autographed bible-- obviously they hav… https://t.co/tdnOzn8kF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CDiriangen En la Biblia se puede leer: " El que a hierro mata, a hierro muere ". El Paramilitar: Fernando Escoto,… https://t.co/LPuZ1sPZyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmCandaceDavis CBD Oil #CBD #cantsleep #healthylifestyle #CBDlife #homebiz #Entrepreneur #earnfromhome #CBDOIL… https://t.co/Rqw6uTm1h6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Among the fun activities at the @JacksonCountyMO Courthouse in Independence is the news screen, providing some quir… https://t.co/Kjemd12Uz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got asked to be in a youtube video yesterday and I cant wait to see it lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at John F. Kennedy International Airport - @jfkairport in Queens, NY https://t.co/qi75E3Rf07]]></document><document><![CDATA[A three-peat with a twist: Sartell rallies for this one https://t.co/2hJpA4jS9Q via @sctimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jaajjajaja aqui mi super oso  vean el video completo aqui   https://t.co/IO3522co5u https://t.co/TZR6iwpQKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I already practiced my Norwegian today, Siri. I learned this useful phrase. Don’t you remember? https://t.co/5poUdwTO1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m super late here, but a shout out to the amazing women that I know.  @candacerthomas @iAreNotAmused… https://t.co/lybnIz81Sw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell What a douche. So you deny the People who work there even though they may not be Trump supporters. Jus… https://t.co/FqP6Bf0t5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allstar4199 I agree I’m just saying Markell Johnson is slept on a lot too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesWStork @JohnCzer1 Why vote when there are so many Russian trolls voting, too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are in #StormAlert this morning on @ksdknews #TISL. @WthrmnSlaughter has what you need to know]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great work @protectourwinters @ClifBar @burtonsnowboard @JonesSnowboards @patagonia. Keep the pressure on! The Powe… https://t.co/UJYebwiWrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthew_loftus Just when I thought I’d seen everything worthwhile on YT! There IS something new under the sun!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the finale to #TrueDetective again only highlights how brilliant the irony is, it's actually a great subdued ending 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @RyanJamesMorrel @Melissamoo @realDonaldTrump @GOP @RandPaul Source?]]></document></documents></author>