<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KFCBarstool  HBD... So the reason McDonalds is testing product in Canada before the US? Didn't Canada just legaliz… https://t.co/cB6gF2mwKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you lied about having experience and your boss walks by https://t.co/K7EMaSu92t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kawhi Leonard not interested in joining LeBron James, Lakers, report says - https://t.co/iFBd37tqL3 Leonard will be… https://t.co/HVIkQtoRdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senate Democrats Have The Votes To Pass Resolution Blocking Trump’s ‘National Emergency’ https://t.co/1qEm8wsRXP via @politicususa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatiKnitt Yep. But kidz these days don’t want simple gameplay anymore. They gotta be hip, kwel, and radical!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @EMluvsPibbles @AnimalFarmFndtn @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/zwh1UZvUhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamianneTweets There's a boutique maker in Oakland, CA, but I cannot think of the business name right now and I'm… https://t.co/Op5Z6aNBUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to hang with bradgarrett at @vhcomedyclub tonight 🤟 Super nice guy and he sold out back to back to back shows 🤣… https://t.co/2HTN0rsnvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdbilotta Really? Just sparking a conversation trips a womans rape alarm?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not sure there would be enough ashes left to draw it any larger. #ashtag #lent @ St. Patrick's Cathedral https://t.co/It5SoTDGJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sound of a calculator falling off of a desk and exploding is one of the most recognizable sounds in the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_haleystehle @jmart2015 Concerts at Mardi Gras is two people screaming at each other two feet away just to have a conversation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory A man who is constantly calling for investigations into everyone else dislikes any scrutiny of his criminal behavior. @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetsByReilly International players help the league in the long run expanding fans world wide. So many fans after… https://t.co/KUOQdKHbJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald @briebriejoy @theintercept Love you Glenn.  Can't wait for Intercepted tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axios one of the reasons why I quit social media crap long ago and I deleted facebook, instagrm, snapchat, instacr… https://t.co/CG2Xwybnxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beardedrogue @dngrstrngr_art wearing a shirt from them today too! https://t.co/ciJ5PIOdw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter @sewell_holly @ricardo_de_anda I wish more citizens took the time to read the entire article and shed their callous ignorance]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are on right now on @wpri12 with the updated forecast. Some areas in R.I. have close to a foot of snow as of 4:4… https://t.co/cTxrKejhhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marin Diving Center Fun Dive @ Fort Ross, California https://t.co/Ogx5fzb5Xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebelTanea Damn liking the paint job too. That brushed steel look with the red is 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[U ladies need to rekindle &amp; support each other again; Sister-n-Laws should be forever good .]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PickensHighSchool #PickensDragons #ThreeDayWeekend https://t.co/0uLaYugcfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a boost to St. Louis, Air Force wants eight upgraded Boeing F-15s along with F-35s https://t.co/h4bqlJ02I1 via @PostDispatchbiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday Night, March 21, 2019. 6-7 PM.  Tewksbury Public Library.  Let's talk about the Patriots.  Hope you can be… https://t.co/k63xZVBS7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[The construction workers at Walmart are BLARING Shakin’ Hands by Nickelback 😂 I am diggin’ it 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylaelena - haven't needed headphones and haven't talked to anyone - Fort Tarsis slowly comes alive and there are… https://t.co/LeKWs5RRaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Kap comes to the Panthers, I WILL GO TO EVERY HOME GAME TO SHOW SUPPORT✊🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geoffreywoo Some kids only get to eat at school and they were intermittent fasting since the previous day's lunch.… https://t.co/ZUoo5AEVRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConsWahoo Who just lost to LSU at home who just lost to Florida at home. Makes sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieCarrel @jordanbpeterson The point is not that they are jumbled but that they are, what she calls them, the… https://t.co/JLzBXCV5o0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fieldof68Freak I'm sure they will beat Michigan State and lose the other two and early exit in Chicago to finish u… https://t.co/A2SI40N3Zm]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK @NBAonTNT is one of my favorite shows and Charles Barkley is one of the funniest guys ever! #JussieSmollettHoax]]></document><document><![CDATA[The biggest lesson in life is to be patient. 💯. Don’t rush anything. It’ll come]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftistOfColor @tomwatson @witliftin @TPVTrevor @jkfecke @TheTomBurkeShow @Patrickesque @IJefTomI @HoarseWisperer… https://t.co/q69C2CAEhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIRLS BASKETBALL: End of the third quarter - Rock Bridge 64, Helias 22. Bring on the running clock. Puett with 26 points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baseballcrank It’s chicken little marketing.  The bet is that they will see it as soon enough that desperate, urge… https://t.co/pi4UKMvIHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rony_garccia Hace días pensé en hacer eso y me di cuenta que ni se podía y me enoje hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNOmaha hi hello @UNOmaha can we also take a minute to consider the safety of our shuttle drivers. if students can… https://t.co/kdp6SrG2YV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I provide #small #business #loans and #equity #funding up to $250,000 to the #cannabis and #marijuana industry. Cal… https://t.co/l8cSqAB9oV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EastTNVol @BTT_Podcast @LesThatcher @TheJimCornette I have the DVD. Great show]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cat_Von_Z @Jason89198088 @bioware Agreed. The internet is a crutch for unfinished games to do DLCs to fix bugs tha… https://t.co/48heAvxI1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gracietpt Boy, Mr. Higgins you came across like Mrs.Wiggins, dumb, dumb, dumb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJeffMatson If phone is on vibrate he perks up. Then waits for actual noise before going ape shit.   The thing i… https://t.co/98JnNhO1A9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aston Martin Vanquish Vision Concept is a midengined stunner - Roadshow https://t.co/Iqhtc3e6mp @cnet-roadshow https://t.co/tUKu5Fe0MI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KBarlor @usatodaynba @NBCSWarriors I really thought klay was the happy go lucky guy? Been hangin with KD too much 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@underdog1965 @FoderaroJeanne @TanyaDawnH @realDonaldTrump Firearms legislation never curbs criminality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TT_4You I would buy two, an exact match to the Big Gold belt and an exact match to the Hulk Hogan winged eagle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫My Heart Would Know by Hank Williams, The Drifting Cowboys, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/vLp9F7EsSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[42. Elastic Band Rows. As performed by my workout partner Rosie, and supervised by my strength coach Luna.… https://t.co/l7EWbxVFed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joe_Herrera69 @blainefrey Time to organize and get this YouTube channel going]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KennyNos67 (I couldn’t retweet this or I would) This is what our men in blue have to deal with (did you see the ot… https://t.co/DsxYtJTcyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cornfrmr @MaxROIFarmer @CN24421 @Chris_Schick @surfingkelpie @cornleagirl @FMHins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @SenFeinstein Spread this across all media outlets!  @LearJetter can you help spread this to your network?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's agenda: a photoshoot for an upcoming project.   Tonight, Jessye Norman Glenn Gould prize gala.  Its gonna be a good day 😍🤩✌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did @Studio_Theatre twice in a week: “Admissions” is a deep, thick, funny examination of white progressives and pri… https://t.co/GkyOAaORr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BRKeogh @Tres_Villain I tell my students the exact opposite. If they’re wasting time writing a sign off, what else… https://t.co/uez3FJWKaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[courtney just shouted “oh my god the snake guy from the taylor swift concert!!!!” and ricky joined in with a “YAAAS… https://t.co/2QeRbQLPsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is making out with Holy Spirit two-timing Jesus? I submit that to imagine to make out with Jesus workout Holy Spiri… https://t.co/xA4PJU6BC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@big12wrestling the 2nd best conference in the country! Qualifying 53 automatic bids! https://t.co/MBLjTQx4VM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@concertman The B&amp;W sound better, but not enough to justify the cost and maddening inconvenience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@73_Carondelet You're fine if you couch it as original research/analysis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s @GeorgetownHoops win over @MarquetteMBB exemplified just how special the #Mackinjo two-headed monster is! #HoyaSaxa!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring conference will be here in just 93 short day on beautiful Cape Cod  Link below offer:  Conference registrati… https://t.co/0Q1HcntiSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[84% said yes. So 2 things. First give me feedback for time ideas to do this. Next wchich personal challenge should… https://t.co/AGTGGGg2GF]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RazorbackWBB has stormed back vs. Texas A&amp;M in the SEC semifinals and has a four-point lead with less than a minute to play. ESPN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was staining someone elses project (bcs i never finished mine bcs i spent all my time in the marketing class next… https://t.co/yBCWcQCqC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[El presidente que necesita la Republica Dominicana, @ReinaldoPared🔥 #LosAlcarrizosConReinaldo https://t.co/EQJalv9BaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OluseyiSonaiya That MAY absolutely be the case. But to my original comment, it’s never black and white. There’s al… https://t.co/3VD3nILifv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews " Watch Out For The Nutter's "......!!! https://t.co/qHPPimRecp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kathlee01561884 @MahgdalenRose I don't think so. You hate fake news. Its in ya schools, not on the news. Day1USA H… https://t.co/sHbxNnVhEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#todaslasmujeressiempre  😁😁😁 @ Newport Beach, California https://t.co/3kAznvaUIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjlamberton1 @b27moore @DennisSantanaRD I still believe Brock Stewart could be solid if they’d leave him as a starter]]></document><document><![CDATA[El mejor consejo que un Médico les puede dar es: compren un seguro de gastos médicos mayores.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews obama was born in kenya but his father was an american citizen. obama released a photoshop doc as his birt… https://t.co/kJdnsepO4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spring_io @starbuxman Just get it over with and start planning joshconf!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelma_salinas Oye amor, fíjate que mis compas andan queriendo hacer una carnita asada, pero ya les dije que no qu… https://t.co/8vhseVIEbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahora que caigan quien tenga que caer x este daño a BSC y pagué x todo lo que perdió el club x este acto de mala fe!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjvenesco Spike Lee my favorite director won an oscar God is so good my Knicks won mj I'm too excited omg retweet this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_AyeoJDure Lmfao Justin.... I hate you. We gotta link when I get back in town]]></document><document><![CDATA[: The adventures of this charming guy and his #Mathias continue | Now his modcoat is keeping him warm in the concre… https://t.co/XgLvkodyoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKatieButtera @KarsynElledge3 @applegirlart @TheKatieButtera Hey...Good Morning and #HappyValentinesDay Very coo… https://t.co/PCIy743Tk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@namujyoon They’ll drop back eventually, but when they initially lose possession they’ll try to close space in the… https://t.co/MjtD8jaFY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rcc441 @PeterTrapino @ScooterMagruder Agreed! My b, thought you were saying get rid of him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cutiemcfly007 I hope it was tender so it won’t stay in your body too long 💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEParkingGuy hey Keith, whats up you big tool, lol jk man. Great to see you putting in that work last night broth… https://t.co/LuntTrTJfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Q:  Knock, knock----Who's There?----lettuce----lettuce who? A: Lettuce in and you'll find out!  #FridayFunny 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on my next book - it can be quite challenging to keep up the intensity needed .... #patriot #writing… https://t.co/LbHpgwUUNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I go to a Black/Latinx medical practice and let me tell you why I love this place. One Latinx patient’s insurance w… https://t.co/fbXzGOyqNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jour 5/7. #7Jours7Couvs #7Jours7Livres. Et sans plus de commentaires j'invite @pbonnefoi31  à nous faire partager s… https://t.co/fsRduidPXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Martech platforms are replacing many agency functions. This trend will only accelerate over time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gavinortlund Thanks for writing this, Gavin. I just brought up at our elder meeting last night how much it hurts w… https://t.co/Uje98hAvDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Travis Weber’s memorial service today in Saginaw, his former bosses, COA Judge Brock Swartzle and MSC Justice Be… https://t.co/2vpfzefo7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tribute to Radio Raheem (Bill Nunn, who worked with Spike on multiple films) though...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Praying for safe surgery and ur speedy recovery!  #Godbless]]></document><document><![CDATA[military recruiters so bold now man straight up coming into my job tryna recruit me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s an absolutely MASSIVE #Goofy topiary behind #SpaceshipEarth, my boy @joeybadabing22 is gonna love it!… https://t.co/taBg1dQOGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oakland Teachers Strike, east Oakland @ Oakland, California https://t.co/paZu72gDqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveAdubato @BradForenza playwright from Jersey City  #TheRehearsal premieres at #EmergingArtists (@EATisTweeting… https://t.co/XAT01YUVTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who think jack white is a musical genius, can go play Mary had a little lamb on the piano for all I care]]></document></documents></author>