<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This thread is really thought-provoking to me (and obviously I can’t wait to read Lyz’s book). My hometown is NYC,… https://t.co/32ZjP8CJu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kissmyconverses @OkoloSC @YahooNews Fair enough... I think that his opinion was largely based on known data regard… https://t.co/flTSvk4IfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMatthewsdavid Oh so beautiful!!! Thank you for giving me a sneak peek. I can hardly wait to see the book!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t worked in over a week, and now that I’m parked outside I really want to call out...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or, maybe Trump's Republicans will all turn against Coulter, which is good, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@james_fromtexas @TheNextWaltz I’ll see you there. Looking forward to hearing your songs live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BIG shout out to @kalos_clothing and @MrStowe !!!! Most amazing dude with an even more amazing brand!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEL_ColonBlanca @RebeccaWuamett I hope you know that each and every single day, I appreciate you! I wasn’t there f… https://t.co/63QsauczYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soccer Bar???? Así se llamaba? 🤔🧐🧐🧐🧐 @mayalmeida11   marijouchi mengodpatricia TAKE ME 🔙🔙🔙🔙 quién se acuerda de los… https://t.co/8Di04LRVQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets More than 12 items in the express lane! #nationalemergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s never too late to get your copy of The Love and Light Tape!! Hard copies are available at any of my live perfo… https://t.co/tBn7e9ZGBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s depressing that no matter the crimes Trump has committed or the damage he’s caused he won’t spend day one in a… https://t.co/UCHSYRHpli]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird conversations you overhear while walking the Lake, "I started drinking during embalming school. All undertake… https://t.co/X9yzl6Fk47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_UnSilent_ @teakinrj Think 🤔 if Obama had “tried” more to get better grades than magna cum laude...oh...and he… https://t.co/5cFxqe7Jvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope.  He thinks whenever he says whatever is truth at that time and dimension in the twilight zone.   The fact tha… https://t.co/GPGLyxwqq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day vibe is strong. May you love endlessly, live fearlessly. 💕 #valentinesday2019 . . . #red #happyface… https://t.co/fGmVH14K4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Buffalo Tooth's Double IPA by @GreatAmerRest at @sweetwater_gar — https://t.co/jGT6sudOvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimmyifuplease Wow because if you read the biography it’slike anfan guy. Maybe he has two accounts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump When are the people that pay for our government going to know the names of the people El Chapo pai… https://t.co/zK4zJyd6oy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PetriOP Page 79 - a hymn praising cannabis flowers by St. Thomas of Villanova: https://t.co/70MDlEbH5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ann Arbor MI Sun Mar 3rd AM Forecast: TODAY Chance Of Snow Hi 29 TONIGHT Chance Of Snow Lo 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylianj thoughts and prayers with you even more on today! I sent flowers since I had to work today]]></document><document><![CDATA[God gave that land to Abraham and his descendants Isaac and Jacob(Israel). Muslims have a habit of claiming propert… https://t.co/C8dS0ni2lj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catblossoms I am mildly regretting the decision but not enough to change my methodology next time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Theorossi @BoRhapMovie @BlacKkKlansman @BlindspottingMv @beautifulboymov @BoRhapMovie is amazing!! I don't get emo… https://t.co/CZPjUNOce4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PartyDarth86 I was gobsmacked! I bet Close would win, based solely on precedence. But I thought Colman was more de… https://t.co/Gy6QVuU3vf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paisano, espere! El pedido de la intervención militar lleva un proceso según el Art. 137 de la Constitución venezol… https://t.co/BJcRAgwmsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UniNoticias @cboteromarino @jorgeramosnews @jorgearturosaza ¡empezó! ¡Qué bruto Maduro atacar a Sir Jorge Ramos! Q… https://t.co/mNrjKYiwYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarthYagos @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump I’m supposed to disbelieve all news outlets in favor for a guy who literally… https://t.co/4KiNELhkef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill No removal from the Committee?   How about removal from my country.  Shes not an American no matter what her status.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CitrusGrovevcs 5th Grade Team. @srhulsman @cohen_elissa @sonicevol @AlyssaBirky @DavidGray120865 @AliaPearlD… https://t.co/pBEYG2LXh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right here. This is where I first met one of my best guy friends of all time, @MootePoints. Miss your face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve learned that if I really wanna baby I can borrow one from my mother 😂🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @PeterPiper_SA for our pizza party! Great way to start our spring break! #MoraLegacy https://t.co/d92cz6DNCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaricakesTTV @queenpamm @hobocita Rumor Willis .  Bruce was on Moonlighting?]]></document><document><![CDATA[and i just wanna be good enough for that one person; but i never will be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya girl just put 18 wings down the hatch and I’m so proud of myself https://t.co/sQWJTo5HAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're probably being sarcastic but hey whatever spreads the word antinatalism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaymontFire Someone really needs to do something about this intersection!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber_Support hey ya. Kinda want to do UberEats and UberEats only, but I'm still getting UberX requests. Thought my… https://t.co/VPM3wXH4t4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKarem @JerryLOakley1 Will it get him off for the tax evasion stuff? If  #45 does do it after all the proof th… https://t.co/mbHqxsMN2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to #TheLaunch season finale wed at 8pm on @CTV who’s with me @GarrickTheDJ @Jessehazen… https://t.co/4bCDUzl31c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I never would do if my body was functioning properly: take a Lyft into town in rush hour.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t continue sitting here worrying about what other people want when I need to be getting myself what I want]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because it's the last chance for cocktail wizardry by Nate (at @ScoutOakhurst in Decatur, GA)… https://t.co/BTnjz86pko]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are very ready for Highland games season. #kilts #scottish #pipeband #highlandgames @ San Diego, California https://t.co/XL9wyad9vI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d eat ground turkey and green beans for the rest of my life every meal if I never had to practice posing 🙃😂  • •… https://t.co/dS8fzRnxj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Bohemian Rhapsody for the 6th time 😂 my favorite movie by far @ItsRamiMalek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brelovestay13 @katscurious Okay we are volunteering a lot for funeral participation 😂 What does this say about us?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremynewberger @PressSec leaders CALL for moment of silence this was “crickets “ cause no one likes ur boss or yo… https://t.co/r4wfyRrMfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Freehold Township, New Jersey https://t.co/fXMcmlvU8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[i leaned over funny and pulled a muscle and it rlly hurt but i played it off cool bc i was like ‘oh, FUCK...  shit!… https://t.co/IrsjnlhTSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My phone consists of mostly screenshots of my friends doing dumb shit than actual selfies... 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[A piece of string walks into a bar and orders a drink. The bartender looks at him and says, "We don't serve string… https://t.co/Rj7i69xcaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomaSPrichard @FIFFNetflix @OasisAnimation We just finished a season. Not sure if there will be another one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alextumay I dm'd you if you actually need some help with your finances]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending our heartfelt condolences to @MichaelEDyson. Let’s heed his advise to “elect individuals that will have OUR… https://t.co/o78WBqsjkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day is still capitalistic af but it’s nice to be loved and to watch other people be in love so overall a 7/10 day &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stranahan We need a hashtag to label #collusionists Bernie is on the rap station proselytizing young African Ameri… https://t.co/heqeQS53Yb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VansWarpedTour can you announce the bands for warped tour please &amp; thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the dirty looks I get from girls at my tables when I talk to their boyfriend 🙃 I have my own boyfriend at home… https://t.co/QUt0MeEYmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love myself for all my failures.  I see my whole self.  Finding an absolute breakthrough is being able to see thr… https://t.co/Pt4gxV0VKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love covers a multitude of sins—but it also points sin out and puts its arm around you to walk through it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The BestBuy Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  C… https://t.co/PoGiigVJ0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BassetLacey Yooooo was 'posed to jump over it all.... take a big run and jump!  maybe on da skateboard!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If we want to pinpoint a moment when women began to be forced out of programming, we can look at one year: 1984. A… https://t.co/fi6ig1Urnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling recaptured only by my visit the the @Scholastic Warehouse for their teacher sale! #booklover]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only had 3 beers last night and I have a huge headache this morning. why]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are in our happy place!!!! @ Buckner's Family Restaurant https://t.co/p6nuGwIr2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[How would the cast of #CriticalRole react if they saw an online magic store named after a magic character from the… https://t.co/ZisZXoclk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack @dozin11 This tweet is 6 DAYS old!!! I just saw it for the 1st time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indianapolis dispatcher coaches 10-year-old through CPR in order to save her mom #cpr #scaawareness https://t.co/wqy3QWxCIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alidaryaeisarab @FLOTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse https://t.co/aqrVmJswrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[These women &amp; their cohorts could be the salvation of the world.  Sort of a self imposed natural selection.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demasiados tuits pero sirve para sacar los nervios, la emoción, la ansiedad, la alegría etc...]]></document><document><![CDATA[She forgets GOP ‘ Illegitimately’.   won in 2016... the majority isn’t as dumb as Republicans think.......trump wil… https://t.co/SOxV7opaQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I truly wanted to work with the elderly . But I’m really about to cuss somebody’s grandparent out if they… https://t.co/lUtORFsgzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay I'm ready for St.Paddy's day! @venicetheseries @crystalchappell  so soft. https://t.co/2F6l7TQ2v7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madosa71 @all_about_Ninas @esferjos1976 @JavierA73286489 @vic_almiron Por lo menos fachas que aman a España. Dígam… https://t.co/QFpki7Qj1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamricpalagi @SenJeffMerkley @89wunderlust Do you have a point somewhere in you fauxhawk snark?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So exciting to watch the #digitalpayments evolution. Proud to have been along for the ride! #lovewhatyoudo… https://t.co/i0o08pnfpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mountain Home man killed in northern Idaho crash https://t.co/iHproNnhSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you’re a singer, sometimes you’re an actress 🎭🎬🎥 @IceAudience  #donaldsutherland @JeremySisto… https://t.co/IlRNBamRYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah and more on this  topic because of their back handling of money to even the tunnels in Jerusalem what they wer… https://t.co/Qb65vmhcp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pietlouter Thank you Piet! I really appreciate your support!! It means a lot!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another delightful gem 🤤🌮 #BajaFishTacos #yum #Asheville @ Mamacita’s Taqueria https://t.co/ZyBIYcjdfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2- when I taught ADHD /LD Ss, many them learned better when provided with visuals, Hands -on activities, and text… https://t.co/Gy1TRNHWPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattDValenti 2002 means the old cafeteria, right? Oh man students now have no idea... :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I appreciate the message, @kroger, but not sold on the use of resources used to make these stickers. 🤔🤔 https://t.co/iQOvCpfJ7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duranduran @SimonJCLeBON @adidas @Cosmopolitan_LV #DuranDuran #duranlive #duranvegas https://t.co/VsbtJgUNvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[👸🏽 3O Things I Like About You🎈: ______________________________________ Found this photo in an old shoe box full of… https://t.co/aSL9iedcpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don’t remember Pusha T being in Clipse and making the hardest song to make beats on the desk in school with… https://t.co/EnOBMufppU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama is still living in DC so he can continue to undermine President Trump.  Do not trust this man. https://t.co/wynTz25Qn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother and I are going to see KISS tonight though I am excited I am more excited for my beer fest afterwords. A… https://t.co/Ctew1bLAnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BabiesLivesMatter  :*( Watch: Undercover Video of Abortion Patient Will Turn Your Stomach https://t.co/7LlUw6vKOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nexplanon bouta expire. Give me one good reason to replace it and not have a child!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_AnimalAdvocate @rickygervais @ScarlettBeagle @PeterEgan6 @ChrisGPackham @Protect_Wldlife Thank you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[At @JHUAPL’s inaugural #APLHealth National Health Symposium today and tomorrow, where the theme is translating medi… https://t.co/zdsl6B7r8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[..feeding off each other.  “Watch as panelists get into an argument! Anderson Cooper reacts to a Trump lie! Host la… https://t.co/J8sHxehzGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drove up to spearfish just for Jamison to take pictures of me- and am now skipping class to go nap ✌🏼]]></document></documents></author>