<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If you are humble nothing will touch you, neither praise nor disgrace, because you know what you are.  ~ Mother Ter… https://t.co/Yr0hivWoNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the man who bumps @Drake and some pretty good hip hop in his ride, and is now good friends with my Mom🤦🏾‍♀️😂  Ha… https://t.co/Dvos6zccnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunflowercafe #breakfast @ The Sunflower Bakery &amp; Cafe https://t.co/475L9YcEDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so tired I can't deal with my coworker today I don't want to be here]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arizona: *snows* Everyone in arizona:  🌨 🌨 🌨 🌨 🌨 🌨    ❄️ ❄️ ❄️ ❄️ ❄️                                         🤠… https://t.co/Zz1F7EdpST]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t make ~too~ many bad decisions last night 🤷🏼‍♀️🙃 @ Downtown Fort Lauderdale, Florida https://t.co/ZGsnFeRcrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just under 6k kids say they have been sexually abused in US government custody. *6,000*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Study: No leaking radiation from Alaska island nuclear site.  @WGME   https://t.co/IDd9q8RL00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaintRPh @justanurse25 Matt. Have you ever considered a career in advertising? 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our mighty hawk diver @nickmccann_ ! We are so proud of your UIL state championship silver metal… https://t.co/pTcuEkIfWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so fucken busy ibearly have time for me...plus usually when people txt me its a favor or some shit...never too c… https://t.co/sAPsBKw7uD]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 still bc this is important. and I feel like a lot of the stupid mistakes made in the writing of Harry Potter are… https://t.co/faSvocwCNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a pleasure and privilege to MC the mastersoftaste media event. Not only were so many of my fave people there,… https://t.co/Q7Ml48Nao8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely blown away by the first @AmericanCancer event I’ve attended! Over 300 people from the West Cleveland are… https://t.co/VhKU73C0dM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrujadeLaMancha I don’t want to kill myself. I’m not even in love rn. I’m just speaking in general. And thank you 😊 you’re so pretty]]></document><document><![CDATA[when youre terrified to go to school tomorrow bcause more gunshots on campus but u literally cant afford to miss anymore 😬 gr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieCalc Justamente así estoy. Deberías de ver mi FB, indignadas porque lo juzgo por su apariencia. 🙈🙈🙈🤢🤢🤢🤢🤢🤢🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeeee maybe it’s not time for me to have kids yet bc i wanna do this now 💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madisonkemnerr Let’s also talk about how ally is a god tier friend ya know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @MstrKnowItAll @nytimes @MattWhitaker46 @HouseJudiciary @realDonaldTrump Ya think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SIGHTSEEING WITH BAE!  Treat your girl right - not only on #Valentinsday. . . . #thedivision #gaming #gamergirl… https://t.co/GMxj9GN5kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@superboyrw @doyalikebaileys Yall really gonna forget mermaidia like that...?!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate the release of #CaptainMarvel with myself and the Marvel Studios Visual Development team tomorrow, March… https://t.co/PLkTz0bnjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que este amor nunca se termine, que siempre se cultive con muchos besos y caricias, y demostrarte con hechos que er… https://t.co/9pScNbKnDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, yes.. I ordered Popeye’s chicken via Ubereats... and when it arrived, slathered it in Manuka honey, devoured e… https://t.co/DbOyjmLcsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[That money could go a long way to help the Palestine people. We need peace]]></document><document><![CDATA[😡 Police fire tear gas to disperse Women's Day rally in Istanbul  https://t.co/W9BUBSdXom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 Same people who think it’s bad “strategy” for the dems to demand so much accountability....looks like “… https://t.co/CBTe71EyIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisHansonRCF @Ifthe_shoe_FITZ I am still in shock from hannah g’s rap scene during the credits]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clairevhill A lot of variety there for you Claire! and you make the most of it!! 😘😘 https://t.co/xGfARK8GUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me giggle. #hilarity #snicker #grin #laughable https://t.co/Eq5mqdjJrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suziday123 @always5star @TravelAtWill @FoodTravelist @DonNadeau @GalsWander @MyVirtualVaca @RoarLoudTravel… https://t.co/G0E1hQQ0Q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LnacreBeth @QuinnDodger @peta PETA doesn't want families 2 buy healthy pups from quality breeders, US or UK. They… https://t.co/Q13eYMQBwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshPlancher @RepJeffries I have a tiny tiny pin that you have to get strong glasses that says Impeach the m-f]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I ever see on my newsfeed is dogs and babies 💞 this is the only positivity I need in my lifen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaPustorino @SonjaNi41294318 @AGuirado5 @queenandadream @DanielaSantannn @danielalippke @MBryant122 @JuliK317… https://t.co/C5TcX6jacf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edutopia Giving time to prepare before they share, opportunities to share with a partner or to stop and jot and sw… https://t.co/Pvkuv5ZQLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing heart healthy information at the 3rd annual Fontan Forum @nationwidekids columbusheart @osuwexmed @ Nationw… https://t.co/3cGeIAqr8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[One person I do want to shout out on #InternationalWomensDay is @katfominykh who, no exaggeration, I would not even… https://t.co/LRDqtMFPcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYSchoolSupts  I voted . Be sure to do so as well. @OliverRobinso13 https://t.co/72jl11KvW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again much ado about nothing. The lukewarm clapping by military officials signifies the sober understanding that… https://t.co/02XfeLtMQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HayleyLemon6 literally the whole time lmao. even when we first started talking before he asked me out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdanClay Carol King  , Dolly Parton , Chris Cornell , Joni Mitchell to name a few.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryxc1128 Tolerate WHAT? A picture? She was somewhere and there was a picture taken. Do you tolerate the pictures o… https://t.co/HJlzSX1Tza]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hanoverstables #samtomjack #futureequestrianchampion @ Hanover Stables https://t.co/j7WspWvq1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleaseeeeeee black ppl let’s stop the rhetoric “we are not our ancestors” in reference to some racist shit, it’s so… https://t.co/BVNAnA9pCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[moved. I have watched drugs tear my family apart my entire life and regardless of how you side on drug addiction as… https://t.co/KgEEfGBo3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyliestuffs @khloekardashian Did they have that same energy when they did it to everyone else!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#c89robandmegan #niagaralandmark #touringwithrobandmegan @ Niagara-On-The-Lake, Ontario https://t.co/JPU9MNfIr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitter needs to find a way to mute memes and videos. Y'all are over doing it with that damn dancing video. The shit is mad annoying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think so, she was loving the view! She’s a thrill seeker who jumps out of planes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayjayperez @hitman604 @JulieReichwein1 No, she is playing alive....Im pretty sure she is dead. They showed a clip… https://t.co/aGrOdn4q6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Animal Planet: anti-poaching and hunting - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/1sIDVAzpBW via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IrishIceSP @ColMorrisDavis I have 2 blank years from my misspent youth. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite Bike events I did. I love Triathlon's but my favorite part is the biking 🚴🏻‍♀️🙌🏼. This was not a… https://t.co/wTxzEmG2b9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from Hanford Calif, we are going to remain cloudy and rainy. Our high today,temperature reaching 67 de… https://t.co/D3T6ysz26A]]></document><document><![CDATA[With so many people I know starting fabulous new #GLAM jobs, it’s got me thinking: what are your best practical tip… https://t.co/kjQPHUSma2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also I'm currently between looking at school for chemistry and welding because that makes perfect sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vickie812 @aliasvaughn @highbrow_nobrow Why did his brother get elected?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitfordBradley What a beautiful picture and that you still think about her on these occasions. UR a wonderful son… https://t.co/1ySbfjZpVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1:  The LITTLE Convos...taking time (even a few minutes) to listen creates sting bonds! #CelebratED https://t.co/QeDReE6BZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[OR my parents live 6 mins awY from my downtown job where a 1 bedroom apartment is $2,500 a month? 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/li7L0gKZRy for some updates on art thingies I’m doin and other randoms 😏☮️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StLouisBlues 🏒💙💛💙🏒 Oh my gosh she is precious!!! I think she looks like her Daddy!!! Congratulations to the entire… https://t.co/LU5vgPsjea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen, the one and only @bnjacobs.  #NASASocial #Moon2Mars @ Operations and Checkout Building https://t.co/HCUfI02gkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melanie_korach Sending positive thoughts and prayers your way today. May your day be filled with love, joy and peace. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m excited and ready to hear what’s coming to R+F! #RFvirtual! #herewegrow https://t.co/cLeXLjLe36]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s easier to learn the right way than to unlearn the wrong way... how you learn is how you will last” @iammiketodd 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encontré a esta chaparrina cerca de las casitas rosas de la cfe aquí en #playasdetijuana trae collar no plaquita 🤨A… https://t.co/06i2MHeOBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How does this guy get away with this? If a Democrat tweeted like Trump they would be in jail by now. This is insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SierraNicole39 Dude I spent 39$ and got free shipping I only orders two things but got a lot of other stuff but I’m not sure 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[please Lord let me find something that I'm passionate about and can work towards to fulfill my future😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bit of hilarity for you. Lucille Ball. "Allowing women everywhere to be confident, beautiful, AND clumsy and hila… https://t.co/fbmNoo2BdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesBond12111 @thehill Dont you dare call anyone a sociopath when democrats voted for infantcide, pure evil, disgusting, and cruel today]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ❤️ a full brow! Signature Brow  Book your appointment online! @ Bonaire, Georgia https://t.co/qbsn9wKB4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm all for a "fair wage" which doesn't mean a "living" wage for all jobs. That said AOC isn't paying A SINGLE SOUL… https://t.co/4OmBUfBSco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meerikulta Oh my goodness, Meeri. I hope they’re safely back in Canada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader Thank you for truth on ABC news This week. The Dems should be a shame!! #InfanticideIsMurder vote has hu… https://t.co/tsxtrYAR1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate is a disease that's destroys you!... So true! https://t.co/lujE3eir3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh Amelia 😢 frick Owen you gotta prove to her you’re gonna be there man  #GreysAnatomy15]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anything on the planet that can make a person feel wimpier than a paper cut? Bested by a Post-It note!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beco diagonal / Harry Potter  Lindo d+++ 😍👏 em The Wizarding World of Harry Potter https://t.co/vaPpPMlzZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@votevets @rcarr57 👆🏼Absolutely No! Time to sue them b/c if they get started, they'll steal every last dollar from Veterans, #RESIST #ETTD 💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[And also, I just wanna be in Columbus playing with the badass squad flooding my IG feed @sarah_bowmar… https://t.co/OGnTlENB5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachel_j15 LOLLL he was like “how was I supposed to know u would be hungry right after you just ate”]]></document><document><![CDATA[if it werent' for humor . . .  Teenager Posts Of The Week: So, What Music Are You Into? https://t.co/eeBJnrn1tD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I don't do 6am flights because I'm not a lunatic but honestly I do a lot of 7:30am flights and they're not bad!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mill_cats @KanD1991 @LittleMaineCoon @BloomNight2 @SassyCassyCat @scarboo @SkittlesFriends @Chrissy7115 @mitsy2714… https://t.co/l0AxM7IEuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Thank God......then for goodness sakes, INDICT HER NOW.......should have happened a long time ago!!… https://t.co/KLQuaxUyrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me raise $65 for #SmokeysChallenge !! #FTK https://t.co/UOBxrU192V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Country music is always banging, but top that shit with a high of 80, a cold drink and good friends and that’s a whole other level]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chriscesq We've met everyone within in a half mile radius - two whole families.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codeofvets @gadiadelman We will cover little Madison Paige in prayer and God will take care of the rest! She is si… https://t.co/WCvQMCNiFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAcademy @lauramarano @louisvirtel @Walmart And these people are telling us President Trump is insane! 😂 https://t.co/5Ke6iQUjbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on Macy’s tryna order a comforter set n I done forgot this boy card number wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyapb3 @ByJakeKurtz bonus Hazel content cause she thinks you're the best too https://t.co/YUrw9c1k1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaitlinLowe @cobalt_alloy @tmas32 @LManuma9 @loviejung3 @JennieFinch @ebarnes7 @AztecCoachTodd @JacqulynnNakai… https://t.co/K4LsZSdqAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacWildxxx @KatieKushxx @mreddiepowell @NSDSxxx https://t.co/gQl5dCjE6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo am I the only one that just saw @evelyncormier_ from #90DayFiance on the @AmericanIdol commercial auditioning?… https://t.co/3NVMc8SS7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[my friends STILL hate on my obsession w/ @JesseMcCartney :( like i’m sorry i’m in love ?¿]]></document></documents></author>