<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Fox_Mulder_8 @SpeakerPelosi Yeah nancy, show us normal beings that We too matter. Sorry we can't donate hundreds o… https://t.co/4jUQcXx6Hn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for that cupping. @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/7PMWPZWEkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told this peon im from Hblock and this nigga made up a block off the dome talkin bout "dblock" on top of that this… https://t.co/vLIciBISgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenSullins Since the first two represent different genres of TV I'd add Simpsons or Seinfeld as the comedy icon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is the most popular Republican Senator? Can we get him (I’m sure it’s a man) to run against Trump in 2020??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyJackson28 @USABaseball @USABaseball18U @jzoll36 @AlexHassan27 @MBorgy7 @IKadishStrength Thanks man! 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[From a diversity standpoint, it’s good that this new field of Democrats includes at least one 77 year old white mal… https://t.co/vuyo2G2QVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SINGING #CARDINAL as I walk to car before day 1 of @SaltHotels @theasburyhotel asburyoceanclub #SaltSchool in… https://t.co/z31FzeYkJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a new world with new forms of war and applications for Game Theory. Interesting discussions with friends who n… https://t.co/pFZL9k8Em9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bossidy1221 Us too, back in the Anthony Harris, Donnail Diggs, Marlon Scott days (late 80’s). They were great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerryNBCBoston @realDonaldTrump @NBC10Boston Death penalty to all who assault and battery...there,all fixed]]></document><document><![CDATA[So in order to open it,.. you have to,... Wait for it,... Wait for it,... You Have to,...BUST A NUT‼️@fatimus07… https://t.co/mb3pX6pR2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t waste time-act now. . . . . #fitnessprofessional #personaltrainerlife #personaltrainer #strengthtraining… https://t.co/31DnuPvKbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShimonPro Aside from the assassination of President Lincoln at Ford’s Theater, John Wilkes Booth lead an otherwise blameless life..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveMurry44 Should be getting our new ones this week. I’ll have to try to remember to get a pic and post it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All @MtLebanonSports alumni coming back the next few weeks if your planning on training please email me. We have a… https://t.co/T9jAaekGMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleWenner @Wikipedia I’m impressed by how well some Wikipedia articles compare to their SEP counterpart. Upon… https://t.co/361pywECvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you need me this week I will be on vampire hours. Seven days of nights started today. https://t.co/Vxbb5UUHA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m the Lakers I go hard after Beverly in the summer! For selfish reasons I hope the Clippers sign him to a reas… https://t.co/KxmkzFXvF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #Richardson, TX! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Senior Lecturer in Comput… https://t.co/MHU766of3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fear of indebtedness hinders your asking. You believe getting what you need from them means you owe them. Actua… https://t.co/UEofWEOVqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 46%? What’s up with the rest of Canadians? I guess it’s ok to break the laws?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 19 / #whole30 / #healthyfood / This might be a yearly occurrence.  🍎🥦🥑🥩]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world is empty if one thinks of only mountains, rivers, and cities; but to know someone here and there who thin… https://t.co/3qeAmwzy1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaseDowningTX I like refried beans. That's why I wanna try fried beans, because maybe they're just as good and we… https://t.co/cdsUrBrkAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikamckinnon What?!?! No radiation shielding codpiece? https://t.co/MGjCAPL9T5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rhacism Yea they had a cream Rick and morty long sleeve, was def top 3 shirts in there. I dont think I’ll ever be… https://t.co/oquGwsu4SV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you brother—  The pleasure was all mine 🙏🏽  Now.. if you will politely call @SC_ESPN 😂😅😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFiWRAL Plus, AMC went: Mickey death, commercial, mourning, commercial. It was like watching the TD, commercial, k… https://t.co/3qOqGNSJde]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well of course he blocked anti-corruption bill. Al Capone would’ve blocked IRS audit if he could have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how the area kids did @CIFState wrestling this weekend. https://t.co/H8HMTSTVvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tatuwah (Link) vs Sweaters (Icies) https://t.co/aeVSVL0jr3 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Princess Half Marathon on my birthday at all the cool people I met along the way. @ Walt Disney World https://t.co/bd3tQUhZGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derekahunter What did two race baiter say to the public after they had lunch together?      Nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yocloclo0 @ChasingWithEcho No but now seeing it like this I might have frame it 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealMBruce @ChipotleTweets @BurgerKing @Wendys @tacobell That was a fave of mine and my wife’s when we were in… https://t.co/dkcvlCltcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crumbled &amp; blew a 2nd half lead aT hOMe to a no Langford no Ward MSU team 🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unless you are a soft tissue pathologist, prudent to be skeptical of (or reluctant to readily accept) if localized… https://t.co/SoxUwalYb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spratto9 @McQueen2103 I’m a sales guy gregg.  You don’t think I asked them 3-5 discovery questions.  I wanted them… https://t.co/hFRrqlWeXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[“How Can Fortnite Be On Its 8th Season When It’s Not Even 2 Years Old” is only one of the thoughts that keeps me ou… https://t.co/yuwbNNkoXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe @RadioFreeTom The issue isn’t Trump. He is the symptom of 2 broken parties. Until American’s realize t… https://t.co/dFjZ2d4Jr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Venezuela #Colombia #Ecuador  #RKelly - #RobertKraft et al sex trafficking  Examples of national emergencies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BDEEZUS I'd like to judge for myself.  Show both and if Rice is better, then so be it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bob_Janke No. No telephone poles for you. Keep sending out jokes please Soup Bone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivEchoLFC It's clear that right now we shouldn't expect too much from these 3. They are off. Our bigger problem i… https://t.co/xeSJFyoTDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The work’s important nonetheless. You never know who you might sway. And lawmakers should never get to vote for any… https://t.co/GBFIkGBnW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1YomBrFUzl @ Trinity Christian Center https://t.co/hn5STsbRBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Applan69 @glory_janson @lukekiveyjr @CNNPolitics Breaking CNN News: RACIST Trump Holds Black Homeless Woman Hostag… https://t.co/pRMPT5LnrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ethan is going to have a big Spring &amp; Summer. Definitely should be kept on your radar! #Crashketball… https://t.co/ZE0p2MS1pq]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Denzel Washington walk 😂 @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/T3jMlcZJlr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repmarkpocan That system replaced an older, less sophisticated simulator that had been installed under President B… https://t.co/Rf6ozGMEVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanecenters You and I both know that a drink is not going to solve a f-in thing. Hang in there Buddy!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The shit show of a 1st period is over but the defense or lack of it rears its ugly head as MTL leads 3-0 #TMLtalk #LeafsForever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ericka88999 Love your beautiful pussy and your sweet beautiful tits sweet heart 🌷💋💋⚘🌷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VladtheImpala Outrageous bigotry and violence against women. Intolerable in military service or civilian life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS yes, Mr. President, we need boarder security. Full speed a head!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big shoutout to @SixZeroAcademy for the dedication and effort to help me achieve my dreams, on and off the field.… https://t.co/qvSSfEBAX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe in the sun even if the clouds hide it. I believe in the Bible even though I was not there to write it, I… https://t.co/76jMVhWtUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialMaleeka You Rock Maleeka! Btw, isn’t it someone’s birthday today or yesterday? I believe I just saw this on FB 🎁⭐️🎂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fave 🤓 high school memory?  Celebrating Euler's Birthday with cupcakes in Calculus class.  And memorizing e to too… https://t.co/F8p62ieMRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @DogoodSeymour for kicking off my new series of interviews with cyclists and photographers. There's a con… https://t.co/KmgmqXDo8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve decided to drop everything and just travel the world. Based on my bank account, I should be home by lunch. Till then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IwriteOK I made a new @bastardspod fan: our Lyft driver during Mardi Gras, also a long haul trucker out of Baton R… https://t.co/IRJVGJZQFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fenrir_71 @Woodyman502 I just spit out my Gatorade all over my pants and carpet and don’t care]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting #45… https://t.co/M1SQQP97Am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylevy *andy throws all of his diamond &amp; silk records into fireplace, dies from toxic fumes of burning plastic*]]></document><document><![CDATA[AHAHA HE MADE HER BLOCK ME 😂😂😂 people really think I’m out here trying. Maaaan I fuckin wish]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShagOnSports @TheHondaClassic Brooks and Ricky ain’t too bad.   That dude just manned up on em.]]></document><document><![CDATA[grandgalaeventsep #grandgalaep #elpasoweddings #elpaso #wedding #elpasoweddingphotographer… https://t.co/LgGm2l3SkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialSPGB @PeterSweden7 A doctrine of hate is one that says I do not  own the product of my labor any more than… https://t.co/ZmamurBanl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where can I buy a baby raccoon and name him Gucci? I want a second pet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP maneuver will block Yemen bill from getting Senate vote: A House-passed bill to halt U.S. involvement in Yemen’… https://t.co/Aw0wXW0Qjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCIA3Mark @GovPritzker Or, cut spending by 15%. Would that force serious discussions on what's really important?]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is not a gift that I could give you that could ever compare to the one you gave me: the gift of life. I want… https://t.co/efzOEiS4KN]]></document><document><![CDATA[just trying to build with the right female, i’m sick of the temporaries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrNunesteach @jcorippo @jmattmiller @iluveducating @jennifer_burdis @KarlyMoura @RandallSampson @dbc_inc https://t.co/5w0YjONE2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicogarciaa Eu reclamava dela roubando com sua quadrilha. As frases eram maravilhosas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t come to Chicago without getting spaghetti and meatballs from Carmine’s. So damn good!!! #goodfood #chicago… https://t.co/9IOSNziR2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, somewhere in NYC a young queer kid is wondering if it’s better to die or be themselves. I don’t want them to… https://t.co/rlcjvRgSAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I had a pack of Necco wafers...sigh...except the chocolate ones... https://t.co/gThgQTy2Ih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHAinSB I don't know for sure. I believe there's no compensation for federal cases though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi caught deleting THIS Jan. 30th statement (busted!) - The Horn News https://t.co/X8yFa3g2Vt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taybeanxx @CNN Well, shut down Twitter then because ain’t none of us been asked!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joe_Spiaggi @DJGalloEtc Franchise record for TDs. Was a fluke year. Variance gone awry. They’re still loaded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonnyBunch @benshapiro Then, let's destroy the transcontinental railroad.  It is a monument to slave labor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dtrinh Imagine if you channeled all that reputation from SF and $$$ from NYC into happiness in PDX 🥳 h/t @joshuafulfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still think about Louie sometimes and wonder what became of him (even after Darren in The Time I Get). So much wi… https://t.co/pgqMqlPm4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t apologize Chris!!! WE ARE ALL LIVING FOR IT!!!!!! #TheBachelor 🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[district/region time was always my favorite time of the year in high school. not being a part of it anymore breaks… https://t.co/aKIO72SPe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The country bows to the all knowing Trump prophecy. Have you ever read the constitution? Of course… https://t.co/KW5hJl1CKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allessier I don’t know if we’re at the same spot right now, but I am having these exact thoughts 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skin and Green Book winning back-to-back is as awful a look as it gets. #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Humble beginnings!!!!!! I understand what it is like to be overweight with doctors wanting to put me on every drug… https://t.co/AfXYGWmYJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryelder @BernieSanders he started his campaign with a truly pathetic attempt to unify with Jewish voters.  I think hes doing LBGT today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was a foul on Davis but since it’s Ky they said he was straight up!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AzChike I see you my boy I plan on icing mine out too, keep aging champ🚀 https://t.co/qvEJSPpkWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most important thing is God's blessing and if you believe in God and you believe in yourself, you have nothing… https://t.co/Fhiv20ndGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re a dummy if you go off percentages when you copping exotics. There’s a lot of gas coming in at 15-19% thc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickNeppach so I understand that st the college level Zion is a dominating force in the paint, but how will he fai… https://t.co/FtwCYGg0xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in Vancouver, WA? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/qMmfcWVdlF #highered #VanWa]]></document></documents></author>