<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@GTWalter1 Absolutely! :) We actually already added a third seat next to ours for the fall. Our ticket rep is worki… https://t.co/Lfq17MQG6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Akira went almost 2 years without human food and then today Colton shared his cookie with her so there’s that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Panther won something so I’m now much less likely to throw my hot chocolate at the tv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I woke up at 6:55am   Yes I stayed in bed watching videos that made me cry till my alarm went off at 7:30am... and what]]></document><document><![CDATA[The car we almost hit pulls up at the light to be an asshole or whatever and my driver is like “o sorry i didnt see… https://t.co/AEM1DWyOSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can tell when it’s a girl asking you a question on curious cat because bitches always ask some weirdly sexual i… https://t.co/yhbyoZiwFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day Y’all! 💕 #love #allyouneedislove #mrst @ Southlake, Texas https://t.co/H9ifMAQfQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincipalMota @NYCSchools @NYCDistrict19 @ExecSuptKWatts @DOEChancellor @sloan_kettering @AmericanCancer I want a shirt!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me crazy, but sometimes I crave a commute to listen to more podcasts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s INSANE how much I miss the cam house.   If you don’t know, you ain’t an OG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Home.    😀   Seagrove Ave. Wilmington,CA 90744 in Carson, CA https://t.co/8wSRTFvRk2 https://t.co/SnstnFJshH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Myrtle Beach Spring Break 19   🎫🎫Text "SpringBreak19" to 843 267 1917 To Buy or  For Info!🎟🎟   Buy your MyrtleMania… https://t.co/i0yTxQ2qXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I go away for a conference, I like to do a little shopping. This, however, was not what I had in mind.... https://t.co/xDRM25EKmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lkwhite @SenFitzgerald @GovEvers Already tried, already vetoed. Listen to the voters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I burn more calories dance-cleaning my apartment to Mamma Mia than actually working out 💪🏻 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisDorroh @SabinoGirlsHoop Very well put and we all have seen the amazing things these young ladies can do!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CassidyRaeOwens Hey I spoke to her, just about bread water and lemons and my bad Malones jokes, but she laughed so 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[What another great event for our community! I love my beautiful bowl and the chili was delicious!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@s8n Just know we did it with our own free will...from @TheGoodGodAbove   #irony #VerifySatan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougtaddison Interesting I used the phrase that I broke out of the box and am eating homemade pizza for breakfast today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegoodgodabove On a scale of 1-10... a 6.  Kick off some humans for me and I can renegotiate that number to a solid 9.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vuhdo @PurdueSports @LarissaLeck @SmashMcCaff @charlesjischke @sadlerimages https://t.co/xCJ4uEkTEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[AFI also had troubles in Russias real estate market, posting losses during the same period. The company also gaine… https://t.co/9sQyI5K61E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Pete's practice of the season. @ Peterborough, Ontario https://t.co/S491zouEdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ewa__Siedlecka @Mir_Kaczynski ...spółka skarbu państwa , więc każdy doi jak sie da! Pytanie tylko, z kim dzielą się tymi pieniądzmi.❓❓❓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s make sure our voices are heard, and Stop the #FakeTrumpEmergency . A wall won’tstop a trumped-up emergency .… https://t.co/iCcqR1dZ3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[i'm staying at a guys house tonight and i really can't be a psychopath up all night listening to a new taylor song… https://t.co/UQbSrGjDbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they call for nasty weather and you are prepping for a “Bethanne” weekend.....you suck it up and leave 3hrs ea… https://t.co/eV9om615DT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dontgasthemeadowlands #stopoiltrains @GovMurphy @billmckibben @WenonahHauter @MattKrogh @sunrisemvmt @FirstLadyNJ… https://t.co/wEWB1ZFjNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamCarp48 @VanityFair PROPAGANDA. The "Liberal order" had nothing to do w/ the secret program of the Joint Intelli… https://t.co/g3xsZbcfpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I must confess when I wear this dress I feel like dancing the whole night with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hkoonce11 I think it's a fairytale. I dont think humans are capable of this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn I really went in the den and smoked four joints this am. Got me a salmon sandwich too ya heard]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rothschildmd I have to say this is probably the stupidest shit I've ever read. But, it did make me laugh so hard I… https://t.co/Onp3VIIwjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#openingnight for #fullonforsythe at @bostonBallet! An incredible three act performance NOT TO BE MISSED! william_f… https://t.co/dGePQ66hBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SummerAWinter I have a feeling Ava and Laura will be friends in some degree.  Time to find Nikolas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaMacRVA @Kirbydc12 @court_koogs @CR8tiveRVA @JMUJONMAC @paulshanks @Paulogan Mundy (&amp; Suzie)! He was pretty happy about it. 🥓]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just started watching this on netflix and this episode made me learn alot of things, especially the fact that men… https://t.co/3SEmVzcCaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll tell my daughter that her first Chicago winter is extra special. 😂🥶😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother kkass1989 and I after we just finished 19.1 of the crossfit open! 🎉🙃 #crossfitrazor #crossfit… https://t.co/UER1W9xTAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can admit that I was very passionately defending Jussie Smollett. I’ve been a fan since #Empire started, and was… https://t.co/8LFVMXN7a2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said I was going to go to Walmart to pick up some stuff an hour ago. I also said that I was going to start meal p… https://t.co/hQ5jJ4d8fR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BIGJAYE617 First thing I typed into Twitter search after Part 1.... What is he publicly saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaganWorld Despicable Liberal Democrat . Their gurl HRC and his deranged party Still can’t accept the 2016 Election Results]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fer_Kari29 De las mejores cosas del mundo, (llorar) es un sentimiento único que claro que duele pero sana nuestro… https://t.co/yN8yMTNY8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[From deep in the woods with Ansel Adams to the Benin Kindom - awesome feb vaca adventures @mfaboston #AnselAdams https://t.co/JYFhV4WUa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[smile and you'll feel better. #laughter #tee-hee #grin #laughable https://t.co/cNAM5ZC11q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robert_harz @VABVOX @BernieSanders It's been pointed out tgat thus statement if yours is incorrect. Will you retract it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING: It’s official. President #Trump says he will declare a national emergency, use executive powers to bypas… https://t.co/RZNQzX0Hqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[she has a list of recommended readings for her album.... everyday there’s a new reason i love her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Belgians have an innate drive to do what they do well. This shows in all aspects of their lives--art, architecture,… https://t.co/bkgtrqSkaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SUNNYDAV @Mirandapaigew11 @DaniKayy @kiajade95 OH MY GOSH! Yes and my bach trip!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, they have money to bribe doctors and advertise to the public. It’s wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacMiller’s “Wear My Hat” came on rn and instantly took me back to the Lair days 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they’re going to do it again!! #KnowYourGoals #GETYOURHVACMILLION 💰💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pipergoodgirl @Kokomothegreat What is remarkable to me, is that old women like her and myself are breaking out of… https://t.co/kpE1Jrse3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scoma60 Is Lulu really going to do this? Is her story that she remembers that Franco tried to kill her? She’s real… https://t.co/kJTNCVhAEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MELisCrazyInAZ My new car uses a start button instead of keys.  I’m always jumping out without pushing the stop button.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I just watched A Star is Born and I wanna know why none of you fucks warned me my heart was going to fucking shr… https://t.co/KKj9UzU13E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight was a blast and I couldn’t have asked for better company. https://t.co/s6hgT3ghAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[thinking about how last summer my roommate explained the entire plot of the Captain America movies to me like it wa… https://t.co/ENHFG0ikFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ElizabethMay The worst wedding shower turned into an Amway sales pitch by father of the bride]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you just love getting ready for bed and get all comfortable but then realize you didn’t take your contacts out]]></document><document><![CDATA[New haul came in. Reviewing resources for our clients and faith communities. #ChurchToo #SBCtoo #WhenFaithHurts… https://t.co/lbUUHIcwTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eww... he needs to take and get all his money back &amp; damn get him somebody better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland That Voter Purge in Texas is THE FARCE that got Trump ELECTED.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a great Sunday!! Getting a lazy start from the west coast!! Enjoy!!! #lovemygirls #missmygirls allylevinee ste… https://t.co/NvxrIWdsXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[No really tho? If I plan on getting drunk... can someone make sure I get home? Or can I spend the night? I’ll buy breakfast/ coffee? 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@r125xiii @Pers_ality @Elle_316 @BrotherNature He has a phone. He has google. He also apparently has friends that a… https://t.co/avuslRjnk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShowalterVicky @D1Circuit @1Tyus @Tre3Jones @PulleyHoops Thank you 🙏🏼💙💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day too all friends and be well goodnight u must have a nice Valentine's 💞💕💗💖😘💘💓😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘… https://t.co/NmH27ZivFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@gtstern speaks with ANA’s @BillDuggan about a new @4As research report and the hot topics impacting our industry… https://t.co/642KFbTHF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox News: Suspect charged after girl helps find man in car trunk. https://t.co/FXAMqa51iK  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t post a Valentine’s Day gift on social media is it really love? #reallove #actionoverwords #careathome #standsmiling #happyfirst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is AOC out cry.. is she brave enough to go against Mayor DeBlasio’s wife for accountability.. Maybe that’s wh… https://t.co/GdTMWFjJMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t listen to any other part of the hearing, because it’s just too much, listen to @RepCummings trying to… https://t.co/qzkHPuZetT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The boop that revolutionized Snapchat. | 22 Boops That Changed The World In 2013 #humor #cat... #humor #tee-hee… https://t.co/nd7PRxlgQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch me being irrationally sad I won't see another NWHL game in person all year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland I think a cell phone EXTORTION attempt IS a cyber-attack worthy of a Simple Assault.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be grateful for who you are and all you are becoming.💖 @ Santa Monica, California https://t.co/9snAQgOpb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fact Friday...What will history say about you?  This months theme is on black history and heart disease.  Stress ca… https://t.co/vnYRV2BAAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely nothing but cuddle with the husband and enjoy great dinner, peace and quiet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swell @RDHague I want to know more about the people who dropped ~$1K on a Canada Goose jacket but not a hat or gloves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @Boo3zero5 @washingtonpost Large media operations WAPO CNN MSNBC know they have a responsibility as… https://t.co/z2JTNFpBq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m certain that if you play a beyonce album i’m reverse that it summons a portal to hell in the shape of jay z lips]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $50 Skype Gift Card Offer  Win $50 Skype Gift Card Offer By Your Email Id Submit,  Click Here:… https://t.co/q9gTxWaxOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the UH graduating seniors!! They will be displaying their digital media portfolios for you to se… https://t.co/1UO0JJHQTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Initiated and lead my first #Marketing meeting with executives today. Now it’s a weekly meeting. Getting hyped!… https://t.co/27Ig3nwYrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryWarnedUs I remember Carter. I remember Truman’s funeral vaguely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yangjinfen721 @LiuCdp2006nyc 什麼樣的委屈可以如此的不顧一切！可敬可佩可憐的老母親！神啊求禰垂聽這位老母親的泣血之聲🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Coffee ☕️☕️☕️ (@ Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA) https://t.co/cVfqjrmEB9 https://t.co/XW1L7cc4H9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bayer pairs its products in first-ever portfolio TV ad for hormone-releasing IUDs Dislike #IUDs with… https://t.co/OItQ8ZtZU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[AKC S.T.A.R. Puppy Graduation 🎓   Woo Hoo Falkor! 😍 First Ribbons &amp; Letters! 🎉  (5 Months-82#) #leonbergerpuppy… https://t.co/UzfqTRfHUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking SUCKS when your deadbeat fucking boyfriend won’t do a fucking thing around the house and he doesn’t even ha… https://t.co/qsLDyW29zI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still can't believe I am where John McClane throws Hans Gruber off of Nakatomi Plaza! #diehard #sureal… https://t.co/NC2wWAD8J7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeaksTruthNow @MastersNan @frmattfish BE it that you believe that or not, when you are speaking of the reasons WH… https://t.co/MvAzCIRMxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many headaches can one girl get in a week? I’m trying to beat my own personal record]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sondra Locke yet again screwed over by Hollywood by being omitted from #Oscars In Memoriam. Not surprised given her… https://t.co/AYuYhbAvCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are a lying cheating misogynist who has faked his way through life. You are soon to be caught.  Gear up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great presentation! Interesting information about the data behind story!]]></document></documents></author>