<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Was real pissed I shot like a 15 last week at darts but now I remember Sean made me eat a "special" cookie before,… https://t.co/Tw4cb85tsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loccdawgg @Block_Royal8 Broly definitely beat the shit out of them but they weren’t as beat up as they were vs Jiren.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como hago para conquistar? Preguntó el niño!! La clave es hacer reir, le dijo el sábio!!  Arturo Javier Duarte-Rodriguez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trump4future @JohnFugelsang It's laughable that you think that Trump and Truth go together in the same sentence]]></document><document><![CDATA[Understanding will never come demanding answers from God. But trusting God will bring the answers and result in understanding. #Slamism]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wickedness  I think #TwistedMetal needs a full on remake https://t.co/qNUfbNZbdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all are into interior design or renovations y’all have to watch Mr. Kate of YouTube!!! Seriously I’m obsessed w her channel🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[the new Republican party is a danger to our democracy everyone should really pay attention Salon: CPAC 2019: Candac… https://t.co/EJWDMRZiPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Domino’s is so crazy about pizza, they’re giving away rewards points toward free Domino’s for eating any pizza, fro… https://t.co/foOgFhxgpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Supporter Sucker Punches Protester While Being Escorted https://t.co/qcFATySqMl via @YouTube WHAT DOES THIS VIDEO SHOW YOU?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBorta As far as fast food goes, nothing is better. Come through with that shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TenilleDashwood Happy Birthday Tenille Dashwood! You’re 30 Years Old Now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[1110-1142 La Cienega Blvd 1110-1142 La Cienega Blvd, West Hollywood, CA 90069 https://t.co/dcpQxxLJXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ride 1: Slinky Dog Dash at 9:08 AM #parkeologychallenge @Parkeology https://t.co/H7Gg9tUxFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You are looking live as Robert McKenzie watches ‘The War’ by Ken Burns for the first time,” said @brentmusburger •… https://t.co/bMmK0LYvJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Billy04959629 @Registered_Rep @someideasnstuff @reddit I'm seriously looking at getting a tesla. If save 500 a mon… https://t.co/uaZEUglvrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to this, and especially now we’ll be discussing a win! #readingfc #foreigncorrespondent]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Intersection : E Sunrise Blvd &amp; US Hwy 1 in Fort Lauderdale, FL https://t.co/hbK2GH9zk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIP #FF @RachelDeAlto @LinseyDavis @sonia_mafs @soledadobrien @TheMindyProject @capthlr @Kate_Chastain @HayleyAnnRN @JenArnoldMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady at Starbucks called be honey, baby and sweetheart during the ordering process. So much affection at 5am. 🥰🥰🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soulexchange1 @It5Holly @LadyLakeMusic @RareHorror @AnnettaOberst @KingDivine315 @LindaChorney @bryanbrtltt… https://t.co/f55FuUkkiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remembered the disgusting salad that rural relatives make that has mini marshmallows in it.  Has anyone else e… https://t.co/1U2XWHUygD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giving back to your community is so important. I am really proud that @compassinc takes giving back so seriously. S… https://t.co/crou22mfjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clairevhill @tuf2beme @geeanem @jewelsking_king @Marg1010 You too Claire😗🙏🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erica___lynn Have you gone to a doctor, this looks ruff.  Real sorry but I had to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheChadColby Used to. If I went back to doing it myself I wouldn’t have anybody to try to upsell me on $500 worth of maintenance]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦄 24 Minute EMOM 🦄   The Simple Setup: Every Minute on the Minute run 🏃 through ~   Min. 1 - 20 Assault Bike Cals… https://t.co/83KnuY0298]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the?????? Ive been here 11 years, and its never done this before, crazy! #vegasbaby @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/qk21pKg0S4]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@HOLLYHORSKY BOUGHT ME A ‘OH H*CK’ @DOG_RATES HAT, I DON’T DESEVE HER AS A SISTER WHAT EVEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is answering bold 🙏🏻s in BIG ways ⛪ !! . . . . #iamfreedomchurch #pray #give #go #increase #campuslaunch… https://t.co/NCBJv5drAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMBWFAN This is the system the players wanted. Honor it or go like the rest of the professional sports and get a s… https://t.co/rvuBk0I19L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ghaff @Apress That sounds like a great plan! Thanks for the suggestion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #BuildTheWall #MAGA #JobsNotMobs https://t.co/eeNjbnN2PB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sternvascular @blakepparsons @BradleyThomas @JimGMelton @theveinlady @kmadass Now those are good points, and in pa… https://t.co/MliciOOxIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJWatt hey JJ I'll be at nrg stadium with a couple other soldiers today for the Houston rodeo!! You should come se… https://t.co/mW2sx0MfcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WISH_TV This dude is in for some mud slinging. Might end up convicted before it is all over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1233 dollars later i have a new and fully working pc built by me and a lil help of @estebanortega30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberAudio @Kevbo521 @AOC When you remove your head from the sand, take a guess as to where this Non-existent opio… https://t.co/ZGLQCOIKMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lyft and the Left: The ride-sharing firm wants the feds to protect its business model. https://t.co/2nvyWar3Hv via @WSJ. 🚕🚕🚕🚖🚖🚖💰💰💰💵💵💵]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last one! One of my favorite Bad Beat IPAs of late. - Drinking  The Floor Is Lava by @badbeatbrewing @ ChiChi's Den… https://t.co/EJ1QeINewV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeilShelat6 That... seems bad, but somehow not the worst possible outcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[People peep threw my feeds on social media and are litteraly probably like and I quote "Welll shiiiiit this kid has… https://t.co/wfB1Gr0t48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWildeGlobal @JustinLevineHBS They certainly aren't a lock to make the playoffs though.  Finish with the 15th pick… https://t.co/iWWotza5pj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t had #Hairspray fever in years, but ever since it’s been put on #Netflix , this fever has been raging!! 🤒🥴🤩🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesertSandsUSD @DesertRidgeAcad @AmideiClass @mandywiltrout @ScaughtSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stream on #spotify #applemusic #tidal #googleplay 3/9/2019 music link in bio to pre save #viral @ Long Beach, Calif… https://t.co/Hts9SD5pd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the neighborhood! #UpperWestSide #BillysBakery #NYC2019 @billysbakerynyc https://t.co/DcqO8T0Yxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#golf 165 downhill. Whst club are you playing? @ Torrey Pines Municipal Golf Course https://t.co/BESijp24Yi]]></document><document><![CDATA[S A T U R D A Y S U N S H I N E . #paddlelife #trainhardgofasthavefun  #itsaboutlifestyle  #fastisfun… https://t.co/AQx3fVu0f9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm giving up profanity for #Lent. #AshWednesday #Methodist #IamAME #ThankYouJESUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I’ve been getting nothing but love on the EP...my treat ☔️♠️ #TheStormEP #OutNow @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/9FUeXQ11dP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien Trump comes from a commercial backgr where MOUs are not binding and are precursors to definitive agr… https://t.co/zXxWdZwRDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[View from the 70th floor with 0 trophies. #intercontinentalhotel #casawards @ InterContinental Los Angeles Downtown https://t.co/ei7IdvgzyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clamaré al Dios Altísimo, Al Dios que me favorece. El enviará desde los cielos, y me salvará De la infamia del que… https://t.co/pmBdmU87xj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a little personal news. I’ll be covering the Colorado @Rockies during spring training for @sportscronkite . Re… https://t.co/swthhgGArv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole interview was a farce. The so called press, who is an absolute embarrassment to the 1st Amendment should… https://t.co/yPwNAAecpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone........anyone.......HELP.....me get Twitter followers #twitter #follobackforfolloback #followers… https://t.co/Y3I9m5hYAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WORLDSTAR The first thing I'd do is buy a @ChurchsChicken so I could have it 24 hours a day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jalenmcmillan20 @salvelaz Go Dawgs!! #PurpleReign congratulations!! https://t.co/5ouY8rwREv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outstanding Performance by President of Student Council Anna Chapa‼️A well earned accomplishment 💙 #GoMustangs]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you feel like you’re feeling someone. Don’t bother. They won’t feel you back and straight up ignore you. I guess… https://t.co/Ls0A4eQZZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twithersAP @WestlakeBasket1 @AnthonyRego1 @Mayjacob23 @GeageaJoey @dylan_bednar Have thoroughly enjoyed watching a… https://t.co/RIkYRgKyzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to go #help #Venezuela right now! They’re dictator has turned off all their power and people in hospitals a… https://t.co/MKxVpNey0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[This place “ain’t” the pits. @OlympianBoysVB @HoosierHPodcast @Sports_Journal https://t.co/MXMnVTvcfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenseiSwat33 @thetournament Register for the Lexington region &amp; keep it simple...38-1.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you all are still trying digest WTF happened in the “Oscars 2019” Check out this piece by Richard Brody for the… https://t.co/vDVxnwLvCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregS1981 @jordan23ww @CarsynCruz I use Dantoni he becomes a slashing playmaker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@narizam28 Excelente. Me permito sugerir Que votes por “ideas” y también por hechos concretos y no corrupción]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOR SALE Only a quick walk from the sandy swim beach and located on a serene park, this captivating bungalow will d… https://t.co/oPwGw1i6Ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NinaHarrelsonTV @3onyourside Hello. https://t.co/dK59RGW104 (an IBM brand) would like to feature your post on our… https://t.co/FhabX9bWkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Emanuel lulls his defender to sleep, uses an extremely useful hesitation crossover and gets to the hoop for th… https://t.co/soCQkmeynu]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling when you wake up and it’s @GatorsBB game day! #TwoClapsAndARicFlair #GoGators https://t.co/GxMKbMenlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just completed the @iste course: "Artificial Intelligence Explorations and their Practical Use in Classroom Environ… https://t.co/NRllr2UTzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ingresa al Sorteo Scotiabank Tiempo de Aficionados y podrás ganar  muchos premios https://t.co/sDZVHyai07 #soyaficionado]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheena6076 @NikkF07 Don't you hate typos lol!  Some of Habs fanbase is unreal blaming Price.   Game would have bee… https://t.co/cWiJhDhrp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/aEb87SaUqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiveFromLiz @DonaldJTrumpJr Great point Liz. Slavery is alive and well. Libs have all kinds of “great” ideas paid… https://t.co/Q1WMBGG9C2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPhilly19 I've been there for USC-CU games and seen it 50-50, but recently the perception exists it is a Clemson h… https://t.co/YzhG8umc3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[No he’s definitely the president and this is #Maga country bitch😂🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackGrealish1 Why do I feel like you should be approaching retirement, but you’re still so young? Are you a wizard… https://t.co/wJoTotSTnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here how I enjoyed the  #funweekend  #SundayFunday #inthebeach 🏖 🌞 ............................................. On… https://t.co/UiuszpqFn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I will never leave my air pods at home for even a second ever again. I completely under valued them and I s… https://t.co/9IZMbBgDj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BAKKOOONN There is something to love from every single movie.  Even Clone Wars had the gladiator scene and I’m sor… https://t.co/7ufW27zMvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OGDannyOcean That’s why you never stop working. Now when you coming west? I got a pack on deck. 💨]]></document><document><![CDATA[you talk about Drake way too much for him not to be doing something right]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Winnavegas Casino Resort - @winnavegasia in Sloan, IA https://t.co/0Vnd98k09S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRzepecki @BenjaminSRaven @therealgstoye The take that paczki are gross is itself gross]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halloween haunt sign inspiration #funniness #giggle #smirk #jolly https://t.co/4bKAxb6wlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camachbrO Humor is the only way to salve rejection, and at my age, it needs to come in the giant economy size jar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🍹🔥 #fiya_flava #drinks #yummy #bday #alcoholic  #nawlins #sexy #hot #wow #504  #party #turntup #sweet… https://t.co/XY0rKTTAgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ho by the way, how’s the Amazon deal working out for your NYrs ??? Oh wait... it’s not!! Lmao NYC, California = idi… https://t.co/ceEipkovIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great workout…right. I had to stop halfway through, my left knee is tingling with biofreeze to reduce swelling, and… https://t.co/vVpODSEqVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully Trump and his entorage has a safe trip,... and no accidents on way to Vietnam. https://t.co/mHcIvvzcQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheStalwart I wouldn't dismiss the superpowers of suburban dads. 😆 https://t.co/ZgmOgWM0qm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go vote for Public Advocate today NYC (@ Ps 249 in New York, NY) https://t.co/OqFW64ii4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @Josiah_B98 asks to play apex at 9 am on my day off and isn’t even on....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selfie with #Oracle from "Birds of Prey"! It's actually behind the scenes at @ShannonDeVido's Oracle screentest pho… https://t.co/T9W08Ac1Cp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsanbrowning @anbrowning We have like 3 houses for rent/sale on our street right now. Move to Bham and you and Be… https://t.co/7Lf8GdJevm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who ever saw me at that party last night Yaa that wasn’t me ok so don’t ask me about that foo lol 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Washington seems to have an over-supply of liars and cheats. Quite a few names brought out by Judi… https://t.co/6TPUV9HX6o]]></document></documents></author>