<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'm not quite sure what you thought this was.  https://t.co/ZRx8mUHWCH #mensfashion https://t.co/mNLGUJa0R3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeMeredithAP @PatHarty @Hassel_Chris  favorite player has to be on the list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The happiness you feel after having a close call with death must be so much fun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@75toRupp For real. She HAD to have watched that and thought “I lose” - too much fire between them in that performance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow thank you SoundCloud weekly😂 ᵗᵒˣᶦᶜᶦᵗʸ level =  hazardous                       ☢️ __☢️@OfficialRezz… https://t.co/8MQEaDff45]]></document><document><![CDATA[The “Zero Sugar Diet” has paid off. Cannot be happier for this dude. Nobody works harder! HUGE ‼️‼️@Cohen_0608]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TRUCKINGUSATN @AskAmex Right please pay off your America express card and cut the card up please call many times t… https://t.co/RyJNp2UdNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azaryajason4 Same &amp; you know he’s gonna be aggressive on the defensive side which makes more excited.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EscosPride I still need to check it out too, heard so many good things]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esperando en el aeropuerto me cuenta que son muuuchos los que hablan español aqui.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Cognizant team! See our latest #IT job openings, including "Senior Manager, Supply Chain Consultant", via… https://t.co/ljUE9DdO52]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The Gur leader himself...was offered similar VIP treatment a year ago...with patients evacuated from three rooms i… https://t.co/zd6hj5XaT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andres_Gomez22 yo gurl made some bomb ass foods and offered me some 🥰 #feelingloved #potroast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drhockeyncoffee @dougie0216 @DallasStars @NHL Got to follow the @NAHLHockey Top Prospects Tournament next week. 6… https://t.co/3Qbiv924OW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eagle Energy $Egl.ca $Egrgf active again this morning ... risk/reward very favourable on company receiving new fina… https://t.co/tnbvP5U8eR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KickinItWitKeef @uSTADIUM Think you missed the point. He was drafted so high because of his 40 time. It earned him… https://t.co/yw2Cwxmu6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wagglegolf @Buccigross I see that mark right in the middle of the club face! Good work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kawasook Disclaimer: these opinions are not based on Tesla. Based on my childhood on solar/battery and my 16.6kw a… https://t.co/LcTfnfUCaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elmijomadrigal estuviste muy activo toda la semana por esta red social... Y ahorita que pasa? Todo bien? 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet Rosie!  Our moms made a play date for today. We had a ball—pun intended—and ran hard trying to be the first on… https://t.co/hiLZTpJcbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 It’s now 3 hours since your tweet. So... let’s see... umm, move the zero, carry the one... oh hell! Donny’s… https://t.co/kTWBCi653x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today: up at 4:45. Get dressed. Oatmeal. Coffee. Wait for Lyft. Wait for start. Run. It’s a great day to be alive and run a marathon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseball and palm trees, I can get used to this combo!! https://t.co/nwPRn6kZn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Let's have a parade and gathering when Donald J Trump leaves office. #TrumpRussia #TrumpCrimeFamily #TrumpLiesEverytimeHeSpeaks]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to create a versatile and more realistic wig?🤔 How bout a dimensional haircut❣️ Who’s hairline does not have ba… https://t.co/uWwktZ75M1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rexparker When he was the Mets' ace, wouldn't even wave hello to kids yelling his name outside the Mets parking lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrennaSpencer billionaire venture capitalist in an elevator in menlo park in 1998 told me not to quit my day job,… https://t.co/yOzgYk9fI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking forward to joining a great group of folks and discussing the role of the courts in a democratic societ… https://t.co/q9A55XcTCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItZ_Cazzy_T @SadDinklebot Not sure what you’re talking about. Been running double smgs and peacekeepers in QP and… https://t.co/NUtpdDo8WJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddiesofficials @SFGiants @SFGiantsSTM You know the ending is coming after this season I think they will eliminate hard tickets]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been feeling so gross lately time to get back on my bullshit and hit the gym everyday and start up my kito diet a… https://t.co/7srnyWCtBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only way to learn from experience is to have different experiences. @SethGodinBlog #learn #live #grow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanKaeser @AkinsMel @TrenisiaEvansHD @mjrawlinson5 @Robert_Daffern @Cali_J_ Awesome job Morgan!! HD is rooting for you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was great to see James Bay in concert. He was amazing. It’s nice to see my bro Jon. Until next time Jonny! 😉😁✌🏽… https://t.co/tdnm1kcHCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence Yeah. Not that he cares but not buying a pillow from this creepy guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Real_Whores @maryjanesosexy @XXValeriay @Mierdafavorita @Follow_mee18 @LadyMystique_01 @OMGitsVanessa2… https://t.co/jppCejoabR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra When you talk opening over and over about Jews not Israel, sounds on purpose to me. #StandWithIsrael]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all remember how lit Pokémon Go was when it first came out. Had my ass walking 45 miles a day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyloRenzGido Eh, I still think Tom Hiddleston should be the next narrator for that. But maybe him in the play pavi… https://t.co/pTrjnvCulb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am actually a fan of LeBron when he's not facing the pacers but he's being a whole bitch this seasons. Doesn't wa… https://t.co/jy6XviORNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNewThinkerr @Solidaritybitch @ChelseaClinton @IlhanMN @bungarsargon Good morning Chelsea! Just checking in. Hav… https://t.co/VFrGOnvrTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fills vacuum? That's like saying the Auto industry has filled the vacuum of  airplanes  because there are less flig… https://t.co/Vv60Qhn6Fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalkToMeForReal Does this duck stain even know what curb stomping is? Curb stomping or “curbing” is when you beat… https://t.co/NwRYhUKPun]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I’m not religious or anything, but isn’t signing Bibles sacrilegious? Like, you’re writing on the word of God.… https://t.co/76RXlOG6Fa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NowFuckingBlasting - @Metallica  SANITARIUM.    JUST LEAVE ME ALONE https://t.co/NnzagMI0Sq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Revisited my alma mater @CentralWashU today to work with our future #PhysEd leaders.  Energy from this group was of… https://t.co/mebzpiVcqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirkgoldsberry We are going to be doing CSA towards the end of SL. Probably July 11th, 12th, 13th, and 14th. Any o… https://t.co/3giIYn0Vyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yankowitz: Question of whether superconductor in twisted graphene is "unconventional" where electron-electron coupl… https://t.co/TV9zq1qt6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfaooooo I use to do this, now I just ridiculously ugly faces until they look away]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotTheChips Overall though, I just don't think Joaquin could fundraise as well as Beto, and the electorate will be… https://t.co/bhvMoIVa5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan Taylor opens up the scoring with a mid range jumper. Assisted by Law. #earlybuckets]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sombrío, en evento se ve el futuro de ese partido -más sombrío aún que su pasado-, y lo hay ningún indicio que per… https://t.co/uxNtWGk23R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PornoDan @ProModelWorld @mikequasar Hide all intelligence, hide every nice possession, down play yourself to a deg… https://t.co/eV6rXFLP1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOneTrace @AbbyMartin @jjmartini21 @AOC @SenSanders @SenWarren Ocasio-Cortez will still be 4 years too young to run for prez.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LolaFaeXXX @rileyreidx3 got it bad this week, but she's not alone. Lots of porn stars had their IG accounts killed… https://t.co/QctWW3USCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Springfield, MA? View our latest opening: https://t.co/hqZ3wLwQmJ #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollandane experimenting with Mixer Brush using Van Gogh’s Cafe Terrace at Night, 1888, in Intro to Digital Imagin… https://t.co/R6wi6Pknhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone knows Modern Democrats are new Nazi, whom shouldn't be in any positions in ours USA government.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jessleecountry @officialchevel @TaylorKalupa @MaseyMcLain @victoriastaley @EmmaElleRoberts @laylaspring… https://t.co/MFnXD20bGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think about modern life it isn't really healthy.  You have all of these groups trying to convert you.  If yo… https://t.co/vaAWP13czG]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Starbucks on steroids’: can America’s new weed cafes make smoking social?. https://t.co/Go2Ft18BQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your narrative, round and round! https://t.co/r7aX2YjfZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I added a “booking” section to my profile, for if you want to hire me to write or act for a project. I also added a… https://t.co/DMvftTrT9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to some wedding shenanigans this weekend @ San Diego, California https://t.co/HGgX9vaNlr]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you and your homie get caught   looking at a girls toes😩 https://t.co/1RlcBy52DU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWStulsa I saw that too. Our station is a bit south of the airport along the interstate. I’ve been standing outsid… https://t.co/8D44WGELJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@totally_t_bomb @DanfaheyJohn @BeloitSoccer I've got Wisconsin as a 4. The way everyone around them has been playin… https://t.co/S5NDRWA6hI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rami Malek in talks to play the next Bond villain, Collider reports  https://t.co/xjAI2FK93Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDaIey ONE OF THA HARDEST UNDERGROUND ARTISTS N HOUSTON 💪🏽 CHEC ME OUT 👀👂  🚨🔥🧨💥🚨🔥🧨💥🚨🔥🧨💥 https://t.co/5lXDge7pdq 🚨🔥🧨💥🚨🔥🧨💥🚨🔥🧨💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh #decadenceaz 💚🖤 seeing allison wonderland was seriously one of the highlights of the whole event 😌 @ Rawhide Eve… https://t.co/8t7eX92deL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I DO NOT OWN RIGHTS TO THIS MUSIC  Beautiful Monday,  let's get this cash my Peeps... One Love .... @ Newport News,… https://t.co/v3VlsqMhWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ImABigBrotherNow #KaturaJHudson  #literacymatters #imagesmatter #marchisreadingmonth https://t.co/dOM5rK3ay0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very happy bday to a close friend. Thank you Connor for helping me in workouts and races. Always making me laugh… https://t.co/6aMZNkWpmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iheart30stm That's cool...what made you want to move to California next year? I would love to visit Japan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChokeOn_This21 😩😂 i respect it. It’s just...when you get that “come to the crib” text you’re not expecting....that]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sad truth about the news today is that we don’t get the truth anymore... it’s all fabricated... whether it… https://t.co/oQjhhBXVIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is Mental Health Awareness Month.Let's remember that Mental Health is just a component of "Health".No one is… https://t.co/OG4LnuMI4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear to god if Bohemian Rhapsody sweeps the Oscars!!! https://t.co/jKSJon1Jq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[CurcuDerm Cream Specials: Buy 1 Get 10% Off on 2nd An organic White Curcumin Derma Cream for all Skin Conditions |… https://t.co/QHwx4RAI2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[First @BrownU_Baseball HR of the season hit by @marks2435 against Presbyterian College - assisted by and thanks to… https://t.co/uycyYDc3bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is Semi Ojeleye not playing? The best defender on the Celtics. Why did Brad Stevens put Rookie Robert Williams… https://t.co/UxVfr1fZio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourMorning. Kelsey remote today as in the words of Mike Myers aka Gold. Member..that's a keeper https://t.co/mVL5Wepplj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Danny Brown Radiohead produced by Samiyam I got into Samiyam more after this track https://t.co/h1cwfWKreb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinmyers good morning Erin.  You’re looking great in the coat.  Have a great day and hopefully stay dry and careful out there in the rain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I cant wait to get my haircut Friday my hair look like a rose curly bush right now even tho the waves still showing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cliverrrrxo @WaltDisneyWorld @UniversalORL Way too much to process right now 🤯🤯🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you do t tho k losing Trey flowers hurts, you’re clearly a box score scout who doesn’t watch game. He’s the most… https://t.co/5eVdRvyXIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerwinJames If u put ur jersey on there with all sizes I be the first buyer because NFL store sucks and they have… https://t.co/c7OT9h4j0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NuanceBro @joerogan @TeamYouTube But rogan’s videos are still being recommended ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsmaris Most men are socially stupid  "Boys" which makes their retorts inane at best! Most women are insecure "Gi… https://t.co/Yhr32Ilp7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending her off to “State”!  @mckenna_sterchi Last competition of the year! @BCHS_DVUSD #GoJags #Zona https://t.co/FvbcdL76Fp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davemchugh @NavyAthletics @SkidmoreBball Former Navy Assistant. We have several doing well as HC’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[At work we work as team on #shoes 👟❤️ and care to support people's feet on the daily basis. #WHPSheInspiresMe… https://t.co/cNqSEwrHgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[**Today only:  Buy one canvas and get a second one of equal or lesser value for 25% off!!** We will have free snack… https://t.co/mcgchRBsyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunterLJohnson Really excited to not be heated and possibly drunk at 11 on a week day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_kylakiara @O_MyGotti Damn near but even the other time still ruined my sheets. 2 times was enough for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcAntoni1985 @cross_kendall @5PtMove If you wanna send them over we can digitize them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big night for Spaulding hoops: boys host Winnacunnet with D1 tourney three seed at stake; girls at Kennett in D2 qu… https://t.co/VlNyqZLsB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gpublicity1 When I lost my job in 2016, I had to reinvent myself.  But the purpose part always eaten at me. It’s b… https://t.co/fHO7F4Wedk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darinlayman @Tesla @SunPower Awesome - my goal to someday have solar also in the Bay Area and power up the card with it! Thnx for sharing]]></document></documents></author>