<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Littlemrs_A Ugh. I hear you. I am often #travel shamed in a similar way and it can be so frustrating.   https://t.co/MljqroHVDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love that i’m tweeting this lol i’m a lesbian but i wanna show my support for all my kweers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having fun being super early #kwfr2019 #imwithgary #KWAG #listwithnikki  #buywithbateman @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/j2OTQgQGRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liloer_ Idk if it's cause I'm on my period but I legit cried for like 10 min 😭😢🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[• THIS WEEK IN CP • Come dance the Shag with us and @UofSCPillars tomorrow night💃 https://t.co/7sKkZELKgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great seeing crews from Indiana here to help my @ConsumersEnergy coworkers as they deal with these crazy winds and… https://t.co/isr2HCXyIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gardez vous une petite gêne, m. Bovet. L'éthique du journalisme est encore de mise.....vous me décevez.#SRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When blake Shelton said “ The person that I’ve been lately ain’t who I want to be, but you stayed right here right beside me” I felt that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always classy, never trashy &amp; a little bit sassy 🌟  #bosslady #subdirectora #concursodeciencias #smiles… https://t.co/7Q5XUxHlYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day! 👭 ❤️ Photographer: @avivaklein  Community: envsnfest  #envsnfest #avivaklein… https://t.co/duEcYo0wjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseDemocrats Not vicious that is a lie.  I do not want to@pay for other people’s abortion.  They were irresponsi… https://t.co/5mC1kzkwii]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off the 2019-2020 school year w/the Class of 2023! @GunterHSTigers Principal Mr. Dodd sharing w/Incoming Fr… https://t.co/GrLYE1pLyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta love those pregnancy cravings! 😂 #Hearties @hallmarkmovie #sweetsourcrunchysalty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyK @Twitter @dickc @bohan @TJay @stephanied @ju2thalee @mooreryan @evanr @semurph @LiatBycel @LK Congratulations!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuinceMountain @JamesFrye @archivalistic @Way2gosassy @GMTminus7 When there is a shift that broadens  administrati… https://t.co/KRkj8yxmcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[De nada me sirvió ir a la escuela para que toda la lógica me la hagan mierda en este país #México]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Popinard @Monmontreal @Montreal @mtlblog @always5star @RoarLoudTravel @travthroughlife @Sostraveluk @CentrevilleMTL @Placevillemarie Wow 😲]]></document><document><![CDATA[Será posible este horror y escuchen lo que dice a cerca de la actitud de quienes supuestamente destruyeron el templ… https://t.co/bo58miHIFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IntegrityAct  Hi, can you please follow me back?  I would really appreciate it.  Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sophadelicc &amp; she changed her insta name booo I wanted to go stalk her page lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That’s right &amp; he should be ashamed for telling them such.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Friday! Grab a cup of coffee and come on by! Retail therapy is perfect for today! There’s plenty winter left!… https://t.co/kM2MTpHm8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why this crucifix wearing man who pushes his pillows on TV should not be given advertisement time late at n… https://t.co/K2j7G6Neyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is literally one of my fave songs and I was the happiest I’ve ever been hearing this. I just wanna go back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joneill55 @Cbp8Cindy @Starofthesea007 @thatsVeryKari @suziday123 @CaththeWineLady @SteveKubota @FionaMorgan79… https://t.co/c2aO3HqSuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hindsite20 @callistawolf @julieschultzsnp What I’ve been saying all along. OIiver is deep underground to fight Nin… https://t.co/o3jHb4B8IS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My stomachs lookin a little flat i better go hit up in n out for the second night in a row]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appropriations Chairman John Stinner said anyone on the committee could ask for reconsideration of the Tuesday Titl… https://t.co/pk1jgnCXaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coating of ice overnight @ Durham, Pennsylvania https://t.co/BStchPn6Aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[We 30 nigga don’t FaceTime at 4am with a stack of money to yo ear asking me what I’m doin 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am 7 months pregnant and have reached the stage where I watch krispy Kreme doughnut ads on YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scotttaylorva You are stunningly ignorant. You know there are already laws against infantcide. You cannot fathom t… https://t.co/1QC0UGAccH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in sharing a #randomcoffee with one of the fabulous @iuhealthlaw students? Let me or another… https://t.co/bovQv5BbPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@troy_andrea @AZRavers @AllTimeEDM @EDMSofa @Edmism @PreciousPetts @_madiixoxo_]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are a few great signs to look for when deciding to work with a realtor. BRE:01193021 #Realtor #RealEstate… https://t.co/ThDSX43dmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weights, Core and Plyometrics! #fitsciencellc #wnbf #wnbfpro #rgv #rgvcommunity #womenwholift #gymowner… https://t.co/MulbWszzHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[All about hospitality. ♥️ Leadership is about people. Period. Great leadership is about inspiring people.… https://t.co/xMfPQaRQvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting a new series where I’ll be tweeting quotes from my coworker Sarah who is a national treasure, scholar,… https://t.co/mYYkOcostM]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ve talked to me a handful on time so now I owe you nudes? Get the fuck out with your lame ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dior4sure @jordynwoods @khloekardashian I can see that angle, and many people do. They certainly know how to drum… https://t.co/lEJMUmEGAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this! I wish kids from 5th grade and beyond would start learning those soft skills— eye contact, handshake,… https://t.co/Qe2XpO2tVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EWErickson it was a stupid twit! You have a hard time not being #NeverTrumpers. Yes we heard all about your time w… https://t.co/e3OCXw0FX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greatstockpicks My suggestion is you apologize to me and we can both delete this thread immed after  ...That's fair to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basil is the most loved rat in the world 😂.  @taylor_bono and I will sitting in our office at work Me thinking: ooo… https://t.co/IdaCb6xdSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @Jack_Hartmann, for helping us master our coins with your catchy song!💰 🎶 #MoneyMoneyMoneyInMyPocket… https://t.co/YDW5L0Q2TQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black walnut hot fudge sundae from Franklin Fountain. Rich, nutty, and a little bitter just like me https://t.co/rEdnhbOfSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep half charging all of my technological devices then using them down to almost a dead battery and charging ove… https://t.co/xHdusIcG7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alternative headline: The Pentagon awarded Lockheed Martin $946 million for a missile defense system on behalf of t… https://t.co/dYUqERv4fQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“United”, I don’t think that word means what you think it means..  USA, UK...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner You should be proud of your strength and dedication. We're sure happy you're with us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted the challenge from @heartzcf to post the cover of 7 books I love - no explanations - just the cover… https://t.co/YyTySQA8y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[REMEMBER  #ZeroTolerance IS child abuse! @realDonaldTrump IS chief abuser! #reuniteFamiliesNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine if I had the power to control the voices in my head, and I could tell them all to shut the fuck up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ieJlqSMVs6 4:14 I bought the matress for you I seen it at the mall]]></document><document><![CDATA[has been a year already? went chitown for a concert but ended up falling in love with the city. tira.diyanni @ Chic… https://t.co/A3Q1IIzr8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jet Relays at Clark Stadium! Love track! @ Herman Clark Stadium https://t.co/GPBCqqu6jp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please take a moment to read❣️ Thankful my brother @BradSerf was at the “right place, right time”...most importantl… https://t.co/2qsIO7ZWLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me Mrs. Lucky ..WINNER WINNER!! First Round on me bruceslounge #CaLottery #Winner #Scratcher #TuesdayNight… https://t.co/rnMA8XrY5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Damn. Proud. This dog!? Is there nothing he can’t do?  Our very first Masters level @akcdoglovers Rally obedien… https://t.co/jbsoTKb3XK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extraño mucho a mis sobrinos , mi único deceo de cumpleaños seria verlos pronto ! 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drobinson018 @NatGeo @YosemiteNPS Any chance you bought it on our amazon 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernardGoldberg There's a whole world out there...for most of us. Some miss the train]]></document><document><![CDATA[God’s by side every step of the way. If he’s with me, who could be against me ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“His secret weapon, though, is taking premises that should no longer have any life in them and squeezing laughs fro… https://t.co/uQeiQbMwnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im hanging on by a thread.. and it’s sad people don’t see it, because if it mattered at all, things would be taken seriously and change...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith WRONG @stephenasmith @AB84 is to blame!! He put this mess on social media!! A man would’ve/should’ve… https://t.co/HbeSClIoIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day. Me and my girl starting off #SpringBreak2019 in a good way.. @ Gulf Shores, Alabama https://t.co/fCHQ9GZzzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes If at this time their naming all these priest for child abuse what are they not saying 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ha ha ha!😂. That is great! I don't know which is more ludicrous, Carmelo thinking he can dictate terms to anyone or… https://t.co/IZDrV9tlrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Everyone call all the representatives in the White House and everyone we need to go out and protest w… https://t.co/DofBmDvJUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HurdOnTheHill  I saw your name as one of Republicans that did not vote for a wall. I see your from Texas as I am.… https://t.co/6a2BZZmFr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1b. Take the time and look at my district's new vision/mission statement.  https://t.co/7C9sK4kyQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[America The Beautiful  @EdgarHinson  @111_princess111 @ShellyCov  @TAL05018381  @2020magacountry  @TPowersledge… https://t.co/itvaXBxlfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encore! Encore! If you already love #AStarIsBorn do not miss #AStarIsBornEncore the extra 12 minutes are “magical a… https://t.co/VayAP2RCSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBC 5 Forecast: More Clouds with Spotty Showers Possible  https://t.co/PdCtcYU5UR]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve had no energy to dress cute all i’ve been wearing is leggings and sweatshirts and u know what it’s okay i can’… https://t.co/1SP6E501UI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normal people: Me ranting about @GameOfThrones : https://t.co/s9PmYPfzJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Green Hive 3rd Year #greenhivespaces #vallejo #cochittafilms #celebration @ Green Hive Spaces https://t.co/j4b8wdTW16]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Joe Harris on winning the #MtnDew3PT but I have to correct you, it’s the University of North Carolina at Charlotte... 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW: City leaders sharing more details on this year’s St. Patrick’s Day celebrations. @WJCLNews https://t.co/CduRg8fLIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marshrau @wolfblitzer @realDonaldTrump He will save the offer not to run to negotiate leaving govt in exchange for… https://t.co/ZoHERpoLGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillHemmer After her upbringing and 24vyears in the United States, I believe she knows exactly what she's saying.… https://t.co/G6jGTdkKdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we please just have @VanessaVanjie narrate or commentate on everything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[No full article this week, but still plenty of impressive stat lines! https://t.co/gC45DfsHqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We didn’t even plan our perfect #FatTuesday color coordination!💚💛💜 https://t.co/z8qaGGAgA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GatodeMiel @KingLeahMay @TheGoldenBuda @MrWoodsMusic @caitlinnowens We are.  No argument with you.  We need to get… https://t.co/iStFfdurVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelSaxby2 Decorated my school folder with that picture!!  Great team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah you’re amazing. But nothing beats having someone warm you up at night whenever you need it🤷🏾‍♀️ distance ain’t worth it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m excited to try out @googletour builder with my class. It’s perfect for our Midwest US unit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to Mineral Monday.   What is cosmetic clay? So glad you asked...  Clay is the earthly material that results… https://t.co/ysMrwXmGSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how many teachers will be singing this in their heads this week...? 🤔🤣 #100thdayofschool   AJR - 100 Bad D… https://t.co/ghtZpm2MDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a student section on Tuesday! Let's get there Titan Nation!!!  💚💙 https://t.co/qIZ9PErtRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ghroehrig But were the able to resist eating the marshmallows? @ Stephanie Carlson and the late Walter Mischel wou… https://t.co/39ld1av1PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the amount of stress I'm under... that friggin hawaii trip couldn't come any sooner. Like.. idgaf about gradua… https://t.co/sMlYiUT4VA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next week is BOGO in dōTERRA land! Follow to get daily notifications!! 💜🌸 #doTERRA #fawningoveroils #oilymama… https://t.co/dXH2DgfsbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎨Dans quelques jours aura lieu le vernissage de l'exposition "Women in art" qui aura lieu le 9 mars de 19h à 22h. E… https://t.co/uiwnfXvKMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STOgonewild A SNOW DAY?!?  I am seeing it on my weather report right now. That shit had better stop by the time I… https://t.co/TyUlWjHhik]]></document><document><![CDATA[letsss be honest, why did we think anything we did in middle school was cool?😹😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting more jungley by the day 🌿🍃🌵🌱 @ Bradenton, Florida https://t.co/o4VhKGLpVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitfordBradley Truth , don’t trust this man . How can he still be in the same room with his wife?]]></document></documents></author>