<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m a Creator _____ @drinkripples  creative +tech =wow  #nylifestyleminute #ibm #ripplesofhappiness #drinkripples… https://t.co/YK3snq1n2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeezerGayle @TomLackey36 @ScottWilkCA @GavinNewsom Yay Gayle! See you in Sacramento next week! Xoxo from this… https://t.co/r8vVP6Z2EJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BubblesResists @FalResistsHate @otter272 @Back_dafucup @BannedDc @CanuckSassy @GotJanie @BIT_Spookery… https://t.co/0Xa4kGfBVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rave breaks over &amp; what’s better than hybrid being the one to commence the raving year???🕺🏼 @ The Happy Place https://t.co/qt3YfxrExc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well... Claire wouldn’t be the first crazy pyro 🧨 🔥 #Days has seen! 🤷🏼‍♀️ But, KM did it better 😏 and the circumsta… https://t.co/cwobsoq9LC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so scared but my shorty is solid 💪💪💪 just gotta keep that in mind. She’s a fighter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeHayes61 @kk_ki37844976 @thehill Mike, how do you know what the Mullah’s teach?  It’s like a Muslim telling you… https://t.co/SXh7C4FbKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe  me..SM SHALL get his.  Why?  For every action there is an equal and opposite reaction!  Imagine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember freshman year Spring 2017, 33 inches in TWO DAYS RITA! and you still didn’t cancel classes, just had a “… https://t.co/yE1bSeXjkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is rewatching/bingeing @arresteddev ever a bad idea? #bigplans #ineedsnacks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You wouldn’t know if it’s a good book you can’t read stick to your pop up books]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haj_lynn Me waiting those extra sec/min because my class is on the 5th floor and I’m not trying to die from them s… https://t.co/AIyHzf88uH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready with my BeastMode gear for when the Raiders get to Las Vegas!!   Text me if you are in Las Vegas and want… https://t.co/tc4FG4d0ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Canadian_Heathn Good call! I was thinking baseboards but this is a way better idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re a communist POS abortion is not health care. Give up your sports car and your houses you Socialist 🐖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/5Zy2VAUyEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS : @AbeShinzo is on line. Tomorrow I will be in Washington DC for public policy event: Challenges of UN on Pe… https://t.co/sYE8vyLdOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Because that was the right thing to do. This country needs ICE, Ice is vital to our country and always… https://t.co/kFQxaRjSi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt_bang22 @syd_vicous @emohleee @kaylafacedd @wiffanytood15 @Lane8music @shelbybrieanne Oakland&gt;LA 😉😉😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@demonrobber Alberta Canada .... found the pic wasn’t there ... unfortunately]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor people culture is asking everyone at your lunch table if they want your applesauce because you feel bad throwing food out :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you find it hard to start or finish projects? This article is applicable to anyone.… https://t.co/d04ejg8T9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giants' CEO Larry Baer Under Investigation For Domestic Violence by MLB https://t.co/D8qWKk6uVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love to support my Girl Scout family! I always try to stop to say HI to every scout selling cookies. This group j… https://t.co/4ONc8hBZcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funnygirlescope @AbigailPrestri1 @GOPChairwoman I’ve been shadow-banned a million Times. I was suspended for 2 wee… https://t.co/8MCPmXy0sE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Lehman is doing great work.  All this will lead to finding more cancers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @TuckerCarlson always has a constipated look on his face, squinted eyes like he's bearing down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 @BarbaraHaysSmi1 Did anyone ever think more immigrants are coming over the border because they are al… https://t.co/q3W7qjArTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDebD @thehill @AOC Let's start with the missing million from her campaign money! #lockupaoc https://t.co/VnozphpsHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealBPhil The fact is, they need X number of people to sling the hash needed to make money. They weren’t overstaff… https://t.co/IfEfmsWtGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scooby_Do7 lmfaoo nigga not offensive , nigger is super racist but COON ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ApplebyCollege students and staff dressing down in purple to raise funds to help battle eating disorders, supporti… https://t.co/ptuXDvhSVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never understand how one day you love someone to the next you don’t feel a thing...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out "SoGal NYC: Build Your Brand with Cindy Gallop" https://t.co/M5IV1sVMw8 @Eventbrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 So  very sorry about your suffering. I hope those days are behind you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me head banging to casual affair not 30 minutes after i was sick and couldn't see mere inches in front of me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally made it to @MeanGirlsBway  Worth the wait! 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼 https://t.co/hfnBj055Zr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colombi88700044 Esa mujer me da pena de verdad ! Es una asquerosa la Iris de Venezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennyblanco1966 @atenciodari Señor, le expliqué nuestras fronteras con Costa Rica y Colombia, nuestro Canal, que t… https://t.co/Bx8oGUBuu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Kingdom of Heaven is like treasure in a field, which someone found and hid. Them in his joy he goes and sells a… https://t.co/GxDloUrMoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pfwd @mattcutts This proves my point: “...websites use the up arrow for upload.” A paper clip is used to attach on… https://t.co/aRWyWVc0cX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful advice John. Now if I can make myself follow it. @johncloonan #WorkLifeBalance #wisdom #worktrends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow Supershuttle has some serious nerve calling me at 3a for my 5:45a pick up 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can the Dodgers Sign Bryce Harper already. They have the money, do this for the Fans!! #Harper #MLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[AYYYYYYEEEEE!!! Liz gets a HAT TRICK and it’s 12-10 https://t.co/YsG4Rryxpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t sleep. but i’m TIREDT. but i also know if i take my meds, i’ll be asleep for the next 4 days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[yerrrr i just got a fire idea for how to set up the Shawn Mendes ticket giveaway 🔥👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got this girl! That’s how I was feeling earlier, but I ended up loving mine! Pick that brush up!💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put your lifebelts on!!!    It’s like rats running off a sinking ship!  @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse     #LockHimUp… https://t.co/SGWR6KnfQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Vonore #TN  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/qhg4ZjF1It]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom asked me what I was doing for V Day... 🍕😂 #BadAtSelfies #AndLove https://t.co/woiZxQ7sT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kjpilcher Those are some seriously awesome films. Have you seen the movie #SaintJudy yet? That one has fought its… https://t.co/qAOgkjNZoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreeformTV https://t.co/L3SJAGLeRZ s VALENTINES daY erYdaY 😒🛩️👨‍👨‍👧‍👦🔥🎗️🌤️🏁🛌🚪🚅⛄️📗🌈🌇💚📗💸😒📱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jake_bummy7 i punched ur head, knocked u down w one hit, and stood over ur little girly ass. you will not fight me… https://t.co/djhh4HE8tS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank You @UnitedWayMiami For All You Give Back To Our Students &amp; Community! @UnitedWayMiami @HMLAdultEd… https://t.co/QqAGQFRNeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi Madame Speaker, why isn’t there a resolution condemning racism? This would be geared toward Represen… https://t.co/PVoLATRWyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kiehlsboy @stareagle @realDonaldTrump I remember trump saying during an interview that he fired Comey because of t… https://t.co/wiMSOteFJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@truffledelder It is illegal.what mercer hodak and musk and zuck..and the robotic guys do..I call them them turtle… https://t.co/fvJnyeunOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The meat offering and the drink offering is cut off from the house of the LORD; the priests, the LORD'S ministers,… https://t.co/LCoggHxhw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAKE UP AND SHARE BAE 💋💓 https://t.co/LzGmP6jR2C @ Stockton, California https://t.co/IBpyr09vh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[i may look like a potato now, but one day i'll be fries and you'll want me then 🍟💕 https://t.co/axaoXlUWGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#protectivestyles #naturalhairgoals #naturalhairjunkie #naturallyshedope #hair #updo #twostrandtwist #braids… https://t.co/FuZic4epgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickDrayton1 @TamarBraxtonHer YES SHE DOES..   SHE IS HORRIBLE... Messing with Gods anointed is no joke..  She is… https://t.co/KVUKzi9m5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharlimae And honestly those types usually think about bucking more. Its eaiser to have a fast transition from sad… https://t.co/FX2k0HbIFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buffalojilll @distracdad As a Karen born in 64 I can tell you it was a very popular baby name in the 60s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jim Casey would have liked this quote...so do I. https://t.co/kQKAPgVJgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EternLRage @AllVape3 @james_bong13 @stonervswrld @Godzmazter @808KushBoys @xStonerGirls @HiHappyHungry… https://t.co/tBwQ0IehcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends Bongino works for the NRA. @FoxNews should not be permitted to use the word news in… https://t.co/1kaOfOIswi]]></document><document><![CDATA[them: put your hands up if you’re ready for spring break me: 🙋🏼‍♀️ @ Frankenmuth, Michigan https://t.co/VLkH8eJalb]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your bestie works at Modells and hooks you up with a Harper shirt 🥰 #phillies #bff @bryceharper3 @Phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter empezará a hablar de fútbol, debería de ausentarme el día de hoy 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_harmony73 @CommishOnline The people who owned before us did it themselves and it’s all pieced together 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quad meet time at Denver #PioneerTogether #du #gymnastics https://t.co/LkNqJocnPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rp_griffin @JohnHolbein1 I desperately want an invitation to this. Please tell me you've watched Occupation on Netflix. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity I know!  I wonder if the Radical Left Propaganda Media will give it the 24/7 coverage they give to everyone else he praises]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is the beach robe I was sewing on Stories leading up to my beach get-away. ✂️  I had been sharing the progress… https://t.co/oguBeIBLT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday’s palette includes bougainvilleas, adding some color to your hump day 🌈   #humpday #miami #bougainvillea… https://t.co/Lx7emcxuRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best friend would’ve forgiven you for me but don’t got one no more so fuck you! And your dumbass forgiveness!!!!… https://t.co/LmEC5PwxE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just FaceTimed alessia to tell her happy birthday lmao. we live together... @arichmond__]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinsley is a powerhouse! @EVJVolleyball 10R1 #GameDay https://t.co/0rCKORGiSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love being able to share these family moments!   #studentmidwife #familycenteredcare #bigsister  #bigbrother… https://t.co/m8zXspS6FR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaynaDunphy HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!! I hope you have a great day! Sending big hugs! 🤗♥️🎉🤗😘 https://t.co/EHulU5xBse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pompanostrappo @PreetBharara Yeah, we don't use that but dived is definitely in common usage. That sounds wrong to… https://t.co/WFvd8vxixk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Math 9-12 friends, the coherence map is ready! https://t.co/JF3scSIA0d Find pre-req and related standards: useful i… https://t.co/oNFSEWjv6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davematt88 Exactly. It's using the tools given to us by our founding fathers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiyyahlong Look at how the average man view women 🤷🏽‍♀️ I used to be so against that shit but standing up for thes… https://t.co/Tr1ilGT5da]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that I've calmed down, accepted into the University of Iowa's Librarian Science School.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacquel14277925 @unapproachable @LoganMurphy1 @RepMaxineWaters @HillaryClinton @JussieSmollett… https://t.co/khkSAD8Rvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatkid_laur @rhianaspence 😂😂 I’d get kicked off *normally* on the first episode. But after this season, all i got… https://t.co/6ROCTkfBPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[hmmm i have a gynecology appointment an hour after i get my wisdom teeth out tomorrow,,, i'm,,]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lashes #lashextensions #lashesbystephanieh #dolleyeslashes #madisonlashes https://t.co/GteF0Ufbz7 @ Doll Eyes Lash… https://t.co/XNJRgysoL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#teatime I hope everyone is having an amazing Sunday 💫 https://t.co/k2CBfiGSPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epcot with my favorite guy! 🥰 #justinandmichaela2017 #epcot #disney #disneyworld #waltdisneyworld… https://t.co/jMDT1IJdEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/MSYf882NKh  If this happens!?  I will be convinced that my country 🇺🇸 is out to destroy 😔 ALL wildlife… https://t.co/ytMPZkBb0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HONKYTONKINTUNE Well in all honesty I feel like a lot of adults can be a lil dyslexic. It happens to me lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atlanta you’ve been a beaut ❤️ but now to head back home 🇬🇧 https://t.co/BIORXR36TU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wild Strawberries and Brambles #foxyandwinston #customletterpressdesign #strawberries #brambles #thankyoucards @ Hi… https://t.co/Ce0u3rx36X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I always do this to myself? I will never learn 🙄 https://t.co/tb5F5Zkh5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TarpeoDesiree I'm so sorry your Mom broke her leg! What happened? That's bad and takes a long time to heal. On the… https://t.co/f637JROU0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many maple bacon 🥓 donuts can one person eat before their flight?? 🤔 #charlestoneats @ Glazed Gourmet Doughnuts https://t.co/HR2Svijq4O]]></document></documents></author>