<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If the Seaver Statue has been in the plans for this year,I assume that the Statue of Gil Hodges will also be done b… https://t.co/j46Dy3njK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @WilliamsCollege ! You gave me all of the opportunities in the world, and provided the tools to help me t… https://t.co/H0YVldfNya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espn played an entire @ESPNLunardi segment during the #KStateMBB game and forgot to turn up his volume...😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[she had nothing to do with it”. I wanted no trouble for my wife. I protected her even aware that the police officer… https://t.co/9xpFapBG74]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas Bound next week #SXSW #festival #ListenToYourOGs #liveperformance @ Downtown Detroit https://t.co/8elchaXA5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ShallowIsNumberOneParty streaming Gaga all evening to cele 😌 https://t.co/MHXKuvhLDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great family dinner at @texasroadhouse tonight until they chose not to honor the kids eat for $0.99 special t… https://t.co/vUOGyuYYmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it true countries in Asia throw babies in the river if they’re a girl or is it’s always sunny in Philadelphia lying to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please post the senators that don’t vote to protect them! We’d like to know whom is a disgusting a**hole so we can… https://t.co/8vYXIfBo2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please ... somebody ... make sure all the info comes out ... Like stars Clinton report]]></document><document><![CDATA[For me to become more approachable I’m just commenting on more and more insta stories 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second straight season Lonzo has missed major time due to some injuries! Damn I’m blaming Luke Walton for this bull… https://t.co/80zFFKFSz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the GOP ship slowly sinks into the sunset...  The 7 most bizarre moments from Trump’s long-winded CPAC rant… https://t.co/1VPBdRH5kd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am blocked by @_BigBen7  Sucks to be him, I tweet high quality stuff!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jade_cabochon7 @TxSBJunkie @p0cketfullasuns @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse I have no dought you are… https://t.co/NyYF4frNQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Cleveland is a #winter beauty on #LakeErie. #ThisIsCle #Ohio #Waterfront #NorthCoast https://t.co/SLwoRZiKOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[You greedy, greedy man. Amazon will pay $0 in taxes on $11,200,000,000 in profit for 2018 https://t.co/CFK4wjA0mj via @YahooFinance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come out for food, fun, heritage, and culture. #fergflorschools #onedistrictunited… https://t.co/8XC1YhwZuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President, we are NOT the envy of the world. Anything but. You embarrass the basic American pr… https://t.co/fBpV5wehI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skull  #illustration #art #sketch #artdirection #draw #doodle #scribble #far-out #retro #skull #funny #head… https://t.co/EButwIZ8eW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fordnation @unitedconvoy Ahhh NO DOUGIE!!! You want to live in Trumplandia, f#ckin move there...and take your bull… https://t.co/dByElhV5CR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard Work Beat By #AnnoDomination by PhillyBlunt2000 https://t.co/NVqYjQ92cR @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Belie… https://t.co/YFgMNUo1fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Galliano and the other bear... #beardporn #beard #muscle #musclecouple #swole #swolemates #tattoo #beardandmuscles… https://t.co/CAZUua3LLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Niagara Falls, Ontario, Canada https://t.co/Bg8EcSET7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarleyShimkus C a r l e y thank you for the beautiful photo and for your Tweet you're a very beautiful lady and yo… https://t.co/lDpRic4CeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchroedervilleA here's a follow-up on the Hollister Ranch beach access story... https://t.co/I6JLPaGxMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[To paraphrase #CarlJung:  “Love [of #entrepreneurship] is empty without thinking, thinking hollow without love [of… https://t.co/fQvlemx5ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbrins @ABC Oh someone disagrees with you? Construction materials are racist!? Right!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simon had a big bag of candy from his Valentine’s Day party. I can’t put in words what it was like to see him walk… https://t.co/MyI1vQ6ZjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonGandy @RexHoggardGC Great for that guy! All the props in the world. Does he play in competitions? If not play… https://t.co/X0D36VQjcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thing I wasn’t there I woulda been right in the middle on a knee 😂💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[That #allstars4 finale felt right... even though it should’ve been Manila #TeamManila]]></document><document><![CDATA[@royse_dana yeah a blameless life  just when you think it can`t get any lower]]></document><document><![CDATA[Notes:  Students not demonstrating learning is not proof it hasn’t been taught.   Anecdotes neither prove nor dispr… https://t.co/U9ipnc2vXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[ஏசாயா 33:21-23  Tamil Bible:    21-23 ஏனென்றால் அங்கே வல்லமையுள்ள கர்த்தர் இருக்கிறார். அந்த நாடானது ஓடைகளும் அகன்ற… https://t.co/WRYTOwpIAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@douglasturtle @ErinLovesNYY @OldTakesExposed Yes keep an eye on our accounts...because we cant speak our minds and… https://t.co/Y9jmlx3Hnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Feisty_FL Not even close. Not one leader in the bunch. Leaders own their responsibilities.  They blame others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dking1108 I always thought the best comp for Sexton was a worse eric Bledsoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTSUNews Lord, please protect, not only the students, but the computers and studios! Seriously! 🤗  Amen... 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear man if someone gets fired from their job because marijuana was the only drug that popped up on their drug t… https://t.co/TkVes7M1lD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naretevduorp MAGA = hate  MAGA IS HATE.  MAGA = Fox News  Fox News = hate  No matter how you add it up, MAGA equal… https://t.co/rTn3B8KkLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[they do have something in common. They will@get paid a lot of $$ and won’t win anymore rings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenApp @lizgross144 @mjpowers @tracyplayle I offer outs bc I don’t really (ever) karaoke. Also Edinburgh is on… https://t.co/xeyIwoaXmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Linda65542703 @MSNBC @mitchellreports Allright now, in fact it's a gazzz. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeshiaClukey @mkink @BloombergBNA We look forward to welcoming you back home]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz Valentin`s Day!! Viva el amor!! en New York, New York https://t.co/l2F8y0I9Kg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump boasts of himself as the hero of the troops but he is gladly sacrificing new service member housing, schools… https://t.co/QtfT9Q88PH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Double #dragon  Appointments: dustin@soldermonster.com  _________________________________________ #soldermonster… https://t.co/65oG1J62N1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Politics for all: A rampant anti corruption bill pushing harsh prison penalties for lobbyist revolvin… https://t.co/xsg3nb0ZWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats of today are”Epitome of Evil”!They generally agree that it is acceptable to kill babies that survive abor… https://t.co/zyTueid83S]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CBJ gifted a pair of odd-man breaks and don’t get a quality chance due to over-passing]]></document><document><![CDATA[These guys are so pathetic. They try so hard and yet getting shut down at every turn. I'm starting to feel bad for… https://t.co/TCgVdp0MuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elvis! #waterfront#oceanfront#beachfront#obx#outerbanks#obxlocals#realestate#beach#bulldog#bulldogsofinstagram#pitb… https://t.co/ShYhfuXpxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Polaris #polarisindy #polarisindysp #polarisindy600sp #polarissnow #michigan #puremichigan #snowmobile #snow @ New… https://t.co/F6ksDEiQLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakeDaveHageman They're doing worse than the NHL, where Dirk Graham coached the Blackhawks in 1998.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment you realize it’s a “walk two miles in the snow and hope the commuter rail is running okay” kinda day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Centro #fotostumblr #likeforlikes #followforfollowback #cuu #chihuahua #mexico #ocio #travel #travelphotography… https://t.co/GPsLcIff8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awaiting briefing from @LVMPD on the discovery of a 2-year-old’s body and injured woman. Live report on @8NewsNow a… https://t.co/DHl1JSm7F0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s get after it and kick this Monday’s ass. Here’s to you having a BIG start to your week. Head down, crushing i… https://t.co/rPcypRz1mJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @PrommyseHoosier well deserved! Now let’s get this outdoor season going! ❤️👑🎊🎉👏🏾👍🏾💪🏽✊🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Detroit! :) #Sunrise 06:56, noon 12:43, sunset 18:30 EST (UTC-5), March 8. Day length: 11h 34m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder how SDNY feels about having to share offispace with mob criminals]]></document><document><![CDATA[I plan on going nude on Omegle during the summer time, do you think I should invite the girl that sold me candies?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLCnotUTAH @BrettCainBooks @JReubenCIark @molly_moo_who @excesstential @Matt____FL @byu_sports7 @drisalys Oh yeah… https://t.co/gxroZVosPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Electroneum mobile mining going well, over halfway to my first payout #ETN #Electroneum #CryptoMining #crypto… https://t.co/QOACCppKIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bailey_marieee_ Going vegetarian is not  reducing the methane gas  output if anything it’s increasing 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a hawks fan. Although between the guy sitting 2 feet to my right announcing the game like he is the color comm… https://t.co/bgFEz7Iky8]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@JohnBKing cites @CollegeOpp’s report citing the obscene number of Black students who start at a for-profit instit… https://t.co/jN6SJv5vVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bmac0507 @benshapiro T.D.S is a condition that rots any cognitive function that processes reasoning and logic. It… https://t.co/9OMyDk9ULD]]></document><document><![CDATA[How long will we the people sit knowingly to the treason and tyranny from D.C. and do nothing? The Enemy is at the… https://t.co/MPp8WXg8zx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@don_chamuco @aguila88888 Ahhhh ...... Pensé que le contestaba mal Vero a Epigmenio (no los arrobo, pues queiro seg… https://t.co/LeDkdWIbQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay Texas spring break is in 3 weeks so get your shit together and let the weather warm up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had take my wedding ring off can not stand it on with my RSD/CRPS burning stinging cramping feels like its eating a… https://t.co/AJyg7s0Adz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IAMUP Does “Oat Meal” count in the cereal category? #favoritecereal @SoniaAzadTV  #healthy Otherwise, LIFE or Capt… https://t.co/5GqCEFD39t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArcherBM @FPGarvin @realDonaldTrump ... and thirdly, any crimes discovered in the course of the investigation. Thi… https://t.co/GmrBUYwsIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GingerWesson @ohsteezus1 @RepublicNOLA You’re the best for this !  See u at BUKU 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP What a ripoff copyright theft anyone call a lawyer Hillary you been ripped off @HillaryClinton]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation @LindseyGrahamSC @margbrennan Lindsey, your closet is calling...it wants you OUT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1nu_jesus Nothing counts...it’s spring but they were still great for an inning and a half]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my classmates are still popping babies out. I can't imagine that anymore! 10+ years of not getting pregnant 😂🥂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JJStempalooza is well underway!  Chemical reaction, matter conservation lessons, and chemical reaction vehicle des… https://t.co/ilHyDuRZCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Variety I’m going to pretend he won an #Oscars for the #MrRobot motion picture right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nosferatusaint @ZeroCarbSarah We managed to survive &amp; thrive for millions of years eating #Meat but now… https://t.co/Nx5CaAIjVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep It Simple. "Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication."-Leonardo da Vinci https://t.co/6yfrjb9dyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chameleon876 @JanetJackson Now they tryin to drag her and say he is not biologically hers smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @KirstyDuncanMP for cheering on FIRST robotics teams at Humber College this weekend and for visiting the… https://t.co/Qi6yybCg1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliVelshi Why did you call the Valenzuela army “forces loyal to Maduro”? You wouldn’t refer to any other nation’s… https://t.co/U3PGSJGOIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wizarding world of @PepperellEddie: The story of a prank, a pair of socks, and trying understand America https://t.co/cFGdMiVEe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UlisesM127 @VexaIG @FortniteGame That area of Junk and the little village used to be so OP.  For an area I mean. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to say this over and over. I'm a mathematician and a university professor and I support trans and non-binary… https://t.co/0qIijn5Dta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz you make it even harder to be a republican when you tweet way below your position.  Hope you are held accountable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxnewspolitics Nepotist Wallace rivals Smith for made up criticism.  Guess he doesn't trust his son/ daughter-in-… https://t.co/6tYGZPJiYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRamirez01 Bro we were up there. Stop spreading fake news. @chrisrios33 @TilmanJFertitta https://t.co/hV0w8ekKyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing these @HandmaidsOnHulu folks walking around #Toronto is a tad unsettling #WelcomeToGilead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeawackDanBlake @charliekirk11 @AOC I know my place, unlike others. @AOC is a disgrace to the latino community and a sham in congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It took mankind thousands of years to realize that the Moon was the logical target for manned spaceflight. Once ma… https://t.co/TkVPX0gL7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our goofball Democrat “governor” talking about how she had to remove National Guard troops at our border. It was ca… https://t.co/ffD0oVG6XQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@polinchock @master_deli @RossBarkan @maggieNYT @AOC I wonder how eager a lot of people in Seattle were willing to… https://t.co/i0O1aWwXrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoboNoire @DanTresOmi I say, and more often write, "black," or "African American." "People of color" is very broad and vague.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Transitions by @heistbox is one of the smoothest songs I've heard in a while, that coupled with dope lyricism, this… https://t.co/89k4CnTfet]]></document></documents></author>