<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[happy Thursday brothers and sisters peace be with all #0nelove  .@78sVintagemusic https://t.co/B4lvJTgovL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewFromPerth Switch countries for the next two years? I’ll live in Perth and you live in Cleveland.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #IT jobs like "Information Security - L2 SOC Analyst" at Cognizant in #Aurora, CO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madShana @nysportsfan2015 @NickM538 @G792Mike @LifeGal4 @Zalman888 @DiStitz @JenDeach88 @Amber00924 @EastBhamKid… https://t.co/DHqfy256mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep playing games and I’ll take your ass to get endless breadsticks at Olive Garden]]></document><document><![CDATA[And finally, day 7 of #7BooksILove. Thanks for prompting me to do this, @Juliedewidt and @SusanWTurnbull. Now I tag… https://t.co/wAbxeRobhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markwahlberg I miss those dances.  I have 3 girls.  I’m envious.    Don’t let go of these moments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good: Blast liquefaction × 1,000,000 Bad: Test to figure out how to kill a whole bunch of folks  On balance: Its fe… https://t.co/7lyKy7uwNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealitySteve LesA-Lph          AmeR-ica            ACI-REMA            AC I--------R:EMA              Amer-ica… https://t.co/A8n4nVas7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BGoodeWAVE3 That’s really going to mess up all the people headed down for Thunder today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The New York Town that Tried to Join the Confederacy and Didn’t Surrender Until 1946 https://t.co/UEZskpZSyz via @AppalachianMag]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been raining so much in So Cal, that I literally have flora popping up in my backyard that I’ve never seen bef… https://t.co/OWH7E8gh52]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to my @UniNoticias colleagues @almudenatoral, @andreapatinoc, @mrodpons! It was a pleasure working with yo… https://t.co/p5IbyrHC4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spittinchiclets @ryanwhitney6 @BizNasty2point0 i need multiple ppl in boston to have their dogs shit on RA’s yard.… https://t.co/sfT4NjYNeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex32059821 @AlexCobb_ XLM Volume Is Way Down As Well... Is Something Afoot???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetsKickASS_Or Is This why?  #ConspiracyExposedTerminatesASAP link: https://t.co/yUicPFWG8N https://t.co/1t91u2aRqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eli_vgkbolts00 @JeffWaddilove I appreciate the passion to live as a non-racist human-being, bt why the outrage/def… https://t.co/cZcpXT6C2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulShortino @BLABBERMOUTHNET Agree totally. Just like we have been taught when we were growing up by teachers, pr… https://t.co/IrWqxkp7ZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ENBrown You’ve heard of the show Naked &amp; Afraid, but have you heard of Fat Libertarians, Naked &amp; Afraid?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miakmrdn @Stallion2011 @bolam12 @thomasneate2 @KTHopkins @liv_XR05 Hygiene is your friend,we don’t live in the dar… https://t.co/Q0l8pFmhid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ So the adult proponents are using kids to get their arguments heard under the guise of a school project. Shady but effective.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@all_eyezonmi @GhostOfTick @Hybrid1979 @r0xie_f0x @joanne48640679 @FREETOMMY8 @Lo_Gannicus @conservativeLe5… https://t.co/OBoT1m5I4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robpizzola @IslesMike82 @EthanGSN So basically what your saying. Is there so much better than. Your top 10 they wi… https://t.co/bmZDbqK9xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CALVINKLEIN‼️CONGRATS @DesireQMia‼️ for calvinklein SS19 📸lachlanbailey 👔georgecortina 💆🏽‍♂️shayashual 💄… https://t.co/z6gtPHe35H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarwindawkinsS @tictoc Hey... we at least agree on no abortions after 23 weeks. And babies feel pain at 20 weeks s… https://t.co/cNKXlcloam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Most ill informed and worst President in US history.....and it's not even close! #presidentputz… https://t.co/Il3MBd368p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quimdomenech No Quim, ya viene El Salvador Vinicius, el que es mejor que Messi y el Madrid se hará con esta liga y… https://t.co/cbI43s8OBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’ve ever told a lie on the fly, this is the face you make.  https://t.co/z5DpimSpNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the truth that, while some of us will lust after it, the Green New Deal will not pass the Senate. Harsh reali… https://t.co/mhVBUAGQX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a suspicion that it is Ashley.  She is supposed to come back.  It is time for Kyle to do something right and… https://t.co/a8lARBFVDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once you find a couple people that are like you more follow it's so weird lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnieDonwerth_C Some great thinking shared on Somewhere Among. https://t.co/jLG6ymXG6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HybaxKWP2y This GOVERNOR is DESTROYING  New York GREEDY DEMOCRATS  IT SEEM THAT NEW YORK IS FOLLOWING BANKRUPTCY CALIFORNIA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ford to Procure Locally Sourced Michigan Wind 👍 https://t.co/liMEvUrqKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PGillySuarez @darrenrovell Nike don’t want you.....you better light a flame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Do you even understand how tarriffs work? The big brain from Wharton is auch a simple man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRaDR An awesome reminder that every moment is a gift, and we must be wise with how we use it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheChrisDuarte https://t.co/e8rjg9wOIs   Hi $ChrisD  Have a favor to ask.    -Steve  $ChrisD = @TheChrisDuarte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TinaCharlesTV @TheresaKereakes @TheMockNash @tonymartino1 @ManeetChauhan Hated It!  ✌🏼♥️ https://t.co/7cki46l2cu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PennyJJerald @SethMacFarlane Loving the new episode of #TheOrville so far. And that's US retired navy sailor approved!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmytotheO @PressSec @realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump Your the one that's an embarrassment to our country !!! BLOCKED !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are a college student and are arrested for any reason. You should lose your educational funding and be dismi… https://t.co/TnFPULRD00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ji_Predicciones @jguaido Guaido no debe estar en si casa y debe de resguardarse bien no es fácil es una lucha titánica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chief45Beast walk down to @OsteriaMarco and eat dinner. It's incredible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uneverthoughtov @StefanMolyneux The caricatures put them selves up. It's no crime yo notice them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aquela saudade...🗽🇺🇸 em Statue Of Liberty, Liberty Island, New York City https://t.co/rjwoRtz8op]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moments after a 76-52 victory over Northern Illinois, the Central Michigan women’s basketball team is giving back.… https://t.co/VELLwsTJqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure to have @FlowingWithPod blasting when you buy a paper from Josh this morning. New episode out now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmehrler What if there was a couples bachelor? You and nick are the main couple. Other couples try to win your fri… https://t.co/hLGXq1uIO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kids of Anti-vaxxers do not need to go to school, the measles gonna get them way before math class]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGlingeanu @mjackson I went through a very methodical process on All of my playlists names 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuck it the snow. Need to throw the ball sidearm so it does not sink. These 3 do well of that happens since they h… https://t.co/h1yH41wmsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EgyptianWisdom @IronCobra انتو الاتنين متدلعين امال انا اعمل اية بقالي  ٣ شهور في الغم دة]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melrosemomof3 @AustinPrepAD @photog24 @HumboldtBroncos @AustinPrep @AustinPrepGHoc @MassHSHockey @BostonHeraldHS… https://t.co/9O0jrDqBUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CBJ go on the power play after Shaw is boxed for high sticking Harrington. Those two players then drop the gloves]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Youngvers123 @Hotgaymen4 @SRhyheim @xBRUCEJACKSONx @HotMaleStuds @pman43 @paupratodahora @LUCAS__LUCASS… https://t.co/8FXGFe6fj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united gotta tell you the A320 seats were not great. 6 ft tall and headrest not even close.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pennstateWREST hey penn State wrestling. Any give aways prior to senior day match for fans to know about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#snow #storm starts in #newyork   #newyorkcity #snowstorms #snowstorm2019 @ New York, New York https://t.co/y5vuFIia4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biggnm73 @boltback2SD Funny because we did🏈 seen a few , support the #SD #Fleet or nah?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSU_Basketball @NaismithTrophy This seems like a no brainer. Lost 2 players to the NBA, 2 more future draftees dur… https://t.co/gd6L9Royni]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mayor’s new scheme for top NYC schools is illegal and racist: https://t.co/SNv0lpaIjC Where there are great cit… https://t.co/Fhhoo7qCcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilvirgogrl Overlord, the Witch, Evil Dead (2013), IT (2017), Suspiria (2018), As Above So Below, The Cabin in the Woods]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter Maybe “Mr Big Chest” would like to buy this house on Mars 👽  https://t.co/QpMDKXBRhN https://t.co/jUUUNMijrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RitaGamer If it gets to bad come to America I'm looking at moving to Austin Texas in the next year I miss it down there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it the moniker? San Fran Friends better? Pacific Pals? Silicon Valley... Chums?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ Considering ONE of the people in that image is supposed to be an actor on Empire? That doesn't bode well for J… https://t.co/MbXMtCNr6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[take time to smile. Cats through the ages. via Buzzfeed, but credit goes to "cat versus human" comic. which is... https://t.co/PQm1bzPMVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGreatFeather @Breaking911 Anyone else and it would have been a “hate” charge??? INCREDIBLE!!!! 😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[You better believe this playlist is radiating through my apartment on this WFH snow day. 🔑♥️ https://t.co/PPMgvynFTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[lost my keys snowboarding today and some actually found them in 4 feet of snow.. what is life?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandThompson16 @TMruczinski @marty713 @RandPaul @realDonaldTrump @GOP Libertarians have a false construct that equ… https://t.co/vL90vmaWDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of Krafts spokespersons denied the allegations, but apparently there’s video evidence of the acts performed. It… https://t.co/hbos86L33x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MistyDragon Definitely... And Flagstaff, AZ just picked up over 32" of snow.  Crazy weather 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Please provide evidence of bribery, high crimes or misdemenors. Until this is brought forth, no basis exists for impeachment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[politics angle: Andrew Yang’s appearance on Joe Rogan was #3 podcast on iTunes this week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pocahontas_kiki I agree with him doing everything he did... I just feel that his whole career was created to take… https://t.co/7g98lEzvJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bill_Kurelic @Bucknuts247 Ohio State is allways looking for future NFL players]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlchemyMd Was the MD really a peer? I start off by asking if they are a board-certified urologist. If they are not… https://t.co/vhf6yuyDzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too windy to go outside but the view from the top of the #stratospherelasvegas was amazing. #vegasrealness #sincity… https://t.co/J1WsrTtYBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@proudliberalmom @ThAlMeArCrEq @Madt44491145 @johncardillo @Acosta @CNN @sabine_durden And why hasn’t Congress done… https://t.co/roYG9wKl7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[ISIS Bride’s Father Sues Trump for Blocking Her Return to U.S. https://t.co/VnfkMDnGax wow some people have a lot of gall!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sandy George started the Al Gordon 4 Mile! https://t.co/6Ff6U1a59a #AlGordon4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE CAN LET AMERICAN STANDARD LAWS AND CONSTITUTION DECIDE. IF THEY ARE LEGAL MARRIAGE TRUTH JUSTICE ABSOLUTE AMERIC… https://t.co/SUrhWBdrPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The word of the day is #gray. It describes both the weather and my feelings for it. #RainRainGoAway https://t.co/BGSBr6BrOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA I dont believe I have ever saw her to ever have anything good to say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super Saturday QB Grind session w 2023 scott.saylor.11 of Ten Oaks Middle headed to Carolina Forest High back on th… https://t.co/HIDRsMjBGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaBissett Paul Conner I am single and stay alone in a town called Hepihizabah Georgia ladies I am tired of being… https://t.co/okusNrOIaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what I’ll make sure I’m okay and work hard, but shoot this ain’t an easy part of my life. I’ll continuously progress forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrKhiLavene @ImBRUCEJACKSON I just keep thinking about what west said to him lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juan came to the U.S. on a tourist visa in 2018. A young man from Venezuela - a country currently going through one… https://t.co/L0snX7nHga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dseLIVEtrader Chaplin does DSE! NO STUNTS? Gist  is indexes headed down soon to initial support green box before a… https://t.co/fWIU4jCybf]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to two people I’ve spoken with, the New Jersey Purse Subsidy bill has been signed into law by Governor Murphy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHosford1 So cynical, Chris. Why, I'm shocked! It's almost as if he was positioning himself for the new job long b… https://t.co/5IsyGuGYGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫I Don't Wanna by @aaliyahhaughton, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/qzqWyZelQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThePassage If @FOXTV doesn't #RenewThePassage there will be hell to pay!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clarencehilljr @awTide Imagine saying no to $20.5 million dollars for 1 year...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edhollett yup. they were going to get rid of him ASAP. after he pulled back the curtain... his RNC days were numbe… https://t.co/YiCHh7J27m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meadow1927 yesterday we had 4.65" of rain bringing our YTD total to 45.32" That also puts us right around 20" for… https://t.co/PO9ah2Ruj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bluehasia @AmericanAir @anthrocon Have you thought of taking the train or bus?]]></document></documents></author>