<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Be grateful for what you have within and those without for the combination of the both helps you to LIVE in the ful… https://t.co/ZzYDzMVooh]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE DON'T GOTTA GO BACK TO 2013 TWITTER BUT CAN WE GO BACK TO WHEN NIGGAS WASN'T DOING DICK PRINT THREADS ??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskRubenHow2Bet @daneledurham Excellent pick Ruben. I thought the speed might carry all the way. #almost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcarpenterafs @Lunatic__Fringe @TulsiGabbard Brett you are clearly ignoring the large curve that starts with the o… https://t.co/YHYziWNvTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEshabbs But then they would win 1-0 in OT and we wouldn't have another UFA Hattrick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to back doubles put NKU runners at 2nd &amp; 3rd to start the 5th. Ground out gets the Norse on the board.  8-1 Alabama T5]]></document><document><![CDATA[First meeting of Minnesota Catholic Advisory Board.  Thank you 🙏. ☃️ #settingthestandard #whywescreen #corporateengagement]]></document><document><![CDATA[Momo told me to introduce myself or else she'll come get me at night #MomoChallenge #momo #MomoChallenge https://t.co/Fqmyki1lpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rufeanderson Canelo would beat the snot out of him he’s not even the best featherweight in the world rn, Canelo is… https://t.co/9cpyJmYFQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markboone219 @MapoTofuAddict @peterjhasson @MeghanMcCain @IlhanMN No, but it's interesting that she won support fr… https://t.co/EUQWrjHuQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You do realize you sound like a spoiled little rich kid that didn’t get his way.... .... oh wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@forceps21 @RubenGMA @RF_LAPAZ @a_cervantes1 @meganoticiasLPZ @gladys_rn @cmendozadavis @HXVIAyto_LaPaz @RubenGMA @CarlosSO_Moro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to receive an offer from Mississippi State University #HailState🐶 https://t.co/bqyZS5nFYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tigerdan41 Did someone else step up by just not collapsing down the stretch?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Greeks if a “GDI” touch your line jacket, key chain, umbrella and etc. y’all being getting mad and be ready to… https://t.co/5k4dgeosCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstherMcVey1 no country in the E.U. will be forced to join the Euro time to come clean that you lied]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s an excerpt from the blog post explaining it, Kafkatrapping:  @blondeandsmart @LORISAXON @dave1963x… https://t.co/QCdgKaNE3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is pretty cool no? It's too nobody was playing it and I don't know how to play though before I got hit on the… https://t.co/tTUsqKQyoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bottom-line we can’t allow cannabis to increase carbon emissions and water usage, further risk our food security an… https://t.co/798mw7Bpnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DemSoftCoup So which two Cabinet Members we’re going to say @POTUS was insane or incapacitated in support of the… https://t.co/DW4hJHPI4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lord_AMO The refs just need to back the fuck off bro like niggas used to throw hands in the nba lol and now they c… https://t.co/o2XtlXrBbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The US politicians and political pundits aren’t even trying. From now on, unless your bits are hanging out on TV, k… https://t.co/g88lYtkwtI]]></document><document><![CDATA[•Number of times I've successfully used @Tinder to get laid: 0  •Number of times I've successfully used @Tinder to… https://t.co/r2VEWGO6ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anupmajaisbjp @kpmaurya1 @CMOfficeUP @UPGovt @BJP4UP @PiyushGoyalOffc पीयूष जी खलीलाबाद बहराइच परियोजना से बहराइच… https://t.co/LjTegZ85NS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon for the first time and making little moaning noises at how beautifully this movie is shot 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[2015 Ford Transit Diesel @ Buy Here - Pay Here - $0 Down Options https://t.co/e1YjAUwquA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcfreelv @SinBinVegas Turk literally showed the team that he threw in the towel. and WTF is a gimmicky goal pull?… https://t.co/tQoQP3mmOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/mPp25y7aOk Obsessive-Compulsive Disorder "Fear of contamination" eh? 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LDU_Oficial Allá vamos estoy viajando de USA para ver al Rey de Copas este jueves ....vamos LDU !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSHobbs @Nickthonton35 @IvankaTrump Mostly republicans and traitor trump got help from Russian bots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.”it’s not THAT the wind is blowin’... it’s WHAT the wind is blowin’... if you get hit by a Volvo...” @Ron_White]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mondaymantra  Having no response may seem like it’s harmless – but it’s actually sending a very powerful message... https://t.co/uDYJqY4gnN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurlyFourEyes Basil's halfway to a Priority Puppy Kissing Booth. He'll make a fortune, I tell ya.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The team always looks more dangerous when Trent is on the field providing service on these crosses]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Kuri Kuro (Dark Chestnut Ale) (栗黒) by @hidejibeer @ Kizuki Ramen &amp; Izakaya — https://t.co/WuoGURG5Ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lawisejr @village_terrier Got a front row ticket in between benches earlier today. Looking forward to it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exclusive: U.S. to issue meat company guidelines as recalls mount - official #foodsafety https://t.co/56aSPhmhGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClarktheCub guess what?!!! I’m coming up to a game again this season.  July 15 vs Reds... KB’s bobble head night.   Hope to see ya then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch w My #1 homie #noahcarterstephens @ Char-Grill Two https://t.co/leF4A6bcEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluesrantscom Roll that beautiful bean footage. https://t.co/Vf77ep41Aa]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Columbus: clear sky, 22°F 53% humidity, wind 21mph, pressure 1024mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recent eBay purchase! Wolverine 1 hip hop variant. Cover is a homage to dmx Blood of my Blood! Sick cover for sure.… https://t.co/Ogk1ouYfGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RapperBRad @Borg99754177 @FlipMyBeatz @wav_Dr @JuanitaCSAthome @DavidDiehl20 @KittenheadLa @ELEVEN11_STUDIO… https://t.co/5HCEEBBM6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I’m seeing people throw their thoughts out about who should sit for TB’s D corps in the postseason. Here’s a… https://t.co/Mo23lXRZDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steveadams5243 @FriskEros @candi_smyles @jessylesby @UCandu2 @desires_unknown @P69Jordanp69 @mass_mistermv… https://t.co/PXlpgR90CV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery @MarkYoungTruth @BFT_Podcast You secretly worship Satan don't you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKatieHill @FoxNewsSunday Not hard on the eyes and she seem to be the flower in amongst the progressive weeds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@LindsayGrahamSC, I really don’t think middle school kids, middle school teachers or middle school parents give tw… https://t.co/HVqDUA3WR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dad Who Caused Vancouver Measles Outbreak Says He Thought Vaccines Caused Autism  https://t.co/CYJsH8lHcO https://t.co/skOP7ttHsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hilarious hearing that about, ya know, an Oscar winning actress in Brie Larson who really doesn't have any bad acti… https://t.co/8JgC1YyMdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtracey I figure it’s more actor, less pundit. Looking at McCain’s behavior as playing a part, it makes sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joelsherman1 He's owed 2yrs/$68M top of the market. Give him $35M over 5-8 more years. https://t.co/nIMwkdt18v  https://t.co/7XO8VDJSGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomNiziol how I yearn for the colonial period when the only din after a snowfall was the crunching of snow underfoot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisPower1 @AOC I’m not a great AOC fan but she does have many points in her Green New Deal. But if @FoxNews contin… https://t.co/yUboCBGpAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toxic femininity rules dem party Can't imagine being governed by 1 They culd cheat their way to Oval Office We must separate frm them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited for this conference. I'm not presenting and really looking forward to hearing all the latest research.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My southern California Barnes and Noble tour has been amazing. It's a Honor to meet with fans some I've only met wi… https://t.co/NvoUzsquzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A home is more than just an investment - so many other factors. Here is what the Oracle of Omaha said about his hou… https://t.co/dMcjkjmLFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMasterBucks When you threw in the bankrupt season to keep it interesting keep it up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TNgolf @TheJackHammer5 @FatdaddyMaxwell @weskorth Does @ryangreer20 have to win another one before he gets tagged in the post?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I hope the Republicans got your back, remember what happened the last time you signed a Bill, you… https://t.co/IiPyE0a7Js]]></document><document><![CDATA[@typedaguerreo @Bruno17686466 @AOC @ltthompso Ma! Meatloaf! There’s nothing about you that’s not a joke. Fake Mews… https://t.co/HFWm3ayzED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking in the beautiful views of the Central Valley. The vibe is quite different here than back in the Bay Area. Th… https://t.co/azHDoOOouV]]></document><document><![CDATA[That surface is a dying breed unfortunately. Nascar can’t undo what they did with all the repaves 5-15 years ago. I… https://t.co/KdWFgwj2d4]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are always, always missing a piece of the puzzle. https://t.co/EOXL3K5kPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delete your Twitter. DONT EVER slander the name of Steve Irwin. That man was a PILLAR of a generations childhood. Y… https://t.co/32P2x0Lsqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Luke Ryewalker by @ironhillbrewery at @ironhillvh — https://t.co/iycjCb8bEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaptinKnapton Not sure if it was me but its almost a reflex now. https://t.co/Y7CzgcX5U0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not among the rest of you lucky motherfuckers who are seeing @metallica in Louisville tonight, so I had to get them… https://t.co/qX1MGyMrMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I need to leave the Internet/life until Game of Thrones is over 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolaHanson9 PPC needs to quit with this bullshit "hot take". Anyone seriously looking at Andrew Scheer and think… https://t.co/jHRj8PzOjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PresidentialTwitterLibrary @TheDriskill Presented by #TheDailyShow @ComedyCentral @SXSW . . #twitter #usa… https://t.co/WiYVe8tyao]]></document><document><![CDATA[The SCMEA Division I East All-County Concert was fantastic!! https://t.co/eqodnqtuXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UVA guard Ty Jerome was asked if the quick turnaround is hard or just like old AAU days: "AAU you don't have to pl… https://t.co/i8yvmArVcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti You should consider a parody of you to be a compliment? Why attack others?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Umbrella academy is a great show on Netflix. Just watched the whole season in 2 days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bthayer @jenniferthang @MarkKonoSky5 @LAflyingcameras https://t.co/V3B19ddche]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do @TheDemocrats and their voters also have to pretend? I’m going to say no.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again. When you refresh basketball reference every night instead of watching while keeping in mind things such as r… https://t.co/DC5zJxt0No]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hayyyshayyy I wonder if they could come up with a “too many men on the ice” skit for him after winning a playoff game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManeatGrass @berracahband I TOLD her to c’mon, can’t wait anymore!! https://t.co/2S6LpkzgaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irisvarela La gente esperando restaurante que voten comida a la basura   Pa poder comer. VENEZUELA arruinada   No no]]></document><document><![CDATA[University of California student indicted for allegedly running drug app  https://t.co/WMSXc9xGUi via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonfavs Is it conceivable that Joe Biden could run with Barack Obama as his VP running mate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personalmente, tuve la fortuna de trabajar en la formulación del plan por más de cuatro años y me sentí orgulloso d… https://t.co/0ETXxNwIij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmamas1973 @mirvatalasnag @jedicath @willsuh76 @DrAmirKaki @fischman_david @chadialraies @KFAFHCards @drptca… https://t.co/bSNFVMWsMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeCHunter1 heres the link for botometer for you https://t.co/elIdlijAtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StudiosSphere Such strange things are latched onto by kids looking to get a leg up on others via verbal warfare.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_Lombardozzi The most loyal friends!  Can I get a follow back since you were in my sisters wedding lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the fuck do we put pillows on couches just to move them when we sit down?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beto4prez2060 @DTraumaangel @RideshareT My mistake I did not know Omar tweeted out that she was praying for the vi… https://t.co/r3uK1WYrbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissJennifer116 Girl you are beautiful and if I didn’t know your age, I would never have guessed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SondraRuthRW That looks soooo good. Happy anniversary! Also, THANK YOU GUYS SO MUCH FOR THE PRESENTSSSS! They were… https://t.co/YtI7B0BZey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran my shakeout and immediately plopped on the floor to roll out and watch the office. Still great]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving next to an ice cream truck. It’s 43° outside. I’m not insinuating this guy is a kiddy toucher, but it’s 43° outside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3: by having a Growth Mindset as a leader that shows our teacher that traditional instruction just won’t work, I.e… https://t.co/NgTgnwKDHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Pentagon Defined Climate Change Is a National Security Threat Years Ago. #25thAmendmentNow https://t.co/qsMdYXtXDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow i'm about to go from 4 valentines dates to 400 https://t.co/Q97ZTIlCQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CindyCrawford just bought 4 boxes of Girl Scout cookies from my step sister 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keto Macros while Power Lifting that is a whole rotisserie chicken and a whole steam fresh bag of broccoli in there… https://t.co/FHjp1TkCRb]]></document></documents></author>