<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I always get too drunk when I’m home to take any pictures man...it’s really tragic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀: The family of @CMTNAthletics senior Kendall Robinson, who passed away last month, was honored with the rest of t… https://t.co/SJ9NCiKAuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much history, culture, and beauty is alive and well in #nawlins Some areas literally transport you back in time… https://t.co/QkkbFhMO6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw the trailer for Ma and I can’t stop being excited about Octavia Spencer in a horror film #ma… https://t.co/mVgFzRVhH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zach_billings @StateDept @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo A good negotiator walks away when he should]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5-I have accepted a challenge from @jimcorns to post #7BooksILove-no explanation, no reviews-just cover(s). Eac… https://t.co/aAAasx8BlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GryanBrady22 @Pete_r11 Hahaha get on it bro😂 I know.. I’ve been meaning to finish mine up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Except the kids that go on a field trip to see Senator Feinstein! @benshapiro @RubinReport]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wild_brian Pretty much the exact same as when he said same words about @MittRomney   Course lefties like… https://t.co/XD3r4aa8NZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewEsarey Very tough watching close losses and blown leads game after game against quality competition. Depth, gu… https://t.co/aLGZ8gmLTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GRATITUDE! #begrateful #actually #extremely #didntworkout #wanted https://t.co/LOR6Tiz5Lj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MyMasonMemory last but not least is knowing that even though I’m over 700 miles from home, I have the loving suppo… https://t.co/52VAg3Uvc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1847Philanthrop Great! Looking forward to connecting! Are you going to the Humble Hang on Sunday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ludacris - What's Your Fantasy ft. Shawnna https://t.co/kV6K84h7zn via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @DailyCaller Save this to show during the Dumocrat primaries]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecretService @FBI @TheJusticeDept @ABC @NBCNews @CBSNews @margbrennan @FaceTheNation @CNN Endorses This ?… https://t.co/fzp93GdmJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sohotitsart @MPAVictoria ... with money stolen at gunpoint from others.  Shouldn’t justice and kindness extend to… https://t.co/39AntX3Qrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but if we ever crossed paths and shortly after you started rocking caps, give credit where it’s due please and thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RShutts @GreatWolfLodge Two nights we got here at 3 today go home Friday pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[A guy named Floyd Brown - shot a US Marshall serving a warrant - no not the Floyd Brown from WGN Radio..this guy wa… https://t.co/BWZOs49lZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm opposed to any tax payer money being used on illegal aliens other than for enforcing immigration laws. So it is… https://t.co/l6HrOpiGMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanhall23 @tigers @evanwoodbery @blainehardy65 You’re totally a couple days early. Are you here this weekend? https://t.co/gIyZOPVzFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally forgot about Daylight savings...  victoriavsbrito @ Clearwater, Florida https://t.co/KToBidOg8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @EricTrump As if he were a good student of history, or even a good student. Hey, Eric, we know people from @TheHillSchool. Just sayin’.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UPSHelp In front of my building is UPS but you rescheduled my delivery due to holiday. Not sure I understand? https://t.co/7eqzRY9cPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Airbnb is great! Kind of hard to get to, though.  #Alcatraz #sanfrancisco @ Alcatraz Federal Prison https://t.co/4ikxOIWL80]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm gonna be honest I'm looking at everyone different that posted that Kanye video of him playing keys with a choir… https://t.co/a74VrnIDdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this is true (and I know @funder is reputable!) we should be angry and afraid. We need strong leadership with Ru… https://t.co/40wTyXPy96]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at that age where putting off the main quest in video games comforts me in knowing my character also ignores hi… https://t.co/LtRzSlsmCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are at #CMANYC19  then Marquis A is the place to be Thursday morning. Why?  You get to ask the New York Time… https://t.co/EUH1g4rpqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy dangling from chairlift saved by quick-thinking skiers in dramatic r... https://t.co/85PHq7n4Wn via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all check out my #lularoemaxiskirt I wore it as a dress ❤️ how versatile it is #lularoecolbyleigh #happysabbath🙏… https://t.co/LJiAFucmUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennfranconews @OANN Water it down Nancy.  That way you can avoid naming names.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Denny’s has all you can eat pancakes for $6.99 all day today !!! ur welcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@german9248 La actitud de Isco y los resultados de Solari me hacen opinar que los dos se tienen que ir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This hearing really needs Alyssa Milano (@Alyssa_Milano) hanging out in the background.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spalding HS (Griffin, GA): Accepting resumes for assistant coaching positions. All teaching fields will be consider… https://t.co/0LciVWg3cZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bestcruiseprices #Disneyland #Vacations #cruise #sandals #disneyworld Want the absolute best cruise or disney expe… https://t.co/9Mv0eC9gj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[“One thing that I was surprised to like so much was the videos. We normally aren’t huge on the dvd learning, but th… https://t.co/2dONdsCCnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mark_Caldeira @NYCMayor @DOEChancellor @SuccessCharters @charteralliance @achievement1st @KIPP @UncommonSchools Cu… https://t.co/9wMwqc4dQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just get me to Curaçao already. (@ Miami International Airport - @iflymia in Miami, FL) https://t.co/IAU8FHCLXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Bourbon Barrel Black Maple by @jackieosbrewery @ Grandview Theater &amp; Drafthouse — https://t.co/w7FLBCzOxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Proud of @IBM for starting #BeEqual. As a leader I want to be proactive, open and intentional about growing a di… https://t.co/La39gmFy4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Medium rare ribeye and baked potato. Dinner. Yum 😋 @ArumsFoodFotos https://t.co/MS1TrkdBSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamCaptainMarvel on @TyltEnt–Captain Marvel is more powerful than Superman https://t.co/bZXoMR5ykH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Been there done that my friend. Lost both mom and dad in 2016 both were 91. You will always miss them.… https://t.co/P0yMdegxUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolyneholmes @profmusgrave Yes. "Blurred Lines" is the definition of this genre.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zamir406 Yes he did, he’s a beast. I think all 4 will be productive for a long time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Senator prayer hasn't worked we should do something else take it from god's hands &amp; lets ask 4 something more effective]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetbetty25 WELL DUH -- IT COULDN`T POSSIBLY BE HIS FAULT-- THE ART OF THE CHUMP  kim made him look like a fool N… https://t.co/HcJOQvKdx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a #Family Saturday before a four day Vegas work trip! #ConquerWhatYouChase @ St. George, Utah https://t.co/DkC7wRJ5yt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods BS. If he steps up and confesses then community service and probation. If he pulls this routine then fines and jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[u ever see ur whip parked next to another car and think damn they should date?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJBirchok @stevebyrnelive @JuddApatow So then there aren't limits. Just things you don't want to hear jokes about.… https://t.co/tiNwpF8mIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld I need some advice from you my wife is a victim of her employer they file the I-9 form checked box saying… https://t.co/QOW6DNkFak]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to work with the best administration team in the game! @davidwebb917 @Megan_McGann @Cemken1 @brettelliott36… https://t.co/GwdrISBfND]]></document><document><![CDATA[The night John Candy waved me in to sit with him and John Hughes at Kingston Mines when I was a college senior and… https://t.co/Kl8aQzW6Kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m money from 45 yards in...just saying! Extra points I can kick with my left or right. LOL #htowntakeover… https://t.co/VzBNHtgDbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checked my pockets. Checked my bags. Checked under the bed. Behind the toilet.  In my car. Under the seat. Couldn’t… https://t.co/cqQwlqCtOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Risk more than others think is safe. Dream more than others think is practical.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna feel real bad for Columbus if they get knocked out in the first round]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abulude @BronzeBomber @Tyson_Fury @espn @frankwarren_tv @BobArum https://t.co/MX0IMTe5tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished JP Delaney’s new book, The Perfect Wife. I was skeptical at first about the plot, but was I wrong!  P… https://t.co/7W4zWDvo8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonralls Yeah, I might have to flip a coin if I was in your shoes. haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holly I always try to do something that I think would make my parents proud. Hard to feel sad when you’re doing things like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBumgoatner Pads need some marquee draw. Hey good luck with that. Guess he could give a shit about winning]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is crazy! The air temp is 24 right now in downtown Kansas City. Can you see the steam coming off the ground wh… https://t.co/Uv5puD8gHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @DonaldJTrumpJr @kimguilfoyle So wrong!!!! No wall! All Bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey twitter! My friend, neighbour and colleague @KlimkowskiMrs is new to twitter! Can you give her a follow and rec… https://t.co/ZDdi0vjqKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, @50States100Days !  Two years ago today, ‘50 States, 100 Days: The Book’ was published in print on… https://t.co/9EBddsdoIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRyanFord I've never heard a valid argument in favor of his whiteness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best Saturday Party! At @tajlounge  Located: 48 west 21st Street New York NY 10010 Doors open at 10pm to 4am  ONLY… https://t.co/rFUsUHoOOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Andy McCabe on 60-Minutes. Whoa. If a fraction of this is true there is no question that… https://t.co/0cCRvn3LgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dog fish head never disappoints me. - Drinking a Namaste White by @dogfishbeer @ The Nest  — https://t.co/h3PBD9IXZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir Gate agents were unable to help. After a valiant effort on their part (they really did try), we are no… https://t.co/PK3TTlXWb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be looking at my Dad like “Damn that man face look just like my face”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DracutSuper @RepLoriTrahan Talking the NGD ,How to be to a US Senator ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorswift13 words of @garthbrooks, "Well I'm #Shameless when it comes 2 #Loving u I'll do anything you want me 2… https://t.co/SZvdAk0YHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s so easy for me to cut people out of my life that don’t deserve to be a part of it... like today i got time cuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s my buddy Ruben - he’s been my friend and mentor for a decade. For many of the coolest things I’ve been lucky… https://t.co/5Mgogengjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drake_patrick I hope they prove me wrong, but theyre too inconsistent at the moment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very happy for @brielarson and the success of CM. Still patiently waiting for the pop colab of all human history wh… https://t.co/GrjJZ4HwN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenSharmaTO Wellington was a poor PM. Gladstone should be on there instead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No puedo creer que seas tan enfermo es que en esa cabeza debe haber pura mierda, infeliz quien tiene el control de… https://t.co/0LOxD0xgvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeLevin09 @HarbormenHockey @BCH_HOCKEY @MyHockeyLive @GlobeSchools Don't think it's the title down there that is… https://t.co/kBXauX2JKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[PEZA Director General BGen Charito B Plaza speaks to PH community at the LA Consulate about Opportunities for Ameri… https://t.co/E8cVcBP1iD]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It doesn’t get any more real than this...” - A man, aloud to himself, watching the end of Chasing Amy at this bar]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm starting to think after dozens of officials saying she's washed up, again and again, followed by multiple "come… https://t.co/SpwB8lSLtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Love day to the wives , girlfriends and side chics !!!  #HappyValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[putting all the text on super small was a really great idea until my eyesight failed at age 21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oab @Haudricourt @journalsentinel @bruter24 I used to love lining those waxed paper cups up and popping them at old Country Stadium!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Improve your target audience with the best quality blog posting site, Blogs Opedia and increase the business. Know… https://t.co/R0QoUwuWbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danlapidus @RSharodi @NYC_LAE @reivey @bartobetsy @austinjevers @gettin2Jazzy @JenniferNatalie @dylanparks https://t.co/cPBinLd7pN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heritage chips away a bit and is down to @TheColonyHoops 22-16 w/501 left in the 3rd #txhsbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited to say I have received my 3rd D1 offer from Robert Morris University! 🔴⚪️🔵 thank you to @80sCane57 and… https://t.co/lHQlYsBE9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s an abstract-ness to reflections like this I’ve always enjoyed.  Barren Fork Creek , Wheeler NWR, AL.… https://t.co/14IPgOpz8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickMarvStutz @MikeJinID @TruthHurst Right!!   Those places are soooo much better than the smoked filled dives or… https://t.co/Bq2SQHCsO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethSenpai Tip: Schedule reoccurring social activities. A bunch of us did trivia every Tuesday night for about a y… https://t.co/bWc9g1MsdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day of shooting #aballerinastale with @mistyonpointe in New York in 2013. Always thank her and @GildaSquire f… https://t.co/zVIxnwlgWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who has asked me how to do something in Mario odyssey let’s go eevee/pikachu and BOTW I just refer them to… https://t.co/crbaqfNmQG]]></document></documents></author>