<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This #RandomActsOfKindness brought me to tears. A #TraderJoes Checker asked “what fun thing are you doing today?” I… https://t.co/2pXGwNQWAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[El problema no es que Margarita Zavala @Mzavalagc sea prima de una de las dueñas de la #guarderíaABC, todos tenemos… https://t.co/fo5tZiZ8sf]]></document><document><![CDATA[for a power grab that could divide the royal family, and might have tried to prevent it. The officials interviewed… https://t.co/qpl0lotJZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajimnie Dude there were some girls who did this in Visalia too while I was working there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGno2trump @lindawallner You bet they are. Sadly these women let them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesliebirkland @CPAC @RodStryker @realDonaldTrump Hate speech=/=Free speech, hun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just blocked a dude for saying that music was a waste of time. Sir, you are a waste of spACE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Controller" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about these types of opportunities… https://t.co/qwDGDobz5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Proudly admits that I sobbed during the marvel intro remembering Stan* *unapologetically claps with the rest of th… https://t.co/6zF2upEDcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also found code: COLOURPOPPIN and it worked to save $5 if you've placed orders through the site before ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akronlibrary @flannelkimono Omg so high tech / I’m so behind the times 😂🙈😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misswhit_86 @SSC_CA @hubert_jessica @Ismus17 @MarcotteKyleigh @Fabs_ulous Yay, team! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #StrikesMakeChange on @TheTylt. Teachers are trying to preserve the soul of public education–the time for c… https://t.co/WK5S66j4Hp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Schoology To me it is knowing how to best utilize devices/apps to achieve your desired goal(s)! #DLDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving Indy in all my feelings-incredibly influential event put on by the @NFLWomenEngage  So humbled to have even… https://t.co/L0QKi8PAs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Hmm, I seem to remember a completely different take from @CoryBooker when it was Brett Kavanaugh in th… https://t.co/PZgIK7Wiyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunday #goodmorning #birdsofinstagram #birds #birdsphotography @ Pennsylvania https://t.co/rbclxzXO2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormyDaniels Happy day and so proud of you! Stay strong, we are with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t wake up this morning planning to purchase Gucci slides, but I did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aldouga @ColorsTV @chopra_bhuvan @iamkamyapunjabi @wordislakshya @VivianDsena01 @RubiDilaik @AvChahat @gagori_uin… https://t.co/wRiBbHtXqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #nerdytshirtfriday! We don’t have school today. For the fourth consecutive Friday I can’t show off one of my… https://t.co/CyhWUZZbPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[not gonna say that I’m terrified that some people retain a mentality that you shouldn’t have sex if you aren’t look… https://t.co/1hzPepyHx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no problem eating healthy I just can’t get myself to workout consistently like I used to when I was in college 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lenetra806 @AyannaPressley @LaurenUnderwood @RashidaTlaib @AOC Beautiful!💜❤️💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Introduced a friend to the awesomeness of @HamillHimself singing “I Go Looney” as the #Joker on the Batman: The Kil… https://t.co/yyTHbldPfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two years...if they had something big it would have been leaked by now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is our home. All the history, good and bad, everything we know, every experience, every life that has touched… https://t.co/LP2NL38cP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rejoice! The wall is coming down!  Ok, it’s only the prototypes, but it still makes me happy 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate houses with pools and the fact that someone paid excessive amounts of money to ruin a perfectly nice house b… https://t.co/viaKFMg9OM]]></document><document><![CDATA[College is feeling like you’ve been hit by school bus, only to be hit by a Mack truck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently sitting here, convertible top down, munching on nachos. How’s your Tuesday going? 🌊💙 https://t.co/ayQsBRxJSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[just saw the most beautiful worker man at this flying j and we had a conversation about my randy johnson shirt #isthismarriage ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DudekLinda @andrerucker51 @SarahGould_SA @judeaa @keanothedog @NOW1SOLAR @Itridpm @JayValenz67 @hey_butter… https://t.co/PlRHZAjXRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Senator this is the kind of backwards thinking the R led SD legislature does in regard to education.… https://t.co/rMpjhMGp7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[PTA coin drive at school! Bring is your extra change to make a change!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Independent’s hybrid of established galleries, more maverick programming, and a significant contingent of outsider… https://t.co/RVKuC6WjYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am grateful to Meghan McCain because the last time i was on facebook was when her dad died and i said something b… https://t.co/d1XL3T0yB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The woman you are becoming will cost you people, relationships, spaces, and material things. Choose her over everything.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[No better place for an @AmplifyPhilly pre-game than the former Real World house. We’re about to find out what happe… https://t.co/tfVY9b5gKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I go into wk 2, these two dance together into DAY 1!!! New firm, first school, who dis? DIS IS MY CREW!! Proud?… https://t.co/zHQJTBhsEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get that sharing is caring, but I’m really hungry. #DBBbyMyself sorry not sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Edgar A. Smith Family @YMCAHouston in Houston, TX https://t.co/Mo1djYtwAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sad when you google dell computer shutting off and so many people have the same problem and @dell people never… https://t.co/0l9rXuFhvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I scream after reading this! Then realize since we got a center probably not getting another! So close to having hi… https://t.co/RYkZYuFXVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is from The brilliant Adam Grant’s LinkedIn, and made me feel #heard, #validated and #understood. 😆  4:30AM MT… https://t.co/5DcsuzvXjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah we’ll Finish that Wall, 3 Sides Concrete &amp; One with Iron Bars!! 😂🤣😂🤣😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hilted30 @meanstreak2099 @AryaResists Why aren’t his victims being called? That’ll fix it....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to be 100% honest. I never eat MoonPies but now I will because of this tweet. @MoonPie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kissycv My best friend and I drove 2 1/2 hours and stayed in a hotel to see fob front row and the next morning wok… https://t.co/hvMGCJriR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frandrescher Going to Instagram to follow you can’t wait for your new show]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frozen Beer - Drinking a Light by @Kirin_Brewery at @waltdisneyworld  — https://t.co/PBF6I1gYCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good times w/Ms. Whall &amp; Ms. Weishaar at the Mark Twain House. 📚 #eaglepride 🦅 @ Hartford, Connecticut https://t.co/BpNMIbMyMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luluHru @JAMESFA95300844 @l26772603 @JoshMyles12 @HjellaJohn @MatherJayson @Rmorrow611 @SweetKat111 @ROHLL5… https://t.co/NNG96yp44w]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what working with a bunch of men do. These are the topics we discuss. Shit that can land us in HR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for clay!  #coil #claycoils #starrynight #claysculpture #cmc #coloradomountaincollege #learning #Iloveclay… https://t.co/sFlNeS9EH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re away all weekend and off work on Monday #LaundryForDays https://t.co/BVXlSGzbmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[**Emergency Health Care Grant for Artists** . . Women’s Center for Creative Work March 1 - April 7, 2019 . . Women’… https://t.co/5qeEfKHByp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I scared my coworkers bc I saw Liverlips and Shaker at the dance party and they just don’t get The Country Bears 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Take care of YOU Wayne. The show is important, but I think you are right now. 😎😎😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, my beautiful BUDDY!🍻 @little_noga https://t.co/s8zFb3oXOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaDivaLisa Lisa, I ran through the airport with my shoes in my hand! It was a rough morning. Nothing nice about a… https://t.co/OrfJa7kBqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started a hobby where I watch a new horror movie every night by myself while eating takis. Send help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen Klobuchar is never going to win the nomination, but I appreciate your sticking to the principle of t… https://t.co/h2a1FSGICH]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing worse than waking up after a night out with a dead phone, who did i text? how much money did i spend? who d… https://t.co/qcQ3MFX2rv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sólo un año bastó para saber que seríamos el uno para el otro!!! Hoy ya son siete años juntos, siete años maravillo… https://t.co/MmdAMwz3yH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @rollcall Leave the kids lunches alone! The Obama's about starved them to death. #leavethekidsoutofit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desperately searching for a friend who appreciates and connects with my style of music like I do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crabbycakess Just get there! Not everyday is going to be the best, but something is better than nothing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottMStedman I am volunteering. I am not obliged to go but I go. What does it tell you Scott?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlanderCostum @MrSalPerez Cool! Met her at the premiere of "The Stepford Wives". Was surprised at how petite she is. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TedNesi Hey, we could hang out with Jim and Pam! https://t.co/NZ6ng4RbZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I’ve learned this week:  If you’re awesome, terminal cancer is coming for you.   Life is so unfair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[never going 8 months without doing my hair again https://t.co/x75kLvq7AL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmyLTyra Omg; talking about your life passing you by https://t.co/IEwIdNsy26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kacie_kellfire @hahahasounds I swear I would never do that to my guitar....maybe my dignity.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loathe making mistakes... Good Tuesday morning @SharonLFOX5 @Justin_FOX5 ! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bunn_and_dunn @akronbakerlady @tressiemcphd I was wondering if there was a language barrier as well! honestly I fe… https://t.co/o5hRj4cmPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faith did my lashes &amp; I feel like a whole new bitch. I don’t even need make up I HAVE LaShEs🤠.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Ronna you are one useless individual. Remeber your family came from mexico!]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy happy birthday @jenmakin_ 🥳🥰 hope you have a great day and come meet my dog soon (we also need more pictures) love u 💙&gt;💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like bralettes are for tiny boobs and bandeaus are for big boobs ijs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m an all or nothing person. I can’t fake it. I literally don’t feel whole if I’m not giving every ounce of myself toward it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4thdimension44 Tonight’s dinner and the other one is for Monday and Tuesdays work lunch. 😋 https://t.co/Iri0zeCKDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost another one to the wrong side of YouTube smh https://t.co/zoYEAb2itO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyOwensJr My confidant was always my husband. Well, he wasn’t my husband at the time lol. But yeah, souses are the best ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVED the show!!! absolute pleasure to be  here, watching them perform  #amazing #saturdaynight #livemusic #concert… https://t.co/FRIwY8Nti6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejtlewis @realDonaldTrump #DelusionalTrumpSupporter https://t.co/libFUzRg9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USMCSSDD You can’t just be Basty to women and.  think you can get away with it you can’t away with shit like Every… https://t.co/YkbUaFEkB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got this from vending machine and... They're individually wrapped fruit gummies. Like why? Such a waste of pac… https://t.co/FgSVGyfK4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jadjad1962 @HCPSCTAE @FloridaDECA @brandoneaglesd1 @BrandonHSEagles @LeanneFussell @castelli78 @stafford33510 Good luck!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone got the Blues Love Your Melon beanie tonight and doesn't want it, please let me know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speak unto the children of Israel, and say unto them, When either man or woman shall separate themselves to vow a v… https://t.co/uB1u1C8WQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I hear someone in Louisiana refer to a place as a “deli” https://t.co/5cL9wl7PzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gclarktweets2 @superunknown111 We took one  on the road doin an eBay trip. It was comfy and had heated seats!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[To ok my hair down so to speak. Can’t decide if I’m more Troll or Don King. @ Vine, Kalamazoo https://t.co/fs771As3i9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garymasonglobe Sadly this is behind a paywall so the very folks who need to see it most can't see it or share it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daggerbyslowdiv I’m gonna be real with you, I don’t know what species of animal this is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Air travel is competitive AF. And there are disruptors in the industry that are making headwinds- did y’all know Al… https://t.co/rQn50DniKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s a hard day when you wake up to your dad saying that the calf you tried to save last night passed away. #cattlefarmer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told this boy at school yesterday that his mustache made him look like Robbie Rotten from lazy town and when I saw… https://t.co/WFr6xUNLAt]]></document></documents></author>