<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MilspergActual @BontaHill Naw I just like fuckin with Bonta. Peep last weeks pod]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiero sexo oral y anal contigo amor bello a love ❤ me gustas mucho sexy boy Hot simpático blonde teen Angels Sing i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uncledonsshop @WendyBirdOZ @SpecificAaron @thefamouspaul Magnanimous 12*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Faller ner på knä by Gyllene Tider https://t.co/c1APDo2kVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasminemruddy @SenFeinstein What’s scary is that they actually believe the arguments that they’re making. These ar… https://t.co/Q5PipNJmBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Devon4Real @ATLUTD I watched the second half.  Barco MOTM for what I saw.  I hate I'm not mobile.  I gotta get thi… https://t.co/PhcrkgleFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw @descendents last night at @Zydecobham in Birmingham, AL. What an amazing show! #descendents https://t.co/x8cps3b2e8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Bri Johns’ trey pulls Edison within 45-36 of Princess Anne with 5 mins left in 3Q.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Al Sazón in Saltillo, Coahuila de Zaragoza https://t.co/fr8bPNFnZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about 'Sodoma': Critics on left, right have many similar concerns about Martel's work  https://t.co/qCIby8khYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronWilson_NFL 🤘🏿Town #houston #sports #football #reporter #texans #college #pro #football #raporgototheleague… https://t.co/eVykvCFCdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougboneparth @WRGuinn @MaryHanburyNYC @daniellekraese First piece was great.  Thanks sir!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RuthieRedSox @KatTheHammer1 Uh like I said like I wanted you to know like I know like The Turks like wrote this for me like ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm tired od fucking bitches man when I see Dakota tarlton I'm gonna fuck his little rat ass up on site]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol it’s quite satisfying actually watching basketball where someone makes free throws.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When this happened, I swear it was a mix of laughter and shock in the crowd haha I just started busting up like "di… https://t.co/3Mb8dEACa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanduhh_pls @jploading Even if zoos were for profit who cares? It’s proven that zoos are sanctuaries for endanger… https://t.co/vKONsh62Nv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Princes07160910 I guess that came out wrong. Thank God for the article and Zerohedge! And for your reply👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proviene la abundancia del ser. Hoy es un excelente día para dejarla brillar ¡Namaste! 🙇🏻‍♂️ https://t.co/c63LcY229R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Orlando Vineland Premium Outlets - @orlandopovine in Orlando, FL https://t.co/sodzb7hqoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikJLarsen From a man who has made a career from abstracting the human form I'm shocked this type of criticism came from you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greenwood vs. Southside JV action. You know I’m making that Booster Club Cash!! #BuildTheProgram https://t.co/v75DFhiW6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliebilello You know this sarcasm will probably show up on CNBC &amp; Bloomberg @ Charlie @ PP has called for a depression.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glen Burnie MD Fri Mar 8th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Chance Of Rain/Snow Lo 31 SATURDAY Partly Sunny Hi 45]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark you calender stunning home in the Lewisville Lake Community on Sunday, March 10th from 3-5pm  Located at: 3020… https://t.co/2YvCGNjQfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Data4SDGs A lot more on this coming from @DGateway collaboration with @UNICEFData here... https://t.co/lnrBfPoxI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joey_Artigue You could join the friar faithful.... 🤷🏻‍♂️ https://t.co/s8kvqLXINU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitchyTeam Our choices are between a Stoned Half Baked Indian with Slave Owners ancestry or an Idiot Pretending b… https://t.co/t8s25bQ935]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeatSauce1 @KarlTowns Because they pay guys like Wiggy max contracts when they aren’t even that good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We just finally sold our house today. Man, our landlord is going to be pissed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro What if Jessie, Paul, and Chelsea Manning all share a cell?  😄 https://t.co/rnREKhZ7tT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a rock show with your buds and a nice cold old style at the bottle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tarlovs birthday is on my birthday. Holy crap! How could she be so stupid?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte https://t.co/19S93VJnLM @Dollar_Bank @WRIGHTAUTOGROUP https://t.co/WSCVVFWghj https://t.co/pHtszMrnCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madyson_parker @BriannaValido Exactly stay together which they didn’t she would not of been killed by this piece o… https://t.co/jyms0Q9Am3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoobPunchTina Doesn't matter how much money you have. My sister is over run by them in plush gated community.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seton Hall shooting free throws every foul here on out 13 minutes left....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just released some new music, take a listen if you have time 🤷🏻‍♂️. Thank you to everyone who helped out on this an… https://t.co/kQqlVPPm2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a lil time to just #relax.  Watch the #fish 🐟 swim and listen to the #birds 🐦 chirp. #RailroadPark #Birmingham… https://t.co/SnTBOVhecz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IgorMinar If your in Paso, you should stop by the @SoCreate office.  We are right up the road in San Luis Obispo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TigerFanInSC @thecomeback @awfulannouncing 1.Are you really making the victims the villains here?  The host school… https://t.co/7TsT3bmTAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnny_rugger @gausby @pressy4pie Nope, I’m in Texas the next two weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapaBeez @Skipaway42 Did you and @Skipaway42 go to a Sonic drive-in? I don’t know why, but I picture the two of yo… https://t.co/xCEBodpHVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Star Wars” nerd moment: At a seafood restaurant, my order is “Order 66.” https://t.co/X7Ot695zdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinsheehanDC Love it - how was the other way working - lets at least have fun while going 7-9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay this is the worst officiating job I ever have seen. Tenneseee getting every single call]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah, the internet won, this whole thread a materpiece, im done with yall, gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_ChrisBryant @garyvee @Schmittastic In extreme occasions, it happens. And that’s fine. But to say you never sle… https://t.co/3rOe0XUiQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyLoretteMusic How is everything going for you?  Hope all is well. https://t.co/WV0GxQiAAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This pretty much speaks for itself..... #jordanisthegoat https://t.co/6tAMIowvYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[come into work and my coworkers is off AGAIN IM- https://t.co/dG7UqISvU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hardball @realDonaldTrump is twisted the real issue and that is Russia. Follow the money people and whatever else… https://t.co/5AqjPK9Xhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mañana: los @TheThreeTimers  play at 8. Following the legend himself, Santi “El Chief” Jimenez, Jr. Big fiesta cele… https://t.co/KVyha0gHVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCNews Why USA sent Marco Rubio, Diaz Menedez and anothers from the goverment if is only internacional aid. I hop… https://t.co/tlWrB121mk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schwarz @DuncanMitchel1 You're apparently some kind of journalist so I'm having trouble understanding your tweet.… https://t.co/erAvKP1aiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ncshusterman This should be a bigger deal. The resulting Saudi projects would almost certainly enrich his family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pena ajena a toda esa raza que se cree blogger y sube sus progresos en el gym a diario, chingón que si cumplan meta… https://t.co/2hVOwOlrww]]></document><document><![CDATA[⛽Shell⛽ 24440 Lyons Ave, Santa Clarita, CA 91321 (661) 259-0169 https://t.co/uWFNwOMDWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sally DeJesus opens up tonight's event Poetry Speaks for Us at Sisters Uptown Bookstore in Harlem… https://t.co/eYbTLxdUSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FortuneMagazine So @forbes chalks this up to the Trump tax cuts plus pre-existing “tax loopholes” which that bill… https://t.co/RSj4ckPzx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miami Beach at its best!! @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/NFDyDb7QbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well... I’ll be at #InterEintracht + #DerbydellaMadonnina ... wish me luck.  Forza @Inter_en #FCIM ⚫️🔵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darren2Showtime @SeanShilinsky I know.  Can’t stand the overuse of analytics nowadays.  Sometimes we just need to use our eyes...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThrasherCoffee I really enjoy y’all’s #45 blend. Good product. Glad to see some companies out there, that aren’t a… https://t.co/Xwpo6v7Fis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Instead of President Trump using this as a moment to unit the country. To speak ab… https://t.co/lt0Y23HCBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadalynnCrowder Become a beautiful ass rave bitch with Yellow hair!!!! Duhhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[There will not be another four years of Trump.  As long as Bernie Sanders stays out of the race and not split the v… https://t.co/w8t50l4MSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh I’ve been sitting in front of what’s supposed to be a 4 page essay for a good 3 hours and all I got so far is… https://t.co/LfTPwvDQ5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yessss! 100% agree. Look what’s going on with Disneyland in California. People are working at the happiest place on… https://t.co/UWigX9qMYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[That power play goal was a "dirty" goal.... Goalie fixated on the screen man in front of him, a "slow-motion" re-di… https://t.co/fCOzAFMG1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[What. #birdsofinstagram #birds @ Keyport Waterfront Park https://t.co/xkL4h0rzOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY!! TO ME... https://t.co/5cXt6Qoy91 @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/LgjuxSaTgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. President you're a goddamn liar there are no 10,000 of thousands of illegals crossing the border you're f******… https://t.co/YJjqej1bjA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @realDonaldTrump Do you actually believe the bullshit you are spewing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chet_Cannon @redsteeze Her team opted not to go with the microphone to bullhorn. For now...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBadWolf_1 I don't think Bird can beat him out. Believe Voit will force their hand. Think he's for real]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even pay attention to celeb gossip but these Tristan tweet are gold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump ‘I didn’t need to do this’   Please use the 25th amendment and remove the imbecile]]></document><document><![CDATA[1) So to check it the story is true, I look for the original source. I find a longer quote:  “I’m deeply troubled b… https://t.co/bFwyQS3bRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NKOTB @DebbieGibson @DebbieGibson u could give @britneyspears and @Camila_Cabello and @ArianaGrande and… https://t.co/mFrO1m41cq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MFRDirtonDirt I’ve distanced myself from them and this is an example of why....I’ll stick with @ReggieRedbird]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half marathon PR Vamos (@ Robert F. Kennedy Memorial Stadium - @theeventsdc_sed in Washington, DC) https://t.co/by88EZTQqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leeazareel @luisfortuno51 Yo nada más no, son más lo que quieren eso que se independiente, respeto tu ideal pero e… https://t.co/AuD3kVrQhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElementalAmber Saw that earlier. I think it’s time for a ‘Willow’ reboot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ken_Rosenthal Do you think the players may be willing to ditch arbitration so they can get to free agency quicker… https://t.co/IlpNgs4Lmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Henry Payne for February 25, 2019 | https://t.co/eSMqRsQRgf https://t.co/uxuMBqxs4j via @GoComics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz día del amor y la amistad! O de los solteros ☺️!   #DiaDelAmorYlaAmistad #14Feb]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Shoshoni, WY job and click to apply: Medical Technologist or Medical Lab Tech - https://t.co/0DAa6a3UsI #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished binging #TheGoodPlace last night and y’all benches owe me a couple tissues. @IMKristenBell @dubjackharper 😭@nbcthegoodplace]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEE G NEWS: Join me at The Sportatorium in Paris tomorrow night for Prime Time Wrestling!!!   #LeeGNews #PTWProud… https://t.co/zg80Ly15Is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCVIM just watched @Ryon_D stream and he just might of forever ruined Return of the Jedi for me #Ewoks 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday fun. Just because. "Hipster whines at tech mag for using his pic to imply hipsters look the same, discovers… https://t.co/hGJX0RTJA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CpaCarter @jed20004 @FoxNews The Constitution guarantees the free exercise of religion, which includes the wearing… https://t.co/syCI2EjenR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mik9703 1. Nick was clear about going somewhere and being the guy 2. The Joe F. Trade and not willing to go to a N… https://t.co/DxvNiX0Otv]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to crush some Apex! Tune in for those hot Wins! . . . #ApexLegends #respawnentertainment… https://t.co/SyUzdNjlEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PennyJJerald @TheOrville @FOXTV Another cinematic feature. Kudos to the imagination.  It's like Cloud City,  meets… https://t.co/PQ7u4gbgbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 They don't need the government subsidies. The manority of those subsidies are returned to the Dems r… https://t.co/4s6Aeudm5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[A student just played the message that Noblesville West Middle School sent to parents on the day of the shooting. I… https://t.co/cF2EgS8RzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our sweet pups. #dogsofinstagram @ Kimberly, Alabama https://t.co/d9aBUcXW1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @realDonaldTrump He’s still not gonna let you suck his dick Jacob.]]></document></documents></author>