<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BrightCarbon @julieterberg FWIW, I tried the onenote route but wasn't thrilled with the results on this particular… https://t.co/1Jud9c2jrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Renaissance Los Angeles Airport Hotel - @renaissancelax in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/SGDsEHMFOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bergeronmf Malheureusement, la population va se réjouir de ce projet de loi 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Well behaved women seldom make history” , and that my friends is the TRUTH #InternationalWomensDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DenverChannel Maybe update it? "The morning commute is expected to be slushy..."  No... Maybe it was in October wh… https://t.co/wAqCmDt4VJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently walking through the creepiest cemetery in my town taking pictures of random historical monuments and grav… https://t.co/T5xYcn60mM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Participating in @PS36x’s #ReadAcrossAmerica2019!  @ElviraMaresca @BrendaGallo23 Thank you for the invitation!! https://t.co/0975lT6RW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gave Marisa coke and she folded all my laundry BET you know I’m telling jo i did it though lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[little girl farts on camera and says its a ghost! https://t.co/FOddl9UcAr via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOOM. 150. DONE. Day 1 ✔️ and look at Elaine Cronk go! Ready for day 2! @8Challenge https://t.co/JNAPKWvphV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kfz1980 @realDonaldTrump OVomit did nothing. OVomit policies crippled our economy. OVomit helped OTHER countries.… https://t.co/DvjKwSEbwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#catsitting for my #beautiful #stepkitties #Athena &amp; #Apollo 😻😻 #lovethemsomuch #rescues #rescuecats #catsitter… https://t.co/9aFqp4wzx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latinovictoryus @AOC OMG did she memorize inspirational quotes!!!???? How about giving the woman some real advice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#audiq7 transformation by #sunshineautospa *complete interior detailing *Exterior carbon fiber vinyl wrap removal a… https://t.co/kX2xenzfm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BraveStern We gave them to the players and some other friends. He thought the players had them made.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤦 But he didn't shoot the innocent autistic man he claims he thought was a hostage-taker. He shot the innocent Blac… https://t.co/TDbirhY0mT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nonchalantly chilling with a snake around her neck.... couldn’t be me, baby!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol Time is up for this craziness! The GOP needs to find it's way out of Trumpland.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BookShare @Miller12Shannon Challenged me to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews - just the c… https://t.co/Gvd5KO8YRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyMcKew The immediate sleep cycle is the deepest one, then you start emerging  upwards I to more shallow and dr… https://t.co/OTSrmME1Vd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antifamos @never_martha @InCorrectRecord @MrDane1982 So we’re going with the Hitler perspective here?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great book in the Spazhouse Research Library. A 1947 Living Chemistry book. #science #chemistry… https://t.co/nOerikhswm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Wednesday morning.  Stay safe on the roads it’s gonna be an ugly commute.    Schwarber and Bambi are both up a… https://t.co/cRzn0dZW0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth @realDonaldTrump And what has Republicans done..Ashamed of You All cause you Brown Nose the Idiot… https://t.co/0u6wlrdDw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Vile. Associating the Netanyahu government with US support for Israel is no different than saying the Trum… https://t.co/UjUElV8Uji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont forget our SPRING🌻 BREAK🌼 CAMP🌷 is next week March 18-22! Register online, link in bio! ➡️ #MyGymTucson… https://t.co/OSngxSLmFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Fuck off, you asswipe. Isn't there some kind of National Emergency on the 18th hole at Mar lago?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelmsiegel @daveweigel Because they couldn’t take the time to actually talk to those who needed and wanted the jo… https://t.co/oxqRBL11ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fox28columbus Saw lightning and heard thunder at about 5:45 am in Hilliard/Dublin area.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattBerkheiser @IshwariaMD @JoeHermanMD @hftannir @CarinHagberg @McNeill_Dr @AraVaporciyan @LauraMComer… https://t.co/K7J2nV4ZT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve officially been awake for 24 hours and I still am an hour away from my bed. When did @GPSTPETE  become a 24hr… https://t.co/FO9wIOJwoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just love this city ♥️  . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . #nyc #newyork #nyclife #nyc_explorers… https://t.co/Nr594r6I7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and we cannot prepare them for the future if we teach them the way we did in the past. #WhiteboardWisdom https://t.co/SHjpkJ7cwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Reddit is the SparkNotes of social listening.” @im_melissa #RaganDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sheesh, this sudden sadness just hit me like a ton out the blue. I didn’t wake up feeling like this wtf. Lord, rebuke it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate is honestly such a sweetheart i can’t believe she really paid me to do her laundry]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I keep hearing this from the universe.. . It can be both a #motivational message or a damning one. If y… https://t.co/wGE0PMbl93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorenzabraham12 Good afternoon Larry and hope you enjoy your birthday ! Do you have anything planned for it ? Is y… https://t.co/ILSKWjBHE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoodNetwork Las Palomas Blancas (I call them chicken burrito enchiladas) ☺️ Lots of garlic, cheese and green enchilada sauce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeana_fraser I’ve been taking Vitamin C and B12 gummies. Definitely seen a difference. Getting at least 5-6 hours… https://t.co/1Nl9DG1rm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oliver has some pretty great friends 😎 happy birthday Bailey!! We had a blast today at your party 🎉… https://t.co/XOoWp0FLCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[While i am enjoying the session @sccm were there no females available to be part of this speaker panel on Fellowshi… https://t.co/f3FM7QLATR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dazza76474385 Right! Plus, what about Blaine saying he saw Bobby in a blueish green car?! Does that seem significant to you??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Are you even Legal and can you prove it, No one has ever heard of you before you took over dem congress an… https://t.co/MIYizn50HI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cherae_kerekes @AuschwitzMuseum I live my life in inclusivity. I’ve lectured at schools where my skin color/religi… https://t.co/uvAxWonyZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working from home on yet ANOTHER snow day. Freezing in my living room. So I’m wearing my @MacDowellRugby sweatshirt… https://t.co/rdMUGfwSgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AricFOX5 @OceansidePD @fox5sandiego This has bizarre written all over it. Any more info, curious about this weird case...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not even a person I'm shaped like an ugly one but in reality I'm a fucking worm]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a load of crock. Barbie you just have to be in the limelight. Nobody cares for you or what you do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SillyDora @RebeccaFaussett We have to stand up to our Government now not later, there might not be a later]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being on dance team and like never getting to sleep In. Sleeping till 6 is a blessing. A whole extra 2 hours 🥳 ...… https://t.co/XLBpBZTOwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pacelattin Because he is a Atheist without even knowing it. He knows nothing about any religion. He knows nothing about mostly everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating a website for work and nothing is doing what I need it to do. Just when I think it's working well, it time… https://t.co/iyDsddMOh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally met the great @howie_hua! He gave me my special heart ❤ #cmcmath #kerncmc @CAMathCouncil #iteachmath https://t.co/bd4m1GtL3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANYONE ELSE CRYING WHAT THE FUCK THEY CAME BACK FOR US🥺🥺🥺🥺 https://t.co/mSZ2fcGHhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall been warned. There will be a bunch of #letterkenny tweets during the #CBJ game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump The orange blob puts HIMSELF first...don't ever forget it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tacos and @emkristen— do you need a better reason to listen to today’s @TACOTHETOWNKC? You don’t since this is as g… https://t.co/bVJbyb9ACE]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE ALBUM PRE-ORDERS ARE GOING LIVE TONIGHT AT 9PM PST/MIDNIGHT EST AHHHHH!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss #Morrissey 's music on #Spotify . It's gone! I can now only listen to his songs I have in my playlists. Hope they are back soon :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_laurennew Plan out a staple wardrobe of about 10-20 pieces that you can mix and match to a ton of different outfi… https://t.co/d9vnSdB6N7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silent Denver Morning - 1/5  #seemycity #quietthechaos #wintervibes  . . . . #themilehighcity #denvercolorado… https://t.co/5gNLbzsBfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really spend my Saturdays waking up at 5 am to run for fun..... boy this better pay off one day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddeanjohnson @ABC7GMW @jessob_reisbeck @VAratifyERA Dean, other than the deadline issue, you clearly have problems… https://t.co/tiDlgWBLLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a cutie little fish and he’s FUCKING boujie. I couldn’t get him to eat. Turns out he just didn’t like the foo… https://t.co/V7bJoMnyvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone showed me this in Guam and if this ain’t really me then idk.   Sadie the Cleaning Lady https://t.co/n9zNuQeKmx via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, I’m officially outta antibiotics and cough syrup. Guess who still can’t breathe without a coughing fit? 😒 back to urgent care..?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurseOfOak @HISTORY Strange magic. Black magic  oak island magic! https://t.co/em9zHjE8Di]]></document><document><![CDATA[#howiethebichonpoo #bichonpooofinstagram #mylove #nopicturesplease @ Pembroke Pines, Florida https://t.co/N1bI41rdPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curious to see who the @geegees_wbball will play for the Critelli Cup @OUAsport Finals]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Coming together is the beginning, staying together is progress, and working together is success.” Henry Ford… https://t.co/exiVzkDTfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 2002 law increased projected farm subsidy payments by 74 percent over 10 years.  In 2008 Congress overrode a pr… https://t.co/AVSNr6aSCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krisis86 My parents had the missionaries come give me lessons when I was 7 years old in preparation for my baptism… https://t.co/VEa756I7F3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its 4am and i cant sleep because i keep thinking about the rest of the stuff i need for his room and where to put i… https://t.co/bPiFVKR05O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ @GallopinDragons No joke, that's what I worry about. Would rather ride in an elevator with absolutely any… https://t.co/xIJADtmk8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@berrydelicious @backstreetboys @bsbgirl2828 @marissakidman @LilMsAllie @Princess_Karah @MsDuchessKate @XzOtiCaNdY @missbreezyy 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[“IM A HUMAN ASSHOLES. I AM MORE HUMAN THAN IVE EVER BEEN.” - anna trying to log into Hulu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAPS_SafetyORG A friend recently told me her Mom had not been cared for all day, missing meals and not being chang… https://t.co/7jBuAPMbu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kuch and Pointer just gonna pass between each other until one of them does the 🎩🎩🎩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helentamblyn Bucharest is super fun! Wild history, good food, accessible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracydavidson @LBustamanteNBC @brittneyshipp @KatyZachry Great pic Happy #WomensHistoryMonth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philosophrob They have insider trading information, they knew before hand about the banking crisis and who is goin… https://t.co/3TvDBHluhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I’ll be repping my city in style and be super comfy! Can’t wait to see @BeOhioTrue grow! Even better, I’ve got… https://t.co/dFTcmBZ2fe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Q - The Plan To Save The World (old version) https://t.co/FAy6AHbP4e via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clare and I went to the Levi’s store and I just bought the jeans that she was trying to return]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's finally here! Who's ready for some wubbs!!!?? Downlink never fails to blow my mind! Don't miss a drop! Grab yo… https://t.co/dyOnHQaqjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite thing I’ve heard in student teaching so far is being told to “floof off” and that was said by my teacher 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love telling people stories about you two. I could talk about you both for forever @Ianbrown120 @USS_TrashBoat 💙💚❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @bRILLIANTLance and team! Stunning. Elevated. Creative. Classic. Honored to be a voice in your publ… https://t.co/oPCQ2NsIZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi comentario #DATODURO La aprobación de AMLO a 100 días: Slim dice: "está avanzando". #100DiasDeGobierno ¿Nos acom… https://t.co/U89MicR8VM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eamon // NEWBORN // Studio Session in Wahoo, Nebraska // #autumnwaldmanphotography #awpnewborns… https://t.co/4T9wEk68hm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAG4All Yuck... don't want to be part of anything associated with Andrew Cuomo he is disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phil_Sledge Awww.. hope it’s nothing serious. Feel better little one! ❤️🐾🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kate_patterson4 @senatemajldr Because it is a stunt by the GOP. You can't kill newborns anyway. Such BS from their mouths these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I FaceTimed Dave last night, and if it weren’t for the fact that he’s one of my good friends, I’d be super confused… https://t.co/MG7FloTye8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hungry? Get $5 off your first order on #Uber Eats with my code: eats-gwendolyw1ue. https://t.co/PlruwDPSW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s safe to say I am prepared for #CUE19 and the #supermuch #stickerswap Thank you @stickermule  I like to be OVER… https://t.co/16st4GFT0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vi un traje de baño que se vende por tallas y no hecho a la medida, dicen que debes de multiplicar el material por… https://t.co/haiQdpCOAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burning a bridge with me means you will never get to the island again #sadboihours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tennessee_Jed7 @HoarseWisperer Come on down!  We catch some beauties here. https://t.co/8TkniyWTNT]]></document></documents></author>