<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[True but I’ve seen many trashy parents who’s kids grow up raising themselves and it’s not a great outcome. I do kno… https://t.co/wIFrlQ29oL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fair play, people listening to the facts and making there own minds up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for the underrated post-game shower beer.  #HotShower #ColdBeer #PureBliss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacob_Rees_Mogg We know who you look out for, you and your vicious rich friends, but we are our kids and their fut… https://t.co/sNmUAw8edJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  will the @POTUS use a on going conflict and near nuke war as the next reason to short cut the next meeting??… https://t.co/n6Y0xBLxKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LANACION Y como se soluciona el acceso cuando hay piquetes? Para cuándo extensión del tren?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate GREAT Women by reading about them!  Visit your (EPISD) Library! @ESaenzEPISD @ELPASO_ISD @EPISDLibraries… https://t.co/0pBWszFlYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥INFECTED DEAD BOOKS-INTL Links 🌎https://t.co/qRIA63fi5C… 🌎https://t.co/IC2Xc0yayU…  99c 🌎https://t.co/XGmUhu1KpX…… https://t.co/IJmEHppbdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @camanpour - who knew Gillian Anderson is British?  I didn't. Possibly because X-Files was gf's show, not mine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kidkerrigan @lawlkat @JessyWang_Blizz @Skirtzzz @Kachelle__ @Selenityy @TheCosmicCake @KiyeBerries @AliciaWinsTV… https://t.co/BcJfnMsLM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love me some BA Chump Change, Imperial Black Saison by @OakHighlands @badhopper @ephoustonbill @JonMontag @JohanBBT… https://t.co/YTL5vlWMDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RefugeeNik @thehill @TheHillOpinion Why dont you look at John Robert's statement]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCleanerSide Soft music, read something that is informative but kinda boring.  Helps me. If I start Tweeting or… https://t.co/XwuAYqf2Q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoePClements @LaraMedley “We can’t have Session in January because of the velociraptors, and by April the pterodactyls are swarming”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Q3: What first step do you prefer in Outside Zone? #hogfbchat https://t.co/F67mtyEQCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little like pixie sticks. - Drinking a Soy Sauce Gose by @WoodenRobotAle @ Hi-Wire Big Top  — https://t.co/w3pI3OvXei]]></document><document><![CDATA[pretty cool to see Solange improve on the Opti-Grab since Navin R Johnson left the game https://t.co/H1N8xiYkM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dreadpirate42 @MilanovNina @BajanJean @veggie64_leslie @tommycanyou @_lets_do_it_ @Sheeple101 @ZinaAntoaneta… https://t.co/HvcTxx2rOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for Jeopardy @UCIMESA DW is on the end for @teambeechwood #FSDLearns @AnneStenton]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the 2 hours of sleep I got affected tummy workout lol I wasn’t really that pumped for my workout and kept yawning 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[His "style" is really something I've never heard before and I thought I'd heard it all.. ain't never heard nothing like that though.. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickToney01 No problem my friend. When they're BAD GUYs to be caught and children to be found I want to help anyway I can. 👍🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serious question looking at Luke Walton in this presser...worse for your health...dating a Kardashian or coaching LeBron?]]></document><document><![CDATA[AHHH OMG. IT'S FINALLY HERE. #UmbrellaAcademy 😭 https://t.co/fOClS7Bv1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr @SenateGOP @senrobportman @marcorubio @SenSchumer @AriMelber @Lawrence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin I promise you I will never bother you ever again if you tell everybody you love her and she wants to marr… https://t.co/K9vg0rY1wR]]></document><document><![CDATA[But you don’t reply to my tags. My tweets. My comments. So no. Fuck off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please pass @NicoleClowneyAR bill #HB1655. We must address the domestic gun violence happening in every community… https://t.co/HEbARquvkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dictators are loved only their first year in power because people change and what they want change too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FinnBalor has won the intercontinental championship. This is his first one in history  #WWEChamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corker of a day and perfect slopes. Scavenger hunt round #2 today. #dayatthewoods @ Bretton Woods Ski Resort https://t.co/OG1FwvT2OQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarah_wigington  You are strong! You are kind! You are special! You are important! You are a gift! You are a frien… https://t.co/PPe9uMmLLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toccaraford we need to see a profile picture good Sir! @Charcandrick26]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not just that they don't value education. The gov calls the system "an abysmal failure" thereby impugning all… https://t.co/G4OZUDJZhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[You just lost the bet. Have shiny nickle ready next time as no pardons given except maybe Manafort ; no  Potus Trum… https://t.co/Jlp9sd1rbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@12thMax @bryand85 @BhavishaPatel @antmay Nothing that idiot does is funny. You are cool though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to watch this, See @lsarsour , terrorist visiting @RashidaTlaib and the asshole guy pushing camera girl ar… https://t.co/gmXzY8PJYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come out and support !! Will be hitting the stage w/ the bros @JaxsonFree &amp; @zackcokas919 🙏🏿❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VICE Unreal  Idiot far left “Democrats” like @AOC are to blame. She should go back to slinging margaritas in Union Square.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hackster63 So do I. I can't believe they complained about this in 2016 and it's nearly 3 years later and not resolved, apparently]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Uh, Tuck-Tuck isn't exactly a Greek god his own tubby self. Does he have mirrors at home? Or in his… https://t.co/96ZbX1aT8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods She is all that and polite. She says "You're Welcome". After she delivers the low down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kavaangel what’s kai waters gif? I’m tryna find it so I can post it on FB lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OSOLO21 @ItsARP You got 2k followers 900k views and you went viral for some bs! Don’t talk to me. I responded to… https://t.co/mGzBpRAzbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SherrodBrown I’m not sure which Federal Penitentiary has a golf course ???🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[COME GET THAT EASY MONEY!💰Giovanni Arreola is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $313.00 and you ca… https://t.co/3KuEu1LrXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@panferse @hrvieda @cesaralo @AccesoWIN @10yorelirincon @WinSportsTV Londono puro cuchacho....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GusslerMark @BernieSanders Please don’t stop dummy. Give me more rage. Cry more :D your your your]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was painting this week. I use the phrase “making another pass” to describe painting on a painting which was “unfi… https://t.co/sAXWraBAu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[15:42, 2H ⏰ @HailStateMBK 43, @RazorbackMBB 41  The Bulldogs are on an 11-1 run in the last 3:31.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ssnyder1835 @TomKingTK Please write some more BANE stories. Its quite obvious the stories will be AMAZING and my C… https://t.co/P51DVIvBkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wcXfYkBxvh #HollywoodRockStars #JamesPaulRowland #MotownNow #HazardousMusicPublishing… https://t.co/p7utJnZNxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dxna Do you at all worry that people will stop raising things? If by pointing something out you create an impositi… https://t.co/DoXxwmkgba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisTheFatRef I was really hoping Jaqen turned out to be Syrio.  Imagine when Arya leaves, he watches her and says "Just so."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @thehill @TheHillOpinion #FakeNews perspective.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Statistar30 And now most every 2020 candidate has adopted his 2016 platform. It is so extreme that Harris has no p… https://t.co/l8hEi8YD2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did the first 4 missions of DMC5  This game is the hottest fucking fire  I'm going to sleep now so I can crack out… https://t.co/oI2llYzJSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Federal Emergency Management situation agency please turn those places into cannabis growing places or just shut it… https://t.co/xBWA82rSif]]></document><document><![CDATA[An accurate thread that reflects on the spiritually and emotionally damaging movements in Latin America and the US.… https://t.co/FhxzECYyA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tempus_edax_55 Q1 sort of like memorizing song lyrics. You know a lot through repetition, but hard to quantify or guesstimate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BTW, I wonder if @AlyssaRaymond @CelinaPompeani @GabriellaDeLuca @Marielena_TV @KellyRippin @KatieCollettTV… https://t.co/Jq7vLbvUlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A moderate risk for severe weather including damaging winds and #tornadoes has been isssued across the Tennessee Va… https://t.co/JJNRRnuz9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codball @report_summer @ChathamAnglers @WVUBaseball Was also clocked at 98-99.  Very impressive debut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @ESPNNFL,  If you’re not considering @PatMcAfeeShow for the #MNF booth, you’re missing a great opportunity for… https://t.co/IGVfYDog8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SInow @NBA @papa_wolfman69 @PapaJohns @SunDropLover69 @SunDrop @RyanKellyPitts @jonfordlister @Justbo1901… https://t.co/JUYZ8nQxJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I realize I love being outdoors, in nature.. living and breathing things that are contributing, especially… https://t.co/3YgRZ9LvWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you ask to end My second amendment rights you are causing the danger that got you shot to begin with. You are… https://t.co/fSzl0CJdus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatsJacqueline I found it.  I hang on to this one. https://t.co/VoLIjFDzWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amber Alert about flooded areas.... look like I won’t be attending classes today 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet more disgusting images of the modern day Democratic Party. Nancy looks like she enjoys being shoulder to should… https://t.co/QqIZpbqQ2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManMet80 I could easily go back 8. With a little effort I could go back 25-30.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visiting Savannah, GA @pitbosshall @HinchmanIndy @CocaCola @IBEW @BryanClausonInc https://t.co/V88K6ABygB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RN_4Vols @ALiferGaDawg Can’t work on golf course when it’s this cold 🥶 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a Providence basketball fan during the 2018-19 season: https://t.co/K28nsp6JP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cannot focus on work anymore today. Only 11am.... https://t.co/kiEeYazBxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Central DI Regional Awards Ceremony. Go Tech! #harfordtech #techyeah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffr0 Scalability. Security. Poor leadership and inconsistent decision making for the direction of the entire project.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you heard this yet? "3 Strikes" by yours truly 🙌 - https://t.co/qyjgYF8N7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Chad Ruhwedel's goal, the only non-goalie to appear in 15-plus games for the Penguins this season to go withou… https://t.co/Tx6rvtIrh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 That’s like begging for a compliment... pathetic. #MAGAMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idunnster12 @mystsams @TalbertSwan @GregShugar @realDonaldTrump Are you a bot?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yourcupoftino I thought they didn’t prescribed pain meds? hmmm wag ka mag rely sa pain meds sisirain mo lang din a… https://t.co/ZFSom4Oyv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the 10 million reasons @chesapeakebay launched the Keystone 10 Million Trees Partnership...… https://t.co/NdCoKaZjbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING AMERICA TRUTH. IT IS MOST OF THE TIME IN CURTISY ANS QUESTION A HUMAN RESPONSE IS DONE. WHEN AN EMERGE… https://t.co/lxxdQbyuix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hospitalitysnob @Bonsse88 @realDonaldTrump So tell me have you heard of any crisis at the Canadian border? At our… https://t.co/8If4LvfrVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SotoC803 @PetitePhD Also per the same article:  “The club has an insatiable fan base with more than 100,000 people… https://t.co/WniQ2CVsxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@avizollman @straussanator And take away my ability to rage? Hard pass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boycott and blockade California's highways and don't buy California produce or manufacturing products and don't tra… https://t.co/Kcg5an12Mw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot to put these up from the art museum I went to the other day it was alright I did like the last section of… https://t.co/6KXEc2YM4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody else i would want to spend valentine’s day with❤️ @ Red Lobster https://t.co/aUzG3W8Prk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three true outcome leaders through the years:  2000-2018 https://t.co/8CwmgknJfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the shout out @cure_magazine For more info on our program: https://t.co/0wVcCzgcY8 #ayacsm #survivorship]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your wanting meets your readiness... https://t.co/v66LBPckDE #WeightLossMentalist #healthyliving… https://t.co/mysX3mqR7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikenedie @zypisfy @PCribbett @Cern_lXXl @yourmumspants @tklforgiven @AprilLigeia @Heliocoptero @BrianSlimdog77… https://t.co/hfSjNNpPwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhanGenghis1227 @joncoopertweets That could give us 4 more years of Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[A morning of errands starts here. (@ chevron in Rotherwood, TX) https://t.co/dPF00t29Bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great night out for Death Metal at the Observatory with stefikins and friends Friday night! Finally got to see Mo… https://t.co/n9LpjtpgN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[We really still doing this? In 2019? Like really? Stop this dumbass shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am out and about in Wilmette, putting these in people’s yard and getting ready for the April 2 election.… https://t.co/uNSsvHqOA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISPEvansville Have a good day Sgt. Be careful. https://t.co/kcSQHFBGf3]]></document></documents></author>