<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@amvetsupport Neither party is capable of fixing the GROSS mismanagement of the VA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnakeBadAss Sure wait till it is hip deep then worry about getting your car out of the garage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenedictDonald_ @realDonaldTrump That outfit fits him to a https://t.co/mwzH0E2OHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moises's sweet sweet mom got me a planner on her trip to pick up Aaron. I love it!! 😍😍😍 https://t.co/Kp42zQh8fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I unlocked $20 Rush tickets for @TheWoosterGroup's "The B-Side" at @stannswarehouse on @TodayTix! Tap here:… https://t.co/EFS16L0xtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Viviane6677 @gabryluce @GizellaGerics1 @roberta_lanzoni @mich_onelove @Jose93571656 @consuiglesias… https://t.co/dmgLglxy0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I now fight with the Night King! I just entered for a chance to attend the #GameofThrones S8 premiere. How do you p… https://t.co/8q9eFIjX4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[She Cannot have it both.for a week she's chasing a staff member around  sexually harrasing the man staff,  says rep… https://t.co/J5sN1k9rJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day !!! 💃🏽🌎✨Flashin’ it back to a killer day working with these 3 fierce women for uwil… https://t.co/lmrMZZ2p0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hydroponically Speaking in 7th grade...Enjoying lettuce grown hydroponically @spmeagles @MagnetSidi https://t.co/qzDQI8xeXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorChzhead Thank you. He was the typical Patriots fan. I hold zero value in him or his intelligence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angsala67 @Fernand80760480 @LilianaSnchez9 @mainzina @szalacain1 @jobragag @Cantero9Vega Buena semana para todos q… https://t.co/jgIw2Nr3fQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@la_patilla Ay Nico, como deberiamos llamarte a ti que le entregastes el pais a Cuba?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBurchard So glad you enjoyed the article, Bret. I hope I was able to do justice to your dad and his achievements.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndiaEaton @ccblueyes70 Fifteen times, why isn't anyone seeing this as a problem?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliaH_1 I’d say dishwater blond... haha. Would you prefer, dark blond? That should work, because you are not a brunette.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiepwisdom305 Girl my dad got a pic somewhere of me as a baby chillin next to a alligator on the lawn when we lived in Ft. Lauderdale 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashaEats @ccatmpt @SLBriscoe @thatsVeryKari @Cbp8Cindy @FionaMorgan79 @joneill55 @suziday123 @cowineco… https://t.co/lcNZMVBciS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALT351 @ProudResister @GOP @realDonaldTrump @senatemajldr I thought McConnell was called a Turtle. He does remind me of a turtle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ali_Viceroy @CNN All of them. He's too stupid not to have followers...the way of the 🌎.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The woman running the troubled Richard Allen #charterschools in Dayton and Hamilton is the same person who the stat… https://t.co/vX6PLUNJ1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You’re deflecting and failing again... https://t.co/nlU0LOCkQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estancia fans got Caught Misbehaving. Twice.  https://t.co/HQGLpUbAcz #abq via @abqjournal]]></document><document><![CDATA[on sunday i'll be recording my stint on the @SSRpod, talking about my ultimate favorite kid's book: The Golden Comp… https://t.co/W9eY6FNVrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what is underappreciated by college girls these days? A hair brush. Brush your hair children.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAMSAFAREE you still are who you are, but I can’t thank you enough for presenting that “Beez in the Trap” beat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy midterms I’m straight up not having a good time https://t.co/6ASHagl4e1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bleu Devil Classic Weekend Scholarship Fundraiser  #GeauxDU 💙 @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/jcFWITWSnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rocknsoul1319 Same in WV. If the sun doesn’t come out &amp; stay for a while soon, I’m going to run away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last-minute #ValentinesDay gifts 🎁 : 💐 , 🍫 and more from #Amazon in 2 hours https://t.co/y38KYN2AwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valentinavee @blakistonr @trello @Shopify @salesforce @Apple @netflix 😂 Certainly learning to be resourceful]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been on sextpanther regularly tho! If u want to chat with me directly and flirt/talk about sex contact me… https://t.co/UakfsNm0iO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeathByLipstik @MarkClarkster @edgyerin @CCHarrison67 @Emdaffodils @deedee_regan @Jay_Rombach @Resist37 @three313… https://t.co/KHCB6wfRXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @jacobcollier, look what I found at Goodwill! 🤗 https://t.co/SKjIXLMyfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your girlfriend doesn’t humo you in the wile of the grocery store, is she even you girlfriend?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zack puts up with a lot and I’m so thankful for him staying with me and not giving up me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maternity leave is fun. Brandon and I have spent the day napping, eating junk food, and watching trash tv.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time for the weekly special! This week we are offering Kidder Infant/Toddler life vests for only $12.95, regul… https://t.co/X83JATsljb]]></document><document><![CDATA[CNN Sanders Town Hall | Demcratic Presidential Town Hall [8PM] 2/25/2019 https://t.co/q2GSSNVemD via @YouTube… https://t.co/M6s8EJe7Z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does the #WWEChamber and #TWD  gotta be on at the same time, on the same night?😧 thankfully, AMC does the encor… https://t.co/QoyKkgbC3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy nerdgasm, Batman! 🦀🤖🦀 @ Universal CityWalk Hollywood https://t.co/TJDEfR1Fk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#d123 #olhms lovely Leahy sisters!!! Where is Louie? @ Oak Lawn-Hometown MiddleSchool https://t.co/GiAhxMzpRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miami beached man-o-war. #sobe #sandyoffice @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/BkCRjDhwHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN #KamalaHarris: questions in #NewHampshire have nothing to do with your race. You have no experience in governa… https://t.co/gdmO9Oks96]]></document><document><![CDATA[waiting for my man to get home from work so i can give him something to eat and then go get some food.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vladimirpadrino Cuando vas a poner a tu amante y el rancho que le compraste en Costa Rica con dinero del narcotráf… https://t.co/iDuzoWLtxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jefflombardo You’re entirely more self sufficient than the usual traveler. Also, you like a varied amount of exper… https://t.co/NyO82bF5fa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyTalk @ChrisStigall @ewarren Exactly. I worked min wage at thrift drug in college then found ups at $8 per ho… https://t.co/nBzE6OiCR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_alpacas @PicPoet @metoffice @ThePhotoHour @itvanglia @ChrisPage90 @PhotographyWx @CloudAppSoc… https://t.co/VEPfCtOdE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it through my first quarter for school ! Got an A on my finals, Only 2 more quarters to go ! #futureMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidwleslie @QAortheHighway Glad to be there and appreciate all the participation... always excited to share the… https://t.co/WFQA4wPMuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love our dancing gal 💃🏼 A successful evening @AlexaGreenNews @RileyKids #bethehopenow https://t.co/90gCyXmNR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrannaWintour You’re right. Up until very recently I wanted to believe he was the innocent, child like character I… https://t.co/l1jM8u910y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stretch it out! #stretch #muscles #boxing #feelgood  #combatcamp #lyfefit  #health #fitness #fit fitnessmodel… https://t.co/bGqPBtVSxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[bro fuck you for dragging a dead mans name through the mud ON HIS BIRTHDAY. I’ll consider what you’re saying once y… https://t.co/MAWNpxOFKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plot twist: Las familias de ambos  donaron cientos de miles de dólares a las campañas políticas en Estados Unidos p… https://t.co/A8EFcbF7QE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BulldogBen @Newlysane @ninampls @nitajojo66 @nomorefreebeer @notabotinFl @OdysseusOfWinds @OETKB2 @OKane33Lysa… https://t.co/m8yNWt73Lg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jager and Brewski #leonbergersofinstagram #leoslovesnow @ Rockport, Massachusetts https://t.co/NlQKpXwPfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can list of ton of traits and behaviors that black children, both male and female without fathers usually possess… https://t.co/Krk5tCqAfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pockets! ⚡️ I am tweaking our first Shirtdress and picking fabric currently. 💫 I’m loving the pockets in this dress… https://t.co/JTHLZTS7yl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zarinacornelius “If she don’t want to fuck, I get on my skateboard and I skate past her”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS #MAGA @JudicialWatch RETWEET! AMERICA NEEDS TO KNOW THE TRUTH! 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🗽GOD BLESS PRESIDENT TRUMP AND AMERICA!… https://t.co/2HnzQp7x53]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you visit @freestore_15104 to give gfett some umbrellas and clothes and she sends you home with a box full of… https://t.co/ileLyCxx23]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your nail salon is in tune to your needs 💕 #ArnoldPalmerInvitational https://t.co/zhB8607z6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[The liveliest he’s been all day. @ North Ridgeville, Ohio https://t.co/D21jgsa4mp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nacho_Mama78 @OurRevolution @Randy_rando To use hidden existing cures. Yes many cures are hidden for profits. Read… https://t.co/YrJtS3HCb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[no matter how cool i become, ill never be as cool as @yelyahwilliams and i just have to accept that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marvin Williams completely reinvented his three-point game in 2015-16. For him to score a season-high 28 points thu… https://t.co/Lw9BODxwDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergioEchazarr5 @FOXSportsMX @UpalabraMX @ruubenrod Veamos lo positivo ;))]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ain’t it funny how the simple things in life are the only things that really matter” -JATL  This really hits home lately]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bridget8195 Omg make a move next you see him!! (But also don’t get fired!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[somebody punch me in the chest cause I’m in my feelings rn and don’t wanna be]]></document><document><![CDATA[American Heart Association is here today to promote awareness of heart health and signs of a stroke. FAST - Facial… https://t.co/vUhHfaFKXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleRichards I am about done with this show. Now you are calling Dr. John Sessa a liar and manipulator? This is DO… https://t.co/WccYAjLJ7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Netanyahu @tv7israelnews @CherokeeNation I don't know much about this account but personal abuse is a real issue i… https://t.co/yLel5vMALZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChromeDome520 @PadmeAmidala217 @DiamondandSilk @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Is that man a using this woman?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alt_FedEmployee @TeaPainUSA @zynr07 @DonaldJTrumpJr Or own a firearm, which will give a lot of large game animals peace!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Lost in the sea” #ScubaDiving #Florida #diving https://t.co/UdPr4t98UN]]></document><document><![CDATA[And without faith it is impossible to please him, for whoever would draw near to God must believe t…… https://t.co/1b9q4d0GfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scairp114 @Merleliz @g_boothbrain @NYC_DOT @nicolegelinas @StreetsblogNYC @Adrian_Benepe Of course. This isn’t abo… https://t.co/bP2UDLbSu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Migrants are legally required to present their documented rights by the way not a forged document we have seen even… https://t.co/uHONW62rWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emma_penton LMAO they literally make us run all the time here, since i’ve been here my legs got super toned]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib In : peoplism" are lityle girls forcedvtp marry adult men and boys are raped on a daily basis because " its their " cilture"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swervingghoes I said what i said.. and last time i checked we all had the same emojis on our phone, you own none of them 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iamdevinnsmart Welcome to the party of moral values. Happy to have you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevehendley @ChuckyUF Good point ! I don’t tend to get too excited for super early recruits either . These kids h… https://t.co/yEfJKxW1wO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ss_gladys @abuelitalizz @Angeline_Celin @hada_protectora @MensajesLuz @MacloviaMontoy3 @MarcelaErcia… https://t.co/YsRX7fJZxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[74/100 #indigo Justin's indigo textured shirt. . . #100daysofcolor #roygbiv #texture #warm #winterwear @ Stella's D… https://t.co/CMqCCYvNFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be at @Brand_Innovator #BISummit today for two (yes 2!) sessions: 10a part of a group of ah-mazing women… https://t.co/2DFvOs0gV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[State hasn't won 3 straight since the 1980's? Wow. Can't get far in a tournament like that. #JustSayin https://t.co/PeRtArmHJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ordered a pizza like an hour and a half ago but I’m too polite to bitch about it. However, I thought I would only… https://t.co/7YwHvNwqpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[we left the bar tonight bc paige had heartburn.. so this is what getting old feels like, eh? 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an awesome day for the #shamrocknrun #5k #10k! @laureltechnical thelmas_sports_nook phnfoundation @ Thelma's S… https://t.co/D9RH4RxmHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Essential read #cloud economics. Flexible, scalable, cost efficient cloud is the building block of all digital tran… https://t.co/uAAaz2vwuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCVIM Just kidding I’ll be using this as a template forever https://t.co/Cb3v2vAiJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IviRoller @twitt_witter @CT3GUITAR @wilkesbarrePA @Chrstine16stone @GavinRossdale Hoping &amp; praying 🙏 you’ll get through this♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg your family as well as the other victims and survivors are in my prayers. 🙏❤️🙏❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar @GlamandGore Can I assist for either of you!? You're both my top two favorite youtubers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know so I walked away and went to their preferred customer counter. The very nice person there was able t… https://t.co/XGB9emtnWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellie, you are such a gracious and thoughtful person. What an honor to know you!]]></document></documents></author>