<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Yo #NICAR19, if you like open source tools (including one by @BrizAndrew), head to Cardiff ASAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib You kinda made a boo boo didn't you there lady. Let's impeach you now too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Such love has no fear, because perfect love expels all fear. If we are afraid, it is for fear of punishment, and t… https://t.co/mLcwHotyzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertmays Damn.  Excited to see how this plays out.. hope they can manage a late 1st or quality player]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Kettler That case is no longer good law. Incitement is now judged by a different standard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a DB not just corner that means I can play nickel or Safety I’ll get in done no matter what]]></document><document><![CDATA[Severe Damage BMW X-5 Very difficult repair due to the severity and location. Our customer wanted to preserve his B… https://t.co/fPdbizhJ4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[The “In Home Banking” Online Course is full fledge running! Derrica will be holding her course for the youngins soo… https://t.co/dJQiXoJIsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out at signorvineyards today from 2:30-5:30PM come have some wine with me! @ Signor Vineyards https://t.co/fIMpogdTSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuisGarzam89 Keep in eye on it, I see someone who love to steal it from you.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CLEUCl Actually white male leaders because Brazil is like 100% white, It seems]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sheep want good food. And they can tell the difference between a well-prepared meal and something you put in the m… https://t.co/6mCqoDZuz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristensonday “ How might we...” apply design thinking to A2J, probono workflow, legal delivery &amp; more.… https://t.co/mlkKse9Lax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sneakersteal NIKE BOWFIN LOOK LIKE THE BALENCIAGA RUNNERS WITH THE STRAPS ACROSS THE TOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@medcitynews you guys gotta fix these takeover ads on mobile. They don’t work (literally) and I can never get to the story from an email.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JtTownsend22 @KirkHerbstreit Actually it will look like this, this time of the year. I live 20 miles from… https://t.co/NmHrU5JeZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickBieker @SpencerJCox @GovHerbert @UtahAG Yes, that’s true. We need the task forces NOW.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mizzvaine That’s the signal to rest: I think your body is suffering from overworking. Baba ang sustansya mo: that’… https://t.co/iZKH9iSv4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[This country was a lot stronger when Billy Mays was alive... jus saying]]></document><document><![CDATA[... pero si las yales pueden bellaquear en la casa ¿pa qué pelear por una taquilla y llamar a las noticias porque se agotaron?   🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great 2019 design refresh meeting with the team today. We concentrated on our page layout column structures.… https://t.co/1GHGcdzw5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebrewer I HOPE that motortrend does a solid and brings this to the US. I sincerely want to watch this show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Miami come and see me this weekend. I’m performing @ https://t.co/GDQOHxHdVJ yeah!]]></document><document><![CDATA[previo a los Oscars ... #saturday #hefe ##hefeweizen #widmerbros #widmerbrothersbrewing #portland #theoriginal… https://t.co/mZs3y30IsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good #Tuesday morning friends! Are you ready? Winter isn’t done yet! Check out the blog and every @WAVY_News newsca… https://t.co/Niz8el21E3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was simply a huge honor for @thesomersteam to be welcomed and introduced by a real estate icon, Gary Keller, to… https://t.co/XHgCpYWggP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler That traitorous bastard sure as hell is not MY POTUS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to my next trip to Brazil where we will host 3 Hero Maker 1-day events in 3 different cities! https://t.co/eVFMXLgGT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyBrunoShow @secupp Tony you are by far my favorite Philly guy!!! Please come back...... just don’t bring Josh with you 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cruelty-free💄, swings and bubbles sounds like a place I want to visit. Congrats @TheLipBar]]></document><document><![CDATA[After seeing Gary Clark Jr. on SNL a couple weeks back I am thinking a @JohnMayer @GaryClarkJr “Guitar Face” Face O… https://t.co/pzN9WCDHg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephanieskene Let me know when you want to play. 😁 #CoD #GameNight #ChargedUp with @RedBullCanada https://t.co/4GVUtX09HI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear ladies,   3 amazing guys are in need of wedding dates this summer. If interested, please contact via Twitter D… https://t.co/O7rKBVJGX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You lie.  Learn to speak properly.  But nothing was misinterpreted!!! Those were your words.  So fuck off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took this screenshot on January 8th. #RaiderNation https://t.co/DHL9K0EgpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders @peaceplay We certainly shld sharply cut Military; as an irresponsible Nation, out of control, driven b… https://t.co/znNGFkGXtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Razin' sum ICP up in hur! And no, I'm not a #Juggalo. I'm just a #Juleokin who enjoys the music, without the...hrmh… https://t.co/Aebanl5SA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention Long Island! Tonite!! I'll be at The Whale's Tale in Long Beach solo acoustic 9pm til midnite!!! Madonna… https://t.co/CsHxgkKT5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bIackcindy Remember when he landed on 2 people when he performed live? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 27th 2019. A very cold -21C morning in Dorval. @ Dorval, Quebec https://t.co/QCQ64ntRQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the statement would be wasted, since they wouldn't understand. #hilarity #laugh #smile #farcical https://t.co/mxg5eknQqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perhaps, just perhaps, "The Mueller Report" due next week is simply a status on the investigation for Barr?  Can't… https://t.co/R9fn9e1xkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[A platform that enables experimentation leads to innovation! - @unity3d #unity3d #MadeWithUnity #unitytips #gamedev… https://t.co/AQmWu0qZYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being “tall, dark &amp; ugly” 😭, having “nappy” hair, having a gap and wearing glasses. It was rough lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOGETHER.  #fortunatefearlessforty @ North Houston, Texas https://t.co/SJ9SrxpYXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao I know parents from around here that disown their daughter cause she dating a black dude.....but they ain’t ra… https://t.co/2pO5mYcnfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUYS THE @ArizonaCoyotes WON A GAME THAT I WENT TO  That legit hasn't happened since 2011]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary lol https://t.co/Ejxn3K7wUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[God it feels great to be talking GoT fan theories again.. means it’s so close to coming back. My prediction is Jon… https://t.co/MpB16nI2tC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not that I'd ever be invited, but the only way I'm going into a Mar-A-Lago is with a HazMat Suit.  Not as an Anti-T… https://t.co/vGYiq7mAQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know that all things are working for my good. He’s intentional, never failing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gillette After using two of popular brands that ship to your home, Gillette blades cut so much closer and last longer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBReich They won’t because they are desperate to be reelected. They aren’t leaders, but followers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @KatieLobosco Like why are you liberals worried about the deficit now? You didn't give a damn when Obama doubled our debt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers @AprilDRyan Their 15 seconds of fame are way over. Can’t wait until trump is tossed, and a New Demo… https://t.co/ZqmKHjRyeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[UMass falls behind for the fourth straight game. Graham McPhee gives BC a 1-0 lead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If You In A Relationship Delete Me I Dont Need That Negative Energy On My TimeLine 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn’t happen often but getting outplayed, out hustled and out coached. By a lesser opponent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great news -- our amendment (Neguse Amdt. #70) to follow #Colorado's lead and implement voter pre-registration for… https://t.co/WrLy93L8wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cinbinbains @StewieGilchrist @valbcat Yeah it’s very foggy. I think this is a travesty. He’s going to spend the re… https://t.co/oC8FG9A8N6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @DogginTrump @judieyoung Plus it is trying to convert me--I type in Good Morning and it comes out "Good Mormon"]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve watched this video 100 times and I still can’t focus on what she’s talking about. Wow women are trash smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Union Pacific train in San Jose, CA, USA, crossing the Guadalupe river.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Igor must of listened to my man @JaredDudley619 because we seen last night why vets matter... only rookies to see t… https://t.co/H9vvMbdUlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetsMeetAtTheQB @DLineVids @jbbigbear @WillieCashmore This is beautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertGarciaLB @sliccardo @LondonBreed @Mayor_Steinberg @LibbySchaaf @AjaLBrown @KamalaHarris Neither you or Kamal… https://t.co/3rWCFa6tli]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Splash series“, watercolor and color pencil on paper 💦 @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/H49vcVoI7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of the .@GOP railing about Socialism is merely a reflection of their collective greed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pintsandpoetry Dude y’all gotta to the burgh - I got a spare bedroom - next time reds play come up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Would it help if I told Killary, yes, yes, yes, please run? 3rd time is the charm, or 3 time loser.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Running thread from the Houston Under Armour thread (Premium)  https://t.co/oOGJAwoF1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[In tomorrow’s print @hhjnews : @CGTCAthletics sophomore guard @ShesAHooper_15 is playing her best ball when it coun… https://t.co/Lii47xYtAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[R.I.P. Peter Tork of the Monkees. #Monkees, @TorkTweet https://t.co/b2yhigfoGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los favores se hacen de corazón sin esperar nada a cambio pero cuando pides uno a quien le has ayudado y te lo nieg… https://t.co/2yFAZhvOSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComfortablySmug Really?? Have you ever met hillary rotten clinton?? I thought you had?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just hit me: why in “Rocky,”’the greatest #Philadelphia movie of all time, is the dog named after a Chicago Be… https://t.co/XuC1jlt1a8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialSPGB @StewartThomasD SOCIALISM IS FORCE https://t.co/mAoata1ik6]]></document><document><![CDATA[MLB seriously needs to address this situation Pittsburgh's increasingly cold relationship with the Pirates is an ex… https://t.co/npX8aIn5vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wish everyone just turned off politics and noticed the beautiful world around us #politcalsphere… https://t.co/7kAslcwYoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendaryEnergy At first I thought you said Texas was a scam. We was about to be fighting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danny_Apajee No ones come up with a funnier joke since I left? Disappointed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHANTS WIN!!!  @CoastalBeachVB beat UT Martin 5-0; takes on Eckerd in under 4 hours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tthayer_03 @rolldog24 @bscatcat @RobertH5642 Cut back on your trade offers last year too, right? I was thinking yo… https://t.co/ZQiU9kKCo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xTMLxPinder17 @NYIslanders Coming from a fan base that makes death threats to their goaltender and posts shit like… https://t.co/Ptz03LSKpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump but you said nothing about them dying in ICE detention due to poor care. you say nothing about the… https://t.co/EEhJe6JMCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkRoeTv I actually wanted to be Rick, from Brenda’s France trip. #superman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FLOTUS @ericbolling @WestgateVegas https://t.co/aXndymbYjf https://t.co/o9AOJEUKsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all know what would make summer 2020 dope ? A fire drake album. And I ain’t even a huge drake fan like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[28 이와 같이 그리스도께서도 많은 사람의 죄를 없애려고 단번에 희생의 제물이 되셨습니다. 그리고 다시 오실 때에는 죄를 위해서가 아니라 자기를 기다리는 사람들에게 구원을 주시기 위해서 두 번째 나타나실 것입니다.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pbnjays @Lvminnati Do you wanna hear a popular theory or my theory cus I think mine is right]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dracut basketball team is ready for its Garden party https://t.co/82gmnhHZAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came across my old phone from high school. Meanwhile the pooka shell necklace and angsty Blink-182 CD are missing i… https://t.co/ha8UDMdqzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sstaffordtweet Part of the sadness of the end of home @FSUHoops season will be not watching @sstaffordtweet go abs… https://t.co/SEyXQCaycN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t take anymore of this @KentuckyMBB orgy on @CollegeGameDay. Vols are a No. 1 ranked underdog. Let’s go Vols ..… https://t.co/YwfrodtHg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@georgevhulme @harari_yuval Wumen says one needs to set aside all attachment to P&amp;L and the gate will reveal itself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeSchneid6 @IFeelLikeKamaaI You can get so much further in life once you drop weed! People don’t like to admit i… https://t.co/gGHjiqlx29]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Oatmeal Stout by @WorkhorseBrews @ Workhorse Brewing Co. — https://t.co/Yznyvmbv5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funniest Facebook Photoshop Fails #laughter #chuckle #smile #absurd https://t.co/8nWDrZu9NI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaDGilbert Good morning Jess! Happy Sunday to you too my friend. ☕️☕️☺️💙❤️💗💛💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bare: A Pop Opera opens at Coronado Playhouse this Friday!!! Get your tickets!!! And when you come, please bring me… https://t.co/ywnW8XOWTE]]></document></documents></author>