<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Happy President’s Day!  Sharing a pertinent quote from my favorite fictional president... https://t.co/7BFvkFpuA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ACSMNews Summit is next week! @jmjakicic &amp; I are ready! Here’s a glimpse into how we approach connecting… https://t.co/rWurrhoknZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[its 2019 now my crushes should like me back but i guess misogyny is alive n well huh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_For_LIfe @AmirAminiMD Why are the Dems running on his platform then? If nothing else pay attention to where… https://t.co/RAJuDDY86e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day @alnicastro13 @PuddingtownDuck @shalimar964 https://t.co/ySixOHFQRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband’s music direction to Alexa has ruined my @Spotify suggested playlists. However he does the dishes and fe… https://t.co/vMNg623wvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bonita noche para todos mis amigos y familiares, que tengan una noche espectacular y un hermoso despertar dios me l… https://t.co/5zh8zIiF8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t understand why exes talk crap on eachother... like didn’t u love me or something like that LMAO shut ur mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday RUNday fun @charmcityrun charmcityrunlocustpoint with a test RUN @brooksrunning and Brews… https://t.co/pQqbnx1R5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @IvankaTrump Her idea of work is furrowing her brow and then Botox for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Mastercard Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/iCQyT7Vb5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dysfunctional07 @nekusa93 I tried calling all theee numbers and got nothing so idk]]></document><document><![CDATA[You struggle to let go of everything that is bothering you. You struggle to just enjoy the moment. You find it hard… https://t.co/lJVGm4o29Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma fight him if he don’t make it in my mouth getting me all wet and shit 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[every time I open my fucking heart and mind its manipulated and abused and I’m left feeling so fucking used]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsraNomani @AIFDemocracy Thank you for your work. I think the Muslim Reform movement is having an impact that Isla… https://t.co/0y7xUzuZqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me bragging last night: I’ve been getting such great sleep lately.  Me five hours later: Can’t sleep, I’ll just che… https://t.co/AxfMtsrbG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lsirikul omggggg Laura! cant wait for your thoughts tho I'm sure itll be in line with all the glee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amante de la comida hipercalorica y los hombres que no intentar decirme qué hacer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ramon Celis did a GIS survey of the fortified site of Guiengola. Goal was to understand indigenous colonization of the isthmus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charbonneau: En 2016, 74% producteurs répondants à une enquête croyaient que les changements climatiques auront eff… https://t.co/uKMtiqHKK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmm. You know, we really need to give back land we’ve used for military bases, the U.S. I mean.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember... your value doesn’t decrease based on someone’s inability to see your worth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bottle feeding baby goats Silvies Valley Ranch. @SilviesRetreat has a Kidding program guests can participate in. To… https://t.co/tttgAn2bPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swhaye88 @MrRonHastings @RepMarkMeadows Well that’s good to hear, thank you 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@honeydeluxed @CoraIsabel5 There is one it’s on my story on insta rn :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohmy1989s @swiftlyinstyle @TS7Track3 Wait so is the logo actually dice or does it just look like dice?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#whosyourvalentine I’ll be ✂️ at the 💈shop taking care of all my clients  #happyvalentinesday 💕#positivevibes  . .… https://t.co/2SkCLulaRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pensé Rendirme... Pero Luego Noté Que Alguien Seguía Mis Pasos... #MiTita👧🏻 #MiBoysito👦🏻#AgradecidaConElDeArriba👆🏻… https://t.co/r6F7BV0eg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennValentyne @cutesygfc @Q107Toronto With your looks, personality and energy you belong in front of the camera.… https://t.co/dHUVxuVb2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredrikSewell @YouTube You are my favorite character on that show!! ♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love a good “box-packing” assembly line.  . . . #lovenodenialfoods #poshnosh #gifting #foodgifts #mail… https://t.co/cbfBLwWpwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Martins Creek, Pennsylvania https://t.co/YNHfzEKvBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank god they are spending time fixing the problems that are threatening their league!!!!!! I was getting worried… https://t.co/WQ2LJqOO15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judithamc @CBCKatie @CBCNews For someone who styles himself a Feminist, Ju$tin of all peoplekind should know by now NO MEANS NO !!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabbieKDrice @madlezbabayo I can't wait for Iowa when Bernie gets like 3%]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlbluedevilclub @merceinmann @mwhiteburgh @MtLebanonSports @Lebo_SS19 @MTSD_ATHLETICS Aww!  That’s awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tithenai I have your spoon!! It shall remain my prisoner until you pay the ransom of a cup of tea with you! Mwahha… https://t.co/h7Ro75XihH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is such a fickle thing. Whether your months old, 28, 52, or 90; life is borrowed and can be taken away in the… https://t.co/AEFHQ7k1bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msmorgan1968 Every dog in a kill shelter sense thier fate...they smell the death.. they feel the fear...they hear… https://t.co/FQ0OrE8irL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianershepherd @m_jneira @DiamondandSilk @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Thanks for sharing. He is not perfect. No one cla… https://t.co/zy7PGFjgwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There’s too many people on this earth, we need a new plague”-Dwight Schrute]]></document><document><![CDATA[Klobuchar ate salad with her comb, then made aide clean it https://t.co/ySjOwLT08b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to rain (and later hail) our Fun Run became a Fun-Circuit-Workout! Kindergarten still rocked it! @RCSDOrchard https://t.co/NuIFgb2qu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicken and corn chowder sounds gross. Nice kratom poster though. Glad you found something good out of all that sta… https://t.co/nChcz2LBjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to senior banquet and only 75 days till graduation 🎓✨ https://t.co/nrLIXjBnAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marketed “Balanced Literacy” programs and products encourage guessing with phonics or decoding implicitly taught. D… https://t.co/o3KwigYIR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great example of how CIEE programs are life changing.  Read how four alumni from our Aquatic Ecosystems and Susta… https://t.co/jVrq0irWG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattatouille @messyepicure The Asians actually in Asia laugh at it, though. Like it's good for capturing Euro/Amer… https://t.co/V4Kl3ed7pw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING One woman struck by a truck.   WHAT I KNOW:   ▪️She has “serious, life threatening injuries” ▪️Suspect dr… https://t.co/ZkT1iCy4og]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s almost 2 in the morning i’m trying to go to sleep and I can’t get shake by @JesseMcCartney out of my head things aren’t going well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendenfingers Also come on, at least come up with an original and better tweet 😂 https://t.co/BjFzBJsbM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd. Ceramic dogs. @Hillcrest_BCPS @HillcrestPTA @visualartsbcps https://t.co/cP4eklN5Wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the privilege of eating lunch with @BrianOkcwalz today! He will always be the G.O.A.T. (greatest of all time) i… https://t.co/2ydkerHMaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Respete señor Pirri ese comentario me parece de muy mal gusto. 😡😡 Creo que es a usted a quien le gusta la morcilla… https://t.co/Hhh9m7a0m8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCRAtberg and @KCRAMelanie Why, in the mountains, does 80 close due to whiteout conditions, but 50 doesn't?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming today at 5:15 PM on @MyNews13: a report by @Becharareports on Valencia's 10-week training for Apartment Main… https://t.co/XxHQQ5pX3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @CorruptCt may end up in receivership. I suppose Congress can meet in Extraordinairy Session to li… https://t.co/VzI6HVhqkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Massive amounts” - do you even know how birth control works???                   If you believe this, I have disco… https://t.co/VrsY5fWAug]]></document><document><![CDATA[can we talk about how it wasn’t even loose like he was deadass choking me akdks i love that for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heather Ahlstrom Kosec started the 50K Birkie Skate! https://t.co/Ts3LP8Jpud #Birkie2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you come home to your dog outside, who was inside when you left, only to realize you left the back door open.… https://t.co/K3IuIeG65y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready 2 B U? 🔎w NEW HOME? 🌞 Dreams/Reality 🖥 https://t.co/Z4JEz45tiZ 🖥🏘🏢 #newhouse 🎬🎁🏡🏢🏘🎈#lovelife ♥️🌞 #newcondo… https://t.co/NevTcZ8Pfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold your tongue, Woman who called Michelle Obama an  https://t.co/SIXulX8LHA via @Hedgebz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poison Ivy - This makes me laugh #comedy #snicker #smile #ludicrous https://t.co/UM9VU3qkc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denverpost We already know this ass is not good for our health‼️📣🖤🖤🖤🖤😡😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juanjcastro 💯💯 You nailed it! Men have killed their wives, but here the horror was a woman sought revenge via a cl… https://t.co/MDqdMmWlTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson @realDonaldTrump Drummer dena,keep your buggy nose out,keep looking for a job,instead]]></document><document><![CDATA[INSPIRED | A year ago, in January 2018 to be exact, I made an unbreakable promise to myself that I would commit my… https://t.co/JPwKxkzlgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in Washington, DC? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/s9NyET7IBD #WomenSTEM #aviation]]></document><document><![CDATA[the amount of love I’ve received already this morning is immeasurable, I love life, living is my favorite thing to do 💛⚡️🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[*****MISSING DOG ROXY***** ROXY has been missing from downtown Medford since early this morning. If you have any in… https://t.co/POb0FZGerS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@captain_thib I saw this on IG and had to come to twitter just to applaud you. 👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽 #NeverWereTruerWordsSpoken]]></document><document><![CDATA[tfw my mom wanted me to change my name to Erica https://t.co/HrGpCUOgxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker @New_Narrative @jdawsey1 Kim must be so proud of his friend (newest dictator)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianbattsjr @Coachjnewman @LBJSports @FanstandATX @centxhoops @varsity_news Congratulations baby boy!🤗 Well deser… https://t.co/y4fbxw6wRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[At my funeral sit me up so I can see if my sister is wearing my clothes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrific thread about art tests! I learned a lot! Art making friends, give it a read!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrcastner My skype name is Mrs.Sandler85 would you like to call us? I am excited to skype on March 1st at 8:30 MST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MassRoots @scapelliti It's because Hospitals get lots of money from big Pharms, not medical marijuana... its discusting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because of you, #SOTB2019 is trending on Twitter.  More than 300 tweets using the hashtag were sent during the even… https://t.co/vgGiQkb1BX]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay for my vday gift should i get a... hurry tho bc i’m trynna go now haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UeRightonq @epidemika @colbertlateshow @EllenPage Didn’t you at least watch the video of her before forming your opinion?]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy 21st birthday to my soul sister ❤️ thank you for always making me laugh with your bakwaas 😅 there’s no one el… https://t.co/5M2zhoN4Ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[why is my most stressful week of school the week of formal? i’m about to throw hands cause i’m already stressed abo… https://t.co/mkce4Q9lcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait.....   If you have two cars with the same insurance account, and you and the other person crash (accidentally… https://t.co/byGnrhVVEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey it’s us! On the big screen!! Loved being a part of this amazing project! #canolaconnect #canolachat]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/f1shf8uhfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BostonWest80111 @JataTheGod @cvpayne Meadows STATED that was his motive. DUH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Lion_Athletics had a great weekend supporting @Lion_Track. @GeorgePincock got to hand out the NCAA DII trophy’s t… https://t.co/dnoUHwaPbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaLeeThomps8 HI-I am cold cause it's like 15 and we are going to get more snow-how are you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just lost $20 and I don’t feel like searching for it but fuck whoever finds it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oscarjoyo It was soooooo good! Very surprised by everything but great nonetheless]]></document><document><![CDATA[In between sniffling and sneezing, I'm reading @Shteyngart's Lake Success, which is so good]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m matching energy the remainder of 2019, so if you catch me acting different, you know why.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRyanHenry @villain_arts Send me info on who to contact for an appointment when your in Atlanta.. Help 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a beautiful day in Gulf Shores for immature and mature pelicans. @spann https://t.co/2mNzV3Bp3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cry___bb i don’t really know you, but if you need anyone to talk to i’m here. i’ve been in a similar situation and could relate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh... So that's what she's been pissed about? Ok. That makes sense.  #CLICK https://t.co/NkVv5N7Urf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in such shock, wow. I had the pleasure of working on the marketing campaign for his special just last year... w… https://t.co/sgjhDp7eUq]]></document></documents></author>