<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@seanpardo73 @BruceJo48327088 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump -Collusion with foreign agents to defraud voters IS a… https://t.co/eOKKPNENgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[GM HUMANS!! It’s Monday let’s go💪🏾💪🏾💪🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾💯💯💯🦀🦀🦀I @ Where You Wanna Be https://t.co/PfrngRtFBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 10:00 AM CST, Scott City [Scott Co, KS] EMERGENCY MNGR reports SNOW of 5.00 INCH https://t.co/niWg05SikS]]></document><document><![CDATA[nirvana lives .. rest in paradise kurt. blessing me w your band + music.. 2017 up until now. wow ur mind Mr Cobain.… https://t.co/OnsU6mEmmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoundsnColor @markboone219 @MapoTofuAddict @peterjhasson @MeghanMcCain I heard a Democratic President called them… https://t.co/6HYNNuGAAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reason maybe platinum. Catalytic converters contain platinum, rhodium, and palladium. The metals are expensive,… https://t.co/xyRlc6N4zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd only really want celebrity status to make it so people just generally know to refer to me as "his royal gayness" or something like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw @LindaGuijarro1 @GOP said Trump's Tax Cuts will pay for themselves. A LIE! We now have a $1 TRILLIO… https://t.co/Lg2rYJrkvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump wants UK and EU to 'take back' 800 IS prisoners or the US will release them  https://t.co/UUocjfSwSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbbyfin @madisongesiotto I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quincy H… https://t.co/xc18Mdigys]]></document><document><![CDATA[She couldn't afford an apartment in D.C. She is completely full of shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democratic presidential candidate Andrew Yang says universal basic income isn’t a socialist policy  https://t.co/i3p4qv4Gzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule Not surprising from a POTUS who undermines America's sense of right and wrong, moral authority, ru… https://t.co/Ez0EOzy28q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob Bradley ..”No quiero que el derbi de #LAFC VS #LAGalaxy se llame más El Tráfico ... se debe llamar LA Clásico”… https://t.co/HvTSlLhnxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interracial relationships should not be frowned upon, specifically where there’s a black man dating a White woman.… https://t.co/qpH4s7NbcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Man the whole Cohen thing is obviously another Democrat driven bunch of crap period another waist… https://t.co/K1hJcGMr3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanRossSapp oh i think someone is getting fired.... https://t.co/Yt17NrFnRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck seeing Braun Strowman get these hands on Colin Jost live in New York #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_maxmaxed @martynschmoll The system was functioning fine without cars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol it really took him that many punches to get an actual hole in the wall 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2Urban_Wolf @WolfVivienne007 @1Urban_Wolf @Hunt_4_Hunters @4Farm_Animals HUH? AHOLES!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Bullshit, your highest priority is trying not to get caught on all of your bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the reasons he is doing this is so the White nationals can speak hate at colleges!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaudesBBQ @carridea @Nic_O_tine “Trust me, I don’t want to touch you.” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephBornstein @BenSasse No it definitely was. My point is that things like Apollo or 9/11 bring us together. 9/1… https://t.co/iKCwSGrtbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@minasamizadeh @sarsanaee کلا اساتید علم‌وصنعت تو پایبندی به اصول این‌چنینی زبانزدن! حالا تازه پروپزال اول راه دفاع… https://t.co/CXYCgJmrse]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, how awesome was @wheelerpro45 yesterday? I re pondering last year, during his struggles, if it was ever gonna r… https://t.co/1mxUP6S1s9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If any of you live out there give me a holler and we can catch a few cold ones. It would be nice to have friends  in my new hood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Corygrant1987 @PeterSchiff Um, 3 phases of Q.E and 7 years of 0% interest tells me no bull market was created by Obama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your sugar daddy says he’s out of money :/ https://t.co/HjjfpznCCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaimeRdzNL Dale mantenimiento a las carreteras pony que están en pésimas condiciones si no date una vuelta por alg… https://t.co/MN8lMfJrU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The MP who cried wolf too many times for me to have any sympathy is ratcheting up her victim cred by going after he… https://t.co/KZzmQKuwOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonGeronimoShow Happy birthday to Abe Vigoda, who would have been 98 today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThriftyYinzr @TienesHugo @billpeduto Seems to me if he actually “CARED” about deaths he’d be more focused on Opioi… https://t.co/AEoqiVmhbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, looking at Trumps waistline, is his real intention to build a whale?? https://t.co/1i1YNJepCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@costareports They all have to go starting with King Spur of Bones Donald Trump https://t.co/LGGJVQEFQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThirdWayTweet @BilldeBlasio @NYDailyNews The moderates have gotten us nothing but a broken empty Democratic Party… https://t.co/eL32B0oohU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilijoyyy thank you for giving all of us Shefani fans something to fangirl over tonight. You were amazing and we'r… https://t.co/UaSXfLqqqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarthaMad99 @realDonaldTrump I’m an atheist but even I know god would be disappointed in the president]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marqed4death @PWInsidercom Doing my best.  Thanks. Just feel bad I can't do more audio.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so ready to get dirty again!! Alabama @SpartanRace in 6 days!! #dirtydanocr #dirtydan #notdirtyyet #dirty #mud… https://t.co/PPCfjDnQI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @justicedems Get your facts straight. Stop inventing and lying contriving and deceiving. You lie because you a… https://t.co/91OmAHy5Lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillGubrud @ATT When will oap start...and dates and times..I tried out a few yrs ago and bc i had enormous health… https://t.co/EIXqLH4PWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichWCampbell I adore your sense of style 💜  (I’m not sure if you really want compliments but here we are)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to add the Steak #carnivoreketodiet #wagnermanor #jdpbeatingdiabetes @ Citrus Heights, California https://t.co/r7obHjovUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quote of the Morning  " LOVE LIFE " Blessed to be Blessed https://t.co/ApVZBnC1cz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielC2903 @Kelmarie2003 I went 3 times in one week to make sure it wasn’t a fluke. Best meal I’ve ever had bar none.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jones and Stone are a couple of pathetic assholes. Both as narcissisitic as the Idiot-in-chief.  😠😠😠😠👎👎👎 They shoul… https://t.co/ERbYuyIpZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[“From the windows to the walls, until the sweat drips down your balls.” Have there EVER been more eloquent lyrics written?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods He does not care! He wants to be governor of Virginia no matter what!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#praprapranigga #nbawhiteboy #tf #hegotflow #tho #funny @ Lost Hills, California https://t.co/JSh7SAzsDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Stone is scratched tonight does this mean Ottawa isn’t going to sign him ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Assembly Districts are now announcing their votes for Public Advocate candidates, Williams is leading, but 48 went… https://t.co/lPkzGyXWfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you won't bother to look at a message I sent you then I'm done with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least when my daughter is learning about the Great Decline, I’ll have these tweets to show her not everybody was on board.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @jfraucci @eamon2tweet check out @messeduppuzzles seems like they are up your alley.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tfisher44 Just nod and try to smile without the tobacco juice dripping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Metallica was nothing short of epic. That was seriously one of the best shows I have ever seen! https://t.co/TdNrjWrfDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[RAYS HS State Champ Recap:  💥47 RAYS, 100+ swims 💥9 Individual State Titles  💥7 Pool Records - Canton 💥8 Ohio HS St… https://t.co/c09FPTjvih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WitchOfTheSith One of my best friends in high school and I played so much ping-pong his parents took the table awa… https://t.co/7vc1two0Eo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@booktraveller1 @GeekToMeRadio @UpToTASK @CBNostalgia @GeekVibesNation @BrianLeeOkert @MikeSchmidt09… https://t.co/DcBSiz0256]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to suggest an updated ingredients list for the True Chef (https://t.co/0uqukUL3LZ) Mediterranean Style… https://t.co/0n77T4bPOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeniseM171717 @AhmedBaba_ @realDonaldTrump But its in ya school. About fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth, no… https://t.co/N3VJzDvBQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truck convoy rolls into Halifax to press the Trudeau government for a pipeline]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @miiidnight_ Thank you, Laura. Hope you're day is great, too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManUtd do me a great favor by destroying arsenal tomorrow..am a @ChelseaFC supporter.. They be making noise all we… https://t.co/VzckrfRbIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump the number of people already convicted, the records of Cohen and Stone need to be released. Everyt… https://t.co/5gk759tKA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcoleman_31 That piece of paper will get you opportunities you can’t get without it. I know it’s hard but stay the course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soarin one last time #waltdisneyworld #prajznersinvadedisney #epcot #werehome #victorylap #prajznerswondisney @ Soa… https://t.co/IXjk3NhJFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesertSeas @tanorlin @HBO @KingJames I have a strong opinion about Faceless trolls online lmao 😂 I don’t give a damn about your opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂 GIRL STOP #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19… https://t.co/o0SlmyjiuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#60 Sec Challenge - Track 16   I’m very glad to be posting a new track everyday throughout February!  I’ll be posti… https://t.co/9qkW9rQuFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIME @JohnCzer1 How do thieves live with themselves?  Having no talent, no skills, no purpose for their useless li… https://t.co/nk8ra5331t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Its_With2TTs @DaveDuFourNBA ...he isn’t going to stay 4 years lol. Yeah it’s fair compensation for Jack White but not the studs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great ceremony to be apart of in Sioux Falls! #NAIADIIMBB #GoHardOrGoHome https://t.co/boeau1wVTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnMa30764363 @chefjoseandres @fema @WCKitchen Problem is Local can only support if it’s strong(unfortunately mo… https://t.co/UdHq5WgZX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP @SenMarkey And again I’ll remind everyone that this is a NON-binding resolution. #GreenNewDeal]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are the chances I can get @pykodasyko to swing through Abelardo's after he picks me up from the airport tonight?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimGaffigan @BrodyismeFriend He can’t hear you. But I’m sure there are plenty of other living struggling standups… https://t.co/zXl6jCVSsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoveCameron Also, we need a Piazza cast album of you and @ReneeFleming... andabroadwaytransferokaythanksbye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the 10-year anniversary of the T.O. signing  #BillsMafia #LetsGoBuffalo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bergen Catholic should be the #1 seed in the TOC. They’ve been dominant. Best team I’ve seen all season… https://t.co/jAGuTCNVIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to the Month Anniversary of My Mother's passing I am taking the next week off of Twitter God Bless.!.... RIP  F… https://t.co/s9RMMqG1ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge co-worker dinner! (@ Moretti's Ristorante &amp; Pizzeria - @morettisrose in Rosemont, IL) https://t.co/SxAaeLHZlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[At one time I thought #ATX was diverse...I opened my eyes and unfortunately we have lots and lots of ground to cove… https://t.co/ghSvLavOW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird Your too late, took everything we had and gave it away. Nothing is secret documents anymore. https://t.co/RvGndHO8Jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve met librarians with more conviction in their voice than Jeff Tweedy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrBoringJustin in “Hollywood”, Maryland #Winner https://t.co/HCEhdIpmN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow just like we have been saying ..funny left bitches about homeless hired to hold spots on DC hearing but pay for… https://t.co/HrLl3w5GZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things are tough all over #djgimports #nofiltertshirtco #sportit #coachinglife #entrepreneurlife #djglifestyle… https://t.co/tOJSUYtvXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost lagordamagazine  ¡Ya esta aquí! La edición de #Marzo con @SOCIOSDELRITMO1 🎷en portada.  Encuentra noticias… https://t.co/c5ZEzHvvnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mastering Contrast in your Images (Adobe Photoshop Tutorial) https://t.co/KpgtAn9aFi via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@labeveryday I still wonder why I don’t have network OS natively build ACLs and other lists off Git pull requests...]]></document><document><![CDATA[the jonas brothers coming back together means one step closer to one direction coming back together and that is wha… https://t.co/0Qaj5v5NN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Hahahaha, Hahahaha, Hahahaha, oh my, can't catch my breath...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyRainbow Sigh, Alfred Hitchcock’s The Birds.....it screams MUSICAL! Perhaps you should write it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandymcclearn Couldn't say, we used the mains in harbor for manoeuvring (full) power, 12's couldn't guarantee a Fu… https://t.co/0Udik94fNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@knicknamej @DineshDSouza If you don’t like it then you should not read it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hopslam Ale (2018) by @BellsBrewery @ Duke's Upper Deck — https://t.co/88ojP9a3PK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hellllurrrrr #SlowFeetDontEat Ova Hea ✔️🤙🏾✔️ @ NYC Diamond District https://t.co/LYbvVqrbSS]]></document></documents></author>