<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[No me chingues @Uber_MEX que los conductores se tardan hasta 22 minutos en recogerte!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please try and take the time this week to post something, anything, that is not political. I know you can do it. Th… https://t.co/6zQQDno2K6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is right in the world again because WORLD OF COLOR IS FINALLY BACK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moonspinner55 @MoMcCormick7 Art Linkletter, that’s a name from the past💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiambraSue @MCITLFrAphorism Sue- you are woefully wrong. What you said contradicts Christ. You are so modernized i… https://t.co/1URCSKsxHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me on Ellen   Ellen: so I heard you really want your vans back.  Me: omg yes.   * Madyson walks out with my vans an… https://t.co/KSISOArV5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patbfsj @treasonstickers Lie and be an ass and get yourself appointed to the Supreme Court!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Wish you were near Atlanta so I could visit you!!!  God bless you and Godspeed for healing 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three weekends from now I’ll be downtown with L for St. Patty’s day and that’s honestly more important than my birthday next weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I installed a camera just to catch people drinking behind the bar and one of my servers drank 11 times yesterday. 3… https://t.co/DSGOtbLRq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cigarettes are disgusting. That’s my tweet thanks for coming to my Ted Talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, @awpwriter I'm confused why people who need scooters and other mobility devices can't reserve them. First com… https://t.co/BY5IHmzqRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#I know this might be a controversial statement, but I’m going to go ahead and say it...I hate google docs. That fe… https://t.co/yyJZfG6N9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/gFno1pQeYq my radio show is online and I can listen whenever!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheodoreBNolan @USATODAY You sound Middle Eastern, whose males monitor and supervise every female movement. She mu… https://t.co/K1dFOcMh5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamboEveryone @Kevidently @TurkeyLegJeff I couldn’t get past the singing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow was my first day off in foreverrr and I made @ home appointments I’m addicted to making money🤷‍♀️🤑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntonioMaio2 We’re still in public preview for many experiences in Microsoft Search, hopefully you caught the MVP… https://t.co/BMyUN3rQKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[He works long hours on 2nd shift, and sometimes arrives only to find out he will work 16 hours instead of 8, then n… https://t.co/txPqbfPo20]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great homily today. (@ St. Marks Church in Utica, NY) https://t.co/3Dhi2bzRL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdeloryn @salesforce @PepUPTech @trailhead @SalesforceAdmns @SalesforceDevs @ericakuhl @amandabauman @ShirleneChow… https://t.co/yK0dQ9rvsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Friday!!! I am bursting with 💛💙 pride. I am so proud of my @WTHSNews students. #GoWave #Teamwork]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iMakeArtifacts @DexterSaysMeow @wickeddelicious @eveewing Rainbow fish is also gory. Everytime I hear it, I imagin… https://t.co/9Cu4Cajgtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParsonsArtRoom @JenniferWarden5 @RES_RSSS @RSSinformation @jenbrown224 That is amazing! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANK voters he's no longer governor! Former Maine Governor: Bypassing Electoral College Would Silence 'White Peopl… https://t.co/QySYQYVtHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiogenesTerp @Lis_Smith @SF_Gary_ My beloved vacuum. #GoGreen! Unfortunately I took the handle apart to clean it o… https://t.co/HuAvPDMvvH]]></document><document><![CDATA['War on drugs' doesn't tackle the drug problem... https://t.co/W4YPi5h49e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARonNBC @keselowski @amsupdates @Team_Penske @NASCAR Yeah https://t.co/7WaevObrfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[:) (@ GetGo / WetGo Gas Station in Westlake, OH) https://t.co/cNfBcGNcMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to show off Boys! @DruSamia @Cody_Ford74 @BigBen_72 @BobbyEvans44 @24RAnderson @TheKylerMurray @Primetime_jet… https://t.co/Mo7M0n7qTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VtLakey @taylorsant @seanhannity @SaraCarterDC @PamBondi Wtf did you just say??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHolyShit5 @SonOfGodAndMan It does not. You don’t act like it. So you are FINE. 😂🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiguelandHolly This MF is a damn narcissistic predator to women!! He most likely only scores with my sistas out th… https://t.co/aflz4k61Ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to fire up the monster trucks!! Join us on FOX4 at 7:50 and 8:50! https://t.co/Q6yURlQIKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometime you get fancy dressed for work and then... Adidas happen to you. @ Mobile, Alabama https://t.co/tw83Oz4YuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Tulsa International Airport (TUL) in Tulsa, OK https://t.co/UPON3MJDEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff @CathULaw @SenKamalaHarris @DanRather @GavinNewsom Could they also be testing to see if they could s… https://t.co/iMCHGTiHoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[This comes as no surprise!  @realDonaldTrump is a known and admitted sexual predator]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrbanOutfitters I been doing the #UORewards contest for years!!!!! Can I finally win something especially this sin… https://t.co/E7SKD6zbE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Trump asked Abe to nominate him for the Nobel Peace Prize. How desperate and pathetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When dudes fwy one day and hu with an ugly girl the next &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️❤️❤️ #Repost @W_W_Unicorns with get_repost ・・・ warriorwrstlng :  #WWERAW We are less than ONE MONTH AWAY from the… https://t.co/nNnHQOEsTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great fundraiser by BHS Alumni. Feel free to share. @Kevin_Richman #BPatriodProud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drknstormynite My husband’s heart doc told him recently there were 2 things everyone should know or have access to… https://t.co/vnaNG8raN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t claim to be vegetarian BUT I can’t remember the last time I ate/craved meat and feel pretty good 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonaquest Yes, I was just specifically referring to that chain's brand and evidently generics are alive and well here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonlatino Only if it’s used in Rocket Power. https://t.co/3NKJkPiDHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting room etiquette for adults: 1️⃣Turn the sound down on your phone. 2️⃣ Turn the sound down on your phone. 3️⃣… https://t.co/sega6PYgZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InnocentByabag5 @Kimblest1 @JenyaDube @Rosfilis @debcarp3 @TdLombard @AmandaH59289729 @Julianoliveira8… https://t.co/z6ubqBRkCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @ApexPolice! You are always on the ball! #LiveApex #Lovewhereyoulive #thankyouforserving]]></document><document><![CDATA[It finally felt like spring time in Seattle today! ☀️ Our first @TMobileTruckSEA event at the newly named… https://t.co/YUebnrVJrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainy day out here in California! En route to #RaganDisney to finally get some sun ☀️🎢☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[T2 | Northwestern’s Goosenberg knocks a single that scores Bourbon &amp; ties things up at 1-1 @CoMoSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[We wanted to give a special shoutout to students in the @CCPirateTheatre band. #cchsshrek We see you and more impor… https://t.co/qj71KVl0Dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateHoot @theofficenbc It’s not Seinfeld but I agree, amazing show. There’s no clear favorite for character. Creed… https://t.co/oKQQkrs7Hz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#realestateinvesting #realestatenews #realestateagents   #TownforSale @tictoc  #investors #investing #investments… https://t.co/08B7NNhEIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to go out with this guy for 2/3 years n there was one time he investigated in me n tried to convince me that… https://t.co/L3ww2nfSv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scholarcation what is March’s theme?  Congrats to @followmsevans (social studies) and Megan Smith (math) on winnin… https://t.co/xTiqGKsymc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KidFrankey @c_guilford25 I’m just kidding I heard that one before though hahaha don’t hate me]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lovethesethree #love #beautiful @ Grosse Pointe Yacht Club https://t.co/O5BIg1XD9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BmoreDoc @BaltCitySchools @AlgebraProject @AlgebraProject is an incredible group of youth leaders]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #SouthBend, IN, check out this #CustomerService job via the link in our bio: Temporar… https://t.co/edlH1iiTaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[hhhhhhhhahahaaaaaaaaaaaa #laughter #laugh #smile #jolly https://t.co/qSs4eIMJRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@churchAlmighty I like to listen to the songs of the church, thank God!]]></document><document><![CDATA[making this humorous. 25 beautiful, heartbreaking reactions show just how important Robin Williams was to Hollywood https://t.co/pQhIQb5gEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Treash Because little girls like her are selfish and only care about what they want in the moment. She didn’t sto… https://t.co/gIrmNQsWsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imo women who defend or uphold the patriarchy are the lowest form of human existence and that is that on that]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Going through boxes of old clothes in attic*  “Oh, cool, I wonder if I can still wear that t-shirt.”  *Realizes mi… https://t.co/eYeVXUKWmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A  chalkboatd sign, my anxiety, and my desire to be a balanced human being led to the purchase of this little plant… https://t.co/AFvvPF5zIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nj1015 @GovMurphy @BillSpadea Bill you're the biggest whiner around LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flight fuel (@ San Antonio International Airport - @satairport in San Antonio, TX) https://t.co/UL8schE1lD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 3 months to our sweet, Kaia!  #kaiamadelyn #rollingoveralready  #timeseriouslypleaseslowdown #babygirl… https://t.co/CPmt4dA3RU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mchappell51 Too bad they plan to tank this year so they can get the top draft pick in 2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel sick to my stomach listening to how those EAs and Teachers talked to that little girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very best wishes to our #Ladycolrs @CentennialCOLTS in your @TheOCAA playoff qualifier vs @FanshaweFalcons… https://t.co/HHHdmSnRwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbaradye921 As a teacher, that really sounds insane!! I would probably get clarification from the teacher and ex… https://t.co/Z8BLxORnPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KStreetHipster @growing0up0girl @BernieSanders Not a fan of Bernie just of facts ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pevenly1 @RedTRaccoon Ok-it’s been a long day of P’sOS- didn’t mean to act like one🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esto me💔mi 🇨🇴es un país d mierda con dirigentes políticos hijueputas,ladrones, mentirosos,brutos, empezando por… https://t.co/phWTxxSJYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelOsteen Amen. Praising and glorifying our lord Jesus Christ at all times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinRoberts @GMA @JussieSmollett @EvaPilgrim @danabrams I believed the story until I saw his interview with Robin… https://t.co/06TvCMUDr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetoyman1 @FoxNews This is not going to be covered by the liberal media though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kisses_hugs_luv This is me after drinking pineapple juice https://t.co/We5dxaW7f7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The RED Circle of @tedxwindsor @ted !!  As a 2x graduate from @uwindsor it is my pleasure to be of servitude to the… https://t.co/92WFeR5Bzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[felt like posting cute pics of me.. these were hard to find 😂 https://t.co/oelHTzm1Du]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara I love that he’s not letting JJ bully him.  He’s making them look pretty sad. #getdtoutofmyWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewMintzer @kaifulee What a beautiful comment: "I believe in the sanctity of our soul. I believe there is a lot… https://t.co/4qW22seaZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my dog trying to cope with the North Dakota winter. ☹😭 #makeitend https://t.co/Xx4CuP7UVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your @venture__out tickets friends. This team is truly incredible, and their event will be highly impactful and… https://t.co/XToLna9wXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students are hard at work on their #BlackPanther project. They are trying to decide if Wakanda should remain isolat… https://t.co/re8MG2VYOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[25 yo free agent @derek_martin23 looking for a job. Up to 95 in past. Reported 4 weeks ago w arm pain. Repatterened… https://t.co/mbZwSS4Ugc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Refusing to meet with citizens while representing policies that benefit foreign nationals over the children of Amer… https://t.co/9UYKAuVDOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeYoungWWE @inagarten You do need to be her just be your own classy self...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a Magician - I make S**T happen 🎩🎩 @juviasplace Magic Mini Palette 🔮🔮🔮🔮🔮🔮🔮🔮🔮🔮🔮🔮 #juviasplace  . . .… https://t.co/CEeWrD3LfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥Boom💥 You vs. you: Acknowledge and accept your greatness. Stop worrying about what everyone else is doing and comp… https://t.co/OG6VKZ9OYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with those who support you, grow with you, and laugh with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @Pugs47 @Jedi057 @jonz970 @NEEL56N @garway95 @QLover18 @PlanoJoe7 @MAGAgirly @BJCollins131 @Ladyjana143… https://t.co/n161MNgGwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh good, it's snowing. I thought we hadn't had enough snow this winter. 🙄😕❄🤦]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO THE QUEEN 👑 Thank god I found someone who eats, poops, and watches as much tv as me!!  Not many p… https://t.co/PPXJUhsTtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back on the air @CBSNews Special Report - Michael Cohen testimony continues. @JimAxelrod @edokeefe @PaulaReidCBS @rikkijklieman]]></document></documents></author>