<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Man lately every day I’ve passed out when everyone is awake and then I’m awake when everyone is asleep and it’s sup… https://t.co/w7GmDUXSbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thank you to The Stoneleigh Hotel for kicking off our 2019 #pouryourselfintohistory happy hours last night.… https://t.co/wiPzrkEDg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this happened today. One of my role models in the #newsbusiness brianrossinvestigates joined me live on set at l… https://t.co/FgXvqYEYAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need @GameOfThrones season 8 to come out like now... hate this waiting game]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @OrangeCrush4  Post 10 album covers that make up the soundtrack of my life: no exp… https://t.co/MFtpyqFlM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[...If the short term problem is under-capacity utilization and tax levels are only relevant when it comes time to d… https://t.co/zp1Qztflrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's great to see my next generation training their next generation!  I hope they can figure out all the things tha… https://t.co/SiyskGa8Q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kazweida Tucker's wife is the daughter of a minister who, as headmaster of a boarding school, failed to report a s… https://t.co/eBikAiv2gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll admit I fell in love with this piece...😘🐘  #brownjrart #art #artist #drawing #draw #artistoninstagram… https://t.co/xOXwwkJMLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[These things are also keeping me from buying a modern personal Mac Book as well. At work I’m fortunately at least 1… https://t.co/0VIguhp7CO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who leaked our secret plan straight from comrade Stalin to take hamburgers away from America? Straight to the gulag… https://t.co/5tSkv7H0H6]]></document><document><![CDATA[James Harden (HOU) creates himself some space and knocks down a three from the wing 🙄  86-68 #Rockets, 4:27 to play… https://t.co/kyvumHIO5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good meeting with client at iconic location, grandcentralnyc #NYLAWYER @ Grand Central Terminal https://t.co/LgWD5EIEu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roads looking good down here in #Plymouth. Plows out there working hard, keeping everything clean. Clean your car o… https://t.co/pAhz7vLIXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Martymvr @OurSantaMonica I’ve heard hitting the pavement. This brings it to a new level.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GanderRVDuel just ride in a train can't pass! What a fucking joke this is the worst impression for the 500 nobody… https://t.co/4dF2oJElkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComplexMusic Let me know when you have a second to talk on interested in doing business with complex DM me a soon as possible thank you 🙏💯🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[PRIME CUT — Even better for Amazon, federal taxpayers gave company $128 million in tax refunds last year. Thanks to… https://t.co/Syiv7j4v2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gun to your head guys , which one you picking ? *NSFW  @FeitsBarstool @KFCBarstool @KFCradio https://t.co/rjpxKzDHAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the photo gallery of the game one high school hockey finals at https://t.co/KZtCM5yweN. https://t.co/0sGyxMf04s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RexGrumpy @IlhanMN Seriously? The response you just made makes no sense at all. The remarks she made were ant-Semi… https://t.co/P44b4iVYxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[this teacher or professor has the patience of a Saint. Who the hell raises their kids like this? https://t.co/N2ZHz0gf2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all use “fag” as a weapon,  But me mentioning that you’re a fat raggedy walrus in tube socks is problematic.  I’l… https://t.co/nC4jMKYHVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[While y’all out here bullshitting I’m busy making moves ✍🏼@AutodeskRevit https://t.co/VcK9ostFxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pk_sullivan Zofia enjoyed her adventure with Pel and Vine. She’ll need a new egg. https://t.co/z31GRZkU9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woohoo! Another #10k in the books. #princess10k @ Epcot - Walt Disney World https://t.co/PVLHFDI5r8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PearlJam Yes we are.... it is called  good parenting!!!! @PearlJam  @TTaubes https://t.co/yV6h6LnPj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The icewater test is the most impressive part and is broken out in this video.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh if they tell you to get on the priority line and you see kids - RUN #TSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[my brother just told me that last year he got a $1600 tax return and was gonna use it to buy something from gucci b… https://t.co/OgHCIQ6N4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @HelenatElevate @TampaHasSwagger @AmandaSiftar @LaurieOhall @alispagnola @Christalynn0919 @yuneekgirl3723… https://t.co/WPdstvDIcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[God works in the lives of His children through Progressive realization. What he teaches us becomes so crucially a p… https://t.co/HlPsHPslEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachN64 when we dare him to shoot @6Dayton6 @drewwinn6 @LilWinn11 @heykatyy32]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I promise I didn’t do it!!...” 😂🙈 bedtime in LA. #mcknight #goodnight #home #blessed #latenight #fitat56 #fitness… https://t.co/O0fJDiTFYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aafstallions @JoelBouagnon Oliver is too. Great to see a running game like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[A life is not important except in the impact it has on other lives. ~Jackie Robinson • • • • • #gratitude… https://t.co/t2UvyCpM7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattSaternus @DukeMBB Zion and Barrett are both more talented than anyone on that team, with the exception of maybe Jay Williams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN All these people are too far gone on the left, Sorry I will vote for Donald Trump once again, No one in that f… https://t.co/k6GIisiuBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some great discussion today about the benefits of @ACEC_National and @acecks PACs for our engineering businesses an… https://t.co/Ftk5lSRtxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@U_N_I_F_I_E_D @iget_buckets35 @zaytodd @kyreewalker1 @The_ColeAnthony @PreciousAchiuwa Thanks man! The futures so… https://t.co/ihRIYqTfqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_311la @jsram311 Got my Chrome browser set to the shows page and I'll just refresh it a couple times each day to s… https://t.co/zAwxricoXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the next 24 hours, I will be donating $.10 for every like and $.25 for every retweet to my Mini-THON fundraisin… https://t.co/IPfN5NTEGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kane asks the school board to help fund this year's after prom party. #prom #livefromtheschoolboard https://t.co/W5kmbRJxja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davlaown @TheOnlyKAVIN @davidhogg111 Wrong...her net worth is around 100 million. She came from a well off family,… https://t.co/wNe4OgSE3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I jus found out what my sign was but I be reppin it like I been knew lmao 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Impresionante! si el domingo en #Alabama y #Georgia teníamos calor y tormentas severas con #tornado, esta noche he… https://t.co/1elBKSWeTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazon will pay $0 in federal taxes on $11.2 billion profits... for the second year in a row! We can’t afford the r… https://t.co/q3qU0Eh1BA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Origamigui Lol! I'm glad I could help :) but the ads could have been so much better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Banks So what is today's Republican Party?  So is the reversal on tariffs capitalism?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning, I addressed the @NatlGovsAssoc on the significance of a strong Can-US relationship. Economic growth i… https://t.co/JfBVKGsP4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrici15767099 LOL @DNCWomen : sad but maybe soon @phillipnhere or follow @NoMoreElitists #WeThePeople : openhous… https://t.co/swbAna7Gzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadWorldNews @PatriotCELL Looking at the Competition... He does not need much Hope!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Do what you love, so that you love what you do” 💭 • Nothing like a United win, let alone a comeback from 2 goals d… https://t.co/jLQlSRuzyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Verttex This is insane! I know we don’t know each other very well but I am really happy for you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@virjn_ Or even traits they think is more common with white folks...yeah that part]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamclanton @JHarden13 The harden hate from some of our own is weird. I get he can be frustrating sometimes but th… https://t.co/akMIxYnZvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And what agreement hath the temple of God with idols? for ye are the temple of the living God; as God hath said, I… https://t.co/DQ8nnlxIkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Canada #UnitedKingdom #London #Europe #BowlingGreen #Lexington #Louisville #Kentucky #Knoxville #Follow &amp;… https://t.co/6CEpVsNEvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @VegasToyCon with get_repost ・・・ Vendors ... check Fans....check Video Games.....check  um...what else??? O… https://t.co/LDHo75qz6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veronica part 4 'Five more minutes' 🎥🎬📽🎞 _____________________________________________________  #mauricePKerry… https://t.co/v7QxDV1MJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@popculturecube @ItsTheBrandi You found her through the podcast and NOT the many times I've RTed her over the years… https://t.co/0dOpXgfn2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[The calls @KingJames gets going to the rim... #NBA https://t.co/IexUkcbFFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2Amatters I believe Dr. Ford.  Blackout Brett attempted to rape her when they were younger, but fortunately she wa… https://t.co/FeP0GElrvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally! (at @ShakeShack in Brooklyn, NY w/ @juanpi_m) https://t.co/VOoWyIsuyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get good @Rogers. The fucking constant dropping of internet connection that we get has made my decision to switch t… https://t.co/bCzamvwJO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabe_prewitt @LEGENDBETS @ShotTakingTime That page is very nice. I'm going to look more in depth tomorrow at work.… https://t.co/CGaE9fC8wM]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:58.5°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another soaring rendition of The Star Spangled Banner by David Smith. 🦅🔴⚪️🔵 https://t.co/Oby9CJK9CB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DustinPoirier I've been a huge fan of yours ever since you were on HBO/Showtime, one of those channels. Lol, It wa… https://t.co/VoTor8lWTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLFlyers @28CGiroux Proud to say I’ve played on the same field as this champ 🏒🎺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ky_33 Good morning Doni. Have a beautiful Sunday. #CowboysFam 💙 https://t.co/INFhNjZHGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[📍You guys definitely DON’T want to try this leg workout. 📌. • If you do, you have my respect. • First off: in hyper… https://t.co/b7wn56QQ4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennaForTruth @BernieSanders Don’t spin this to suit your desire to argue. Once he knew he responded and took resp… https://t.co/tvwvSJCPTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[SV Space Meetup this evening 🛰📡✨ Space Operations &amp; Mission Control. Speakers from @SpireGlobal @planetlabs… https://t.co/Ff6u3DkkQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GLOCKOHOLICS He thinks he’s smart, cool, intelligent and beautiful when in fact all he is is a racist. His own words!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenMarkey Typical...you leftist get called out on your bullshit, then you whine that its a trick.  Go big or go home!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valley View Ave Valley View Ave, La Mirada, CA 90638 https://t.co/lzPnaZ9Ko7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If it isn't Hillary it's obama please change ur pissy underwear and give it a rest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up before dawn for travel to SFO for @MyVMUG #vmug #VMUGAdventure #LeaderSummit2019 #LeaderSummit  It’s gonna be a long day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleman_peanut Never understood not that hard headed! Sometimes my family calls me that just level kind of guy ! Never unreasonable right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some notes from my trip out here.. -Met so many athletes/coaches that I can't even begin to thank them all for bein… https://t.co/A9ZgNphCGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome stealth pow day coppermtn 🎿The mountain destroyed me as you can see in the first and last picture.… https://t.co/cvtm3VZf6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@digital_mine_ @Kacper_Wro This #ATM get robbed. Victim of Fiat! #bitcoinyellowvest https://t.co/xCqzu3YY8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miles wishing Fox 5  Happy Valentine's day morning FOX 5 Team.   #FOX5MORNING https://t.co/j60mAWIr86]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheChrisDuarte @darabella @LeahBMH @ChaseTheSol We need to have an Equality bedazzle class!!! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielDumile2 @askin4friends @tylermeredith @CPC_HQ @AndrewScheer @liberal_party @Puglaas No,  you just called me… https://t.co/rgtNxvPJC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pinche chayotero de mierda al servicio de los corrupto cuanto te pagaron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now you see, India, an eternal enemy of Pakistan, is engaged in the acts of terrorism in Balochistan. Jhadav, an In… https://t.co/mPU6FRU8Ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer Our freedoms are being destroyed by 1% like the drip, drip, drip from s slow leaking faucet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vladsavov Why not it’s basically as thick as that folding Samsung phone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone in this bar is wearing “Swiss Army: Altitude” and it makes me want to grind with someone while listening to Usher!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrSamMorris This article has been thoroughly debunked by so many sport economists over the past three weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[El continuismo de la corrupción no es bueno, Leonel, gobernará con sus corruptos, Danilo, también seguirá con sus c… https://t.co/83fvzPty8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the @gop and @realdonaldtrump say about @berniesanders and Socialism is how will it be paid for? God Said Ameri… https://t.co/obTHOj5Fyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tackettdc @maggieNYT @nytmike @anniekarni Yeah. Writing a self-serving, secret memo is a great way to protect our national security.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Son_mamadas @princhipesxa @Una_tal_Dian @DafneHDSM @lopezobrador_ No los tengo, pero por lógica: que buscaban esto… https://t.co/pNOUHYBHfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pray every damn day to of been born in japan because females here in soflo are always so F$!%ing uptight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Imamofpeace Where never lark or even eagle flew -- And, while with silent lifting mind I've trod The high untrespa… https://t.co/qbWTxi2obU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HitmanDonnie we would have so many videos if we recorded our living room dance sessions 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Eubank body slams James DeGale. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/TpAkx33duk]]></document></documents></author>