<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@civale10 @LWC_GypsyDancer @LakerPrincess72 @difusella @Julia_Eaton_UK @ClayneCrawford @jolynn_headley @DrJimmyStar… https://t.co/4FHVZHZFtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Professional MUAs:  I wanna upgrade from my ring light. Any of y’all have a light system y’all recommend?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenWard1920 yes  that's why it so cute. if they gave it to me it would just go into an overall pocket]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out BTS MANIA SHOP for their BTS merch, like the one I've just bought here ! ? Go take a look and maybe... bu… https://t.co/LrnjFbE8zM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMoon42 How’s their brunch? Had dinner there 3 times this past week but never tried brunch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have Mercy is Right ! All Our Characters still have Stories to Tell and The Fans are Ready to Listen !! Bring Back… https://t.co/9bcvXLcdM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday funday continued 🎉🎉 (@ Magnolia Motor Lounge - @mmlbarftw in Fort Worth, TX) https://t.co/eRtSrW8sof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARONFOX I beat my 2 year old grandson today at basketball again today. Yahoo. That's 10 in a row for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdelaineMorin Hiii I would absolutely love to be apart of something like this #GirlsSupportingGirls 💗 hope to see… https://t.co/3DkAeUZW0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caden really likes to wrestle but Dad’s not home so I guess he thought I wanted to... so maybe next time he’ll ask… https://t.co/D4OnPvWrFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elon Musk thinks layoffs will keep Tesla profitable as $35,000 Model 3 arrives https://t.co/xDuEvnrc91]]></document><document><![CDATA[every now and again im reminded how absurd it was that i should have been born an american lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Now can you do something about prescription drug costs.  This is with a high deductible health pla… https://t.co/Ke2iTh2z0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been awake for about twenty minutes and can’t already tell you that I need a nap today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump Did they really "Say Render"? As in depict an image artistically? Or to offer a se… https://t.co/n1ccbBrcRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicLombardi Thank you for sharing Vic. I will tell my new husband to get this test done. I hope everything goes well for you. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaRealGrizzle @JohnTrumpFanKJV @RandPaul Serious question.  Does this have something to do with the money use/tran… https://t.co/RFDuaY2kLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Holli_Alexa @MSkinner2016 Well. The judges think she’s a 99.75% Superman. Geesh !!!! What does she have to do to get a freakin 10??!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t be happier!   You scared me Ruthie!!! You are such a valuable 💪piece to the puzzle!! 💚💛🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love a good mirror selfie ... also, thinking that staying around for kink night could be v fun. https://t.co/4eZCjh4ZOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[became friends in middle school, started liking each other in 9th, dated in 10th for three months. then broke up bc… https://t.co/t5a8g0pvdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[THREE THINGS that have helped me be successful in my fitness journey:.. . 🔘 Accountability.  🔘 A solid program.  🔘… https://t.co/j8L46b1o0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@furtogo @cspanwj @TPCarney It's not simple.  If you were raised in the Catholic church, you are now realizing you… https://t.co/Ejh7CqXQN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toilet is running Shutoff valve wont close all the way Hubby is taking this personally Think Caddy Shack  SOS sent to plumber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Because they have no substance re politics.  They are angry cause their not in control.  NO CLASS. Have u… https://t.co/OjtwId1752]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maduro do not surprise us. All of them are corrupt and none of them is a democracy and many of them are owed billio… https://t.co/IftpXTMM6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jzulgad Again. No fault of coach ? Players need to make plays. But obvious maybe not responding to him]]></document><document><![CDATA[If at noon tomorrow you are free, go to https://t.co/y4VfUQX68u and you can hear myself and a few other teachers fr… https://t.co/sSTB1ZQ1HG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so surreal to think that there was a time in television where black people completely dominated. You needed us… https://t.co/4tOi3scxrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[These four have spent more than half their lives together. #friendship @fc_impactsm #churchbabiesallgrownup @ Faith… https://t.co/htfzF1sPE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carltongebbitch @RHousewives101 I am getting the sense that Gina goes off the rails this season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelBalcom1 @realannapaulina Except the legal firearm owners who threaten my safety.  An abortion doesn’t threaten yours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Voted to allow babies killed after birth 👿☠️💩 https://t.co/Wm3zM5QF6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why We All Deserve Our Own Hype Person https://t.co/48LsPWU7u6 via @shinetext]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @MBH_Lead2Learn to post covers of 7 books I LOVE: no explanations, no reviews—just a… https://t.co/97zMHhXVUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kstal21 @hanmuellernah @lisashimaa He doesn’t know what to do with his LIMBS https://t.co/jo3LBs5dbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhutWouldWoodDo Um well I only told 4 people until this tweet but uh yeah SEE YOU ON ST PATRICKS DAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Study suggests most Americans couldn't pass a U.S. citizenship test  🇺🇸 I passed!! 🇺🇸 Thank goodness! How embarrass… https://t.co/wDCSZuqbgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWils101 I thought you were about to do a Christmas countdown and I was totally here for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebeccaballhaus Right @RudyGiuliani no one is that stupid to believe this crap that continually comes out of your mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchgarber Lot's of people give to me the nick name "Monsieur Expos" since long time! I like my nick name! Go Exp… https://t.co/yy91sGUq9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let Light In 3x4feet #details of this rosegold beauty #rosegold  🎨https://t.co/rjNeF0P3Df  #art #abstractart… https://t.co/EOzSZM9d4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be a Heart Hero by donating to American Heart Association! https://t.co/SWGgwU5U71]]></document><document><![CDATA[96% positive ducks are building a nest in a bush RIGHT by my front door. My dog is either going to snatch one, he i… https://t.co/9CHUYcG8ig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Santa Claus Of The United States: #MembaThis It was like a #BirthdayBash... https://t.co/9vKVkEDa1B via @YouTube Th… https://t.co/GJnGWrFuwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel sad for women that think this is cute or acceptable. Like something is truly wrong with you🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @kelleyk70_key to post 7 covers of books I love:  no explanations, no reviews- just… https://t.co/LAtij6bFuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supermarkets have ALL the candy at checkout —- I remember when I was little at least they had books! #FoodFri]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindajeanlee How does it help me to leave before the sun rises? #AskingForAFriend]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Eden Prairie: overcast clouds, 17°F 67% humidity, wind 5mph, pressure 1020mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt_odell All it means that you will be able to store your private key where you store your passwords today.  Really really bad idea!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyft need to hire drivers that speak English!!!! This is a huge problem in Miami]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csivells24 @Picayune_Fierro Mustangs are rooting for our neighbors to the North. Go get 'em Bulldogs! Best of luck at State!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This chick I guess forgot her earbuds or thinks we all want to hear her music because she has no problem whatsoever… https://t.co/0FuRc7UaxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take me home, country roads has been on repeat all day. If that’s any indicator what mood I’m in. 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnsonKeesean If I see you on the sidelines when the band is on the field I will be sure to say hello and give a high 5! 💙🐾❤️🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bleu cheese wedge salads🥗🥰 are my absolute favorite in the world to eat. I love them like this or w/ steak or grill… https://t.co/Dju259YH9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[We gonna see a ball brother win a final this year . Y’all heard it here first]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ealbert0802 There is a lot to consider on top of all the other changes. I am curious to see parent perspective.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the love in the air is so thick you can feel it..! 💕   #annyphotography @ Glenview Mansion https://t.co/C5FwO4VTnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning to everyone besides myself for being so neurotic and incapable of sleep!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lion dance performance at 2019 Hong Kong Association Spring Gala at Ocean Palace Restaurant. @ Ocean Palace Restaur… https://t.co/JVmsbaMm71]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've always been self-conscious of my witch chin- but I'm almost 30 so I might as well embrace it 🧙🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/SZhSuhIuOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fvvcking_maria Follow my nail page on Instagram you won’t be disappointed I’m located in Grand Prairie, TX 📍✨  IG:… https://t.co/K64qutHbjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I know it’s smells worst from a strangers butt” - brought to you by the N train guy with gas ...letting it out inc… https://t.co/Q3WKJ8WQdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[For today’s #humpdaymotivation, I decided to share a few things I’ve been working on to generate more power and str… https://t.co/LKBXwIUtxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring-Break-my-back-sitting-on-the-airport-floor-doing-homework-twenty-nineteen https://t.co/SVghed49Ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[People keep saying “Valentines day” and I just think that’s a really weird way to say “Jaehyun day” and IDK I’m jus… https://t.co/JowUeTZFeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #SeeYouInCourt  Liar! Thought Mexico was paying for the wall?? Liar!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to finally be drawing this little scene between the animal familiars, Archie the owl and Rhonda the hedgeho… https://t.co/SChxlBjW2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joefaz From their pulpits in the country preachers preach the end of times and tell their flock no more bills. Puff we all be gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I’m at a point in my life where I say, with sincerity, “Look at my new book lamp!” and, “Check out… https://t.co/CH9Dxx8Zmj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really pumped for #girlsnight at samigracefitness this Tuesday!  Check out the Sami Grace page for sign up info… https://t.co/jGBAPPVjXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bears....pretty intense cardio workout today!  #f45training #f45challenge #nomoreexcuses #f45pasadena… https://t.co/WyTt6o7vqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Perorationer @Markgatiss As a jeweler, I’d recommend running the hand under cold water or, in my shop, spraying on… https://t.co/JA12BegEac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @20thcenturyfox you have condoned the DIVISION that this @JussieSmollett HOAX has created. You are ALL SICK AN… https://t.co/FQdRKqqjbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulaMariaAussi @BillOReilly @realDonaldTrump I also respectfully disagree Paula. While the wall was a campaign pr… https://t.co/v5cdIhWEGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[So . The morning of my 40th birthday...  my guess is I am going to end up making breakfast otherwise no one will ea… https://t.co/IzjLxY2q1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the Dodgers but would not root for them if they sign Harper. They got rid of one  ass in Machado  now going after another one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SupFletcher  We are here to support your leadership for prompt  implementation of SANDAG bike projects f… https://t.co/v5lTsDCdkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Lt. Governor @GeoffDuncanGA for attending the @GA_FFA legislative breakfast to celebrate #FFAWeek2019. https://t.co/kttTtRaTqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starCgarcia Ew I have to go there Saturday with Byrd for adventure club]]></document><document><![CDATA[@immigrationcom @RitaOldLadyDem_ @realDonaldTrump I totally understand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m looking for entry-level jobs, but they all seem to require 1-2 years of experience. Someone is misunderstanding… https://t.co/qJIgDf2mXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen I just wanted to let you know I made Beef stew this morning and it was missing something and remembe… https://t.co/hZOW91G3pg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is hilarious. #funniness #snicker #smirk #farcical https://t.co/QERjGEovVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnedwinmason @eiksleig How totally disgusting. So very sorry to know this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wavy_legend23 @taheen74 @steph93065 @KamalaHarris I was running out of characters 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larkscience Day 5 of #CoverChallenge I love Rachel Hollis. She motivates me to be my best self! What are you readi… https://t.co/C40nxAx08J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The Instant by @newanthembeer @ Coastal Craft Beverage Co. — https://t.co/t4m1MPl4q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me last week: I can fast 10 hours for bloodwork. No problem. This bloodwork is important. I’m a responsible adult!… https://t.co/cKVYF31j6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look who going with M for March Break! Have fun Mr. Pete the Cat. https://t.co/wGIx3NwjlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stuthefarmer Made popular in Moravian churches? I guess, compared to the kind I grew up on up north, there are no… https://t.co/hZoA8wm1pD]]></document><document><![CDATA[GREAT coverage @ErinLischNews of the #NFLCombine Such a FUN experience ~ thanks @NFL &amp; @VisitIndy! #LoveIndy… https://t.co/hysfrPFQV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without any help from textbooks, Jackson said he mainly relied on trial and error and an online forum for amateur p… https://t.co/psW6F0V54h]]></document><document><![CDATA[US Senator Agrees To Meet With Laura Loomer About Social Media Censorship https://t.co/goU9jC0dCL via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande I just really need to know who said this stop teasing us bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in the world of wonder,  @WeatherKitty provided an image of an orange cat in a PT setting, and I’ve never fel… https://t.co/CXGik4LD1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solumnsorrow i usually work 7-330 at one job and then 4-1130 at the other. the first job i get a 30 minute break a… https://t.co/OXvQRIt0Oo]]></document><document><![CDATA[before it’s too late, happy valentine’s day to the one who makes me laugh hysterically every single day❤️ i’m so th… https://t.co/khFW8jck6U]]></document></documents></author>