<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[In a rural area we have a 145% increase in homelessness.  American citizens are on the street while illegal foreign… https://t.co/QasIvfbdRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianInst Amen. And pray for your city. Sincere, heartfelt prayers. He might have mercy. We love you, Jesus. Praise Him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kaiser Permanente's upcoming new medical school will waive tuition through 2024, NYTimes reports.  Kaiser Permanent… https://t.co/Ki0ja8X5aE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burek75 @ZoeDodd @alexmcclelland @PozPrevention I mean death is inevitable for all of us really but when health ca… https://t.co/pFKdo8jt6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students @WakeGirlsLead make me feel like a superhero! Thanks 6th grade for the party, gifts, and fun!… https://t.co/56Az53IpNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBertShow do you have the address for the women with the birthday? I’d like to send flowers 👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gpublicity1 @ChrisYandle Chris, since your daughter always seems like such a big part of that purpose, maybe play… https://t.co/kafjTc4zyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband: I’m not gonna get sick  Also my husband: *currently puking*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keselowski Just glad you’re feeling better! Congratulations on the awesome win last week! You made this Michigande… https://t.co/NABzdquICg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weirdradopinons @kkelseeey_ @momof2dinosaurs @xoxoelley I’m not an idiot. I accidentally linked to that. I’m a des… https://t.co/sb65GcCVvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you send your professors the link to young wild and free before skipping class it’s legally an excused absence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bconsdr8 Listen to QANON Tribute from TOOTS SWEET #PSBArmy #WWG1WGA @heytootssweet https://t.co/cCjvNbg8gL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZooWildlife @dprusick @FOX10Phoenix How more stupid a human can be??? Well folks here is one of the best examples.… https://t.co/godmrVkWVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realtimrozon YES! YES! There’s no other answer but “Hellz Yeah, Baby!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je tape des tours de voiture à LA dans deux jours ce sera andrezieux quel échec, ou seront les palm trees ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[New EP out today. Here’s a video of me making a mistake while recording. https://t.co/RXD1QDj0QR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boy thought he was slick saying he wasn’t going out but I saw him on snap at Buffs 😂 dummy I got eyes everywhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥Breaking JHS Scholarship News🔥  Make that three Class of 2019 Elks MVS Semi-Finalists! Welcome to the Elks family,… https://t.co/cMJUMwIWya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellelboth This rang SO loud in my room too and again at 12:30 am to say it had been cancelled and she, found. 🤦🏻‍♀️😬 terrified me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please tell me I don't have to do any more blood work I'm still lightheaded from this afternoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at Old Leadmine Bend Rd #SharpsChapel #TN  #realestate https://t.co/ytSshW2tEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Son tan tóxicos que cuando mueran deben ser llevados a un sitio que no contaminen, así como las baterías o peor com… https://t.co/1VGBzZbR4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at that weird age where I finally have a purse that’s perfect for @letsmakeadeal.  Wet wipes?  Ibuprofen?  Hard… https://t.co/U2cdfqupO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TodayWasAGoodDay!  I want to end the day thanking those that were by my side, those that prayed for and with me du… https://t.co/yd39xlmb0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeathHussar I literally have the same laugh so zane and I are basically connected. That’s the tea on that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently blocking self-proclaimed abolitionists who shame and shun folks for going to the police or feds but also… https://t.co/mionsDX3BI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shani_aka_Ace @verge same - I turn notifications off for nearly everything and keep my phone flipped upside down (… https://t.co/mhvD99kkoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is official... if Tamar doesn’t win this may be the MOST disappointing season of Big Brother for me. Yeah, Lolo… https://t.co/cVEdtB2xuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might slide through a temp service but ... Joanna in a warehouse ... oh no]]></document><document><![CDATA[Babe and I made our homemade nachos from scratch and tried to make it some what healthy. Like using lean ground tur… https://t.co/Vz3bqcp987]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me trying to calm down my 5 year old niece when she gets scared of the thunder even tho I’m equally as scared https://t.co/CKW3lAukQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo mas cerca que voy a estar de España en estos momentos 🤣 https://t.co/jugc8VyWd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[DID I TELL YALL THAT MY MANAGER IS LETTING ME LEAVE EARLY ON FRIDAY JUST SO I CAN TRY TO GET TICKETS FOR DAY 2 LMFAOOOO I LOVE HER]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 seconds after this picture I fell lmao 😂  I hope you all are having a great day! I edited a video that will be up… https://t.co/090A89h660]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you liked the unlikely friendship at the heart of the #Oscar-winning #BestPicture @greenbookmovie, you’ll love T… https://t.co/Ts3oji4ORh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tuesdayselfie #dolantwins @GraysonDolan @EthanDolan https://t.co/kyrZtpkpkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_verynicegirl Love the honesty the unreliable parts my favorite that's relatable.🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click here to support I NEED HELP FOR MY BIRDS SURGERY organized by Michelle Mercieca Young Erkenbeck… https://t.co/kDOma8YHnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hack and I have pretty much the exact same food taste. Except for potato salad and cilantro]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Tampa event has begun @Dyn365Community    People showing up by7 am https://t.co/DQqCju18Qu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cooldogfacts about dogs having souls. You are so correct. My Frankenstein eyes could burn right thru you!… https://t.co/zpCW83cCXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repost:  ncsva_pacific westcliff_vb         Congratulations to Sierra and Mikayla for winning the women’s division.… https://t.co/0s8NEbgzFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@furcaylenfox happy birthday fluff. I know we don’t talk but good to be a follower of yours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@8NewsNow My son was able to make a snowball ❄️🥶🌨⛄️ in #Summerlin https://t.co/0ntkQWiqjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw @Patrici20765403 Whatever happened to #ImpactStudies? #Environmental, #risks? Who the fuck, gone maintain… https://t.co/ogrLNu8h2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this humorous there's something wrong with you. i love this idea!! Maid of Honor: Email the crew… https://t.co/BniX1qKwfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sure is nice to see people get their karma. Just leave people who hurt you alone, theirs will come, don’t worry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can tell by the smile on my face that I’ve found my other half 🌼 https://t.co/S8N4TdiOcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fox5dc #fox5morning #HappyValentinesDay My little love bug. My 4 month old nephew King is my Valentine ❤️ https://t.co/8trb3CAM5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski a person who forgot it was Valentines Day or forgot the gift and realize that buying the rose at the… https://t.co/eV5CFSvaMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattJames5150 #RT “Our potential is one thing. What we do with it is quite another." -- Angela Duckworth  #quotestoliveby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to our fav lunchroom manager. We love you April ❤️❤️ #aprilturns50 @ Riverbend Elementary School https://t.co/gBma062YNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bawling, #ComeFromAway so good. What we will do for each other ❤️🎶 https://t.co/p7V2Wt2zJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the point of having friends on IG if they ain’t gonna like your picture. Like man, show me some love i know… https://t.co/8352Gl1YPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dolphfish67 @brithume @realDonaldTrump Really, then why isn’t it done?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fear both the heat and the cold of your heart, and try to have patience, if you can. 🔥❄ -J.R.R. Tolkien  A look bac… https://t.co/wBEl1WXuaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndependentReb2 @PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Barf....those morons would be the last I would call....ugh...hillbillies and freaks]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Ravens are holding a press conference tomorrow at 11 with John Harbaugh to announce a re-signing of a player.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @Cressy777Jeri @AOC Let's now ask @AOC @SpeakerPelosi @KamalaHarris at what point is a border keeping out… https://t.co/lwMY3yziBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌴 #beverlyhills #losangeles #socal #presidentsdayweekend2019 https://t.co/lXauyO3Bgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland A downtown parking meter that actually takes quarters. https://t.co/ryV0yKg8H8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever breathed on me last week and gave me this crap is in BIG TROUBLE - my head weighs about 30 lbs!… https://t.co/loLQLqt4YM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight all stay home be safe stay warm it’s an ol man kick our buts winter day. Blessings all https://t.co/UzSKNGx5Nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @HomaBashWEWS when will people learn to stay out of areas for wild animals??? So glad they won't eutha… https://t.co/h1jzu5tqRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump I can’t believe how spot on Alec is in this skit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hilarious Pictures of the day, 82 pics. Kids Who Are Too Good For This World (Compilation)... #laughter #giggle… https://t.co/dXycxu3aQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJr88FanNate @JudyJ31830202 @chevychevelle48 @43324FAN @kross700 @laura24fan @ToddTPrice24 @JLee418… https://t.co/Oyvaj01729]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only do y’all have zero confirmation of this other than what you see other fellow speculators say, but they’ve… https://t.co/j09AGrHvl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cb916 VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥https://t.co/vaAT1XmggR]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the real though, has anyone seen hot Cheetos astroids anywhere??? HELP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working nightshift &amp; trying to maintain a good eating habit, active lifestyle is soooo hard. But I’m doing my best to make it work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imsoloveLee girl you should go see #SaintJudy this weekend then @ AMC Arbor Lakes 16!! I just watched the trailer… https://t.co/BowQVh2tbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lonesometoast That’s frightening. But, I love crafts so I’m in support! I’ve never felt more middle-aged-County-la… https://t.co/KdbXXlsMEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Santa Monica: few clouds, 59°F 55% humidity, wind 3mph, pressure 1018mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly, Rep @Bill_Zedler cut class all of high school science.  #Embarassment  https://t.co/HShIIPKMzA via @usatoday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bringing technology to my classroom to allow kids to practice and develop 21st-Century skills through STEM, STEAM,… https://t.co/OFU1MLkgSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[VaCiNEs CaUsE AuTiSM #APGrubb #apgov @Grubberment https://t.co/8fSo1EPMPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[THEM BITCHES YOU FUCKIN WITH, I KNOW THEY’RE GONNA NEED SOME PRACTICE SO BRING THEM ALONG W YOU, I’LL TEACH THEM HOW TO SMASH YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Luke Bryan said “rain is a good thing,” he didn’t think about college students walking to a class on the opposite side of campus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iTunes Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% Free in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/WMo4KHYoJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rochelleliss @tweetNorvena @SourceRobert @AlliCamAllison @Danielle21A @OncerHardy @frostgirl11 @hjhollis93… https://t.co/W22hy8RPYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[First visit to @StateFarmArena and doin’ it right! #suitelife #fridaynight #datenight with @JohnWWoodward… https://t.co/3c0GtLZRwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@t_shawn_d @jdavidgoodman @AOC @NYGovCuomo Great point Shawn. Western Queens small biz were lucky to dodge the Amaz… https://t.co/2sk4T0UK1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[C A N D L E S | Gusty 100 km/hr winds calls for a day in don't you think? Currently fighting a headache that won't… https://t.co/qbVq7czGcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently at church and hungry but lord is keeping me strong and safe #GodBless]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sekelow another of trumps lawyers?Just how many Lawyers does trump have,I'd love to see how his lawyers connected a… https://t.co/xRIPTLkkKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turn this ball of rage in my heart into a fire that can burn down the bullshit. #latenightlyrics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diamondfrost129 Captain Marvel is 3 days before mine. I get that love but yours is so much better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jedi_Mace_Windu @FollowTheRuless @SUCoachPerk @ZachSarginger @CoachDetweiler @ACPatsfootball Thanks brotha!!✊🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[200% content with having a lazy day especially when it’s spent with my other half (my dog) 🐾❤️😄 @ Fort Worth, Texas https://t.co/KSzyo07N4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlysMartinezTV @KEYTNC3Senerey @KEYTNC3Stacy @KEYTNC3Beth @melnewmantv @AlexBistonTV 💪🏻❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[u know ur getting old when ur still recovering from a fun night out 2 days later...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorCollins @RandPaul @LindseyGrahamSC @senatemajldr @SenateGOP If you vote against securing our So.Border beca… https://t.co/phfZoWmtT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SabrinaAnnLynn Please follow @andyriken we are both coming to see you March 6th! It would mean the world to him ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[dude I never had a dream that I had to force myself up and start crying 😭 like wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vine a visitar a mi tia y le traje unas humildes hojarascas de la Letty, y resulta que anda en Francia, jaaaa, y mi… https://t.co/HDJFgioPz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iAmBoomerStrong @FollowCarolS @OldSmokeEater @gigisc1969 @SimonSaysMoo @camela415 @Ginger4EverMe @TimAlle97055825… https://t.co/6KYBeyCXFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Agree, but shouldn’t you be chillaxing on your honeymoon? ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannaPeeples The key word being authentic which is a specific type of validation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family saw "#HowToTrainYourDragon3: The Hidden World" last night. We've been anticipating it since the end of th… https://t.co/hjgQC2CstM]]></document></documents></author>