<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[thinkin out loud. 🤔💭 #livelaughemilov #keepcalmcollection #thereisnosubstitute #chillin @ Porsche Centre North Toro… https://t.co/ssGxMO2wBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live footage from the UNCG locker room. #BidThieves https://t.co/NBsGNitMXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@berner415 I told my wife , instead of a wine cellar, I'd rather have a Bud Cellar! ( Not 2b confused w/ Bud seller… https://t.co/L0PehB3D3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wolv54b1 @SommBeer Thanks Gary.  I’m taking notes.  When you add the peppers, do you put them in full or chopped up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MutCallahan once again @AlexReimer1 is wrong. @GerryCallahan and @gregdickerson13 please get him a muzzle. Anyone… https://t.co/jq8HuGbeJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought some Amiri jeans... shit fly... but this shit was NOT worth the bred. 🤦🏽‍♂️... fuck it.. my gday weekend bought to be in full effect]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EVR1022 @SteadyLosing Its the only food establishment I’ve worked at so I have no clue if that’s out of the ordina… https://t.co/cyEF2zlgTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to be a quick night of bowling (@ Sterling Lanes in Sterling Heights, MI) https://t.co/LvZYNtPub5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream I was going on a cruise with my mom and like always.. running late I forgot to pack my makeup. And it felt so real. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Yankee Melky Cabrera is starting in LF for the Pirates today. I am 1 month and 3 days older than the Melk Ma… https://t.co/y4fv7mVRfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Trump wants to keep all the power within the family.  Since when Ivanka is a politician?  She didn't even ha… https://t.co/BC4ib3v06K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think of this as a relay race. CARB-X funding stops at the end of Phase 1. Without antibiotic pull incentives, the… https://t.co/igFNpWz8RX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @deliciuslyew !! Go party and have a great time you deserve it🍻🎉 can’t wait to see you again at another fest!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XoJackyra I be trying my best to get back to the dream cause i swear the next dream be ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m off to the Wilson School and Oriole Lane School School in Mequon, WI this morning. Can’t wait to share my new b… https://t.co/G3Lffk5UuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to welcome 5 new Residents into our #RepriseDigital team this year. Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s my nephew waving on the @tdgarden #jumbotron last night receiving his scholarship award from the @nhlbruins.… https://t.co/ECJlJ3CFh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn, no more Church’s chicken in NYC. Looks like I’m gonna have to hit one up when I visit my brother in Philly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheManager_BR @WWE_MandyRose @SonyaDevilleWWE Me too. Now it's time for Sonya to go grab that SmackDown women's title]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wgbhnews @phillipWGBH When you’re famous anonymous sex is a must so he was forced to gamble with a massage parlor… https://t.co/2GSsu3ZluC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Friday! Let me throw you on my guest list tonight and I will buy you a drink...or 2! As always free Drake’s Vo… https://t.co/zjDqt021Ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[I officially have the coolest room in the school! Grant $ well spent...calm down corner emerging. #cota #otlife… https://t.co/jWF2d1tZqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[JAKE (and Tom) TIME #seawallalife #jakegyllenhaal @publictheaterny @ The Public Theater https://t.co/jIROCE2eN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a night of music with @donnathebuffalo at @Center4ArtHomer https://t.co/adF8u4tgb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theunlockr @SamsungMobileUS @SamsungUS @SamsungMobile @SamsungBizUSA Dammmmmmmmn so sick 👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein 🤣🤣🤣 they are backed into a corner so not wanting to lie anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yessss! I am now a proud patron of Paul Harrell on @patreon, and you should be too: #NewPatron https://t.co/Z0VVyyi9Ym]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating the sessions - mock up brochure for hair education.    Put it out there, and you better be prepared to do… https://t.co/36eEBvRa18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because pain is still a signal that cannot be ignored at all times! These approaches teach sensory literacy, increa… https://t.co/ARKPeXwS4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't tell anyone, but I kinda like avocado toast. So, suck it California. Yes mine has meat and cheese and onions… https://t.co/KwnoIsi2wA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I wrote a referral on Monday and that student hasn’t talked to me all week #petty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the thing I don’t get about the Bryce Harper saga: if a team isn’t sure if their bid is enough, why not up t… https://t.co/xkAamAAXxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[, I’m bout to fight a bitch foreal.  Bout to pull that motha fucin pistol on a young bitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PARADISEDELTOR0 The white girl during the beating https://t.co/MAZihbk4bd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate #ReadAcrossAmericaDay &amp; read “The Adventures of Peter Gray.” 🤗📚🐺🗽#PeterGray   https://t.co/VZLbIAAacc]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Twitter line breaks at the worst possible time... https://t.co/VSHymlCj7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ 1st United Methodist of Callahan https://t.co/Jlt9MAOyiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last time I evaluated Miles Boykin’s film was in November. He is on top of the list of players to re-watch. I w… https://t.co/7pM7CvGrWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMS_Show @BMS_Billy @BMS_Derek my lady wants a 3some Im the one that is chill right now....because we have had iss… https://t.co/MYDzzayhro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zypisfy @Cern_lXXl @horusrage @debbiepalm44 @yourmumspants @mikenedie @dadbaddy @PCribbett @Heliocoptero… https://t.co/dOJ6j9HGAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aldotcom The 12-year-old also has a copy of “The Art of the Deal” that Jesus signed and gave to him 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just flurries @gilsimmons so far here in White Plains. Let see how the commute back to NH goes. Going to take Metro… https://t.co/2VIkJUl5ZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited about this! Only negative is I'll be going alone 😥.... But maybe my friends will come over to watch Fastlan… https://t.co/11V0Ik4ahT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omgdalton @Kessol @RealLonestarTX @nemesis283 @ChuckCallesto I'm a natural born citizen. What about you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[On 1/1/19 I made a goal that by 1/1/20 social media’s function in my life would’ve become more tool and less distra… https://t.co/ksVDI0peSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainbow of precipitation colors. We're going to stay in the freezing drizzle pattern for a while. Temp is 31°, dew… https://t.co/dV8TydE75p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@business His message to Americans- don’t vote for Trump in 2020. Quietly to Hollywood never let him win the Oscar for directors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSkipBayless @undisputed Guys like him usually land well in the end we are still in the Randy Moss/Terrell Owen… https://t.co/uCf1xLnkmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Mercer’s? Most of your Dem party cohorts, especially here in NYC, have been saying the same things as that bil… https://t.co/NqST0jsfol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciate the gear @CyfairA  The fun is just beginning! https://t.co/tnlKV3ltyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @TrussElise aka Evil Trump Supporter, go fuck yourself! https://t.co/YxxrnxtvvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna know #nba #finals #lebronjames #mj23 #shaq #hakeemthedream #magicjohnson #detroitpistons #blackmamba… https://t.co/sXFpNSAnG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before @TrueKofi can sign the contract, here comes @VinceMcMahon! #SDLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found a lady bug while doing dishes and let her out, then had a great view of a rainbow while listening to the thun… https://t.co/wPClMulZGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found this on FB @bradgilmore  @BookerT5x   Clean up on aisle 6: Featuring Stone Cizzy  G.I. Bros Over Hoes Produce… https://t.co/XLv80WXdNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[MÉXICO VS PANAMÁ 2 1 PLEITO ENTRE JUGADORES POLÉMICO PARTIDO COPA ORO 2015 https://t.co/OM1B2JmnuK vía @YouTube rob… https://t.co/NFCnR7DNp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bjarni I most certainly do not have anything like this in my country. I very much figured Europe was light years a… https://t.co/dKseZ9ZHlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadalynSklar @SabrinaCadini @alberMoire @darcydeleon @s_narmadhaa @KHetrific Looking forward to seeing you in a 3… https://t.co/vdhasxMlKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing wrong with having a big crowd. As long as Jesus is the center and not the famous pastor.   One day as Jesus… https://t.co/PewUt52giu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinNapp Agreed. It starts with our PG. frank cant get into the middle and draw to kick. Makes us shoot conteste… https://t.co/qk36xWqarn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope to finish this Obi Wan Kenobi build today for a customer. https://t.co/w0EwPXAEY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLando__ Nope. It's basically cable but online. Have FoxSports Florida, ESPN (s), TNT, NBA TV, all OTA channels… https://t.co/3gLZezACxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpecialReport NK will probably wait to see what happens in the 2020 election! The American Press and the Left are… https://t.co/3GuF0gU3ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astreurphoto True. Rain has passed and it never changed over to snow. Winning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SIUC Athletics has updated their logo ahead of the "official" reveal at the top of the hour. Story tk over at The… https://t.co/xAUpTSEk0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mamievandoren Deeply regretting betraying your country is not a reason to be allowed to return to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@becausewecare1 I answered. More wild accusations. Unable to engage in a logical discussion. Random personal attacks and lies at every turn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manny Pina circles the bases with an inside-the-park home run for #Brewers in seventh when White Sox LF Nicky Delmo… https://t.co/QepI6vckkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also remember: The US has an actual peace treaty with Japan and still maintains thousands of troops there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dying @LEXXXLIEEE @VLEXTHRVSHXM ya’ll crack me up 😂🤣 https://t.co/YFE3ou8qzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dsilver88 @JerryTemple And I don’t see how taking the best deal available is panicking. You take what you can get… https://t.co/dQroI3KRT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Public cloud: Real-world examples of strategic success https://t.co/NVAaKT4RPO https://t.co/DWPFmjMqGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justintreichler Win this one. Easiest game of the season against the FHS starters 💪💪💪💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VexingVixxen Consumed this while in the Dominican great stuff spicy or regular]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph ---. Barometer 30.238 in, Steady. Temperature 45.0 °F. Rain today 0.00 in. Humidity 88%]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz how much did she donate to you? And did you receive the "happy" ending special? Utter trash! ✌🏻🇺🇲🖕🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing like finding out antonio brown is going to the raiders while you’re drunk at a bar and many straight while… https://t.co/ncfXVHSRjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the road already this morning. Going to evaluate things in Jackson because of continued fluidity in the forecast… https://t.co/metTXxnC4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman We’ve been calling for tRump to get out of town for two years but his fat ass is still in the people’s White House.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is me in every social situation, my wife even knows that she pinched me when someone says something]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarboyHsp Will be my next purchase. Have to wait until Monday though. Wife is sick and I need to take care of her… https://t.co/h9DGWChBWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OHLHockey @jasonwillms88 nice to see Sam Rhodes and Jason Willms on top line....top line should be earned......you… https://t.co/q7wKHckPMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeSticeOU I think of @MikeSticeOU and what an amazing leader he was for all of us at Access. #SticeforPrez #SticeRulz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could not be who I am today without the person I started off as yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Jacob Wohl using his Criminal Daddy twitter Account since his account is suspended? Just saying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanking God for traveling mercies. Made it safely to the home of the World Series &amp; Super Bowl champions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertoMachicao La Razon periodico parcializado sin profesionalismo y ademas aburrido.@AndrsGomezV @roblaser… https://t.co/S1nuNyp4m7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneMinPsychic Nathan Phillips is an Omaha based agitator who makes his living by playing the system and milking en… https://t.co/JtjNRRQuJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minco Bulldog fans. Thanks to several local sponsors our Area championship game this Friday night at 8:00PM will be… https://t.co/ZAJDkXnar9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne There are plenty of other candidates running for the presidency that are better choices than Berni… https://t.co/r2eXdzN9Gr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhogAdvisory He is awful.  Just awful.  I would go for conference realignment just to get away from having him on games I want to watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sanityreturn2us @RyanAFournier So the videos we’re watching are fake? And the GOP being white supremest is BS. The… https://t.co/Hi7FWzuMrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@watspn1013 @TrumpTrainOnly @RealKyleMorris You don’t know much about BU then. Its reputation was not earned.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speed DEBATING using ethos, pathos, and logos. Some serious and some silly topics. Fun and engaging class!… https://t.co/sFjhKyrSCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[but like, why do I wanna know the whole story about this unsung bathroom antihero 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hitched was on the last puzzle of The Cure but sadly they didn’t escape in time!!! That’s okay though!! Just means… https://t.co/vt3yWpbxUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you find yourself in the middle of nowhere, and sometimes in the middle of nowhere, you find yourself. #pcm335]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StansburyShow @Fantone I can't figure it out either. Maybe @MunchCleveland will know coming up at 7 on @WRQK1069]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkilahObviously @SquipFitch @farabundista_x @ThatGuyRubik @DominaFurore No one thinks white people are truly oppre… https://t.co/zyMtOLs6sz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PornBoob @xxxworld4 I'd have to go to the gym 2 wice a day, every day!]]></document></documents></author>