<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@IndiaHitchhiker @RickGriffin @MattsRoadTrip @MadHattersNYC @CharlesMcCool @VISITFLORIDA @VisitPCBeach… https://t.co/2fkwQJ8etx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open House this Sunday. Feb 24th from 1-3!!!Come and see what all the excitement is ALL about !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[RESPECT a relationship. I promise you MY MAN has no time for your irrelevant issues. Maybe Get yourself some real f… https://t.co/b9EpIsMqYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrazyCajun2015 @LinseyDavis @ABCWorldNews And more ridiculous is you believing those liberal lies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[not worrying but praying instead 🙏🏼 I swear pray changes everything.. God is soo good ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 6 I have accepted the challenge from @BA_MathCoach and @ICEasterly to post 7 covers of books I love: no explana… https://t.co/jx3RiJ6Nmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almighty God, ever-living mystery of unity and Trinity, you gave life to the new Israel by birth from water and the… https://t.co/8QbE5Hb9Eq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This still isn’t nearly as humiliating as the #Blackhawks game earlier. So there’s that. #FCCincy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi @traciewashere—after our @wegohealth dinner, I am still VERY interested in your research on engagement and how i… https://t.co/9egTpqfLwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out the @RedSox have a spring training game in Lakeland on Thursday and I’m so sad because  1. I have… https://t.co/HkIs920Sc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strive for #brandequity, a derivative of #authenticity. @adamjapko #designinfluencerscon #influencermarketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaalakawaa To be honest, in 2019 going viral without attribution is probably a blessing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now you are a biz whiz when 2 months ago you didn't know how you were going to pay your rent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Northstar Roller Ice Skate Rink https://t.co/YCF4jeJxSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[• TIA YOYO × EASON • . #tia #tiayoyo #auntie #aunty #nephew #sobrino #family #familia #fambam #baby #boy #babyboy… https://t.co/WP6Yrxt81C]]></document><document><![CDATA[The future of community development are in our small businesss! Get it #Lansing! @MiPlaceNews @lansingmichigan… https://t.co/gMQ00cgwrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[putting down my 25 followers on twitter on my resume under the accomplishments section]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in transit @CityPtbo ?  Participate in online survey https://t.co/0cDdiZmW83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashorem and I were talking about boys &amp; she deadass said “There are 7 billion fish in the sea and all I want is a damn shark”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Your the scariest threat to the United States, go away!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my #AI peeps @thechataHQ! They surpassed our #JennieApprovedApp testing and are continuing to work collaborati… https://t.co/EJZczAWCeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogerfederer @DavidFerrer87 How did you know? I will be leaving Florida for Madrid in May. Will be there when the… https://t.co/pmA62SCxVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3V3RDR3AM just buy them oh my god idk why people make such a huge deal out of them they’re only like $160?? i get… https://t.co/8cfgyZPfgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys! Swarm of #butterflies in my neighborhood🦋🦋🦋🦋🦋🦋🦋😳😳😳I thought they were leaves for a moment!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWERollins I was watching Fast Lane I think you did good job I am big fan of The Shield good luck beat Brock Lesnar at Wessel Mania]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amjoyshow @JRubinBlogger Looking forward to seeing them on record, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#90minutes #hot #hotyoga #bikram #bikramyoga #strong #wellness #healingjourney #whole @BYinAlexandria #bestrong… https://t.co/yPsOXNT4Q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We want to make it simple when love is often both incredibly simply and heartrendingly complicated at the same tim… https://t.co/qa8brb8gXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I remind myself that keeping to myself forever is a possibility that I’m more than ok with because I know I’m a handful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daakardior @FiveThirtyEight @RAYGUNshirts Just listened.  They didn't need to be such haters.  Especially about ou… https://t.co/sBGprn6Pvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephanieRuble I had to stand. I couldn't take it anymore, I can't imagine your hallway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenefitBeauty oh hello kiosk #NOLA airport 🥰💄💋 https://t.co/gSh5Ot7nPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING I GET TO SEE MY FUCKING BEST FRIEND IN THE WHOLE WORLD TONIGHT AND I DONT EVEN HAVE TO FLY ALL THE WAY TO CALIFORNIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_real_coach @BrookGeraghty @cieraeastin @RupertBoneham @sugarkiper @JonnyFairplay @jolandajones @TinaWesson… https://t.co/333acgtROM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xtcsharem Learn something new everyday lol. I have a film guy hun.I am just not willing to put my flap up yet. I s… https://t.co/HHSQ4eZMoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘3 things to consider before posting on social media’ today on @IndyStyle with @LisaMitchL   in other words...  ‘3… https://t.co/gV4QkYe5mj]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my roommates and I would order food in Korea it was delivered to us hot and fresh via moped.  It came in reusa… https://t.co/U2xgm2Lw0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rhizoctonia is one fungi that is not such a fun guy. These jokes are free. The fungicides are not, but they'll stil… https://t.co/dv1XjGeFWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[When there is only one choice the student does not have to make choices or discover anything new. https://t.co/f5N0tD3P41 via @alicekeeler]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes im extra and i really want it to be from inside disneyland and not a meter further 😂 (i’m leaning towards the first one)]]></document><document><![CDATA[📍SATURDAY:  @heritagefarmers Market at Terra Vista Town Center, 10808 E. Foothill Blvd., Rancho Cucamonga, 9am-2pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning!! Try to have a Marvelous Monday!! https://t.co/3Ri1adXPap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jason is using my kuchi kopi as a pillow right now and it’s so cute because he’s fast asleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great idea that will never come to pass. *sigh*    If it DID get created, what would ghosting look like on… https://t.co/u5xYo0kN3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielaRpo “Let me down slowly” is my fav right now and “sunflower”. That’s the best I can do, I need new music to… https://t.co/BpN4aXGtFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast and Tea ☕️ (@ Home Kitchen in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/Vtn5yMewhP https://t.co/pBOYQ7sCiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys...I-I think Rodger Stone has a YouTube channel... @TheYoungTurks @cenkuygur @AnaKasparian @bretterlich… https://t.co/4KPArIQSvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christylorio Girl. If you need any help or snacks or whatever, please holler.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Metrorailinfo @wmata same shit different day. The fuq is wrong with y’all and the red line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is keeping you from buying a car today? Message me and see what I can do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleRempel This type of Liberal MP just believes that everything underhanded is fine. Corruption at its finest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s a liar and a terrorist. Sarsour is against America..I don’t believe a word she says, working with Muslim brot… https://t.co/CqrVdsasH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be a #loserteacher alongside my inspiring, brilliant and dedicated colleagues.  Hoping our collective work… https://t.co/Ri3bSDP5wF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Honesty and Transparency is what @PressSec wants to be remembered for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Condor_Law @joestornaiuolo @AOC Groomed for the left.  It’s out of Hollywood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulesRosario EXACTLY. She’s not into him 🤷🏼‍♀️ she just wanted to go on the show for the IG followers and then dip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe I felt a tug on my arm, and this nice woman said, "Come on, let's go get coffee." I sniffed, "Who AR… https://t.co/1Yy37W9QYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddydion Tragic because she’s so beautiful, especially with her height]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of people about to get egg on their face. Maybe they'd like some ketchup to go with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Cambria Heights, New York https://t.co/VQqIilhmED]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sad to see that we have a president that is just racist to people that want to be happy in life and just want to be in love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I don’t engage with drivers. I try to be polite and look at the bags he makes on Instagram and he goes… https://t.co/sxOGZbQli8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same. I wouldn’t care if I had all the money in the world. Imma still ride till my light turns on because I don’t w… https://t.co/wuNdK4ClyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know there is a long article about the 2020 election scrolling inside of your ass and you need to be up there to… https://t.co/tlLnU3hMni]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was a dream and a half. I really hope to return one day. #artspowerlaura #littlesquadontheprairie @ Paper… https://t.co/F3ECialiRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helped a friend and her husband with a gender reveal photoshoot today. She picked a super cold weekend when we’re s… https://t.co/LJAaRHE8ZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tatiana is at her metro 🚇 station 🚉 in #TysonsCorner #Virginia https://t.co/FmLBvOkB6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/K9c306HW2T 2:42 actually exacts ruined my life along with criminals]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a steak, sauteed onions &amp; mushrooms with green beans and corn kinda night 😋😋 https://t.co/QvBkppZffa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My birthday is 3 days away and I’m so fucking ugly rn it’s not even funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[The many phases of Famous Fred.  #sundayfunday #bassetthound #bassett #bassetthoundsofinstagram #houndsofinstagram… https://t.co/UBFwf48jms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Korn- Forsaken (vampire Lestat) https://t.co/191Rl9Tz4Z via @YouTube Released 17 years ago💙🎶🤘🏼@Korn RIP @AaliyahHaughton 🙏🏼💙🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonswaine Who is the idiot who didn’t put a gage order on Roger Stone ? Shut him up !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having flown through Addis Ababa airport, I am extremely saddened to hear this news. Prayers for all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@molson1401 Lawdie, I'm sure you believe you know wayyyyy more than anyone else (prob even God). But I prefer to le… https://t.co/9VVfoJzjzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daniel Bisogno Conapred es hora de tomar un fuerte ejemplo no  es la primera Ves que lo hace. #fuerabisognio… https://t.co/xBsg5r2W46]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko @steveio2 These briefings were nothing more than Sarah spewing lies and the press acting like a bu… https://t.co/GFZCTj1QfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO @MrJonCryer One of my favorite movie's as a teenager.."PRETTY IN PINK" #theDuckMan..#duckie… https://t.co/RQlv4TyyEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[😱🛫 🌟 #TravelDEALOfTheDay 🗓ᗪᗩteᔕ: 6/1 - 6/4 M⃣I⃣A⃣M⃣I⃣ | Plan Toᗪᗩy ✈️ #TravelWithTash *****************************… https://t.co/7Lea49GUeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leah on @AmericanAir flight 4843 is TOP NOTCH!! 10/10 service and class in handling rather dumb passengers. If requ… https://t.co/wwfCFJCQcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pamelap70825368 @chelseahandler So true!!  But the media never talks about that! Talk about corruption!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A guy sent me a video of him in a diaper asking if i liked “his diapee”. I feel this pain]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real test of intelligence is, “not how much we know how to do, but how we behave when we don’t know what to do.” - John Holt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance Yes, Jeanine Pirro has had way too much of the Trump koolaid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_Smart_Liberal @charliekirk11 His mind is now blown, he can't process all of that....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shame on me for not realizing that when you say “I have good news” as a woman between age 22 and 40, the correct answer is pregnancy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zenspaceman @garthbrooks I am so sorry Stephen. My thoughts and prayers go up for you and your family]]></document><document><![CDATA[My next sweater to buy and keep. @ Down in the Valley https://t.co/KwSBxSLAN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbeysy Aww don’t feel bad. *hugs* Focus ka na lang sa positive vibes for your full time work for Art. 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorJoeNBrown @CNNPolitics @Trump @ObamaFoundation Ughhhhh.. Like cardboard cutouts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Congress, certain members insist on investigating instead of legislating. Campaigning can wait-we the people w… https://t.co/TkDC3uqNzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Cole, JC, John and Steven for your great customer service in the aisles!!!! @Raulchaveztx @czech_steve… https://t.co/mLQ4K25pGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or laid in bed talking and laughing so hard your stomach muscles are sore and you’re crying? 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psmealey Shit like that soils your mind late at night. Shadows, ghosts, trolls, and fears always look worse in the… https://t.co/34HqsrBYOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hand is going to fry off for holding my damn phone so much . I hope someday I can overcome this addiction 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colleen_eileen @WillieGeist @christinageist Great idea.   Don’t forget the Margaritas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus died for you knowing you might never love him back. THAT IS TRUE LOVE ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bill_Maxwell_ And he screamed that the liberals were trying to take his gun away during his entire trip to the ER.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRobRoberts @olr Is it bad that after the relief of the Mr. Smoosh being ok, my first reaction was to make sure I… https://t.co/4ujL705ZH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#anabelgonzalezfigueroa #merienda #pmbreak @ Melao Bakery Restaurant https://t.co/hmUWoVIMdF]]></document></documents></author>