<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump #hiLIARy is winning by 20 points....   Memory lane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump don’t take $ away from the NGA development in north city STL. We need that complex and the jobs!!!… https://t.co/1S1XwnV1U8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tracktwentynine It has now made its way back to Newark. https://t.co/SUQrbXZyGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jar_O_Cats @williamlegate @AmoneyResists That's a normal reaction to whatever it is about his voice. Perhaps an ex… https://t.co/4jazGfgAAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because you can't see the chinks in someone's armor, doesn't mean they are without said chinks]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOYS HS HOOPS  FINAL  Rio Grande 57 @bulldogs_AHS 69  Jude Tapia 28 pts  Bulldogs now tied with Manzano for 1st in… https://t.co/rWhFhlrZiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felt shity during practice feel  asleep right after woke up at 4:30 am feeling like a million bucks #wokeupfeelingDangerous]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is a different world 🌎 for $500 🙄🙃😂 @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/z6wyVFzYrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to receive an offer from Louisiana Tech University 🔴🔵  @CoachSHoltz https://t.co/DTYXCAgSVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jelani82 Speaking of rent... never in NBA history we’ve had a “Rent-A-GOAT” in the league... 🐐😬 #Lebron https://t.co/UL0ejDSxJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big S/O To Our Tucker Boys Basketball Team As They Battle In The 6A State Championship 3pm Bring That 💍 Home Tigers… https://t.co/cer9GqgP5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/O to @AnthonyGinger18 and @CoachGoering for all their hard work planing Graceland University Civility Week!   You… https://t.co/KQyfVYAqJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MotionToDismiss in Municipal #Court. Sometimes we may go too hard... 🤷🏽‍♂️ @ Stillwater, Oklahoma https://t.co/DmjO5RGv0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AP So your mom had to escape to a red state to distance herself from liberal democrat policies..... that's just classic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenFulop I’m not saying I oppose it— but we should call it what it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 I was in the A1A traffic jam waiting for his entrourage to drive into that monstrasity of his. I'd gl… https://t.co/JB7ADLk3G1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcspocky Cultists don’t see until they do- Marshall Applewhite, Jim Jones]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy has flat-out quit. Please - and I'm begging - don't ever mention him in the same sentence as MJ again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Women’s Tag Team Title match was awesome! So happy Sasha &amp; Bayley are the inaugural champs! #WWEChamber https://t.co/9nXxnWuyxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colosioriojas Déjemos de hacer olas mijito, los contrapesos solo se dan cuando el lado opuesto es mayor. Aquí solo… https://t.co/XcFEPQQui1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree, but probably a bit biased - Thanks for watching and the fantastic TweetOut 😎😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMikofsky @WeatherGeek68 The Whig Party came back (Modern Whigs). They just merged with other party’s across the c… https://t.co/5GKDn4iSBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[He probably learned this trait from  his pal Vladimir who has his own propaganda outlet also😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Gumballhead by @3floyds @ Lizardville Beer Store &amp; Whiskey Bar — https://t.co/VVUJPKD9a5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carterxdane @_CARTERDANE @CarterDaneNews @cockyboys @RJ_SebastianNYC @GayVN @QueerMeNow https://t.co/jYNQEot4RF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Russian weapons are already targeting us with weapons that violated established treaties.  We have to respond now !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHURCHLADY320 @eVilleMike @Selena_Adera Great I will have to study these two, and even more so after your endorsement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freckleeesssss Bro you &amp; Dede never answer back &amp; im just like waiting for a reply 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Rave by xqlusiv_dancecrew team_xqlusiv song by @voicemailmusic @kevynvoicemail @craigvoicemail #newrave… https://t.co/0gP3lepSal]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like game designs that take chances. This appears to take several head-on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TD_Canada Oh got it. So it would be $7.50 Cdn plus whatever the amount i need the draft to be. Is there any item s… https://t.co/PDEUXWFIzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a hard time following your dreams? Ask them where they're going, and hook up with them later. #boom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful and looking forward to what’s next. 🎂🎉 #birthday #abckitchen #nyc https://t.co/FLQQQTj5Nk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to welcome Genesis (McPherson) newest members to our family!  Welcome Darren Ehrlich and Denette Hatch… https://t.co/uMwjOKYAxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Usurp their Illuminati like control of the country. And they don’t even see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fanofall64 He will have a new deal with the Raiders come March 13. It's a substantial boost from his Steelers deal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders is the ONLY Candidate Standing With Striking Locomotive W... https://t.co/Oe4QlSgatF]]></document><document><![CDATA[What y’all doing? @__Reece @DeangeloYurcek @Trey_Da_Great88 @TheeBBush @UrrnnnKing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good night people compartilham aí e RT parceiros @luccas___luccas @SamMorenoX @jerkoffbaddie @100kamisa… https://t.co/cweWmX1Iru]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t feel comfortable rting a tweet with the q slur bc the word makes me uncomfortable but yeah https://t.co/daxoSDwuOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd like to state for the record...that I do not have Netflix...but will now because I must, I mean I must see this… https://t.co/W6UBagDViG]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO HALL COUNTY NEBRASKA LEGAL MARRIAGE TRUTH JUSTICE JESUS CHRIST . MY LEGAL HOME. TMA TRUTH MR AMERICA.  YOU DO UN… https://t.co/byoikHYAcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stained glass ceiling of the Gare du Palais - map of #Canada in reserve so the light on the floor is the correc… https://t.co/ikQMc6PSHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[nao posso ficar acordado q da vontade de fumar e o corre ta acabando e to preso em casa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizWizNewski @AmandaABC27 A plane might be different bc you can’t entirely remove yourself — but a screaming baby… https://t.co/7IuNu7IWXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HardballChris @amyklobuchar You can only give so much Freebies out for votes. Once people know it’s their money fo… https://t.co/JcnTOy3FU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always said the best way to quit the juul is to start smoking cigarettes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erichogue Of course, leaders of a different God and different cult leaders will say the same things.  Why are thos… https://t.co/pIvAwM46Ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @pj_spagno! Thanks for all you do for the #vCommunity. Have a great day! 🎉🎂🥂]]></document><document><![CDATA[LATE NIGHT APEX STREAM... 500+ KILLS LIFELINE MAIN https://t.co/oFx63VF2ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freak_OTRT @Fen_the_Wolf If you dig Disney you really should check it out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny how life works. Me @lifethegreat and @samjaycomic ended up at a bar on Edgewood that’s hosting an open mic. T… https://t.co/W9u2a8iava]]></document><document><![CDATA[My biggest concern with #cryptocurrency is that its very anonymity makes it ideal for fraudsters.  #risk]]></document><document><![CDATA[No emergency at the border treasonous people in the White House that’s an emergency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yesitsmecrissy I would use both of those adjectives to describe him — necessary skills to have in a surgeon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[By request, here is the direct podcast link to the conversation with the twin sons of different mothers, Damian Bre… https://t.co/YxRrXdk051]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINALLY!!! I got these achievements for Tomb Raider Definitive but they glitched and never unlocked. Four years lat… https://t.co/MyyE6MO3kd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fedupcitizen16 @agueros_henry @maziehirono It doesn't have to solve everything, just slow down the invasion to lev… https://t.co/P4eCPQiz34]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealGlenMacnow Are you about 300 pounds by now. https://t.co/OtpXAoMvVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#amazingnature #onedayatatime #livewhereyoulove @ Signature Place Condos &amp; Lofts https://t.co/7fjYec4oH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Piglordmma @PlatinumPerry What's up brother. Yea idk who that was or posted that link but that's not to my shirts.… https://t.co/vG49PK4Gyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tdrane33 @McGinnisPGA Nah you're right, not an idiot in the situation. But you compare this to something like obj,… https://t.co/GtNPVdj546]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nocompsnoconvo he is def my most popular cosplay fkskgks thank u! https://t.co/sOKHkxJb6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ I'm still working on the Pythagorean Theorem from junior high so there;'s all kinds of shit I don't understand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[sylvia makes my heart happy. it’s 5 am and she called to make sure i was okay (‘:]]></document><document><![CDATA[should i go brush my teeth now or fuck up this burrito. OR should i save it for breakfast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great news for air quality in restaurants. We recommend induction cooking to reduce pollutants but you still need e… https://t.co/uVrF0PpRaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennisTFP @BrianBlessing @stevieslapshot @KSHP1400 what was Dennis' Twitter?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonrwatts @NRA This guy has probably watched “Red Dawn” about 100 times. https://t.co/8UXtioWQfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you dont eat this with 6 spoonfuls of sugar you ain't eating it right]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confidence is everytbing. I feel for Cody Garbandt because he is a good fighter just lost his confidence you can se… https://t.co/MzsLqAxDJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida bound!! Midwinter break! #golfgrind #byebyesnow #funinthesun #boystrip @ Gerald R. Ford International Airpo… https://t.co/bQLwIAp3ei]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk who needs to see this but if you need to drive anywhere today let’s not be a dumbass]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CBJ could use a solid, veteran D ... especially now that Murray is out “indefinitely” with his undisclosed upper-b… https://t.co/MhtMSW3rkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearBubbie Def worth looking into or just pregame with a shot of the ACV have the mashers and chase it with anothe… https://t.co/SACVaWTJJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan why aren’t you talking about this?  North Korea rebuilding long-range rocket site, photos show https://t.co/Rk5WruHJ6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jw_hanson @guy_fromthemoon @BrandiKruse Believing talking points. Here a dem slip “Nearly” half of illegals in the… https://t.co/LwCipSKaOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sandwich in LA be 3.99 plus tax after Tax that same sandwich 9 dollars 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn 1 year ago today.. the most traumatic shit I’ve ever been through but we still here. More life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No removal, you guys kept Steve King on committees for years after he made racist remarks. She kee… https://t.co/2pb2MhXe6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[And despite the few grammatical errors, and the fact that I used “thus” so much which really hurts me soul (I will… https://t.co/7aejlY7eKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheeTedSmith you sound like Tony soprano when you talk about your parent who argues with you about going to a retirement community]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can the #IowaDemocrats @iowademocrats just tell the @NYCMayor to go home. Or at least tell him forget about running… https://t.co/gPdU3TMsCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Olivia93409861 @JacobAWohl do your relatives need help loading the moving truck?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DameDoodyStench @Dogwhistle1984 @molttedduck @AOC Won what? A minimum wage job at Taco Bell, living at home🙄every… https://t.co/6othCBtU09]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debostic @TrulyTrumpette @MiesW @nytimes @TwitterSafety @williamlegate You can tell him that, or dm him his DM’s a… https://t.co/uJuAyQigkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Hitler took names of his enemies and even his own party members suspected of thinking differently o… https://t.co/Jmg5nnJ3E5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whitneyballen but it is fucked. i have done it and at least i got to see a whole@bunch of friends in one city for… https://t.co/s2oYPES5p5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nueva Imagen / Bendita Caffeina #cafemexicano #cafegourmet #veracruz #chiapas #oaxaca #cafedeolla #coffeeshop https://t.co/OvBuslQDzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FSNGorg @fsnorth @Osiecki24 Great man. Graded his PE classes on your finish in a bracket and his full contact hock… https://t.co/XiQLtuPc2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like spending 25 minutes to clean off your car in the cold when you have a 2 door garage @ Connecticut https://t.co/0B8oUdyZZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrFNA @Sara_Jiang Yes, but sometimes when they’re ready is after they should. But it should not be a number, as pe… https://t.co/WF60I5WKMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rowdy18TrumpFan @GABR_Bassets I’m proud to be BFF as well.  A great way to support @GABR_Bassets .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosPatar @luismorales0621 @EnriquePenalosa Uh no hablo el cientfico]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not even 8pm and I’ve fallen asleep on the couch twice now and drooled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanSlocum @SWMBlades @PortageNorthern @trhswildcats @HCAthleticDept @PNorthernHockey @JoeInsider @MichHSHockey Peter Todd was stellar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Low key though I agree I wouldn’t pay that much either. Maybe Vikings at home but not traveling to see it. But… https://t.co/0bOCESYDG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonnyOfTheMeek @BostonGlobe I got what's in ya school. About fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth,  now on the… https://t.co/7nPBcVeZOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making further continuing appropriations for the Department of Homeland Security for fiscal year 2019, and for othe… https://t.co/AXSzXKwKcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScrewedHumans Sure is. Democrats angry!  “Orange Man Bad!”  The Socialists are taking over this is NOT your Dads D… https://t.co/nWNtXRr70C]]></document></documents></author>