<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[New signs in the shop!  Hand made by a women in Aston, PA.  They can be hung indoor or outdoors #hollymackdesigns… https://t.co/3PjhUsmdmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@700club I don't understand how Pat Robertson supports our president when He Lies and cover's his tracks in everyth… https://t.co/OHRxiwYh8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y toda esa fealdad interior se refleja en un físico que mete miedo🤣🤣🤣Esa mamarracha diabolical regalada es cara!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember a professor of mine at @PNCA tore me and my art to shreds when we presented our portfolios because “you… https://t.co/b8K5hRffJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sowecouIddances i really thought that these moose were gonna age prices listed next to them]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no idea why I love this line by @slimthugga but I do.   "Now look who creepin', look who crawlin' still ball… https://t.co/Oc5JVtHUp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando tengo este tipo de trabajos actuando de adolescente, juego un juego secreto: me mezclo entre ellos, aprendo… https://t.co/NFmtZnHLMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GBPackers4ever @ACarrizle I can send you a 10% Off coupon code if you want it. 😎😏 https://t.co/KiOLMkuQPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you put your sweetener in the spot where the coffee pod goes instead of in your cup, your day may not be going… https://t.co/tkeDEraekV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supreme Court, in unanimous ruling, moves to limit state and local governments’ power to impose fines and seize... https://t.co/DxZ831sGhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cobalt_alloy Are you in Tucson—- cause rumor has it there’s a group of people that would really like to see you 🐻⬇️🥎]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Border of San Francisco/Daly City in Daly City, CA https://t.co/N4ySdlLzOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Your such an ass! Shut up! Get a real job...you would be destroyed in an hour...same as you and you… https://t.co/Sg7ds3Dloj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti @TIME Now you want to make pathetic excuses for a planned Coup D'etat that failed backed by a two… https://t.co/M25MUjGKtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodbæ February!!! ❄️❄️❄️  #goodbye #february #windburn #bae #niagarafalls #niagara #canada #whenincanada #yyz… https://t.co/imi8AajqUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drahus11 @suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy @cazij @JackConnie @thatsVeryKari @ja2cook @CaraMiaSG @ccatmpt @simplysallyh… https://t.co/SJJ5lMOWcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I met and talked to one of my favorite singer-songwriters, who was in one of my favorite bands, Yellowca… https://t.co/PWgu5fSCpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhiPhiOhara @TrinityTheTuck @monetxchange You know my story sis ! The struggle was real !! And you came to safe me ! I love you 💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of #WomensHistoryMonth one of my favorites - we know how it feels to be torn down... why not lift each other… https://t.co/9rN8RrzPP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megspptc This has been the most surreal of all the celebrity passings. I don't understand it, but it hurts, all th… https://t.co/mXBDiXZD71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inkstainedretch @suzola2 Also like to point out that most citizens could never afford the thousands of dollars it… https://t.co/zwFAQKakGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @VanEBlantonES 💯Fluent Reflex Math Superstars ⭐️ Sweet Success💚 #ReflexMath]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell Put a hat on Eric. I’m sure you’d want ur kids to wear a hat!  Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do you think priests do that? I mean sure, priests get lonely but so do we all. But we don't just go around hav… https://t.co/c5qTSOKvc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes The failing NYT has NO INDEPENDENT JOURNALIST- THEY ARE ALL SLAVES TO LIBERALISM OR MARXISM. The thoughts… https://t.co/52hHSBZDfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like I need to buy my wife a new PS4 for her birthday. She's still rocking her release day PS4. It sounds like a rocket engine. #PS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smerconish "I don't begrudge the man a vacation" is a Ridiculous Assertion because we know that the majority of… https://t.co/rhi1qlVZty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moralezagustin @banda_35_ Banda if you dont go somewhere with that 😠 https://t.co/6raFwii0A8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnyosmond @MaskedSingerFOX All it takes is one small leak to ruin a good show - even by an intern who didn't mea… https://t.co/nahoUHyR4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sb3361 @LrmPublicity Or the space the bed is in or the energy of the place itself. Yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitMarieox @AOC I guess AOC doesn't know the difference between CPAC and Liberty University. She is such an idiot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@its_kiiaraaa Why do u leave your food in the microwave for days until it rots? didn’t ya momma teach yo  ass better 🤮😂 #ClapBack]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AcademicTwitter Poll: How many tabs do you have open on your computer right now? (I'm working on two computers --… https://t.co/C0qrORDIcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the @ledyard_nahs projects is complete! Thank you @kcurriesmith for including them in your great idea! It ca… https://t.co/3qXRhCeVLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[You work at a minimum wage job and then you're dead for a billion trillion years]]></document><document><![CDATA[But this one gon' last because her name is Nelle and I'm so good with that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend just sent me a video of her meeting @theestallion and honestly I’m so jealous idk if I should just block her now 😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smc429 @KassandraSeven It does not seem so. She ignores me all the time. I can take a hint. 🙄 #YesWeCan days we al… https://t.co/ALkhBN9Zfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@romyreiner @realDonaldTrump @nytimes 😂😂😂😂 girl you're just like your daddy! Good stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out all the other amazing items and receive 15% off of your order with my code: Arleen4BD #bdrocks… https://t.co/VmgZFijB8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[A flashback from divine Dotti yesterday. A shoot we did in New York together with jameshoustonphoto and @emmawatson… https://t.co/CtD5exOoZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @MrChemGeek and @SGilletteEDU to post the covers of 7 books I love without explanations/reviews… https://t.co/eU7kNMyL8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation it looks like @Sean_C_Larkin is wearing Jumpsuit Orange tonight. #escapeconvict. LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaseelliott @KyleBusch @DanielHemric @ClintBowyer since our son was born in 2015 we have shared our love for nasc… https://t.co/I9ewkT1eTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumorMonger31 @AnupmaMichael @greatairi @SsanjayTaannk @IamSunitha777 @yogeychauhan @GCHDutta @u_mirella @panjami… https://t.co/dsxntqUWpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up on the couch to jersey shore reruns and now I want my black hair, tanned skinned and big silver hoop earrings back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGhost11 Hahaha - grew up in the 90s, that shit doesn’t leave your language 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ana_Elle971 with Olitz stories when new Olitz/Terry pics drops...and I can’t wait for the next season 😂🙌🏽🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshMBernstein Wait, you stop getting Rosé pitches? I’d think there’d be a deluge. And how long is the break - lik… https://t.co/lJU7MvZKJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dream Up the Perfect Wedding with BlueBay Hotels | Essential Coordination and Travel https://t.co/7HuT7LBOYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[same dress three Oscars in a row. a true fashion icon. https://t.co/lVJ1tYDArL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskPlayStation my account was hacked an now says I'm banned ..please help!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess what guys? Im going to annoy you from TWO twitter accounts now cuz we are trying this platform again...Follow… https://t.co/m8HM5uFMnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myrahenry24 @SarahPalinUSA Name me the names of these billionaires that don't pay their fair share of taxes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#coloroftheday #FridayThoughts #FridayFeeIing #thankgoddessitsfriday #Friyay https://t.co/uwFkELPVsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The devil suggested to the woman saying, “No! You will not die! God knows in fact that on the day you eat it your e… https://t.co/ga0UfLYUTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[magical Saturday #HarryPotter #sortinghat #magical #weekendvibes #hatlife #truth whereintheworld https://t.co/UAOx4j6yTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seul pour la Saint Valentin? Alone for Valentine’s Day ? 👉🏽👉🏽https://t.co/s7nn79XELE 😘😘😘 https://t.co/kQTXQn3KLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Is anyone else getting tired of anti-Trumpers playing the victims of hate to cause trouble? It seems… https://t.co/tJXGyF990B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to one of my fav human beings @_serena_kc thank you for always knowing the song in my heart and help… https://t.co/VuRjwl8zX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a tremendous amount of experience on this #stoy panel today at #ECET2NM Thank you all for sharing! #nmstoy… https://t.co/oVwpIKpsli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Why was "Salad" not an option? It's probably closer to donalds IQ &amp; leadership capabilities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, it's Tuesday, so you all know what that means-- TACOS!!!!!! 😁😊🤤👏🏻  As you know, we always try to eat healthy-… https://t.co/0XbrZ90Qxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Day 1 of the Florida Legislative Session, friends! https://t.co/i5WOTsbiWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissG015 @Doseofcolors They had a bogo sale so I bought their liquid lipsticks. They are freaking bomb 💣!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eisaiah_e @basiaderkowska @dez_blanchfield @evankirstel @HIMSS @RasuShrestha @Colin_Hung @JoeBabaian @nickisnpdx… https://t.co/HBHkGkGeNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GatorsFB @gloryboy_Sean Awwww we will never forget about you . I wish you all the best and can’t wait to follow your career]]></document><document><![CDATA[10/10 times if I encounter a jerk driver on the interstate it’s a truck. Can y’all just calm down for a sec???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost I totally believe her, but my main question is:  Why was a woman of color who isn't Omarosa (opport… https://t.co/z8IDrvOMxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“She looked like a Tim Burton character in the face but she had a fat ass” is a sentence I just said out loud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg Mandy Moore said she was 34 on @WTFpod and because of #ThisIsUs I was like....she’s 65 what?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what you’re doing. Please don’t give up. Don’t stop just because it isn’t going your way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, this was a surprise! @ Wells Fargo Center https://t.co/BTesaacJZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[A list of women I would marry in a heartbeat no questions asked: @LanaDelRey @lucyhale  @AshBenzo  @MsSarahPaulson… https://t.co/6ENQJHYqhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t bought nikes in forever but daaaaaaamn I’m about to go buy some shit 😫😫😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[letting the kids growing up think its okay for mixed marriage. I dont think GOD  had in mind.the faces are more whi… https://t.co/Mm3edtlbVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[De a de veras que vainas será que no sabe Guaido de las andanzas de estas joyitas que tal ojo pelao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrNicoleArcy @DrPol @ChuckPol You all look so wonderful together and how is Mrs Charles Pol?💜✝️🙏🏻🤟🏻❤️🌹🌹🌹🌹🤟🏻🤟🏻🤟🏻♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it to the southernmost point of the continental US! https://t.co/Hi4URrXllg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwmtnews I’m not a fan of the new political commentary segment. I find both commentators annoying. If I want to he… https://t.co/8T6Kv4K590]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who doesn’t take Reading Recovery seriously, has OBVIOUSLY no idea how rigorous the training year truly is!!… https://t.co/srqevEXjsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HomelessnessSD What the hell is wrong with these people who have a warm bed to sleep in, food to eat and money to… https://t.co/QBv7iVTHEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeToda So if everyone believes him he spent his childhood as a sex abuse victim. If no one believes him, he’s a l… https://t.co/gONWTItfwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding your focus: meditations for exams and presentations https://t.co/KFge0GD3MK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OPBronteCreek Looking good @OPBronteCreek! Super cool to be able to step back in time at an @OntarioParks. #WeGetOutside]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrew_wiebe The crest/logo don’t matter. We’re all just going up there for the BBQ and hot chicken. 🍖🍗😋😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog Great, great show last night! I was riveted! Let it be. Let it be!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo miedo saben. Me pasan por la cabeza cosas horribles. Qué pasa si Guri ya no da para más  y necesitan semanas… https://t.co/0yUlAJvfmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamHeughan @emmagbeauchamp @Outlander_STARZ OMG..  LOL now I am mortified and speechless 😱 Thx 😊🇩🇰]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AtlanticProWrestling @masshole_617 vs @DannyMilesUSA #HeavyweightTitle @ Newburyport Elks https://t.co/vrpcKbfOIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews Sad to even think he went to these lengths for what attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL 😊.. ahhhh.. 😁... Hahaha 😁.... Before or after I cleaned and disinfected my bat? 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YandR_CBS This is gonna piss me off more than the baby switch on @BandB_CBS .... please freAking don’t. He answere… https://t.co/8FnqmmQbP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidDTodd @ChicagoPenguin2 @BxglL @fanactionsports @MrsSpuds @72cricket @sannbs @CSonafelt @sharon_schwan @RidenerTina @ACog1984 So sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh man. poor Reem. you're digging. your grave is going to be deeeeep. #survivor]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wwefastlane #theshield @wwerollins romanreigns #deanambrose #onelasttime #emotional @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/U1ToDW6Scu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica Put #StokelySandersCarmichael up on #MountWhiteSMore!😂#Vermont isn't the most #EuropeanState in… https://t.co/KX6IPj99lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get you a @its_paigeey , who just types up a whole page in less than 15 minutes for your summary essay. #bestMom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficiallyAlly I recommend #theGallghergirlseries and the #Heistseries]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was 21 when I got pregnant, in college, in NC with my family in OH. When I went into labor, IDK about 25-30 frien… https://t.co/UvnGb1XwWQ]]></document></documents></author>