<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Good morning!! Happy Sunday!! @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/6wDlTy4TTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgeveritt Butapub in the South Wedge announced this week that it’s closing next month. But in fairness, my comment… https://t.co/4CGkCMkQzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_MattBarile @kmariano13 @DanMurtagh5 Barz we must’ve missed you out there in the state tourney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Qantas Yep! Please move to the back plane stop crashing airplanes with your cell phone and leave the peanuts on th… https://t.co/jddvoiHNfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adsh01 @jameshorowitzmd @PERTConsortium @Vascularman @LukeWilkins_UVA @2Scottish @AlexCVIR VV by the way is much l… https://t.co/X6X8IZV1w9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idiot. The measles virus can cause infections by itself (i.e.meningitis) or  secondary infections  o antibiotic res… https://t.co/Up2Appn5Qh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please consider taking this global survey on #sustainability! https://t.co/QVKBBTcwoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game Day! @MastodonMBB vs Omaha 5:30pm EST! #RoadTough #HaveFunBeUS Listen @BrettRumpSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @realDonaldTrump @mattgaetz you're not the fox any future questions 🤔 https://t.co/pA6vAdLy2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@svdate @RedSaintPotion That is calling the kettle black, I could say the same about him. At least she is better to look at.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ex calls me every night talking bout shit she heard lmFaoo and it’s always her swearing I’m gay 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenWhyte3 Tell me that when the bid prices come in higher than the budget governments are willing to pay... The en… https://t.co/2fhZHCFj1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daubon nails a 3 and Demelis follows with another -- this one for her 1,000th career point -- and @athleticshpcsd l… https://t.co/IX3Jrw8V1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LanceHuntUNF @JUBaseball @SportsCenter @Kenny_Mayne @ScottManze @OZZIEtheOSPREY It was scored as an error for the Osprey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a final in Pacific League softball: Arcadia 7, Burbank 5.  Apaches score winning run in the seventh inning.  T… https://t.co/cKfHvtAfAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright I just heard @pepperlive cover of the Police song, I Cant stand losing you. LOVE IT!! Can't believe I never… https://t.co/cwSVIVwAEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irock_headbands Who did kuzma switch too? They both were standing at the free throw line guarding no one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling John Kelly!!!! The Senate and House Committees are looking for you!!! Oh yea, and Mueller!!! Hmmm maybe eve… https://t.co/oqUP1te8dQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Best grab a few rolls of paper towels and head down .... #Dolt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inforum Anyone who is able to read can figure out for themselves how credible Cohen was. Also, he worked for Trump… https://t.co/bNQb64q7Wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raaaaaannda Idk dude we were in trunks and it disappeared and tell me how I have 3 charges on it since I lost it.… https://t.co/RyT3w07bUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gym Jordan has found that waiting years and then gaslighting victims is a strategy that has worked well for him so… https://t.co/Bbs5DFQ9Ht]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buying or selling, call me! I'm here to HELP!  ERIC GUTIERREZ (714)926-7545  #EricGutierrez #RealtorEG #location… https://t.co/2HkSNLJRqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump I tried posting the actual truth to @facebook about the #NickSandmann story. They… https://t.co/TsNcPfXyLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgBioWorld @jgkoomey Also no controls or case-matching, not randomized; plus undisclosed financial conflict. A com… https://t.co/Oql6kFMy3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Progressive pays nearly $2million in settlement with Rhode Island for overcharging citizens https://t.co/ljWbgYEl9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Draco613 You know how Vince is gonna do This he's not gonna give her the title as long as The Riott Squad is still The Riott Squad]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the heart of the greatest state in the greatest country in the world https://t.co/MZM58WAAq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA So Democrats are already trying to manipulate the election by taking a SITTING PRESIDENT off the ballot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For you are my hiding place; you protect me from trouble. You surround me with songs of victory. Interlude” Psalms… https://t.co/7Cirl9ysKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arkansas HS Girls BKB 5A West contests via seeds: 1 Vilonia v 4 Russellville 2 LR Christian v Siloam Springs 3 Gree… https://t.co/PhMZWXLzrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dizzysinclair Try to invert it slowly once or twice you can get it mixed well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Venice311 thunderbirds are flying around LA on Monday 1215 and 530. Santa Clarita ,JPL , Hollywood, SMO Pier , Malibu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SanAndreas_11 Te espero en la caracola, para llegar todos sudados juntos yy...😏😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[In squad we trust 🙏🏼 #LittyCity 📸: @seeyouonthewest @ High Fidelity L.A. https://t.co/GCelildoXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Algún día volveré.. #crossfitter #EliteTeam #MX #acuña en Ciudad Acuña, Mexico https://t.co/lURRxdse62]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimValley @davemeltzerWON @richpatterson1 I could see that being the case for some of it. But a lot of the Portlan… https://t.co/dtASMkgiif]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started my own business  Curt Collins Media and we are open!  Does your business need help managing its social media? I can help!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manafort is also in danger of going on a Polonium diet outside of prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t fun @maytengonza y todo ese entertaining #chisme N #celebrating #womenshistorymonth or #wemansecrets ✌🏻😂 @… https://t.co/NFJqQZ4fXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hale_razor @TheDaleJackson @TheJuanWilliams He and all of the rest have to say it. They know it’s going to be obvi… https://t.co/k5PWwGAvxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Word of the year seems to be “disruption.” If it doesn’t help you place a sign in the yard it’s simply a: ”distraction!” #WinTheDay #JPARUSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[HIGH SCHOOL SOFTBALL  Middle 5th inning Odessa High 5, Bushland 3  Lady Falcons go down in order. @OA_Sports #oavarsity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get their lips pumped up. It always looks weird and obvious. #IDontUnderstandPeopleWho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got up and time to get ready for @ACGCSchools wrestling at state. I’ll have updates throughout the day.  In th… https://t.co/fSwHH0Uq03]]></document><document><![CDATA[This photo is powerful AF.  • Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez • Rep. Ayanna Pressley • Rep. Rashida Tlaib https://t.co/EHZi2btIKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[DANI FILTH of CRADLE OF FILTH @cradleoffilth over the weekend along with @officialwed13 and @ravenblackband in Sacr… https://t.co/fpsWJW4E1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd like to take a moment to applaud all the creators of the world, the originals, the people with ideas.....there… https://t.co/1z3rXyEeRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same Joe Biden who trashed Anita Hill and gave us Clarence Thomas on the Supreme Court. Go away, Joe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was one of the most fun shoots I have ever had and holy fuck they were all so sexy😍😍 Couldn’t imagine a better… https://t.co/r3O27irhLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone from simi water wars that has alicia porter’s team they’re all chillin at palm beach tan on madera💅🏻💅🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GADeptofTrans @RobyGreenwald @GDOTATL This was on north sidewalk of Memorial Drive across near intersection of Oak… https://t.co/OL4dFqgHge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kim Jong Un told me so and I believe him.  Vladimir Putin told me so and I believe him.  MSB told me so and I belie… https://t.co/nBwBD6FyYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The old famous #pointreyes road @ Cypress Tree Tunnel https://t.co/PEVyzFiEqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awkward and amazing, love my executives. ❤  (Not pictured: Stingray and Macey) https://t.co/kNzYUzQnBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaReef70 And i can’t speak for anyone outside of me lol but all I’m saying is for me personally the information b… https://t.co/LairstuUJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comsurv @CGRTeams @RaceSonoma @scottdixon9 Thank you for your kindness it’s very much appreciated God bless all of you 🙏🇺🇸❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardmarx Did you expect anything less?  You really should’ve known better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see my pals, @TheBlueStones , rock London, ON tonight. I hope that stage is able to contain their ene… https://t.co/Nggg9e66Tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@txcelat @ShawnG927 @karli_bonne @JohnnyB371 @OutOfRegister @Jetsta812 @Maggieb1B @TWITMO_INMATE @RoseDC11… https://t.co/JoUYeLIxID]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Claiborne Pell Elementary School in Newport, RI https://t.co/7HwTxSnD9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craigcalcaterra What's that? That most of them are hired out of thin air. I find that hard to believe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you fucking LIED, you sorry piece of shit. Your fucking wall means more to you than the health of your people!… https://t.co/hOVdY1Syz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mycoskie Don’t know if the recommendation was from you or @TomBurnettSLC but thanks. Well worth it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LJVMColiseum @madea @tylerperry This was very poorly done for this performance at 4:00 pm, one gate open, no traff… https://t.co/eKxfQ9A3lt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, you could just skip the app/hat and use some type of face concealing hood that hides your identity. Might k… https://t.co/C1MW8OUO2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Center Square And Beyond Alfred E. Smith Building on 3/14/18 https://t.co/fKvojqTmPq https://t.co/DOAiizcx9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  the quebec court of appeals decision.. would not normally be seen in any .. westernized nation.. but the queb… https://t.co/uwx61GC7My]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden you are a disgrace to America. This country is the greatest but you and your party are trying to destroy… https://t.co/fjv2yRnGXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[U15 Boy's Midgets - Consolation Bracket (G5) - @WolverinesElite def. @MississaugaBall 70-50 #EBAThunder @exposurebball]]></document><document><![CDATA[#makeupmondays Artistry Brush Set How to use the Concealer Brush and the Powder Brush. @artistryus #like4like… https://t.co/AalIdT2FI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tyler__Jones38 @WalderSports Nope . Contact was initiated by the shooter. Ie. he purposely leaned into Lowery. Not a foul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out #TheBridge, our revamped Youth space at our #Hawesville campus: https://t.co/VeHstHkyRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Youngbull23 @TheOpening @RivalsCamp Got you in my prayers! Hope all goes well! 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexis’ big night. Grand Champion Market Steer, Lincoln County. She worked her tail off with this calf. I’m one pro… https://t.co/vLfeoMXPIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of additions this morning to the Noles247 Junior Day List (VIP)  https://t.co/zggiuwTeJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So can’t wait for beach 🏖 weather!!  Right now is actually great time for a beach session minus the rain or even wi… https://t.co/TJ8XnquIiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecadencelux @VeronicaAvluvXX @AlexisFawx @thebonnierotten @KleioValentien @cutelunastar @ZoeysSweetTea]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEY, @Spankmonsterxxx - thanks for the RE-TWEET; if you have time, please leave a COMMENT (under the review)... REA… https://t.co/ruc9tHQsdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joacircost @doisdedosdeteo @teologueiros Cara, eu não li. Não posso falar muito.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikefreemanNFL is out here slaying peers, board operators and other fools.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Fake News is so bad for our Country! Just as bad as a fake president. https://t.co/rtSVxx8o2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[For it is by grace you have been saved, through faith—and this is not from yourselves, it is the gift of God— not b… https://t.co/cV74xnB0xV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliaMorales @AstrosRadioMLB @SteveSparks37 @raford3 The BEST radio broadcast team in Baseball!!! @raford3… https://t.co/lOj8sqkmdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[She likes " mi cama suena y suena" @ Frederick, Maryland https://t.co/hdzMJrnoXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think a response option for favorable/unfavorable presidential primary polls should be "Who...?"  Schultz fav/unf… https://t.co/Lj4sS6FrOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren @EricLesser To bad! Maybe they shouldn’t have borrowed the money! Tax payer $!! I want my money back! I… https://t.co/mYAA9NVJiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eriksen has looked tired all game, and his passing and shooting have been awful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boxing_fan88 @JackAlterr @SibbieBoxing @Im_gr8nss @TheKidIrv24 @UnkhanciousAmir @SmokinYungBruno @Yogi_CapAlot… https://t.co/TBcLRV742R]]></document><document><![CDATA[The peace and the Love God Can Give u  the world can't  #Overcomers in Christ # Glory Carriers# Notime for foolishb… https://t.co/0HKqffWNSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the main thing of all. I hope that my niggas, my bros and I will come up in this world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFacelessGame It's the same people as Get out and Us. Have you seen the gift?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be honest, I’m a dumb bitch BUT a lot of people really out here making me look smart asffff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family painting night was so much fun! 🎨 I’m sure you can figure out which one of us did each one. 👩‍🎨👩🏻‍🎨👨🏻‍🎨… https://t.co/2UvFCeErd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mediotiempo @11carlosV @LAFC @MLS TOP en la MLS, eso no es parámetro para ver su real nivel, pero bueno mínimo si… https://t.co/KDY52MkEmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Embarassing performances by the Raps &amp; Leafs tonight. Both locker rooms deserve a visit from @MarkForwardd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAO!!! Malika beeeeeen a messy bitch. These old folks coming out the woodworks today]]></document><document><![CDATA[This final stretch is going to be fun to watch. Every night is a must win. Early playoff hockey! #Blackhawks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodSaltyDog @jmatthew @Eireknight @DanOakesWriter @libbyking @MichaelSimpson7 Where talking about Pink Floyd bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silagechopper @courtlee05 @koinzangreg @PerformanceBeef Only if it’s got the pen number in it]]></document></documents></author>