<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[High key need this, high key have the money for it, high key need to save tho… shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraLMonroe33 When he is calling a game I mute it .... just can not take it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smoke with the Ally Opp ( got skinny 👖on ) @BouieDeyon 2022 Ath 🐇  Bainbridge Ga   @Trapp_SETA229  @DemetricDWarren… https://t.co/XBtJxJ3qY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMccafe @oldlife @SamGrinis @micahmattix “Roman Catholicism closest ecclesiastical analog among indigenous America… https://t.co/mWBB8E0ZM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realnickfrias @AlexDaugherty1 @RStanleyNHL I want absolutely no part of that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SupremeAce_ happy birthday man! To me birthdays are the start of that persons new year so also happy new year brother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If you weren’t a con man or a #FakePresidet the Democrats could get on with legislating. Oh, and a crook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Football is BACK! Excitement through the roof!   #GoArmy #SpringBall2019 https://t.co/23TUs0PZlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  after the Many republican senators in the senate side with the @POTUS and his fears of a crisis at the border… https://t.co/D2Egd6iJ9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trend following has suffered because the models can’t move as fast as the president's tweets. Not climate change to… https://t.co/rHKicbKVR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk how it happened by I am now a coach for T-Ball 😂 gunna be my little children until May]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee and sandwich in preparation for today's travels  ✈️ LEX ➡️ LGA ➡️ YYZ ➡️ YFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikodup1 @sondermoon She done went and ungracefully ate a whole dinosaur. I'm hurting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder if @QUACKHOUSE would want to check out the rodeo this weekend in Houston 🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vitali17 @RichieC1189 Can we expect them to make the playoffs next year?  The year after?  As a fan how do u not c… https://t.co/1SUlivmXbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think that more #WomenInStartups are needed to advance gender equality today. Do you agree? #SheBelongs… https://t.co/POQI7QkH8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: knows i should be on anxiety meds  also me: nah i’ll just smoke until i pass out and hope i don’t wake up with… https://t.co/RB0Dnk0ckX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whats a real nigha if he ain real with ya? And whats a down bitch if she ain still with ya?? 💯💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday March 1 - Balance of Power:     Donald Trump is back in Washington, where the political and legal peril he f… https://t.co/2uM7TTDork]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven't seen #theumbrellaacademy  that's on #Netflix you're definitely missing out. It has my #mancrush… https://t.co/d9c7vSmhev]]></document><document><![CDATA[Claimed the other day he’s in Mexico yet the woman in the pic is wearing a T-shirt from Tenerife hotel that he went… https://t.co/A4aPj9RPRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work pants just ripped at the inner thigh, so that’s fun - Thank you, Gym. I’m just too slim thiqq now. 🤦🏾‍♂️ https://t.co/bSVC8gHNEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shakespeare &amp; Company interacting with their audience after performing The Taming of the Shrew #shakespeare… https://t.co/FeE2QgZBqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBrofucius @The1stBAT @UpToTASK @BrianLeeOkert @The_GWW @CBNostalgia @GeekVibesNation @mrjafri @GeekToMeRadio… https://t.co/JEwIJc1wIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Melt had this earlier in the week 🍔😃 . . . ❌ignore these❌ #burger #food #foodie #sffoodie #sfeats… https://t.co/yMuC69ZMVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelbwell @JeffProbst @survivorcbs Maybe you should name it Kat.@KatEdorsson 😼Ha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basketball skills development training tonight 6-7:30pm at Singing Hills Recreation Center 1909 Crouch Rd, Dallas 7… https://t.co/XCfZuDa5rV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yayraaa Hi!, we are conducting a free 45-minute martial arts workout tmrw @ 12PM at 285 Green Street in Cambridge… https://t.co/kcqsllmFbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to more upcoming tour dates, starting this weekend in #Louisville, KY THIS SATURDAY (March 2) for t… https://t.co/dnYxDisLyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your bother hunts city deer!! 😂😂🦌🔫 #hunting #citydeer #wearprotection #pittsburgh #brookline @ Pittsburgh, Pen… https://t.co/5t9TIxO2mO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HzRph Me guiare por el de metacritic que es 68(similar al de ant man) y fuego 🐑]]></document><document><![CDATA[The majority of Canadians, when asked, do not want ISIS fighters to be allowed back into Canada - others, less that… https://t.co/UpFJeXp6Np]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grphcnvltywife @fafhrd01 I keep making PCs so @fafhrd01 has a reason to keep playing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strong faith (in HIM) is all it takes, HE will handle the rest...you’ll get to where you need to be. Y’all have a b… https://t.co/huxbQbw2Ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurnsJ33 Padres making the playoffs and they still could pick up Harper]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bitch @TeshPrettyAzz BLACKEDDDD‼️‼️😩😩😩 She a hater tho https://t.co/ZaJVIz3EuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobGMacfarlane "We were somewhere around Barstow on the edge of the desert when the drugs began to take hold. I re… https://t.co/yIDYhYLlAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthStationBOS on a Sunday night with snow❄️coming to Boston 😖 https://t.co/1QdTwWb1Vg]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔴⚪️LIVE⚪️🔴  @PlayApex until 2 am CT  3 wins and counting how many more can we get?!  Monthly Goals: 6/10 Subs 113/2… https://t.co/NWZb7xJUoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlasHernandez1 @rulosk_el Soy de barrio bien humilde y en casa muchas veces un refuerzo de mortadela y un vaso de… https://t.co/4YhkiwGEvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iDavey My mom and I don’t fight but I just need my own space because everyone irritates me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carmen_allgood @DEF407 I’d LOVE to see them build THAT in Atlanta or Orlando!....Sit back with a bucket of popcorn… https://t.co/kwQTg7Gopn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The car sits in my driveway, not in a stream.  I find this troubling.    They dealer won’t attempt to fix without m… https://t.co/l2yHceic2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[FRIDAY IS NOT SUPER NACHO DAY...dang kids today have it pretty darn good! #supernacho #spoiled @ Lakeland High Scho… https://t.co/bBAoinYsbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Happy19111 @OutlawedMind @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1 @billcrowley3rd @Flavio72162205… https://t.co/ruxArNk0o7]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 razones por las que me pueden contar sus secretos. Totalmente cierto. 😎 https://t.co/3UhTe1sIpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great stuff @breckbrew! #MangoMosaic #PaleAle #MangoFetish #CraftBeerDrinker #AfterWorkBeer @ Willis HQ Beer Garden… https://t.co/ptwNqLpqwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LevántateAEntrenarQueElQueTeQuiereGanarYaSeLevantó #FoamRollingStinkyBallCoreWheelsYRuntasticResults lunes 3:30 am… https://t.co/jJtM5w2NpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there an over/under on politics done differently?  #cdnpoli.  #lavscam done differently= mea culpa and two invit… https://t.co/5Eh2FoCB3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kmega4 Put your shield out when you run bro then melee with it. You are like a steamroller.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit's about to go down....Com on you Wiz!!! @KCCauldron @SportingKC #131FearTheReaper #Roaddron https://t.co/zseI5NtZtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Experiencing painful during sex the O-SHOT CAN HELP! For more information go to our website:https://t.co/qyIiHaClUy https://t.co/iV11l5d9H0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachBaileySHS and @LoosemoreScott we need to go find this black and white cat textbook tackle 😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind That's for dam sure the Russian republicans party is trying so hard to cover up for Trump and they mus… https://t.co/E0gTkpEupQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jadastevens420 More beautiful than a Texas sunrise! Wow! 😉😘 https://t.co/Ek87T7jKHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYG_Andrew @jperricelli_ @GMEN23MNB @pmurph790 Yup we used to have ball every morning and then..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joyful are those who obey his laws and search for him with all their hearts. Psalms 119:2 NLT… https://t.co/tzS8ufMPVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫Church [Take Me Back] by Cochren &amp; Co., from #SoundHound https://t.co/nVYUAdFKeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeTrumpEmergency #FAKENationalEmergency #TrumpFakeEmergency @ABCNewsLive @SkyNewsBreak @CBSTopNews @ReutersLive… https://t.co/EJmCVLxFEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate waking up middle of the night tired as hell but can’t go back to sleep.... this literally on happens when I’m off the next day]]></document><document><![CDATA[A heavily edited clip from the far left wing and so many people are eating it up 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted the challenge of @CACoachMiller to post the cover of 7 books I love - no reviews. My day 6 challeng… https://t.co/Vy6RDMohMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UncleGusNyc @telbreezy305 Idk gus rent 1 for a yr or 2 but the edge to me at 6 is more important 2 possibly 3 wins… https://t.co/etumKhNwCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samyliam19 @zenzurzb24 @InvajyC @p_ganzel @bhatanagarntn @OohLaLaLina @67Mandie @gloriajkenyon @bionicanadian… https://t.co/F9Rekpga61]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar so disappointed in your vote to leave a live baby to die!  This makes me sad!!  This is why it’s so h… https://t.co/SA6txYdHdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is not a problem to be solved, but a reality to be experienced @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/xy1qe5cMNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tejano Music Awards Nominee, Ramiro "Spuds" Ponce of Grupo Respeto, out of Corpus Christi, TX, performing for hundr… https://t.co/kQBCY8RdDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slush fund just like the inauguration fund. Ivanka will rent space at trump hotels at 3x regular rate and much of t… https://t.co/AtzsEv18Ji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevcmoore @danjenkinsgd @JayRevell @z_blair @SweetensCove @someguysbackyrd I know...@TheMasters should announce to… https://t.co/AV0OYYwCBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetsBaby3k @Semaj5280 Looking at this from an objective viewpoint you might be on to something. Think about tho, y… https://t.co/mBk6zl3om3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HawleyMO congress has a sgt of arms. You act like you have no way to bring people in. You just havent held anyone… https://t.co/K83vm5jMeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“How we can nurture creativity”, it’s our responsibility via @lisaannefloyd What a powerful message! @WesternU… https://t.co/g1L0VaG62t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@minter @NHLGoalLight @expomick @MapleLeafs @TBLightning @PredPAPaul We have a member of our game crew in the box, on headset]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸📸Savannah Cotton Exchange 📸🇺🇸 . . . #travel #savannah #usa #street #photography #georgia #photooftheday… https://t.co/mBiRYomUMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeilFlochMD So then it might make sense to self-identify as a cat, thereby giving you nine lives and access to nin… https://t.co/y2GwuvobHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever just think about your friends and how proud you are of em? 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr They are a frustrated dog humping air. They will look for other avenues to attack our president. Th… https://t.co/wxIbn4aDVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDavidsonWKTV I’m definitely gonna miss him! One of my favorite rangers of all time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m surprised the Zeke hurdle isn’t on here. Thought that was a top 5 play for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stuck at work all night to watch refrigeration... this is creepy. https://t.co/9EqblWV6ez]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not quite ready for February to end yet! #snoopy #peanuts #goodbyefebruary @ Spring Valley Village, Texas https://t.co/ov8rMvG6IM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alan Michael Alt, 32, is on his way to #Miami Dade County Jail after being held @MiamiBeachPD HQ for questioning. H… https://t.co/QgZUzBGM2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBS I dined It’s also cool to have our own space and private room just for ourselves. We loved the food as well an… https://t.co/UU2SOwJsQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Squills__ Haha yea yea yea bro all us New York fans the same ready to toss you for the next big thing. If Aaron wa… https://t.co/oL3c8HIfXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tallahassee weather will deteriorate quickly in less than an hour. While no tornado warning with this, the storm h… https://t.co/2UNukQRrVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A good tree can’t produce bad fruit, and a bad tree can’t produce good fruit. ... A good person produces good thin… https://t.co/SC28L101Vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great swims by our boys tonight. Saturday is going to be fun! #whynotus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to former Chugiak (Alaska) HS &amp; @NotreDameHounds D Zach Plucinski on his 1st USHL goal last night! @ZPlucinski11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnSears80 I’m arguing with one right now, although it is difficult, also very fun especially when you know you’re right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2-0-1-9....I think fractured my right wrist. But, that won’t stop anything! Tour starts sooooon!… https://t.co/ldwZzGgoF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillieWYMT and I are headed to Lexington?! Who wins? Keep it tuned into us tonight for previews, news, and updates… https://t.co/dGfJfVgEQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @WIMSconsulting with get_repost ・・・ To say it's been a struggle to make it 5 years in business would be an… https://t.co/ag6IVzcrt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davegoldsberry @RonFunches I thought it was for "shit, I dropped the ball again"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NGameTheCube YouTube is broken right now I think I heard about Youtube breaking today or so]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know friends are keepers when they like ur insta posts with both their main acc then their finsta immediately a… https://t.co/ORTypCpYlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GottliebShow @ryancombs19 7 all star games, 7 times all NBA, twice first team, 2 scoring titles. LOL. Doug you sho… https://t.co/bVsiu6PUVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[5:15 1Q: Rhodes 11, UMHB 5  Cru call a timeout after a first few minutes filled with mistakes, trying to re-group @KCENSports @KCENNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just learned that panic comes from the Greek panikos which refers to a half goat half human god who would let out… https://t.co/d3cOvMs5WS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The God I talk to isn’t anywhere close to the God Christianity/Islam/etc. worships. It’s just the universe. Brahman… https://t.co/Rsy3Dy4nYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brothers🐯⚾️ #NewThreads @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/jhgJ3oF0Dc]]></document></documents></author>