<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[i finished one and a half boxes of girl scout cookies within a span of 24 hours sooo.. that’s where i’m at in life]]></document><document><![CDATA[countdown for bea miller’s “nice to meet u” tour in san francisco 0.5.15.19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terapia... en la chamba y con sinusitis a lo que da,  anyway. ..buen día! https://t.co/ke1aQ5iD6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Then your salvation will come like the dawn, and your wounds will quickly heal. Your godliness wi… https://t.co/wuAi5Lb39e]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of you pseudointellectuals who think you know what antinatalism is, spouting of like the mouth breathing know i… https://t.co/id9siibEFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBaxterBean @realDonaldTrump America. Has. Lost. Its. Fricking. Mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[May we continue to inspire and empower those whose lives we touch! #InternationalWomenDay https://t.co/ovRWstGUnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have to use panoramic mode to capture the #StormCenter spread #wakeMEup https://t.co/cyjaUWaQ9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[CJ, you are spot ON!  AOC is not only ignorant, she is clearly immature.  She speaks like a kid in junior high, and… https://t.co/vbYN6XXAdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump You will stop at nothing to get a win and stop what ever Trump does. That’s so sick… https://t.co/jziiJf0z9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyJamiC Come hang out with us again before we move to SF! (Moving mid April probably) 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: U can defend your culture, ethnicity, and teach folk your ethnic history without being xenophobic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a little girl throws water on my daughter on picture day... smh.. trying not to hulk smash a little girl. https://t.co/3kY956s7JV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me estaba acordando cuando Leslie le dijo a su mamá que Jasiel no tomaba porque estaba juntando para su visa y tenía 2 trabajos JAJAJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although the only people I look like on #MexicanDynasties are the maids, this brown Mexican girl relates soo much t… https://t.co/ArJEzUFtfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never get over the fact that I’m literally only 5 feet tall and look like a 12 year old boy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UIScott @JustTheFacts37 @PreetBharara @Mimirocah1 Yes and that’s why we have a Vice President not much better but not electable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Belated #bonkbakes video! Made some challah bread and cinnamon swirl bread this weekend! Back to watching britishba… https://t.co/jSvigIjLcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealLucyLawless @seashepherd You think I would ever be able to go aboard and be a warrior? M.S. girl can dream!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2dagmarDagmar @TelemundoPR @DiaaDiaPR @JAC_Consultores Gracias Dtb !! Vamos adelante !! Fuerza tranquilidad fe amo… https://t.co/BCUNpNo7Y3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You haven’t cried until you watch A star is born and the end scene switches from Lady Gaga singing “i’ll never love… https://t.co/v4NTu3S2Z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broken window shades are in play today. Stabilizing my plastic fire escape.  ▪️ ▪️ ▪️ ▪️ ▪️ #artbynatalya… https://t.co/TQY1VciqaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this review of Me-n-Tito's Mexican Grill on Google Maps #OnGoogleMaps  https://t.co/JAB1NA42bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGComedy I remember a time, when only certain, #types, of "#Gays", were allowed, to #DanceTheNightAway? Sadly,… https://t.co/NL0LPFBk7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Even in your one issue brain you cannot believe this to be true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MIT at LHS teaching teachers new science methods to enhance their teaching @LHSHelpdesk @sahoban @LPS_Tremblay… https://t.co/6wunpNlYPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derryX Unless it’s this specific one, or a $4,000 holographic Louis Vuitton, I’m having none of the fanny pack bus… https://t.co/diTrTBLlNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[But did you even go to a con if you don’t take as many gratuitous selfies as possible ....... @ Portland, Oregon https://t.co/KejGmfnkT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@motherofcakes I am a Taurus and that’s why y’all are going to be so happy for me when I have to go home 🏠  Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my @BRITs special in today’s #SundayMirror - including saucy @mattgoss who talks about joining the  mile… https://t.co/ipcbWAlhLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jollysquatpump @captainmarvel @brielarson I didn’t get this thick by saying no to butter 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day home so far: Ethan’s iPad is blasting stupid hoe through the speaker while we’re frantically trying to fi… https://t.co/LjfYfdCl9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @WinstonLaw If you're not demanding Trump's resignation or starting impeachment proceedings, you're not doing your job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t think we can say this is a lesson that has been learned in the last three years. https://t.co/E9IXrOFgzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennayttt I probably don't know half my snap friends for real because of drinking]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only good thing in my life rn is how comfortable my pillows are 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[birthday in less than 2 weeks.. what am I getting myself?? 🥳 #marchbaby]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS SATURDAY ANYBODY GOT ODDS ON  MAFIA FOR THE WIN?  #ALLWEDOISWIN #SeeYouSaturday tamparollerderby @ SkateworldT… https://t.co/L61k280gwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had so much fun driving over speed bumps in marks car on the way home 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Why do people drag their sick ASS kids out to Walmart  so they can cough and sneeze right in my Fuc… https://t.co/lB8vcQxAXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump and his administration are crazy enough to militarily attack Iran, the only reason you may have doubts about… https://t.co/IgW3zWEpoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course, this would be the week I decide to move from Harlem to Brooklyn. Pray for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like this proves we need to get rid of Wiggins 🤔 @Timberwolves #Timberwolves #WIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey when Bradley sat by lady Gaga on the piano to sing it ripped my heart out through my eyes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChefAlliSosna It is also an incredibly powerful flavor in my @Robitussin. I feel like I’m am chugging straight hon… https://t.co/B02m5lAtGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[i dont really know you personally but ive gone to ur shows and ur such an amazing artist, i bump ur shit all the ti… https://t.co/4py03SF3kc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tweeted this 11 minutes ago and she’s taking another break bc her “calculator is broken”. 😭😭🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemolitionDan @dave_landman13 @MichaelJSams93 @KathyMu87484671 @shearl_d @SkyviewKevin @KamalaHarris I agree.  I w… https://t.co/SbCrZN1zT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warriors night at San Jose Sharks game. Best of both my sports worlds. https://t.co/FHKtnBOGA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myfriendalex015 Too late! I saw that! Well part of it. I saw fan made and...something else XD I won’t say but awesome!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intentionally choose to be joyful! Even hard stuff serves a purpose to be joyful about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love having my grand supreme, @Meggers90 here in Vegas tonight🎊🍾🎊🍾❤️ @ The Cosmopolitan of Las Vegas https://t.co/wDwUm3gwTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[You also can’t be a Christian if you’re a judgmental bitch. Stop worrying about others and get that giant stick out… https://t.co/A6p73Xxp7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #block on #thevoice remains stupid. You’re thwarting the actual singer from who they want to work with for cheap gameplay. Gross.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brad_x78 Every time Kody runs his hand through that rat’s nest, I wonder if his hair is clean. He’s looking more a… https://t.co/dMKZbZiON8]]></document><document><![CDATA[“March Gladness”  We're melodiously marchin' into March with some majestically choice tunes from Reyna Tropical, Jy… https://t.co/CgMO6nyvss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze Males with a few female hormones cannot complete with normal females]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Talk some sense into him Ann....he doesn't know what he's doing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[neighborhood (not really) (it will never be, not so sadly) https://t.co/gsVZra2jJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shariah5 &amp; I danced our asses off on the dance floor while eating chicken wings and fries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt to summer of 2014, back when I first got my @telefunken_mics #m81 🧜🏻‍♀️🤘🏻 Since that day I’ve exclusively sang… https://t.co/xTpibeIOv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuardianOutpost It happens to the best of us. I still like it, but I don’t put as much into it as I once did. What… https://t.co/Z6Y5T4GtT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markluckenbill Not much! And you? 😁😍 will you be my valentine? https://t.co/xeg4v9u9cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiannapxo I miss when we all got hired and would go on our little lunch dates 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnandWrites @rcbregman Why to go speaking truth to power.  Trucker represents Fox News - tiny brains]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC They have no legitimate reason to see @potus tax returns. This is just more hate, resistance and abuse of power]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMillikan @thecjpearson And....  🤔 tell me HOW they swear in Congress folk to adhere to and uphold the constitut… https://t.co/IvflU2FiYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump acted like a sweating, red-faced wild man during his two-hour unhinged rant at CPAC-2019, screaming his innoc… https://t.co/9SYt7PpTWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikedebonis @mattgaetz That is not how that works. If you are trying to provide him cover, you have done a terrible job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before you ask, yes my wedding dress I just bought has quilted flower pockets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lalazzland @tweetmommybop You touch my heart sweet one.  Thank you si much. Blessings🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lootcrate Sushis" Grey Pearl  &amp; Rastafarians' Reggae  Williams were my dogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@robynkonichiwa &amp; @MALUCAMALA left me bald https://t.co/Y4GfjvWJ1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had amazing meeting with writer partner, director and manager. Got strong notes we will use and get them script ASA… https://t.co/E8V5CsCtSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey guys i just masturbated also my skin looks amazing https://t.co/ZpQck2Eys7]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many product bros am I going to have to step tomorrow as they man and product splain marketing to me @ tech conference... 1, 7, 100????!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had all day to write a paper but I waited until now. Yes I choose to do that. But am I still going to complain about it?? Uh heck ya I am]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThrowBack #SleekDaSongtress #Musician #DMVmodel #LifeOfAnArtist #MusicLifeStyle #FashionLifeStyle @ Washington, Di… https://t.co/UdJNIOOAH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love you i love you i love you more than words will ever be able to describe 💛🥰 https://t.co/bnnpnGbWRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant believe my baby is gonna be three this year 😭😍💓 https://t.co/7PlOF29qh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clever words with hollow actions on your part in the past. Be brave and actually come out against the crazy man in… https://t.co/Xjc7VC8vKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelVPratt But hey, #OnePercentWilkinson said he was sorry folks were "miffed" by his comments on renters.… https://t.co/RlOcXU2Wqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carmelsupt @LouRiolo Apparently Principal @LouRiolo doesn’t speak whale!!!! 🤣😂😅 https://t.co/mpfq3LrzP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful hike at Coachella Valley Preserve today 🌸🌼 #wildflowers https://t.co/kq8kM8awxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, I think 2016 music is missed Bc of all the memories associated with it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick #gradstudent tip: download @tide_app! It’s pomodoro meets nature! I love the various sounds, but it also help… https://t.co/9ELiqT3YMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another layer....it changes so much depending on the light.  #abstractart #texturedpainting #seascape… https://t.co/LWbc9wKHLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uptownloner @MissFit56862376 Anything that irritates the BRF she will do for the publicity alone. It's also been p… https://t.co/hBmoIVX5QX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love being part of #BeMightyLittleRock. This campaign will help kids access meals-all across our city. Want to help… https://t.co/4DPgghhltq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful opportunity to connect, learn, and share strategies that support student learning ! @KristenVFisher we ap… https://t.co/MGX5oOOYoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamLemkeRacing Thank you for the hero cards! Good Luck to you in your career! 🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[a customer super SMASHED my hand and told me ice would help after he asked if it broke my fingers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kate_mccrea I think cause he’s kind of a chick himself. Ariana is def the man and I think they’re ok with that 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[And has train 322 been on time once this year?  Every day there are delays from PTC, maybe @metraUPN needs to revie… https://t.co/tBVt6ZqpZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Hermitage, PA? View our latest opening: https://t.co/bvqYgPXWum #CustomerService]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 How is this not threatening a witness? I hope you lose your seat over this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yhall last night I looked by dog in the eyes while petting him and cried I love himmmmmmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodtimes at the #ultimatefootballexperience flag football charity event for the #kurtwarner #firstthingsfirst Fou… https://t.co/1SveXf88Zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bestest Valentine’s message to date #maxélamemoirs bringing the #love @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/Rsk4HkuG4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved #collaborating with @mclainteacher and @techoodie to share steps 6 &amp; 7 of @Seidlitz_Ed’s  7 Steps. #QSSSA… https://t.co/X6c6LgLmY1]]></document></documents></author>