<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Continuing our mock debate on raising the age limit to 21 to purchase tobacco/products containing nicotine! How wou… https://t.co/WZ1tgfWhj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings We so appreciate and admire you and your service to our country Congressman Cummings. In an era with f… https://t.co/HzBGn4APXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AirCanada why do you say switch to airplane mode when it doesn’t matter? AC394 YYC-YOW, young guy next to me kept… https://t.co/MvqQONKjoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@takerfan4Life1 @ThotusBegonus @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump A desire for authoritarianism on both their parts, I thi… https://t.co/4f0HVoILVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brentalfloss Not a contest I ever wanted to win, but thank you I guess lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free idea for @SethMacFarlane or @KeyAndPeele  -behind the scenes at @ChickfilA training -navy seal style boot camp… https://t.co/4jc7rCIDBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miss Miskelley —- “Mrs. Howell”  Wes fave teacher ♥️ @ Magnolia's at The Ritz https://t.co/0FXrDRdbJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow.. wishing this would have popped up on my time line 2 weeks ago 🤦🏽‍♀️ #93 /100]]></document><document><![CDATA[#saturdaystartslikethis #pinkandblue #lovehangingoutwiththem 🐶🐶🐶 It’s getting tough to walk with them on the lake… https://t.co/ffZThLooIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes age pays off. Won big playing Space Invaders. 👾 Date night but always thinking of our kids. #swords… https://t.co/yGKeQT1yMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoyed learning more about critical literacies at the Spring Literacies Conference by Red Mountain Writing Proje… https://t.co/LTJwAFtzzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t had a headache or migraine in over a week and honestly this might be one of my greatest accomplishments to date]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 Wife beating, raping, and pedophilia are requirements for @realDonaldTrump's administration and… https://t.co/kIzUTJYZn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s only crazy until you do it - Nike - Dream Crazier https://t.co/c3Of2hfTMq via @YouTube. #Nike #women #nowiam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OaElem @HarlemWizards look at this shout out in the @gvps ! https://t.co/JPEhWblFVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 🎂 Birthday @Call_Me_AR!   Wishing you much love, peace and happiness in the year ahead.  Hope you had a great… https://t.co/32p1vXDapP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofeyahhh @Highdee95 Bitch we still friends better ler me know too hoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris @CoryBooker well we now know #JussieSmollettHoax WILL BE CHARGED, so.... still a modern day lynching?… https://t.co/qmCm14RYty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CCRJSamson @DouglasConley13 @NumbersUSA Nobody chooses a guest worker over an American worker.  Why would they?  T… https://t.co/fP9rdgryTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DominicusSaxon @AdamCarollaShow @adamcarolla Yep, but they’re all missing a few keys. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it strange that I need to listen to this album before I can watch the visual? #WhenIGetHome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking how I got bailed on all the time yet let me ever bail on someone it’s a problem. Over how shit ain’t ever even.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ferg playing solid defense but offensively boy can’t catch a pass 🤣 he’ll be fine lol no worries]]></document><document><![CDATA[An interesting and authentic discussion about what it’s like to be a young woman in politics. Another home run by… https://t.co/rhxOHBk1Nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I go see Captain Marvel Thursday night by myself?  I think I just might and get some dinner too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks but I can’t use them because of a prior commitment. Please choose someone else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@george_capen Yes. If the worst happens I’m going to hang out in public places day and night to try to find people… https://t.co/YoXs3edvo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bringing some Valentines Love to the staff of Cape Coral Hospital today courtesy of the FUN Committee and Scooter’s… https://t.co/q9wsdSzWi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickHopkins52 @peterbakernyt @JeffersonObama Shame. I sort of miss the days before Twitter when I didn’t find this… https://t.co/j6SrNPKXAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#celticraypublichouse #stuffedcabbage #valentinesday2019 @ The Celtic Ray Public House https://t.co/lEpIhExt6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing red in this paint-by-number country of men colored white  puffed up on thoughts of silver and gold all the w… https://t.co/IpAEOSeEhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win a library of Page Street Publishing Cookbooks https://t.co/lKNJJ36cF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evacuating for a fire alarm in my building, I remember to grab a coat for my dog but not gloves or a hat for myself… https://t.co/6YC2cIjpqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[how did we function as humans before peanut butter m&amp;ms became a thing? just sayin...it’s the best m&amp;m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at all the media coverage when our @POTUS does a wonderful thing to protect USA 🇺🇸 he gets zero but Fake News!… https://t.co/plFUuD9qHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynnePattonHUD @FightForNYCHA @monicamoralestv queensbridge houses they lie my bathroom needs to be fix ceiling, w… https://t.co/YuzKlhqa5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you open up your suitcase and realize that your hair product spilled out all over your clothes. Awesome. Now m… https://t.co/UrAELhfgra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMAGASteve @Lukensmemos I wonder if a lot of them are Illegals? Something to 🤔 about and check into!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathanvswan Just when I think  I can not detest him more A new level of  disgusting]]></document><document><![CDATA[people who hate on thrift shopping are exactly the kind of people i don’t need in my life 🤧🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhatsUpToonboy Dunt bring negativity into a post about my grandpa. I'm looking forward to it I don't care about "let's hope it's good"]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was falling asleep in my screening today but luckily John decided to open up his can of sofa right behind my head… https://t.co/TpbtEcdo12]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has got to be the wildest story.... Imagine being so damn high and stumble upon a 400lb Tiger 😂😂 like wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just bought concealer and a new foundation and I’m pretty excited about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fleissmeister Yea just offering you step in a big pile is drama.  That’s what they are about. Yuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@objectpartners amazing dinner tonight in Paris! #opirules https://t.co/O5zuB5PheF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirandalambert Thank you for posting those legal credentials 4 us !  People, there are scammers EVERYWHERE !  Cong… https://t.co/0eNdjUi9h2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreClark_11 @NewtonRamsBball @GabrielStovall1 @TyreaseBrown12 @VCU_Hoops @_armaniharris @Mike_mathison… https://t.co/7s7uBs5yRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[When life gets tough just keep on moving forward. Even if you don’t know what you’re moving for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m crushing on Meghan’s dad. And he has a nice house as well. All the parents have tastefully decorated houses.… https://t.co/B8aRM1ULmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrShikharMisra Thanks Shikhar!! Hope you've had a good day. https://t.co/9EhNRxkfti]]></document><document><![CDATA[been thinking a lot lately about how we mostly communicate by making sounds with our food hole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking off work for the “There’s No Crying in Baseball” tshirt #OsPromos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AyeYoBreezyy YOGOS was rite on them bad guys even after the bad guy ran threw water, awesome dig. I have 6 dogs n I'd like to train. Them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan Largely due to moral panic that erupted across the nation after Columbine and Jonesboro. Be more thorough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If schools claim to have a “zero tolerance” on bullying, why do the officials dismiss the fact my child is being th… https://t.co/CRYnLWgqOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twosmartbunnies @DolphineM It was actually a Chicago Bears book.  Thank you again for tweeting out mine and my cow… https://t.co/GajeJmqmnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh lort, Kung Fu Hustle is coming to Netflix. 😪💜💜💜 best movie ever made https://t.co/pW9ldp7Ob1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Point Me In The Direction Of Any #Dj You Know That Offers #Promotion For Radio Spins . #Promo #Dj #Spins #Radio… https://t.co/zOX6u9NZ7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stevie Nicks Instagram today brought tears to my eyes I don’t want to talk about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsBlxine @BarryMurphyPT @writtenoff_mufc So then what is the guarantee his idea of players would jive with Ole's?… https://t.co/bwywn3rhQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReliableSources @maggieNYT @brianstelter @CNN Or how does the media separate fact from fiction when covering the m… https://t.co/GodyzqeBQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani @realDonaldTrump Hmm...I count 3, names, of #BadGuys, on our, side, Rudy? Let's see how many, other n… https://t.co/EaIKT7MvBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TibbsLay @Tahines99 I love you laya bear ♥️🐻 (even though you just called me a rat) lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacksonpata @ernie_plumley @Caliicoder3 @POTUS Here’s to your lovely photo, https://t.co/8hawHDIXrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[So all those mothers that are in prison for killing their babies will be let out?? My God this is where we are]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 🤡#ClownInChargeTrump @SpeakerPelosi and @realDonaldTrump the entire world is laughing at Comrade Bozo… https://t.co/q9dPPqDNwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how much fucking attention I’ve been getting because I love messing with people 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a thermacare back patch for my back since it has been killing me for 2 weeks and it barely fit around me 😞😞😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[When SZA said “I moved on for the better, you moved on to whoever” I FELT THAT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bluemorphobutterfly wings closed sucking on the flowers of choice #butterflyexperience #philadelphiaflowershow2019… https://t.co/PSckHQGcgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning and happy #sundayfunday ! - I still don't think any chicken wings are going to be apart of this day..… https://t.co/0UIXR0frNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[My office overlooks Bistro Vendome, one of the most magical views anytime  of day. I see school trips weekly, disco… https://t.co/VhJIGAE8bQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will you be there? Join us at the JW Marriott for snacks and libations 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALSO, shouts out to @ColourPopCo for helping me be maybe the first person to wear metallic lipstick on @Jeopardy 💄💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smile. It changes all the molecules. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/3Eyq0Sbvsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobMurphyEcon @nsarwark @Walmart How are the future employers going to know if the job canidate is allergic to a particular food?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FridayFeeIing  #TruthWithTed.  #morningjoe. #FridayThoughts  #GettingtheDafterVday #PleaseMe… https://t.co/ZfwmYhmcgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@walkerhayes SMH. If they don't know that's a tribute to Alan Jackson....literally 90s COUNTRY....are you even a country music fan? Uffda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealALEXAN @KSEE24 @realDonaldTrump What a lost soul. The hat incites people and thus can be banned without infrin… https://t.co/JmXIrveNSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregShugar The fact that North Korea wanted all sanctions dropped and Trump said that couldn’t be done, Trump prob… https://t.co/oxVeie1pJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[4114 chili cookout was FABULOUS! MODs made their best cold weather dish! #D95funday #Yummy @Lorrainbutler… https://t.co/PLk4FfSeMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you forgot - today is a B day! 4-1-2-8-Lunch-5-6 ❤️#HappyValentinesDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/2GjMIgAJAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a pre-oscars party at work and I am LIT 😂. I honestly drink more here than in my personal time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took out my braid and I’m not feelin my hair rn. Wanna get it done again already]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StopandShop @UFCW1500 @ASpeel1500 so I’m not understanding why my store isn’t giving me hours especially my Sunday… https://t.co/yNZbNIKK7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't forget to "Spring Ahead" this evening.  Daylight Saving's Time begins!!! https://t.co/5pNOQdkxYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CocaColaCo Do you think you can make a sprite that has 25% less sugar don’t put any artificial sweetener in it jus… https://t.co/IKmq01kL16]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Joplin, MO? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/uje6TqSiP2 #HealthWelfare]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ariana honestly proved that you can’t buy happiness by saying “happiness is the same price as red bottoms” because… https://t.co/ywFjRfAKgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBrown_80 And please tell me your girls also loved Wonder Woman. Because I LOVED Wonder Woman!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristinaBosw16 @WynneEverett I would love to help, my brother is an old law prisoner, been in 26 years Ohio parol… https://t.co/zcfQY8Ph4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RueNahcMohr @YouTube I don't know what an fsm is, but I like that thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wonder out loud why the hell anyome would want to live in upstate New York]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiguelTax5 has killed my vibe one too many times so I had to dedicate him this beautiful song 🤗😎 https://t.co/cEuEdwgQJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christian goes to work at 6am and tells me "I woke up too early so I went back to sleep" when I asked him what time… https://t.co/JsMAknIsbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @ZZTop Love ZzTop too!  Saw them in San Antonio with GnR!  Loved both bands,  great concert!  Wanna see again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Women’s retreat/conference was a complete success. This was the highlight of my Saturday❣️ 🇵🇷🇺🇸🇨🇺🔥😎👍🏽🇮🇱🇬🇷🇧🇷🙏🏼 📖… https://t.co/4sm8wuqvB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s 2019, we have an exponentially growing 7 billion people on this godforsaken planet, and people still have the nerve to park like morons]]></document></documents></author>