<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[“Not a Bad Thing!”  Among other not bad songs by me and other songwriters to be performed Sunday, Feb 24, Songwrite… https://t.co/FOxHgSWiST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMcGrew1 @Headsnipe011 I will not. Can’t help people with reading comprehension. Another government failure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it. Sore #muscles. #transform #scottsdale #arizona #jayjasper #desertselleraz… https://t.co/Kn7t1IYWg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teams going back and forth in first half. It's @coastalwbb up 35-32 on @gsu_wbb DJ Williams already with 16. Walnat… https://t.co/bBpOiSnjHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for the position God has placed me. There was a time when I prayed for positioning. Forever working to mai… https://t.co/iL2gsTKLSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this picture of Larry as a little boy with his mother. He was adorable https://t.co/le9nmWkUgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si AMLO rectifica es un triunfo de la “sociedad fifí”... si se equivoca es parte de su necedad, autoritarismo, impr… https://t.co/3vOcAM4lUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billygil @AllysonTurner Well, well, well... look who just won an #Oscar .]]></document><document><![CDATA[i never believed more in a saying “if you love something let it go, if it comes back, it’s yours. if it doesn’t, it never was.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeff_Griffith21 Well and Jordan not getting his gamer in within 4 hours of the end of the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry for all the Five Finger Death Punch shinedown amaranthe halestorm hinder zack brown band Ghost]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yes we r here. The boys got Holtby a pregame puck toss too!!!! https://t.co/9TCIh9xdyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[what party best represents their best interest comprehensively. Just as I respect his right to reach a different de… https://t.co/QqmvMHTwUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marmacostt South San Jose, it happened on and right around the Valley Cristian hill]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I were to choose a favorite DCEU film, it'd have to be #ManOfSteel. It solidified my fanhood of #MichaelShannon… https://t.co/Ianmk0n4IY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drink Water Drink Water Drink Water Drink Water Drink Water Drink Water Drink Water Drink Water Drink Water Drink W… https://t.co/qhi9bsTSNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrscookesclass3 @CressidaCowell Free Write Fridays! Let’s plan a ‘book cafe’ soon where we can share our written s… https://t.co/MullUA6tmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Democrats run on working with the legislators on the other side of the Isle then get voted in only to do the… https://t.co/cvMDr33Ofj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to @LWCGolf men's and women's teams who start the spring season today in Mobile, AL. #goLWC #BlueRaid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steve__Bowens @Ginger_Zee @RobMarciano @danpeckwx @DanManWX @SamWnek The pattern is looking up! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArleneDickinson Good morning Arlene.. Today is my birthday 🎂 so I'm going to spend the day with friends😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfection @robynkonichiwa @TheAnthemDC #honeytour 🍯 https://t.co/mbXmjxF1gW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steelersdepot They can't get rid of this guy fast enough. It's addition by subtraction at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@INTERPOL_TIGC @INTERPOL_HQ @PGR_AIC @INTERPOL_CBT @SATMX @COFEPRIS franab nukerJee]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: If you eat meat, you need to go to a slaughterhouse vigil for pigs in Vernon: To the editor: Thank… https://t.co/5Hlp5k0rid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gnvmom I knew I needed to snap a photo when the sun peaked out after the rains. Only for a brief moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the 2 brothers and this dirty ass should go to jail partners in crime]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday everywhere, there are big decisions being made in relationships with children involved.   Remember, divorc… https://t.co/c4w4ukYeGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eureka_math Great to see so many strategic math ideas from 2nd graders to show their understanding of the math in… https://t.co/I63ddYXn2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustBleedMMA I feel like every time we think someone has no chance they pull it off 😂 anything can happen in mma so we will see]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManuelOrtega3 Juega tú mejor y seguro que eres mejor! Sabroso criticar!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeopardy @RussoHockey All the best to you Alex..we’re all rooting for you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[HIPÓLITO MEJÍA UN DEMÓCRATA DE MANOS FIRME, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/acqUwMT5DN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uno de mis poemas del libro: "Memoria del Silencio" en Hazleton, Pennsylvania https://t.co/4p1s1ylAWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Don, GOP did worse to Obama when he stopped Iran from developing nukes. You killed that, remember? https://t.co/o3mzo90yYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr i would think if you were in prison in ill. and jessie is not charged w/  hate crime.  then you hav… https://t.co/elY7g5n5Wo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only objective of most of those people you mentioned @RosemaryOHara14 is to keep Runcie in Broward. They are no… https://t.co/LBw3VNJOHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#handmade #sweetwhispers #lifestyle #jewelry #https://youtu.be/ssgUnPXJVlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the true leaders on #PresidentsDay https://t.co/Ppy2j7O5iK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 8205 Waters #Moorpark #CA  #realestate https://t.co/CfxlreySJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamaleone14 @realDonaldTrump What more or less amounts to a meme... Coming from Trump. Show me the allocation of f… https://t.co/2t1Xv6yfqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[i know it’s been forever since i’ve tweeted, but Shawn Mendes’ Calvin Klein photoshoot is more than enough to bring me out of hiding. 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kylie and Kate Miller both placed in the 1600m at the Corona Del Sol Aztec Invite! Kylie placed 1st and Kate placed… https://t.co/PKvRh0fcbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dariusspite Bout to be unleashed on this next tour https://t.co/maznw2YR8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You should do calftime. Summer is right around the corner... you don't want to be one of those gym bros who skips leg day...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye this reacl shit for Capricorn ... Cross me once ita fuck you ion know you we not cool suck a dick and die slow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfGWhiz @john_sipher @BillNigh Yes, amplification of message through bots is already alarming. This specific cas… https://t.co/7tzO6DUecR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MidwestFigs @Walmart I don’t think they know what the definition of the word clearance is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turkey burger is so 🔥we came back! #RESET #FUEL @ Sugar Factory Chicago River North https://t.co/s5b6m9aAHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youngbxnji @DomTheGoat5 @NickDIZASTER_ It’s not about Jeff anymore WHERES MATT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump Wish in one hand and shit in the other and see which hand fills up the fastest you bli… https://t.co/K0xYzWiwV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MashiRafael El impostor reacciona ofensiva y altaneramente ante sus propios demonios de culpabilidad. Un tipo sin… https://t.co/spsXIwoDig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrimdorkDesign I don't have a lot so here's my top and only 3 https://t.co/bllKBDtX0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool part of being a coach, your own kids develop relationships and look up to the kids I get the privilege of coac… https://t.co/dg2V5r2YzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[thinking of going to see cap marvel thurs night, just to stick it to the nerdbros]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKyleMorris @PoliticalShort Sock it to 'em Covington. Hit them in the pocketbook &amp; make it hurt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm hiring an executive assistant for my children's unschooling education - all job details here: https://t.co/GVO4ue90o9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ya0guo Should be doable. Might need some custom VBA to update all charts displayed at once. I’d start by building… https://t.co/HRccwkObBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeylaRosa_ You’re so right! I’ll do nothing like most people and hope the situation improves! Thanks for the const… https://t.co/04Xhb342yq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to @VHSJagBaseball this season! It is always a blast coming out to the yard to play against the new gener… https://t.co/piOxBkLjOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_1lucky Such a lot of love for Jaws. From those of a certain vintage? Great film but the shark doesn’t age well, e… https://t.co/7keg0rnHqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ehcampanita @FabioEscote Si me lo dices así mejor no cierro la cuenta...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobAbramowitz @ThatCroatianGuy Schoolyard, Bennett, ft tryon, coop yard, it's easy, my kid, and lots of kids,  jus… https://t.co/8BsFgCL07b]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodtimes with my girl on a shitty day  Ava's haul @amoebamusic  @thebeatles  #letitbe  #abbeyroad @queenwillrock… https://t.co/UlDDiks7Wi]]></document><document><![CDATA[So it’s Valentine’s Day... I’ll be buying chic fil A tomorrow and it’s going to be Aweshume!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NosedaG Your Berlioz was on a par with the great Temirkanov.  TROYENS some day?  Act 4 would be great in concert.… https://t.co/BnXapEOR3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Across the Alley by @CigarCityBeer/@3sonsbrewingco @ Hunahpu’s Day 2019 — https://t.co/2NNNrMlyLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sydneyymariee_ I know I know , it’s just uhhh... https://t.co/WUjIEVqGjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TouchEmAll_X @TheScottCharles Works for me! Those trucks clogging our city with Amazon, UPS and FedEx deliveries could also help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy day doing what I #love to do most at @iconboxingclub. 👊 I appreciated the #surprise visit from #Loki,… https://t.co/dtfQl7yROm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to these amazing 2019 #PaSTEMAbassador’s for making us #STEMstronger in PA! And special shout out to our… https://t.co/zmluX4zoFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCalabrese1 @RossInsana His parents at a Rangers game https://t.co/ouIB0l8fDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC joe biden, soothsayer &amp; mystic, now channeling john kerry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E9onthenest @MaeveReston @emmyruiz @KamalaHarris Says a coward behind anonymity! Show your name &amp; face, bot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just sectionals but if you ever have a chance to go to the Tourney in St. Paul. GO. It’s a perfect hockey e… https://t.co/0wQeFO9vvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[All-Star Weekend was incredible.   Here's to the legends on and off the court, the young talent and the buzzer beat… https://t.co/Q3leqlxrIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Piqué really out there rattling full grown Spanish’s men 😭 I love this game]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Koch Brothers want criminal justice reform but they give campaign money to Ted Cruz and Scott Walker? What’s th… https://t.co/QHwkku7vrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillybeanRRTX @ProudResister Glad to see another Yankee here, can't wait for this state to turn solid blue]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you @gordonhayward you have no idea how much you mean to me right now @ACHLeague #PlayoffPush]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarijuanaPosts Until we struggle with the enemy. The majority always wins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LevineJonathan @CalebJHull She's an Anti-Semitic, America hating scag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonkylesmith @TMobile @overwatchleague @JohnLegere If T-Mobile cared they would give you good service instead of… https://t.co/rv7nmwD3OU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te deseo felices sueños. #sleeptight #felicessueños #fernandoallendeoficial #amazinganimals #humansandanimals https://t.co/ui6Cjm6aLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a whole trash can and my room mate still piles trash on the table and floor. I hate this nigga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 8 of 25 of facts and explanation of misinformation of Bill #AB1713 “Liam’s Law”. Impairment begins way earlier… https://t.co/ojas5bL7FY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Midranges Rock #emactruth #bedynamic #growthesport @ University of West Florida https://t.co/CHLBh3Xb8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is National Cheddar Day #cheddar #nationalcheddarday #food #foodporn #yum #instafood #yummy #amazing… https://t.co/SVsGgybLr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DraftKings I guess they're going to make you stay in Pittsburgh is your idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kenny Williams should have, at least, 3 fouls! #HackandFlop, that’s all he does - he plays perfect D for the @NBA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clairlemon So you’re saying western white women might feel differently about abortion too if they knew the gender beforehand?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same dude I saw smoking on the morning train commute a week ago is now smoking on the late night commute!! And… https://t.co/4DOIfkgXPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never forget the people that make it work! Thank you.   Antonio Humphrey! https://t.co/IV8fkHPLSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShakthiJ I can’t say he’s anywhere near forgiven, but wow! The stuff he’s saying in public about his complicity is pretty compelling stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@As_TomasRoncero @SergioRamos @diarioas Pidan vergüenza que no tienen descarados]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here I am again wondering why I ever bought a Samsung Refrigerator/Freezer. For about the 5th time in less than 3 y… https://t.co/rA6aJIYXzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[NV Pascal Doquet “Horizon” Blanc de Blancs  _ I love small producer that delivers a bang for the buck. Energetic, s… https://t.co/yMcATgPZls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/hM6wwA9uiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen alleges pardon was dangled. Others say his lawyer broached the idea. https://t.co/fRL8Bmb4yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redsteeze I think she, like others, have stupid staff weenies doing tweets.]]></document></documents></author>