<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@elianatmaxim A grieving heart is a heart full of love. I’m still and always sorry for your loss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hollywood icons that the Oscars in memoriam forgot  https://t.co/WlRsBwJIlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradfatherSpeak @UVUmbb @WACsports @UMKCmbb Rooting for the Aggies since my alma mater aka the Aggies in-state rival stunk this season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who cares about the size of the ring? When the Lord calls her home, the ring is staying behind! Status and possessi… https://t.co/uvHEiouKIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Number 1 wedding date ☝🏻💕✨ #winterwedding #congrats #mikeandsara @ Schomberg, Ontario https://t.co/tX93oPEr5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing wrong with therapy. If you have a problem or if you know somebody who has a problem, suggest it. We… https://t.co/OZZURtInKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kaitlyn??? Not procrastinating a huge assignment????? In this economy??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a45cooper The roads are fine. No body wants to be on them today. This is the latest I have ever been.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I know... I’ve lost it 😂 #lovemyteam❤️  @yankees  gmsfield  #springtraining2019  #tampa #yankees @ Tampa, Flori… https://t.co/22Zx7nH6Zw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Double today and a triple last week. 🙌🏽🙌🏽 don’t have time to tweet anymore! Lol #ChairmansClub2019 #ImBack… https://t.co/SfokSAomU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Marketing job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Senior Marketing Sp… https://t.co/jRCrpKHgPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ColorOfTheDay: GOLD It’s windy and warm so far today... #MardiGras underway 😃 . #CarnivalSeason… https://t.co/GJ5nIIIx7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[been sleeping on my own for 2 years now, almost ready for that to change but only if it’s for life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficeOfMike @ChatByCC Obama implanted 70,000 Muslim refugees In Minnesota and now Omar is in Congress! Wake up! W… https://t.co/2QdIbhYT9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parscale Michael Cohen is the biggest liar to the liberals until TODAY when it benefits them.  🤷‍♀️ Now they are b… https://t.co/UHEQfYuOyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @neal_katyal @JenniferAStorm One of trump’s people.he is appointing judges for that reason.we the peopl… https://t.co/WJzUjAwdHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your pups will love the newest update at Townsend Place! 🐕 New Dog Park with a view of the Boca Raton Resort Golf C… https://t.co/dPDBaicFH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen to @Jim_Jordan: "I just find it interesting, sir, that between yourself and your colleagues, that not… https://t.co/ce8dAdyzFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveZambrano @AMLONEWS @LaCalabaza4T @Reforma @aesquinca Mmm, tambien Gali y Andrea las que se sentian dueñas de M… https://t.co/Wd8Rfr3tAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jelly8297 Caelynn is going to be the next Bachelorette and Demi is going to be on Bachelors in Paradise😭🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last few hours of parading my craziness before I have to hang her up.  #paradeyourcrazy #besttherapy #nola… https://t.co/fzK5OiZsz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[running thru da money and she keep calling, she gon have to wait on it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it wasn’t for my 1 friend Jayla I would not be rushing to come to Raleigh all the time. I love ha ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[hate when I’m trying to find someone on sc &amp; I can’t remember their name 🤦🏾‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaribethThomps1 I loved that show. When it ended, I went in Netflix and binge watched it all over again! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evildildos @georgiam00n What!? How can you get denied? You’re so talented! Literally in Awh at your works. 🥰😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[This goes out to all those in crisis or suffering...we must keep out heads up and keep on keeping on  All the love!! https://t.co/fHKeLjgRdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PetraMcCarron2 @VanJones68 he may very well still be a victim. There is more to this story than we all know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @ServeMN for another great blogpost telling the story of the impact and value of @AmeriCorps in meeting n… https://t.co/b4zGezMZGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro I also agree @ananavarro but  I don’t think Trump wrote this. It’s too adult sounding &amp; actually makes sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz dia twitteros @Pukkka @LizzieeZamarron @nagely @bettysanchez811 @ElCharrocker https://t.co/EN80pDGqLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CherylAnnPeter2 I don’t understand why he never received an Emmy for Quantum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the most amazing fried mushrooms today 🤤 I think I’m gonna dream about them tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stylesmunson @SteveStuWill Wow I could watch this forever! Plants are the real ones in charge on this planet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being an entrepreneur requires an entirely different mindset and skill set. Especially if you’ve been an employee.… https://t.co/xwzYQPSoTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeopleOfUK My favorite - waiting for the Mailman! https://t.co/bJqFrax7jF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks like Blair is in Takotna, but I'm not seeing her on the live stream... #uglydogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnrobertsFox @DNC @FoxNews Short sighted really underplays the insanity of the DNC...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoraOch97135339 @FelipeCalderon @lilianasanroma1 @MexLibre_ @tumbaburross Estoy lista.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpaceX #Rockets #Charmeau @Arianespace @blueorigin : competition among commercial rocket launchers is good for ind… https://t.co/vefeqnoWMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si lo crees lo creas!  Tendré una foto con ella, sorry pero si me inspira!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well-written op-ed on an important topic...particularly following the observation of #InternationalWomansDay. Age d… https://t.co/llsyM9kkj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoticiasRCN Miren quien opina 😱😱 el que dejo el pais inundado en coca, lleno de narcotraficantes...  poco o nada d… https://t.co/MSMtbBXqu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Testing..testing” Please turn the mic 🎤 up its ppl in the back that can hear 👂🏾 my goodness this is beyond true 💯… https://t.co/ilzyuNrmGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best friends seriously got me a ticket to see Zomboy tomorrow 😭😭 so thankful for @EllieeMunoz @Nandlow]]></document><document><![CDATA[First skiers are off at the Kawartha Invitationals! #LCSAthletics #lakefieldcollege https://t.co/Q8n0EYl9Rr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissingKids @SCPDHq Praying that new and accurate information concerning Tiffany’s disappearance would surface. Al… https://t.co/mvZNg4ch7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veteran_BP @chrismanack @Cowgirls4Trump @TNTrumpGirl @caskett2014 @goofballgeorge @FemFoxx No doubt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[17 of my friends threw a surprise birthday party for me last night and I hugged all of them. https://t.co/53GUezgVOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinaANDMaya Thank God there okay I had to watch the video and it come out a happy ending for both pup`s that made… https://t.co/In7HOCByba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftwardSwing I was there when the bird landed. 10 ft. away. I was the ADA facilatator that day in Portland for his event.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry this literally all happened because I saw this and was like “ALL?? You really mean ALL?” https://t.co/5dSifcAs6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait I forgot this is what 6pm looks like with #DaylightSavingTime!!! Nooo !! #amnewserstruggle @WBRCnews… https://t.co/kbxzmyD351]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 6: I know this would be more on the math side, but I absolutely loved #themiscalculationsoflightninggirl so I’m… https://t.co/rpEeUncG36]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Heather Overstreet. I am a middle school librarian. This is my 18th year in education. I am a reader, ba… https://t.co/Knm7S9jOjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcDeRosa1 @jwolfeeey I didn’t know how much I needed this thread until I saw it]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s official this summer I will be going to Alabama, Louisiana and Texas 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me trying to be happy with all this negative shit in my life rn. https://t.co/vbtLyi8Ssg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askchoy @velocityconf Good catch! They take a lot of pictures of the front row, if you've ever wanted to be immort… https://t.co/QISAWBIFqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I know for sure: We need a strong woman in the White House in order to truly drain this swamp of men whose ego… https://t.co/8XOsguhto7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another #snow fall in #Vegas. Twice in one week!   #Winter in #February @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/ewrNwtVlaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend wasn’t what I planned but it was so awesome; loved it all💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[After I'm Done Watching  The Good Doctor  That I Missed Last Night ,I'm Going To Bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[And when I thought “Free Will Wade” was chanted 20+ times, @Amie_Just comes in with the concrete 16.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennyjohnson What?  It’s absolutely laughable that Blow*** Booker would be assigning ANY kind of sexual innuendo t… https://t.co/fTIl1EVzXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torilikespizza GoT was the first one, they’re going to do it again soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[The trip is like months ago but the pictures keep coming #lasvegas @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/XnhAsi4i0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[So... I may or may not have @jamescharles social blade on my TV. My dad just walked in and asked why I was up at 1:… https://t.co/3Szj3afIPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 We need a responsible tv station to see the news. There must be a way to create one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just did my makeup lying down. This is a whole new level of exhaustion. My body HURTS. I might die today.😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoHWFanClub I can’t imagine. It is hard watching parents age. He may not drive, but he is still the same man he always has been ❤️🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[trying to go back to normal after yesterday’s mess but oof yesterday really really really fucked up my progress]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow the past 48 hours have been the most unbelievable series of unfortunate events it’s almost funny (i said almost)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats indeed! Here’s to dynamic and powerful advocacy serving as a model union for the next 100 years!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Becoming so domestic I am actually proud #kale #food #foodporn #foodie #foodpicoftheday #foodpic #foodgasm… https://t.co/uvF4ATUyfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mitch McConnell stunned after being forced into allowing vote on new Dem... https://t.co/ATSuXPxzLT via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[The defense asks about Daryl jumping on a moving vehicle. She said she was not there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Block without remorse is my favorite piece of advice to give. #TxBikeSummit]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been watching this for five minutes now this is literally me when I’m cuddling a dog at work and they want not… https://t.co/Ld8OCd5mPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love all your pups, but @lisarinna we need to get your Rocky and my Payton together!!  PayPay is a Rotti/Shepard… https://t.co/M8Z7HEAQ9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGeaster @EdKrassen @nashvillez The other lawyer that cane up with this plan will be expecting a visitor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Wow to think what you could do with that money to change the lives of many....and it will not work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahbsampson @hitRECordJoe That movie was engineered to break us, I will accept no substitutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gypology @neentx I must have pushed the right button somewhere! Lol. Picks made. Thanks for the invite. 👍😊🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[House Dems push ahead with bid to terminate Trump's "National emergency" declaration https://t.co/6eAqjK9mrH via @nbcnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starkville boys will play Southaven on Monday at home at 7 pm. That game was originally scheduled for tomorrow but… https://t.co/oQStyuvZWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump , On behalf of many of the Republicans in SC we feel the Democrats should pay for these investigat… https://t.co/UCJWgB2gap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyways I’m not on any side of this debate... I’m just a local business owner who is feeling conflicted and is wond… https://t.co/eLUbkAs13n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Mr. @matthewmercer, in case no one has told you today, you are a wonderful world builder and story teller and… https://t.co/ViPhVmFyhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#truth #chanel #cocochanel #chanelquotes #original #classic #timeless #iconic #chic #alldayeveryday #lovelovelove @… https://t.co/ZU86WBt9yA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter You're a liar, stop saying that parts of the wall are being built, they are not, not y… https://t.co/HNJFLdXjtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another word for climate change is—-ready? Another word for climate change is SEASONS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[hoje foi dia de ler textos lindos de tirar print e também de ler textos cheios de hipocrisias. equilíbrio sempre importante né 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[But yeah I can't stomache not having my own catalog of lo-fi beats when it's the very music that corrects my chi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are justifications for excluding people who commit a few select offenses for a limited time from #voting. Tho… https://t.co/y8ChmEudkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always thought that Teddi wasn’t the brightest bulb in the chandelier. Now I’m sure. #RHOBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t find asteroids ☄️ anywhere!!! Come on @ChesterCheetah 🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plottmom1 @JeepFlyer @ChasingOz_ @NRA @DLoesch So is that an actual charge? Because if it is I think you need to r… https://t.co/0KHJpwMduU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally, the five love languages made relatable for @jottke2 ... could substitute wings, Canes, etc.  Miss you kid. https://t.co/trj7ZFUa4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dyl_leighfavrot @Miles_walker37 @yagirlpiper @Cyrstan2 @kerstin_nic @504JRill @itsmark32 @bryn_welch I’m leaving t… https://t.co/Pq02WQGG3g]]></document></documents></author>