<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My #pick is @memgrizz @FedExForum  #GrindCity #GoGrizz #Grizz #GrizzNation #GoGrizzGo #GoGrizzlies #Memphis… https://t.co/XVkcCuvknu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @realDonaldTrump How the hell did you get a blue check mark??!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its amazing what you can achieve if you stay consistent. Thank you to all  DJs and Radio for the continued support.… https://t.co/9Rh6qfSaYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cincysoccertalk I mean.. it was awful. But it’s alright. I’m having fun. Maybe get Powell the hell out of there, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP Well VP start the Articles of impeachment on Omar.   And dont stop there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evansville...future HOFer @LarryFitzgerald in the house!  Welcome #11 !!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a puppy but being scheduled doubles is the worst like fuck makes me want to call out every time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to finish a tube of chapstick without losing it. I feel like I’m the first person ever to do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentsMind @nat20selfcrit @theneedledrop obviously you don't even know what the accusers are saying.  They were no… https://t.co/7k8GU9yzVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know if anyone is interested but tomorrow if you want to watch the Oscars, I’m having a watch party In my room  #ArenaAcademy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBigCat @PFTCommenter Abducted in Plain Sight WTF https://t.co/UDRu8Qf9T0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time at @Animemilwaukee  this year — particularly enjoyed the unlocked panel with @VoiceOfVegeta ! Here… https://t.co/MwUtHlwQZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday brax, @BraxtonLawsonn miss you and hope you have the best day 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@voxdotcom Sinking deeper into National Debt at a rate of 1 Trillion a year... Thanks to Trump Tax Cuts... Where is… https://t.co/4LAzKA7aDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: Dr. James Leo Garrett Jr., who faced an acute crisis earlier this week, is improving.   Because of the incr… https://t.co/IqiIeAYsdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryjanesosexy @Follow_mee18 @Virgin_Adults @sjerhera @Real_Whores @Princes_Jade21 @desires_unknown @TheLightPole… https://t.co/gZQvSZ8I9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very talented man in the industry that could paint the moving action of @NASCAR motorsports with a brush creating b… https://t.co/5CAsLuHRxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dr_DylanJackson The best is part...that is the Nebraska’s actual tourism slogan 😂      https://t.co/ZbFrg7Dye3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh hi we trended in the US at a hyper-local event.  #TwitterImprov @HBO @bincerli https://t.co/ErMc1PF3ST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katyaelisehenry @BootyFitspo @r0naldwayne Fuck yeah, that's a nice ass!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love yourself with the confidence of a giant tech company powering into city building.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only the cowardly repubs wouldve gone after their criminal president as frantically as they have AOC! LOL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[EVERY educator needs to read this!  The Opportunity Myth https://t.co/nXbujUrun5  @mwalke0628 @SpringISD… https://t.co/XqKlJFONWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Never tried it but if it would help tolerate democrats, I’m willing to give it a shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TROTWAM @djbiggboss @SBRSportsPicks @nolly562 @SkeeProfit @JayMoneyIsMoney Damn Raptors! Lost 1Q and half! Maybe t… https://t.co/wSaiXr53UA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting hybrid style, dry and thin..rich malt that's a strong roasted approach that falls quickly. - Drinking a… https://t.co/QLqVgy6rrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2heelsandaface @OfficialEGO @BLabelPro @JordynneGrace @thekingnickgage @iam_Lander @W_W_Unicorns @indiewrestling… https://t.co/NjwJWXEMqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The snow plows have been circling our location on the @NYSThruway in Cheektowaga, NY.  Rush hour is a mess due to t… https://t.co/suRCAM9iLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mayor @LondonBreed remembers @JeffAdachi in highly personal terms. “Tomorrow we get back to work on what he cared a… https://t.co/IEYmsTkEn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbcdragon #MrSunshine #ListenToMe #LifeWithTheGuzzos https://t.co/Plf2GvwAXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kentucky winning 17-10 on the glass, have made 10 of 13 free throws (to 3 of 4 for the Gators) but shooting 40.9 pe… https://t.co/t6px1UZbqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TetrisRoyale gets me way too riled up.   SOMEONE COME TAKE MY SWITCH AWAY FROM ME.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyNeistat I feel like red gives more of a True Tone. God Bless you Casey!!! Wish all the best to you and the family!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iandelpire @SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Asg your girlfriend how many of her friends have been assau… https://t.co/8BWOAYihkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[You simply can NOT miss out on Harper by offering too little $$$. Offer the guy 10 years $350 mil, if he decides to… https://t.co/OMHEeikaKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daniel__Nash I hope so. I got up 15 mins ago and am driving into Detroit to watch with other palace fans. And by d… https://t.co/Xyx3Ry04nE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump has only scratched the surface! Look at the evils done by all his favorite autocrats. It can get far, far wor… https://t.co/QZPqdZO5ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank god @HerbDeanMMA is reffing this fight!!! Let them fight! #ufc225]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Muse blowing off a little steam in Oakland last night 🎶💨🎸 @ Oracle Arena https://t.co/8DPAEYk6bh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caroljsroth Then there was this. Now, let me tell you, this little device looks rather innocuous, but I can tell y… https://t.co/mXA7F9pc7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 I guess if you defend your family and kill someone you better just do the three sss.. Shoot, shovel, shut up!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I tell you I’m there for you and always gonna be there for you, I’m being serious, don’t hesitate to ever give… https://t.co/exmuxr5czT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning (@ St. George in Staten Island, NY) https://t.co/p3cIEtMC9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a roommate at my apartment in Austin at Sur512 I’m South Congress. I have a beautiful 2 bed 2 bath high… https://t.co/83Xc6unswe]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of my fellow Democrats...we must seriously scrutinize the reality behind #BernieSanders rhetoric.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenCarman LOL I think it’s in your neighborhood too... on Downing... 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seniors: 8 on a roller coaster. The amount of exhilarating moments will far out way the bumpy ones!   8 seniors  4… https://t.co/rlpM8eRRcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valealazraki gran ponencia en PBC2019, felicidades Valentina! Planeo estar en Roma para Semana Santa con mi esposa… https://t.co/gJGibryVPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come join us and pups for Fido Friday at the Philly #FlowerShow TONIGHT (3/8) 6pm - 9pm: https://t.co/yW0NY1mz9Y https://t.co/2t6rsuWgRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying a Barrel Aged Broadside stout with my baby @annamomma at @alamedaislabdbc https://t.co/1Ikc59RG1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusieQ99345590 @anonymous_sith @EmeraldZoo @Hippie_of_Love @SmoknSara420 @rustman_the @AllVape3 @_jena4n… https://t.co/enzX6TBWHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone bring me to Avery’s Soda so I can get the Don’t Tax Me Ned labels. Fucking hilarious 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Memes #memesdaily #progressive #dank #dankmemesdaily #dankmeme #crossovermedia #tampa #miami #orlando #capecoral… https://t.co/HAP6s79y5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rev_heather @danielhayward Nope! Looks like they haven’t started flying yet. Why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewWHAM Funny cause I watched Bohemian Rhapsody tonight for the first time and they did a hell of a job with that movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great-West inspection serving the Central Valley since 1995 @ Merced, California https://t.co/dcZFk9ZOCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebradfordfile @Dave13593715 80 foot tall is fine ! Listen to Ken Dulin and Vote #Trump2020 SAVE your self, and y… https://t.co/gdPN4wMrMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#trees #clouds☁ #sky #photography #atlantissonphotography @ Glendale, California https://t.co/D4aEXfKrdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m putting an album out before the end of year. Hopefully it does well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @nytimes Not by any help from you, you have done nothing. You took away funding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget that no matter how much life has you felling down and out, there is a person who adores you for who yo… https://t.co/cBiKJ172Mo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Purple #tea with a purpose from @purpose_tea, as founder Chi Nguyen explains at #ExpoWest #retail #grocery… https://t.co/fPTOFCdB3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what, fine let the ISIS bride back in the US.  Once she is her arrest her for treason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gjonesbass thank u for such a fun night ur creativity always amazes me https://t.co/7Nds7hpA1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to my hotel in Indy and the front desk asked me was I competing in the #2019NFLCombine. 😎Looks like this workou… https://t.co/xloLZQ6S3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[This from Independence Day last year, but having just read and thoroughly enjoyed this book, it seems appropriate f… https://t.co/1rjRYZQwzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LootAndDagger @FindThePathChan @StellarArcanum @SoundsofCrowes @glasscannonpod @iamstiver Ha! Now I feel honored.… https://t.co/nPE5rz77ir]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish you where here.......... @lstshow @kickeraudio #postcardfrommyhouse #homeiswhereyouparkit #vanlife #texas… https://t.co/SwYUZf4TlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[That being said I’m back in Chicago and I’m ready to get some shit done! New podcasts, new videos, CONTENT and fun! https://t.co/IZOmF1uxsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 13 and C Community Park in Washington D.C., DC https://t.co/KhVNqqM6Jo https://t.co/e7VHMtULa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if Murray State will get caught looking ahead to Austin Peay Saturday and struggle at Morehead.   /checks… https://t.co/2Q3B1mpEis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hbeedubz @Jeffle @amyklobuchar Yet you support a pussy grabby bigot. Go figure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Six fire trucks have responded. I’ll keep updates coming here. @SpokesmanReview https://t.co/moVAGQP2MV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Street Photo no.1: #Photographer #Photography #PhotographyIsArt #ArtistsOnTwitter #OriginalArtWork https://t.co/WGJdRklnmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’ve put it (commuter tax) on the table as a possibility....” -@DaleyForMayor   #ChicagoTonight #ChiMayor19 #CommuterTax]]></document><document><![CDATA[When black roadtrippers came through Denver in the '40s and '50s, this is where they stayed https://t.co/RL4LMJAykj via @denverite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3WinstonSalem Grab your snorkel and read about the happenings this morning at #Purgatory.  https://t.co/qxruM756Lx https://t.co/gDL818kMKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@overhead440 @cleared37Joseph @JohnLeksander @RodStryker @AMike4761 @bobsacard @bestdad2000 @dmitriperov1… https://t.co/MIjCoVt5xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not that anyone will probably see this, but just want to say while Atlanta fans are gnashing our teeth over here, c… https://t.co/PwjxCLmbtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyond the obvious racism, this statement is just absurd. Right now my state of Tennessee gets no attention in Pres… https://t.co/IfheUyeSID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing LeBron and Wade’s last game in Milwaukee all in the same week is going to be legendary 🙌 even though the Buc… https://t.co/WJ3a4klrp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LunkersTV One day I watched someone pour concrete for an hour. This was after working with concrete for 10 hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the record, the music that the western release of Yakuza 0 got to replace the licensed music wasn't terrible. I… https://t.co/kXejZOpR4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephbaiocchi You’ll never find a more genuine smile than that of someone in the middle of a puppy pile. #FACT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonShoffner @BillGates I originally thought about him, but couldn’t remember if he made the George Forman grille.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Gun violence is our national emergency.   That and the crooks in the White House.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly a year ago, I got my flight ticket back to Manila. I remember how excited I was before. May pa countdown pa… https://t.co/P6V5P1rOFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting closer to that time! Wheelersburg and Berlin Hiland square off in a Division III, Region 11 Final and for a… https://t.co/DbhRvMwQkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s too many “fuck this planet” people living on this planet and not enough “help preserve this planet” people on this planet..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJThr33Trey @2forme2foryou @YoungMikey17 Negative. Warriors bout to 4 peat on the league fanly, it’s a destiny thang]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AzureSupport i am still staring at the ceiling in sadness. i need more time https://t.co/BTGGsoyIZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días amigos y familia espero estén bien y que tengan buen día y buen inicio de fin de semana y pues muchas f… https://t.co/rGYpCSbc3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elisabeth   2 bills introduced today to end cash bail. No one testified in opposition in committee hearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[A New Approach to Branded Content Benefits NFL Players and Partners - @frntofficesport -  https://t.co/HDMIn7gTeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, call out to #triathletes and #cyclists  First race coming up in two months that I’ve had to fly for. I don’t ow… https://t.co/ixh2RFB1JS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my interview with @kanevangate38 on his latest episode of “The BHL Life” and some highlights from the… https://t.co/ThgPRe4vFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McguireScotty Huntsville Alabama??? What does the Huntsville Police have to say about ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙄If a restaurant offers me a $50 coupon and I decide not to eat there, the restaurant doesn’t suddenly have $50 to… https://t.co/BgjRWWxI3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B9lyEquivocal @UnfilteredSE @secupp Yes in reply to la la land. Give childish stupid responses the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ángel Mena y 10 Panzas Verdes más   Torneo de ensueño para el ecuatoriano]]></document></documents></author>