<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I bought it!  Alright! Now we've got something to celebrate! #GreysAnatomy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OvejaElettrica @AlejandroSanz En lo personal  me encanta Maná pero en esta ocasión no los apoyo. Venezuela merece… https://t.co/VL99ZSUyqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetitanpi And the repair bill for the windows will be way less than repairing a scratched up, dented in roof. Thi… https://t.co/yZytr1tzQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make me blind when your eyes close, sink when you get close, tie me to the bed post]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will be closed Feb 19th.. See you all Wednesday at 10am... #cupcakegoodness #sorrywereclosed #itsjustoneday… https://t.co/PyBfpWYYiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_gianpi_ While the original tweet is a bit of a simplified generalization, I totally agree with the sentiment. suu… https://t.co/VFrltpW4ir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Yeah he's the victim...poor baby https://t.co/CwD1hW9K4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baarolinaa Yeah they tell you that since your car is newer but I wouldn’t recommend you wait that long lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better acting than all 74 seasons of empire. You are going to jail, period]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost left the bowling alley with the bowling shoes and left my vans behind 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re crazy for Dr. Seuss!! Happy crazy sock 🧦 day!! @LibraryCCE @CastlemanCreek #thisiscce #ccepride https://t.co/O6Ftolb5XP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a dang good time tonight at the Roadshow. It’s just what my souls needed. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a momma of a previously tied up and forced to fight pibble this new Pixar short killed me. My heart 💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well we know what flavor the newsroom doesn’t care for 🍇 🙄 https://t.co/WhMgZ3Si11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@venezolanoenpie @dcabellor @dcabello MADRID ESTA LLENA DE FAMILIARES DE MILITARES LADRONES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericmartsolf I so would pay if I was going to Nashville.....you have any plans of making it to Bakersfield?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paid in full 🤑 #PaidLabel  Shop online now! Click the link in my bio https://t.co/eHc5l1TKkK . . . . . . .… https://t.co/JrnNuOPgg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give me my bag!  🥴  Almost home... #happyheart #gratefulin2019 @ Reno-Tahoe International Airport https://t.co/8SEoP5FvqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsungMobileUS @SamsungMobileUS how do I teach my predictive text to guess a new word? when I first got the phone… https://t.co/0sWIgS2Y3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TankSchottle Good day, Tank!  I hope you have an amazing Saturday and spread your love to people who need it.  You… https://t.co/VqemTDz9Xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melinda_yesi But also I’m so happy you’re having a good week. Chisme time 🍺(pretend it’s a michelada)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saraoleary @RonCharles Excuse me........ but, how is the library "under attack". ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a good feeling knowing your hard work at your job is finally paying off lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be wanting to call my man after parties and then I realize ion got one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The trip was paid for by Global Citizen, a nonprofit that lobbies for anti-poverty programs around the world, the W… https://t.co/K4i79alX4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaneStanley64 @PainPlayhouse @Chronic_FLKeys @headdock @GCharcz @Deeenst @StaceyF62 @RogueWolf2001 @ClarisseTru… https://t.co/MrJKWgCdwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[While @SherrodBrown is in Columbia on his “Dignity of Work” tour, @CoryBooker says in Simpsonville that he supports… https://t.co/ZErKKC0H5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can’t take the time, or aren’t able to clean the snow and ice off your car you shouldn’t be driving.  Drivin… https://t.co/AWnkRjTG8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iimsoKrispyy I feel like I’m just in a life-long crisis bc I’m only gonna be 23 but I relate  🤷‍♀️🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Not surprising that people who dislike trump think Cohen is doing great and trump supporters think Cohe… https://t.co/EU6wvZH5GG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephencbigelow @BayCitySchools I am getting a kick out of reading what the kids are saying! 😂🤣  So maybe one day… https://t.co/4fhjGkqEGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[...he didn't try babe...he just slowed ya down, imma bless you now...have faith in me...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup, just hanging at the #seafood bar at #wholefoods with a little #charcuterieboard and #wine on the side.… https://t.co/bU0zs91xXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Betrayed by the leaders of the Republican Party,but not by the American people.we will remember that when you come… https://t.co/PSmXNog4wV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have entirely too many shows to watch on Wednesdays #riverdale #grownish #rhonj #rhony #thechallenge33… https://t.co/XpXrsXyglZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anon_decoder That's strange. Kamala listened to music before they were recorded]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shuboogie @GetUpStandUp2 @BernieSanders @ninaturner @RoKhanna Hillary will not run again.  Objective ~ Beat Trump… https://t.co/jXEg1NW0Vo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BitchWithA_W I am a cancer and that's why I was asking you to do the needful thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelaishere It’s crazy how duplicative it is, right click to scroll and everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is going to be a great day because WE GOT OUR PREVIEW TRAILER FROM OUR VIDEOGRAPHER https://t.co/PB0pvn1WRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[New issue out now! #ggx #teacherstrike #emergencyalerts #shooting https://t.co/JHKLpKVCcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My big baby about to graduate in a couple months 😭 Damn how time flies!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tasia_marie1 I blew it out of proportion, yet I’m not the one using profanity or calling someone stupid. Just mayb… https://t.co/cLjlTlNkXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up bright and early with a stomach ache 😫hopefully doesn’t last the whole day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samstein @willsommer Great, now I will know which restaurants to avoid! Thanks for the heads up!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter @KingJames That’s awesome! And Lebron is doing this for the youth now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to hear the world famous @RaymondArroyo on @ACloserLookShow with @sheilareports tune in with this lin… https://t.co/KBzx6j6360]]></document><document><![CDATA[missing someone whose passed away is a whole different type of heartache .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP The GOP are lying pieces of shit. Majority of drugs coming from Mexico come through the ports of entry. Not ha… https://t.co/7p5QpBMi9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris87439298 @AOC @RealJamesWoods @realDonaldTrump @IngrahamAngle ☺️ https://t.co/6t9IzBDKQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[in case anyone is wondering where i am mentally today, my brain just sang “lo mein” to the tune of dolly parton’s “… https://t.co/rWQUIElPSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to to be presenting at US-IALE again this year. But really not excited to AGAIN be in THE LAST SESSION OF THE CONFERENCE. 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still think Bruno Mars would have been an amazing coach this season! #thevoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu Of course it doesn’t happen but he’s talking to conservatives who believe ANYTHING they’re told.]]></document><document><![CDATA[El discurso de @JMVivancoHRW hoy en la. Reunión del grupo de Lima 👇 https://t.co/AazqW5IhHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had spelling errors sorry lol this hurts so much😢glad 2 have it all out tho. Now it's a waiting game. Praying my sp… https://t.co/OdWDLHcPR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Honey Orange Tripel by @newbelgium at @jlbeerssf3623 — https://t.co/pdkd1Jkx34]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Verizon Foundation announces 10 winners of the #5g #Edtech Challenge and awards a total of $1m to bring these cla… https://t.co/Ni0hiiSC27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s do this. #hungerpc19 @ Omni Shoreham Hotel https://t.co/7SRf6tbvMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Music_Connect_ @TheCubicleChick @4everBrandy That was definitely a favorite... but wow, that long ago 😨]]></document><document><![CDATA[how did I get lucky enough to get the FURTHEST clinical location from my house 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luluHru @TakebackUSA2 Where the hell are the Republicans who are supposed to stand up for Americans and the Constitution?]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it possible that I've listened to Seal - Kiss From a Rose every day for   over a week and still don't know t… https://t.co/QW300rGAaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @m_driscoll717’s @KirkwoodCC students for making us feel so welcome. I love having these kinds of conv… https://t.co/cCvyX76Dr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janepohlmann @MLDeLuca5 Yea.  I feel sad for Katie because, I don’t think it’s going to last...🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the story of the American divorcée without alimony, boring I know but, necessary. 20 years of marriage 3 ki… https://t.co/XOtt5hrZy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daasssshhhh @Jay_Kidding I literally just randomly play into the things people say for absolute no reason and just… https://t.co/7XjI9xwo65]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could delegate my expense report to someone to complete... or I could do it in time so I’m not up at 2am..… https://t.co/qRv10IK8EQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBarrowman @scottmale Sigh!! Lol. I will buy you new ones John. No holes and made in Canada!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was that good to begin with and still is!!!! #STEM #STEM #Space #gnosef]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw the Jonas Brothers 11 years ago and my life was never the same after that. https://t.co/UI7tc2gA8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only in the opening plenary but already super jazzed for this year’s #SAHM19 “Psychological Well-Being: Internation… https://t.co/SbzrJpPdx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Trump: Please, for just once please show some class and just shut up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBeschloss @jeanieous The corruption is breathtaking https://t.co/OfGN2njuMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is early for me !! ... up and headed  to teach .. time to rock it 💪💪💥 @ Upper East Side https://t.co/jjP6GM9Myg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJoeKennedy @vooda1 Since Russia put trump in the Oval Office he has ‘assaulted’ nearly everything in our Countr… https://t.co/V9KUW1Mydy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jillicita @NicolleDWallace I don’t think she sleeps at all. Between her family life, reading, researching, watch s… https://t.co/3AbX89Yiuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Is that why you cut funding for WIC? To protect babies? You are a hypocrite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when I was late for class and got a call from @BushidoBoggs asking where I was bc there was an exam that day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like just stop venting to me about shit if you’re gonna catch a attitude when I give my input]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResourcefulMom A9 We are mostly lower carb or keto so frozen meats, frozen veggies, occasionally frozen berries. A… https://t.co/iEHOxVsZzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[how does this even make sense ?? I’m genuinely confused. I didn’t realize “flaunting” a rainbow flag that supports… https://t.co/kwrgamBSXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be a Rotarian with such a great group of people to serve my community!]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the media does backflips over the #JussieSmollett incident likely being a hoax, note that hate crimes were up 18… https://t.co/8GqhpHdwG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loves Got Everything to do with it #SequelsToSongs https://t.co/e3n04nwvvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[You cannot kill someone just because they are an inconvenience to you and your life. #AbortionIsMurder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Note to self: when departing MIA, best not to check the weather in Chicago. 😢🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaySekulow Frightening that butchering a living baby is OK. No. It's FELONY Premeditated Murder on a newborn baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m loving this! ❤️ Article in The Atlantic mag: Intuitive eating gains in popularity https://t.co/hPxKBMracL #IntuitiveEating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ybukele Confiamos en nuestro presidente electo y sabemos que El Salvador será diferente. https://t.co/j4K9wE5gsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning #Charlotte! Loved being on @FOX46News this morning  talking about our partnership with @nbwassoc raisi… https://t.co/e4182hLtMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I NEED #Monday COFFEE 4LIFE @Jojozoey1 @EfiMakri7 #getfit #fitspo #fitness #gym #health #yoga #gymlife #goals… https://t.co/37MWCcpNLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I appreciate Rejoice America Radio for sharing my segment Real Talk For Real People with their listeners! I pray ev… https://t.co/eEF517ItpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Holly_Hanna @everthenomad Would love to help you update this. My life has changed a lot since this interview!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[U all need to stop being rude. If u don't want to be bothered pls turn ur notif off. U can always go back to scan t… https://t.co/PkkZbGi8lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it strange that I feel very protective of Mark Zuckerberg given that my future son-in-law bears a striking resem… https://t.co/qWtXXjvqtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonnieStewart17 @SpeakerPelosi @NRA @realDonaldTrump @VP @seanhannity Oh Nancy we are not stupid. Guns ownership i… https://t.co/UtkpzlXZ9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren How about we try to stop Trump before it’s to late! Or is it already! Get him out first before anything el… https://t.co/Q1zb9AdfV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PorterTWC @BoeingAirplanes Oh well top of the morning to ya buddy! And hey at least an hour is better than none! C… https://t.co/X1godi2dv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[But why so many people and fans outside of the building where he goes to therapy. That was ridiculous smh]]></document></documents></author>