<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Burbie_Anne2012 Exactly. And we haven’t had this much snow in a long time but in Nebraska we get snow you would th… https://t.co/EyUo13Hbbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@binkysdoormat @remhq @m_millsey @BertisDowns4th Every streetlight reveals the picture in reverse]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup looks like ill be inside the rest of parade season. You young niggas be blowing it. Atleast y’all ain’t shootin… https://t.co/JEvBvndR7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThreeDailey There is NOTHING to exfoliate in there. “Callus” What the fuuuuck wit these people https://t.co/sKndAO9qj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @acwahlert to post covers of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews. I’ll challenge s… https://t.co/RIEWVbdxoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trtworld She is a sick thing. Get rid of her now @SpeakerPelosi civil war if you let her in there 200,000.00 petit… https://t.co/tREovZuply]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC - Cisco Women of Impact Event...#cultivate2dominate @cisco_woi  #WOI2019 https://t.co/i2PqK9jj76]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sangabriellunarnewyearfestival @ San Gabriel Mission Playhouse https://t.co/9CcdnAR5XF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career Corner: How Does an International Experience Give You an Edge? https://t.co/rojjmY7U25]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it!  Staying motivated, focused and working on goals. #5amclub #goals #healthy #active #motivation #itsearly https://t.co/EKEiQ36IXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HikindDov @fwbla @SpeakerPelosi @AOC @IlhanMN Nancy Pelosi and the other Democratic Congress people can sit there… https://t.co/FhdM0eO6WU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesHo03148924 @latimes Um yeah, it’s getting super duper hard for trump peeps to find hypocrisies isn’t it??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #YasLizzo on @TyltEnt—Lizzo is an icon in the making https://t.co/ql7NE1z6q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nucgirl75 @nflcommish AMAZING I would like one also but i know i couldn't find one in Spokane Wa.!!! Their is a Te… https://t.co/tzU3QQvbX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Probably, you already ruined it for all businessmen wanting to run. Especially now that voters kno… https://t.co/JKWWQc6sbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE did that! We hit 20k on @WatchMixer I could never thank everyone enough for the continuous love and support. My… https://t.co/Ghkd4kLfGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some bigot just yelled about a Hispanic worker at the gate counter because he skipped a group #. He said group 6 in… https://t.co/kKtUWVdYzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s game day!!!!   #rollcougs #purplereign @ Highmark Stadium https://t.co/3ydDxvlM78]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RabbiMaxNissen @ImTheQ Yes! My recommendation too. Fabulous show on soooooo many levels.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today my favorite show will become a reality “I’ll fly away” #windy 50MPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeidreHenderson Oh, I love that!! And ... great job at the press conference. I watched the live stream. 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐊 the state of #Louisiana has approximately 2 million #gators --- Here's a few of em'! #bayou #swamptour @ New Orle… https://t.co/FsBa0CX1Sv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good fun start to #mardigras in @visitneworleans #Friday night at @sukhothaifood #nola #neworleans #foodie #vegan… https://t.co/iWdrFlfQSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys- “I really do like you!! I’m just not ready for a relationship right now I thought I was but I’m just not.”  S… https://t.co/dhNq67q0fe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Trump-Pence administration's dangerous #GagRule is designed to cut patients off from care at Planned Parenthood… https://t.co/OoZC3UoAQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ciiiscolemons Naaa that’s the greater than side- - crocodile mouth opens to the “greater” side 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OceansOfTime123 He is just as Beautiful on the inside as he is on the outside.❤️😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time with my gal-pals @HilaryGardner and amycervini when duchesstrio headlined the @demierojazz in Edmo… https://t.co/8WswvxO0aE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhhhhh it’s all just sad. I thought we were playing the first games of next season?? 😩#lovemyKings]]></document><document><![CDATA[ಠ_ಠ I'm not sure about a definitive chart that places McDonald's fries anywhere that high]]></document><document><![CDATA[who let the jonas brothers straighten their long hair in 2008? mistakes were made there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selfish little mess, you hated all my friends You always had to get your way 🎶🎶🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real sad truth is these #entitled, #arrogant well-connected #wealthy #men are supporting #HumanTrafficking ever… https://t.co/guneMpHFxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanStern @NewHorizons2015 Instead of counting #Sheep while I sleep - I'm counting rotations of #UltimaThule… https://t.co/OgSDvVPBIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a much needed thread and educational reminder for all of us who care about intersectionality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBrennan You can’t believe the jig is up- huh?  And exposed by a guy you despise. Running to your bolt hole won… https://t.co/axn14OSrcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames come on bro gotta do better i know you tired but we can’t do this rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO you lied racism is real sadly you don’t use your voice for the truth reality is not going to be good… https://t.co/61gT61Zb1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Small open space done ✅ perfectly! Go with the flow of the space. Sofa 🛋 and table aligned with shape of room. Refr… https://t.co/t9f3tVJQVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_UnSilent_ @CNN Kelly Anne doesn't believe in what she says. She is just a cut throat hack who fights for the o… https://t.co/Js9et4f2bO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Babygirl If at this Point You’re Still Keeping Tabs 😂 you Must Be Obsessed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "RN Clinical Nurse I - Behavioral Health Davidson" at Atrium Health by asking for re… https://t.co/QV1ciSKLkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a second mom AND I get to share her 💕 #neat @ Kappa Sigma Alpha https://t.co/iYbMM3lwR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsecureHW @HOLLYJBIRD @weirdlouise @Phigella @picksuppennies @Fuel_Coffee_Fit @FluxingWell @casual_my… https://t.co/DtwVRzDOpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet The Lone US Attorney Leading Trump’s Non-Citizen Voting Crusade https://t.co/A5i7LtBPX8 via @TPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamaubreyblack @RickAngelPorn @toniiolovee I totally agree with you here ! And after we are surprise of the reputa… https://t.co/xVOEMf9ETL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganHickeyCBS2 @cbschicago Aren't there still possible victims missing? Am I crazy....not executing a raid of his… https://t.co/Z7H5lEhChy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want the Best Online Business Card Printing Services? Get in Touch with Four Sisters Printing Today!  Click now… https://t.co/xtZHX7WTsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCoveteur Most people do an oil based cleanser and then a water based. But since the urban skin bar targets even t… https://t.co/9nCJdX4Q9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life has gone from 0-100 in a matter of weeks. Finally optimistic and looking forward to what’s to come 🎉 https://t.co/4GAzrXwgJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: CMPD is responding to a related shooting and bank robbery near the campus of UNC Charlotte. LIVE:… https://t.co/p3DUfyUThd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Haracz @AH_Michael I only eat cottage cheese when I’ve decided I just really hate myself. 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetNorvena @Danielle21A @NGDAverk @darker_dearie @AlliCamAllison @hjhollis93 @SourceRobert @giulia_belvisi… https://t.co/G2a1KRu3a4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my husband pops his gum one dang time....🤬🤬🤬 #allovermynerves #dontmesswithmetoday]]></document><document><![CDATA[When surgery means you won’t be able to use your dominant arm/hand for about 8 weeks, desperate measures must be ta… https://t.co/Jl2HuIfUfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hmmmthere @wikileaks Trillions of tax $$ unaccounted for at the Pentagon, while imperalists /profiteers create war… https://t.co/IQbNjmaoQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it ain’t even 6 o’clock in the morning yet, but I’m bout to wash my hair, blow dry it, and then pack a bag and go home...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanKEberhart So l can see that a despicable man and his money wont be soon parted? So l can see him devour his 50… https://t.co/53u295VZCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[SELL OUT ALERT! 🚨⚠ The #ToolroomInStereo Pool Party, Friday March 29th is about to #SellOut! 🎉 Don't miss one of th… https://t.co/OG9QEApVtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coolinoliver Wow...I get that... and when you let go of past ties you can feel like an alien in the new country...… https://t.co/7QNw2EcBPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[G-Eazy &amp; Halsey - Him &amp; I (Official Music Video) https://t.co/aVXfoPn6fv via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacarthurLeigh I’m for the surf board - that’s my vote ...... I can’t but I’m sure you have mad surfing skills]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you guess my age? How old do I look? #birthdaygirl #makeupartist https://t.co/6ctWb5aXft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZJemptv Was so glad I was able to drop that shit but so mad at my advisor for telling me I needed it and wasting o… https://t.co/uvTB72rV3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Is Abraham Lincoln a racist because he didn't have a black person in his West Wing?” He was racist for holding the… https://t.co/GffCKxRRbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aloooo!!... muy buenas tardes #Martes como va su día mis amores? Yo ando un poco enfermita de la garganta ya fui a… https://t.co/APuVsNSCt2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because other idiots are putting them in front of him. This is a godless president and the best that Alabama can do… https://t.co/TjScVsBXWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elwood_Blues68 The Oscar Meyer Weinermobile is here in Denver. If you hear about it getting hijacked....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanspicer Sean, I am a former Soviet attorney. If you want to win the 2020 election, please read my No. 92- Rippi… https://t.co/HJzvvzeRAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[LAST CALL! Where else can you get this huge bag, containing over 25LBS of carefully prepared food for LESS THAN $10… https://t.co/2Y7JNEB6qf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andibeth012 @Barbi_Twins That is bad real bad that is not right!!🤬🤬It pisses me off to hear they sell this kinda p… https://t.co/l20zD6rqb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think this will not happen. Please for the Love of God wake up Gay community. Democrats only using u to further… https://t.co/KMCnb6R36l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juakar @DrJenGunter @taurusangel26 @MeghanMcCain @secupp I trust in this Country and the Justice System, #Manafort… https://t.co/pV1V9kQ0xY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz Talk about “sad spectacle” 🤪 Sit down &amp; shut up. You are irrelevant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar Jesus, how does she just get better and better as she gets older?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YEROWNSTUPIDIT1 @OLNband @TrevorOLN @MattOLN @WoodyOLN @Timothymolloy Rescheduled! 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleBusch driving the No. 18 Toyota Camry for @JoeGibbsRacing . Busch won the TicketGuardian 500 yesterday, earnin… https://t.co/M2EgPd1hpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ida May Park | Ep. 7 | Ballin' With No Balls https://t.co/tm9LfQQXjw via @YouTube Loving this series!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Illy took some gorgeous photos up on her site for sale. Link in tweet below y'all!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstherThePig @dodo And because of you guys I have a pig , thru seeing you're world..cause like you said..there's n… https://t.co/725mzvqcfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoseKellyPC So stupid that they didn’t tell her and put her family through that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[will someone please bring me graham crackers or vegan chocolate chip cookies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anas is a young man from Tunisia. He was raped, robbed and then arrested simply on charges for being gay. Sign to h… https://t.co/uRw1dCcsxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to be welcomed to such a great family! Looking forward to learning from people@I have admired from afar. 🤛🏻… https://t.co/J6G8h1vHk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zra_research That’s unfortunate.  One persons success in a department is definately something everyone in the depa… https://t.co/ZDnSSezh0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Well that and the fact that he’d date her if she wasn’t his daughter - CREEPY TRAITOR!]]></document><document><![CDATA[American Assoc of Intl Healthcare @AHAAdvocacy Another organization looking for FOREIGN cheap labor. Why not have f… https://t.co/mG0AX21QzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@29rain And u are a sick man posting  videos  of u eating  alone  no one has ur mind just so u no]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrwillw @WarnerBrosCA @isntitromantic Ooo I’m totally going to check this out ! Thank you for sharing Mr. Will!]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY RED FRIDAY Remember Everyone Deployed! @ New Mexico https://t.co/QAi7c6SHv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter Yeah, so how do you "constituents" feel about camelbacks's expensive shopping spree?  So kind and c… https://t.co/nDP45ORMdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @foxandfriends How come you’re not discussing cohens testimony hmmmmm are you there Tomi. Tomi ???  Ah the silence is deafening]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @realDonaldTrump Immature name calling from the left as usual]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of the #pathwaytogreatness vote was watching Chairwoman Paula Lewis vote yes to close approximatel… https://t.co/cXI4ejINYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is EXACTLY how I feel when I get to work @UNCWAthletics #FridayFeeIing #Empowerment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tristamariemcg Well that just means that there’s more for me, so it could still work 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this building in many ways. It doesn’t hold a lot of happiness for me but it holds a LOT. Fear, anxiety, def… https://t.co/nyQT7Udxk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance I lived in Saudi Arabia for 3 years. I’m still baffled how a Jew was allowed into that country. He ev… https://t.co/oW3zraes7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ass hardly even gets any sleep with that extra hour y me la quitaron Alv 🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoodooStomp Love's truck stops have some cool stuff inside. I'm trying to get a skull shot glass from every state.]]></document></documents></author>