<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mpross1 review board member: The Diocesan Review Board created the list of 28 names of priests credibly accused of… https://t.co/i2LuERarHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dune grass at night....last night before heading north @ St. Augustine Beach Southside on Anastasia Island https://t.co/if5sGi0dyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope nobody sees me ugly crying in my car listening to resentment 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a candidate has not released thei taxes, they should not be allowed to participate in the Democratic Presidential debates.  @DNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Umm Khalil will be this child.. he got a history of greatness he’s gonna follow D1 here we come🙌❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE VISITORS... Thanks @OFTadvocate for stopping by as we discussed how we can protect our teachers and make sur… https://t.co/mzMiMJUiDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[she's gotta pee but she's scared of the wind @ Lansing, Illinois https://t.co/zW0DBJdIXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyEngland2016 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Peeperpea29 @ClockworkHamma @karenslinn43 @Iluvinspireu @Jimmysimmonds1 @JackConnie… https://t.co/gZ0ZsNo4T0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HHMU_Banksia @GeorgeW78246413 @mikecoulson48 @CannaFrom @crazyjane125 This is beautiful I would love to try to do… https://t.co/dRoqBwOw9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of you can fuck off. I’m deleting my twitter. None of you deserve to know what I’m doing in life. Fuck y’all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesbondlive Just make it more Casino Royale than Quantum of Solace and it's worth the wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Binge watched Fuller House this weekend and I’m not even mad Bc I keep saying oh mylanta and I like it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halcena13144 Awwwwwww! Beautifully done! Him and Rome are definitely our true warriors, after all the hell they've… https://t.co/vcaKUkrrIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quando eu voltar pro Brasil vou estar comprometido em aprender a tocar a música do Naruto na flauta]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you so much I’ll be home soon don’t forget me https://t.co/zFUxxTTNwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got to spend an hour with my twinny today eating lunch! I miss the easy days when we saw each other all the time @LiNzYMaRiEm ❤️👯‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still don’t have my answer on why in hell would a radio station censor the word FUN in Pearl Jam’s “Jeremy”?!   @CRTCeng ‘s fault?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first year of marriage was ducking HARD. At times Austin and I didn’t think we’d make it. It’s crazy but once th… https://t.co/bpUDP8kdNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know what’s more funny the fact that the boy looked up that or how the dad said it😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @NuevoCascabel !!!! Well done! #itsagreatdaytobeaRattler]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a patient comes in with flu like symptoms and the doctor decides to do a stress test]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amypeck2011 @Elenaandherword @MissJulieBehave @50shadesofdandj @50Shades_JD @truefan50shades @Fiftys_Fitties… https://t.co/TW29eK9pou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to the dog park today. It’s very hard to see puppies that are too young to be there. It’s hard to believe that… https://t.co/FBTT4yCc6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaSuhler @realDonaldTrump @DevinNunes @FoxNews You are supposed to be an educated woman. What is wrong with you… https://t.co/Oion97S9Ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrowofJustice @screamingmd Any particular brand?  I wouldn’t be able to join you because I have a messed up stomac… https://t.co/hRYS2QHuQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orderly and predictable describes Eva Marie’s life, until she accepts the dare of a Brazilian soccer player with wi… https://t.co/Bi3nzdrAdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sxIxc @preslatte fuck that follow me on insta 🤪 https://t.co/L4YTwUs160]]></document><document><![CDATA[I waited patiently for the Lord; he inclined to me and heard my cry. ~ Psalm 40:1 (NSRV)  Find strength and peace t… https://t.co/iT7aHgQ7ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[The absolute greatest collaboration this world has ever seen, debate me!!! https://t.co/hbl664UrOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday #PLN. My wish for you today is that you have a joyous day, make memories and let your light shine br… https://t.co/d0fan1Rpvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sparkle_clark @librErinP @MrRob_Educator @GamecockWBB @dawnstaley @itsBTerrell @rfigueroa20 Issa blanket!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cxTIFF @reachmp @TonyaHurley Taking the picture! Where’s my 📸 credit man?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to speak at the largest student-run conference on Asia in North America by @HarvardHBS.  From Mesopotamia t… https://t.co/gNmFJBo7Z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes @Martina So let's organize a meet between trans men and trans women and see who wins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my coworker friend autumn asked me earlier what kind of soup i would be and i couldn't think of one and then she te… https://t.co/TaOghpM8h2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hempveganlove I was so afraid it was just going to let go and drop down on my head. I’m not scared of insects but… https://t.co/oDCN6Blwrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenKamalaHarris Lynching?  Kamala, WE have a huge on going problem ... WE have no gun control in this country. Kid… https://t.co/Tgzmx4lHD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saraherib Jeez, @saraherib, it’s cold to call me out publicly like that... https://t.co/iRWPtRF3WM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @madelynjune_ ❤️hope you have a good day love ya💕 https://t.co/2VpNUNtcHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FisherJillian, one of the throwers at #WATL wants to throw axes with @GrittyNHL. Will you give the commentary during the match?]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the blog today, sharing a secret weapon I’ve been carrying around in my bag all month long - @5hourenergy Be sur… https://t.co/onCTsfVSh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agamanimukherj1 Oh my George!!! He lived a long life ..you were lucky to have him with you this long...bless you💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThirdEyeBlind Reppin' on the beach. See you this summer. https://t.co/wyrlwcVLnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsfanRISH @GoPackGo2012 @grayeyesdontlie I almost cried when I saw that yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[. #330am #silvabakgzbitch #SilvaBakGz #YungJedi #silvabakgzclothingco #silvabakgzclothing #SilvaBakGzclo… https://t.co/hSpLCujiRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hmarieq14 @realDonaldTrump Those are killings you just can't Stop... Just Life ...Mental illness is #1 reason...… https://t.co/ukQrsiEeOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaceprian @ColeAnasGuinea @trilemaedu Buen trabajo y gracias por la iniciativa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fawfulfan Remember how they demonized Nancy Pelosi every day?  They are in a permanent negative mode now.  Time fo… https://t.co/83wTzdCYDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorldofIsaac @sportsrapport But this placed reportedly only charged $60-$100 plus tips.  Can’t wealthy dudes afford better hookers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@floraalmind aw thank you uganda :,) when these get put up in museums ill mention you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does the waist of every high waisted jeans go straight up and not curve in?! SOME PEOPLE HAVE A SMALL WAIST AND BIG HIPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pro tip: don’t wear makeup to work so no one can tell if you’ve been crying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelauraspeck Same. I was watching old Dylan and Brenda episodes last night. Remember we used to call each other a… https://t.co/VyxVQBPtML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomasj87548619 @davitydave @maison21 @lynnv378 There’s the blame game, too. Must be somebody’s fault I’m _____ (p… https://t.co/aF1bDrzEeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments Never liked the guy or his acting. Always wondered how Maureen O'Hara could have been his friend. Different era, I guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[poucas coisas me entristecem mais do q alguém q mente pra mim mesmo eu tendo dado TODAS as oportunidades pra pessoa ser sincera.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_silverfox1  What do you get when you cross an elephant and a rhino? . . .  El-if-I-no https://t.co/1YLRRbimZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see what comes from this year’s competition! I’m so excited to be a part of the planning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all better get your cake orders to my momma now, she’s almost booked through August😳🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CohenHearing watching Micheal Cohen bring evidence to this hearing that confirmed Trump committed fraud, documents… https://t.co/fuuhF4OuiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The World Wide Web — not the internet — turns 30 years old https://t.co/PblmrS1zKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm voting for #Gracie for #CutestPet at the #iHeartAwards. RT to vote too! https://t.co/HnVutU2ew6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apiecebyguy I feel like we should call the police https://t.co/dexQm22hzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnorCougars So much better for the littles. Better grip = more control = better handwriting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonBeBooling Sleep is for the dead! Jk lol. I sacrifice sleep all the time so I can enjoy myself after spending my… https://t.co/zrH8o2F15d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayer partido en directo!  #unlujo #feliz #GoCougars 🏀🏀🏀 en Emil and Patricia Jones Convocation Center https://t.co/XmWkhsirQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of Building Family-Friendly Jails for Migrants, We Should Just Stop Jailing Them https://t.co/niaxTT0YLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I3urton49 @TwitterMoments @POTUS Not saying it didn’t exist before. But my president said we were gonna have great… https://t.co/cuBPFBSiTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lvl28mage @KevinLougachi @ryanobles @BernieSanders he says he is a socialist.  Medicare  for all,  free everything… https://t.co/Ofz1Bs7MZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ftnwife @charliekirk11 NK had not been itching for a meeting. Kim had never even stepped foot in SK until Trump. H… https://t.co/jcz84kiGXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler I’m pretty sure that I could do a better job ! I think for anyone who is potus has to check their egos… https://t.co/uD4ZEAJMD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're every part of me...I feel you rushing all through me.   https://t.co/HVpOtkJk3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing one of my favorite Starkids in one of my favorite musicals? YES PLEASE! I absolutely loved Ragtime at Pasade… https://t.co/XFPLfnH8FZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueCQ58 @Amy_Siskind You're right about everything you said.  It's just the worst of Americans get all the media attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JwhitlowJ @MeanGreenSB @UAFSLionsBSB Awwe thank you, miss you and your ornery side kick.  I keep following Allie, wishing her the best!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patricia__Braun He is in a better place.  Jesus saved him before his second coming!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope your fridays are fabulous ✨ @ San Diego, California https://t.co/zKI7G7afdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever sadist dreamt up 6 am flights I hate you. Not a morning person but this is some holy hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMDR13 ofc! greensboro is treating me well. keep doing big things Corey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cae nieve negra en Rusia: es tóxica y daña la salud https://t.co/M1m70J9sfd #LoViEnUnoTV vía @UnoNoticias]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to be that girl that wears her boyfriends name around their neck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiewebhair I mean, you’re my soulmate, so I guess we shouldn’t be worried about men, anyways? #KidToMySheryl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adtr @Kevineffinskaff Where can you buy them with this password? It still says I have to wait till March 1st. 😬😬 h… https://t.co/m3PmLVpiDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my sophomore homeroom teacher that I’d no longer be standing for or reciting the Pledge because I found out… https://t.co/9btFwtNzIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t have to like em but daughter like mother, &amp; yall know @KrisJenner stays giving the devil a run gor his $$]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sausalito: House that slid downhill was vacant. Woman in a different home had to be rescued and is now at the hospital. @kt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our superintendent, Dr. Courtney Orzel has been named as a 2019 Women in School Leadership Award finalist. The winn… https://t.co/f77HWi4cLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGlanceOfChance OMG IMAGINE IF WE HAD GOTTEN TO SEE ILLENIUM AT THE HAKKASAN 😭😭😭😭 you better go for me and face ti… https://t.co/uEVLl5EbfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kxthxryne @CedarParkPD Sweet!! Thanks Katharyne!!  These tired eyes couldn't tell since you said Cedar Park PD..]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @emmyrossum It just won’t be the same without you. #GoodbyeFiona #Shameless #heartbroken]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miltshook @sandyburrell8 @POTUS   you won't be running either....so don't count on it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fully believe in speaking things into existence , so if you’re out here being a hating ass bitch 24/7 don’t quest… https://t.co/GBO3Odppy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole362821651 @CNN This seriously happened right after we had passed through! Somebody was definitely watching over us yesterday! 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1stChAKAlate @FredMcNair5 Well... Lane is my fiancé and I’m proud of his particular role and there wasn’t room for… https://t.co/muy64WPKw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[God really did bless me with FAMILY when I came to college. He really DID THAT! So thankful for all the new people… https://t.co/nh55qshdBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ETSharp13 Who do you suppose I should root for in the NFL since it bothers you so much. Only reason I’m a pats fan… https://t.co/PrnWw0ghiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews How about all theY know what's you kissed to get where you are, Many of the people you associate wit… https://t.co/9zRo0KX29Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m redecorating my home office and I can’t decide on a paint color. Bright and happy or dark and brooding ...or so… https://t.co/WobRww4HE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Republican voters should raise hell with their representatives. STOP this tyranny..gop will be over if voters not speak up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just what I needed. Humidity and time soaking in some living beauty @longwoodgardens #savor #wintercures @ Longwood… https://t.co/BB3ZJZxO9x]]></document></documents></author>