<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/skIjkU4OXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @buryloyde  Your new to Twitter.  Here’s the thing, @SoSofieFatale is one of the more consistent voices here.… https://t.co/OZlFFNprHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[MISERABLE drive to work this morning.  Yuck.  Due to the cold rain this  morning...you all have my permission to ca… https://t.co/cQZrtKgsdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leftistdeb @Aprilleahl @thistallawkgirl I think he grew up to be a pediatrician in Miami 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalTimms As Garth Brooks sings “thank God for unanswered prayer..” I was going to be a pro baseball player until i… https://t.co/8DB28WuHn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachFetty84 @jasonjwilde My Packers fans friends are feeling this way too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BWOODKNOWS B #1OF1 @liljon ♻️ #vintagemashups ✂️ #sustainable couture #zope #newwave #madeinnyc #AGASSI #ATL… https://t.co/Gxi1TpDaZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me:  Tall guy walking up stairs two steps at a time: https://t.co/8PEv7i7WCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So fun to see my ladies getting their beautiful mugs!!!   https://t.co/XnVsjDfPLU https://t.co/jr8rbtFVYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breathe @NHLJets breathe ... What a great game ... @MattBarnaby3636 @NHL @SiriusXMNHL game over🇨🇦🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tiny changes can have a big impact. The business world glorifies disruptive ideas but, in reality most progress can… https://t.co/hbw0QfMTkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The first temptation is the temptation to make the kingdom of God solely about social justice.” - @BrianZahnd #UnvarnishedJesus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HHSswim Thanks, Matt. I appreciate it. Mr. Beaven is going to cover the state meet, but I'll make sure I do someth… https://t.co/wb6JHXuLsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aschiavone Jesus, I can’t like all of your tweets without being a psycho. So here’s two. Know  I also like the Cha… https://t.co/bE7Os3AbnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packed house tonight #DJ #karaoke #entertainment #music #crowd #singing #singers #yyj #explorevictoria #victoriabc… https://t.co/g5fRIG2YBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just convinced my body hates me. Whenever I try and sleep at 9-10 I wake up at 1 and can’t go back to sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Chef Kayla's Old Fashioned Brut IPA by @listermann at @roziswinehouse — https://t.co/wMnRmb49MZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@lowellwrestling @Lowellredarrows with an impressive performance across the board, some of the key highlights and… https://t.co/Ej4qmNjGUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBiggestJim It would be neat to see episode 26 end with the back cover of the book (in S1E1's cold opening) closing. Book ends!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanHoch @LuisSeverino94 @ElGarySanchez @MLB That lady change up was absolutely disgusting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pregunta seria:._ ¿Has sentido panico o terror? https://t.co/jUBgTi7gPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police say the car was going 100+ mph and the impact was so hard it flipped a RTA bus in Trotwood. https://t.co/oAv2xFZCUf via @ABC22FOX45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @WandaKA66182301 Donald is an expert on trade(NOT). https://t.co/ikFQYsENRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woodbrothers21 My money is on the 21 for the W today That car has looked strong all week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NituPerez Debe ser que te sirvieron un cocktail puyado, Nitu. La mayoría no es institucional, son obedientes a las… https://t.co/M9EGUlzZ94]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three episodes into #DoomPatrol on DC Universe. Like it a lot more than Teen Titans but my god the CGI in this show… https://t.co/jvvaclrKAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[2020 Southmoore WR @ReeceWr2022 always working to improve his craft, and don’t forget, very high character young ma… https://t.co/VkmkK0qBlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[live in moments  Presidential Press briefing....first one in a month  https://t.co/UkEX8UzieA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being able to recall the population of a random country feels like it could be a trait of a serial killer.   “There… https://t.co/Yrx4FNYe3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilia_suze Not towing party line, she’s toast. She’ll be lucky if she’s Arkansided]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next issue of @SoundandComm IT/AV report will have a piece on that by @CaseMurphy "Data Lake: an AV guys guide… https://t.co/AcyEmiN70e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration Trafficking is a sham. Every year thousands of young Asian women come to the US legally to work in… https://t.co/3zrWVWPlNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting to hear where Antonio Brown is ACTUALLY going. https://t.co/uXc2hhLcB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy “Fat Tuesday” My Peeps!!! 💥🎉 #FatTuesday #MardiGras https://t.co/RFq6wgy8T6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cmrl7 @MsMollyRachael I finished red notice in a day, couldn’t put it down. Great read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Medium is interesting – different levels of "I like this"   https://t.co/RzltITz6ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought I'd say this but thank you @tedlieu for having speaking out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time with the @thisismosaic staff teaching the Enneagram! Thanks renautv @philtaylorxp @ Bethany Center https://t.co/XWDEgg9ic8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharonVonberg Are you serious?  You think Miami will trade a pro bowl CB and starting WR for your backup QB?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends nice story about the pregnant waitress and the $100 tip. Ummmm, question,, does she know who the dad… https://t.co/jqsNoH4x5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Wayne—as American as apple pie, racist, close-minded, white supremacist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine day!  These pics/videos are from 8 years ago! We were young(Raf/Nina) and stupid(just me)! She used… https://t.co/QxhLzFsjK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not just a shooter @russwest44 you're his favorite player. Can we get you guys to meet? @TheEllenShow @jimmyfallon… https://t.co/GbAw4CCnU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertoRavell En eso nos convertimos, unos oportunistas de Mierda, en medio de una situación tan delicada, pues pr… https://t.co/TX75SXCrDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelxMihri @RE_Games Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/yx7hiiCcgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[New England Patriots owner Robert Kraft accused of soliciting sex, police say  https://t.co/bIrD9iGfLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was Nov 8,2018 news. Ruth is healed and working every day. Some asshole putting fake just in news today.😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@just_Fletchy @bigsemaj_lee @JayBilas @GetUpESPN They should also look at the body of work and a player “resting” t… https://t.co/gTvgX8wiEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Idaho State Department of Education for pioneering parent and staff perception surveys state… https://t.co/UeJzWPCqwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveMissionary @theghissilent Seriously, it really helps to be Catholic someplace where you're legitimately in th… https://t.co/L2fR5PAI9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[4A Bi-District hoops end of the 1Q West Oso leads @LaFeriaSchools 16-7. @theroyreport #RGVHoops https://t.co/J0fomuBix8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexJFurtado @iamstillLAMike @MiiNi_mB @basketballtalk What’s your source? All we know if Kyrie said he’d commit a… https://t.co/SlsK9qSdHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[i move into my house tomorrow and that means i get to setup my computer again and im so excited 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrat's are now scared to death with there hair on 🔥 that Trump has beat them and Bitch Slapping them to show th… https://t.co/2WTvtzx1tU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Week 6: MACS was lit. My face is cold because I had to shave my beard. Don’t let me take 2 exams on the same day be… https://t.co/krq0YD2EtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cher - If I Could Turn Back Time (Official Music Video) https://t.co/A5gH2rOiZE via @YouTube Yup. Wouldn’t it be ni… https://t.co/oYUXBwHEI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm live on Twitch - Watch me at https://t.co/UsgQrKwKI5 @TwitchKittens @TwitchSharing @TwitchSupport @TwitchSquads… https://t.co/oyboi4TotO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristanConvery *Happy Saturday* #ChrisMazing! Hope Your Day Rocks!!! And Don't Forget To FLOSS!! haha!😎👍🌈☀️ https://t.co/7yhRSFarPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genuinely surprised City nicked KDB and Sané from Bayern ever talent stripping ways...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blackwater's Erik Prince: Iraq, privatising wars, and Trump | Head to Head https://t.co/CsNDRI54rM —entire Erik Pri… https://t.co/G9tRez5MqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woo ! Calling all fried chicken lovers!! #RaisingCanes is opening up Long Beach (traffic circle) this FRIDAY!! March 1st. Come truuuuu 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theyearofelan Probably the same thing you are with the time you save by typing thanks instead of thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvanDuque Y Uribe pa cuando??? A el también lo queremos tras las rejas 👍🏻😉👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y eso que te llevó ha España, deja que te lleve a Estados Unidos y ahí si te vas a cagar de risa 😂. https://t.co/f3zh7M1mFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRoyalBallet @RoyalOperaHouse ★ @Bravo550 @StarOneUK @NAMELESS @316London @iamjohnoliver @SweetFeet_White https://t.co/fMZF4wTSB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think information, video, social media has made it harder for a lot of white folks, myself included, to self-serv… https://t.co/1vs40Zsv7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denisselebron @BernieSanders @ninaturner @RoKhanna @CarmenYulinCruz @YoBenCohen @cucusahernandez @maver23… https://t.co/2JT7rGkqxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_Erway @AndrewBabyroo31 But these hands are under the ball, they just didn’t get called. What Harden is doing… https://t.co/nHPFP1CWf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is a story common among small, boutique winemakers. Don Stutz had been making wine for personal consumption and… https://t.co/gaDJpyGj0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaylaMickler But i would recommend a nespresso machine that way you can do espresso shots all day 😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erik_jones You probably get tired of seeing my posts but I had to brag about my 1st Craftsman piece. 😃 https://t.co/LC5R7V2NV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFranken thank for being a member of the tribe. Like Carl and Robert reiner. And the movie star on mash as well as his beloved father.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevpluck @theowlinthewood Saipan? Tutuila? Utqiagvik? That guy knows his corners! ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoOneLikeD @RAWFShowtime @WWE I will only get excited if he's in 2k20. Hof just doesn't mean much to me anymore. Glad he's going in though]]></document><document><![CDATA[My prediction for the @lvlightsfc 2019 season. Lights FC reach the playoffs and earn a few victories.   Don't @ me.… https://t.co/BlDI1JVKgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiMartinoBooth Money growth must go vertical.  https://t.co/efLY09pa9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARKneeShoulder Huge graft, lots of collagen. Nearly pain free at 3-5 days. Most have a good SLR by 1 week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Water won’t ever accomplish the end. No matter how much you cry. Flood’s not the answer, people just float.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need a stronger statement here. Not “fix our laws.” We’ve been trying to “fix the laws” since the 80s. I can’t get… https://t.co/P58uBmUrZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦆 These Ducks seem to be involved in a conversation. I wonder what they are talking about in Duck langauge? #ducks… https://t.co/67IZAP4Rhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alisdair_wood This is the dream. Hoping to be able to do this, someday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@43Fellow @crashpalace @MyLittleRascal8 @MyLittleRascal1 @isaacrthorne @skipbolden @12nighthorror @TraCee_tr… https://t.co/sk7ZRQHiAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @MaddowBlog The White House is under increasing pressure to force Acosta from his post, sweet music to my ea… https://t.co/JMeMI059tj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finishing up an amazing show!!  Time to go out - National Margarita Day  #rehoboth #radiorehoboth #imadj… https://t.co/zfR8fcMPHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaReefKnockOut You keep saying “one time” to start off videos, but you’ve said it way more than one time. Just con… https://t.co/HrgxaCjZMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didnt lose all my money friday and got super faded lastnight so this weekend was dope af. Happy birthday to me😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dfaber84 @MontcoPA Probably because this “cow” is a virgin heifer. But still a little on the thin side]]></document><document><![CDATA[Won’t be surprised if philly fans burn half the city down when he slumps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @SouthwestAir no #wifi on this flight to Phoenix for #WLPC. I may know a few people who could help fix it...the… https://t.co/M5dBzqb6Wm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivingS95822941 @PLATOSCAVE007 PepFuck through the isness of W:Hat Here And BRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @maddow Nope. Not one @GOP #Coward will stand up during this #ConstitutionalCrisis. The Rebumblican’ts… https://t.co/mxjNb8kyLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait until people stop copying all of their happy birthday posts to their IG stories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMVivancoHRW It was obvious you would say that, when have you given a shit about Venezuela? or anyone? Your just t… https://t.co/Q4PSeRho30]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your unhappy about your fucking situation fucking change it stop tweeting to the two people on here that reads y… https://t.co/ZQNLX94Mqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[2,000+ VIEWS; GONE 🤬 📣#SHOUTOUT to the  😫#JEALOUS 🤬B!TCH WHO KEEPS REPORTING MY 💩🙃 !!! YOU AND YOUR FAM. ARE TOAST… https://t.co/hL2oa2nQzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realannapaulina Keep her down there, actually throw her in the Rio grande!]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOLUTION. AUCTION. UBER/LYFT discloses complete information about both FOUNDERS and FUTURE BUSINESS PLANS to the ge… https://t.co/Q4gEqEHhd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[John O  teaching today in Louisville, Kentucky at the  Jewish Hospital Kentucky One Health. Joanna Howland, one of… https://t.co/pFkFh9KcVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rxpert86 I feel the same way, push this mention that don't forget the autofill it's a sad reality that the job tit… https://t.co/Me08syEEpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y aun lo están haciendo reprimiendo a la comunidad de Santa Elena de Guairen, en estos momentos.@jguaido… https://t.co/K83OJqduth]]></document></documents></author>