<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Day two of the PIAA Wrestling Championships set to get underway. @69Sports will have AA and AAA Quarterfinals for y… https://t.co/pbL6S1J8iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I a 20 year old women cry for most of the #HowToTrainYourDragon3 ? Yes. Yes I did. I cried with love, sadness,… https://t.co/swVGqAqgmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does Spence think he's the Goliath? People who think Mikey doesn't have a chance don't really know boxing, says SPENCE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please! Someone tell me this isn’t real. The hell with global warming. They are putting absolutely insane people ou… https://t.co/U52abMTLfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday night fun!!!  #dadlife @ New York, New York https://t.co/qmLaYQfCTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Gregg and Mick in Adair Park near West End looking at @USGBC Leed Platinum multi-family development. Upgraded… https://t.co/8NksAvFHkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitaniaMcGrath Or, if you’re a Person if Colour, and it has the same reaction to James Taylor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Elevate my soul. Elevate my mind. Elevate my body.” #deephouse https://t.co/srjfogIOa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WAGSocialCare Thanks JL! It's our neighborhood Walgreens in Buena Park, at the intersection of Sheridan Rd and Irv… https://t.co/7rUjVvT7UC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapanoStina @bubbagump324 @Haven_Resists @2breakthewheel @james_qualls @7brdgesroad @princessfemme @dion_pryor… https://t.co/8GC0WIWC5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[We watched Disney’s “Tangled” yesterday, fun movie, 3 year old loved it...think she might be ready for first Theater experience]]></document><document><![CDATA[Announcing https://t.co/Ryb1M38abX's newest specialization, TensorFlow: From Basics to Mastery! In partnership with… https://t.co/bsRwbLkf0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone want to see my shocked face? The peanut gallery has been talking about this for years #Baltimore]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told Gregory I’m buying a pair of Common Projects as a celebration present to myself and he said no? What kind of logic is this?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @JHveem @SunSentinel What I find ironic is the Democrats were the ones who screwed up our health care to begin with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever happened to Karen and Steve? I hope they never had kids, that would be a horrible combination, can you ima… https://t.co/QIZ6ki3YPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHILLS 🥶!!!!!! (even though I’m rooting for the 🔥 squad) #GameOfThrones #WinterIsHere 🐉👑]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got murder on my mind 😈😈 should i set these niggas up?? https://t.co/hxFX7tj0a3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t say enough how much it means to me that for the first time ever professionally, I have the opportunity, as… https://t.co/PjhxcZHYFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing the Direct at 6am PST is kind of a scumbag move by @NintendoAmerica. Doug Bowser is already committing heinou… https://t.co/YwOPWyeh35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams @AOC @Ilhan @RepRashida @realDonaldTrump @GOP @thehill @TheHillOpinion Stop playing that card Mayb… https://t.co/MUJ11AgzHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillisKing what does BP think the Cuse spread will be with not know about JB or Zion #askbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[An ant on the #MOVE does more than a dozing ox.  #WordOfTheDay  #LaoTzu #Goals #Grind #Gains #GETAFTERIT… https://t.co/RC5idZbJnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ritchiesix @ChetSokolowski @reachjulieroys @HarvestBible1 @SarahMaldaner @kdsherm I don’t understand how being in… https://t.co/wFsOxaVdFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GotNoSperm @HalNiederman @JoeandEvan Those are the FACTs.Mets were far more pathetic or underachieving in my lifetime!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tanksinsanpedro #fortmacarthurmuseum #greatlaairraid #thatsopedro come down this weekend to the end of the 110 fre… https://t.co/PTQF8w5r77]]></document><document><![CDATA[True but call for the same for all discrimination and your boy who slaps women the boom boom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning rise &amp; grind. Give God the glory today &amp; everyday.  Let's get it. . God bless. #lscsports… https://t.co/KjyfwVCGUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC I DONT HATE THE BLACKS WHO SCREWED ME OVER ,,I JUST CANT STAND   TO BE AROUND BLACKS ANYMORE ,PERIOD!! I DONT TRUST THEM ,,PERIOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wshane_pursley5 “...or consecutive expositions though a book or large section.” Paul White  Said it better than I could have...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DefiniteDisney @DrunkAtdisney Well done! Saw you finish, but I didn't realize it was you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Not all of them had to do with women” ~Cohen  So @realDonaldTrump paid hush money to men too! 😮😮😮😮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Norwegian Oscar Weekend  #oscarweekend #venice #thankyou dominikapounce @ 800 Main https://t.co/WFwv1FoUY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA The entire Scalia interpretation of the Second Amendment is nuts. Even if it were right, it would be nuts.… https://t.co/cYEe5rIivk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feelings Fade When People Change 💔| insta: @theleathercactus 📸 • Model: Misela | https://t.co/53Kvl0MxWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[parquelaruinahmo  rockolatelemax  @rvstaidayvuelta  dpaulpacifico chris_carnor  #barber #barbershop #menswear… https://t.co/SQpLPFVsJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HKateE Stop supporting cyber bullies who cause vulnerable teens to kill themselves and I'm outta here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems very on-brand that they wouldn't even specify what kind of beer it is 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg y’all if I am friends with your friends don’t try to finger me outside of their apartments this could be niche… https://t.co/TUmH7f54lF]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT (and I can’t stress this enough) ?!?!?!?!!!?! https://t.co/GLY0WIHVWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Kadri for main practice.  Jake Gardiner is also not present.  #LeafsForever #NHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @scarlette_J_V aprovechen un año más sin clásico.  El otro año ya con @NashvilleSC no vuelven a ganar una liga. https://t.co/0IjAtJPZhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMackBrand I agree with Steven.   Do made-for-TV movies get nominated for Oscars? No, they’re nominated for Emmys.… https://t.co/4GHSbyInuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump time to see if a sitting fake president can be indicted? You are a low life criminal and need to b… https://t.co/j6VQcJvGzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS President Trump sir please release all of the suppressed technology held back from the Amer… https://t.co/XaRQ3AXD2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DPutza @LynxDeplorable @mancode1972 @RexValllachorum IKR. This one doesn't even know what a country is... is dumb… https://t.co/wLZ53XcpVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alathea: really insecure and into rituals for some sense of control, when hurt or rejected by anyone feels it deepl… https://t.co/KyWlFNZMdg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man the @Lakers do not look good right now... @NBAonTNT #LakersNation #PlayoffPush]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Debwrightjones @POTUS 🇺🇸🧞‍♀️🇺🇸we must do all we can, contact your local republican office and volunteer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pooshung WHAT THE FUCK BRO THANK YOU SO MUCH AHHHHHHHHHHHHHH https://t.co/tE0kIARtJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rammys nominations are now live! Go to https://t.co/a4weIbUuXd for more information! #AngeloState https://t.co/YldX9Qmjjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it too much to ask for someone to connect with me and maybe go out and have a good time with? Or am I just that antisocial?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are an asshole for getting on a bus right after smoking 😠 #ttcproblems https://t.co/IotjJoZzhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPXI @WPXIMikeHolden Let all those who protest the wall and the protection it will provide for the southern border… https://t.co/wsbUfAxgEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swore off FB debate after that. As entertaining and enlightening as Kruse’s interventions are, I very seriously d… https://t.co/lsnBQNVoC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inside the Hottest Job Market in Half a Century https://t.co/cXPz8bgNoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Equality Utah’s Troy Williams blasts governor, quits a state task force on youth suicide over changes to conversion… https://t.co/fk25O4LkkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeWhoLovesWords @KAYLEEBURRIS We just went back to 1960. This is why conservatism is not good for humanity. Time t… https://t.co/dBR8sXn8Bn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennajameson I’d take your option over a liberal any day ! https://t.co/79qH63A1gG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s “Afterimages,” which a French listener I never met described as follows: “The eponym song is so ambiant and… https://t.co/6QB3UDGwou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus... no, ask. Dropping hints will get your feelings hurt. I promise you I’ll see the hints and ignore THE ENTIRE fuck out of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packed room at the RISD Teen Equity Summit! I’m so excited to hear some powerful young voices and perspectives!… https://t.co/8DA1j5P23j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahhhhhkim Lmao my boo asked me if Anthony is a koreaboo and I told her at first nah... but then I remembered he re… https://t.co/RiumMubeMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir @Jeremysockwell I’m sure @AmericanAir will compensate you for your time and inconvenience due to a pro… https://t.co/QnHmxmcOGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaycow15 Bro bet we could have written our own ticket most of the time lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#machosalfa en #washingtondc #doctors #surgeons en Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/hJ9XXYVJyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally getting close to having the Resolver/Forwarder refactor done for the trust-dns-server, and of course I’ve a… https://t.co/XtAdrDhNSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Popservations @Carolyn_1228 I don’t think she’s overpricing it as much as I just can’t spare the money for the tic… https://t.co/LpyXdRpzBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you start your week with positive thoughts, your life will start to change in a positive way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[He who dwells in the shelter of the Most High will abide in the shadow of the Almighty. Psalms 91:… https://t.co/dMoEAoTv1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is disgusting is marrying your own brother #ImmigrationFraud #IMPEACHILHANOMAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Geeks in this spell tryna steal my technique note to myself nerds with money it’s probably stolen celebrity probabl… https://t.co/txvQXcBaNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeRut Bruuuuuhhh. That Russian Doll shit is in my face every day and I STILL haven’t watched it 😂😂😂😂 Issa coverup. They have an agenda 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[No experience necessary; just a willingness to spend an evening talking with underserved high school kids who are i… https://t.co/DmVQmXK4yw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beansmankato Never used chapstick more than once. Will buy it for a specific reason and use it once, lose it, and… https://t.co/DzHIYXza7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was an NDP policy last election. It was economically illiterate then, and it’s economically illiterate still.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 No way, shape or form should this person be allowed into the US, given her history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AveDeFuego29 I’m positive that this could finally happen this week but I also thought the same thing last week 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonMurray @denverpost Fancy seeing this dude again.  (Congrats on the new gig @JustinWingerter, I’ll see ya tomorrow)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacoAffcionado @Addison_Russell His hairline is as strong as his ability to read pre-written statements and make them sound believable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe.  #Padres #HotTalentLava #keepthefaith  #BrycetoSD #PadresTwitter https://t.co/xIkYumtGzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grave_Girls Outside of the acting, everything else is meh! In my opinion, I would wait until it ends up on Netflix or something]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppSnkrs handing me alllllll L's. It's a tradition at this point. 😥 https://t.co/QlCYkaB8bC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BakerEDMLab speaks on the importance of measuring long term impact through #experiments and #openscience in his se… https://t.co/jLQ9a1NHcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another terrible experience with @SpiritAirlines. Flight canceled outright due to 1” of snow. Next flight available… https://t.co/9DKKSTHBkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialLivePD @PascoSheriff @LivePDNation @LivePdFans @Sean_C_Larkin @TomMorrisJr1 @danabrams @PatrolPd… https://t.co/52eenI0xUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[A tradition unlike any other... Employees quietly whining about the food options at the company-sponsored lunch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch Excuse me but minimum wage jobs were never meant to be the primary income. Never.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftistWriter @NippySweetyLass @El_Tapatio96 @WASBAPPIN @willmenaker @AOC And yet here you are, posting pro-Assad… https://t.co/0AMIsEJYOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've had it with all these snow storms lol I'm at a point where I actually want to go to school cuz I'm so bored… https://t.co/W7gd3mhJJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@all_eyezonmi @FREETOMMY8 @joanne48640679 @Lo_Gannicus @BertJ4411 @CoachforPOTUS @dgvreiman @Hybrid1979… https://t.co/J5ePRgmc7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[But on the bright side, last night was the smoothest belt move I’ve ever been apart of 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once the @Buccaneers are on the clock, Reshad Jones, pick #13 and pick #78 for the Bucs #5 pick, which becomes Dwayne Haskins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to understand the complexity. And obviously I don’t support human rights abuse anywhere.   I vehemently… https://t.co/KJQNBr9PWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AskPenny since you took over at memphis, many of your players have endured a strained labia minora. how will you a… https://t.co/ohxwaHuIrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @Mike_Stud for the chug bud! Changing the game https://t.co/yDeKIBkq56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleWalker101 @SportsLine Who played Alex Lin? Why would you do that!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is bigger in Texas! *including the track  @IndyCar Spring Training: Day 1: ✅ Day 2: Let’s go!  #INDYCAR… https://t.co/vkvjz3KFhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandybastin the only thing disappointing is having to wait for season 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently there is no longer a play area at @DFWAirport? Lame. Do the people who run this place never #travelwithkids?]]></document></documents></author>