<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Celebrating #InternationalWomensDay and Diversity: Accelerating Representation &amp; Inclusion on Boards… https://t.co/cyUgvGznzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greenbaysucks13  these guys say you are a closet packer fan #GoPackGo  #cheeseheads https://t.co/BE3DB6Roel]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇩🇪 Amazing German Food &amp; Beer at @CafeRustica 😋 #sehrlecker https://t.co/WZeQkfTZxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LKLiterary Well - I had a sonicare a long time ago and it was TOO INTENSE for me. Maybe going manual to quip will… https://t.co/dCbeOC5ZYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deposit your treasures from what u focus upon- in2 My “goodness account”. Your wealth will increase from good depos… https://t.co/8KerTAMpGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’ve ever wondered what we do during a Color management workshop, here is what last week looked like for us in… https://t.co/pfbFstWmzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lorenzo_Murillo agree -- what life skill could be more important!?! Nutrition, Cooking and Finances should be a priority!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍊🌼What goes best with your new patio set? A PERGOLA!!!  Nina setting up customers for their dream patio!! 🍊🍊this is… https://t.co/oWFNmIf0WG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Harbor Freight Tools team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/tZno0GnQ0V #Sales #Waldorf, MD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jake Brown started the Cowtown Weekend Half Marathon P/B Sprint! https://t.co/FSLxveJYCJ #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhatRU4USA @JustWonderinwhy @thehill Really?  Do you really believe the IRS wouldn't notice Trump and his mass for… https://t.co/p5pcGlD7vQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[short Layered💇 for Andreaツ • • • • #layeredhaircut #haircut #shorthair #shorthairstyles #shortlayers #hairs… https://t.co/otbaXhTz46]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace This just in... for the first time in DECADES “background checks” before purchasing a gun has been… https://t.co/SNbWMQSqca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan Maduro is a socialist, but he's not a Democratic socialist. If u truly value all human rights u should not s… https://t.co/A1PZN3Hjdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle Did that really happen or are you gaslighting yet again?🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also had a dream my boss told me it was time for me to go home and I couldn’t handle this job anymore when she li… https://t.co/RNTWAbUNCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you’re telling me yesterday was #NationalPetLovers Day and tomorrow is #NationalMargaritaDay? What a time to be alive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When giving feedback....What you show is more important than what you say. -Joe Hirsch #r10learns #feedbackfix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please retweet! So many people have viewed it but only a few have retweeted it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[see now i gotta rewatch it and put myself through the hurt again. thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That fucking NYC public school pizza on the French bread was absolutely disgusting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blkumathurman @Alapanic My train guys are usually homeless or old 😐 https://t.co/oQzi6cM5Z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markreiland @TannerRohweder I will definitely be looking forward to a duet from you two]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anitasamarth @Google @sarahkliff @Farzad_MD @chrissyfarr @boltyboy There are better solutions out there check out… https://t.co/bs0RdBdnip]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TWBDimash #WorldsBest ....Dimash will always be the best...no matter whom you choose CBS https://t.co/KIWXS47323]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention #MOLeg: Vote NO on #MoHB581! Don't erase my voice! As an educator, I oppose charter school expansion with… https://t.co/jz9qCNqIaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I #WouldntWantToLose my sense of humor. It’s gotten me through some of the darkest times in my life. 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisMul @kystokes The hail just made it to San Diego. @KPBSnews pausing on deadline to marvel. https://t.co/q1OPvZAE4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMHSRams Girls Soccer lost in penalty kicks in the final four of the State Championship. We are proud of their season!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lil line dancing today to wish our coworker well in Texas ... God bless from 6687 to you and your family Brett https://t.co/wtWnXAUuXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@90sWWE I love how much Hart Foundation stuff you put on this twitter account and keep the memory of the four who passed in our minds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YuleTimes @LittleSproutLyf Interesting article by JAMA pediatrics   https://t.co/JQxxp80oDk  “Child care experienc… https://t.co/Jhfm6sGxNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched Crazy Rich Asians for the first time and damn, how did it not win all of the awards?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living alone is fun. Until you get sick, and have to do everything yourself. #sendhelp]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG....this skipping up the court is killing me! https://t.co/FaL7WttDe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Joel Barnes' father says his son wanted to be a firefighter since he was 10, and that he understood the ris… https://t.co/euvRo62d6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChocoHarveyMilk I care. And I feel the same every once in a while. Exhausting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keepingupwty123 No bc why tf are these comments like this like I just don’t get it 🙇🏼‍♀️🙇🏼‍♀️💆🏼‍♀️💆🏼‍♀️💆🏼‍♀️💆🏼‍♀️💆🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our justice system was built on slavery and chain gangs. Not much has changed since then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayKnightCBS @RealJamesWoods Yes and many more may die to fight the likes of these idiots]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️The good old days...#nirvana #smellsliketeenspirit #kurtcobain #rip#2cellos #grunge#thosewerethedays got a bit ex… https://t.co/AxkLC5Dx4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathalieR71 @leemaxfield29 @KristinGlaeske @march4teachers @mexusmx @JonBlackAdmin @RandallSampson @comics_teacher… https://t.co/ujhGZtxHR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[What... I was just doing a little taste testing Bobby... #boyscouttroop117 #PancakeBreakfast2019 @ St. John the Bap… https://t.co/gVwF5Q2k0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you answered yes to the last question, you’re already killing Monday. 😎#MondayMotivation https://t.co/26PBnW1B9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealelp Yes! Wht tf do I look like being confined by commas and caps lock?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @LucySullivan888 She is very fragile... Prayers for her ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTesque @fessland @Braves @Nationals If you two need a celebratory night, I can hang with Calvin...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDIYYY I tune in every morning to see who is upset with POTUS... I seldom fail ...there is always someone who is f… https://t.co/X7N6Ge7UXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llegando y paseando! ☀️🌊🍹 en Topolobampo, Sinaloa https://t.co/XU8qPJXrba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@504DubbBeats Morning! Hope y'all are having a good Mardi Gras #HappyHunting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepBarbaraLee He had two robbery convictions and one cocaine bust.  Do you consider him a choir boy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TorontoStar Menon. does he care that 300 Americans per week die from opioids that are smuggled through porous bord… https://t.co/zedSLXVAvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[No time for losers 'Cause We are the Champions  4.2💛  #NCAnationals @expresscheer  #redemptionSzn 💍 https://t.co/XFIeFSxmtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine @Melissa82225794 Why am I not surprised? https://t.co/9IvhWqMqOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC Biden is senile.  Period.  He needs to be sitting on the front porch with his house slippers on, sipp… https://t.co/MQTMyhuoCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hankschulman I bemoan losing Hundley as well, if it matters to anyone. 😩 #bigfan #SFGiantsfanforlife #couchcoach]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shundawg @singindiva80 @mamaque4 @AlexiaGIL7 @sayasajo @thedetectivee @Lovemypirates @Frodocatsmom @haeewee… https://t.co/BXcxweM5K3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying some deliciousness #FLG  #hopjack #partypeople https://t.co/GB5RlnGL8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Program Mgr" at ResCare Residential Services by asking for referrals. It's a great… https://t.co/aCbmpfTcs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urbandecay @maccosmetics @revlon @narsissist @ Kingston, Ontario https://t.co/v1h8JD8ZQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulinebeatricx Hahahahaha osige penge laman baka magkabuhay naman yung buhay ko nudaw 🤦🏻‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Night #wine #wines #winesofinstagram #wineoclock🍷 #wineoclock #wineonwineonwine #wineoftheday #instawine… https://t.co/VHDACO4HQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you say you love me KNOW IIII LOVE YOU MORE When you say you need me know I need you more 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you go on https://t.co/1T1ODFpRug and all you find out is that you are in fact very, very white 🙍🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[BigHit acting surprised when army come for them because we only have 10 days to save money https://t.co/ocy3j8vdiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrumpCrimeFamily #TraitorTrump #Trump #Dossier #FBIR #FollowBackResistance #MuellerIsComingForYou #MuellerTime… https://t.co/7EG7KJRAru]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burning essential oils right before a showing is an eco-friendly way to scent your home. Remember, however, that yo… https://t.co/pKRvahN75m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @DonaldJTrumpJr I know people can’t help what they look like but Don Junior gives me the creeps!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grayson has two great loves in the world: desserts and the Disney transportation system. Do when I found out that t… https://t.co/2xcNLeVe4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steelers Happy, happy Birthday Big Ben!  Hope it has been truly blessed!  #SteelerNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[As i got emotional watching the main event of fastlane tonight I kept thinking to myself that yeah it may be the la… https://t.co/EYsv8rwMVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so excited to be part of @GardenStateFilm and presenting a block on Saturday! @EMACCNJ connections create fun… https://t.co/B5sZUg0Lhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry not sorry for having my tweets be about the @jonasbrothers today. my 12 year old self is freaking out today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KajEriksen @KikiAdine @DevinNunes Thank you. Thank you. Laughing so loud, I woke up the 10 year old. https://t.co/OOV3WznfPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The American People declined to take jobs this month to put pressure on Pennsylvania employers to pay Pennsylvanians more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derek_mafs Being a proponent of anti-bullying is a bit contradicting when we have Trump as our president. Also- th… https://t.co/6ka1Ole0qZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntonioArellano @D_ere_k @realDonaldTrump Nobody cares . He has proved himself. Your narrative is dying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i mean i know i’m the shit and all but people stay talking about me for NO REASON when in reality i barely even leave my own house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like this is our true trajectory, @LissaT1818 https://t.co/Erkd4Dg8b8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Intolwoods @Proud__Bastard @SunnyJWriter Wow. I’m sorry you had to even try to watch. I know it’s important to ‘kn… https://t.co/VAAVESKIIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[In earlier news, I attended the Red Rock Historical Association Event (RRHA- Gladewater, Texas) in Longview, Texas!… https://t.co/KmIuT4rxeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Math Coach's Corner: What Great Teachers Do Differently https://t.co/qjvfkRXtXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Agent_Moe And btw, I find more specialized stories fascinating, too. I just think common themes reach a wider audi… https://t.co/HjZHQ7K60r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView show us that you are really concern about our rights as women, we want to hear from an OBG a real expert i… https://t.co/OAlzYcGRLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨Pedestrian Crash🚨 Lanes are closed on I-81 SB between US-30 and PA-316.   We are headed to the scene now,  stay wi… https://t.co/y4Cr32HUTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mackenzydg @sashasytnikk @nikeboy_tommy Sorry if it seemed condescending but I’m not being classist for just being… https://t.co/hpVaKYLUZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarah_SKG_1983 @PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump ONE MORE TIME!  NO COLLUSION.]]></document><document><![CDATA[like no one knows how freaking happy i am that why don’t we is actually coming to albany this time!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulGerke  I started the #flowerchallenge for v-day. What flower am I to you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine seeing this dude at the Gym I’d be mad as hell dawg you won go fight with the avengers damn 🤣😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[they should have fleshed out the relationship between the Doctor and his daughter, giving it more than just one epi… https://t.co/YRKRBDO632]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moserslaw @MSNBC It isn't just that. Many of middle America's tax deductions were eliminated or severely reduced..… https://t.co/Quf13y6wSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the killer whale totem that was carved to raise awarness for the whales that have been threatened. #jou3109 https://t.co/vjjEBzPcHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#theporchgang is trying a new technique of holding the door hostage in exchange for treats to pay the toll 😉 @ Unit… https://t.co/he7yLQM3iv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexbozikovic @synoec There is an important hidden point in what @synoec says in that many large and monumental bu… https://t.co/gMINyWhVsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmicaAli @abigailkjohnso5 I talk about her often. No one seems interested that we have a Veteran imprisoned for ne… https://t.co/1PJQl4RBhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Good. The current measles outbreak was completely preventable, if children had been vaccinated.… https://t.co/opkTJNt9LN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddyorBiff @Statistar30 @ChelseaClinton @IlhanMN Oh that lobby that funnels money to both republicans and democrats!! Gtfo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_thom2 3 security guards AND Jerry AND Doug for half the lease lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Top 2020 Dem Caught On A Hot Mic – This Is Sickening https://t.co/R0NjSindeZ]]></document></documents></author>