<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jannellartiles4 @a_lyssam_arie my baby boy Benji 🥰 https://t.co/r2fN6WL8Zf]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASH WEDNESDAY documenting in my portlandleather notebook. #idocument #carlascreativelife #photojournal… https://t.co/WJzhftRjEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericbolling @AOC SNL-Weekend Update: Girl You Wish You Hadn't Started a Conversation With (Check out AOC!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready to spoil tf out of someone n I’m not just talking ab gifts and shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Even your dad is smart enough to keep his pie hole shut while Coen testifies. You might want to do the same]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have a shorty that you don’t show love, oh yes son I’m talkin to you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our dog clearly has to go to the bathroom, but she is refusing to walk in the rain and what's left of the soggy sno… https://t.co/GrGH5R7TmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein It would be great if they worked together to take the filthy pig down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[KIND HEART ♥️ FIERCE MIND ♥️ BRAVE SPIRIT♥️  . . . #bossbabe #buyingahouse #southcarolinarealestate #screaltor… https://t.co/zc44rv5FKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grimmy_Coyote Purple is because of how our brain perceives light waves. Mostly to find other birds to fuck. Sam an… https://t.co/JOPmWbVhIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@what_eats_owls I really need to know why Sensual is capitalized it is CREEPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earth’s crammed with Heaven,  And every common bush afire with God, But only he who sees takes off his shoes- The r… https://t.co/FQpXhor1Vv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Hey Gym - maybe you can tell us why are stood around and did nothing while young men under your watch w… https://t.co/0b8gbVQ8c9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tartecosmetics Simply gorgeous! May I ask how I can review products from your brand?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidBflower Ah!  Just finished eating breakfast David wish you could of joined me! I had some good original oatme… https://t.co/aqbtiC5zcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 ex-NYPD detectives admitted to having sex with a teen after arresting her. They won't face rape charges.  https://t.co/EkQMmYKwKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleBogey971 Lmao. Alright , alright, et’s not get carried away Bogenshits…]]></document><document><![CDATA[tan payaso que es el funes mori, que cuando si le hicieron falta no se la valieron 🤡😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[10:57 on a monday night and i’m drinking some lime perrier and eating a nacho bell grande]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonyMusicGlobal and RCA records have dropped R. Kelly, but they still profit from abuse. Sony Music must do more:… https://t.co/xqeVvVHzOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just keeping this in circulation #FakeTrumpEmergency https://t.co/SY0xy4ZsEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang laughable. Funniest Facebook Photoshop Fails https://t.co/LWibgFYDLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna go to sleep but my phone jumping... I don't want none of em 😣😕😒😐😤 But I hate putting my phone on to not disturb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damm you autocorrect that’s the second time you’ve changed it a a curse word 😭😭😭😭😂😂😂🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who has supported Edenton Athletics. We are ready for another great season!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: The man next to me kept looking over at me with a v confused look... it turns out I was laughing out loud 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristinaToms My wallet &amp; waistline are wanting me to post something contrary here, but I refuse — those scones are just too delicious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nynfa711 Good news is alway wonderful. Congratulations on the cancer news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP. So this is how you are going to govern?  If you don’t want POTUS to have a SCOTUS pick, just don’t allow it?… https://t.co/9mqR1SZnQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lululaura And he makes shit happen..had a great pass but we're didn't score]]></document><document><![CDATA[let their be L I G H T ✴️ #lacma #lights #museum #LA @ LACMA Los Angeles County Museum of Art https://t.co/IqaZSm2qiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain’t no party like a Markstrom party cause a Markstrom party is mandatory  -My PoliSci Instructor, J. Markstrom]]></document><document><![CDATA[So wish time would just slow down instead of going faster cause I would really like to enjoy this day more!! 😞😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews @ITweetatTrump1 House needs to investigate Nunes cuz he is definitely a Russian operative as well, it seems. #TrumpRussiaCoverUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@addair154 @seanspicer @thehill @RepLeeZeldin @EliseStefanik @RepTedBudd Talking about yourself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm a part time vedette   #evitaparty thank you!  You liberated the showgirl in ME! #Nightingale_LA #andresrigal… https://t.co/eNxDsyn6wy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @kmorg83 and his beautiful bride 👰🏽. . . . #photography #photographylover #canonphoto #canonphotography… https://t.co/YNzgbz5e7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im fully gonna do this ... I dont litter... Garbage goes back in my pocket till I get to a garbage can ... which ar… https://t.co/QPpxWBzcDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ambergulbin @stylesdobrk @Harry_Styles Ok but actually my PowerPoints for school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning to shop for new micron pens 🖤🖊 #penandink #artist @DM_Minions https://t.co/oR9FPW4t90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikel_Jollett I’d like to add that they pickle their own vegetables they grow in the co-op garden. (I’d imagine Silverlake has one)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign the petition: Demand the U.S. Senate reject Andrew Wheeler for the EPA. Sign here: https://t.co/28vAwtUFTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally had the most outstanding gin and tonic on the planet.  #wow @sfgov  @50BestBars https://t.co/jdgcpe4BXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaunAlex87 That is so funny to hear! I love rice putting ever since I was a little kid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still waiting for the @WizardWorld Cleveland guest schedules to come out. It's not like it's a few days away or anything 🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: Doctor is sending me for x-rays. Might have broken 2 toes. At the pharmacy now, waiting on prescriptions. P… https://t.co/LgiyqbGNY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[the highlight of my day is when the lady at the nail salon said we need to tell men what we want because they are “empty up there”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenCarman @SportsBoyTony rami m did not sing in movie they had voice overs also Lambert is a legend with queen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you had a go at this?   @FrontierCollege's #Scrabble4Literacy https://t.co/bKOcmHixWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CCSO228 @Plouffe24Fan We already had the worst blizzard i remember in RST 2 weeks ago...there shouldn't be allowed… https://t.co/bvFKv0Qc0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weld Co. Commissioner: oil/gas bill not about local control—it’s about total control. The commissioners oppose it @denverpost #coleg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IfIFellInLove he would have to accept my noisy, messy parrot. We are a packaged deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Idris Elba is rapping now, and apparently tryna get fucked...  By me]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's right, Mother Nature!! I'm getting the second week of a series in before you throw more winter weather at me… https://t.co/QYyQGGPumu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey y'all! I'm at @sxsw! Make sure to check out the Hilltop Views Instagram @HilltopViews to see some SXSW social c… https://t.co/74TZh0IGF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open House today! 3-5pm — 2551 W. Maryland Ave - Tampa https://t.co/PZqQt339iV]]></document><document><![CDATA[More friends at our IFTA Women’s Networking evening. #iftawomen2019 @ Rochester, New York https://t.co/vm4ql8JzRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikkspresso Technically you can go forever without washing it.. your hair only produces grease to compensate for t… https://t.co/FGLE7A4Iph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mommy had fun with some real cuties at the #shelter this week!  #AAWL #Fureverhome needed #AdoptDontShop this is Ma… https://t.co/4rCQgap8aX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Southwest really had one way tickets to Hawaii for only mofreakin' $49 got damnn but it's sold out now 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[She did do something wrong she was wrong for sitting like that next to him and having her legs dangling on him]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when a student pukes during your Formal Observation! #wecantmakethisstuffup #shedidntmissabeat… https://t.co/jxPEKsxPSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamilSmith @ClaraJeffery @MotherJones Why isn't this all over the news and Congress addressing it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure how it happened but I ended up at some random Chinese food place then at Kelly’s bleachers and ordered a pretzel lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are shaped by our thoughts; we become what we think. When the mind is pure, joy follows like a shadow that never leaves!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#benice 🥰 @ Cornell Museum of Art &amp; American Culture https://t.co/kRZvZ6c9rO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delta turbulence happens. Good job on your flight crew and everyone alive and kicking]]></document><document><![CDATA[El éxito espera por ti.   • • • 👔 #Inspiration #Motivated #toptags #SuccessQuotes #MotivationalQuotes #Millionaire… https://t.co/CbTSb9UyO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[get the vanilla latte... you’ll thank me a latte @ The Mill https://t.co/pXVxT4ODNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's like there's a contest between these mfs to see who can look the worst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLeguizamo @TheEliasRework @robertjeffress @Paula_White @RickWarren @Saddleback @nickvujicic @kirkfranklin… https://t.co/T5b9v5VYMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CommunistBernie @BernieSanders wants #Venezuela for #America.  Bernie can go straight to Hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Kmoore3 @harrietwrightx It’s just obvious. I don’t even watch KUWTK and I noticed that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GroovyBruce Well, that would be awesome! Too bad I can’t afford to go! But then, if the past is any indicator, upo… https://t.co/K1TJd6BM1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanlindberg @janashortal “Work from home”. Right, there’s no daytime snacking M-F at your house....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched a snap and forgot how fine he was. I really fumbled the bag on that one smh 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethKinn1 @ItsmeEddieC @_CourtneySnow_ @LindaC2010 @smittytoooo @stephan67212617 @pro360tb @KYHorseCountry… https://t.co/BTlLoDqOdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye this filter is bomb tho 👌🏻 @christophervele @CNCOmusic https://t.co/ALPaIUk5nB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndTheMeltdowns @SlaxxMovie Yup. The truth is even more interesting than anything I could invent in this case 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[we not in middle school or high school anymore, let’s recognize who tf we are and where we are and handle situation… https://t.co/PdudNJBpEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatsVeryKari @Cbp8Cindy @ccatmpt @AkronWineGuru @Dracaenawines @SashaEats @simplysallyh @jay_eatz @joneill55… https://t.co/ThT9FbBDip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malcolmX4life @matrixmethod @DumasMike @Colten_JB_Moore @summerbrees84 @ShannonSharpe He didn’t say that for publi… https://t.co/k695tSOKXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did wet out here? #ls1 #lsx #c5 #c5corvette #corvette #corvettenation #narcissistic #carsofaz #carshow #carmeet… https://t.co/kz3XF9aqv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, waiting to be happy longer than 2 seconds for once in my life (or at least not be depressed 24/7) https://t.co/ijTiXA4pfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎵 Through it all, my eyes are on you 🎶  WE got this! #floridarunner #wellington #blessedlife #winterinflorida… https://t.co/TphOOGWhTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wjxt4 Jeez I know he shouldn’t smoke in hospital room but he has cancer We have lost compassion in this world Not like he was selling it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do we keep saying we want to eliminate terror while simultaneously giving weapons to terrorist groups?]]></document><document><![CDATA[and i love dfasman and bestiebarnes and ieuanofficial and queergirIs and witchybix AND EVERYONE ELSE ON HERE ILU ILU ILU ILU ALLL &lt;33]]></document><document><![CDATA[This mornings #sunrise.. or lack there of😉 #WindSwitch #LastWeekInTheTemporaryKitchen @ Shorecrest Preparatory Scho… https://t.co/buJhRuiZTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yasmincnunez @Alvin_2058 "Clase Magistral de Trump" Jaaa, Jaaaa El Mejor Chiste del día y Su cortina de Humo que No es El Puente...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of Matt’s photography progress @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/pffPcBsAQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSetoro @treasonstickers Cheers! @s8n @GrimReaperInc @AlcoholicsOf @MoetUSA @LVMH https://t.co/qbFUbAZQZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enews The important part of this statement is "the Jussie I know"  He's not defending him, he's saying the persona… https://t.co/Y9OivsFfpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cloud21wAM @itsmeashley32 @seargantgoober @not_mchammer time of done: 10:52am CST]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooooo many thanks! 🙏🏼 for a super fun set last night @BarberAndBrew —— It’s hard to capture the special vibes in… https://t.co/BvCEsvo971]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Sunday morning has been made by an early morning walk on the beach, relaxing by the fire, and taking it slow a… https://t.co/04k3hvLJe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jreineron7 straight rain on the roads of S.Plymouth #buttermilkbay https://t.co/ufx99JI3M2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #mcm is Nicko Wolfe. We filmed a hot scene when I was in Vegas! It’ll be dropping soon. https://t.co/2sf5rL4QYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tuttut @FaceTheNation @IvankaTrump Computers had a lot of information collusion collusion collusion but that's not… https://t.co/UU4eETxtyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are Republican members of Congress? Where are the pundits? Defenders are as scarce as moderate Democrats.   T… https://t.co/lqfiOxrVLP]]></document></documents></author>