<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Los Angeles, California. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .  #noirstreetlife #streetleaks #leica #leicaq #spi_light… https://t.co/0a9da1lPw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cost of Universal Healthcare Sinks Finland, Forces Entire Government to Resign https://t.co/MjJGLlJabN via @PoliticsIsDirty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsbatman2016  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu Making America great again, are we? Why do so many Americans just continue to prove how absolutely idiotic you are?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll drive back to the mid-state for Easter service if @PrMikeEdwards does this after the choir performs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need to clean my rings more often because chile...  when the ice hit the light it twankle and glistens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FCCartagena_efs @EladyZorrilla @LaMangaClub Me encanta esa actitud y el hambre de triunfos. Forever Efese.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @senatemajldr Again the #Democrat Party shows they not only hate humanity but they hate life. They are… https://t.co/dgS5g2UyZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna say that I’m actually really happy that both @monetxchange and @TrinityTheTuck both won drag race! Bot… https://t.co/yikOAB7ySB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AfroJediii Thank you Vernon! I’m doing what I can to make sure I make it to that premiere I need the taste of the red carpet!!! haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living in Illinois more news is making the papers. 1st hospital where Smollett was seen has fired ppl for "reviewin… https://t.co/qsKBI8SCjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are the @BuffaloSabres always out of postion?  Why is no one in front of the goal on defense or offense? #LetsGoBuffalo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingMaxGainz Man, @DylanWaco is running head up against the Crockett Cup?! SMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LocoLobo79 @3ddyN @ProfessorF We actually team teach this course. Look closely and you’ll see his bottle of Perrie… https://t.co/hqVjiNCJjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskAnNFLAgent @JBennett13 @AlfieBCC And I’m guessing the Steelers were able to get permission from the league? If… https://t.co/f9rE0NMUow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneBillsLive Have fun at the combine. Qadree Ollison RB from Pitt and Canisius High School is there until Friday.… https://t.co/hQhCHxF5Uy]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best interviews ever. The Jim Collins and Peter Drucker segment was amazing! @tferriss]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CosmicMacabre #CFBallou #fiction #nonfiction #writersofinstagram #poetsofinstagram #teachersofinstagram… https://t.co/OxESqO65K7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardSitler Trump Keeps Doubling Down On The Same Failed Strategy | FiveThirtyEight https://t.co/Rkk7EEvNi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just find myself on google maps with the work truck.. damn.. I’m famous now.. I can die with peace now.. lol haha… https://t.co/ExGiMfrGAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenjeong is officially my favorite guest on @firstwefeast Hot ones .. Funny and informational]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robcorddry Do you two guys ever compete for the same part in the show or a movie? https://t.co/QvtSTcR59z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Polit_eurOpines @giulioiacoviel Maybe not, I have a personal connection. My roommate last year went to high school with his daughter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VANS_66 @DallasMantei @fleccas @PacSun @gotchabebe Yikes!!  This is how Pacific Sunwear treats customers! No wonder everybody has amazon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSkorpion @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Don't try and justify a true hate crime with rhetoric]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWESuplexSgnGuy It’s the best feeling. I have 2 kids 20 year old daughter and 14 year old son]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParkwoodBB falls tonight in their home opener against a very good Christ School team out of Asheville! Rebels back… https://t.co/RUWFLVw81t]]></document><document><![CDATA[WRONG-WAY CRASH: Four people, including two juveniles, were injured when a wrong-way driver crashed over the weeken… https://t.co/sQQPgSJKf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zhawke2002 @NRA @ChrisCoxNRA @SpeakerPelosi @GabbyGiffords Have you read the article?  They're not calling for vio… https://t.co/Ke9Op641Kk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HastHawk Yeah, there have been three of those in the last two games. And then, of course, no call when the Marylan… https://t.co/dOaOwoM5rJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plantjoys being attracted to men was the worst thing to ever happen to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[For now, Anthony Davis remains the NBA's best part-time attraction: Maybe it was the roar the Staples Center crowd… https://t.co/xnexQYdN0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 You are a professional liar  what is the source of your statistics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FernandoAgunde4 @ESPNLasVegas @cofieldandco @RyanMcKinnell @chrissyparadis https://t.co/a3fatYiwmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baileysouthside planes exterior fuselage have a very thin conductive mesh that wraps around the fuselage under the… https://t.co/xyernUUye7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0bedientSLT @STFPromo @johnboyt_2 @amwalker38 @BabesPromo_2 @Amat_Porn @TSMsexyChat @ShadyCamsLive @9Perverse9__ Beautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThaYoties at the Gopher Hole tonight - right now! #Flagstaff #livemusic @ Weatherford Hotel Flagstaff https://t.co/xCuUiTjaGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexTitze That’s pretty good, but you literally can’t not have Moss in your list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teamviewer ID 1054877668 password 123456 lock my keyboard and mouse I'm a Sissy and I have to let anyone destroy my… https://t.co/zBY1CZXkys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianaCohen16 Trump is like talking to a wall. Thinks the Oval Office was named for President Oval. Trump is to S… https://t.co/1z5vUQqG82]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord of the Rings. None of them... #AdmitMoviesYouveNeverSeen https://t.co/0Ov8DkPkht]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't worry Jessie,  Bill got YOUR BACK!!!! Lmfao! @ Washington Heights, Manhattan https://t.co/Hc2nbqyFan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Self made? I have hated you since I first saw you on Seinfeld. You have zero comedic talent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darkskintdaria @PWTpodcast Pokemon World Tour: We're Watching. https://t.co/QYy4slCwPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FLEXFRIDAY...💯💯💯💯 Top Shelf... If you don’t know, your Welcome...👍🏽 I need a translator...🤷🏽‍♂️😂😂😂💯… https://t.co/YR6KYsZMFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved this episode of  #StarTrekDiscovery.  @actordougjones is good in everything that he’s in(I’ve known that si… https://t.co/5g0Cm3xBfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bighugh53 He acts like anyone can’t attend an HBCU   Best 4 years of my life #TexasCollege]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marvin Gaye your legacy and your music lives on. Thank you. We are Black History everyday #BlackHistoryMonth… https://t.co/ClqS6PV19n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776Stonewall @sgtrock1970 Actually, she's a month that never shuts up, knows nothing, makes up anything, and spew… https://t.co/fy8Wwb8CBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steveluvender @breynolds_66 @RaceSpotTV @iRacing @breynolds_66 is this what eating fried chicken all the time trained you to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UtdRobbo @utdxtra You mean latter. And we need Kouli more the de ligt. De ligt is young and still developing. Kouli would a lot straight in]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Life is all about stretching yourself- stretching your muscles, stretching your career, stretching your mind by le… https://t.co/JqAJRtve6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CptAnarchy @AB84 I am saddened that we didn’t get something. I would have been happy to see Conley in exchange vs the picks we got :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SJJIF I just want to confirm that according to your website, men are allowed to wear rash guards under the gi? Thi… https://t.co/lTNOKSGNJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mexico #Canada #Michigan #US #Usa #Police find meth smuggled into Canada through new Ford cars built in Mexico Mor… https://t.co/6hE2MziaeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:37.4°F WchillLow:28.3°F Wind:4 mph Dir:W Baro:Rising Rain2day:0.13in Hum:74% UV:0.0 @ 23:00 03/10/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will be serving Lanb shanks tonight as one of our specials tonight. @ Rosso Vino https://t.co/rHwov6MBYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dankennedy_nu It’s Barnstable County commissioners. Basically most people don’t pay attention. He had been a peren… https://t.co/KyXUcxPJ8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Poultry Production Manager 3rd Shift Canton, OH - https://t.co/0XLiY5nFeb #ProductMgmt #Canton, OH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we could get @DanaBrookeWWE as Raw woman’s champion this year that would be https://t.co/W2Tg5eNTuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DangerPowers19 @TheTank_91 He took a high stick in that game too could have a broken nose or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWilson411 @untappd What is the Judge’s name so we can tag him or her?]]></document><document><![CDATA[now i see why my mom always ask me "how are you feeling" she probably can tell when im at my fucking lowest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love living so close to the border. I fly from Mexico at such a cheap price, antibiotics from there work in a mat… https://t.co/O7BSMhceY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[DA Funk responds, briefly, but doesn't address the TN Supreme Court. He notes 3,000+ cases per year have discovery… https://t.co/RNzLfeSCrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen Up! If your not training with my guy then your missing something special! Trust me he can get you quicker fa… https://t.co/RXBF0BMxmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was only a matter of time before these dogs chewed up something important. https://t.co/wLdld4SBUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unos auténticos hijos de la chingada, y nuestros políticos no son más que el reflejo de una sociedad muy gacha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @NHL, why would you want a fairly officiated game, when the refs can hand the defending Champs a victory?… https://t.co/cd7PmwUTKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ab_Synthia2 Thomas is one EVIL, HEARTLESS, SOULLESS CREATURE for wanting his own kids killed too! 🤬🤬🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fair play to Klopp for smiling. If that was me the little shit would have had his teeth in his hands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do I have the sudden urge to get a septum piercing i’ve never had interest in them but all of a sudden I want o… https://t.co/00fAKHzRSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AverageHunter Yes. But similar thing has happened where the big wigs appointed a new commissioner even though most… https://t.co/eWbOYKOfwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisissigrid I made an 8-bit graphic version of your album cover. Hope you like it. :) https://t.co/sIXEi9quh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, to my trainer:  I’d like a body like Ryan Reynolds.  Also me, to my trainer:  How do I do this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Video - The @ATTCyber Approach to Threat Detection https://t.co/OG2rzm831z #RSAC #RSA2019 #ATTInfluencer… https://t.co/uvQ0xZWOeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[from the desk of Tony DeMaio, NMD Story # 3 ....Both our parents were Italian immigrants that came to America the c… https://t.co/WmmViR1v9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remembering Karl Lagerfeld in San Francisco, and beyond - San Francisco Chronicle: Remembering Karl Lagerfeld in Sa… https://t.co/NWtDxrp2ej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horror movies scared me into nvr getting a two story house, too many places a killer can hide]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does that make you look as a friend if you’re constantly posting on social media about the situation besides co… https://t.co/OR8qyghEl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[7th NKU walk of the day puts @Johnnyhawk12 aboard with 1 out in the Alabama 5th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsJimWolf @bensbiz @fsudruski Great game. Played Clemens with @bpn224 back in the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[7:32am I caught the traffic cop writing me a ticket There needs to be a damn grace period!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're about to check into room 13666.... #k13kids #WDW #disneyworld https://t.co/LvSqoIDbb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BardicLoreBlog #Homebrew Bardic circle rules: combined power allow for higher spells, wider ranges, other tricks #Hmmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[PEMEX = Mercantilismo Estatal Protecciónista, antiCapitalista pues, por eso los “robos” de combustible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlowPyroclastic @anthemgame @nate4657 I can agree with you there what have they been doing. I know game developing… https://t.co/P7OVhFujd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OTD 50 years ago, Mickey Mantle officially announced his retirement. https://t.co/dOAuaQwopE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TabooFetishTalk @ReelTalkInc @hushdirectory @LasVegasXXX #ValentinesDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KipHenley You been in trouble with the Greenskeeper lately.. he careful 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UniteAlbertan #cdnpoli #abpoli Fighting against people https://t.co/jR3a1GpVQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is greatly amusing to me to see the rush to Elons defense. The reality is he broke rules, then broke the terms o… https://t.co/lmzxEWUqr5]]></document><document><![CDATA['Truly unique' reentry program gives students second chance in #AtlanticCity  @NJCRDA @NJLaborDept @UHLocal54… https://t.co/jcTnacC5M6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never met Cody Legg, but mgreenlee27 and I did a documentary on him and the men in his life. Google it if you hav… https://t.co/wIIy4KalIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #MondayThoughts #MondayMotivation  Problem: #Delusional #DonaldTrump's SO Driven by #NPD, Narcissi… https://t.co/i2VirNyu2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork @pewdrdad Enough is enough! When is @SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer @StenyHoyer   @RepShalala going to work w… https://t.co/qRukTyidrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[1970’s Lover Letter. #photooftheday #photographer #photography #treyvisions #treyvisionsphotography… https://t.co/E75T6TgqQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cool #hot #halsteaduws #newyork #newyorkcity #ny #nyc #manhattan #pic #picture #pictures #picoftheday #photography… https://t.co/JNaaqimlPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k_samuwal @JurgenPressed @NayefAbdulai Yes, Milner was off, but it wasn’t called and overruled]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Pro Basketball: LeBron James Was Supposed to Make the Lakers Great. But When?: Behind James, Los Angeles is emba… https://t.co/8EGZhDDgAP]]></document></documents></author>