<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @KrassenCast Making money off your Trump hate boys? He really does put everyone to work. Without him you would be nobodies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Christmas Bomb! (2016) by @Prairieales @ Chicken Express — https://t.co/BacbPJhyqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never know where ppl head at anymore so I just stay quiet 🤫 the truth will reveal itself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best Valentine bake sale ever! Way to go Nicole H-B!🎉 Sweetest HHS bakers!💙💛 #authenticLeaning #makingChange… https://t.co/x8CkaxVJEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went thru a practice state assessment with my 5th graders, as we’re going to be testing pretty soon after break. Ev… https://t.co/qM9s8YUdji]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@KaceyMusgraves singing Como La Flor tonight is the highlight of my life #RODEOHOUSTON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeborahB17 @sh143333 @19dicembre @LaniLobo @victorianoffner @ItsDiamondMarie You are sweet and always in our heart… https://t.co/gnMvxKijE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johndavidbreen @boglethemind @EugeneBu @emartinez78987 @Just2BiZI @Sheeple101 @HappyBigGrin @45HammerTime… https://t.co/NSo8MjjGqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting way too much information at once for my little brain to compute &amp; I’m gonna have an engine shutdown soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kids are not brain washed. The old fart woman lying to them is! Are you brainless too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed the last few days taking in the sights of #zionnationalpark and showing this bad boy off. I’m new to this,… https://t.co/6QsukV6U3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChicagoPenguin2 @CSonafelt @72cricket @sharon_schwan @sannbs @MrsSpuds @RidenerTina @BxglL @ACog1984 Can't wait to read it Marcie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the swim teams with a strong showing at district. Girls take second place and boys win it all. N… https://t.co/LykPfZS3py]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our awkwardlyseries won #BestWebSeries🥇at the @nyciff, among other awards pouring in! All due to the creative geniu… https://t.co/cgQEOXnGGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀Con Sue Photography and Design🏀  🏀Like our photos...Follow our IG 🏀  🏀This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/cPdfR0gctK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for your allyship @art_lucero! @JKalena123 @Ev_Roj @jgebing @KimberlyJWyman @LynnePutz @JohnDeMarcoPCC… https://t.co/nTgm3c9Ujr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @Beaufort_Gage Holy crap,take no prisoners! I love this!🍷🍷🍷 I think after this long day you should h… https://t.co/Xv8Zii4Vlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Chrome Domes will Rock Rosie O'Grady's tonight from 10:00 - 1:00. and will be playing your favorite classic and… https://t.co/YQyuJb1b6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottWalker No one cares what you think. Start living in the now. Let me guess you’ve been going through your HS y… https://t.co/ZT6Goj6CqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomchaplin @BBCRadio2 @QueenWillRock @tomchaplin this is amazing but I am beside myself to know that… https://t.co/5redGWmLao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonestradamus I can’t recall having mine ate that’s how long it’s been]]></document><document><![CDATA[my inner child— you light up the entire room with your smile and i will do anything i can to keep it on your face u… https://t.co/eGSmRGuRRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[an account that's 10 months old with 352 followers and 11,000 tweets. is this a bot??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @BreitbartNews I’m sorry the weight of saving our country has fallen to your entire family.  Well t… https://t.co/31mQQqWlrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoJoMorr1231 @MotherJones He probably fell asleep, that’s why we forgot about him. Good riddance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so worried when he told us last year that the cancer was back now I’m crying tears of joy 😭💃🏽 My fave is back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ustedes son los que han mantenido al usurpador en el poder, háganle un favor grande a Venezuela mantengan la boca c… https://t.co/n0Hu7u9lxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory oh, now she wants to make up for a mistake that will affect many or our lifetimes w/a stupid national eme… https://t.co/QyD3erAe0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting- a Memphis City Council committee just approved $5,000 from Maggie's Fund for Memphis Animal Services t… https://t.co/pWWigByUEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sstorck @redwingsrule71 @Talkeetna101 @rlamartini @EqualityCouple @NickCarlin6 @Elianok10 @VickieLBruton1… https://t.co/arikh6mTQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fabianer6 @amvetsupport @realDonaldTrump There is no such thing as abortions after birth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bills all paid for this month, still money in checking &amp; savings ......  And yet still three more paychecks deposits for this month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DEPLORABLETEXA7 @BarackObama AG Barr! Hope he doesn’t disappoint. When Dems turn on him, it will get very interest… https://t.co/BGv9n3xPT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TIME #Miami #Florida #LoveFL 20 years anniversary. #Tatiana 🇺🇸 https://t.co/82ozPiQLNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ijefferson1776 Hattie reports low effect for class size, in general, but anecdotal evidence from educators in my w… https://t.co/uj1Ns1CH2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[ST. PATRICK'S DAY WREATH SALE: We all need a little LUCK of the Irish this St. Patrick's Day! With this Wish in min… https://t.co/CdpMGmEka1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, so back to elliptical lady for a second. She STANDS BEHIND ME and waits until I get off (there were three other ellipticals, mind you)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sammcknight1 @SophieJewes You and the House of Ashish are a perfect magic in the world of fashion. Cheers for the… https://t.co/10PEUQuUB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarrietBrompton Yes, quite close. I take this bus every day and I get off in Roosevelt and 74th Street to get on the train.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am beyond ready to graduate!!!! Undergrad was great but I’m ready to level up and learn more things]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyEngland2016 @Peeperpea29 @karenslinn43 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @ClockworkHamma @Iluvinspireu @FRISEEMYRIAM… https://t.co/kbpRVkGQeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Convincing yourself to be something you aren’t will mess you up creatively. Feels like I’ve wasted two years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just goes to show you can be gorgeous af, rich af, dope af, fit af, funny af, loving af, humble af, have his baby a… https://t.co/oPRpjczN7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @Emmmm_41 to post covers of 7 books that I love.  No explanations, no reviews.  I'll challenge… https://t.co/JMBXsuF59I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TorontoStar @ScarbTO Exactly. I would like to know from the City of Toronto directly - why are you short on salt?… https://t.co/8Nd34M8QLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lillianmarian_ @emir_paul jk but btw when we set a date obv you’re getting an invite !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heartfelt thank-you to Fr. Marcin Szymanski of @stcatherineslc for offering the opening prayer at @RepChrisStewart… https://t.co/zW9wLEfnGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity Pinocchio called. He would like his nose back, Again!🤥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkwilsiii @juliezwahr Yes!!!  The original JZ!  She’s been my #schoolpr rock and friend for years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gus_FTW Such a good Gus Gus..I new you would be good at this job..It is in you D.N.A.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fitnessista Cycling is on the way out--as indicated by big movement at the top of the cycling studio chains' busin… https://t.co/hmVhYtJDid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Sorry Paul you’re a day late dollar short. Just build the damn wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class List for Thursday, March 7, 2019: 5:00 am Kettlebell AMPD with Cheryl E. Wood @senseicheryl 7:45 am Yoga with… https://t.co/Tzf7s2aF5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[#worldgeochat a4 gender cultural landscape. On 2/25, teachers presented to Tx Senate committee on pay raise. All speakers I saw were female.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these people watching the secret skirmish can’t seem to get that dark isn’t @dakotaz . It is a fight in all the chats watching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaHol It's not like every 20 something young woman's mother doesn't want her to get married.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I need to do my nails who cares leave me alone I am HAPPY💗🍓☀️🤗 https://t.co/8fPzxLZxbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephGlass1 @charliekirk11 @joelcomm @TPUSA @realDonaldTrump What extactly should I check? Fact: millions, yes, m… https://t.co/Ji6uKLaRKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaLoulouC @LantagneS Queen est plus petite que Sookie et est une championne en course et en sauts en hauteur, elle… https://t.co/rHE2M3GOsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted a challenge from @MrsHuebner1 - Post 7 favorite books, 1 per day for 7 days, no reviews or editorials, j… https://t.co/OAM7eTqehg]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why I love him 😭😭😭😭 I can feel and hear the pain In his voice when he sings ❤️❤️ @AugustAlsina ain’t nobody… https://t.co/raEXFuvQTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey y’all peta is disgusting trash that shouldn’t be in operation and kills 80-90% of all the animals they intake i… https://t.co/dFdLgiKn5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[He said he wasn’t doing business in Russia when we now know he was working a deal.....so yes he has lied about Russ… https://t.co/qAsqxiQ0lc]]></document><document><![CDATA[That awkward moment someone sends you a text about you that wasn’t suppose to go to you mid convo... “she’s so pret… https://t.co/MexhGIVt2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[H B D / / i l o v e y o u 🖤 @ Streator, Illinois https://t.co/RQZRQy4TQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshWasHere21 @thisisbangin @thenapturalone @thatsaltyorange My new dish gloves!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why isn’t Allison a liability like Vanya? She wasn’t super helpful during that big fight. @UmbrellaAcad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saddened and desolate, he sought the gleam On that white summit where lone beauty dwelt. He far from us some fragil… https://t.co/G1suuof1Us]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh @leeleeb50 Really, really mean. Not a confidence building gesture]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final score: @eah_eagles boys 56 Westover 50. Eastern advances to the fourth round of the state playoffs. #NCHSAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZoiePalmer @WynonnaEarp @emtothea @MelanieScrofano @realtimrozon @DominiqueP_C @KatBarrell @chantel_riley Thanks Z… https://t.co/nnxIyILStL]]></document><document><![CDATA[We as citizens of this country have to come together and stop gun violence! Gun violence ruins so many lives. Very… https://t.co/vLc2UIwnjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Odio cuando me dicen: Enserio te estas tomándo eso a pecho? SI MARICO SI ME LO ESTOY TOMANDO A PECHO Y ME DUELE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for 7am Board meeting 🤓 (@ General Dynamics in Plano, TX) https://t.co/MsBOFRyHKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today Tuff fell off the couch and he cried and I cried and I just held him and cried]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched Bohemian Rhapsody on the flight and it’s the absolutely sensational 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it too late to switch careers? Because I look pretty good holding that #IndyCar Radio 🎤 // #GPStPete… https://t.co/WSGy7u5LeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JHonlineTV Thank you po sa LS nyo. If not for you we, from abroad, will always be behind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Every adventure requires a first step! ” I’m available in San Diego right now! https://t.co/8omwr1zH6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onionchutney @LogoTV @EllenPage @TheEllenShow That’s awful. Some can be bullies too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing I kept asking myself was... WHY WOULD ANY PARENT LET THEIR CHILD SLEEP IN A STRANGERS BED?!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In need of Senoir pictures!! Give Eminence photo and video a call! They did my daughter's senior pics last year!! A… https://t.co/47rG3nrlL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidRutz @donlemon @JussieSmollett @RobinRoberts https://t.co/uy7BhuNNUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say if you want something, go get it. Ferrari has his eye on the food in the table and he’s gonna get it 😈 Hap… https://t.co/0B83cGIG7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched last nights episode of the Bachelor.. and fuckkkkkk and I’m SHOOOOOOOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This wind is FIERCE! I feel for everyone who has lost power and pray I don't lose mine!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #humpday everyone! 🐫🤪. #pilates #pilatesjokes #pilatesbarrel #pilatesladderbarrel #workoutwednesday #fitspo… https://t.co/VQpGnM4m7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dislike the @nike campaign's heavy centering of the word "crazy"; it has nothing to do w/ mental health. They clear… https://t.co/oPc8Qa4bBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennisrodman Wow Dennis, I'm sure hubby will be so thankful for the smoke blown up his ass. He'd be the first to s… https://t.co/llwNnfzEoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m an Aquarius and that’s why I am so happy that you made me feel better about me]]></document><document><![CDATA[بخوابین تو برفا..یکم به دونه های سفید و شگفت انگیزی که از هر طرف دارن میان پیشتون نگاه کنین.دستاتون رو باز کنین و ت… https://t.co/jVszMyRvOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC_Breaking KCDC has no issue stating liar.  It APPEARS the president is a POS. #wetriedtotellyou He learned it… https://t.co/lOFbyJyubG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan To say Cohen wouldn’t lie because he is already going to prison is insane. He wants revenge so is lying… https://t.co/pSKw7l0VJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[New video on what I have purchased outside my #nobuyyear categories! #livinglife #lifechats @ Catonsville, Maryland https://t.co/uwoHJ7blwc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually, so do both. Some things old skool is just GOLD. Some things millenium is just VITAL. #Wisdom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Planning to watch hours of Netflix this weekend? Same, but that doesn't mean you can't go out and do something fun,… https://t.co/lEKG4D82Of]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kind of want to change my phone number. Also want to disable DMs on Instagram.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luke5SOS hope you had a lovely day today and have an a great night. thank you for everything. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will fight you to the end @mylifecom in my dead mother's name, so help me God. You stole the wrong woman's identi… https://t.co/PGXxx3hYpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just LOVE this animal print blouse...#gorgeousgeorgia #cutetop #animalprints #youneedthis @ Say La Vie https://t.co/UlMhTrVM7o]]></document></documents></author>