<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[When you’ve realized that love is fake &amp; everything in life is temporary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best experiences I’ve had from this series. Following, our group decided to meet as a small group. We no… https://t.co/9sA3msskvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Running one more mile when you don’t think you can that’s what makes all the difference in your life. @ Orlando Wor… https://t.co/SngrGfiAO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZnzAllen @business @EliLake @bopinion Name five that are officially Christian and Democratic, (that don't also hav… https://t.co/mDc680sopq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Jessie, I got him now he's it :) @ Henrietta, New York https://t.co/3bubghwyjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to get over a break up... step one:  go listen to Bladadah. Step two: go listen to 1 up top Ahk. Step three sla… https://t.co/nN2y9tHKwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_muslimshady valid point lmao free palestine and all but some people are mad antisemitic about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EternalFlameGuy @adolther3d @LegitEricRobles Only @LegitEricRobles and @xXIbgrahamXx get my senior nerd references… https://t.co/LhnhefxVRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a couple of pictures from this past competition https://t.co/L5Qi2KjXsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arrived at the park at 8:30 this morning. Left the park at 1am. Split the double header today but man, beating WVU… https://t.co/1xEkmNOYcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi Democrats in the House and Senate don’t play Republicans and Trumps game, if you need things just su… https://t.co/2UYcyWFbuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[eu provavelmente estaria trabalhando em algum emprego ralé em araçatuba, com uma guria grávida do terceiro filho mo… https://t.co/5jhrFKnpgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to “managers” from a different company talk at lunch reminds me how lucky I am to work at a company that… https://t.co/YplHC7W5J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnknownGuy20000 @WillBrew_10 @getnickwright Yes the almighty Scottie Pippen who wasn't even a starter and averaged… https://t.co/0GW5R9inem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another killer day. Sized down today to keep myself level headed after a monster Green Day yesterday. Another 4 fig… https://t.co/xRZu8YP16q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warner Robins GA Wed Feb 13th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Partly Cloudy Lo 31 THURSDAY Partly Sunny Hi 65]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rappers who battle rap are better than the rappers in the game right now, they need more recognition]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ It’s always been the woman’s indecisiveness and independence that assisted with my player attributes, you see lad… https://t.co/4NusaIlgnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy for my buddies @LaneJLuzzi and @TheEwockey on the wins today at @SHRPRacing. Well done, guys. @AgentBdub88.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elizabe97751640 @ComentaBBB19 Mas ela sendo lider 3 vezes fica dificil receber votos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could #Eagles actually sign Le’Veon Bell? Here’s how they can clear enough cap for top free agents https://t.co/oC2uXEHGJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressHereJG @kylegriffin1 The Kremlin has the BEST bone spurs therapy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@memigr Que a ese tipo se le cae to’.                                          Si de al la’o, tu te la va’.… https://t.co/3ItiyNQPRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #Durham on Hillsboro Rd near Hwy 15 #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for great role models that are willing to make connections with our young students!! We need more of this… https://t.co/kV0LCme8MA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad I went back. My 4D/3D showing was too distracting for me to unpack this very fun and entertaining movie.  The… https://t.co/gheot0IOlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Restore American Glory » Rand Paul Vows to Vote Against Trump’s Border Wall Declaration https://t.co/dGvHktzjlT yea… https://t.co/E8WYeU6uii]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SenSanders ! What a BEAUTIFUL morning! Ready to continue the political Revolution for a more socially ju… https://t.co/2PwNqiVria]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar Review me @JeffreeStar let’s spill some tea together 😭😭😭❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/Y5VPDqwFIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Usually try to kill myself on the stationary bike every morning, gonna give this whole “Zone 2” thing a try]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolfChannel Thanks for sharing this, but I do not want to find out how Jack impressed his playing partner… https://t.co/M2FG9UCgx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nightnday87 @Ringside73 @KOBE_BEAN @jhabeeb1 🤔 https://t.co/nyoLQBWTcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A “like” here is inappropriate. I commend @IlhanMN &amp; @RepJasonCrow for their diligence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 The White RACE BLONDES👑Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!👑👸🌐⚽🌎🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝🍭… https://t.co/wJdayQ3n3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had a dream of swimming in an ocean of orange soda, guess it was just a fanta-sea @ The Highlands, Louisville https://t.co/Yraiigtich]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had an absolute blast this week getting to perform my song live for the first time as well as speaking and sharin… https://t.co/U3ypatRMgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing with Happy Meal cards @ Moore, South Carolina https://t.co/vtUfknFevb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lewy_blue @alteredq @mrdoob Yes, I neglected to convert the vertex colors when exporting these to glTF. Planning t… https://t.co/GReJxerylN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darren2Showtime O’s fan all of my life, unfortunately I know all about them..]]></document><document><![CDATA[LITERALLY WHY I DON’T INSTANTLY BELIEVE WHAT MEDIA SAYS LIKE MOST OF YOU UNEDUCATED, UNCULTURED SWINES.   Lmao, let… https://t.co/hNoHcIVKbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnNosta @DrDave01 @CMichaelGibson @DrKevinCampbell @CardiacConsult @FinnPartners @American_Heart @NancyatHeart A… https://t.co/iLFhpOnn6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeslerKYHomes @garyvee It’s like getting a fresh start no matter what was going on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Streams up! Come watch some high level Rocket League play! We whiff plenty! https://t.co/9hMscxT0bQ @WeAreHive… https://t.co/8cFcIs4ztm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men Who Can Do More Than 40 Push-Ups Far Less Likely To Develop Heart Disease https://t.co/RvbKXyccUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes the fix is easy, The Swanp, Republicans backed by business want cheat labor and Democrats who want voters. The… https://t.co/98uO7KqIAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karishmaokay @KimKardashian Welcome to 🇨🇦  haha   next time dress for it or come back in June    lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seth Meyers Finds The Trump Quote About Fox News That Best Sums Up His Presidency #Topbuzz https://t.co/ZYqcVBgLNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[For some reason I thought Gerry Connolly was someone else but it looks like the main one is this Congressman after… https://t.co/CymXbypEV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two day without even mentioning the terrace from the Coast Guard! What’s wrong nothing to say about him? I’m sure J… https://t.co/eW7IJcdPTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wrestlingmuseum @ncaawrestling @GopherWrestling Fond memories of watching him go against Mad Dog Vachon and Nick Bockwinkle in the AWA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Periop DM- overall low evidence. Avoid hypos, avoid DKA, and be safe! Remember pts with T1DM cannot have all insuli… https://t.co/0ZErcPUaqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@retsebez I agree totally. Positivity is a choice but pain is not... . Luckily for us positivity is a direct an ins… https://t.co/vuxQxT9TBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seguimos tocando los #Macorisanos en la #ciudad de #ny #ConstruyendoUnaCandidatura con mi manita elianahdzofficial… https://t.co/gx0MlREFOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbyMartin True , corporate Democrats funded by Wall Street secretly love @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[New interview released by The Movie Elite. https://t.co/cygFi6wcHX  Super excited for this new timely doc exposing… https://t.co/89u8eVF61e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twit_terence @ijwmpabarn___ This is that moment in every anime that the protagonist realizes they don’t really sta… https://t.co/aiNOCqZUJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Irish Blonde And Friends in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/PYplo8gzep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceCa46804123 @Bornabrit1 Putin rejoices as Trump undermines our sense of right and wrong, moral authority, rule… https://t.co/k6ufsyVHje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stefanie and colleagues’ best practices suggestions in Nature Scientific Reports 2018 https://t.co/FWgF42fBjZ (https://t.co/kD2M7MsktK)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freehandvenus13 @mymixtapez Good afternoon my name is Curtis sweetheart I would love to talk to you baby so honey so I can send you a pic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathieLGifford Nice dress today, that wine Festival but be grt, everything sold out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pray my ipad never breaks because that’s the last of it. that’s everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Finally, brethren, pray for us, that the word of the Lord may have free course, and be glorified, even as it is wi… https://t.co/JeNqb0IKgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lopezobrador_ Excelente manera de perder el tiempo. Trabaja cómo crear empleos @lopezobrador_  oh no sabes lo que es trabajar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Jordan was defensive player of the year and lead the NBA in scoring in 1988 so I don’t want to hear anythin… https://t.co/rCZv9T1AZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @sunrisemvmt @justicedems @RepAOC @AOC CALLING FOR A FULL INVESTIGATION OF JUSTICE DEMORATS AND ALL THEIR ENTI… https://t.co/JjDoCIoUj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @KingJames on passing Jordan. Regardless of everything and how the season is going it’s still a milesto… https://t.co/psQNOPZsrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AdmitMoviesYouveNeverSeen @kaitlinmonte  #Aladdin #TheLionKing #Mulan #Pocahantas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game #1 of the 2019 season tonight in Goodyear vs Millennium High School! First game of the Wayne DesCombes Pre-Sea… https://t.co/oHOq6q2QO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayBilas #drexler &amp; #Akeem @UHCougarMBK ! @PackMensBball still unbelievable! @theacc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome black history fact! Thank you to Dr. Hayre for blazing the trail for so many that came after her...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oregonian Too bad. I was hopping he would stick it out a little longer. Weak and pathetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrShaena Here's the true conspiracy: the dinosaurs made US up. I mean, seriously: intelligent tree-dwelling euther… https://t.co/zWjaejaAta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmakaUbakaTV Welcome back Amaka! You look lovely in blue this morning. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator Paul is flushing this country down the DC sewer by being slave to Congressional traditions You can't stand… https://t.co/hsheeEvJTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't figured it out yet but some guy at this bar ALWAYS play like ten fucking 21 pilots songs in a row...IN A… https://t.co/3I9pVHRsuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoooPapa @DatoFreddy @loveshoulas @ValerieBaxter76 @davisallen46 @ejin_elan @StevieRayHubcap @GillumShavett… https://t.co/j0O7tL2HNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@principaltharp @tammyallenread2 @tbohrer09 @mradamwelcome @jmattmiller @SteeleThoughts We also review staff attend… https://t.co/xub8vxlJUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The idea of “universal healthcare” is the biggest load of shit on the planet.   You’re not entitled to shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@positvpessimist @patio11 If rewriting your product to work on an alternative PaaS is only as difficult as moving a… https://t.co/J4rGAoO0ww]]></document><document><![CDATA[Western Bluebird, Male #planet_birds #ighub #feather_perfection #best_birds_of_ig #birdsofinstagram… https://t.co/UTd00NZ5XZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next winter season flag football I’m getting one of these. @ Randall's Island Soccer Fields https://t.co/PnUt0MOOQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaronDestructo Man she correctly identified the emblem for the cuff links.  She’s not after your heart, she already has it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First speaker quotes the Dali Lama. And then a bell rings and it’s onto the next speaker. #PD15]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just fot done with ‘The Monster’ on #Netflix and all I can say is...WOW! What a well-made, beautifully acted, and e… https://t.co/dhhYJft2OF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LorenRaeDeJ I have lots of diplomat and national security friends and respect them all. I think 99% of Americans a… https://t.co/J9Q1DMMEYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPayne42 @scootermcdoog @jrwdawg @altladylike @AP But you don't understand Aurora is in the Chicagoland area... #clueless]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @TheAuCourant to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations, no reviews-just the… https://t.co/lPriADOu0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @benshapiro Glad no one pays attention to that crazy bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's just something about heels and a suit.  An·drog·y·nous: Partly male and partly female in appearance; of ind… https://t.co/Kt83hhhKVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias Amaina, no olvidaremos su contribución al trabajo de nuestra embajada]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no ide what this tweet is advertising.   But it has everything: Pine Bluff  Michael Jordan  A Razorback win.… https://t.co/cn9x16634T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something is going on with this team. Hoping this is the team, the manager and the strategy we see from here on out… #ChelseaFC    #CHEMCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetsOfficials For me, it’s Ironman 2. Thor: Dark World isn’t TERRIBLE and it’s before they really honed in on Thor… https://t.co/5JQirQNKGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iowahawkblog "Groundbreaking"? I've been not funny telling jokes for decades!]]></document><document><![CDATA[📹 Filmed 1/1/19 via thewoodsskateco 📹 I had the pleasure of bringing in the new year with my sponsor thewoodsskatec… https://t.co/Hm87uRdkOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias I haven’t voted on an election day in several years. We had over a month to do early voting and still… https://t.co/Z2LyynciZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@autkidd @bhambackline @bhmlegion Great constructive comments, Tommy! We'll discuss on the Podcast tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #Ocoee, FL! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Furniture Repair Technician at… https://t.co/pC8kAH6KHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its rumored that Apple is having an event on March 25th 2019 that will see Apple launching two major services inclu… https://t.co/Iz7Hg1rCMd]]></document></documents></author>