<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Michel61901582 Si vous lisiez un bon polar ou appreniez une langue ou dessiniez, cuisiniez etc. aviez une vie remp… https://t.co/klZUrkGmDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day! @ Sarah LaValley Garden Design https://t.co/WOcY2R1NK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trial wrapped for the day. The plaintiff's attorney hasn't finished examining Dr. Ritz, so she will be back on the… https://t.co/0dfIiOnaY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[*when someone is mean to me* me:   *when someone is mean to my friends* me: YOOO STFU I WILL FIGHT ANYONE WHO SAYS… https://t.co/cK0qevHphA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question to self  Leaders mobilize people to do things. What are we mobilizing people, organizations and community members to do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @Pirates just tied it up in the 8th inning! Let’s go Bucs!! 🏴‍☠️ https://t.co/zBhZF8hDW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @MSNBC @LindseyGrahamSC Lindsey is so Stupid. Trump showed all of us in his Unhinged Press Briefing last week… https://t.co/My0f8WHz9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle He’s like the Christmas Fruitcake that never ends #CohenLied]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SV_Sports @WPIALBasketball @Big56Conference 6 years straight to first round. And multiple falls to Bethel.  Good Job Lady Raiders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[kinda wish my body candy stuff would be here today &amp; not tomorrow..]]></document><document><![CDATA[This jumped out at me this morning! often we are looking at what is right in front of us....our circumstances, our… https://t.co/q52A6pnwmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeHamernik hi Mike! Is there a projected last frost date for this year for Chicago (city proper)?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think it’s funny how famous singers and rappers always create songs about all the illegal shit they have done]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been cleaning my room for like 7 hours (no joke) and there are so much clothes!! I never realize how much me a… https://t.co/47Kad3E775]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who got an interview for a Summer Externship!!! https://t.co/NYCCJ6GNzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MosheHolender @sfzionist I’m with Andy on this one — I don’t count for a minyan or as a witness and I’m no less Jewish than you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samikate_02 OOOOOO hope you’re alright 😉 falling is pretty severe ya know, watch out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CIAnderson3 @maryh92 @MrsRabbitResist Let's do this, https://t.co/QB0Cncld2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiebugg82714 @SCdeerseeker @Liibbbaa @MayBuhhLean @Jo_Rager Educate YOURSELF. All you have to do is google “what… https://t.co/luziflijI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[💓💞💕#drsuessweek 💕💞💓 #ReadAcrossAmericaWeek2019 When a 2nd grade student asks you to partner for  #twinning day.… https://t.co/Jd382bxegF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendaryPask @maydaymindy9 Yes, good point about acting under pressure and being able to withstand the ongoing as… https://t.co/zGe6yhbWEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bnygrl_btrcup @thedavidcook @CHRIS_Daughtry Well there was this @BigSlickKC in June😉💙 "I Won't Back Down"… https://t.co/CBPJ5iGHdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bad and Boozie 💋#nola #neworleans #mardigras2019 #nolabachelorette #beadthebride #beignetsfordays #teambride… https://t.co/xBxDwqI1Ht]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to my handsome husband as he starts his new job today!! I am so proud of you 😘 https://t.co/sMmSFiNkYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeautyDefyinAge @ABC Aw I’m so sorry ❤️❤️  yes I am sure I could. I have this Monday’s video already planned but I… https://t.co/pKHs1TghkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to do something with my life cause ive just been pushing a day after the other and i cant anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapaJohns y’all need to get your employees... charged twice for an order and the owner of the franchise not only c… https://t.co/nCcmI3RW4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@insomniacx29 @maydaymindy9 Yep ,,you gotta give the little dangerous, two faced bitch credit. She didn’t fall far… https://t.co/G7qjy67rB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[COD Modern Warfare remastered looks pretty good. Tempted to download just to play Shipment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pandaslvsandy @EdKrassen @KrassenCast So sorry for your losses.  May their memories be a blessing for you and all who knew them.❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Sudbury! The view from my hotel window.   Great international tourism workshop and so delighted to me… https://t.co/7oaedjmbKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[One Behavior Separates The Successful From The Average https://t.co/cuYSID1fXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GSREYNOLDS2 @Platejockey @BuckSexton and your getting this pic off social media.  I can make one with my picture and tell you lies 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s finally yellow ball season at TSP!!! I’m listening to Thomas Rhett while getting ready this morning and then o… https://t.co/0Qeh8dFqUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk what this fire in me is i don’t like it. too many different negative energies i’m facing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending prayers from this long-time @Jeopardy! fan. 90% of every battle is attitude. You've got this, Alex!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen We’re in a housing crisis and this zero has done nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night with the fam!!!! @ Visalia, California https://t.co/MTXU77Z8vh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here he is, speaking publicly, and they are not saying a word to him. Have the authorities really concluded that he… https://t.co/yYQTPo8sI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol khloe, lets be real.. your man is the real reason why your family broke up. So relax! you sleep with a dog.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aneisecorpos Hj msm minha médica olhou bem pra minha cara e falou “JULIANA, YOU’RE A MESS”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had the worst and best dream ever. So now everything sucks. It’s currently 2:18am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another reason I’m proud to be a @KyStateU staff member. #cultivatingcircles #KSUForward]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wanna meet ya momma, i don’t wanna meet ya kids, i don’t wanna hear them stories bout what ya bd did. I be… https://t.co/UTAZuiOrIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmilieeBritt @addyebeans I feel like she’s the type to be in love/lust for some years and then be over it. Why she… https://t.co/oPO8kP3yyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerardCosmetics @AdrienneRoyale 😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱 @BeautyDaughtMom  @Geekgirlfinds @TBeautyspell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Representative Steny Hoyer, speakong to public media employees takes a cue from Sesame St.: “B is for bipartisan. “ https://t.co/l4d3uaxBA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[When in doubt G U C C I 💫 + S T A R B U C K S are always a good way to go ☕️ Mid -week slump or halfway to the week… https://t.co/mqzp1ZQZbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chase: “Over and out” *walks the wrong direction* Chase: “Over and out, again”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/wv9VwLudcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsGrondin Thank you. So grateful to be teaching and learning in the same  village with you! @MrsGrondin]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY TF IS ARDEN MALL CLOSED TODAY??!! I NEED TO GO TO @lululemon FOR AN EXCHANGE!! GREAT, THANKS SACRAMENTO! https://t.co/9MGc8RO31x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FilmmakerJulie Oh yes. And my FIL has a complete set of the blue flowers and the orange flowers.  Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest Portland, OR job and click to apply: Supervisory Air Traffic Control Specialist, (MSS-4, Level 9), A… https://t.co/47KagJA57P]]></document><document><![CDATA[angelo is genuinely the most tender hearted toddler i’ve ever met i’m so lucky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PSDesertDolphin Lol yeah, because Democrats NEVER support legislation to benefit themselves. Come on, really? Why… https://t.co/pQCXqPXaIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackRussellBro1 Sending lots of love &amp; hugs to you &amp; Mummy. You take care of Mummy 🙏💞🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[CTSO Day at the Capitol was this week. Thank you to all who brought students to see their state government in actio… https://t.co/2sB4Awzwcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a mf stop fuxking with me all I ask is that you tell me so that we can be on the same page!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He scares the Crap outta you..... Smart....rich....and articulate... All things you know nothing about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a guy here dressed as Johnny Depp &amp; I’ve never been more ashamed to be from this generation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie @SarahLongwell25 @BulwarkOnline I think the whole notion of the Dems turning left I just something th… https://t.co/6vCVxsC7dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eden_Eats Or one with a bottle holder big enough for my margarita 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is all I see on twitter scam ads for real skin care brands? More importantly why isn't @Twitter doing anything… https://t.co/S4LyHykwDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 50% Off from Jody Steinmann at Mira Bella Salon and Spa https://t.co/U6mWVnkF8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bajopants She loves pets and scratches but always sits ~just~ out of arms reach. You have to prove your love https://t.co/QEM3bp9PCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @lschwade to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations, no reviews- just the… https://t.co/xiaDkxsJEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fodderfigure Yep, both my guys have been anxious about separations to a greater or lesser extent. I have used soci… https://t.co/ovdzrnO8TP]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk if I believe in all that zodiac stuff but I was thriving before it switched over to pisces season and now life… https://t.co/Dns7bUo4Ec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenidraRWoods_ Disgusting! Her ass should be locked up. This is ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to the realist, hope 19 treats your well 🧁💗@ayeenathalie https://t.co/R165QAER1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP And you've got to wonder why ppl who are no longer in his present inner circle now see what they were mesmeriz… https://t.co/nv2YJHWiEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Implicit Bias Training w/ Linda Rawley Thompson. We all have biases; no one is excluded. It’s the way we respond th… https://t.co/sG2J5j0deZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If every lover was treated like they matter every day, Valentine's Day wouldn’t be so special]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t worry I’m that person too BC PEOPLE WANA BE PIGS AND LEAVE THE MESS!! But it’s nice to see someone would clea… https://t.co/9ARvLDcDB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these rumors about another #amc reboot are getting me excited!!! I’m really hoping it comes back!!! 😁😁😁🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🤞🏼… https://t.co/dBr8FvnicU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mac Hand Pies only available on UberEats! Stay tuned! #themacmomma #ubereats #macandcheese #handpies #fooddelivery… https://t.co/s4P89nqGXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuneBug88Fan @hallmarkchannel @brennan_elliott @IamLaceyChabert It's very true. I'd live to see where their life goes in an #AOMH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even in our middle schools, “all” truly means “ALL” 🌟🍎🌟 THIS is a TEAM THIS IS Marion County Public Schools!… https://t.co/P0cYH1GmP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[So cool for the #Cyclones! This hasn’t happened for the school since the late 90s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Любимая часть любой игры у моей собаки - случайно сесть в миску с водой и разлить все 😄 Если этого не случилось, то игра прошла зря 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deleted61717 I had pizza and some weird chicken pasta thing idk what the hell it was my friend orders it. Pizza wa… https://t.co/6aaCmlwPyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when people don’t take care of their animals but post pictures and act like they do !! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom: “no quiero nietos todavía”  Also my mom: *sends me cute baby videos everyday and walks through the baby sec… https://t.co/RmhCUqZTdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 3/11 Day!! (@ AMC West Olive 16 - @amctheatres for 311 Enlarged to Show Detail 3 in Creve Coeur, MO)… https://t.co/CUYJVQzMPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Customers are getting pickier. Not just 'any' design will do. You already know that!  But your product traction is… https://t.co/tGJLD19dR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Google Featured Snippets Combine Content From Multiple Publishers https://t.co/bCBF7bnKiI via @MattGSouthern, @sejournal]]></document><document><![CDATA[making this cute. 22 Times The Justice League Proved Their Superpower Is Sass - BuzzFeed Mobile #laughter #tee-hee… https://t.co/wzoc8waUKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 years with @JayZab19  time flys when you are loving the adventures you take with the person you love https://t.co/PAwrrp6FpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acakes421 Hun, you ever need someone to talk to, I might be a stranger but I am a good listener and it looks like… https://t.co/ah3be7vFV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I like groups like @loonatheworld who are producing videos that are a positive representation of a storyline that… https://t.co/aD2VgCyIZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @LukeBryanOnline #WhatMakesYouCountry #Number1 🎉🎉🎉 https://t.co/EW0rd5GaXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Massive Multi Family Moving SALE! SUNDAY, March 10, 8 -3. 🏡🏠🏠🏡 📚Books📚 👗👖Clothes👚 👔 🛏Furniture 🛋   🕰Housewares 🍽 Li… https://t.co/ImMYunXvxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks like all fun and games until I’m the one cleaning up all those messed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somewhere, Paul Bullen is writing a 20 page manifesto in which he explains to his wife that actually she did come]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today the @miamiherald published bios of all the students killed in #parkland one year ago.  The bios were written… https://t.co/Em4Lp6moSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist The question is: how much would they have to pay me to take one ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to snicker. #laughter #tee-hee #smirk #hilarious https://t.co/xAnLDnI5Sw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jttrisky @TRIP_77 @theappeal I don’t think so. In that case the more of GOP would get a spine, put country first n do their jobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I learned last night that there are some SERIOUS #MeatRaffle lovers out there...bells, whistles, chants, claps, hat… https://t.co/ah5PYABNWv]]></document></documents></author>