<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Facts don't care about feelings but it's how we feel about the fact that drives more facts to the surface.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJeffries Well Obama himself said he was on his visit there quote so good to be home]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SherrySherrmorr Yeah, no one stands out in the pack. I wanna be galvanized by somebody!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s worse is Cory Alexander preaching to everyone on the broadcast that it should be a flagrant despite the flop… https://t.co/LArXPivYy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yowescain True. But there are good Skrulls and Kree ain’t all that. It caught me off guard but wasn’t a deal break… https://t.co/CEwjzqSqsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not often that I eat steak frites, but no regrets after devouring the juicy flat-iron with espelette-herb butt… https://t.co/oVhEdfZl5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arts Sector Contributed $763.6 Billion to U.S. Economy—More Than Agriculture or Transportation https://t.co/SCXnFHL79X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoCoHowie @gluestickgirl @MMRDisneyWorld Don’t you have a creepy baby in a cake to go enjoy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisneyDude3 I’m like you, I lean towards purist as well. But it was needed, and this fits the future world aspect… https://t.co/GooNsAQqHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mama gave the password to book my own flights over honey i’m leaving and not saying a word 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwoGuysNoCup Yup. Exactly. And historically hes been solid at least. This is brutal. I think his controller disconnected]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big fan of those little fans powering the drone shots of the #Daytona500 @NASCARONFOX @NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickiDeaun @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Here's what I don't get about your attitude. You say, you respect him, but, it… https://t.co/b5OhvWOfDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HEB Thanks H-E-B!! I know that I can always count you! https://t.co/HxbActKxWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[About next week previews: there not  going to need a blowtorch they're going to need a thermal Lance #Siren]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OkCallMeAL We as Americans are more distraught by her feelings because we are the people of America that I have to… https://t.co/MgHYrB73JE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAdrianGM No recuerdo cómo se llamaba, pero es una paletearía que queda por el parque San Felipe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charles Davenport Jr. is channeling #AlexanderHamilton’s #USA 🇺🇸 in order to make his point...um, it’s 2019, not 17… https://t.co/UeRK0BuVhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5GramsToFreedom This better not just blow over. Fucks that. All pedos need to be in jail 4 a long time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow on the white tanks in PHOENIX. Unusual... #snow #winter #nature #mountains #snowy #snowing #snowcap #cold… https://t.co/bOD5JLzwrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/bFqmbDm7I5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TannerChambers4 @mattost7 @pwnnoobies Almost every player averages more in the playoffs, that stat is just based o… https://t.co/1sSFC4esWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker Lol  - a failure asa mayor remembers a failed green effort as a success - a pathological liar every day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patimoma56 Muy buenas tardes ya para ti Paty y feliz domingo familiar cuídate mucho saludos cordiales,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBJunkies @1067theFan This is what knee replacement looks like https://t.co/WYUGAmryTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red Violets are blue The Cougs won their bowl Went eleven and two.  #GoCougs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSN_Sports Yippee! Pardon my French but F*ckez Boston!😂☠️ #Boston #Pittsburgh #Toronto]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone comments that “they don’t use something disabled people use because they feel they’re not as bad off as… https://t.co/29uoQ1ivJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying this morning for my #UMC colleagues (and I cover your prayers as well) as we engage in the difficult task o… https://t.co/Yc34HLAQ9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because God is eternally merciful, He will never forsake the work that He started in each of us who have put our fa… https://t.co/mrkugkugUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[the red eye correct on iPhone is legit the most inaccurate and annoying feature #firstworldproblems]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a good night for college hoops! Watching Indiana beat #19 Wisconsin in double overtime was a pretty good way to end the night! 🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is an extraordinary amount of privilege and lack of understanding of economics and history in this tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPAOG Heck yeah; the IOCT was about the only thing I was pretty good at during my 4 years! #NinetyGreat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CKPremierBall I'll admit, I did take some perverse joy in assistants from 2-17 programs dismissing me while my dau… https://t.co/XPyG3NH7Mk]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @JanetMefferd I continue to be thankful for your faithful stewardship of the Christian viewpoint and voice! Praying for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“May I have your attention please. Jeff Kaiser, you are lost and your party is looking for you. Please return to yo… https://t.co/JHZVtYKgdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow @RealWayneRoot @dbongino @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr Knife-Wielding Muslim Declares Allegiance… https://t.co/O0nB2mAPyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hbowman1H @Rubiconski @MsLynneMiller @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/q0KVswzlbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trumpussolini The George Brett rule...you just have to hit .391 to pass...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not great if you believe folks without a lot of money or expertise should be helped through the land use appeal pro… https://t.co/Jh9xXA6qLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathansnewman @neeratanden @IlhanMN The Labour situation is bad. No way to sugar-coat it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDChina Hey, how about those two Canadians you are holding on bullshit charges as retaliation? Do they get to sue China?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A warmer winter that year. Currently, there are no geese, and the pond is still entirely frozen over, and probably… https://t.co/dosUDpfxcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess between @CodyRhodes and @MikeTyson we'd have a fighting chance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 #HIM posted @F3Columbia #Brickpile for YHC’s loosely planned Q. Have you ever done merkins in a Piggly Wiggly parking lot? We did. #DRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matrobert777 Uwazaj co piszesz...Starsi i Madrzejsi stoja za tym, a i sam Prezes nie zaprotestowal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my @ABHcosmetics @norvina1 email came at the exact moment I was checking how the look I’m filming using the rivi… https://t.co/UubWWfO6Jo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @IAmJamesStewart @Toucherandrich is the Thomas, Bradley, crowder just better than the Irving, brown and Tatum?… https://t.co/1SgPCoMLvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Simon team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/48vdnIXwKR #Simon #Marketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amiguitos de la Prepa 15 Madero los exhorto de la manera más atenta a no pichonearse en el camellón de Av. Madero. No la chinguen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You 3 girl are what made Womens Wrestling and InterGender Wrestling fun because you guys like to have fun, and I thank you for that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really is a War Inside My Head every day somedays it’s uninteresting others it’s intense n anxious rn it’s intense and anxious Shit! 😔😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyRichter @charles_gaba Andy, I think I’m going to make it....but if I don’t, bookmark this account. I want my a… https://t.co/G0KlBeOJhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama Oh shut up about your basketball crap your not thank our President you never were you were only recogn… https://t.co/FfzIOWYlnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He’s gay and 50 pounds is heavy for a girl” I can’t believe she said that!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Epcot #DisneyEpcot #DisneyEpcotCemter #EpcotCenter #Park #Parks #ParquesPeloMundo #Trip #Travel #Tour #Tourism… https://t.co/9xV5VHqK5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[From now on, when I say GG and don’t get a GG back, that means you are upset and need a hug ⤵️ https://t.co/EHVQFLBQw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[RANKINGS👏🏼DONT👏🏼MATTER👏🏼   It’s so funny to see people upset over some random dudes AP poll ballet. Like at the end… https://t.co/HE9tNLmgAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda wished Jodie Comer would’ve replaced Emma Watson in Little Women so we could’ve had a movie with Comer, Flore… https://t.co/uug8UxWBOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevBo_88 @esperanza_703 I'll take it. He will be a star for us the future!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m staying in the house this weekend but I want vibe, watch movies, play video games and drink. Who wants to come over? 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is no one arguing that extraterritorial is wrong regarding Shamima Begum? Her citizenship is hardly as relevant… https://t.co/nVsElDDefP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theweeknd The blue one for my headache and the red one for my neck pain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[dinoragarza10 por fin pude conocerte !!!   Gracias por contestar siempre mis mensajes en #Instagram 😱👏🏽💯 rayadas en… https://t.co/WqOh7A7TFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[the fact that a draw smiley faces for my teacher m she draws them back is great]]></document><document><![CDATA[A look inside the Middleton-Harper/Boras meeting:   https://t.co/PM6GbexP78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending IECSC in NYC this weekend?Visit SilcSkin @ Jacob Javits Conference Center, booth #1333, March 10-12th. 👍C… https://t.co/X3u6ATARJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cercerilla Hi Rebecca - I help to recruit for several FinTech product companies.  I’m not a staffing agency recrui… https://t.co/RNZVukz4kc]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's my little Nuk Nuk, always trying to be heard - Proud Mom somewhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Arizona Cardinals like Murray better than Rosen,then they should draft Murray number one,and then trade Rose… https://t.co/C2LtyABmGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArcticPanther86 Sweet color on the mustang! I’ve always been just a little too tall for them so I stick with my trucks haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapaBear1713 @AwesomeAJ25 @_annagorman_ @Balltice_17 @BarstoolTenn Coming from a man saw a tweet on barstool Tenne… https://t.co/T5vww9ka3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrap around energy and thus upslope snow enhancement esp. in southern Hills looks to be main concern after recent a… https://t.co/ejBPkw5XxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrooganFox26 Not surprised.  You have a left wing county judge now with a social agenda which means redistribution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing but net for #Hugo as he helps us assemble @SUNYsGotYourBck comfort bags @newpaltz. Thank you… https://t.co/nVTK6qNZmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let the Chicago AAA hockey dance begin grab a partner #becareful #coachsucks #practicestooealry #toolate… https://t.co/ZkHzgtrz6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lava_like I still take Klonopin and Valium for my (treatment resistant) anxiety disorders, but I always am respons… https://t.co/pcW0ZI7ex0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The weather killed us today... Had to pass on a few installs today 😆 #samepaper #itaintmyfault #rainydayschedule… https://t.co/O96VmKRBDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping to work with an orphanage in Mexico, @PatriciaHeaton believes God gave her an acting career so that she coul… https://t.co/eAtmKUJlh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CallMeBroah_ Nah I feel you on that. Especially from Rozier’s perspective. Bc that dude could easily be a starting… https://t.co/IuGcqcP2Mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Administration Loses Fight To Kill Equal Pay Regulations https://t.co/Afo6ZlYJc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@migoodridge1 @cannaworldsite @Bklynbby @Raymosaki @Smokette_ @EmeraldZoo @OneFallenAngelM @james_bong13 @_jena4n… https://t.co/oZJ3cXcwMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Does Murray need to have a significant role for #GB2020 to be a success?”  Complicated.  Don’t think he needs to h… https://t.co/FYlKVsWdmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrFuhrman Hello Dr Fuhrman. I’m allergic to nuts. I eat pumpkin seeds, flaxseed, and sunflower seeds regularly. I’… https://t.co/geTn11c2XA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iranianactivist @peymanyazdani_ آیا شما از همونهایی که فکر میکنی با عوض کردن اصالت و پاک کردن تاریخ میشه نژاد یه م… https://t.co/FFVb6WNC1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching episode 539 of One Piece. #onepiecesailson https://t.co/ZLe8gZY8aO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DittrichJr @ShellyVogler @JoeVeldhuizen @HancockTigers @HancockSupt @AsstSupHancock @MrDePung @kmdunn3 @TBidlack… https://t.co/ObCsXyXFlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DioCinicoXXX @teleSURtv Para meditar... YO DIGO QUE ESPEREMOS PARA VER EL FINAL. Esto no se acaba, (sino) hasta que se acaba]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have somewhere between 38 and 7 reasons the Broncos sending Keemun to Washington is hilarious to me. https://t.co/ckTJr9jSyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Aint_Kiddin @DineshDSouza @IlhanMN Not a word was heard 3/5.  I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day… https://t.co/HXTlnL4Vss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@birtymotogp well at least this guy has a week or so to recover from the bruises]]></document><document><![CDATA[But, AOC’s going to have to deal with the Million $+ Campaign PAC $ graft problem she has now, before she can be th… https://t.co/QIgtLePaij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maori Karmael Holmes was tired of seeing monolithic black representations in film. On the last day of… https://t.co/GP70GenB2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:34.0°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorruptedPOD hey Joe I literally LMAO when I saw anderson coopers tweet bout trump having to pay that porn star mi… https://t.co/6bejEwNtsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#China is rapidly becoming a dystopian #surveillance society and minorities, especially #Muslims, are among the pri… https://t.co/RS4il0580i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateDems @SenBooker uncontrollable temper cory booker. bad news jerk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lip fillers honestly is not the look y’all think it is. https://t.co/7W0J4F27jn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BozacSupertramp @BuckeyOn @AOC Nope. I have a BA in English and an MA in English Ed. I also understand context and… https://t.co/8p3JSq3Hc6]]></document></documents></author>