<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Oil on Canvas 40” x 80” x 2” Gallery Wrapped  Time to slumber and rest  Back to the comfort of my bed  Nestled in t… https://t.co/BqzPAHG8dB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for a great day of cold, shopping, phone losing, lunch and laughter!  Thank you for the delicious smellin… https://t.co/ZsILbXvPIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolineGx8 @Dr_Niamh_Shaw @Lottie_dolls @ian_harkin @esa @blackrockcastle @AstronomyIRL Whoa! Checkout those… https://t.co/D2JCO9ZnoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was chilling with a Hispanic and he said I don't date black women because they are dirty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thefallxxo What really happened in my head lmao https://t.co/fG1zze2620]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raymahl Let’s get breakfast tacos when you’re here https://t.co/xIWAYS5ztP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz You assh@Ies have promised me you were coming out with gluten free options for the last two years, a… https://t.co/vvGKHsCI9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cruisingqueen13 @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump McConnell Ryan Grahm Nunes Session Whittaker  McCarthy....are at… https://t.co/MIhYFT29Op]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the phone with my mom and she says “I’m trying to keep a positive attitude because if I don’t I’m gonna run somebody over”😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TuesdayMotivation #TuesdayThought #LifeLessons https://t.co/dB84jPdgLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@network_gal @h8Wankmaggot45 Yes it would save so many tax dollars😂😂 or they can just keep him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump I'm sure it's all trumped up numbers.  Pun intended. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @1053SS, @JC1053, @ktfuntweets, @gavindawson, and @kandc1053. When are y'all in AZ? Would love to fellowship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akarl_smith @AOC Dilutional immature vision ! It’s NY they never supported your dilution]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its raining. Its cold. Going to remain in bed until I feel the courage to do something else #SaturdayMorning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misterarthur @UMassPoll @MollyJongFast @BernieSanders @JoeBiden @KamalaHarris @BetoORourke I’m betting that he is… https://t.co/LRut9qJWue]]></document><document><![CDATA[A marvelous sipper for the weekend ahead - Yellow Chartreuse, Reposado Tequila, and apricot brandy liqueur. Get the… https://t.co/FoMC3YDtvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any Dem who condones her Behavior or ANYONE who uses 'sick humor' in reference of Jews, I have one short 3 word Mes… https://t.co/Y8L2noRJ1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar i’m so sad i didn’t get to see you guys at arden mall😭i was so jet lagged and there is always next time😢💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kickass time at @theforum seeing @bmthofficial @fever333 @Thrice https://t.co/yTMb4kXR4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Complex Lmao this must suck but Kim has the better material one... quality&gt;&gt;quantity]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Long Beach Airport (LGB) in Long Beach, CA https://t.co/XxUb2iJpl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@furikurii I love him too :( but I like the grass boy too. Everyone’s saying this but I have to wait for the evolutions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACTBrigitte @funatanytime2 Getntjis demon out of OUR CAPITOL! https://t.co/IcANXuEgOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I didn’t say this, but most people suck... They do. Some of them are wonderful, but mostly they’re not. And the we… https://t.co/fAdsdgpuVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[26% of children 0-4 years ago have experienced trauma in their lives.  @ConsciousD]]></document><document><![CDATA[In other news, I would officially like to be adopted by Bradley Cooper and Lady Gaga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry that you actually had a faithful, responsible, beautiful woman who would bend over backwards for you but that… https://t.co/OImDwIfXH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I realized from my engagement brunch that we clearly can’t have a small quaint wedding...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ILLENIUMMUSIC ❤️❤️ - Crashing (Lyric Video) ft. Bahari https://t.co/ZmZav8MMkM via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oscarlararocha1 Saludos oscar lindo dia bendiciones amigo 👍🙏 cuidate  😘🐯👍💛💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d be lying if I said I was familiar with him.  But tons of comedians I admire and respect really loved him.  Ment… https://t.co/MpEm31BkSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go the extra mile, it's never crowded.  #CelebrateMonday #unicornslead #ThisIsEvers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being loved this much 😭 get you a man who loves you this much but loves Jesus more ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, yes it has. 😎 Can’t wait to finally see what this Western Iowa ski hill course is all about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my 12 yr old self would be soooo upset that solange is trending higher than the j*nas br*thers]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sweetest little lady in pink for Valentine’s Day! Walking into daycare like a big girl these days.  #HSEDS @ Hol… https://t.co/KDJolkOYqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wee bit of wisdom. I discovered this in my writings from 2013 and thought this still applies. Trusting it inspire… https://t.co/JMrFKtwvIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dillman_diana @sandyknauer @BettieRose100 @ChicagoMGD_SD @thefishermon @SallyAlbright @SadAmericans2… https://t.co/YNlHZgtxJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllyBee95909640 @charliekirk11 She doesn't have any children or grandchildren.  Her husband does from a previous marriage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics Is this being handled like @BrettKavanaugh's accusations? Think hard now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fichmart @ortega_mmo_ Seguro me odias, por eso te voy a dejar en el A. 🤭😛 Gracias, amiko. Te tqm. 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IkaRuss6 @tee10202 @PrimeCreator2 @theColor13 @MAGAforc @anonwulfhund @AboveTheBurgh @JeremyRobards7 @AlanaDCNews… https://t.co/Q1BHGgCSOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥 Check out this MASSIVE GIVEAWAY by @RomanAtwood over at https://t.co/3iY5F3k6fn! 🔥🔥    WIN BIG PRIZES from… https://t.co/6cQiPQfrAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usminority @sue_meadows11 @FoxNews @marklevinshow Thank you for your common sense and educating the Dems. You've d… https://t.co/L3qhOcQAdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllaCantaloupeH @clao50 @vorrathpaddy @martuchi63 @salakill @ssamtaoying @Eri_Lab_Es @ErickGagni @BlancaNayelyNT3… https://t.co/Po0hZ9bitk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsTylerKSR Gravy in UK hoodie (with the hood cut off) https://t.co/IclHRaPFmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diepthought @SenGianaris Good for you!!  I lived 27 years in Seattle and saw what Amazon did to the region, and yo… https://t.co/KujE7LBQR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever acidently cut your pets quick when you’re trimming their nails and then you feel like the worst person in the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[It breaks my heart to see all of the hurt and pain we put upon each other these days in the name of “being right”.… https://t.co/cneapqX4SC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latimes @GavinNewsom I beg U, DO NOT trust gov w/your healthcare. Woman w/Wrkrs/Comp w/severed back waiting 2 year… https://t.co/S6hSQKDQTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylanmalone @DavidNakamura me too. But I think this is more about fear/self-preservation than "Smarts" or "walking… https://t.co/W4SSrMF5Bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zbarnes 🙋🏼‍♀️ Special Education teacher that left MNPS in January 2018 here. Lots of reasons for my departure. I’m… https://t.co/ZR1bfXxyef]]></document><document><![CDATA[This 👇. And Arizona still has the highest student-to-School counsleor ratio in the country. We still have outrageou… https://t.co/T2wn1dfXx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery The young Democrats  are getting to her. She's losing her power.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima keep it a stack, Farah is one of my most solid friends. I’m very happy our friendship went passed just highschool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aw miss having u at home to laugh with you everyday. 😢❤️ But on a more serious note, please help find her a man 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scaling walls, charts and global access with @grabrinc team 🧗🏻‍♀️📈🌎 #MyGrabrStory https://t.co/DpbmHXjmE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nowhere to go, but up✨ #shesofficial #wdi @ Epcot - Walt Disney World https://t.co/bi8PdECt81]]></document><document><![CDATA[The children were nestled all snug in their beds, while visions of the Coogs beating the Bearcats danced in their h… https://t.co/KVZNZXUl4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Vendo Apto en #Bogota Belmira remodelado 1 hab, 1 estudio, 1 Baño, Cocina, Parqueo, Gym, Preciosa Vista, Excelente… https://t.co/zIZQ3evfXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I admitted my wrongs and I learned my lesson and you still wanna sit there and act like those were my intentions. NO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinMcCoy3 (On the “lucky day” assignment, I blatantly swipe this from Bruce Schulman. It also makes for amazing… https://t.co/AilbN3KooH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I just find the person I’m gonna get married have kids and spend the rest of my life with ? Cause my single lonely ass is over it 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being in yo own apartment faded &gt;&gt;&gt; enjoying the peace and shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation @LindseyGrahamSC Really so a wall is more important that repairing/replacing a moldy leaky School fo… https://t.co/S3YmjypIn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asked Alexa to play songs by @redmarlow and guess what??? She now plays his songs!!!!!! I am close to heaven!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ieizlem @aysegulaydinter @irem_kirazli He has nothing better to do I guess 😂😂😂He isn’t the only one either - the p… https://t.co/bqRCu0zDrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog is concerned that I'm crying so much while watching #Afterlife. @rickygervais https://t.co/Io4JEW1hdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at eckford and calyer street in Brooklyn, NY https://t.co/HtiYtEXAFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids in the hood. Making snow forts and enjoying our beautiful snowy day. We live for this shit. #snow #bendoregon… https://t.co/riTrm5KwEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rascal5623 I love u and hope good things start happening to u ❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing that this was an issue, if toilet paper and soap were ever authorized (spoiler, they were and are). https://t.co/XGwwSzNKJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@totashafeq @iraqiconsultant @alikhalafbs لعد ميخالف ما يلامون احد يربيهم و احتمال كبير يتعرضون للتحرش الجنسي و جرا… https://t.co/ro5h6Juvkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham Praying! Yes I tell everyone the same thing, they took God out of everything starting with prayer… https://t.co/9KC1t9YAe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani @realDonaldTrump LOL the gang of 8 knew what he was doing. SHAME ON YOU RUDY -- his interview does NOTHING of this sort]]></document><document><![CDATA[90% of things we say to the puppies include "no" and "what are you eating"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sorkKari @cazij @simplysallyh @ja2cook @suziday123 @Dracaenawines @hmgivingsoul @Cbp8Cindy @FinValko @Oberreimer… https://t.co/lkHoWX5ptt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thefreeddove @Qrytczyrofsyn So yeah...this has been  a thing since the early 2000's. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going on 48 hours awake &amp; 22 hours of travel 😬 starting to hallucinate 2 more flights to goooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Partidazo🏀🏀🏀 mañana, al Arena a ver más Basquetbol!👏🏻🏀👏🏻🏀👏🏻🏀 https://t.co/TrbmvRUMmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mzansi_savage @AdvBarryRoux And we will never be serious, everything is a joke 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoodwarddianneJ I love it. I had a soap and bath luxuries business once upon a time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great floating energy at JW Anderson: Floating hats, models seemingly floating on carpet, fabrics floating through… https://t.co/2eHjy6GsW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hodakotb @klgandhoda @JennaBushHager @KathieLGifford @KathieLGifford thank you for all the years of entertainment.… https://t.co/WO3Lynh8tF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si cometes un error se puede justificar, cometer diez ya es a propósito]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collin County real estate stats at a glance! #realestate https://t.co/0a3L3krE8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtf why is Eastlake closing the part of Lakeshore  I need to use...all freaking month?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don't know what i'm supposed to do w miley's insta post https://t.co/gI9XxoRM39]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BEEEMANIAM I literally exclaimed "Is this real?! Like is this how people interacted?!".... it's so bizarro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starbuckshelp I did and she told me they don’t reload at that loacation. I’ve been a gold member since 2012. Perha… https://t.co/uEmTMthdw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[New job on a cow farm and this is how we light out cigs 😂 https://t.co/sQp0DxsyPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule That flag needs to be washed after what he did https://t.co/WfcjXi9CEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jasmine said let's do a hanging table and here we are! Check out our booth today! You can get married under the arb… https://t.co/FPyR5ZueIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Dr. Seuss, thank you justbecausedesigns_  for our shirts @ Fit Kids of America https://t.co/aroHihVCVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza Yes. I was once friends with one of President Johnson’s personal secretaries and she said he was one… https://t.co/GKo7k82j8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all are giving up sweets and stuff for lent and how about instead you give up your old sinful ways to follow God… https://t.co/ESZxT6EVGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[And even knowing all this stuff... I still don’t have it in me to hate you..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Javedakhtarjadu You'll say anything and everything to save your head in India!! Rotten piece of crap! Done respect… https://t.co/PQq9RYicv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the #cityofyes, equity is our goal, inclusion is our method and connectivity is our tool. Digital equity begins… https://t.co/94P0jxeBeb]]></document></documents></author>