<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Don’t get why people are freaking over trump signing the Bible. Aren’t they both full of lies and exaggerations?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s already a socialism state. And that’s what they want to do to the USA. They want people to believe that they h… https://t.co/P8AF9wcgIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love these @OFRACosmetics Highlighters 🤩🤩🤩 Use code MARIA for 20% off ✨ Link https://t.co/TK3lxi8TpQ https://t.co/0K1HTOegTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then again hearing Eugene Debs mentioned on CNN this morning was kind of nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lovers12567 Thanks! I’m filling in for @sal_castaneda all week. Hope you have a great day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait until our lease is up so me and my babby can buy our condo 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still hear this on local radio at least once a week, by virtue of existing in the nichest of niche markets. And I… https://t.co/eeddQ9qV6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blacknform have you seen this concept art, I know you're a fan of Maleficent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkGreen WHY ARE YOU TWEETING WHEN YOU'RE SUPPOSE TO BE ASKING QUESTIONS TO COHEN?! HYPRACRITE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty much .. yeah .. 🙄🤦🏼‍♀️ @ North Little Rock, Arkansas https://t.co/tnycbTQEa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CajunNavy in #Alabama helping with #tornado search and rescue https://t.co/0IClJnI0Y5 (@WAFB)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know #Mendocino has over 100 #wineries? Excited to spend the next five days here exploring with my parents!… https://t.co/sgX1KE8xfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedTRaccoon Was a Senator Sanders supporter voted Madam Secretary. I like your list]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennamac111 Never had to "get over it".....knife incident was because of of Liv  his evil sister.  Now don't screw… https://t.co/kktekjb6ZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Washington Park - Ashaki event, my dance kids “The African Cinderella” performance🥰🥰😍💃🏽💃🏽🕺🏽 For any donations of co… https://t.co/lDISmhMCaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMarkSalivo would you kill a baby for that, whenever you want, always fresh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[smirk to make it happen. cute animal sayings - Google Search https://t.co/IsG3251tKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 90 YEAR OLD grandmother with molecular degeneration lives here. #cityofkingstonwasteremoval please respect her a… https://t.co/YLaBJJHSRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeniseNakanoTV @TheScottCharles @TempleUniv When will the adults have to take responsibility? More of an observation than a question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedPlague55 Lol just weird all around she would comment on things I’m selling and post sold then not even end up getting them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Enjoy! 😂😂😂 NORTH KOREA CALLS TRUMP ADMINISTRATION RACIST BILLIONAIRES’ CLUB   https://t.co/STqiCsHqWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want attention... bout to go to the community pool and pretend to drown 🏊🏼‍♀️😎🤙🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all just learned about going crazy &amp; stupid but I BEEN on that shit. 😤😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[So after looking at it for weeks, I decided to join #dollify and made this #dollifygirl #dollifyapp @ Montebello, C… https://t.co/USV2UKpsE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stress Free Roller Ball is officially sold out!  Thank you to everyone who supported the release of our very first… https://t.co/NFaMUiR3As]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love both of those gifts but honestly .. I would be crying over the shoes 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been spelling ‘traumatic’ wrong this whole time. Smh. https://t.co/ZBFQEP0f5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy viendo #OneDayAtATime y lo mismo como rio llorando😆😆😂😂😂🤣🤣🤣, estoy llorando 😢 😭 al siguiente capituló, realmen… https://t.co/6OFE02lpRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic piece on fake victims.  “The very words ‘racist’ and ‘homophobia’ now possess a generalized and imprecise… https://t.co/OHXgwMlrkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I decided to stop chasing women and started living my life a very long time ago. Not concerned about anyone whatsoever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An ashtray(glass) zipping thru the air headed straight for my dome is crazy I'm sowwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don Lajoie from Norwalk Connecticut my favorite driver of all time! Hey @CoreyLaJoie I bet he loves seeing your fac… https://t.co/R3vZY301i6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pushed my button for @matthewjsings! #TheVoice https://t.co/nuRjEDsBtL So good!!!!🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[My feelings every time I see a person using an umbrella in Buffalo when it’s snowing https://t.co/bqYGIenDlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great day! #maggie.daley.park @ Maggie Daley Ice Skating Ribbon https://t.co/P3pEUySiTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyra Banks is opening a model themed amusement park called “Modelland”. It will feature an attraction where you hav… https://t.co/ymTKTL7Rqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Kyla M. and this is my 2-Year Thrive Experience.   I watched my social media friend Thriving for over a… https://t.co/BmqESEHxqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WomanCrushWednesday #humpdayhotness Repost from the_amanda_nicole No filter. Shot from my iPhone. I bought myself… https://t.co/CVUAXvQJbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eddie38377038 I am still in the process until f moving between two apartments. I am sorry for my delay in my respo… https://t.co/7gRiUeMw5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioNichole @six_2_and_even Yup... The first movie I ever saw in a theater was The Blob...... and the Blob "ate"… https://t.co/4psFuYtVIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nearfallclothes why are you not in El Paso?? This shirt company that is here does NOT compare AT ALL and are charging ridiculous prices!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain’t nothing stopping me. Cut off all ties that slowed me down and I feel great🤘🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews @Wendyho45007705 The character of Trump was shown before he was elected.  Read um and weep GM voters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allisonanneee do it so i can observe and find out if i wanna get one meself]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can NOT wait to get away for an entire week in the sun out of the country w my best friend. WELL needed 🌞🤩🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[I answered like 2 grammatical questions in class today so. Guess I’m fluent in Italian now. Ciao bitches]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far 1. Plants are closing union jobs gone 2. Farmers and other industries suffering under tariff war. 3. No wall… https://t.co/xCmJwo8pKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing payback and learning how decisions can affect their student loans. @NCBFIT #CurrituckK12 #finhero… https://t.co/7kExVvxwaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’d get more content with a subscription to #Hulu or #netflix than what you pay for on #CBSAllAccess. But, if you… https://t.co/zotvrbBEj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThewardmomCindy @Karrasamelia5 @WarriorAllways @andrewdecker593 @Lynette84649831 @army_bc @KathyDutton16 @Mopor777… https://t.co/Uj2YJviSjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The big ol tree in Alder Cemetery.  #rootsarewhereyouplantyourself @ Alder, Washington https://t.co/iERlYccAjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump LOL!! You should know about low. You are a belly crawling snake. I can't help but… https://t.co/foVvVRo1ek]]></document><document><![CDATA[how do i get @taylorswift13 to perform king of my heart acoustically at my wedding because suddenly it’s all i want and need]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog senses when I’m going into a panic attack a lot these days—or I’m doing it more often. 🤷‍♀️😥 #stress #PTSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support who you like now but most of us with a field this big will have to accept that their candidate will not be… https://t.co/vDYytOcAYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Private employers with 100+ employees: watch this closely.  EEO-1’s are due 3/31 and the pay data requirement is no… https://t.co/do4ImSNcCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is a very racist term here in Canada. Extremely offensive.  Maybe it's different in U.S.?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreeing to a 7:45 am meeting the Monday after #DaylightSavingsTime was not my best move. Oof.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackLam42356343 @LamentMyIcarus @StripeysRiposte @FikeMartin @manlogic2 @ColoradoMGTOW It’s also the smell of thei… https://t.co/P0YBTqhB0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[How an app a day just might keep the illness away, and the doctor closer! #telehealth #virtualcare #wearables… https://t.co/1T7asgPfZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you order lunch at 2:30 and it never comes @tacobell @Grubhub https://t.co/cViWnG0UPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's laughter. Elf Yourself, such a parent pleaser as a present to take home, hilarious when all the...… https://t.co/WHcSVm18Un]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMeadows just because your niece and nephew are people of color, definitely does not mean you aren't racist. Thou dost protest too much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanningAndrea That was a heartbreaking story, @CanningAndrea . You were an excellent narrator. I’m not convinced t… https://t.co/6kkKuBZ7z2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WVParothed You were my friend LONG before that blue and gold hit your profile picture....  And you are married to… https://t.co/XbKo80jzoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravewriting @madfoot Same! Damn. We have to fight MAGAts and Berners AGAIN. I’m here for it though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't this so beautiful? I love how the red stands out among the green. #nature #flowers #plants We went for a walk… https://t.co/3zS2HjQyR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FordFischer @JuliaKozuschnik It sounds like she's not unused by the lack of interest in what she has to say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allahs_SonOfMan @SirDougunefheir @supremekimun @XiJingpingReal @narendramodi Burn Fake Christianity and let Living… https://t.co/kBrycYnAE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @HillaryClinton @ChelseaClinton OUR COUNTRY WILL NEVER START HEALING UNTIL YOU AND YOUR FAMILY IS P… https://t.co/aYV2IRjPiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[An important goal of @flemtrockband and I was to sign with a label that would share our passion in making them a su… https://t.co/vwXPE4bCph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jenna and i pretty much live at flower child 😇🍴 https://t.co/xuOiOsOQOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charrlygirl Honestly, it cracks me up when people think audio books don’t count as reading. Like, I can’t even beg… https://t.co/YlxW9DmB0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amybruni Is it your line of work?  I only say that to people I actually know personally - not that I don’t hope ot… https://t.co/GUTTtcFw9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog Maybe AOC could hand out Planned Parenthood free abortion coupons. 345,000 abortions a year is just a good start]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idiom Day! It’s a Great Day to #BE a Benold Eagle! #pieceofcake #rainingcatsanddogs  #bunintheoven #smartiepants 💙… https://t.co/YtX4X7FKOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bodega of loveeeee! Did John Mulaney write this sketch bc it was ridiculous and a perfect homage to NYC bodegas! @nbcsnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[He simply looks at me the way you used to make me feel and I can’t help but get 🦋🦋🦋. 💕🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[No entiendo por qué me llega este tipo de publicidad 🤷🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️ Jajajaja https://t.co/RYf4tyX4ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Puffypuffmcpuff @BTStephens007 @GangewereApril @GOPLeader God help you]]></document><document><![CDATA[i bet i’ve said this before, but there are some songs that come on my gym playlist that i just can’t help but bop to]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell trump to stop 🛑 golfing 🏌️‍♀️ at $3million a pop! Kids private business meetings $100.000. ⛳️$50,000. Golf 🏌️… https://t.co/mpG03M5ZiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KLFC92 Such a scary time.  The unknown future of a child you love dearly.  I remember although it was 26 years ago… https://t.co/fxjeIZagqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chilling (@ Reserve Square Parking Garage in Cleveland, OH) https://t.co/38oPEuZOCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ben_mckenzie @missmorenab @camrenbicondova Here we go @Gotham #HappyValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[being able to shoot around today &amp; have no pain for the first time in 4 months is a whole new feeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist @IreneSundberg1 I will never let go..... never. Love you JR!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por favor Dios ayuda a Venezuela esa patria tan hermosa con seres humanos y vidas que merecen ser felices y libres,… https://t.co/esdz4Wj0By]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a good day to have a good day☀️🤷🏽‍♂️  #wdw #Disney #purplewall #magickingdom #disneyland #epcot #animalkingdom… https://t.co/pyttwY6jCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shadeofpinkkkkk I love my work buddies! I honestly have some good laughs with you guys ❤ I look forward to seeing everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take me back! The Pray For The Wicked Tour was so amazing and I am so happy that I was able to witness it 3x and st… https://t.co/RPUfApmxuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlenderSherbet @Mitumba10 As a good "pupsychopath" he is eating his trophy, again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack He should be sent in Venezuela now. #MAGA #Trump2020 https://t.co/diJ5hwlz4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[was wondering why my lyft home was SO expensive but realized everyone gets kicked out of bars at 2 here…. LA is dumb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner Don’t waste any brain cells on him. Manafort on the other hand is 9 months in solit… https://t.co/o6Ztc1vQbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the part when i tell ya i dont want ya im stronger then i been before this is the part when i break free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Setting up the @hapara_team Workspace for our Dare To Lead book club that started this week. #ocsbBookClub. If anyo… https://t.co/ZyzdgBEPYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you think of this poster design for my latest film, I’m Not a Robot? Constructive criticism welcomed! https://t.co/vHFE2aCBK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJJAAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJ… https://t.co/Xu8mrNDZwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[guess wat i just bought #fuq #yes #breakupwyourgirlfriendimbored https://t.co/ZVRXpIGYGh]]></document></documents></author>