<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Love this.   I’ve found some of the greatest joys (and greatest challenges) of parenting has come from introducing… https://t.co/Xw7euF6rtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @fordnation I thought the OPP served all Ontarians... equally and impartially.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students have a right to speak about what they see. So often when bad behavior is exposed, it’s because a kid had t… https://t.co/aj68njsNcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it should be a crime if you have a degree and don’t understand what intersectionality is 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m talking to you, just know you’re the only person I’m talking to. I’m not like the rest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissyKeriBaby @OriginalYoni If the Nats end up beating the Phillies in the NLCS bc of a Harper error, this gaffe,… https://t.co/EpsMcYBgQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Endymion parade for Mardi Gras in New Orleans! #goodtimes #neworleansculture #htownborn #mardigras #htowntoNO #fun… https://t.co/ctsrNLyRZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanehaggerty @caceacace @Carla_Pereira2 @ShawnMcKillop Not sure today is a good day to be wearing them... Just li… https://t.co/ui5ef7QC4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing news today at the Sydenham Campus in #Wallaceburg. A $500,000 planning grant was announced for @ckhamedia t… https://t.co/5jWrrjqnIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arianatooneedy Who's mfn handling you wrong boo! Let me Kno I'll be on a flight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Voodoo Child (Slight Return) (Live) by Stevie Ray Vaughan on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/1Zhtgp78DW https://t.co/juzjfG7131]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiffmarieeSD Order has been restored. And I have completed a compensetory act. https://t.co/rAwiYzSMgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoContigo is the Grace 24oz gone for good? The push button is perfect, no flip, no twist, no straw. Grace 32oz (to… https://t.co/BCYH8ckeyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raymond120155 @charliekirk11 2 years is nothing for an investigation of this scope. And it can be argued that the… https://t.co/lY7vLEmqNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juicetintweets @azimechprojekt @daveanthony I mean, that’s the whole concept behind marketing. Marketing, virtuall… https://t.co/9C8JJ6xjls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SweatSuitCHAMP Age definitely plays a factor when it comes to the NBA draft a guy could be listed as a freshman bu… https://t.co/P8cvHQFWwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DBYankees1 True on both I believe myself both will have good seasons if Sanchez does terrible again I believe Yank… https://t.co/suSALDLqrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Why should I have the right to evict without cause?” asks Hayward CM @AlMendall, who says he owns a rental unit in another county. #haymtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent the afternoon at the botanic garden in Fort Worth today. We were pleasantly surprised to learn that they were… https://t.co/OcFMcYRRv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear #climatechange experts; Did putting ( 500 cubic miles of rock, and dirt ) in the ocean, in order to make more… https://t.co/cGOTVWJKIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathanwold this is your fault. You let hot dogs pass as sandwiches and now anything can be a sandwich apparently. https://t.co/zKF6pbfOqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abryl12 @RoberthFM_04 @RPPNoticias Burra!! Defiendes a un acodador!! Sabes las leyes? Joder!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Prof_Richardson @YFeyman I’m sure it happens. But so much less frequently than errors due to data mishandling, bad… https://t.co/j65nccuNYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HighGrandview @Hannahyochem The boisterous Student Section was a key factor in Bobcat takedown of Warriors! https://t.co/X4f965EJD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattowanHP Bobby is a lot smarter than me and could have saved me hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lástima Sr. Sánchez, cuando los RAYADOS hacían burla y demás actos provocadores no lo condenaste ¿y ahora si esta m… https://t.co/P9FfjbyNOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colts Fans wanting these over priced Free Agents and justifying paying players like Flowers $15m and $12m for Colli… https://t.co/p81b6AuDyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarinColville @CunningSq16 @elizabethspinn @donaldhatesyou @unbrokeMs1 @runPattirun @Miduswell @JCoker13… https://t.co/a7M1S7YKdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton, you’re just embarrassing yourself at this point. Cassie should have been sent home a LONG ASS TIME AGO #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Y’all Always In The Klub 3-5 days Out The Week... Who TF Watching Y’all Kids?? Babysitter Need To File The Kids On Their Taxes 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackHind Firstly, as I was there, I can confirm it was warm inside. Secondly, it was awkward as I wore the same th… https://t.co/bGwxMYhjcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:33.6°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllaSewell00 @SmiljanicKarl Contact somebody at Michigan State.  It was founded as Michigan Agricultural College. https://t.co/ZLqPd8vZV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all really let me walk around this thick in high school huh #FBF https://t.co/WBnzE6bcpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said this when the trade went down that I did not like the #Celtics trading for Kyrie Irving. They will never win… https://t.co/ysi9JjCKc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@industry86 @Suzy63152212 @AandGShow I love learning. Constantly. Autodidact.  Don't buy the fear mongering. If any… https://t.co/aFBfmTIB54]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cluther_wmc5 I decided to stop after the first paragraph. https://t.co/Srv79PrAOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nominate a Teacher for Computer Science Professional Learning -Code.org @TeacherDevelopm⁩ ⁦@BCPScoaching⁩ ⁦… https://t.co/rmmA8VDiEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, this offering from @MuskokaBrewery @kawarthadairy gets mixed reviews. A couple of my friends were meh. Last n… https://t.co/fr4ivUU3pL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColoradoParaMan @roripierpont1 Appreciate your service! You matter to ALL of us! #WeMatter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo....you think a grand jury indicted him on....what exactly? PROOF and EVIDENCE is presented to a grand jury, a… https://t.co/wAihoH0WQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[So incredibly excited to have this driven and passionate advocate on our team! Welcome to the family Brandon ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theMickeyMod @LiaraRoux She can evolve on an issue just like Obama evolved on LGBTQ and marriage equality. And tha… https://t.co/65qM16SmKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird how all these TVs just changed to watch the big game - GO UTD @ The Bar LVBLVD https://t.co/AVLNCK3eIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tuckettweets @LeahnGarrison @LisaM3732 @fasterbunny666 @WilliamFPeters2 @Shaken0Stirred @Richard_Stands @Wipapa5… https://t.co/JIZLlhThV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepBarbaraLee Being a woman definitely doesn't disqualify you. But it doesn't qualify you either]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Breaking News:    R. Kelly released from jail after $161K in outstanding child support is paid     Via @nypost… https://t.co/j5ELm5GgK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@americanrick4 @Dax_x98 It's from a parable that was very plainly saying that if you don't do these for other peopl… https://t.co/innpIaFwc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hip2jive @dmack1966 It correlates that divorce court outcomes are a leading cause of homelessness?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had 2 open faced PB&amp;J sandwiches, 2 pieces of cinnamon toast, &amp; now I’m making sausage balls...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelbatnick @PeterSchiff @SamRo He says the same thing every year so I will forgive him on that .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Denver... this goes down tonight! Be there!!! @ Herman's Hideaway https://t.co/ZxyhoF3c7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of my eldest son Mickey Landvick who graduated from AIT for the @USArmy today!  #ProudOfThisSoldier 💜🇺🇸💛… https://t.co/v8syMI6aTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even more striking is that the 25th Amendment "does not" come into play until "after" a President is removed via so… https://t.co/y66xaGyBNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elfremi @encodeddesigns @GHC_and_Tacos @mattmorrowart and @encodeddesigns know how to make my mind images come to… https://t.co/Mpe3p9ew0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think this is good...that the direction the NBA is taking (attendance down 22 %) and a near unwatchable prod… https://t.co/d1C4XyWAyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al Sharpton is 109% racist - without his driving and faking race issues the man is broke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceArians if you want I will send you the hat if you send me an autograph for my man cave.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buried_In_Books Managing individual cables, I just roadie-wrap them and then manage w/ a hook/loop cable strap. Be… https://t.co/DRu4IwlJ1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnieKarem @abbeludwig @thewebbix @KristyLyn11 @ShelbyKStewart @AussieDebBell @tlccourville @Kewlbearhelloki… https://t.co/omdXbIsDTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such an inspiring read &amp; one that has me re-focused and re-energized! Thank you!! 🙌🏼 @CardenasLawLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGingerMamba @rickcenturion RICKY DE LA GENTE! https://t.co/KljhHdciDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Night of the Creeps Ghostbusters The Crow Shaun of the Dead Buffy/Angel Creature of the Black Lagoon Mummy (Karloff… https://t.co/hecIXj75LP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you thinking what I’m thinking? @justinsuntron @VitalikButerin @ameensol @TRONDApps @sarahaustin @Rachelwolf00… https://t.co/h3pD5FwJbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1stColonel Tulane an all-time great SEC program. https://t.co/PyTa0XOrbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@academicfammed S.304 - Training the Next Generation of Primary Care Doctors Act of 2019 #STFMCHAT   https://t.co/h7zKmglKC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crocNballs me                 this format             🤝 what the games been missing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in the front row, ready for the final night of #sfit2019 @ Jet City Improv https://t.co/UjELWVwwdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/o to the first generation college grads. A lot of us graduated and had to figure shit out on our own cuz none of… https://t.co/yiF9bchUPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[commercial: "you can really tell someone's culture by the way they move, dance, and create" well considering I trip… https://t.co/pp91GAvygZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBSing with a Sega Dreamcast! @Level29_BBS @AtriumBBS #VintageComputing #RetroGaming https://t.co/h8MDgX0Wun]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Franklin: snow, 18°F 72% humidity, wind 3mph, pressure 1023mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ain’t a chick I’ma ever fuck or work with and if you ain’t a nigga I ain’t cool with or could never work with what’s the point 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsSeanBroleson @EdwinSenior @SkighKing @GrahamAllen_1 @AOC @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Do you realize the av… https://t.co/Y7ifJAp5iC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second row of the #blackhawks game with my gorgeous wife lizmarsh20 = perfection. #happyvalentinesday @ United Cent… https://t.co/VvclzJXVcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#myboys #goldenretriever #blacklab #blacklabsquad #goldenretrievers #doggos #puppers #shuksy #pudge #shuksan… https://t.co/HjVfdq9WXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[For years, he had a small band of mostly senior citizens support him outside the Reading Terminal Market in Philade… https://t.co/q3kbdcIX2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning Work 2. Some of my work is available on https://t.co/bo67fHYDel   #thedailysketch #drawing #sketch… https://t.co/3PsL0DKV5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski The breakfast cereal has entered the race. 🤣🤣  "Former Colorado Gov. John Hickenlooper enters 2020 pr… https://t.co/hyyFi6AGUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to the illustrious ladies of Blackman High School Girls Basketball Team - we stay ready to grind. Game da… https://t.co/pbodDOvvvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@speechboy71 Schumer does not support a two-state solution. He just says he does. Nothing in any of his actions in… https://t.co/NSKSkoeaqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instagram is a photo and video-sharing social networking service owned by Facebook, Inc. Bigdoggpinc is an Eyeball… https://t.co/mqE7bB5pNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first rule of the husband's club is: Hold on one minute, I'm waiting for my wife to tell me what it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scarr4155S @wxyzdetroit @POTUS @GovWhitmer I never vote #Democrat i work for a living, I  always vote #Republican]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 2020 Democratic nominee for president will likely support legalization of marijuana. We must ensure their plan… https://t.co/gVNbZ62Vrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @AOC Dude I don’t think the shit on your nose will ever wipe off. Get your head out of her ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING INSTATWTTAFACEBOOGERS @ Farmington, New Mexico https://t.co/0NKjFAJpsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Howdy_Doughty @joshmccormack @ScottOntiveroz @AnOrchidInBloom @JimCanto @BPucino @MattJ_O @JoelRRenner… https://t.co/sdqzZpfzkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTailgateWRUF Love to listen in the car on the way home but after that I never remember to tune back in. A strea… https://t.co/hSMh8XAlL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those new Samsung galaxy S10+ look so clean, I’m tempted to make the switch to Android.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today purpose to remain diligent and steadfast in seeking God and keeping His desires at the forefront of our minds.  #closertoGod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beckiandchris @Apple CAN YOU BELIEVE SIRI COULD DO IT THIS WHOLE TIME!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realizing that if I got God on my side I can do anything I set my mind to]]></document><document><![CDATA[God bless Texas... #FitLeaders @MrCourington53 @jonflores_01 @MrRileyjo @fit_leaders https://t.co/T3UbTJu4k2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I e always been afraid of new things like experience but, when it comes to the involvement with my people of color.… https://t.co/D7D4okdZt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruckerDesiree @mkitchin63 Ever feel like you’re in the wrong business]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah. I think and know I be right lmao but ppl be tryna make me feel crazy bruh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldn’t know where to start Seeet music playing in the dark. Be still my foolish, don’t ruin this for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌴I’m off to live in Florida🌞  Time to start rehearsals with an amazing group of performers. I’ll be back ...eventua… https://t.co/PBoWjh1x5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missjessyjess U not even chubby in that pic! U just a beautifully thick woman then and now]]></document></documents></author>