<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Found the best pillow at Trinity’s of Athens! “loved you then, love you still. always have, always will. Sox and Po… https://t.co/qXBfxL9kdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnvyNesha I was so scared you know what happened with my nose piercing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kgo2017 @Terra_Ista @BoDietl @seanhannity @POTUS So you voted for the most vile and corrupt politician ever. That… https://t.co/nnoz9jf9H8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MCPS_Sunrise for inviting me out to share the power of @myONreader with your teachers during collaborati… https://t.co/pc5mP9Vifa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP This thing of firing off one round after another at Trump needs to be reversed. Republicans get off your… https://t.co/SyweCVNkvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrBradBarbee Right. I think we all know Cohen is a liar. But what does it say about @realDonaldTrump character tha… https://t.co/PZ5rXVHoEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katie_Doell21 @cheylambert24 @BarajasJulie @BrandonBonta Hey, love you cuzzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SabresProspects @ukkopekkaluukko Love to hear the updates and hear that he’s doing well and that might be my favor… https://t.co/it1YKuqtKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was 5 years old, my mother always told me that happiness was the key to life. When I went to school, they as… https://t.co/5yhumDMAfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Theory: Winter cities that have been insufficiently moved by housebound seniors and wheelchair users and stroller-p… https://t.co/mMbTSLVMxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amalt I have a folder like this but mine is called “When you are feeling down” ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left my Phone at home today, &amp; no breaks at work today, so I've got like 10 hours to catch up on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please support public education by calling the hotline and opposing HB 205. Our kids need us to advocate for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't help it. . When a camera is pointed my way I have to do something like this. . Every time someone, includin… https://t.co/X5O5CLDu7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[God Damnit I broke my no twitter at bed time rule #suddenlyangryaboutpoliticsat4am]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU ARE LIGHT...When God's light is allowed to shine unhindered through our life, the darkness around us will be di… https://t.co/F0TO84z8Qz]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Fancy, King Ubu director, is sharing his insight on bringing the production to the stage in 2019 #UbuRoundtable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeesSwimming @CoachP08 @medinaathletics @MedinaBoosters Congratulations Boys!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@njfarmerwife @erik_jones @CupCakeLady1313 @Jbriggsy_14 @DannyLeBlanc24 @Varightone1 @CMANGO @4judyblue… https://t.co/fjHvGrbmWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 years old, in a ballet class, teacher says "put your right leg up on the bar." I put up my left, then convinced a… https://t.co/uGCxFwJ7PO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Amen! Bible should be taught in all schools! Let’s get Go back into our curriculum, our homes and our daily lives!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz cumpleaños hasta Francia Brotheeeeer 🎈🎁🎉  je t'aime moche!  @alejohezz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#big #3dprinting #nofail #instagram #igers #instamake #engineering #materialscience @ Kentucky https://t.co/9oBMv0CsjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Charlotte, NC, check out this #Finance job via the link in our bio: Quantitative Mod… https://t.co/QgIF9kNtQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtrench Tonight’s crowd was so much more fun than last nights. Had such a good time!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @realDonaldTrump is the enemy of the ppl because he lies to the American ppl at every turn. The media k… https://t.co/BLtDtyYNYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[im gonna watch some bob ross videos and hope to fall asleep or somethin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the guy who had sex with a number of underage girls Epstein provided should stfu.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a difficult time finding your ‘perfect’ home? We can help! Another great property soon will be coming on the… https://t.co/NdwviokSnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You are a lier just like your pathological liar father. Do what your crime family does best ripping… https://t.co/E5i9bT6Hg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingFanMan Hope doctors visit goes well. Yeah playing solo definitely a different experience. But all good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[JESUS IS LORD IN KENYA....anyone wanna go to Kenya with me????   https://t.co/QshDpQkEF5 Non Stop Swahili Praise an… https://t.co/rJdtbTXw7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please donate what you can to this campaign. Every donation helps. Please share this with others. Thank you. @ Cana… https://t.co/QkrCu2RJFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know this couple, in a famous photo; the end of the world war 2. Didn’t know each other.  Just happy! Today… https://t.co/dwEMJkQmi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out If I Can't Have You (From "Saturday Night Fever") by Yvonne Elliman on Amazon Music https://t.co/XLxczkFDhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[So tonight, close your eyes. There’s no more need to fight. Watch God provide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[all this talk about wanting to help the earth but here i am wasting millions of trees on notes... i need an alternative!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[DEFENSE!!!  It’s so much fun watching this team continue to buy in and play together💜💛AWESOME TEAM WIN👊 #family… https://t.co/436wpMM2qm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneFreeBobcat @pedrocastillo @IlhanMN OK, when is going to make remarks about the homeless? Besides, NYTs is not d… https://t.co/kh9uvGHdxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can't #TheRussians play nice? Build it up! Show our strength and put them in their place.   European Commander… https://t.co/LBQYbi5rNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[What ?? They need to stop her now ! She don’t deserve to serve our America!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MayoCP10 Don’t forget next Independent Reading Project is due Thursday!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i really be absorbing everyone else’s energy it’s hella annoying how do i stop that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Science books! @Inhabit_Media @Inhabit_Ed @AnnickPress @DKCanada @ampersandinc @FitzWhits @GorillaStoreTO… https://t.co/E1Rhc5bCyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The High Frequency Storytelling Challenge! https://t.co/CuKGgc12Cq #langchat #tci #SpanishTeacher]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ouchinagirl @DaRealGrizzle @BernieSanders Anyone supporting this old fool is as stupid as he is. Some really dumbass people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn’t agree more...talented, relational, hard working, nothing-can-stop-us group of women!… https://t.co/013CrujRhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSasse @USATODAY 🙋🏼‍♀️: “First, do no harm...”. Where on Earth have I heard that phrase????? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me convocaron a una junta y va a ir el rector pero pues hace mucho frío. Thank u, next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to my favorite guy. I love you so much 💕🥰 https://t.co/A6tLyJolRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ppl that dmb has brought into my life are so fucking special to me. Wow. So happy right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning snow!! ❄️❄️❄️❄️ 🤦🏽‍♀️ I wish I was back in ☀️ Florida #brr #snow #presidentsday #itsmydayoff #staying… https://t.co/y5vKXYFj7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC He never could and France these dictators in person. He is a coward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can read this, you’ve helped me reach 10 followers. Thank you!WiFi’s f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohjustcrystal Once I see her name i know it’s gonna be trash and there’s a 90% chance she’s gonna be dating a white boy 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricky_martin  a veces la nostalgia se apodera de mi , y aquí estoy enviándote un #tweet #besos desde #Tijuana]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy bye! We don’t need a hoax to tell us how racist MAGA folks are. #HaveASeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[This why I don’t go places without my gf, I get hit on by 12 year olds and almost kidnapped by 50 year olds]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 figure salary, travel like I’m on the run. I won’t work, I’ll live and enjoy every bit of life. Motherfucking DEB… https://t.co/NUK3G4Z9yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gnuman1979 This what I trained my little guy to do https://t.co/8e3Wa6O8AZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nelsonbocaranda Porque no se va a vivir con ellos, asi completara su dicha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPingitore @ManInTheHoody @ALT_uscis @IvankaTrump @AltHomelandSec I LOVE THAT IN MY FIRST LADY AND MY PRESIDENT😀❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@502Heathen @therealdrix78 I use to breed hamsters. It was very easy. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trent from inventory prep team shows rack diving pays off #CardboardChallange https://t.co/AxfYC2hkL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new bill boosts that threshold $250 billion in assets, which means that many of the country's largest banks wil… https://t.co/tPbudin9OL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard @Libra5405 Joe Biden is a pedophile and a child pornographer]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT if you think #RachelMaddow is a #rockstar! Why can't we have more in Congress? Be a shocking surprise to have a… https://t.co/4TMEtcrXXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[:) (@ Journey Church - Avon Campus in Avon, OH) https://t.co/tviF21vS0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell in love with @project86band and running together about 14 years ago.  I can't help but think today's renewed… https://t.co/2VTJf52Wls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expecting him to be blackballed from the industry.. and he will be a much poorer man now because of it 🤷🏻‍♂️  NO ON… https://t.co/txyzwZX5uP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobconfer @TheBuffaloNews @allwnynews That was awful nice of you Rick... Sorry it didn't work out. RIP George..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JParishMN Yea I was really referring to how much he loves his family but yea that too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best chicken I think I ever ate and I used to eat homemade fried chicken from an old lady (I just called her The Ch… https://t.co/4ccqkuperO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was wiping my tears when this scene came on and was like *sniff sniff* “...whaaaaat?!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopChassid @AOC Question: Does she own a bicycle or is she going to walk from her district to DC? Such a hypocrite… https://t.co/hO8oEZIf4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[geese are taking over the space between stuwest and noyer, their domination is inevitable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WickedDecent @SXSWEDU @EduQuinn @cinehead @bhodgesEDU @manuelherrera33 @mrhooker @JenWilliamsEdu @rlfreedm @mjcraw… https://t.co/gn6OM6CxUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halfway in, only conversation from the men, and one was saying how true leaders are asking the bold questions. A wo… https://t.co/7Up0WIa5d5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Billings Public Schools to have delayed start Monday due to potential -44 morning wind chill… https://t.co/cJujlHiQNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so ready for this!  . . #chicagolyric #elektra #ninastemme #lifegoals #perfectperch #dresscircle @lyricopera @… https://t.co/prms5ww6J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DPretzel @NathanPetzoldt @MrsPretzel8 @nat_roseee WELL THEN https://t.co/DtRb12qt2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rahimjivraj This response intentionally ignores the point I made: Not that I disrespect the decision to remain sil… https://t.co/Fv2l6091FO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @maggiereilly15 for staying up to watch @nbcsvu 450th episode!!! Time to live tweet with @Mariska… https://t.co/eCPdVMhMma]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP #lukeperry, you will be missed by so many ❤️  . . . . . #photooftheday #travel #dylanmckay #luxuryrealestate… https://t.co/VhgKPfAWj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RiseAndShine @philliesfan1000 @Goldengal301 @bean_cheile @Claire_1224 @bcmom5  @BRNRGAL @LGiaPeace 🌐✌… https://t.co/mKE2cx7LYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petrogustavo Usted trina estupidezes bajo influencia de medicamentos, de sustancias extras y en sano juicio... q n… https://t.co/mCql9qZNhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OregonJOBS2 @ElleGeez It is not fun. It was a long time ago I was in my 20's, I am 73 now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ELLEN: So I hear you’re a big fan of joke formats?  ME: Not really—  [producer walks out beating a dead horse]  ME:… https://t.co/Lu6Q7051TM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgutmanABC GREAT job reporting on the @ABC2020  @Uber driver story!  The combined reporting from everyone’s per… https://t.co/XzU7yuXZTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Campus Life Network Young people will change the world. To see abortion end, our generation must take a st… https://t.co/Pb71q4kMr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continuing the trip down memory lane 2018... that time I met #MarlonWayans after his standup routine at… https://t.co/FBWuOkemL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I just found a new LA business venture. Hanging in the corner ready to sell straws to bar and club goers as… https://t.co/RHY6i1zoxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning tweeps! Have the squatters been removed from the White House yet? @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/5V8S09CZ3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m all for being a free spirit and being different. BUT.... Antonio Brown is shifting my opinion with that mustache]]></document><document><![CDATA[@formerlyphread @TheMormonNews @dyejo I have a hard time with entrepreneur. It’s embarrassing, really.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to be off work so I can watch this interview with Jordyn Woods ☝🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 4 year old convinced his entire pre-k class that trump was the first president... they had to re-teach all the k… https://t.co/ap951aXNkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine being the person who flew past Ethan and I going over 100 in a 65, THEN proceeded to throw their empty Redb… https://t.co/EgWifJhhBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird colored (and sometimes weird tasting) cold pressed juice, skin care, and sending my shoes to the cobbler to b… https://t.co/L7c0SumC8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinbieber Hey Bieber, listen to #BTS music. They make music to heal you and help you find self love. I’m sure i… https://t.co/Gsv8ylgN9F]]></document></documents></author>