<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@daniel52464547 @RosaRubicon There is also no such thing as a logical fallacy of appeal to population.  If you mean… https://t.co/GwnqCoXy3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favourite moment of Drag Race is the S9 finale when @sasha_velour has to react to their "celebrity message"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_FlatLine_x Go for a walk and blast your favorite tunes - that’s what I always do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComebackCt @ElisOrange @BrettBroesder @JohnKleinhans Great work, guys!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @sacks_jim Could not agree more !  Maybe was done to impede investigation into Hillary]]></document><document><![CDATA[So close I can taste it, you guys #livemusic #acousticguitar #attleboro #local #psah #parkstreetalehouse… https://t.co/NZ3TuVyvoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't slept still, Patrick went to sleep at like 1 am, I'm gonna be dead by 10 pm today]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨ATTENTION: USM STUDENTS🚨The Men’s Basketball program is seeking Student Managers for the 2019-2020 season. If inte… https://t.co/vcEGT3MQ6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias por esta linda nota @SpanishINF Agradecido en nombre de todo el equipo de CALA Enterprises y @CalaFoundation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out by the pool and fire pit with some hot chocolate 😉  #winterinarizona🌵 #tedandseajaytravelshow #corgi… https://t.co/ztVEzHZJPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMAHAGEMGIRL There are no more adjectives to describe these members of the GOPee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliDenee @fentybeauty Press it with rubbing alcohol, then let it dry ❤️😘 It’ll hopefully fix it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do want to point out that I Know it’s just an entertainment trend but, seriously. The reaction is so overdone. Es… https://t.co/UPOXO7KPmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deadlines... I have a feeling I'm going to understand this at the end of the month... #hilarity #chuckle #smirk… https://t.co/CvNnNKGHCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurtisNeadow @Lowenaffchen @HillaryClinton Thank you I hate trying to parse whether a tweet is from you or your social team]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WNYC It’s awesome that straight up liars can go on the local public radio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stevie putting in the work to make progress. A 10# PR on his power clean. Progress not perfection is the goal. Than… https://t.co/ApGx3vr8Dd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@808sophie @AcademicChatter I kept up a hospital job part time during mine ... But it was really hard, it left me h… https://t.co/m2JmSmfhsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump the father of fake news. We must impeach him. https://t.co/lRYVjf8ugB]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to Blue Jackets head coach John Tortorella, Artemi Panarin pooped his pants today.  This marks the first… https://t.co/oZY7v8ufz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinRBrackett Have to been on The Cat in the Hat attraction at @UniversalORL #IoA?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calvinstowell Promethazine syrup works sometimes, but when the nausea is really bad, I need marijuana.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan That  class act is at Camp 7 at GITMO. 😂😂 Facing charges of High Treason. Wondering why hes not on TV e… https://t.co/jd09jxfZ9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a @skennyung class!!👌🏽👌🏽#SOLID !! - @treysongz   AND since I will also be teaching to Trey songysongzzz TODA… https://t.co/0WiTV1cK7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great opportunity to engage officials about priorities for the coming year. Put it on your calendars! @RCFCMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewmannMichael @Eathbound420 @FixesItself @minhtngo @sarasotamike66 @Putzy2010 @TezHug @aspiringinvntor… https://t.co/cnuSYe0ANz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get her out she has no business  even being there  she isent an American and married her brother to come here  out… https://t.co/gAypcjmK54]]></document><document><![CDATA[An hour and a half for a scheduled oil change at the dealer. Wish there was a strip mall near. https://t.co/xybADO69le]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big thank you to all the guys at sbgidaho  for allowing me to come in and get some work in starting my training cam… https://t.co/zwubF9LRNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I am approaching my day!  #paceofownership https://t.co/vLzuUYo052 https://t.co/7xG5NbZ1jn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeAnneCaris Haha no I wish! I would have totally asked to join his campaign. This was Vernon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spencerhuntosu I feel like stink bugs are not far from cockroaches in their durability. Nothing can phase them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimCarrey Pretty down the middle objective guy, I think this hurts that ability you always had to be an above the… https://t.co/iMO5DBkjsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell @RaiderVaderGirl @jaketapper Dumb.  Are you guys REALLY still pretending the President was referring… https://t.co/uONryxGxpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soon as Cohen said it, I fully expected Trump to jump on it... I thought for sure the Republicans would get up and… https://t.co/LTUeKEUBqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sin4Vik Lmaooooooo! I always read usernames because some of them be so funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[What A Night @pumprestaurant - Love You lisavanderpump - Happy 210th Birthday Abraham Lincoln &amp; Congrats… https://t.co/LssauHmVCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[🧨 A Democratic member of Congress says at background reporter roundtable that the House is considering ways to unco… https://t.co/ionwG0iMgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elder_jodi Lol I can’t even listen to Trump hate his voice and seeing his tiny hands moving around!! Visited Europ… https://t.co/CSlinbhBUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ingram’s game is suspect. Not a fan. No moves, no handles, average shooter #LakersNation sorry dawg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ok so let me get this straight. You called the #Venezuela president a puppet for Cuba. I guess it… https://t.co/sWNAtFInLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbagump324 A dude here just got 6 months probation for rape...  He isn’t compromised he’s just shitty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bharper3407 walks up to his first plate appearance as a Phillie to the willsmith Fresh Prince theme song @phillies… https://t.co/jXZ1k85tdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachawarner @coachawarner, what’s your email so I can send you some ballers. DM me Coach. #SHOWTIME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Heritage, Fort Worth, Texas https://t.co/mUcHItyVM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Super70sSports sad to report we need a super sky point for Rollo from Sanford and Son today 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachRodgers14 Not sure. I don’t like any other democrat that’s running yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t text back right away... it’s because I’m busy working or looking at memes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Under this new plan, the budget for kids like my daughter will be more than they can use. "Hey, want a new iPad to… https://t.co/Cia3Nj658l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaLu67248180 @M_OlgaSCordero @martibatres @BeatrizGMuller @yeidckol Tranquila Mary, tampoco es para ofender.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fundamental difference between “democratic socialists” and constitutional conservatives]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MNC010101 @mtracey @RubinReport @jack @vijaya @Timcast Even though I (like Rubin) favor tolerance for this repelle… https://t.co/O4az0Ykc2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beard gang #nyc @ Mel's Burger Bar - Upper East Side https://t.co/cFJNp3qPut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill Shocking news, he’s from VIRGINIA. The state that promotes hate and racism. Dude probably skipped history class to hit his Juul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamanthaBrown @WorldofIsaac a few of the places we talked about on here and Cafe D’Mongo is one of my faves Larry… https://t.co/2NKgnYhXuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wowowowowow. That may have been the most fun I’ve had watching basketball all season. WHAT A GAME. 🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise! #bjjdaytonaretreat @ Daytona Beach, Florida https://t.co/HGH5vHb4aq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFInvesting You missed the Polar route via #Arctic. Probably the bigger option.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro The only people I see upset about this is liberals trying to make it a big deal.  Didn't your side lear… https://t.co/jLu2oEnlVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venezuela had a 2nd ammendment they wouldn't have to put up with the bs. Humanitarian aide sitting on a bridge with… https://t.co/NfuwbW7znq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up until a year ago, I thought this sign meant "watch out a building's window washers could sway in high winds" https://t.co/fOybhk2Afx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former KWC/WKU head coach Ray Harper and 3rd seeded Jacksonville State will take on University of Tennessee Martin… https://t.co/ymHBPudnVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Your wife and father must be very proud of you for supporting Traitor trump Ted. Next to the traitor you’r… https://t.co/CeHUf8XExn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thank you for that time saving advice President Criminal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LACourtReport I’m bias but Bassett Boys Basketball got to the Semis in Div 5AA as a unseeded 3rd Place Team in Lea… https://t.co/EarPVT3dSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here fishy fishy fishy!  Nah I’ll stick to sushi! @ Kobe Steakhouse https://t.co/S3DrzmGQj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Crown Heights Animal Rescue And TNR Inc. https://t.co/KsRYuOSnlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathleenBaitzel @TheMeadowlands @JessicaOtten1 Live video on https://t.co/Oy5elOZPyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo whoever was in that blue fiat mobbin w me hmu I’m tryna marry you or something]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Target for the BB gun. My tongue is now clean.  I've not been smoking real cigarettes for a month.  Candy gives… https://t.co/XLNapX9Oqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Happy19111 @OutlawedMind @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1 @billcrowley3rd @Flavio72162205… https://t.co/exDxwWGu6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone who works in my lab is suggested to watch "dress to kill" by eddie izzard. it's really critical to getting… https://t.co/slF5bcpDL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[8. Britney...I’m a Slave 4 U, Breathe on Me, Toxic, Gimme More, Get Naked (I Got A Plan)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want it, I got it, I want it, I got it You like my hair?  Gee, thanks, just bought it.  I see it, I like it, I wa… https://t.co/Uzf41hSn7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look with wonder at the depth of the Father’s marvelous love that he has lavished on us! He has called us and made… https://t.co/HjYNqopgVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GamingGal63 @CyrusMMcQueen I also want everyone to get along. We are good people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love etymology:   MUSHROOM  #etymology #mushroom https://t.co/qx50Du3YKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abcWNN Kenneth is not a comedian I'm so sick of it I'm going to have to quit watching the show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting the week off on the right foot! Let’s go!! @ New York Sports Clubs https://t.co/QHsYsjfdOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badwillhunt have you tried fast forwarding on the Amazon Fire one?  It's HELL.  I can't get one of my apps to work… https://t.co/SGLynr5Bjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be part of @nyrr Open Run expansion to #JerseyCity! Starting 4/7 (9am Lincoln Park), this community-base… https://t.co/Z01IdLQXwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[God's power is incompatible with our performance. https://t.co/WeE2zshBUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive been nominated as a finalist for my alma mater's 10under40 award. This award celebrates the academic, career an… https://t.co/s79GaMkDR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made the list...Top 30 Beer Youtube Channels To Follow in 2019 https://t.co/AysRi7C37K via @_feedspot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KySportsRadio @ShannonTheDude @ryanlemond Alex Poythress was from Clarksville Tennessee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I'll put some money on your account so you can buy enough cartons of Winstons to keep the securiti… https://t.co/nbHU4jv6Mi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 @LouDobbs  Justice will be served. Thank God for Elections and people seeing the charade being pla… https://t.co/KMyknmbWFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HadleyTa @Prunetucky37 @Amy_Siskind The media is so blind to trump hatred that they can’t report this does not fit… https://t.co/DFkYpNyZSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rm_dickson You never know! He could be referring to his home state of Michigan!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicagotribune “Chilling effect” if you’re a snowflake leftist trying to censor ideas which don’t match your own!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need more green spaces in Las Vegas for our kids, families and four-legged friends! #LVward1   Learn more about… https://t.co/ZflDe9BMXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DontMessWitOpps You think he go pay Clowney if he didn’t pay Mack ? N clowney want the same money n not even half… https://t.co/sbjS5473IR]]></document><document><![CDATA[C- tonight I have been thinking about annoying being a childish thing and the last thing a group does.  If all you… https://t.co/yNO2dgi7Ig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trauma_Connect @BlueHelpLE @CathyBustos936 and I are looking forward to seeing everyone there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @STLSharks Girls’ Basketball team will begin their District 76 first-round playoff game with the Beal City Aggi… https://t.co/gUJx7qO52X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not every man wants 2 hear about what another one says about his woman. It doesn’t matter 2 certain men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeebusTrump He had violated FBI policy. First, he allowed the AG to bully him into calling a criminal investigatio… https://t.co/z6tI2X1iiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani @foxandfriends @FoxNewsSunday @MeetThePress @BWilliams @Morning_Joe @FaceTheNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pegz87 If I can’t have olive oil and peppered triscuits - wheat thins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oysters Rastafella // @jusdachel &amp; keenanpnp  . . . 🎏https://t.co/9yOie9Gkug @ Jewel's Bakery &amp; Cafe https://t.co/587377c1Fy]]></document></documents></author>