<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#TONIGHT #NYC #NEWYORKCITY WHO 🤓: Singer/Songwriter/Actor krodbmusic WHAT 🎹🎤: Karl Bynes: The Acoustic 2.0 with Kar… https://t.co/iU34ddVJlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to fight pain, anxiety and disease.   CBD oil in its purest form, zero thc, no pesticides and organically gro… https://t.co/5JPjnlivuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian Yes, be grateful for what you do have. Things could be much worse. God's not going to give you any… https://t.co/vZfwSfEVhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Kentucky coal company put its miners at risk for black lung disease and lied to the government about it.… https://t.co/WZXhiU8jF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Crew96 Season Kickoff!! (@ Bluestone - @the_bluestone in Columbus, OH w/ @chrislamacchia) https://t.co/IofEBcXAyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had the best 24hrs of silence #nointerruptions #shetried #valentinesdayisforlovers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello; this good boy would like to invite you to my stream of the tail end of Dark Cloud 2 https://t.co/JHa4bMBZZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been eyeing the new Rivera palette from @AnastasiaBevHil &amp; he surprised me with it 😢🥰💕 it’s so beautiful 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyHawkins I feel so blessed to have @garrsbeer as my brother-in-law. ❤🍻❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any nation that condones abuse of ANY CHILD is an inhumane one. And, that’s who we’ve become 😢.    @ACLU… https://t.co/6gv9LayRFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisisinsider aaaaaaactually life changing wow.. it’s over ladies! Hellen Keller is coming at your necks upon purchase]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE HAVE A WINNER! OK. ACTUALLY 6!! - Thank you to everyone who participated and entered our “It’s About Time” Targe… https://t.co/txKHzZCVij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the 2019 JA Titan Challenge statewide winners from @ErskineAcademy! Each student receives schola… https://t.co/CzKhURuPrU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite laws and education, discrimination continues to be a wide-spread problem throughout the world.   #ZeroDiscriminationDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AgentCoulson is 7mo old! Happy Mardi Gras! @ Bradenton, Florida https://t.co/swBUdUsD6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[No sir you can’t take me to dinner for Valentine’s Day as you scream at me from two cars over in traffic ... like w… https://t.co/aT9N2u5hDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge shout out to one of the most resilient and boss women in the industry  🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bowman03Troy @Frankr0d @RomanMichaelXXX @MaxAdonisxxx @DJChiChiLaRue @mrPam @cockyboys I love their scenes. Need t… https://t.co/rF6sNfnSTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[sooo this whole time “5 heartbeats” wasn’t “The Temptations” &amp; the Temptations have a whole movie called “The Temptations”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportingKC @danielsalloi #FanAppreciationMatch #SKCvPHI @GAstarwarsfan]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've had the honor of watching this upfront. I love the way the mom and pop elephants walk with the babies in the m… https://t.co/IGzH9X0IUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest Fort Myers, FL job and click to apply: Accounting Clerk II - https://t.co/9UH2H6zfGI #KellyJobs #KellyServices]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating pre Mardi Gra party with friends and family #fergieandfoz https://t.co/Xd4P1tnF3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImNotOwned @jackjluke @maggieNYT She isn't perfect. Didn't handle it perfectly. The short video was crap and didn't help the dialogue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s hard to accept  that some people will never give you what you give them and you still will love them give them all you have]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adumbpearl @RahzyVonParty @TheKuhnerReport No one said what she said threatens what. But that she said people shou… https://t.co/kQpYeZBBma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@21__dreamz @FoxySashy @_slimsheadyyy @MaurBink @_Lenroc22 @BriTheYouTuber @Badgalkita @Dri True but would it still… https://t.co/jDPaaoLYMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bob_s1966 @eScarry If $ actually did trickle down to the poor but it doesn't rich just make rules so they his get… https://t.co/AaV8C9r0N8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronofseyer @Green_Gecko11 @wzzm13 @jpascuawzzm13 🤣🤣🤣 I thought maybe it was because he didn't like your forecast]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he would have said her name y’all would be big mad 😂😂😂 Yikes this shit is mental illness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luisitobb80 @eldosmiluno @revistaproceso @ManceraMiguelMX @SaraPantojaF Yo fui secretaria de Slim y lo que dice la… https://t.co/mjdkErNqJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaceyHarkey Support like this keeps me going. https://t.co/0daj4NEBzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[He blocked me in the last election and I never even questioned him...but now, I’m not so bothered by it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes, when they don't care enough to call and see how you're doing, it's because they know that you're doing better than them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannibal-LaGrange University provides preservice students the opportunity to graduate credentialed as a @PLTWorg… https://t.co/iDyK8DouWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HakTunechiii Lol I think he the annoying one and she don’t wanna be out with him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christhechang @rdavbritt @TIFRScience Last week he was freezing in Wisconsin, where it was most certainly not that warm!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.#ThingsThatGiveMeNostalgia, cassette tapes, CD's cassette and CD players, and good music! 🧘🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARONFOX HE WAS ON THAT TEAM BEFORE I THOUGHT  LIKE 5 YEARS AGO  HHMM MY BRAIN 😉🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter storm to blast 95 million in northeastern #US with heavy snow ❄️ , ice and rain 🌧 . Stay safe! #Tatiana https://t.co/G7hHxbw9Ay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaARees @RealPaulPutner I see Winston Churchill giving the raspberry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/5D87iO9WWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders @OaklandEA Kamala has it all figured out!! Her and Maxine..lolololol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CamiloCommercialFreeMix is on @HOT97 right now with my boy @djcamilo ROCKIN!! Light the city 🆙 camilito!! ⚠️⚠️⚠️⚠️⚠️ ✊🏽😎💋💎™️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sandy_Poynter @los40monterrey quiero boletos dobles!!!!! ¿A quién le tengo que vender mi alma?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smith58_robert @zinarosek @iraqschristians @realDonaldTrump @VP @POTUS @Israel Didn’t know Kurds were Sunni either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__annie27 I mean...don’t google her lmfao she’s just a plus sized model who thinks she’s groundbreaking but she’s rEally not]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ultimate Man Cave is calling, and it’s your time to answer! Enter for a chance to win now. #DEVOUR #Sweepstakes https://t.co/DyvAkEbwzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just witnessed one of those weird ass couples in the science center rubbing soup on each other’s hands. Can today end already?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stan good moms forever. I miss my mom who is, if you wondered, very good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another terrible example of how our court systems favor white folks over black.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimGettys @KindaCoolGreg did you guys know that both the hot dog on a stick and the ms fields cookies at stonestow… https://t.co/FPOHagqV4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Krieg_Blackpaw In a way I envy you for that. There are some days when I see shit local furs do and I just wanna fly away for a few days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inner City Rats accepted and viewing at the Phoenix AZ film Festival in April! Congratulations to us all @ronbarba1… https://t.co/gBu3Vyh7nx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohevelynnn Take her to the park with us someday so we can walk the girls together! Bring Oliver and Joel too lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeed This is #fakenews, unless @kyliecosmetics changed this in the past 20 minutes or so... all it took was 2… https://t.co/CEGI6KVUoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANK YOU THANK YO THANK YOU LEAVE NO PAWS BEHIND for allowing this beautiful soul, precious Ollie to live out his… https://t.co/ZUyQNx5fI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComcastCares #mobile_Care wtf ? Again??? Hours out and no help from you? Lmao scheduled maintenance??]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are very accepting of deception by the Dems, Socialists.    You may not realize that God is in control.  He ano… https://t.co/D90qiMnTWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattapanviv @bigwillardstyle @bostonbikeunion @wutrain @bostonpolice @BOSCityCouncil Hearing is Tues. March 12 at 3pm!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChengduHunters could you imagine signing someone into the OWL just to play ball lmao #hammondgoals #ameng]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timothy will always have a special place for this reason https://t.co/Rt9zxPgYqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving through the canyons listening too shaesuniverse ❤️🥰🔥 @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/UAVkEcBbbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skberry64 @Iluvpuffins @Jkirchner12 @ChrisJansing @JohnJHarwood Way too many Pats fans are justifying it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got spoiled last night and was lucky to spend another evening with my handsome Mr. G 😘 https://t.co/leY5WrFY2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/N2XNEY0Vvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@life_of_boris @NoleNurse00 @TatrateaUSA @fsunole98 @DannyAller @sweeteabourbon @CarrieQ82 @Greg_Tish @KA_Carlton… https://t.co/seK4BrY3X0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate being up this late bc I can hear all the weird noises being made outside and I am not about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my room in my apartment is actually the HOTTEST room in the apartment. I’m always sweating, whatever the season is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday @MichaelJWoodard hope you had a great week doing what you love to do! Thanks  for your IG post so good… https://t.co/PvBaVFFziF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmoreno274 You must go to Mangos in SoBe and get photos with the birds that take shots.  And the fire and ice plac… https://t.co/n2oPkm5eM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4GISHandReedus @Moonkat1234 @Heidi_Eileen73 @Stef_Helen @HeyMo517 @AntoniaSchmitt4 @smoking_reedus @Cheryl_W61… https://t.co/jo0o40r3b7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auntiesophsoph_ Like the talent amazes me! 😂 but honestly this is a grimmey ass situation smh fuck niggas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's to strong women. May we know them. May we be them. May we raise them.  #internationalwomensday2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait to get back to Chicago in a few weeks!! My ❤ is in Chicago https://t.co/nRTCNCkusx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I CAN’T BELIEVE THE JONAS BROTHERS ARE GOING TO BE ON MY TV!!!!!!!!! #LateLateJonas]]></document><document><![CDATA[your standard green background photo to get the jist off NYC at night 🌃  #NYC #bigapple #citythatneversleeps @ W Ne… https://t.co/ZvOqZH0eKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone have that one girl in class that feels she needs to sit by you everyday? I do. I even walked to the opp… https://t.co/3Rafbevd8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland I solved ALL these problems.  What did you do today? https://t.co/pX4Zv1Lygs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students engaged in collaborative discussions about disarmament of terrorist organizations on day two of the SWFL M… https://t.co/pfpCc9nre7]]></document><document><![CDATA[the one that bring me back up when im feeling down. ❤️ https://t.co/bY8wmMqgvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Where did you get those statistics, Sean Hannity? It's actually 41% approval rating and 53% disapproval rating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerseygirl582 @FiveMeadows My mom’s have to be 50+ years old; she and my dad were married in 1963. We still use th… https://t.co/dSujNW8t1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know who needs this word but I hope you receive it.  https://t.co/ZwhG1sL8SU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mraspinall I’m not a principal but ... 1) don’t jump in too early, take time to teach. 2) You will need to make de… https://t.co/i29FklJiUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h3llh3ro @TwitchSings I had your set on in the background while I cooked dinner last night. Thanks for the tunes!… https://t.co/AVxBbO951Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words of wisdom right here about having a successful team. Take a minute to listen to @CoachPainter. This is what a… https://t.co/BHa88kc4Wg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with you am a big fan of his but I feel very concerned  because he doesn't need those political baggage he… https://t.co/EHjI0JZ2ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I Remember having no money sleeping over my ex house and Ma couldnt take me at the time, so she had to kick me out… https://t.co/q5dVFmKjT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I just saw Bohkee without a surgical mask and outside of the OR! @GreysABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[So smooooooth. - Drinking a Wake Up Dead Nitro by @LeftHandBrewing at @kumascorner  — https://t.co/2zrOqLjze6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw these pretty pink roses at Publix last night.  I had to stop and smell them.  While I was shopping my sweethe… https://t.co/iNYY5ps3Hy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macktastico @PaigeTurner62 @gdalton64 @WhiteHouse Doesn't look like any of these signatures . Close but not the sa… https://t.co/GszTnvFk1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Google currently resides in the #RestonTownCenter but is eying a move to a larger building at 1900 Reston Metro 🚇… https://t.co/Q9LUXk0w3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well this sounds fun. One more reason to not kill Bambi. @shadereed @SkyeJoReed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjaime95 @LauraGrider_ Misss you toooo! I am open the 12 or the 13. I will keep you guys posted if that changes. 😊… https://t.co/8SoMDBZPz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who are turn 22 before I turn 21 are honestly the most selfish people I know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti All the facts aren't out yet. As for me, if this turns out to be true, then I have to deduce that… https://t.co/mvtBD0izYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job tonight Panthers and a great job with the lady Panthers. Keep it rolling. Go Panthers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra She needs to look in the mirror, America is not garbage, however people like her certainly make it ga… https://t.co/7pNHtXKDJO]]></document></documents></author>