<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[A girl in the crowd asked  “Are you Adrian?” me: *yes* “I like your clothes”  me: *:)*]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Tarpon Springs Sponge Docks in Tarpon Springs, FL https://t.co/iluKhFoFtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brose_Brocisco @KING5Seattle Her provider only offers DSL.. girl that’s because all of your neighbors’ businesses are meth kitchens. 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexkidwell didnt tell say Wes was not looking long term or something like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mango manchild is on a tweet storm, he must not have gotten his tug and pull tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @CrackerBarrel, this is Lebanon, Tennessee. One tiny ranch cup ain’t gonna cut it for the house salad. https://t.co/XfbhbDJsBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShuntellaSpeaks The image attached isn’t available. I need to know about this great event.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great chest and abs workout tonight. Tried a new exercise - instantly a new favorite. #vanagetsfit… https://t.co/z374WVxEAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Umyfareenahmad @Dariathatsall @Justcause40 @CEThomson @GerrickKennedy As long as it get a nice size  platform.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Failure is a part of the process. You will not be successful if you don’t fail. Fear of failure limits billions.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski @realDonaldTrump Is that a compliment on the amount of work he gets done on the golf field?]]></document><document><![CDATA[U ever have to cough real bad while you’re in class and you try so hard to hold it in because you’ve already coughe… https://t.co/p4VeDSUYra]]></document><document><![CDATA[So today I took a pocket microscope and looked at all the TVs and monitors.  Turns out the pixels on ips panels loo… https://t.co/cjtm3Awk7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree.  #MAGA acquaintances who share my faith bring up superstitious aspect of association with Christian concer… https://t.co/GnjMRdUui5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its just you and me for eternity ♾ • • • • In Frame: Madelyn Ubalde  https://t.co/SbYwdiQKdR https://t.co/cri95F9VBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSLewisDaily "After each failure," "CONFESS" to Him, and those we harm for the work of "FORGIVENESS" was finished… https://t.co/SiNXvzHckR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Jay Campbell!!  #WCHSalumni  #1WC #CTEmonth #28daysofCTE #BusinessPartnershipsMatter #FBLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick delay before galaxy data reduction: quick ERG quick — block the Estimates ;-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec I seen earlier where Mr. Gowdy referred to Adam schiff as the three eye raven. I about lost my, you k… https://t.co/nDQmsAwYSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you never listened to 40 Funk- Post Malone, you should go listen. That is all for Ron’s Music Corner today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turns out @peta is in favor of involuntary genital mutilation of animals.   Weird stance for the group that didn’t… https://t.co/f6oGyJF8mH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe John Podhoretz???? I’m out!!!! I’m NOT starting my day with his argumentative, mean attitude on my scr… https://t.co/Q8MWPtNEqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking Evie for a ride... @ Travel Town Museum Foundation https://t.co/ERqFPiWMYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kwytiaz @CARandDRIVER @JohnPearley #IROCRaces were boring? Not sure you were watching the same races that I did. IROC ROCKED!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulsperry_ @realDonaldTrump BREAKING NEWS!!!  Mr. Trump has once again found some unknown right-wing internet hac… https://t.co/d8BrAlhqLm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjeaninemason GUuurrrL you were on FIRE tonight! I only hope one day I can get my acting skills up to your level. #favnewtvcharacter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonBaker @ShaunaBaker @TheBakerTwins @semouiller @SheIn_official So hot that ass is 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juanitawashere @bduty47 @PudLightLime @violasmart4 @HHS1DPU @rudepundit @RealSaavedra @AOC What does that have to do with anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisisweedies I don't vet everyone I follow or who follow me on a daily basis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett You @realDonaldTrump of all people would be an expert on hate and racist rhetoric… https://t.co/YSgifbsEi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus Heals the Broken-hearted🌷  With a Word, Jesus heals a man who had been an invalid for 38 years. Jesus asked t… https://t.co/WbDdUUV2au]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very even start to our 113 sectional title match. Dominic Savoca of Crestwood the quick footwork to escape two quic… https://t.co/gmwnyF31Na]]></document><document><![CDATA[A different State of the State perspective in 2019 compared to 2018. https://t.co/YV8E8BV8n7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connally’s lead trimmed to 38-35. CS’ Cade Kortan has been excellent in the 3Q. Connally calls timeout w/ 46.9 sec left in 3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Available soon, the new cover design to compliment the recent literary decision to evolve the story into a full tri… https://t.co/taTqO3kT1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremiahOshan That makes sense, and this is probably the “accounting mechanism” or whatever he called it earlier (… https://t.co/89V5hka6mU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harper_coach @jwfaure LOL...just down the road from Australia and New Zealand, I believe. Japan, too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @USPS keeps marking packages as delivered on the @amazon tracking, when in fact they have not been delivered. T… https://t.co/J4OStOA63Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier today, I watched "First Man."  It was brilliant.  Especially the soundtrack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sketch1984 I can live the rest of my life without another Tokyo Ghoul adaptation]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are the wines poking the ball out, they were the ones with the passion and the want to win and take the ball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyD624 @PatrickEaddy So, it’s Triple H who’s never beat Bautista. Got it.   Dave Bautista does nothing for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any time Gudbranson is forced to move the puck under pressure he’s folded like origami #TeamToughness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats!! Our team in #JacksonTN looks forward to having your team here this fall to begin our next five-year stra… https://t.co/QzPOiDR3U6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill Really happy for him! I'm not a big Kap fan, as a player (Seahawks fan here)! But, the man is unwaverin… https://t.co/81MoV33645]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TellyvizionR This is Amazing can't wait for #thefirstinning to get one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonlietaer A great way to celebrate #InternationalWomensDay Trudeau’s consistent challenge seems to be working w… https://t.co/le9W4AKnwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacitusPublius @clairlemon Similarly, Leftists are promoting the traditional racist stereotype of the Black Women… https://t.co/tqkCC4TKU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s so true - we adults need do talk less and do more in #Sustainability and #ClimateAction]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_kevstaaa Oh it slapped alright...slapped every hardcore ECW fan in the face again and again.  December To Dism… https://t.co/kybzjIw9n5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrTGIF LMFAOOOOO THIS CAPTION JUST SENT ME!!! Get off Twitter. Right TF now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eviephinslvr @tcrotwell @MelindaHoward4 @mjust126 @ms50trailrun A look of total relief 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leodudeman @whatmaddness February included several "official" luncheons which were way too boring to tweet about.… https://t.co/sikr1apBfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Telefèric Barcelona - @teleferic_wc in Walnut Creek, CA https://t.co/dhKGqFdH3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@refusabsurde @DeanObeidallah @docrocktex26 @realDonaldTrump Black=great, perfect, superior. Whitey is bad, evil...… https://t.co/pmURgCU3ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three pieces I'd like to conduct before I die: 1. #Prokofiev: Symph. No. 5, mvmt. 3 2. #Rachmaninoff: Symph. No. 2,… https://t.co/TaDWURuxCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima beat the shit up like Ike turner, check dat bitch like she got nike on her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missmayn Sadly it just makes me dizzy and sleepy.  But I do bake great brownies.  Or so I’ve been told.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg those weeds!! Call a Gardner @HGTV @HouseHuntersUSA @CastleHouseJT #HouseHunters #TheCastleHouseEstate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secretart77 @Chuyvega77 @Chadkelly_6 Yep- I sleep well. Speak the truth- live in reality, don’t be delusional.  Do… https://t.co/LYuK2MYuJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LavishChic @Ashlee_Rezin Maybe the home is no better than where they are now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenTi_GuLwisH khosh raheen aabad raheen Allah ki preyshaniyan dour kareen]]></document><document><![CDATA[if u really wanna know.. jesus has a mexican name but, only whites will argue about his ethnicity and/or complexion… https://t.co/9m3vAI14HQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arielkassulke Just saw them last night, I have to say @flor stole the show!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wore it better? pgatour @apinv @paulazinger @iamjamiefoxx #arniesarmy @ The Range https://t.co/7vEkKrevtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scotty_sloan @youngyellafella @IvankaTrump That’s fine at least they have an opportunity to make a living wage]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not gonna be happy until I’m my own boss. Shit takes time but im so depressed with my job and being patient.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just to be clear, if you're speaking out of your social location and telling me what I need to do to serve the… https://t.co/smV0rocSjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great keynote on orderly migration in a disorderly world starting now @perryworldhouse and available via livestream.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full time job. Part time student. STILL. CLAPPING. HER. CHEEKS. DAILY. 👏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my poll. I'm honestly curious and of course no judgment from me ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alek_Bittinger Forreal though man about Westbrook lol I’m a HUGE Westbrook fan and he gets the worst rap for it. A… https://t.co/MRjjNsIqem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dream and #REACH for the stars. If you miss a star, grab a handful of clouds. #WordOfTheDay #NormanVincentPeale… https://t.co/P0Q3dJzwbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't believe the swallow it. They are quite deliberately accepting this blatherskite out of fear of being outed… https://t.co/REsJNUqTnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell As a liberal gun owner, I find the @NRA compromised and/or full of 💩...]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y'all dont quit gassin up Steph Curry  with them Kurt Rambis lookin ass dunks. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todo Lider Narcisista.. Construye siempre un emblema que le represente. Trump demuestra que es cerrado y necio de c… https://t.co/AXnKhGaIjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnKiriakou @jeff_editor @xychelsea #RussiaGate https://t.co/xz1EmxUCrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nikki_0422 He burried the Deletion, before be got started... He must still be haunting from Heidenrich 🙃🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanuckSassy @skullmonkey7735 @edthegodless @LadyGirlPerson @kenserlore96 @NoSacredCowsGOB @HondaGuy4… https://t.co/9kLsgxDRRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleStraz Not much but it's pretty nice weather in Manhattan ny about 50 for February not bad 👍😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wfaa Taken out of context!  She said, “compelling, overwhelming &amp; bipartisan!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Week One: National Athletic Training Month ‼️  Athletic training encompasses the prevention, examination, diagnosti… https://t.co/zGJNdSXKoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bryce Harper really hit .249 last year and about to get paid 300+ M. I couldn’t imagine what he would be getting if… https://t.co/A16EwBnqrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lakers scored 69 in the first half.  They have 28 so far in the second half. And it’s the fourth quarter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidBegnaud @CBSEveningNews None of that monster’s voice should have aired. None.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confirming zero wildriverranch on the @PatriotOrdnance P-308 SBR and the primaryarmsonline Platinum 1-8x in a larue… https://t.co/CDmUef5ZMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow our @PCNHPatrickM today in Tallahassee for updates on are legislators efforts for Hurricane Relief efforts.… https://t.co/XVYNWwMnAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NofretPerez Ay santo Dios.... Eso es lo tuyo, nos contaron a mi y a @elmasvariado que ya no te fían, que pasas de 4 mil y no pagas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoBuzzJoe @JodyPorter @goodbeerhunting I think the theory that people are throwing them out and coming back and bu… https://t.co/x0ubiTbAZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Keep up the good work GOP !!!!  Her cage is rattled !!!!  You and your ilk are not welcome in America you… https://t.co/qayAPoK8wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paulina enjoying Fettuccine Alfredo ! (@ Gabriella's Italians Grill And Pizzeria in South Padre Island, TX)… https://t.co/D9q5DQn4Fz]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great thing the Twins are doing for their fans. Competing and lowering concession prices. Kudos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheClosedFist No offense but I hope your wrong. https://t.co/jeEMBa0FRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noah Syndergaard: &amp;#8216;I feel like I&amp;#8217;m going to bet (on) myself in free agency&amp;#8217; https://t.co/D0nqTGeAix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBlues_Biceps @DougRipleyODU @ODUBaseball That’s true!!!!! When will I see you at a baseball game though!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ClydesRides @mimee119 @rjprosr2020 @CaliRN619 @RosenbalmMR @ImabitcSumtimes @CathyCS @briantopping66 @colfer36… https://t.co/qiG1nW7n0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolsmith11111 Not sure if one should answer one "what about?" with another "what about?" Nevertheless, if the ob… https://t.co/wQI2Wp7Oju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bulouvere @KimStrassel @WSJopinion @realDonaldTrump @POTUS How can you defend your enemy? Didn't you know that he is a racist?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rip @LukePerryIII like I said earlier today - a little piece of me died with him ... https://t.co/sYDs5P4Qls]]></document></documents></author>