<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ethansaslater I’m sorry I made dead ass eye contact with you as soon as the lady scanned my ticket]]></document><document><![CDATA[bruh said “everything in Mexico is better, except for the cold showers” 😂😂l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yikesitspam @kennedyamara1 @PayneYasmine @PalayeRoyale https://t.co/KuewQByarK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@failed_q I was going to do the plasma thing. At lest twice. I’m not into getting poked by needles, but having some… https://t.co/JAp1I8ZKCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[***ACCESSORIES...ACCESSORIZE ....ACCESS-A-YOU!!! Accessories can turn simple to GLAM and glam to FAB‼️A~List Luxx o… https://t.co/g5LNdjrTDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[murder can be justified or understandable in certain situations but there is NEVER a way to justify rape or molesta… https://t.co/2r1fARnpPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SydesJokes @JohnPaulCline @Journeyingdave @Jpofgwynedd @JusJane53 @justtaffy @kayfreck @kcmwilson @KehlWindows… https://t.co/wNHwXBth2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edgar ran in to gas station with 1 minute left til they stopped selling alcohol and he actually made it 😂 shook]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marieosmond I would love a follow back. I have been a fan for years. I am a wife, mother &amp; grandmother. I am from  a big family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶Some Enchanted Evening🎤🥰 from the South Pacific Musical  Performed by: Christopher Berrios  Proud @pbcsd… https://t.co/FY2r0calU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now all Drake needs to do is drop some videos to a few tracks off So Far Gone and I’m happy. 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a fun game to play when you’re of heart attack age - I call it “where is my passport and why isn’t it where… https://t.co/FblqeuMmDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hoping Mueller is making progress revealing your collusion with Russia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you tried @epicbooksforkids in your classroom? 📚 It is a game changer!  This website offers free digital books… https://t.co/5HSJXD5doL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sshhmmalex @kbellar01 😂😂😂😂 Yeah, hats are a huge no no. Definitely reaching with this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToumsyBell @JackPosobiec For the last 40yrs Dems have used minorities to gain power.They have done nothing but pro… https://t.co/vWF5YfruCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee is the lifeblood that fuels the dreams of champions. -Mike Ditka  #kickingandscreaming I❤️☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every “designer” on house hunters renovation: ”so for your kitchen, I have a white shaker cabinet with brass hardwa… https://t.co/TKnk5Qsjhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt #throwbackthursday #2015 #fouryearsagotoday #meandmyboo #alabaster #boo #booboo #oldblueeyes #siamese… https://t.co/dfTAukac6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK MOMS OF FACEBOOK. I do NOT want to see your baby’s diarrhea. Please stop sharing things like we can all relate]]></document><document><![CDATA[The US has offered up to $1million for information about bin Laden's son  https://t.co/tEn961oIOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[In support of our brothers and sisters affected by the deadly tornadoes in Lee County, we will begin collecting new… https://t.co/r6GEZoWmgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all deadass let that shit sit there for WEEEEKKKSSSS and not touch it????? GTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluesformami @katrinanism I... hate that I thought... it was talking about the question marks https://t.co/Zetbyep4gC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MonsterMask is everything!! I’m not even sorry how much I love this show. I watch it LIVE. WITH COMMERCIALS. The s… https://t.co/RucEPIiJK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idrc but when they was out stealing other peoples men it was funny but now that it happened to Khloe she wants to c… https://t.co/60V6mJamOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[welppppp im planning too many trips with not enough money at the moment 🥴🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you like to visit the moon? I sure would.. and it looks like many of our students would too! 🌚✨ https://t.co/fYpuihCKfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friend 1: Why didn’t you get the crunchy peanut butter?  Friend 2: Just in case someone is allergic to peanuts.… https://t.co/NpUF4gRXmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starsegoviaa @real__vlp That was literally her face yesterday when we were all on her ass ☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadreTorres A las 5:00 les di su comidita hace 1 hora ,sólo esperan algo siempre ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @nytimes You aren’t calling them fake news, what’s up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[These gluten- free carrot cardamom cakes blondies are pretty tasty. Recipe is from Vegetable Cakes  I am interviewi… https://t.co/y8GJC5PtqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw an ad for #Branson while watching @WCTH_TV! Excited to see my hometown represented during my favorite show… https://t.co/3ZDdG6hPFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just chillin. Flight delayed. I see something move from the corner of my eye. #prettybird #bird #airport https://t.co/lrC6WfYa9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 5th.  #illustratorsoninstagram #illustrators #illustration #artistsoninstagram #womenwithpencils… https://t.co/HSN9BHMscH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love people from a distance. No hard feelings, some people just gotta be let go💆🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to meeting with @SenatorBennet and @SenCoryGardner from Colorado to talk about #dcstatehood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally. It’s a self-awareness crisis. 😐 ‘Can’t believe Dylan is gone, &amp; I’m next!’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep and someone always walk-in on me like wtf I’m doing lol 😂 https://t.co/2yYh91Puhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaamanthaCheyne SAME !! Let’s just get a condo there and move there together for the spring/summer]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a pleasure to meet once again with Mike Weiss from @SenRonJohnson’s office and discuss the importance of the… https://t.co/nNHZ9ThQnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[So true !  Get all the facts out into the open and let the chips fall where they may!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once, there was this girl in yellow. With her friend. His name was probably Joel or something. ..............  Toda… https://t.co/lG1xqWPgU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So mad that I went all the way to Dutch Bros and grabbed my ID instead of my debit card. 😖😖😖😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smh why did my little brother just add me on snap. Now that’s someone else i gotta remember to block🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arnold leads off the bottom of the third with a single! 👏🔥🥎 @athletics_pchs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting better with this. I be trying to give ppl time to redeem theirselves but like....I’m tired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intoxicated with the Holy Spirit!    Come to the @hiltonlax this weekend for the #ConsciousLifeExpo and experience… https://t.co/S7lKDhS9ZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm watching the #MBKRising LIVE and you should too. Tune in here: https://t.co/EeQdBPv0yV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kadieelmore @hotboxcookies Ugh OMG! I can’t believe they would do you dirty like that 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[League Night with my boo (@ Evergreen Lanes &amp; Restaurant - @rasturent_id in Everett, WA) https://t.co/WQYwgRYeZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump DUDE, HE HAS EVIDENCE! YOU LOVE TO PUT YOUR SIGNATURE HUGE ON EVERYTHING! SO, WE CAN ALL SEE YOUR… https://t.co/HBs6wHfSLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[five more stadium shows (in the us &amp; europe) for them https://t.co/kHt43z1200]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattCleveland33 @RandyPete Has to be hope until they play and see the product on the court! Hope is what they have… https://t.co/G4PVWqxk6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We can all be surrogate fathers. We can all be big brothers.” Barack Obama talking about the importance of mentors… https://t.co/xfT46IG4qp]]></document><document><![CDATA[POOR AMY ADAMS SHE HAD TO DEAL WITH BALE IN VICE AS HIS WIFE AND NO.AWARD FOR HER. HE PROBABLY.BLAMED HER FOR HIS L… https://t.co/XcqPAPvRwc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pebud2002 @60Minutes @JuddApatow It’s a tragic loss of institutional knowledge &amp; experience; &amp; a dream come true for Putin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VSALES Girl I know imagine feeling like that and, still have to take care of your kid lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mortgagerates https://t.co/zDJ0n7N2Vl Rates are still historically low. What are you waiting for? Let me connect you with a lender.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monsterscruise here I come! Thank you @carriestevensxo for my #evhgear ♥️ #monstersofrockcruise #vanhalen… https://t.co/OdVP29wYfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshiepino It’s not a matter of showing them off using social media, because I completely agree with you on that,… https://t.co/k0NIvGjCc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The good news is that you are staying open-minded to this new idea of things. You are opening yourself up to an awa… https://t.co/LCBxXDW7jf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shareably i never believed these claims until I used Dawn on a favorite T shirt that had  salad oil on it, worked like a charm !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In love with Josh Dylan aka Bill in Mamma Mia: here we go again. Can I meet some others who Stan?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheStylesFandom @Harry_Styles @KaceyMusgraves #iHeartAwards #BestCoverSong #StillTheOne]]></document><document><![CDATA[💎❤️ | bitches swear they pregnant 😭 . We became cool instantly , it was crazy , that whole weekend was lit tho 😩 we… https://t.co/H90DqLE9mW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier The media should also be held accountable for aiding and abetting a liar !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesley_jordan @LunaLuvgood2017 I’m sorry, dear ones 💕🌟💕 I hope things get better soon #StrongerTogether #LoveAndLight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeEspyMS I drove and walked by that area hundreds of times while attending college and not once,, not once did t… https://t.co/baKby9MHkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DepietroJustin  Follow me, I follow back all #MAGA #KAG #MAGAVETS #DEPLORABLES  #TRUMPVILE #TRUMPSUPPORTERS… https://t.co/FQNMegfjB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The weather is changing. Time to break out the knee brace. #oldladystatus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okWessler5 @ItoniLl @lwpcds @AsiaTater @krunalley @lulump007 @mymynags @Lexa_Merica @LazyMeatball @my3monkees… https://t.co/YAASicMQOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standing O to @MumfordAndSons for a kick a$$ show last night and for the #InternationalWomensDay shout out! &lt;3 https://t.co/Il4Xa0a3Oy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyschwartz Exactly! I ‘see’ her as very scary, one excellent liar and bullshit artist. She feels totally fake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lessons I learned while there:  1. Don't stop creating 2. Don't feel that you should sacrifice your life for a job… https://t.co/XvjuX8bNpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arkiegal411 @colleensteele09 @praisehymn1 @briansangel @BibleBeltDarlin @tnmynatt @TinaHerig @MrsRonnieM… https://t.co/tGb3MJuJLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best gift I received.. 16 years ago today is the happiest day of my life. I gave birth too the most important part… https://t.co/oWQT0Xw6St]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siempre que pongamos el corazón en algo, esa cosa siempre florecerá.     #televisasinaloa  #yolandadelacruztelevisa… https://t.co/uojspcKDik]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinaANDMaya Sounds good Carer got what he deserved as far as that goes it will teach them not to beat these animals!!🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[m: not mentally ready for class, would much rather be anywhere else right now, i think ive officially begun the che… https://t.co/mdGhZyYxNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not real unless he calls you “dude” as much as he calls you “babe”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonRFloyd I do agree with you. My elderly father purchased a huge box of the scented bags at SAMS. Ughhhh. Hat… https://t.co/XEwIbOTMXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews @Kris_Sacrebleu I was a teacher and i will be partying by the time this asshole goes to prison and ill… https://t.co/HXi1qQPxCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Amazon Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below   Cli… https://t.co/GjOI6lWYiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[After school enrichment. @Birney_CJUSD #BirneyProud #kidsdeserveit https://t.co/ZNQ0Cqr5mJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday this random guy caught me singing in my car on campus, then i walked into class and saw the same exact du… https://t.co/kGl6ImNXAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ginsburg said it best. “I would like to be able to take out my pocket Constitution and say that the equal citizensh… https://t.co/qnSTkz9qOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @CNN @MSNBC I’m getting a little skeptical of CNN‼️. Anybody else?‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catrinagallardo @JasonWiethe @ErikSzobota This still brings me an immeasurable amount of joy 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Culiacán, Sinaloa https://t.co/UtVcWWXfZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psyched to see this and unemployed. I unlocked $20 Rush tickets for @TheWoosterGroup's "The B-Side" at… https://t.co/yQeFXVDVrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is always the unspoken things that reveal the truth.  https://t.co/zizF9T56IE]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all the emotional laborers out there. I see you. I fee you. Tuesday PM mood. https://t.co/x4WBOASAsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hire people for where you want to be, not for where you are #wholechildsummit2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @melrobbins ・・・ If you’re waiting for the right time— THIS IS A SIGN. There is no right time, there is only… https://t.co/zMhpJ53pMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beautiful sunrise from outside our station. Happy Friday!! https://t.co/SvTVFDUbKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to work today for me🤪 and brrr it’s cold🥶 but it will get warmer😎 soon enough!  Today on my blog I’m talking a… https://t.co/nfZH6gPOKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ethio_Sunshine እነኝህ ብአዴን ሳይሆኑ አርበኞች ናቸው። Olf ከጌታው ከ tplf እንደተማረው እያጋጨ ነው። እግዚኦ።]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ladies and Gentlemen I give you he President of the United States   Who clearly likes thing about Pee]]></document></documents></author>