<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@CNN White people bullshit.  "Color blindness" is a shortcut to ignoring issues that plague POC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #SurveillanceState Is at Your Doorstep   #care2 https://t.co/qlWJUCxKRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RedSox All-Access continues live on ESPN! We’ve got player mics on during today’s @Twins game, incl @mookiebetts!… https://t.co/5RcHn9aPyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hodgetwins She is delusional. How about California Elections? How about non American voting more then once? How ab… https://t.co/0HFjLo56Vb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need an intervention. #Tetris #Tetris99 #NintendoSwitch #Nintendo https://t.co/ot6ryAo5k5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hesitant on watching the Michael Jackson documentary, big fan. But fuck I gotta see]]></document><document><![CDATA[@racoon_sa @ibyshire That is the best gift! Those two goofballs always come through for us. Thank you for sharing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Folks, this was a super cute/fun basketball thing that I didn’t realize existed before tonight and I loved it]]></document><document><![CDATA[First session on this shattered wolf calf piece ✨ @ Lucky Bamboo Tattoo https://t.co/ElSnCE4okQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Envision team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/3rcukwHwm5 #EMLIfe #Physician]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg, remember 2013 when we all used to mirror our photos? I should’ve thrown up a peace sign to really seal the dea… https://t.co/BVwCnqdnyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheesemouse65 @realDonaldTrump Can I make love to you? I love you wall..... we can have the best relationship....l… https://t.co/QKQVwS93yz]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're loving this handwritten note from sweet Devin.  God bless him 🙏♥️.  We're so happy to help send Devin and oth… https://t.co/n3sDUVlvyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, I’m about to double my rent and get less square footage. Adulthood is a scam.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump pledged to "drain the swamp," but lobbying firms have been one of the main beneficiaries of his trade policie… https://t.co/g8gRhd7W38]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WorkingClass knows what's up.  #Repost https://t.co/E0ydG1tUzi • • • • • • ⏩ Follow 👉https://t.co/E0ydG1tUzi👈 for… https://t.co/a0BRbhkMVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great @StribOutdoors profile of Alex Wardwell who does important work for birds and wildlife in northwest Minnesota… https://t.co/yrgmM8wy5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[you heard here first folks. maddie, lib &amp; i will be taking on isu when im on to getting my master’s degree 💃🏻🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ertgeologygirl will be here on scene snapping #photos of your #favorite #racers doing #icerace #ovals #gp and… https://t.co/snnrViJXgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely love this dress by @isabeldepedro the fabric holds all of you in and you’ll feel sexy and confident wh… https://t.co/qarqMpovEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theMelanie_ Not my fav - but Seven Lions remixed Sahara Love by Above &amp; Beyond &amp; it’s 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[We ate pizza together and called it a normal day 💙 https://t.co/Oi3bKu57ih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPaine10 @STabbytosavit @ProudResister And what about 9/11?  To be fair, there was one FBI agent, last name Crowle… https://t.co/urhaYwQwU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoniaSeccarecc2 Omg with the icy side walks in the background 😂😂😂😂 just imagine is she had slip 😂😂😂 we are covered… https://t.co/dxwu26bLPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anon2World I did see that reported elsewhere. This is insane. It is the whole point of allegedly being there. We h… https://t.co/NxDk51OrEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HezekiahWalker Hey tweet a Terrific Tuesday morning to you and your family]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hidden Pedophile Ring, corruption outside Detroit. Mind blowing. Repeat of series will air on Sunday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This finish though.... 😍 #pitchingmechanics #lovethegame #trusttheprocess #softballlife #spintowin #fastpitchlife… https://t.co/EcTDmXfHO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmajusiak89 @Rbluemner @rick_thd @sjain3472 @MattDLC1 Congratulations 🎊🎉!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Greys Anatomy is basically studying for my A&amp;P test right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[New today!  “Give Facts a Chance: a Global Playbook for Teaching News Literacy”. Can’t wait to check this out. I us… https://t.co/KL1KXy6Uiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we just take a moment and appreciate this tweet?!  👏 👏 👏 #EmojiGameOnPoint]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sokolowskia Yeah fuck Instagram and their haters I'm over it it's really chalked for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HELENLOWE0912 A 300 is 12 strikes in a row. Perfect game. Both son's have bowled one within a month. Their Dad is getting jealous 🙊🙊🙊🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows @DonaldJTrumpJr Schiff. Aspen Simpson meeting.  Standard hotel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think beetles penguins or trees  are exchanging soul ties...im just saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emporbooty I have a lady brain, it is smooth and shiny and wears red lip stick and sometimes a fetching gold purse… https://t.co/3EAtl4CXIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tonlee01 @HillaryClinton Yea she should be at Putin's side since she believed in him enough to slide him our urani… https://t.co/VjhPR4JEcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gun violence is a public health CRISIS! Here are five things the public needs to know... https://t.co/8NrLvEU0QF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt When you're down and out please tell someone. When someone trying to tell you something and they're s… https://t.co/5PlTL3BJtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day2, #7DayBook Challenge. And I nominate @afuahirsch ! https://t.co/krd1rrLJtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parke Heritage Senior Ben Lynk signed his letter of commitment to kick for the DePauw Tiger football team. Shown is… https://t.co/pWoQCIZxGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before today ends, I just gotta say that this planet has been lucky to have @CoachLV36 on it for the past 30 years.… https://t.co/b2TzqmVyUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohsocynthia This was her hair after the Burberry show she walked in probably...she just didn’t take it down. Pleas… https://t.co/CBEEck03fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Kind of like you saying only the people who support you are “REAL AMERICANS”, calling respectable… https://t.co/I8XwDPEZjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sacred_smoke @Cordicon Moral superiority...I like it. And that is how I felt when I used to watch Nemos. When I wa… https://t.co/CqC84VXZ4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[sister what foundation do you use???? IT DOESNT STREAK WITH ANY TEARS @caelynnmk #ineedit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoundOne14 @WillTrumpYou @HeidiM_67 @LeonWhi63670221 @tony_tonyt @akuscg @akvawe66 @AuthorLRiddle @abytw… https://t.co/bYEH233YFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ring caught a couple birds eating in the front yard and flying away. @ring #birds #ohio https://t.co/pmtQ25XihE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can y’all chill the fuck out!!! This is a face mask from a company called The Ordinary. It’s the BHA Peeling Mask.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exercise gives you endorphins. Endorphins make you happy. Happy people just don’t kill their husbands #legallyblonde #aintthatthetruth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes a 10 year old photo sums it up perfectly.  ....... #tbt #soldbyteammclaughlin #chicagolandhomes4u… https://t.co/Et4r4m3L7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is it. I'm gonna say it. STOP throwing cheese at your poor cats!!!!! The babies are fine, whatever, but these… https://t.co/wXRD3gKgOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recording https://t.co/96Ny1cEd76 tonight with @bluliner98 and then @SportsOTHP at 7-  DM me any Caps related or not questions ❤️🏒❤️🏒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mother of 5's death ruled accidental; investigation closed: https://t.co/T8QZOqwzyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why the feedyard and confinement hog model works. Why would I wait years for meat? https://t.co/4me4YrU7Qh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diiiiis liddo piggy.... #CuteShit @ El Don Bar &amp; Grill INC https://t.co/GRRVpUZdd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giving back and sharing your story...#ThisisAVID thanks https://t.co/dPmzP80fp5 for setting the example.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just flabbergasted @ how @Chicago_Police is conducting the #JussieSmollett “investigation”.  Putting out info that… https://t.co/P5pWV0lLBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oneato @greta I was mean and terrible! In my defense(which I truly have none) I was so mad at the President yester… https://t.co/nHXRPQysmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Never Delete  People  Cause None Of U Bitches Indemidate Me .I Will Continue  To Say Whatever And I'f U Feel A Way  Then Oh Well 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then #NationalMargaritaDay happened😜 #anhourofhappiness #cheers #salud #slainté 🍹 @ Maracas Cocina Mexicana https://t.co/pb2WcGBHtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WestCoast_Spurs @JanVertonghen god he’s so fucking dreamy. totally my #3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flying to Florida has never made my theory ring more true: when you treat people like animals, they act like animal… https://t.co/wF8yl5wzMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There’s just a real, thick, beautiful, cohesive spirit of solidarity that everybody’s united in prayer for the sla… https://t.co/JGM7nM2cmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sansanmario @Antyok @sydneemcelroy @verified That bio is next level narcissistic BS. I’m going to update my CV wit… https://t.co/Mm0dRmmNEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cc me dijeron que a pesar del fisico jlo cayó a sus pies por qué el la tenía a raya ...y si a veces una quiere a un… https://t.co/CocLDjJCcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix @OneDayAtATime So... what you are saying is I get to rewatch with subtitles? Yaaaas. Also, #renewODAAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna sleep in my own bed, in my own house where no one will wake me up making coffee at 5 am or doing laund… https://t.co/DpozMSLPp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucifansgroup1 Yikes! Hope the find out what's kicking up in the chest and help you get some relief from the pain.… https://t.co/bPKSsJZgYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[C o c o  💕 C a l v i n @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/N4Od79pJXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect Full Moon watching. Go outside! It the biggest and brightest of the year. 🌝#FullMoon #Toronto @ Toronto, On… https://t.co/XyEqgASbxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melaniejoly @marbleziptours @ChurenceRogers @TourismeCDN @cdntourism @Gudie @SeamusORegan @NickWhalenMP… https://t.co/1ZPPqhKSoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump CA should try to plan Forrest Mgmt before fire season. This year could be highly unpredictable, bu… https://t.co/4ndPL7WqqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed. There is a lot of racism in Mexico towards other Mexicans . It’s about time we start calling this bullshit… https://t.co/u2JXHv3RUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another good night at the plate for this girl. A few shortened clips of her 4 at bats. #16 #thatsmygirl 💚🐾🥎💚🐾🥎… https://t.co/kNmeH4Tgfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahmcelrath @peterdaou After the Kavanaugh hearings how can anyone think being the victim is not a winning strate… https://t.co/Zn0OkrrCqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ben_garrod @BBCEarth @UN @ChrisGPackham @BellaLack @GretaThunberg @NaturalistDara @IUCN @uniofeastanglia @biouea This is so terrible!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day party fun❤️! @ BerryhillElementary SchoolSouth https://t.co/RAox2sp1v4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go Joey Buckets!! Brooklyn is behind you all the way!!!  #WeGoHard #NBAonTNT #NBAAllStar3PointContest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn...just spent the last 30 mins cleaning up my Laptop desktop...it looked like a bunch of files exploded on it.… https://t.co/rrh7Ki4QGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HippieVol @beers300 @Shawn172510 @gr82btnvol @madsatan6969 @GTA_Redhead @DollyVol @Smokeyholler @gwoman9810… https://t.co/DRLMoZ5D3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caution I'm PMSing so I would be very careful with what you say......I could flip the... https://t.co/SJovpFE1Jy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deniseb65028372 @montalban86 @POLITICOPress She’s the Ron Burgandy Candidate. Put it in Flick Speak and she’ll say it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you would've work for Hillary after she allow men to die in Libya when she could've save them at least tried to… https://t.co/L7ESgojK5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitches on the move!!!  #torreypines #dayoff #lifeaftermusical #oldglobe @ Torrey Pines State Beach Hiking https://t.co/kgztzr7ZEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Capitalist, socialist, progressive. I'm tired of labels. I don't give a shit what you call yourself. Call yourself… https://t.co/38OVyaPF83]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you, as an expert on something like diet present at a conference that also hosts noted #antivaxxers i will now l… https://t.co/ze3sHscdDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceej0nes Their strawberry cream pie is in season again and we thought of you ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @ProvoEDU to post #7BooksILove (no explanation, no reviews-just covers) Each time… https://t.co/upCbRjL5Se]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the3Dbunny @ey_fields what if we made keychains one lanyards like this with the QR to link to their portfolios?!? Or digital badges?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aorticinkwell That’s weird. You’re just down the street from me. We drove in it tho to drop bby off at my parents… https://t.co/utATZamhxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dude. We’ve been over this before. You — comrade Donny — are the enemy of the people. #sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are real consquences @realDonaldTrump for the shitty things #Predators do, other businesses are suffering bec… https://t.co/yHQQc6ddRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uravityyy_ Me too! I’m also 23 years old, 5’6”, and the oldest of two siblings. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[**Game Update**  Due to inclement weather, tonight’s game in Granite City has been postponed until tomorrow night at 5pm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grace Eve (@Acute_Aphrodite) will be visiting New York City from Mar 4th to Mar 6th! https://t.co/wHk2y99Hy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessleblanc1981 So beautiful Julia! Once again another masterpiece from you. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got woken up by the dramatic ass thunder, &amp; now i can’t fall back to sleep 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr @LindseyGrahamSC @GOPLeader @JohnCornyn @RoyBlunt  Are you proud of your leader on an unhinged, sick… https://t.co/u8RxsecaVt]]></document></documents></author>