<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TueElungJensen @axios I assume his actions could now justify a firing w/ cause... but we'll have to wait and see I… https://t.co/oxoi4AkaOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[These girls are real troopers! 10 degree out, feels like -6 degrees and still have a smile on their faces! Hope the… https://t.co/iXv2E2iKPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super classic trance song by #tiesto #djtiesto #edm #dailydoseoftrance #feelstrip #plur #trancefamily #trancelove @… https://t.co/F365nXhR1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lymanstoneky @jbouie Of course you’re (technically) right, but no one really takes it this way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re: #Amazon, I think @RepMaloney just said it best to @AlexWitt on #MSNBC, “We would’ve become the Silicon Valley o… https://t.co/ESYFJayCWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another #DonnieBoy appointee about to "bite the dust"  in the Epstein pedophile case in FL? #LaborSecAcosta was one… https://t.co/Vt0C99OZnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The replies are much better than I thought they would be and possibly much better than they should be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @DaveVescio for communicating this to the world. https://t.co/62GVJcFn0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlippi72 @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews You’re another one in a dreamworld!!!  Wake up and smell the coffee.. Democrats… https://t.co/6Nm4QadmCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when, you’re part of the family! #IFLY #ramonisnotalone #benjaminesparza #CesarsMusicOfIllinois… https://t.co/6FuKUMEkFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me with my #Friends @mikesweep and @cjsingsforyou having #Fun at #Hadleys . They got on my level, literally. Welcom… https://t.co/chfr0edED3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CUAlum81 @BluejayLife Wish they would take the free ticket benefit away and sell those seats.  Been like this for years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Switching gears just a bit, I wish the #Royals would either wear their ‘85 powdered blues as a Friday road alternat… https://t.co/gNb7KzHqtk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever at @TheAcademy choses the #OscarShorts needs to be chillaxing a tad more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This issue came up again recently because of the pic of @BillLeeTN wearing a Confederate uniform while a student at… https://t.co/PtTKv4dTrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Greater Columbus Convention Center https://t.co/UimyLVe571]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s an idea: Netflix show based on the Coraline movie about the ghost children.  (𝚂𝚞𝚐𝚐𝚎𝚜𝚝𝚎𝚍 𝚋𝚢 𝚖𝚢 𝚏𝚛𝚒𝚎𝚗𝚍)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kidkerrigan @lawlkat @JessyWang_Blizz @Skirtzzz @Kachelle__ @Selenityy @TheCosmicCake @KiyeBerries @AliciaWinsTV… https://t.co/7DnLVgZAxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[humor right? Webinar? Oh, I'm sorry... I thought you said "winebar." | Weekend Ecard | https://t.co/dVVQwvYdCZ https://t.co/OARmrQ0rDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows @realDonaldTrump Allot of former and current US Intelligence Officials should be prosecuted.  Donal… https://t.co/tldgVtNTRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennLahmers @sukanya The Fact That you don’t crack up  laughing when talking about #RobertKraft going to a Massage… https://t.co/gRdA3YEus6]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Tener que pedirle a los R1 que no te hablen de usted es señal de vejez? Sean serios.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these triggered guys leaving bad reviews for @captainmarvel 🤔 https://t.co/50qqhcqca3]]></document><document><![CDATA[DTW --&gt; MCO (@ Detroit Metropolitan Wayne County Airport - @dtweetin in Romulus, MI) https://t.co/wFkgdfpFNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hullboydan She is a shameless liar, second only to Tge Huckleberry (and aside from the Liar in Chief). Even George… https://t.co/3BF0aSKnrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlgdrizzy @NBAYOUNGTOY @GOAT_vicc @fortheleaux @TommyHilfiger @PacSun @UrbanOutfitters @INVICTAeurope Ima still th… https://t.co/4uncTwVZUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“#txtshow: 10th Anniversary” begins @Kerouac_Project in @citybeautiful today at 3:00 PM!  Tickets available at… https://t.co/iXZjruBUoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man stuck to and believed in the process. Fly high my man                    🛩@Frank_Melgarejo 🛩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its not just the games...the training / practice side of team sports also makes it look fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianlilley I had a double one on Ash Wednesday! Maybe I’ll find some other fish and chips today. 🙂 Oh, it’s too l… https://t.co/R0WDNbfr9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ZVBO_ @kendrabrobbins @3YearLetterman @avagrace222 @ArianaGrande https://t.co/W7xcmzXpaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netanyahu praying for you PM. The Lord is watching all that’s happening to you. בואו נקם להיות נאם שלי אדון Romans 12:19]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re really moving through this thing this year. I can’t decide if I miss having a host or if this is how all of… https://t.co/Aiefza1Xs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VezoVezir @simon_baston Non en effet 😉. Je voulais simplement dire que ce que nous sortons est imposer à un autre taux que 8%.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinSmiiith False information, 1000+ kids would make the school one of the largest in the state. This would not… https://t.co/SHfvkhIZKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not looking for praise but man you don’t know what ppl are going through. If you can give someone a hand. Get back to caring for each other.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudRepublica4 @Steve_Pippin @TexaLonestar @MAGAFORALWAYS @JakeHighwell @JacksThorns @crotts_dan @WyattEa48022125… https://t.co/a3cTu2E6ce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shayleybourget Phenomenal song.  Can’t wait to hear what else you’ve got with the upcoming album🤘🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOAL Odessa High Maya Sanchez puts one in the net in the 60th minute.   Lady Bronchos are pretty much scoring faste… https://t.co/t5eOkAJ05G]]></document><document><![CDATA[damn it’s supposed to rain on Saturday in Pilot Point ya mi planes estan ruined]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilJackson11 still need his ass whopped for not drafting this kid! #Smfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trenton_wert @DEvanAltman Oh. I’m sorry. I sent Evan Valentines roses for Saturday delivery. Gotta recognize the boss on every holiday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love watching Austin City Limits,  because I love music. But I also love crowd shots where we see white people aw… https://t.co/fCtWt8s2O5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manifest your Gifts - Dr Myles Munroe | Steve Harvey | Denzel Washington... https://t.co/FIPXlMhdrp via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[ABSOLUTE. THE A MERI CAN WAY, LEGAL MARRIAGE WAY. NOW REMEMBER AMERICAN LEGAL MARRIAGE TRUTH JUSTICE JURSDICTION. A… https://t.co/lxZCaIss5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eyes were red like he was tired, I told him “sure I got you, what do you want?” He pointed at the rotisserie chicke… https://t.co/9KVXluMDpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL’s. LOL… https://t.co/HSP8Hwc3ct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld We don't NEED to crush them.  Just get them to destroy themselves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Los Angeles, California https://t.co/qVshyxTx2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tampas_Iceburg @PressSec I don’t miss the Press conferences. They are a waste of time watching reporters insult an… https://t.co/uHTrtjxdCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GSJ44 How would you erase a state championship? That’s something you can’t take away. I bet the small schools woul… https://t.co/sFq4t6ugre]]></document><document><![CDATA[no Hispanics. JD’s appointments by contrast looks like the United Nations, or better yet, The Kingdom of God. Grate… https://t.co/iurxZJt2XE]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you ever see your mutuals interacting with someone who said really horrible disgusting stuff about one of your f… https://t.co/sRpDSzlDJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulCharchian No hate from me.  He’s just a barometric quarterback where his entire ecosystem needs to be darn nea… https://t.co/AzGDlTLG1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leadership is not a license to do less; it is a responsibility to do more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beware the Twitter trolls people. Just got one named @hannahcunha1 trying to pump me for personal information. Fort… https://t.co/IHR385TTFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[More surprise visitors for #NASAsocial as we’re joined by NASA Administrator @JimBridenstine and Kennedy Space Cent… https://t.co/Tu1vfMnpol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamtheBullFAN @Chico923TheFan LA. Magic Johnson failed to get Paul George cuz he thought they were entitled to hi… https://t.co/ECqYTqF4uQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madeline is happy to be here today! @ Cordova, Tennessee https://t.co/z6K5fFOm4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SabiDaddyDoo @JerzeeReaper @SteveScalise @NRA @least Ur so Stupid,I misspelled ur name on purpose. Say it out loud… https://t.co/QDvl131cnq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The time something crazy and scary happens right next to my house in the Baylor bubble and no mass text is sent fro… https://t.co/Wn978WNZQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow Powell is hit no fuckin call as Wiz now lead 65-59 at the half. #Raptors should be leading by 30. Reality conti… https://t.co/OClRfiR2YT]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫Lovesick Blues by Hank Williams, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/fbtr3QIwWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenjaminMoser_ @AlSacco49 That division is tough, it'll be interesting come draft time and with FA signings. My te… https://t.co/io5B6bTrDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnjanuszczak @johncutlefish @usabilitycounts The first use case I read about was at a very large company... See… https://t.co/gmc1MnVwn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kristileenews Is it Workman’s comp if that server by Josh’s table doesn’t flinch?  Ha !🤗Holy Smokes that was close!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sakura is starting to bloom. 🌸 #dtla #losangeles #flowers #flower #cherryblossom #sakura #spring https://t.co/zjMGt82m5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyDiComo This is of course not at all the same as saying they are the team to beat in the division]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new keychain is in. Everyone should have this keychain. I have spoken #ruizing]]></document><document><![CDATA[DICTATORSHIP? ARE you crazy Nadler. I think you have your pants up too high.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldpeaches WAIT is there a workout competition app??? i probably need this in my life - which might not say amazing… https://t.co/4r7UnBf8YE]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of the accomplishments of all our faculty directors. Great researchers and great teachers - we are so luck… https://t.co/J1Xy5l0VvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travistritt @MarkPhialas That’s a concert we need to see. Make it a benefit for arts in the schools or something s… https://t.co/1VmFCQgHhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've never seen this clip before and I'm not sure how!!   #DallasCowboys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimpaquette @gift_4000 @28delayslater @kalichaudhuri @markbspiegel @scot_work @elonmusk @GerberKawasaki Kim brings… https://t.co/PPTiDmNutF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fort Worth’s Sweethearts do it again!!! @NCHS_Royelles GRAND CHAMPIONS 🏆🏆🏆🏆 https://t.co/yMXifXF4X5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The strongest factor for success is self esteem: believing you can do it, believing you deserve it, believing you w… https://t.co/RiMcAdII0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveHammActor @sweetishj @AuStar3d @ladava @Na0sGlass @KMFras @Angelab0424 @bdckool @biogeek7 @cookingupfun55… https://t.co/5HnN3bEZhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StuSource @MikeGrinnell_ Stu I sent you a DM! Let me know if you want to chat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only qualification for performances on Grammys was nobody sing on key. Dang where’s the basic talent?]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing I’ve learned? A dude can cry, have an entire mental breakdown  in front of you &amp; and still be lying lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner we all would win that so hell yes we should sue his ass. he has proven too be a loser]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump please don't cave in to the dumocrats.Americans want the wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[About a half a dozen @MarlboroHSinNJ kids earned awards and recognition #njdecabold #TheRegional https://t.co/bC5W1CHMip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FopItLikeItsHot @DwyaneWade They swapped already bro https://t.co/shY7RbqNsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ngalindophoto @reporterjulie @IsmaelPerezSA Y’all the suggestions, guau, thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JandFinthecity @Trumpbane1969 @AbrahamAlyzah @SONADORLIVESON @danny_buder @GhostOfTick @cancunbound2022… https://t.co/esLfLO4ZKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a lot of followers I'm trying to split a story around the world please follow and spread my story]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re-modeling a condo in Paradise. Not a bad way to make a living  #Floors #Tile #WoodLook  🏖🌞🏝 https://t.co/aOS4FwZBCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MandoV41 I live in New York, I ain’t got the space for all that...🤷🏿‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Downside!!! Real Madrid are prob going buy all of Ajax players at half time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loves spoilers SOMETIMES - NOT all the time. Today I revealed to myself the antagonist of #TheUmbrellaAcademy… https://t.co/nj10KdUmTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I look high here?!?!? Be safe on your new adventure with the Navy 1s1k.domo  ———- Enjoy the Domo charm and m… https://t.co/lMgyTkT489]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly nearly all football players should be able to throw down. Lmao y’all made of 99.99% of muscle for a reason… https://t.co/weTkXEwZrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill If anyone argues for Bane then this conversation has already ended.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking at the airport before 7:30 in the morning is an acceptable way to start a Sunday, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The Perfect Disguise by @dogfishbeer @ Growler USA – Gastonia — https://t.co/QktBe1AlfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Paid subscriptions to music streaming services hit new high of 50 million in 2018, RIAA report say… https://t.co/3PMzlKKrJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok last one then i’m studying. i have not had enough hook ups, i’m so lame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4YrsToday @FoxNewsisFakeN2 An asshole never looked attractive unless he's in prison !]]></document></documents></author>