<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Can’t find post pics of the piece I am working on just yet, so sharing the creative juices of others at this retrea… https://t.co/X2k9RnkH3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaFarkas  Can you help my elementary public school students with Virtual Reality kits on DonorsChoose?  We wil… https://t.co/GrCNKr84Xs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatiJinich My go-to airport candy bar is @SNICKERS. Glad I'm not the only airport candy bar indulger!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neosoulgirl49 @thejessicaraven @LorenzoANC7C04 Exactly how is your life endangered? Because of a condom in the gut… https://t.co/5onKObnusS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrzeszkowskiSLD @FMS_kraj Co to znaczy "dostęp do antykoncepcji"?... Chodzi o rozdawnanie darmowych prezerwatyw na ulicach?...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Franky frank is a duck dynasty fan! #frankyfrank #duckdynasty #duckdyansty #cat #cats #catsofinstagram… https://t.co/WvBaFrvdmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our besties moved to Kauai and we flew Alaska with our crew to be together when they needed us. It was the BEST tri… https://t.co/nVh83vN7hn]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLAY BALL!           @bryceharper3 steps up to the plate today for his first at bat as a @Phillies! We have more on… https://t.co/GA8MyBLqia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_CoreyL Agree. He’s horrible.  Please watch the new episode of the Shop with Lebron.  AB talks mad shit about Sh… https://t.co/m5GKrO6HEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning ☕ . . #goodmorning #hello #newday #reset #coffee #sunshine #judiskinfetish @ Skin Fetish https://t.co/zDv8T2OmiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Facility… https://t.co/O8yKfeKBV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart hurts for my husband today. 💔😔 Losing a sibling is a whole different kind of pain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know its kinda early but idc I saw montreal is having this roller skate event lets make it a thing “roll bounce” typa vibe #myvibe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiring a social media agency is a very important question that you will want to take time to carefully consider.  G… https://t.co/VwY3k9aL27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @realDonaldTrump The really dumb ones are the voters who keep electing these dingbats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ll be able to spot Rickie Fowler at the Arnold Palmer Inivitaional. Why? He’ll be wearing custom clothing and s… https://t.co/a3rZBFv6Td]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worked an overnight. Attempting to sleep annnddddd I have 3 fans on to drowned out my upstairs neighbor. Please wor… https://t.co/L5wuE0YeEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has #NBC thought about reducing #Days to 30 minutes so it doesn't have to fill it with highlights from the previous… https://t.co/pBygPDaRom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perlmutations She is the worst kind of human.  I don’t have enough words to describe how awful she is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peccaviology @Lady_Star_Gem @realDonaldTrump it's a tactic that is as old as time; divide and conquer! :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi Rey!! #AmordeGuela #JacksonAlexander #MyKing ❤️ @ Desoto Lakes, Florida https://t.co/1NEheeanrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I 🍓 U-Pick Season! ☀️ I picked about 5 pounds of strawberries and bought 3 bottles of berry wine from oakhavenfarms… https://t.co/BZD7fAhOrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynneedenise U know ZNH was a singer, actor, composer. She slipped in/out of character @ whim, for her own enterta… https://t.co/HG7munpr4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afinekimmie @tiffany_annx3 @FortunatoEddie @siggyflicker @DrJamesMercer @lilTNangel @LeeAnneLocken @Loubiegal… https://t.co/g2u8DVmVVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drivebyhardcore @dabstarlaurel @TRIVLBYFIRE832 I wouldn’t even buy one]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Caucus idea Parents Against Fascism.  Pararades, Dadrades, and Momrades United against fascism and hate. ✊🏻🙌🏻🌈🌹… https://t.co/rZKFAcTgtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessedriftwood1 You're pushing the line, not crossing it. I think you're currently inspiring a whole new kind of c… https://t.co/5v1A8vmL2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @foxandfriends segment about odd  courses offered in top colleges.  “Marx For Today”  @ U of MN “Unsettlin… https://t.co/et2jpcETz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Seditious_medic So... curiosity question. What was the final decision on the X5? I thought it was far too big but… https://t.co/mkPyRq5XGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Campestre La Herradura https://t.co/d3CyFYtwUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing surprises me about this deplorable man or his associates.  I just want to wake up one morning soon to the n… https://t.co/GkLLb4A9N9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattBednarikBDK @kara_ann410 Haha yeah it’s definitely a girl thing. I’ve had at least one wedding nightmare per m… https://t.co/lfxUeza0Mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only reason why the economy is good as because Barack Obama made it that way he did his job he worked hard and… https://t.co/mXytopB7Km]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robotviking Nope, I've been chillin on my day off before this insane weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmartosko @DailyMail @AOC #FL #600 Most people move to Florida for the weather. AOC’s mother didn’t become homeles… https://t.co/4IQxWU6koH]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone for me. I love and miss you like crazy my beautiful Bambi eyed baby! Talk soon. 💗, Your Stacy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost forgot what it feel like to get mad at a nigga I ain’t gave a fuck in forever 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiariWarrior37 hello girl!! Guess where Kobe wants to go for his 18th Birthday.... NYC🎉 it’s not til August tho🤦🏻‍♀️ lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[People in Miami don’t even speak English but drive cars on highways with English signs lmfao like what]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just finished criminal minds for the third time and now idk what to do with my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendanKayes I mean right? Interesting how that didn't make it into the edited version.🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanyLaplante1 @LucianaLamb Kkni Moncjoik k v noon oxen  i no only he hjjkbhojCheju:o]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are really some 20 year olds who come to class for the test and be like “I don’t have a pencil”]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Pharmacy Technician - https://t.co/epc6tMPLPG #Healthcare #SantaFe, NM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo I spent the morning with a kid with a broken wrist. For the third time. How’s everyone’s Monday going?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it weren’t for my sweet husband whose career is in manual labor doing hardscape installs for a local landscape c… https://t.co/la2aBMZazp]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can ask my conservative pals, I have never once criticized them personally on their beliefs. Come at me though… https://t.co/JVfW4P9jO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life, my loves, my family ❤️ @ House of Blues Las Vegas https://t.co/RYQATQNn0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@place_s @nearpod @OfficialDLDay My favorite Nearpod activity is a tie between Collaborate and Draw it! But I also… https://t.co/rdUyE7gguG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nueva foto muestra el fondo de la Casa de Máquinas de Hidroituango via @elcolombiano móvil https://t.co/WRRKL7NRsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPG36 @RealJamesWoods But they are getting the attention they so avidly need and we’re talking about it I’m over i… https://t.co/POiMRCANUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I FaceTimed my mom and joined my family for dinner :’) https://t.co/TFPFACDrR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucky_im_irish @LacedUpBreezy She really is tho 😂😂😂😂 and getting drunk in my bedroom ❤️❤️ let’s do that again !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IInir26 Exactly! People have different thoughts and reactions... I reacted to the tweet, just like everyone else r… https://t.co/I4mlscsS25]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red Cross CPR training going on right now in T204 https://t.co/M3Jg5PoZmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson is an ignorant sexist troll! I can't call him a man because he isn't. Women of America should boycot… https://t.co/Y39zFBZAJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'LL FOLLOW YOU ,  IF YOU'RE A DEMOCRAT TRUE! OR A LIBERAL TOO, OF RED, WHITE AND BLUE! SO FOLLOW ME BACK, UNLESS Y… https://t.co/qB5M8FRKB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBC why didnt you mention DUMPING of #INDIA and china worker bees on AMERICA, or any  other country can dump them?… https://t.co/LHyTpqyk5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Titans GM Jon Robinson has made significant trades during the NFL Draft in past years.  Will he continue that tren… https://t.co/3kyPe016GM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please follow the bpi folks. Amazing powerful imperative work!!  We are so honored to partner with the. @TCCGROUP… https://t.co/l1V4DIfjqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashaEats @MyVirtualVaca @VisitSanya @MadHattersNYC @always5star @suziday123 @FoodTravelist @TouringTastebud… https://t.co/gGilzXeIkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @SpotHero for making our parking so easy in #SanFrancisco ! @ the #RSA19 conference #CyberSecurity… https://t.co/Uz44KziBkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt to baby Wendla. Miss these ladies. #leamichele ha @ Webster University https://t.co/2u1fdOQP7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm honored and humbled by your kind words, sis. They came at the right time at the end of a tough week. Just remem… https://t.co/DucktEBEX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow...This time last year we were launching @mio on Product Hunt, and one year later we’re launching it within a Fo… https://t.co/8iA6BcWsfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaEdwards4 @CageyGirl1 @KellyannePolls I suggest YOU do your homework. Are you a proponent for selective law en… https://t.co/Q06SZGSUSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna write a book about all these men cus you really cannot make this shit up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day for a little joy riding + dress up. 💙🌈 . . . #sundayvibes  #brothers #momlife @ Tennessee https://t.co/7kCeaCC7T5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It breaks my heart my moms feeling so much pain today. Please prayers.. I’m totally heartbroken!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Very_Feline3 @LolyCruise @Crazy4TomCruise @mebranca @ZuzanaSuzy111 @lanaazzati @mametom1269 @KgwRo @joelledray22… https://t.co/Ce6p5QchFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The BestBuy Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  C… https://t.co/ID10HyI5O4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@avgnsdave Hmmm interesting read. Child care has always been one of my biggest challenges because in the Canadian F… https://t.co/g2jS41X9D0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom posted this on Facebook about her and my little sister lol https://t.co/DPaQQjHfW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaylexington The divide between work clothes and festival clothes is real. I have two closets for a reason, and I… https://t.co/KP11AFbYcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tapps6anorth @SportsDayHS @ihss_dfw @LSCSN @dfwelite The Liberty Christian vs Bishop Lynch 5:30 pm game is Boys, not Girls. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnA_USMCvet I agree John. I see this nightmare going on &amp; on &amp; on. 💔💔💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TraceyGambill LOL...it is. But we’d do anything for that number today!! Lucky to have had 80+ in Key West 2wks ago. Pure Heaven. 😎💛☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am not ashamed.  I am getting surgery asap.  They are facing attempted murder charges for the FGM.  I am speaking… https://t.co/dhCm3dKtWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolNevada What’s embarrassing is the major lack of pack loyalty from our own school’s barstool tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tweeting so future me appreciates the fact I get to laugh with friends and see comedic legends on a whim. It’s the little things. ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bakitza @CodeNewbies As someone who remembers the 1960s, I would not hide older experience, just condense it. Act… https://t.co/q5jyv7fbNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely!  When it comes to marriage you don't keep certain things "secret". If I were in the lady's shoes I woul… https://t.co/vA9jDFM9CQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrKarlButton It was a good year. It was the year I panicked and lied to guardians about being friends with @mega64… https://t.co/uu7R0ZwM2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready Or Not (@ Broward Health Medical Center - RCU in Fort Lauderdale, FL) https://t.co/SUVeskqPdg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@builtfoesuccess Thank you! Yes, the AM/PhD at SSA. Also—I can’t attend Beyond The Bars this year, but I hope to co… https://t.co/MGXa1NU5V0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estudiar, trabajar, ser foránea y el futuro de México está acabando conmigo 😩 but it's worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let the 90s night celebration begin!!!! #Disneyland #disneylandafterdark #scootnscope #darkwingduck @ Disneyland https://t.co/gdBqh8WO7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikarayrayy This is motivation for me to do the same ugh 🙄 it hurts so good!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofacouch813 @HillaryClinton @realDonaldTrump Actually @sofacouch813 @realDonaldTrump has made life easier for me.… https://t.co/Up4lDaquU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, now I can't stop listening to @ArrowsInAction. I'll see reality in a while ✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is this Ellie if we actually let her hold our phones 🤧 @RonTheNomad]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great day for education in Houston at the @Hispanic_Forum Career and Education Expo! Always a pleasure seeing our… https://t.co/e1D4N0ykq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayla_strelsky up and up is the best diaper brand!!! hands down! wipes too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching my days of leave go by like... 🙃 • I'm happy to be home for a while, but I can't wait to get back!!! I mis… https://t.co/9St0h7djh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msinsulindpndnt @Birdmischief It's horrible. No one should be forced to pay that much for meds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burger &amp; truffle fries! (@ Charbar Co in Hilton Head Island, SC) https://t.co/zcRMFGcwLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UncleJoeGTA @kidparker @DeathByLipstik @SPHCOMMANDO @JohnDerringer @zipbolang @MarkClarkster @RpmacPaul… https://t.co/Erst680noR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doctors are wild yo, patient pulled out her central line and the doc ordered restraints 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahMartin05 I’m not asking you on a date, I was showing u the place butttt OKAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Diary,  on Valentine’s Day 2019, my dog ate candlelit oysters with me.  I didn’t even know this was on my bucket list until now.]]></document></documents></author>