<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Carter taking Mark’s stethoscope has to be the most touching part of this episode. #ER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmoraleswrites @SFerika Agreed as long as it is used properly. Great point! #ContentChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shoobe01 @ftrain Oh I most definitely remove those. Disaster waiting to happen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from _rezyms  -   @MiaMariaDoll @ Harlingen, Texas https://t.co/LhEoQ5zdct]]></document><document><![CDATA[#7booksIlove nominated by @amybanyadams to post covers of 7 books I love without reviews or commentary.  Here is bo… https://t.co/gtJX5y2j6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[but you think it’s okay for you to judge others and call yourself a Christian? it doesn’t work like that homegirl 🤭😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trisha_Brett I watched it with my grandma. And she’s like “see! This is why I never let you spend the night anywhere.” Wtfffffff]]></document><document><![CDATA[We loved having @raven_solo at campus today! Thank you so much for speaking! 💙💛 RSC Senate Executive Board https://t.co/H7qqk4QyYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevekraske No Baseball stadium Downtown.  I already don't go down there because of parking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baseballcrank So says you and @SpeakerPelosi how about asking #BorderPatrol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with people who lift you up, not tear you down.  ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ I'm constantly inspired by the strong… https://t.co/11cwlry3ZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katrinasdc @mtharnett @realDonaldTrump Obama the Racist Divided this Country]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas lawmakers revolted over White House plans to tap Hurricane Harvey funds, and Sen. John Cornyn, R-Texas, said… https://t.co/jTeXI7CcQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[my boyfriend booked me a spa day for my birthday and I have never cried so many tears in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, being dramatic  Haven’t worked out cause I feel like poop &amp; now I feel like a potato haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga just sent this to my 13 year old daughter who has more talent in her pinky than I do in my entire body. H… https://t.co/XjYk1fNmKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__miirandaa__ @CarlieKaku Dude that makes me so sad. What a scary world we live in 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[I binged @willam’s beatdown til 3 am. I had a midterm to do this morning and now I’m at work til 5pm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh fudge🤬  Bad enough I'm having Victoria withdrawals because it's season is over on PBS d  BUT, but  Now during th… https://t.co/w25EmOv1vZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check this out! Another great song is available from my dear friend, @CharlieHines1 ! Take a listen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is just NO end to the corruption!!  "Massage parlor owner sold access to Trump officials, Mother Jones report… https://t.co/ZqKLc8AuYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cost$ of the outfit?  Since DoS is the only one who buys clothes while you embellish the cost to distract from her… https://t.co/ukwWM02ooV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so very excited to share my student's work at the Teacher Talent Pipeline today 🦁💙💛 @armendariz_ms @ccontive… https://t.co/4uyIEExcLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bpiw_big @ChuckRossDC @realDonaldTrump @DailyCaller The deficit suddenly became no big deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the thing, no one, and i mean NO ONE is just going to casually lean in for a kiss...like SOMETHING is missin… https://t.co/h7SPdEPsXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[shoutout to all those couples out there for vday, but most importantly... shoutout to us single bitches!! we’ll be alright. we got this 😤💘💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will try and try until i  succeed 💪💪 #Postselfieworkout #dontgiveup #nofilter #offday #fitmom #fitnessmotivation… https://t.co/0JEL376zep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our band is better than your band. @MasonMBB &gt; @DuqMBB  @gmugreenmachine #masonhc #GetPatriotic #masonnation https://t.co/jtfvR7MInd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for sharing this! #ocsb @ocsbindigenous @WestbrookMarina @DaphaneSandre @klewis_prieur @deb_lawlor… https://t.co/01zZF0r1J4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Talkmaster @THEHermanCain That would be nice but I doubt he will see one day in jail. Of course the rest of us wou… https://t.co/aDSgnzjhvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gator_Fan_Jenn @cirrus1701 @cincy_browncoat @TheLarkyfarken @RantsOfIzzo @JayRFifteen @nolefan01 @VekaFitzfrancis… https://t.co/7OTWyzleet]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you need to fake a little rest, there’s #undereyefillers for that 💁🏼‍♀️💁🏼‍♀️💁🏼‍♀️. Gives an instant concealer… https://t.co/qjKWldfZmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar Voter ID please. I only want people legally eligible to vote to do so and only once.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachariewilson @bluebottleroast Haha hours later the genius phrase "small-bladdered nomad" is still bouncing around in my head 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estou fazendo uma compra agora na Amazon e vão entregar com frete grátis amanhã que é domingo. E mais, ainda tenho… https://t.co/t9QJrvf11r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, I definitely recommend checking out Tiffany and her besties blog 💕 also head over to @Bookwormgram1 bookstagr… https://t.co/gS9fvGk6z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part 2. In case anyone was wondering what our friendship is like https://t.co/TL0e8ZN2nR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterSupport What happened that Utube Videos sent to Twitter no longer have cover photo +Titles  Also when sendi… https://t.co/oDbEAbYgd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying some much needed sister time ❤️ #sisterday #soup #sushi @ Little Tokyo of Maine https://t.co/dWL2zHD0qB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldn’t be surprised if I had some kiddos show up in my classroom tomorrow🤣🤣 They did NOT want to leave me and e… https://t.co/mVEm0hxTAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleycantstop_ I can’t breathe..  damn that made my night.  Was this recently???]]></document><document><![CDATA[1879 "Exodus of 1879" southern blacks flee political/economic exploitation  1882 1st US college cooperative store o… https://t.co/zzhDkpwMIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um okay so my friend takes really good photos of me thank u https://t.co/njmv5BHkrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland If Mueller publishes his Character Assassination Attempt on Trump doncha think Trump is gonna get Death Threats too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last chance to get a great deal on ski packages at @winterplacewv during CSA Winterplace Club Days! Last club day o… https://t.co/jhNjAvAPYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenMusings 😭😭😍😍 thank you Karen! Couldn't be happier to share a book birthday with you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theJagmeetSingh How can anyone acknowledge the harm it will do and then APPROVE it? The NEB needs to be sued and e… https://t.co/1n6qwoU55l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Louie living his best life today! #minigoldendoodle #babypuppy #louieslife #sunshine #michigan @ Ada, Michigan https://t.co/iDYuGJDO0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_kathleenkerr I do too! 😂 I kept staring at Corey and he was like "QUIT LOOKING AT ME" 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s hostile rhetoric against everything Left can be a source of extremely accurate information concerning his own plans and actions. 🌊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you EVER seen anything more BEAUTIFUL?? #gorgeous #breathtaking #nature #Earth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ I have students who are just wrapping their heads around the idea that anti-slavery doesn’t/didn’t mean a… https://t.co/ecrU5cXJeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you stand with the #DarigoldDozen? Do you want to support retailers who work hard to source their products from… https://t.co/zj5ZKSZFul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephbump I'm so sad I didn't get to take a nap today.  Thanks for taking one for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me encanta la gente que va por la calle sonriéndote aunque no te conozca❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyD I live on a Naval Air Base here in California. There are Military families living in houses with mold, lea… https://t.co/z5y1zHM4vn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GametoGrow @matthewmercer Hi there!  I am a Board Certified Behavior Analyst who games weekly. I’ve worked with ki… https://t.co/6BwDhuvTcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[PROTECT CRIMINAL ILLEGALS!  ICE ARRESTED 3 Undocumented Immigrants W/ Criminal Records — for DUI, OWI and ASSAULT —… https://t.co/undAd7SaZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanMcGowan @MSten37 @RICenterFreedom yes, it could and I have seen that play out more than once. I'd be hard press… https://t.co/laTqr1hsFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fedagntmulder @MarkFerenchik @ohiodotcom Thank you...I was going to reach out to you on this...time to talk Friday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bittersweet @swankywineguru last day here ! We love you much boo! Some #Champagne @duckhornwine Discussion,… https://t.co/kKGmXLyVgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarthJada_ You won’t stop this and even if you do it’s for a divine reason. But you got this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker Thanks for voting for infanticide today.  It's good to know where you stand without any camouflage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That beautiful moment when you suddenly realize, you were once so blind but NOW you can see. #blindnomore… https://t.co/akbVUqtUnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: R.Kelly pleads not guilty to multiple charges of alleged aggravated sexual abuse of underaged victims.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christmas Cartoons And Jokes | ... to: Top of Page , List of Christmas Jokes ,... https://t.co/xGGFGOPNPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Moon and #Jupiter @WYMT @AndrewWYMT @brobwx @KelliWYMT @PaigeWYMT @JimWKYT @ChrisWKYT @Kentuckyweather… https://t.co/i2wVIKKkwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexLJanin @AOC @nowthisnews And fracturing the Democratic Party which helps the conservatives so bravo !! What’s… https://t.co/8SmdSpZrBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 your eyez only will always be in my life... my children will know of j Coles wonderful music]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed listening to this panel of inspiring women today.  #IWD2019 Thanks #herhalton for a great event.   E… https://t.co/ofMPCdtTPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing! She is not only a great artist, but a wonderful student and high achiever! 🎨 I’m so proud to have known he… https://t.co/MJCLnRkQEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BodhisattvaKat @ronda_rl @uurrrraaaa @co_rapunzel4 @mydoggyruss @Maryc1850Sadler @tribelaw @RepAdamSchiff 😂😂☹️ sure did.😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think #InternationWomensDay should be celebrated more and Mother’s Day less. That way even more women can be cele… https://t.co/h7uLYgSXMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsaRenaeLifeee When I said, yeah, I just didn't want it to come across like I was forcing you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifewithshar @neuroticjomomma I’m in SW MI but we would sure have a ball wouldn’t we?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UWF_Baseball @GulfSouth @CBUBucs Live feed went out before the end of game 1. Any chance it will be back up for game 2?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carolyn21_t @venicetheseries @crystalchappell Enjoy the day!! https://t.co/fKwNsOKG9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 15th Birthday to this little beach bum of mine 💙🥳🎉🧁 https://t.co/dlWfGkapic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t expect loyalty from a traitor. There are no accident in life. Stay tuned big revelations on someone credibility]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyvalentinesday #love #nails #friends #family #blessed #ilovemylife #ilovemykids #ilovemypaul #thankful… https://t.co/PcUNWdeU6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took a few hours, but Nope has finally forgiven me for putting ear mite treatment in her ears.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished the first season of #Luther on Netflix. 😱   If anyone watches that series, you know that Alice is the… https://t.co/0AnFbzNiWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CBBUS2 if these idiots are stupid enough to drag Dina along with them then Dina should win .. would be a wonderful… https://t.co/BYqbO6CCje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder how Mr “common foul” Kenny Mauer would like to be commonly fouled by Harrell??  He’d break him like a twig😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaAndDoug @gbnewsdotcom #whoyougonnacall restoration.hardware #dashiellkingbiehn @ Woodland Hills https://t.co/zwzI7cnyit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan holds the blunt for 3 years but if I hold the blunt for more than 3 seconds all hell breaks loose. Noooo sir p… https://t.co/ktcNKH0jCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@presentefect @JamesShawJr9 Know that a lot of different faiths used to teach that "our way or no way" doctrine. Yo… https://t.co/1yQf7RGPjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fairyadventures I mean if someone lives in an apartment they could just step outside and smoke/vape in front of th… https://t.co/r0wFGpqz6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiljanaZJovano1 @celestialthread That’s good to know - I hear about people writing things in a year and I wonder h… https://t.co/jbGDZn8G5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlanetTyrus @foxnewsradio @GregGutfeldShow @FoxNews @foxnation @KatTimpf BTW I agree with you and said the same th… https://t.co/PtWM8XRMqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s an A&amp;B song that I love but I forgot what it’s called and well it’s hard finding a song without words lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aromaladyellie @TaraSlySays @HogwartsMystery Looks like I found the Harry Potter thirst police. If we want to lust… https://t.co/Z3PuP63gYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tu felicidad está dentro de ti, no con alguien, no en un lugar no creas a otros tu sentir, vibra con Amor y datelo… https://t.co/DIlsT6bndq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching someone vibe out to their favorite song is such a wholesome feeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh how u not supposed to be mad at someone who completely wasn’t there for u in your worst times ???? Lol suck me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roseandlune I need the real set and I need it now. I have 11 days to get right with the songs he’s neglecting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me recuerda a la placa de Crónica “Murieron tres personas y un boliviano”. #TuitLamentable #HumanFail]]></document><document><![CDATA[She got my green eyes and funky shoes down right!  #adalynashley #meems❤️ #meesandpops @ Moss Bluff, Louisiana https://t.co/2qrzU5vhw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@me0wzaaa @LostInAmerica77 @CarmelaTheKitty @profitnothealth @KemMinnick Let’s not pretend that almond milk is in a… https://t.co/VGISQwZHtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniellee_sloan You're going to be fine, Girl! I believe in you and know your path will come to light. :)]]></document></documents></author>