<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What a 💥⭐️stellar example of Good Sportmanship‼️❤️  Thank you Dunlap! @IHSAState #DoWhatsRight #AddATude… https://t.co/vMaKNde31a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump It must be nice living in fantasy land. Come join us in reality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlenaMaschke @airfrezno @Sammy_Roth Is LA also going to replace their Kern County power plants?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the first year I did not watch the Oscars.  Last year I saw less movies at the theatre then in any year I c… https://t.co/uNNdftNMRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of y’all weren’t at Reilly Walsh’s 1,000th point game and it really shows 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my last time peeing at the Toyota dealership my client works at today until I can go home. Shoutout to the Toyota restrooms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t ask for better weather this early in March. Absolutely gorgeous day for some baseball! ☀️⚾️☘️ https://t.co/0EfPf7rpfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I'm watching a medical drama and they shock systole I'm done. No second chances. https://t.co/HANsmz9Afo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJuanVargas I’m not a constituent but live in SD. I’m incredibly disappointed in this tweet and your take. Calli… https://t.co/N1ac6irJCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Air Chief Marshall K said on India Today  he’s ready for round 2 And started talking about this like a boxing match. Wtf.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProtoAngryBird @AnnCoulter Take all the money from the rich but not from rich politicians like Nasty Pelosi she is rich and have a wall too]]></document><document><![CDATA[“freshman Kadie Hempfling had 11 points.  Hempfling's well-rounded game included a team-leading nine rebounds, five… https://t.co/LKBsKprVmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dem Candidate Claims ‘Short Time’ Before City Is ‘Underwater’ https://t.co/YonRgTD8T0 via @ConDailyPost]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lawler says he'd like to run it back with Askren and do it again. #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[As most of you all know, this year has been challenging to say the least. This morning I received this text to my w… https://t.co/pbH3S9RwEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StellickSimmer I’m personally not thrilled they couldn’t do one move. Not even simmonds? Last I checked Calgary ki… https://t.co/e1cmGlcZhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ChrisHatfield Maybe. I doubt it. I mean if enough young folks are gullible enough to believe all the free stuff g… https://t.co/8ojtxQTc1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[That jaguar singing... I ain't never changed I like lemon pepper on my humans wang. 🎼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skating and smiling: Two of my favorite things. The Hidden City Derby Girls in the Zevely Zone https://t.co/IaedFzW6bK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsiaTater @DoingRight1 @go4itbas @leftovergravy @sherrynron @TrumperSeaney @MissILmom @TomExposesLibs @tammy_maga… https://t.co/Z3eIZp4w0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFromCranber What did Chavez/Maduro do in order to ensure “compliance?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovBillWeld @realDonaldTrump Yes it will America is essentially broke with a 22trillion in bills how can we not be… https://t.co/x8ZyICM0af]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProcterGamble  Wiped out: America's love of luxury toilet paper is destroying Canadian forests  https://t.co/7msMkG9VTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottRomportl @melaniebricks @Bucks I saw that cool jacket at the Bucks Pro Shop on Thursday. They were selling fast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Recurre a la descalifican personal y al insulto el que ayuno de ideas y conceptos es incapaz de construir una prop… https://t.co/W99bYXgeLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never have the same level of confidence in life as the people who call me just to put me on hold]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end of the day, I know I’m boyfriend / husband material &amp; im content with that]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Carolina Hurricanes wearing the colors they stole from me. https://t.co/B3CrN1p8pL]]></document><document><![CDATA[NHL Trade Deadline Day! Will the Bolts make a move? We’ll hear from GM Julien Briesbois this afternoon, then live from Amalie Arena at 6:20!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t had any time to ink log or even read many comics lately but happily the crew is still at it: https://t.co/HwATBzzf1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @fctucson for having us out this afternoon at the Kickoff Event. It’s going to be an exciting year! @ Kin… https://t.co/Ql7cqT5Jxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarthBlount47 @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @EricTrump @IvankaTrump I still wouldn’t vote for him. 🌳🔥💨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissBrookeHaven What's wrong Brooke talk to me bb..please get lots of rest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meltedpotmama @NBCNews That’s what religion produces. The Bible actually teaches that religion is bad. Religion killed Jesus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeerLeagueHeroe I think Hitchcock being honest with this team publicly and being annoyed with their shit game afte… https://t.co/ucFphy8YjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sis I have spent the last 3 hours applying for better day jobs! 🙏🏼 well I have a good day job but I need something… https://t.co/CatxGKZRYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[All you @Twitter haters, I had contact with @MarthaQuinn and @MrJonCryer today. Yeah, this Twitter thing is pretty cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF Memorial Spotlight Remembering Thomas R. Carley Sr.  December 14, 1945 - March 8, 2015… https://t.co/YaG3eDBJLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitcoin will never be plastic... bitcoin will never! Ever! Have to go to bed because it has to go to work! Neither… https://t.co/uUWkwRkFrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krazycy Always Stand! I went with my Best Friend a few years back to see @asiageoff and @yesofficial in a Theater… https://t.co/6PVQ03J6jc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think my fave thing about this shitshow is that there has obviously been a body double.  It's pretty hilarious an… https://t.co/ibBoIjVNBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cam_Redd04 I bet if I went through your iTunes I’d say that about some of the stuff you listen to. I don’t have to… https://t.co/fvepO03dJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CReynolds__ @MHubeM Of course, I had to compromise and include some red. #LoveAndHonor https://t.co/moD1f0FGH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obianuju @JessieJaneDuff So true.  It pains me to where the church has gone.  There was a time excommunication wou… https://t.co/pyD4XLeEtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckGrassley @SenJoniErnst @RepAdamSchiff @RepCindyAxne   Was anyone, other than @realDonaldTrump in the room for… https://t.co/LQBuZzOUUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheBestThingISawToday was these two Kdg boys using their imagination playing football on the whiteboard.  Loved he… https://t.co/RY6iGU9047]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bgdavis Same w NC team a few years ago man. It’s amazing how much these guys love each other. My dad always told m… https://t.co/X84YxwOW0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reinhardt @R_U_Football announces their spring practice game will be Thursday, April 11 at 6p at Ken White Field. Hope you can join us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A PAT bus slid into a house on Seneca St in Uptown between Forbes &amp; Fifth. No injuries and home is vacant.… https://t.co/xgUCowii26]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now, THIS is a NATIONAL EMERGENCY @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @VP @mike_pence @LindseyGrahamSC @SenMajLdr Toxic ‘Foreve… https://t.co/Fox1sEfxsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up. miss Danny. A lot. It's ok... Dang. This is always just gonna be there...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at AMC Evansville 16 - @amctheatres in Evansville, IN https://t.co/gxZ0ZJ8s1y https://t.co/qbGDf170D1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micheenelson @CityNews Michelle what’s the highest the wind will reach in mid town area #annex #forresthill #rosedale area ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule The more time for Mueller, the better, although he is ready to turn in his final report. The quest… https://t.co/eAD29dt0Wv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisgeidner But very careful wording.  Never authorized a recording is different than talking about it, and sayin… https://t.co/O9T3cDMGQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamaalStokes Preciate you Maal!  I see yall cookin! Keep it up boss. #RamNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pop Punk fizzled not because of some cyclical musical genre thing....  Pop Punk fizzled because Facebook replaced i… https://t.co/rBg9DDOoor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnschuhmann @WolstatSun Only Dinwiddie and Lavine have missed more big shots than Kawhi this season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do all of us really move the headset off one ear first to listen?!😂 this thread got me dying]]></document><document><![CDATA[this lady at the bar bought me a shooter bc both of our birthdays are sunday but it was prob one of the nastiest th… https://t.co/ds3s59c9qf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving a little after-shower gift for the next guest.  Hope it brings a smile. https://t.co/0XybNmvAcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Pittsburgh!  I was enamored with the @NeonMuseum in Las Vegas. Here’s a sampling of their stunning bo… https://t.co/Ho7KTPSdIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForecasterEnten Though you can track how an MC shifts over time if you’re worried about change...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I still love Emma Watson with the love of God that much and she got manipulated and hijacked by Hitler to have… https://t.co/3UWTBELwS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Friday of mandatory OT for the next 4-6 wks 😡 before all you accounting people @ me I know you guys are going… https://t.co/KMxcvAg23P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DierksBentley Nobody, I mean NOBODY, is more excited to see you this Saturday night in Omaha than I am! You’re my… https://t.co/LopmNA5LbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday night session. #winterfest2019 #ink #penandink #hardinguniversity #artanddesignmatters @ Gatlinburg Conventi… https://t.co/Ny7wtfs0AK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido @MariaCorinaYA @DrodriguezVen @Pontifex_es "Siento compasión de esta gente, porque hace ya tres días que p… https://t.co/w1n8ubwFgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovernorVA Your still a disgrace. Step down or get knocked down by the people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you complain when you serve, stop serving until you get your heart right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is way too short. Always tell your friends and family you love them.... you never know when they’ll be gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SudburyHomebrew @FlyingMonkeys @DrunkPolkaroo @david_buist @linda_lballis @raeraegck @SOBeerBoys @ottawahockey… https://t.co/vpgQJ6hwoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassandraSeven I do. I agree with her.  I think this is a smart  move to protect her Caucus from going too far too… https://t.co/iSqBDpcELE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LonghornNation please follow @sdave903 and welcome him to the best #Longhorns Fam on twitter. #HookEm 🤘🏾🐂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWeezytheDon @Nwerner08 100% agree. He was pretty straight up on that one]]></document><document><![CDATA[An email from @diecast2 directed to @chrisrtxv regarding Hasbro Pulse. This is peak Diecast. https://t.co/QIuNFYs7Rq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darth @chrissyteigen New @Twitter board member. https://t.co/zox6aCNZRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I lie by myself or by him who send thee, before thou,,,?,,,I can't find one,,,damn,,,righteousness,, https://t.co/u5Qvac7zRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou I'm not a Bernie fan unless he wins the democratic nomination. Then I will support him 10 thousand per cent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should listen to a show from a few years ago compared to now and just listen to how arrogant you are]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is #amtrak's fleet getting to old?  These 183 passenger may think so.  "Amtrak train with 183 passengers on board h… https://t.co/rkj9GTOb0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TianaTheFirst Remember this fact of history !! SOCIALISM does not care about humanity at all , it only cares for i… https://t.co/ufT8iEzFwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@electroslaggg @DoorDash_Help a bunch of drivers disagree with you: https://t.co/koSRJmlWLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where does Petro get his twigs from?! I’ve had high school relationships more stable than his sticks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’ll be a long 6 months without this goofy fella around. Thanks for being a brother to me, take care my friend❤️ https://t.co/ZvbmQJYtLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last nites awesome sunset from Silver Lake. All kinds of weather going on here. @CBSLA @KNX1070 @KCBSKCALDesk… https://t.co/FdlzPWLEcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelOsteen @JoelOsteen Hey...Good Morning! Hope you and @VictoriaOsteen are having a nice week. Prayers you and yo… https://t.co/pp8gPZ0JGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been wanting to try oysters on the half shell for a long time. Today I finally got the chance, and they weren't bad… https://t.co/D1uXaT4lzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tar Heel fans who is y’all favorite Tar Heel to play? Mine is Psycho Tyler Hansborough and it’s not close]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @BizNasty2point0 we’re trying to take my kid to his first hockey game and we’re looking at going on the game in… https://t.co/uZIZ3QTqOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lowandslow see ya in a few hours... 🤘🏻 @ Doylestown, Pennsylvania https://t.co/LKgZOg5KRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning and #HappyMonday my a.m. crew. @sdeebocane @KPRC2Britta  @KaraSewellTV @jasonwheelertv @wfaa @News8Daybreak… https://t.co/xsIiHydI9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pot_incorrect @iheartmindy @JacobAWohl If you are scared of guns just say so.  If guns scare you don’t buy one.  I… https://t.co/uIpSKnPT7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle how was your ride in Orpheus?? Said Hi in convention center and did you feel like”A Rock Star for a day”??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Red5StandingBy9 @SallyAlbright You seem to be focusing on corporate and other industry lobbyists representing idea… https://t.co/1YOIAzZ36A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaggerJames_ @WWE @WWERomanReigns @WWERollins @TheDeanAmbrose @USA_Network Your brother is pathetic 38? better off using his ✋😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got Bless Ted, and Texas! Like many true Texans he wasn’t born here, but got here as soon as he could!]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 3 @CCHSHoops_ leads Tyler Consolidated 76-35 in the WV A Region 1 Co Final.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you guys get mad when someone snaps you back saying   “Wait what did I say???”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh gosh, how I love this book. You can also pre-order a signed copy here: https://t.co/gsXK9ik7fJ]]></document></documents></author>