<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaRage Agreed. Dont throw more wasted time at him. Not worth it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorCantwell Attack, attack, attack ...Stop the hate.  @SenatorCantwell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conspiracy time.....the SB was fixed. Had to generate a big upset for the AFL (AFC)....allegedly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherNation Unless I can claim Fergie Jenkins, who asked me once if I could talk when my dad requested an autograph of my hat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Exodus by @SweetWaterBrew @ 39 Acorn Dr — https://t.co/51HZVl0YFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[lebron to the lakers is the worst sports decision in history don’t @ me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 Courage if and when he is successful, stupidity when he doesn't!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlomurray @TheBlackChannel @MichaelEDyson @KamalaHarris Yeah I see that now. These 50 and older activists need to… https://t.co/hP4WdEubOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Gentleman's Relish by @lonepint at @craftgrilltx — https://t.co/jCq2BmPQQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scifijunk @Jewelsquest Any complaints about Common Core MUST include quotes from the standards to be proven as a cause of concern.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maness89 @NBAOfficial All time clipboard smash though gets 5 techs one for each all star]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonnoxrevanche @BarbaraCorcoran is one of hundreds I can think of.  That wasnt much of a challenge #InspiringWomen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idea 5: a splash pad...we run hot and we’ve been asking for one for awhile now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wbuxtonofficial “one of Marc’s major rivals” is a lot of words to say “Ferrari.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[If every kid who wanted to be an astronaut, became an astronaut, we’d probably be to mars by now]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just met the gentleman responsible for designing Steve Austin's Bionic eye!  Btw, he liked the ink. #Kenner… https://t.co/L25Uzd2kcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@titopuccettic @DIRECTVSportsCo Asprilla y Falcao..no hay debate...los demas galaxias de distancias.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UberEats This is why it’s hard to put trust in you and your drivers. He’s supposed to be a bike courier but says h… https://t.co/HXEmzA45Sp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ @RepMattGaetz Did you sit down with her and discuss  the situation over a bottle of something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Probullstats Did he use a @badboymowers to get back to his Hotel last night? Best @PBR event EVER]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is something that so many of our listeners are having a hard time with. In episode #119, we discuss how if you… https://t.co/LCyRZ7nShp]]></document><document><![CDATA[💱LEMME’ HEAR YOU SAY!💱        ❤️ Me Some @iamcardib https://t.co/VVI1v6Zk6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[There were more passes on that possession than in Grant and Johnson’s tenures combined]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TekCharlie @prpltnkr Dibs on the vendor hall. It’ll be a room of tvs printers and iPads. Each tv Video conference… https://t.co/dSDVUXMaQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cujorulesdtown9 It's no STL, but still pretty cool to see the Dayton area well-represented. Even more so when Impa… https://t.co/VY6HwCHwqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saint Valentine healed a damn blind girl, so I’m sorry babe, but this decadent box of European chocolate and dozens… https://t.co/5LNDC2ZgnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first @DenverSUG of 2019 was a great success! Thanks to all who came out. https://t.co/FgkOFMnS5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnburke I believe / hope in our lifetime we'll get to commuter public transit by sky. Meaning helipads in NJ/LI/… https://t.co/xRPDqj6T2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES JULIAN!!! NOW LETS GET TWO MORE AND POUND THESE PRETENDERS INTO THEIR PING PING TABLE TURF.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The redline day song reminds me of my girlfriend 🙂https://t.co/VCooKf2yCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AShihipar @nytopinion @nytimes The opiod abuse crisis affects people of ALL RACES and ethniticies.  All demographi… https://t.co/ZXQG8tf6UN]]></document><document><![CDATA[DM Me for to ⭐️SIGN UP⭐️ for #thefitlife30 🔹First 10 People TO SIGN UP receive a $20 Discount!!!👈🏾👈🏾👊🏾💪🏾💯 ⭐️STARTS… https://t.co/dNyM4pmrT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GhostPanther Did you hear the NPR piece about the theme from Black Klansman being based on Hendrix's interpretatio… https://t.co/l3xt5Q5cO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump No, that is a lie. Finishing only 1 section. Quit lying, cost will be more than a plane… https://t.co/RgFebDq6FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[A huge THANK YOU to all my coaches for the countless hours helping me get to 3rd in the state tournament.… https://t.co/SF2xG6hJvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why sign in laws that would kill babies. You will someday feel the pain of those babies, if you have a conscience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zachary_Cohen @SenatorCardin @ChrisVanHollen @rachelkaras THE GREATEST STATE IN THE UNION (besides New Jersey)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juanma_rguez Juanma no se trata de injusto goles que fallas te los hacen y eso le pasó al Real Madrid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megynkelly @seanspicer Come back home, I am sure @foxheadlines could work out a deal. Fans were disappointed you l… https://t.co/90uunSqyZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who can forget this proud moment for Crooked Hillary, Obama, @DNC @TheDemocrats ? Peace with @realDonaldTrump is po… https://t.co/etrdvaGiMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bruce_Schaller Yea it's a little Strange how much they hyped up getting rid of cars when their business is only go… https://t.co/N4ei3dyAUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TobysMom1015 @KatBarrell What I actually posted. Really wish there was a preview for IG via twitter.  Also, just t… https://t.co/OGR5In5Xgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is off to a great start...we’re getting even more snow after a record setting February! #Lego365 #Snow… https://t.co/gLVysycdnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that Bill Dickens is not longer with us. Hacksaw becomes the snappiest dresser]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rardk64 Yeah I also said like everyone has a different favorite game in this series. It’s really fair to not like… https://t.co/UOjlAOp5JH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump enjoy your day in Vietnam before Cohen rocks your world you fucking crook!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s Mavs vs Heat game will probably be the only game D-Wade get booed at.  #2006neverforget #GoMavs #DirkNowitzki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSL_AlexCabrero @News3LV Hello my brother!!!! How’s it going? I knew I sensed genius in town!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanGraca Just like @BigOShow I wear @newbalance gear, and own zero Nike gear, although my kids do wear them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrhVenezuela @daoryebba @xxT1KExx @Noralex06 @MovilupPolitic @Juanpalic1 @maruvilla @_Gabbyta_ @MyrianeLibre… https://t.co/nPlCFMovY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The band playing when their team is on offense isn’t that big of a deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what they say about chicken skins... • • #Repost @rielhouston with get_repost ・・・ New to the Happy Hour Me… https://t.co/6pwbRcEhGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍳🍔 #MySurpriseMeMeal "Humphrey Pete's", Brownwood, Tx.🥗🍕  ~May You Be Blessed With Enough~  #LoveOverHate… https://t.co/mkBulLurQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is total bullshit false advertising and I can’t believe @jack allows this to happen.   Twitter is a greedy bas… https://t.co/2QS2jk7vv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imashton_ @nard___ He from out west and scared of some hot sauce? Poor baby special ed omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ve yet to have your finest hour. Radio, what’s new? Radio, someone still loves you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s honestly insane that his Oscar clip is for lip-syncing Freddie Mercury poorly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I get a tattoo, it's gonna be of Aristotle, Bach, or Barney McKenna.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arkellsmusic @globeandmail I read all of them and I found them all short on foresight.   🇨🇦is much more ✅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chipsy231 i thought stage looked like waves.. thoroughly enjoyed oscars shed a tear when Peter mentioned Kathy]]></document><document><![CDATA[2.4 million dollars a year. What's the exchange rate in Rubles these days? .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @realDonaldTrump Remember there's ppl whom are haters, no matter what they will always be haters, n ha… https://t.co/YBeb84iCTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delainmusic thanks to @brianslagel  turning me on to you guys I'm your newest biggest fan!! Would you please follo… https://t.co/OhpzfM3JIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sun is up so you can now see how significant the damage a falling tree is on an Upper Providence house.… https://t.co/YKNjBPHvZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure next week it’s gonna be fun to watch cable news every night... #nothingburger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d @KarlaDeVito How do you know the numbers? Are you asking everyone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LazyMeatball @jjauthor This will force the Republicans to compete for votes in states they usually ignore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HydymaeS The tall one looks concerned and the short one looks amazed. They'll make a great team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extinction allies checkpoint at worst Alliance checkpoint at worst or best. As soon as possible thank you God bless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have an excellent donut shop near where we live @CJDDonuts. Here was their take on heart shaped donuts  for Vale… https://t.co/95GnWbLgWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Orioles I love this organization even though we might lose 100+ games again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did I fall asleep with my phone in my hand and one sock on. That trip took a lot out of me and the madness still isn’t done yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/8/2019 - 00:29 Temp: 48.2F   Hum:  87% Wind: 0.0 mph Baro: 30.005in. &amp; Falling Rain: 0.00 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeWml7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was just informed tomorrow is Family day.  Then it was further explained that all 4 kids are home from school tomor… https://t.co/lI8uFdRSIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Benghazi ain't going away!  U have no right to criticize anyone #ClintonCrimeFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews He did not try to throw a coup...he talked about if the 25th amendment could… https://t.co/Y74uTNALWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when I go to Puerto Rico and see my sobrinos that don’t know bout  me 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse President Trump's border wall, space force program, and his huge tax give away to millionaires and bill… https://t.co/SKPPu5s6xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Widely read historical literature suggests we learn about ones heart by letting them speak. Why would we stop peopl… https://t.co/cxPCAcTTbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five days since I laughed at you and said "You just did just what I thought you were gonna do”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Now that the shoe is on the other foot guessing justic is not so important to her anymore!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LedyardNFLDraft For sure, you were in and out quick last night. Hopefully for good info or good film time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteSikora1 @KatBrezler @camillerrivera @fightfor15 https://t.co/Mw1Sxh7ykh  https://t.co/x3rMgflaC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crackdown any reason you lock your games to 30fps in cool that isn’t a flat out lie?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GetReady #NewStuff Check The #Profile #Link 3 #Shops To #Shop #TheaJ #Music #Vocals #Talent #USA #Australia… https://t.co/04CDNpGtsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great discussion, one of the most interesting conversations around data security I’ve heard recently. Real issues n… https://t.co/CR3HJBjwV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewGooden @Big12Conference @Phillips66Gas There were better photo options, person from Philips 66 gas. https://t.co/0z2gvUQFB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if that’s the toughest question you have to answer today, then life is good! See you soon, my friends!! #btcfs… https://t.co/P7qaCF2lpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol at work bored as hell 😂 #workchronicles #bored #work #nightauditor @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/J1lLgVU9ES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge Congrats to @SJA_hoops on there district semi-final win tonight! Congrats girls! #gojags]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skovatch Oh yeah, totally. I remember when Dragon’s Lair came out and that was the only game they had that week (m… https://t.co/sfTutROiLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[BE the FRIDAY DIFFERENCE today.  Make that POSITIVE phone call home today.  I am pretty certain that a student(s) m… https://t.co/pHcP3096Th]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscars watch party 2019. #oscars #goodtimes #vivamexico #roma @ Pasadena, California https://t.co/b5LewB67Jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Real_Cackman @CarmellaWWE @RonKillings @WWEAsuka @SonyaDevilleWWE I think that would be a good match, too. But I d… https://t.co/chbXSIcM8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sex robots could be transformed into killers by hackers, security expert warns https://t.co/96vaAAA30z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to freshman @Justin_Schaff12 on his first collegiate hit today against Albright College! I👀U brotha! Let’s… https://t.co/8VPer1jvEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[esse lightroom cc ta com o workflow mt lerdo, ae @AdobeBra arruma essa pa nois. Cade o layout normal meu parça??? https://t.co/KThvcrDdqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra They can all dish it out like no tomorrow and more but they can’t take the truth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So true! Funny moments that remind me of why I have the best job in the... #comedy #lol #smirk #amusing https://t.co/agkmVLOpdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet another predator priest -  McCarrick(spelling?) Now known as mister! It takes a flood of sexual accusations bef… https://t.co/dcH2OS5nP7]]></document></documents></author>