<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Join the Fidelity Investments team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/WPtf7ojG3r #Westlake, TX #Finance]]></document><document><![CDATA[2020 boxing olympics is cancelled. Because Eddie Hearn will have signed all the amateur fighters by then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Night Shift Brewing, Inc. - @nightshiftbeer in Everett, MA https://t.co/TNiu9Q2yzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Dan Dakich do color commentary of the Wisconsin vs. Indiana game on ESPN https://t.co/5sMnBvRQcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Crazy Bowls and Wraps in Saint Louis, MO https://t.co/0lOoajBTkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mmercado2333 I dont think time of confession should play a part in it. Nor do I fault them for it. I just think th… https://t.co/vQGI5fXfLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReidRavin @Angiologist @faznet @docmrjaff @VIVAPhysicians @VascularNews @EVToday @VascularSVS Auf Deutsch geschrieben]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone at #searchlove is interested, a few of us are at the bar watching Champions League. ⚽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hqtrivia That was amazing. Thank you for your service, @ScottRogowsky. https://t.co/nyLSAOLnnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 49% Off Haircut at Rachel May at Eve A Salon and Spa https://t.co/fS4F4IpSZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoItWithFlareon Isn't he my mom is not even a wrestling fan but she likes Pharoah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myteks @NicolasMaduro Exactemente lo que haria si no esperaba invasion americana. Que disfruten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5eyedsnoop @KamalaHarris Yes but after you have to defer the loan it doubled and you are able to pay mostly intere… https://t.co/D6iEoz4GAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hai_vee It’s not an invincibility cloak fellas. It’s just the safest human transporter ever produced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The A’s are really doing a wooden Khris Davis bat giveaway...  Handing out wooden bats to everyone in the stadium s… https://t.co/IRAsbBCpfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy recogiendo recetas para preparar con Maduro  🍌 en todos los estilos. Gracias por su colaboracion. 👨‍🍳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safe_its I can’t remember. I do recall my brother saying to me once “remember when we were kids, how it seemed lik… https://t.co/0U9UjqSTMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Chief?  You got to make this happen faster.. I'm about to lose it.. and have to go to prison for t… https://t.co/tHjyebUtGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@9AbbeyOZ @createstreets @41Strange There’s a residential building immediately off Rock Creek Park here in Woodley… https://t.co/jrTxo3T0Sn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dukeblogger Yep. Did plenty offensively to get it done. Defense was not good. Just worried that even with Zion the “it” factor is gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow morning I'm joining @jlengstorf on Twitch and we're going to add user authentication to a @gatsbyjs site l… https://t.co/S2kWKqKHPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxFriendsFirst    I thought the groundhog did not see his shadow JD ??? https://t.co/GFwfpcxeVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceciliasotog @senadomexicano En serio los creen tan imbéciles? Tanta ineptitud es normal?  Y no será.. Pensando ma… https://t.co/Xm9xf0KEFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottBarrettDFB @evansilva @BradBiggs Except he signed an extension and publicly stated that he wanted to stay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photographing Global Mashup 1: Bollywood Meets Global Roots Blues, for Carnegie Hall as one of their neighborhood c… https://t.co/GGSwdeakTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwiftOnSecurity @SteveSyfuhs @moulidorai Don't get me started on CardSpace (I was the Product Manager).  Is was a… https://t.co/yKF2eOkZL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[18:48 Temp. 26.4°F, Hum. 60%, Dewp. 12.6°F, Bar. 30.32 inHg, Rain Today 0 inch, Wind 139° 0.6 kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The angriest Republican in Hollywood: how James Woods became a MAGA martyr ' | via @telegraph https://t.co/MgjUBvSfbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday women’sday they surround and empower me! @ Harbour Island, Harbour Island, Bahamas https://t.co/17pwN60OG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putin said they didn't do it.  🤣😋😋  Russian hackers targeted US think tanks in Europe https://t.co/StCQCzORhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamWolpert1 Is Will Smith backs out, he probably backs out for good reason. This worries me terribly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astroleek Very wise and mature stance to take. Those who don't show love are the ones who need it most. Stay blessed. 😏👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't fucking sleep on this. They're playing some shows this weekend stop by if you can. Let's evaporate into one s… https://t.co/JIoHB6Hfkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life has been boring lately I need to jump out of a plane again, jump off west cliff, or something to get my adr… https://t.co/kuMBgbbT2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@s_colton Exactly. So can you see why people get a little paranoid with DeeTeeFortyFive when he is siding with thes… https://t.co/CtLU1C86QO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was pure gold @Benaskren @PatMcAfeeShow cant wait for ben to armbar @Digz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markhughesfilms @ilyseh No you are just proof that stupid people fill Twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final in 2A Sectional at Tolono, GCMS 58, Central Catholic 53. @SportsWjbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dfsblazeNBA Have you decided if you’re gonna play tonite? Just curious]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need so many things i think i don’t need #35mm @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/yGhnZfatHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grown so much these past few years. Definitely a major passage to my life story since I’ve started this LA journey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good win Tar Heels, Duke is trash juice. @ Killeen, Texas https://t.co/Svv7Giz8qS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShelbsssFaithhh And someone is always mean to me when I’m always nice. Smh 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elaprise Lol. I know Keto is a diet but my understanding of it stops there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still trying to convince my wife to name our kid (when it is time) Jimmer. Dude was absolutely unbelievable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_bonafide @safelydoingless @ecoonr @ShawnLRalston @IritMd @PISCE_LDI @Rsbeidas I went last year! Very good. I… https://t.co/whjQ1vrxHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Banana3Stocks Saying that if the bear trend continued in stocks, AMZN support resides below $1k? No I don’t regret… https://t.co/9xxa6Qteep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join Ibotta to earn cash back rewards on everyday purchases. Sign up and get up to $20! https://t.co/7NV89hDtex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another ride home with absolute f***ing #WhiteOut conditions 🤬I'm so sick of #Winter enough already #FU 🖕🖕🖕🖕🖕❄❄❄❄❄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willsommer You have a gift for finding this stuff, thank you for your service]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiguelFuller @RadioHolly I don't know what's going on with @ScottTavlin but it's not a straight guy thing. I'm loving the JoBros new song!]]></document><document><![CDATA[14:59, continuing forward through "Everybody Hates Christian Laettner, @lpresti45....? https://t.co/Wk9tKg1BIG spon… https://t.co/eR5CbSt15r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Gone Away by Five Finger Death Punch on Amazon Music https://t.co/r9A5DNX4u3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 2019 #FoodService Forecast will be presented Thursday 2/28/19 at 9:00am at the @FishnickFSTC in #SanRamon… https://t.co/0PT940mYts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackAftaThis Could also bring up the point of Michael Jordan being a great GM and drafter of players because he wa… https://t.co/8tzlj90Yyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cody blaske's Keyblade is the The Emperor's New Chivalry, equipped with a crown keychain. Strengthened by altruism.… https://t.co/6W6sIQnYhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drkknight_ @YiskahTweets @CNN It’s not my kids I am worried about.  It’s  yours and every other person who feels legalizing pot is ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if anyone would've cared if it were black boys who said that Michael Jackson molested them after he had be… https://t.co/EKyIHiPzJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettDieselberg “Average BF for a person is around 20%. Athletes get down between 6 and 13. Male bodybuilders some… https://t.co/TjY8TrASw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard a little girl say, “Step on a crack, break your father’s back”. Gender equality baby!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t know who my favorite djs are, we can’t be friends, sorry hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good To My Earhole, March 10. #musicjunkie #khalid #rosieflores #titorodriguez #orquestrarevolucion70 @ Second Ward… https://t.co/pOiw524R9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UntamedBeauti @leeleebb21 There are three kinds of people in this world: vegetarians, people who love bacon, and liars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffVeillette The crowds are bigger and better there. As long as they keep showing up I’m fine with it. Maybe the… https://t.co/Lp4U2hlj3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ranger_Up This could be a good thing if India and Pakistan goto war it will divert terrorists from Afghanistan to… https://t.co/ETE14c9G7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so over the whole life thing. Hurry up lol universe you are fucking me in the ass right now. I need peace lololol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmarisJessica Faithful are the wounds of a friends, but deceitful are the kisses of the enemy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come get better. Track is a sport that will benefit you in almost every other sport. Yes it is tough, but in the en… https://t.co/A4yM4S6ch6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will literally move mountains for ANYONE... just a simple thank you works.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcelobalboa17 @NicK_Balboa @FlemingSport @jpereznavarro @univisiondep123 @Migue5Angel @raulguzman Grande Marce !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even when you have doubts, take that step. Take chances. Mistakes are never a failure – they can be turned into wis… https://t.co/JXNNHckBxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Dominia Yeah, I add all sorts of oddball channels on my Roku to find stuff like this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poetgambler Hank says, “Have you ever seen a man say goodbye to a shoe *before*?”  BEFORE. Not now. Before.   Ther… https://t.co/dsd7pXbcTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FairQuestions @martinpwilkins @JustinTrudeau @Puglaas @garymasonglobe That would be the folks opinion not the politicians]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great night we were the first people to book the Level Up Lounge room @yestercades. @ Westfield, New Jersey https://t.co/FHJ2HQU1P3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't let them fool you, it is cold in Southern California too!!!  Uncle Richard is FREEZING!!! Where's the HEAT???… https://t.co/frCOYOyMA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[And all of Trump's Sr Veteran supporters, who got Honorable Discharges, support letting the housing rundown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parked under a bridge in Brooklyn. These two have earned a rest!  #ontour #prevost #tourbusesgalore… https://t.co/k3bA29tn2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @racquelgoldy!  It’s your Birthday!  Happy Birthday!!  #Woooooooooooooooooo https://t.co/X2zTZ6MPbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 6th 2017, we lost the greatest voice of his generation. My Artist/Client/Fam @Hradguitar5 made the biggest im… https://t.co/hSWmh03zTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GangBonanno @ElliotStone17 @DaytonaCopWatch @Whitema48082595 with hostile defiance by college officials. Most cons… https://t.co/GU8SlLKoGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wittman7 @jjlamberton1 @LAtweets22 @ems_b @DustinNosler I think Verdugo’s hit tool is exactly what this offense needs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to present the collaboration of my healing through sound with my Didgeridoo Chakra Meditation and Essential… https://t.co/oOiUQSGKCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practice tourney today 1145@ Harber high AAU @ Har-Ber High School https://t.co/roxLyAdzUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOSEOBDULIO Ahora los mamertos salen a decir que eso es un montaje de la DEA, la CIA o el FBI.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitter world. Have a Blessed and Wonderful Friday  " LOVE LIFE " Blessed to be Blessed https://t.co/aawgrkexIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @UtahMBB players have missed 8-times from the line tonight... it’s not helping... #ASUatUTA #GoUtes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two Plain Hot Dogs. #ApollosGameday 😇 For You Dad! https://t.co/9HCeipFrYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I see these I think of President Kennedy smh. @ Jacksonville, Florida https://t.co/zEwvdAgmat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whomever is doing that bird call during FT's at Ohio State/Wisconsin needs to be thrown out of the arena.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game over, the Flames fall 5-7 in game 2 despite a fairly solid final inning. The Flames are playing at home tomorr… https://t.co/HEkaLlp3UZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation Words... Think About It 🤔🙏🏿🇮🇱🇺🇸🙏🏿 @ Tampa https://t.co/eemfll8Nh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hbowman1H @Rubiconski @MsLynneMiller @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/qUvJZb7Bvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greg81102 @Dagsy_ @InsideTheKennel You can put them ahead because literally every single metric worth its salt has us ahead. Go figure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisT_FFB @PFF_Sam @minakimes @damienwoody Ya that’s a Chicago dog which is a delicious dog]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my repeat client Rachael! She drove home in her first brand new car, a 2018 Mazda 3 Touring in S… https://t.co/q2tqo1Igzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjbowles4 @CensoredC1 @hopelynn1018 @deborahriccio2 @wantmyturn @Tyson_211 @FLDeplorableVet @suprdupe @formulalol… https://t.co/P9h5lEQSFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright Has anyone told #Bernie he won't be on the Ballot in NJ... and soon several more States without #MustShowTaxRTs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Alexa play #PleaseMe by iamcardib ft @brunomars “ #Atlanta #Diva #Dancer #Baddie #lgbt #mua #DragEntertainer… https://t.co/vgFZpQKRGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeCHunter1 for now lol , Have a good morning i'm off for a few hrs sleep]]></document></documents></author>