<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@NotMyPrecedent @spiritmoon7 @LA_Karma1 @bubbagump324 @mommamia1217 @RexThomresist45 @ItsMeCandiceTh1 @PollyPapaya… https://t.co/wIevLtgqEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatStudMuffin Glad you asked that bc I asked about 2 hours got no reply guess we needed a very cute winner from… https://t.co/3GQg2jWR06]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want in life is to play with these gorillas.  I really feel like that’s where im supposed to be]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't get me wrong, I'm incredibly blessed to have such a caring and thoughtful Mother... But I'm an adult let me m… https://t.co/IWAO7KxzQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get a LOT of questions about strength training. I was fortunate to stumble upon the BEST strength training coach… https://t.co/3Lfrs8fSB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo glad we stayed in #thecity tonight instead of #uber or #Lyft home 😴😴😴😴😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find someone that looks at you like @ladygaga looks at Bradley Cooper. #oscars https://t.co/iSVoEnIFkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashmc091 @DoloresCatania @Teresa_Giudice @daniellestaub And why wasn’t Danielle there last night?? Is she not a “full time” housewife???]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: :(  chick fil a:  *         *    .            *     .   *      .   *     .              *   .    * .         .… https://t.co/10EjFVcxFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfloresRRISD @RoundRockISD @VoigtAIA_RRISD @CedarRidgeHigh @RRISD_PIEF @cspanbus @uiltexas @sfloresRRISD I receive… https://t.co/9m1Rt5vmoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Jonas Brothers: Music from the 3D Concert Experience” was released 10 years ago today! It’s still my favorite movi… https://t.co/PRXGMY0t9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[She went to help people being terrorized by ISIS...she didn’t join ISIS. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sad bc I feel like I deserve it, but I know it’s not my time yet so I’m happy to see other people who deserve i… https://t.co/u1UroRlAWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saraashleyo I love that's it's mostly women. Like we all figured out we need fluffy adorable pets who can also do… https://t.co/LJQ5oT4Anq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red Shawl Fundraiser April 12, 2019 at Potawatomi Bingo and Casino benefiting Gerald L Ignace Indian Health Center… https://t.co/6q5WLbpBE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want everyone to know that I did a ~2,250 mile roadtrip by myself in a car with no cruise control. I should… https://t.co/wMAHvRM4F4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cotton voile #scarf or shawl (or decorative piece) 60x60" was first hand dyed with my own #rosemary grown on the ro… https://t.co/Lqqn4WSVW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldenxpvsssy:  “ i thought he was hot soo i checked his age... he’s a 22 year old that rides a scooter” ......]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all would rather be in a toxic, controlling relationship than be alone....that’s real life sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtf was that whiskey cavalier commercial?! They’re straddling each other while exposing they’re “related”. More sho… https://t.co/FsVDHT1UFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[More damage does Trump have to do before we get him out of office in peach Trump now throw in jail and make this re… https://t.co/P4RiIEw4jT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank You for this reminder @lorishemek &amp; to think positive thoughts about myself_'cause my body is listening]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donlemon I don't know how your an anchor of a news program your so biased why don't u do opion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cup of flowers &gt; Cup of Joe🌸 #vsco #vscocam #Bestofvsco #flowers @ Haddonfield, New Jersey https://t.co/pu3B1Sx185]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cosplayamerica @gallifreyone One of the best cosplay communities I have seen. And I been doing it since 2003. Hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[CAUSE AND EFFECT Used to be if you killed a pregnant woman you were charged with 2bd Degree Abortion (murder) but l… https://t.co/Sjpp5PAEwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RochVoisineRVI #Fourirematinal (6h30 ici) Confesse? Sérieux, tu parles de confesse? Depuis quand votre Sainteté ne… https://t.co/8nTLkMnZT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you agree? 😉 - - #nyc #newyork #oldnewyork #old #travel #love #instagood #photooftheday #fashion… https://t.co/2eZawqw3UN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I definitely need to go to bed cause I’m about to catch a mean ass attitude I feel if]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pcastanon_CI Thank you for setting this up, Patsy! We all had a blast💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t wait to isolate myself in NH when i’m older https://t.co/yT8H6tCPUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaBertrand @MSNBC I missed it, what was the tea? https://t.co/psqXpPRKYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite nickname for brad rn is mink i can’t stop calling him mink !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @senatemajldr @SenateGOP @HouseGOP   What does AMI,or Donald Trump, or Putin et al have on you?? It must be am… https://t.co/W30wSAzpS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellesevero2 @KDKNSolidarityS @bernardokath #VoteKathrynBernardo  #KCA @bernardokath]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone want to just come and lay in bed with me? Maybe just lay here and talk, watch a movie, etc.  Hmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WarawuthPongsee @dinofantasy @BlackedRaw @iamjasonluv @LouieSmalls69_ Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[when tracy turnblad came down in that hairspray bottle she did not fucking come tO PLAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teddypinderass Ummmmm some private school that was ranked in the nation at a Christmas tournament]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucky lady... #gimmejimmyfishing #budnmarys #keys #reefandledge #costasunglasses #luckylady #strikezonefishing… https://t.co/JfXsfPEsgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not just absurd, it’s genocide. Precise language matters. https://t.co/2bAiiaEccz  “Killing ... Causing seriou… https://t.co/YqO1prWWyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows Let me continue.. If I was a Republican, You bet your ass I would  Change parties. You… https://t.co/1GU3X1OG35]]></document><document><![CDATA[70 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19… https://t.co/LTilFPWPnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen I’ve said Trump liked Hitler and hell he is like Hitler. Shame on the GOP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation @JakeMorris186 @SlidellPD I love seeing him too. But he’s not @JamesCraigmyle or Lor LOL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveLetarte But the struggle is real. Happens to me every night.  Hope you get some sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Followed all these amazing #women Rix. Appreciate your supporting #women. #follow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matsikoudiscom @amywilson @SustainableJC Aww! And I haven’t seen you in so long!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please share and join us! This event is #FREE and OPEN TO THE PUBLIC!!! https://t.co/wH5JFJEPGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arielsobelle @benshapiro @AOC Ariel, willfully ignorant people cannot be reasoned with, it’s unfortunate that she… https://t.co/4QyfONdkMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[After my father has once again downloaded too much onto his BRAND NEW iphone  I have scheduled a meeting https://t.co/3u5CwX4bNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamCarollaShow @adamcarolla @LynetteCarolla @ChassyMedia @nateadams26 Mazel Tov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of these strong, brave, persistent, diligent, tough, and hard-working leaders of North Posey! Nothing artific… https://t.co/wIaRG5Gvzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[We offer aqua fitness programs, swim lessons and recreational swimming for all ages. How do we do it? By recruiting… https://t.co/DwLx0eHg4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[#celluliteisfine #aginggracefully #shepower #powHER #goodenough #worthy #godschild #mirrorwork #fitness #health… https://t.co/VCxqd0AAZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re looking to find me, try to spot the girl with the biggest and thickest hoops because you already know tha… https://t.co/DvXUtka0v0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sweet Home Alabama-no matter where I lay my head. #ROLLTIDE!! #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VandyMGolf Glad you chose Gold Patrick. Love you and your wonderful family⭐️⚓️⬇️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twenty miles and more than four hours later, I made it to the other end of the NCR Trail! I have completed one of m… https://t.co/IVrOMko2P0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cousin left cold and snowy Portland for some sun in CA. The weather clearly followed her. @ Disney California Ad… https://t.co/7DMF2ZaY7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryant_rf @News8Daybreak @GeneralMills Oh! Yes, I've mixed Fruity pebbles w/Rice Krispies before. #IAmUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MontagueSupina Also N. Has no real gel with the team in real-time games ever. She has been 2nd bench b/c of slow r… https://t.co/st8X1UwTqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multitasking queen 👸🏼 @MeredithBarack not only leading the anchor desk solo, but every time I look at the tv she’s… https://t.co/68MyHtSKp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting a church that hates people is just as bad as trying to say you support and voted for Trump but you’re no… https://t.co/y2yaYEssiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is near but explains how people fell under the spell of Hitler and Jim Jones, to name two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freefanaddict They we a gift from hubby and I know I'll have fun once we get there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how now they refer to him as a ‘British rapper’. Just twisting the knife.😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsJeffHudson Amazing🎈. Keep going, it gets easier the longer you stay sober.  So proud of you👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AnxietyMakesMe talk extremely fast, space out, and embarrass myself because I can’t control anything around me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puxatawney Phil and his inner circle have been trying to convert the United States into an Authoritarian Oligarchy… https://t.co/MwgwGBZyXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Understanding who God really is will lead you to boast about him https://t.co/6M0CwC2LbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My birthday gift to myself - a jacket based on the art piece of Pam Carter called "Early Snow in Iona". Absolutely… https://t.co/pFujZAvs0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chrissy Goheen REALTOR® RE/MAX Best Choice 573.518.4178-573.431.2210 https://t.co/EfmXqdyUoA… https://t.co/CqBAZA2EQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiscountChuck @SalVulcano I love how unrelentingly real he was. Damage control with no apologies. It was very much needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meant to highlight #1 @PCCLancer &amp; #7 @deanza_college --- in the entire U.S.A. !!!! @CalCommColleges @cccoer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greatest joy in life is when you’re listening to one of your playlists in the car and someone asks you to send it to them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy MonYAY from the crew! We’re looking on the #Brightside on this first work/school day after… https://t.co/mxGyevZSt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isbradwalker Aw geez. My dawg is 4 today, but he’s just an animal from the pound who I love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading about the cleaving of American journalism in the 1890s leading up to WW1 for a class and realizing that med… https://t.co/SGMS8RBV5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you take the elevator to the third floor, I genuinely don’t like you]]></document><document><![CDATA[👇💚The Secret to Success💚👇 👉The key to what you want, Press More 👉 . You may think I'm joking but I'm not, this is n… https://t.co/k3HvvoPE9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbrogley Hang in there!  You’ll get there, just continue to listen and lead. https://t.co/v6YDkuvEk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TWPundit @ChelRBR Psychiatrists Will be making an case study about TDS congress celebrities MSM have gone over the… https://t.co/dEGIYtucDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kurland_s @louzival2011 @Aroly_YO @9339Wingmen @ZURUMU1 @mariajo66360450 @DropShipCircle @BiggBillztheone… https://t.co/ZBlTBs5pC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our first ride on the greenway for 2019 was cold and rainy. 🥶 And if that wasn’t enough fun I thought it’d be cool… https://t.co/MAFfbah5Di]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in front of an off duty pilot who is talking about the logistics of airports with passengers beside him: lu… https://t.co/qweHDPOAai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh @United what a terrible experience we’re having! 4 hours and counting at the Dulles Washington. I just want to get home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#valentinedayhottie Repost from cindytraining Hey everyone 😍 How are you? What’s your favourite muscle group to tra… https://t.co/N8LfpsWkn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe there’s still people who don’t have a debit card/can’t just send money online 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queen's Tea with my #twitch #teamakeseverythingbetter #familyislove #twincousins @ Emma's Tea Spot https://t.co/NyVlIeRrOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelfish74 @omaha_hawkeye Congrats! I think so highly of you both and think you make a great couple.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was intimidated at first bc u were super pretty and ur layout was cute ! I thought u were super cool and goth !… https://t.co/bPXKPrCIQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @TheDemocrats I’m not much of a historian but wasn’t this the kind of decay that fell the Roman Empire?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The pups are adorable and after all, she is Ma so if she “adopts” I will say that counts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean we all knew PETA was shitty the second they compared the meat industry to the HOLOCAUST but whatever I guess… https://t.co/s8VftT7fpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've officially hit the point in my single life where I have a big bed but half of it is used for clothes, movies,… https://t.co/HWANpeipja]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to our @FIU_OFGA, @GoGlobalFIU @FIU_StudyAbroad and @FIUISSS colleagues for hosting a great Florida Assoc… https://t.co/BciwljJRu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Modern medicine=$$$+discomfort Ancient herbal medicine=health wellness and comfort]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntBenavides_33 Go wake up your dad @Its_Just_Nico and tell him to take me to get food... specifically a big fat cheeseburger]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Automation Test Architect"? What did you like most about that job? #KellyJobs #KellyServices]]></document></documents></author>