<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This dude on Cheaters said he built his girlfriend body for his enjoyment and not for it to be seen on social media… https://t.co/sdjl225vQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodyear says it is eliminating approximately 60 hourly positions at their Danville manufacturing facility. https://t.co/bMpSWxOsyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We have a long ways to go,” Maria Muhammad - I Am My Brothers Keeper @IAMBKCDC #SDGreenNewDeal https://t.co/YRHwdvWUAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to dinner with former student and future teacher @ally_sarnowski Friday night before my last… https://t.co/HmXRdL18X0]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you think will happen to Trump?  Not what you hope will happen, but what you really think will happen.  Twitter, do your stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this Valentine’s Day, here’s a love story: #Petska ❤️❤️❤️ (Swipe to watch all 4 little video snippets) “I knew I… https://t.co/sQAqE9fvrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heversonsantos5 Separados na maternidade!!! É muita desgraça pra um pai só]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NEHumaneSociety She is so beautiful she is going to have gorgeous puppies!❤️🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last minute 4-day weekend turned last minute race entry means this is my third race weekend in a row!! 😆😆 (y’all kn… https://t.co/GmqvmFKM7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melanie is an award winning journalist and author. She came into the studio and we created several looks for three… https://t.co/g6nHs7IlvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[11th Annual Pre -Patty Pub Crawl @ Jacksonville, Florida https://t.co/ZSDgE23eRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Schools want to preach about bullying but at Central that’s what the teachers and principal are doing to my daughte… https://t.co/zPTjgxsnMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Home.    😀   Seagrove Ave. Wilmington,CA 90744 in Carson, CA https://t.co/XgcglC9fPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of today was when duck face asked if I was a troll.   I felt like I almost reached @MongoGoesInsane status.   Almost.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeLindblom @CityofSeattle #Seattlewomanstatue Dorothy Hollingsworth was the first black woman to serve on the sc… https://t.co/BoJD4QOSS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[After taking care of everyone else today, still had to get my workout in......How my legs feel right now after a la… https://t.co/37mh1hOj2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been out of Texas for roughly one week and I’m heading straight to @Whataburger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gogettavee__ @yagirlsam_efff No ring we not a thing https://t.co/BWjYE0oohC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cs00582scs @LadyRedWave @LouDobbs @RandpaulS @POTUS @RandPaul I AM SO DISAPPOINTED IN YOU, RAND PAUL!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning and happy Sunday. This morning inspiration for you and food for thought truly 🕉🐉 @ Pennsylvania https://t.co/ARTh9JSexe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoverDov123 @KFearri @petergraigs @grasshopper_42 @star_indie @HammerDownHard1 @Lonnie_Hammer @Bren_O1967 Thanks hum]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for 2nd half of @CardinalCage vs. Brush. We're up 40-30...and it's hot up here!#onceacard https://t.co/cUHckzKALJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got Kylie a new bed. Her other crib was seriously held together by screws, gorilla glue and rope 😂😂😂😂😂😂 Im still no… https://t.co/hXEzRiSVd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #StormJavelin is my @anthemgame exosuit of choice. Make your selection to unleash your power and watch your suit in action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chalkymacalpi @KittyHavenNY Heehee! Yes dat right we all lubs yours smoochies. Fanks Mr. Choo Choo. Umz, one more… https://t.co/y2l3u73m1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[times like this i wish i was still in south carolina cus my boyfriend meek mill in north carolina and i would’ve fi… https://t.co/Mym1mCZbN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baltimore launches new effort to place homeless families in newly renovated public housing apartments https://t.co/8YCCuRGXzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Venezuala is about corruption.  Democracy is not immune to corruption, best exemplified by you and… https://t.co/JgYsPMlNDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems this doc will be studied in future film classes of how to use documentary film making to manipulate viewers. #LeavingNeverland]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nike THAT MADE MY DAY. Great piece thank u for doing this for everyone to see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to take product photos then I will have resin pendants, wrapped beach glass, and later today a super cute bea… https://t.co/1lvg5VISmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[roof raking adventures from MN @ Mounds View, Minnesota https://t.co/aMuDJ9SREB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottLivingHome @TheDIYMommy @MrDrewScott @MrSilverScott @TheBrick Um ok... Maybe it's my phone.. they look yellow.. sorry 😁😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my job. For real. Gizmo is a new client but utterly adorable. ❤️ #petsitter #petsitting #ashevillepetsitter… https://t.co/4KBKzAeA1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MishaWhite_ You know it’s trash 🗑. You don’t have to ride the wave 🌊 lbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one time i wish i was still in high school so i could stay home today 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfection 💋   What happened to Baby Momma? #FuckFace lol   This show.. ✨ @SHO_SMILF  @frankieshawisag  @Rosie]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAOOOO bro why I thought this was a regular video, whole time you doing a voiceover 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was an honor to speak at Aubrey Middle School. I was excited to see so many interested in how to have a healthy… https://t.co/XVP8eL63ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[#outsidewedding #wedding #weddingphotographer #weddingphotography #photographer #photography @ Sperry, Oklahoma https://t.co/Siuf5unJx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkraju @CillizzaCNN The opening statement is a bombshell.  #MichaelSpeaksFebruary27 #TrumpCrimeFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEYY TIMBERWOLVES!!! Dates got switched for the March Spirit Week (Karaoke and Giant Musical Chairs)!!!! Be prepare… https://t.co/2NAerIlqZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canadians are proud of their health care system but we know too many pay too much for prescription drugs. Today's i… https://t.co/lRLFfLysMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Identifying cause and effect relationships with our buddies today in Explicit Comp #AACPSawesome @TylerHeights https://t.co/F74GBgStfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes he is! I have a problem with the Republican committee members. They really weren't going for the truth of the w… https://t.co/LLmBj3DVT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Technology Tribe You Need For Your New Business  https://t.co/auTIznaasp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaLem_n Oh no! I hope she has a speedy recovery &amp; everything is okay. So much love to you. 💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markjacksonacts @TheOrville Sorry, but that is hilarious!!! Hope you can get it fixed soon❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merrickEMS @EMSHuskies So excited for my daughter to have the opportunity and exposure to amazing opportunities in Allen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BagginsSuperCat Red: Me needer, Baggins!!! Lily: Me needer, Baggins!!! Mom: Me neither, Baggins!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jospacebear @prettyrickyroo Always happy to talk about my work with @ACLUOK's Campaign for Smart Justice (and plug… https://t.co/GnSKi4nW6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Create a Personal Development Plan and Achieve Your Goals via @Entrepreneur @briantracy https://t.co/yZEgRsEcQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clt_TrafficGuy @OnStar Looks like at least 3 cars. Everybody needs to get in the middle lane, but I don’t think anybody is hurt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m proud to be a consultant for Bedroom Kandi, I would like to announce that we’re launching into the cosmetics fi… https://t.co/4i2U98QDWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man works a 10 hour shift and still picks me up from work after and that right there is my fucking man idc if I’… https://t.co/lJtUuwoRd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michigan_Hawks Dave is a wonderful coach - A true players coach - He knows his players and gets the best out of them ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheMerryWriter D19: I'm a rare one in my family of seven being right-handed. My little brother is also right-hande… https://t.co/aeEuIwfiTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s never a dull moment in my school, and I don’t mean that in a good way 🙃.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m happy 🤷🏽‍♀️ I can’t complain ... even tho I probably will later about something 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Procrastinating on a project that I really should’ve been working on MONTHS AGO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @Starofthesea007 @AkronWineGuru @CaththeWineLady @Julianna_glass @ccatmpt @joneill55 @cowineco… https://t.co/1t5hMOs2et]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goliveros Hay muchos tipos de persecución y una de las peores se vive cuando las propias mujeres no se solidarizan… https://t.co/NvAJ2cgnP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Admittedly I’m feeling a little confused about my own direction today amid all the things I’m trying to catch up on… https://t.co/sgZMT8KnYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGno2trump Can you imagine those young women having this idiot and his ilk threatening them with countersuits?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcsosazpurua Hoy volvemos al principio Q entre la Ayuda Humanitaria con policía y militares íntegros q pongan ORDEN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mealprepsunday happened!   First two pics are post-workout meals: zoodles and turkey kielbasa with either roasted… https://t.co/DqX7bw2Qf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meggie1188 @bkiefer1353 I like half naked pictures of Michael B Jordan, OBJ, Trey and a million other celebs haha.… https://t.co/pIclS4fkN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a blast styling this Beauty @edwinafindley and her Beloved Baby Bump for some Oscar Week Soirées. “Mommy Glo… https://t.co/FcgCtEC4el]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGno2trump Many GOP women have wealthy husbands and therefore they don’t work. They could care less about equal pay for other women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[74 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19… https://t.co/DnQgzwWGlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KShamshoum Yes! This is such a problem for me as well. YouTube is a big one , but I also get stuck on Netflix as w… https://t.co/z2jT5TjxmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“for now you are just gunna stay on facetime with me and let me sing to you” @ja_salvage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uberbaldy @Hyper_RPG @IfyNwadiwe Ugh, I will probably choose Sobble, as I am blue 4 lyfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sr. Vieira, parece que Usted no ha leído el informe IDL_Reporteros, léalo antes de mal informar a sus oidores. Al p… https://t.co/g4fNZf1l5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you say “I wish I were a Martha” out loud and no one understands the reference cause you left Laredo.… https://t.co/jJGBDlFet8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celineorelse Does it taste like regular milk? Or like milk in those tetra-pak cartons?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandicarlile @TheEllenShow @FSMaui You deserve the best of everything ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m drunk when I can walk like a boss ass bitch in heels, but I’m also in the mood to fight a bitch. Fml.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be honest, do people that go to the University of Kentucky deserve rights?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunstone Tree Of Life Necklace handmade by me 🖤✨ Available for $40 on my Etsy ~ https://t.co/WejrcGEHEb #rt #share https://t.co/cSdYIGoDyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fmartinmoreno Así despilfarra #AMLObipolar el dinero de los mexicanos 😧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinMcElroy Does this come in adult sizes? Asking for a messy friend....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OHCowgirl @alisoninsco @shannongailmc @Mommandem @roseoleary58 @Boatoptional2 @cathyhadenough @devlyn_angel… https://t.co/9AdTHe0ltv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Last Time She Called Me Mama Shared from @wereparents https://t.co/80tqUaYp8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @tedcruz has a plan to build @realdonaldtrump's wall and make El Chapo pay for it... Join the fight to… https://t.co/Nxujb7wddx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter Tork Humour And Musical Talent R.I.P.  #PeterTork #Singer #Musician #Songwriter #TheMonkees   Live Performanc… https://t.co/q5j0T8sG0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m sitting at work just doing paperwork and started laughing bc i thought of that video of kodak sayin “lemme driv… https://t.co/CCW5W1zAJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DNC - #Milwaukee and #Miami have terrible weather that time of the year.  https://t.co/NdxtDF5Kel via @POLITICO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ja2cook @SouthernerSays @Sostraveluk @thethirstytales @FoodTravelist @MattsRoadTrip @radiantwanderin @GailBenzler… https://t.co/X9HMxklEQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitches always wanna try my mama when I ain’t around wow the nerve of this cracker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grad school poster competition Judging today (@ Georgia Tech Global Learning Center - @gtpenews in Atlanta, GA)… https://t.co/POGESnu17T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dederittman Great quote. The past us done. Learn from it and move forward! @ERobbPrincipal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikaSpencer @Dax_x98 He stayed in the race for entirely too long in 2016. Continued to fracture the dems fight up… https://t.co/HDLYpielkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrissyWeigand @DavidKoechner @FortyThrive Thank you. ❤️ come to my workshop if you are in town. https://t.co/OlbatRV0ZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExposedCold @SpicyFiles I saw a pic earlier like one of the ones you had up, some screen shots from her account, a… https://t.co/uxiZqr7jDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC He's lucky the sentence for treason (death) isn't imposed on his nasty nazi ass.   #traitortrump… https://t.co/Iw4knvAabO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karagoucher @nuunhydration I appreciate it. Thank you! Very bummed to miss you last week in Seattle. Stay safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NBAAllStarGame  #Basketball  #NBA  #ILoveThisGame  #LoveAndBasketball  #KevinDurant #Wade  #JoeHarris  #Curry… https://t.co/MoJLKRfh1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t watch lacrosse but I’m sure this is just as disrespectful as when lonzo crosses bruh then helped him up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samyfrmtx i’m just tryna see how she thought that was remotely possible.. 😂]]></document></documents></author>