<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[One more thing, apparently they can't comprehend the fact that the radical rhetoric they're feeding the public are… https://t.co/cuUzvYrQfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[12 años se dicen fácil pero en realidad están llenos de tantas cosas Muchas aventuras, conciertos en los mejores es… https://t.co/vct2Dy7L1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talley sends Jernigan home off a sac fly. 2-0 Georgia over Kennesaw State heading into the 4th inning #GradySports #KSUvsUGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right back at you @courtneyjshaw1!! We are so lucky to have such an incredible group of women to work alongside… https://t.co/FydvaMRnjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalkrStalkrCon @RamboDonkeyKong OMG!!! You just made my day! I wanted to meet him so much. I am super excited abou… https://t.co/PwF1b2hl3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirstenAllison @andyjamesdalton For you to ask that question tells us you are completely unaware.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got use to the hate now love come around that shit just don’t feel right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I showed anthony this &amp; first thing he said is "what's scold?" 🤦‍♂️🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alguien que me comparta este dato? Necesito saber cuantas calorías pierdo diariamente, gracias.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still feeling so energized by the Heartland-Delta Faculty Conversations this weekend at @JohnCarrollU. Loved hearin… https://t.co/b7qC5dteLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MooreBrett Thanks Brett! I better still get some text messages during home baseball season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Richard Montgomery High School in Rockville, MD https://t.co/mT2ezPY9lV]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time I was in the bathroom for awhile and my 4 year old brother yells “why do you eat so much cereal!?” Because… https://t.co/ytUXGKLLt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonovision_man @kinsellawarren Exactly. Then why resign. Full investigation. Now. 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[How one can espouse the #GreenNewDeal, but continue to buy clothes made in factories, drive cars, and eat processed… https://t.co/LwWWjMv5F8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aeching1 Kyle has one already I just have to change my last name eventually.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MHS FIELD TRIP at The ZOO today!! Rule breakers!!❤️❤️ @ Phoenix Zoo https://t.co/7zZXGS8W54]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got beast in trouble and let me tell you I’ve never seen a dog kiss so much ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RangerDainko @NBCNews Trump and his crew are your idiots. You found them. Now please help remove their carcasses]]></document><document><![CDATA[awkgingy's giveaway! https://t.co/r0TkFo5twc check out @awkgingy channel she’s really cool and oh yea and this is an amazing giveaway]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m fine. #19point1 #wheresmyhappyplace #synapsedoestheopen #bestgymever crossfitsynapse. thank you Jackie for push… https://t.co/MGdv9bHWSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecspike Groovy, more than @gradle 's DSL  @gdgsv #DevFestSV #gdg #googler https://t.co/HDtEFwO56p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I just burnt my forehead real good with my curling iron #dumbbitchprobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s crazy how some girls r SO obsessed w me like worry about urself girl! i’m doing WELL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two men found partially bound and shot to death at the villas at Oakwood Monday night, according to crime insider s… https://t.co/JMTIwfiSND]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoyed anchoring with Jeff! San Antonio will miss him https://t.co/5TvR4YQr8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[First one asked if he could join me for the movie because he wanted to “tickle my popcorn.” Second one talked about… https://t.co/UM4YSL2kME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me waking up to my smoke detector chirping loud as can be every minute at 5:30 am on a Monday.... Over 20 minutes l… https://t.co/hejOB4kgKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxBoot that was my thought as well since he was referring to Cohen stating that Stone told the president about the email dump]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBTich it's 1 o clock and schools hasn't been cancelled !!! My heart hurts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @tedcruz has a plan to build @realdonaldtrump's wall and make El Chapo pay for it... Join the fight to… https://t.co/fQQtf6Bboq]]></document><document><![CDATA[So adults are injecting sedatives in teens necks at concord mills?? What in theeeeee hell?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders You are a curse. You want to give free tuition, and already college degrees are not worth spit becau… https://t.co/dKIFRBBF4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski That's what Eunice keeps saying to me. https://t.co/qazm8lF4Og]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews 60 degrees in Philadelphia on Sunday in February wonder why Donald Trump thi… https://t.co/0TTDPhKwDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirstysemanuel @Rose_Mclean2519 @backstreetboys Amazing! I need more shelf space.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CLINTWESTWOOD_ @sixinbrian @kwilli1046 @crypt0k1ng @officialmcafee You climb I hold drinks and live stream...deal… https://t.co/nuE2CZCQcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[These guys are all masterful in their technicolor camouflage, but I think my favorite is the Pajama Squid, last ima… https://t.co/PwOV9vin6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chiropractors work to remove any source of irritation by keeping your spine healthy and aligned.… https://t.co/9RJPlOQcLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unions fight the adoption of money-saving, efficiency enhancing technology at every turn. So many menial govt jobs… https://t.co/fxMI4sQdcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralHospital Hmmm, how did Jason &amp; Robyn’s footbridge end up in Niagara Falls?  😂❤️ #GH]]></document><document><![CDATA[135.4 lbs as my phone still weighs 0.6 lbs. 😉 Down 2.2 lbs from last week! 🎉🎉🎉 Been going super light on workouts t… https://t.co/MYkPnrTwfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad comes in my room and goes “ur staying home tonight?” And I was like “yeah :(“ and he goes “good for u” like whaat 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[27 Pictures That Will Blow Your Mind To The Moon And Back  https://t.co/6u84EhRoOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Bondage, the bondage of the Serpent.  Only the Lord God Jesus Christ gives us Salvation through his name.… https://t.co/20fEofHPEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before worrying about my pregnancy, worry about your kids running around acting a damn fool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another amazing #waterfall from this weekend's hike in #santamonicamountains #grottotrail  #visitcalifornia visitca… https://t.co/lnZAnfFaNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join me in praying for @BaylorWBB’s Moon Ursin. Her grandfather passed away today. Baylor says Moon plans on… https://t.co/mz4KSPUw4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the #Oscar to documentary short subject goes to Period. End of sentence https://t.co/kAzzHVDrvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBTA WHERE is the 1 bus to Dudley?! A bunch of us have been waiting at Albany St for 20+ minutes! And it’s 15 degrees out!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbiebrox @TwoHappyTigers @SpeakerPelosi @OversightDems @HouseIntel So when Trump is found guilty of conspiracy t… https://t.co/YEHI2NIMSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nartist @chrishayes has always worshipped Bernie. I knew he would pushing him again this election. #inners #msnbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krisyasker always killing it on styling! 💃🏼👌🏻♥️  #NYFW ✨👱🏻‍♀️📸 by.joshdavies @ NYFW https://t.co/A1ykJYB9Kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Embracing winter #hockey #momentsthatmatter meliora_at_sola_studios @ War Memorial at Oncenter https://t.co/AUJO5rdHH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone keeps asking me about spring training,  and asking" Arent you going soon?" 😭😭😭No, No I am not. Damn vechile😔🙁 #baseballwithdrawal]]></document><document><![CDATA[A commonly used cliche, but SO very true ... people don't plan to fail, thwy fail to plan.  #HereToHelp… https://t.co/fQ5xo2ZW3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many people with mental illness try to hide their inner turmoil from the world. None of my friends or co-workers gu… https://t.co/XXkvqTxKu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlieberman1 Los humanos no deberíamos  tomar leche, es para el ternero. A mi tampoco me gusta, y de paso la carne.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericchurch  hey dude...Matt Phillips’ assistant softball coach here..I need your help so hit him up and let’s meet… https://t.co/njA379VAD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #internationalwomensday  and I have had the pleasure of spending a large chuck on my day reflecting on all the… https://t.co/M5JU41zsQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot even post a photo of my coffee this morning, because the mug is going to offend someone and I’ll spend my… https://t.co/3RbHnD6c0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is 2 AM and I can’t go to sleep since it storming so heavily in the Sierra Foothills.  It’s pouring cats and dog… https://t.co/aljIlNCFzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[At half Labre girls lead colstrip 22-15. Nice run by Labre to end half #mtscores]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jameslfregosi @KirstenPowers It takes courage and integrity to admit our failures of which we are all guilty.  You… https://t.co/oC66GSVqQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darth My late husband “ordered one for the table” to save face in front of the waiter who didn’t know what his wif… https://t.co/T9VDcxkV2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegoodgodabove @TomiLahren God don't bother she sold herself years ago, and now is realizing just how far down she has gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think we all learned a very valuable lesson today: if you want someone to give a GOOD talk in church don’t ask Jules 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m really just sitting here upset that Alex Trebek has cancer and NONE of my friends know who he is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus. Christ! I swear these things scare me more than spiders. My whole body is covered in goosebumps right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Cant wait until u r in jail and someone's bitch so u can see how it feels to get f-ed in the arse… https://t.co/SuLWngG99H]]></document><document><![CDATA[haven’t felt this confident with my body for a lil while, water water water https://t.co/jwZHVrhPsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t act like you “know food” unless you know what’s about to go down in this kitchen https://t.co/t6wqtXluxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SInow @PatMcAfeeShow This would be the best thing that could to the NFL brand in a long time! #PatMcAfee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddematteo1970 @WCVB @Met_CindyFitz @EmilyWCVB @WxManAJB @antoinetteA Thank you! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlatantlyOb @cblessey @daahmom @DPlorable17 @jsfw66 @k80krickt @RoyaI_FIush @smalltownandrew @PayItForward213… https://t.co/0gRzWsUnU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Modesto Police Officer Juan Arroyo is happy to be back on the job more than a year after being seriously injured by… https://t.co/mXBa11kDDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will comment on people who are using private jets. Hey @Diddy. Drive. Use commercial flights. I crack up when I s… https://t.co/ozNYzf5wP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well,I actually don't remember,what this was about, something trivial,I suppose,and I am ignorant with regards to m… https://t.co/7BL6tEs7px]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIME @OfficialJLD In conclusion, healthcare is a fraud. Knees dictate health. Muscles reign supreme. Both governme… https://t.co/PgLPssPOq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CWillis191 @JackPosobiec Because the Constitution forgot to mention stupid people shouldn’t be allowed to run for… https://t.co/Aje7PmDmQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[had pretty horrible news at the beginning of the week and i’ve tried to shut out any feelings i have towards it bec… https://t.co/jo8WLvb9EI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinKopnitsky I forgot to mention I’m taking the dog in the divorce.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for making the trip. Tonight will be a fun one with @YorkDukeBBall #aurorahuskies #nebpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cada experiencia de servicio fortalece el alma, alimenta el espíritu y engrandece la fe.  ¡Gracias Fortes por sacudirme de nuevo! 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAY 2 REVIVE #revivecsra @ Curtis Student Ministry https://t.co/IXJQV0YW82]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU POSTED THIS FOR EVERYBODY TO SEE SO AGAIN... where is the disrespect ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @telisayancy for sharing your inspiring journey at #SheRunsIt.  We are proud to be part of this team with… https://t.co/VRfmZbhu4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing the sunrise but always appreciate light at 7am. Losing it Sunday but gaining more light in the evenings I’l… https://t.co/VudB4BnfqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solvent-less concentrates are the connoisseurs special treat for those extra days of the week that seem to tack ont… https://t.co/o7JuUnP04p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning Meditation: Lent, Day 5–The first Sunday of Lent.  Every human heart is vulnerable. The temptation of Jesus… https://t.co/5gdOnATd4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need models y'all!!! Let me play with your face! https://t.co/Szlr4XMAcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson Some of the children have been placed with “Host Parents. Maybe she should also explain that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the idiot Trump basis his decisions on?  MAGA'S, BE SCARED, BE VERY SCARED!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @GabbyGiffords @lucymcbath @SpeakerPelosi Good, however, real bad guys are not going to buy guns legally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@momma_review Leadership - Lifestyle - Fashion - Travel 💕 https://t.co/mUYoEu2S1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Uncle &amp; Niece snuggles. 🥰 @B_Houser_Swag20 https://t.co/WzwDUzItlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GulaboTheRose @BeingUmarNawaz Ooper wala,barra agg lagdi ker raha hai .. Dp per haula hath Rakh lai zara 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤩Con Sue Photography and Design🤩  🥰Like our photos...Follow our IG 🥰  😍This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/niGJiCbQH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m over here in aisle 12 wondering if I should start eating cereal with water now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powerful #HealthEd message how to address body image from @MelanieLynch52 Dying to Be Thin  @NJAHPERD #NJAHPERD100 https://t.co/6z307fuE6M]]></document></documents></author>