<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If you’re awake and reading this what are you doing there is a ZERO PERCENT CHANCE I sleep till 8am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissamorris50 but Melissa the world doesn't work this way Steve: then change thev]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boxingscene @EditinKing Never happen. Though it is nice to dream. Could be bad for Floyd if it were to go down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle GOOD PUT THOSE COMMUNISTS OUT OF BUSINESS!!!! I SUPPORT POTUS NO MATTER WHAT! @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's stunning that this is not OBVIOUS! We are living deep within the Upside-Down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesNe23829680 @JohnHookfox10 @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama Nothing like a dose of stupid with my morning coffee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Madonna WE FELL UNDER GOD ON MY 1ST BIRTHDAY BECAUSE I CANT GET THE TRUTH FROM THEM. IF CONGRESS CANT GOD DID. THE… https://t.co/SLiQn1I1bZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DemandasSNTE #SnteSalarioDigno #SNTE #PalabraDeMaestro #SomosSeccion35 https://t.co/PlaCVM1Elc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FilmLadd @KurtSchlichter I remember when they used to make movies everyone enjoyed watching.  Even white dudes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Joshua Tree National Park - @joshuatreenps in Joshua Tree, CA https://t.co/c0jkN3RLf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trapcry @jb_fly @Rogersj1980 i said so many times this is only a conspiracy theory. i appreciate your input though]]></document><document><![CDATA[A tornado touched down a couple miles away from us and killed two people.. WILD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t decide whether to try to use this in a sentence today or implement this in a sentence today. https://t.co/P7auPD2RHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockstarGames Every time I try to join a Gun Rush match the game get’s stuck on a black loading screen and this ha… https://t.co/G3k4oRzGEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then other women, especially black women glorify said woman being a hoe. Shit is sad as fuck out here. Real talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Durham Art Market meet and greet. . . . #durham #duke #durhamnc #bullcity #huntstmarket #crafts #raleigh #apex… https://t.co/2qwKSTLfas]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 great young New York Point Guards. RJ Davis (Stepinac) continue leading the way. The youth are following your foo… https://t.co/h3eGZjnwje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the day! @ Universal Studios Orlando/Citywalk https://t.co/dErvR12IV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics @TheView I believe secretly that Meghan McCain support bigotry and racist and Trump she shows her true… https://t.co/viufGWpc64]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again, I have no problem with people liking or wanting to watch those videos. I am just not that audience. It would… https://t.co/jaW26xkgyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaaah @PF_Compaore tu vas payer un jour pour ce que tu as fait à ton propre pays inh...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so it seems every time there’s an earthquake the “Prisoner” (stage 4) skin gets brighter and the magma becomes… https://t.co/Hr0KOhq1aA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving home from the gym listening to @1067theFan talking about @AEWrestling!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geraldwolfe1 1. Blake's Lotaberger (Unfortunately they are only one NM and I think El Paso.) 2. Five Guy's 3. In And Out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump WHY IN THE WORLD can't you wait for the report to come out before taking the VICTORY LAP you're go… https://t.co/jkw2mmh4d5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniellevford @shaunking Triple yikes!!!!! If we are renaming buildings and removing monuments, this needs to be s… https://t.co/ESjRZxPWtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So it’s OK to break the law, as long as it creates jobs. Really? So where do you draw the line? Are drug lords exem… https://t.co/Cr1el0FGnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Washington Twsp tonight, boys basketball 🏀   How about those Dumont Huskies, topped @WWRSDAthletics in OT. Huski… https://t.co/Hc9xAC6asI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steven_curry rips a 2-out RBI single in the 4th, Eagles cut the deficit v UGA to 2-1!  AUDIO… https://t.co/QXT4PBRvxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a few interviews, filming a new episode of Nikki Skinner Nerd Teacher, a ton of Real Estate, Updating the movie… https://t.co/ECMD68Xk9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_Guillory96 Wow so my opinion doesn’t matter apparently. Big fuck you too lil shoots]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alan9609 Una vez hice un experimento en la secundaria con ese jabón, no piensen mal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helaineolen I did. And it is presumptuous to believe that since I dont agree with it, I must not have read it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Workshop on #innovation in #hydrometry starting today in New York, jointly convened by @WMO HydroHub, @IAHS_AISH MO… https://t.co/1UNI3Q1pV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst part about being hosed by the refs is that we don't get an actual good game. Just more questions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorgMoss_ Passing through Huntsville, TX  Morgan: “Ahh Huntsville, home of the death penalty. :)”]]></document><document><![CDATA[On God bro you on some fuck shit @FloydMayweather that money wouldn’t even hurt you to help your own. Remember when… https://t.co/GskWzPXiDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost https://t.co/os3ZfIiWD2 ・・・Amén . Todas las flores del mañana, están en las semillas de hoy (Proverbio indi… https://t.co/qFopIc82jZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The pre mixed salads from a bag should be considered finger food. Should not be a shame to just giver on that guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr CONCENTTRATiON CONST ITUTIONA-L WANTTNAW WANTAGH, L.I.,,,N.Y. US of A]]></document><document><![CDATA[U tripping cause yo ole lady flirting , nigga could’ve got her ass first 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caleb__Eli Put some clothes on dammit I am not ready to fall out this early in the morning. https://t.co/48iJsIPe1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever want to see what’s wrong with society, go to a gym and observe how the members there fail to rack their weights properly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView I never imagined I’d hate anyone more than trump, but smug Meghan has filled the position. Ugh. stfu please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are black racists, Asian racists, Hispanic racists, white racists, etc. @JussieSmollett is living proof. I'm… https://t.co/NMUgB7Tf9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dustinbixby @BSmithFlyers @WildJoeRadio I never worked a game from the danger position. All of my broadcast memori… https://t.co/6sOKGuJJtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but you cannot say that you wouldn’t rather live in the 50’s rather than now 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewbr007 @g_bensinger @SpeakerPelosi It's the islamist way. Paragraph 30 of their handbook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not open game for us all. I share my work. I put in the work. I submit, I audition, I keep landing these small danc… https://t.co/0dGypjWTuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDun07690396 @Wrix2 @DeborahGeeMusic @ThoseUSAGirls @JYPESuzy @willpowerentllc @DrJimmyStar @CrimsonSkyMusic… https://t.co/pxGzKLvj7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[#3am findings. I did some research today and found out that if you ever get a random emoji comment on your Instagra… https://t.co/6QYJQLfyMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st song done epduets #karaoke #passengermusic @ Duets https://t.co/qPc6VDSCUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlHeastie You know it’s critical, Carl. Some Dems might not support it but you have to push them. That’s your jo… https://t.co/yB4q60y5xr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @WildgirlAthena @Serenesirenxxx @nikkibenz @izzylush_ @KayleighCoxx84 @VictoriaVoxxx @addibabeee… https://t.co/lXlOVMdKbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex_etal @KurtRexCooper @nytdavidbrooks Yeah I’m torn on this. I support the concept from a moral standpoint, but… https://t.co/AOZzyWKsyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[We see it as Border Security. Make no mistake Democrats see it as Voter suppression.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carlawrightsha1 @26RJeremy @Shellsinsofla @KarenHBStanley @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @FLOTUS @POTUS And the Obama… https://t.co/mL5Xifg8tO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micah_bowens got 702 Elite all the way to the semi-finals, imo might have been the best 3 star at the… https://t.co/9mNh4VGD4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo am I the only one who thought sex and the city was a televised porno series growin up.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[2:21 remaining in 3rd Qtr: McCluer leads Surry 38-29.  Bre’cha Byrd with 4 pts in period to help the Cougars trim the Blues’ lead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thanks to @TCBOE’s superintendent, Dr. @LaceySuzanne, for #emPOWERing our young girls today for #IWD2019!💜 https://t.co/ab1RyhZxEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartySmithESPN Check out aftershox!  Safety first, buds are not in ear so you can hear traffic and music is awesom… https://t.co/Qv2n9mTpON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else not have power in their house right now? &amp; can anyone tell me why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine Charlize Theron as the President of United States and Seth Rogen in love with her. Is THAT a #LongShot ? -… https://t.co/V9sZLMW1ZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so true what @DaleJr is saying! My wife, son and I had the honor to have dinner with Sam just two weeks ago… https://t.co/QOXor2J8hq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I vote @ellatoone99 for February @FAWC_ Player of the Month! https://t.co/AQ6dh5CNGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arcfontis @aravosis I am very confident that Mueller’s report is substantially drafted and getting updated all the… https://t.co/BqyuvtlCY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so worried about learning the Dewey decimal system as a kid I’m so glad that became obsolete early on in my lifetime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFrankOzJam Well? Don't leave us waiting. Did it get made??? The suspense is looking me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second dinner in Memphis and of course I had to have BBQ again! This time I had to try out @centralbbq and man this… https://t.co/xIXYT33tgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pontifex Yes Papa. I have been praying and I will continue to pray. we cannot proclaim the Good News if we're the… https://t.co/cPcL9PT8hl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your sacrifice, and determination  rivals that of those men who took Omaha Beach! #RealAmericanHero]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOXSportsMX Zinedine Zidane regresa al Real Madrid C.F. Canción https://t.co/1B3ij4yfy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonybsiny @HondoShootist @LolaR4E @PoliticalMrBill @deserttrumpster @RTrumpforce @co_rapunzel4 @CindisPLace… https://t.co/b4e5TeavoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I commend her for trying to brea a barrier but her ass is gonna be out on the first game . I believe women can do a… https://t.co/3pCOl90Utp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatJunkman Of course AT-AT is pronounced "at at." https://t.co/vaTDQNCJFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[😸The coolest doormat ever😸 @tjmaxx . . . . . . . #chandlerarizona #gilbertarizona #arizona #southwest #cats… https://t.co/RMpk8drDGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's always fun to watch mom @brandi_love do some friendly cocksucking... I "cum" back to this one often;… https://t.co/vPVM0K5GSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do we need to borrow money to provide money to other countries?!?!?! Americans First!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PearsonFootball I get tomorrow off work, right? This...might have been a bad decision. I could use another day after yesterday. Oof.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @HillTVLive “Vote yes because we’re cute children” isn’t a winning formula for the Democratic Party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicky_Jay_1977 @TimsStacey @Real_Luckykid A face only a mother could ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[it feels INCREDIBLE to be away from my ex.   i am happy, i am loved, i enjoyed by most... i am H A P P Y !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need “common sense” guns laws, but “common sense” abortion laws would violate women’s rights so they will not be… https://t.co/Y68tqDrPhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GimmieDaFries This is what leads me to believe that find a good bud man is VERY DIFFICULT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FSUBaseball More than a 24hr delay so far... poor @Millar_Matt ‘s stomach must be a wreck from the stress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Playboy Does nudity negate professionalism?  Well it seems just a couple of years ago @Playboy said it did when it… https://t.co/98MBK8VM9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch @cassiejokes at Big Grumpy Comedy 26 on February 28th for #InternationalWomensDay in support of @SisteringTO… https://t.co/7EOAY6zcTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m listening to Radio Disney, Your Music. Your Way! ♫ #iHeartRadio #NowPlaying https://t.co/tpTwm2oHJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A qué mi @vuelaTAR , me la volvió aplicar 🤦‍♂️, nomas no dan una, en serio ya aplíquense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Season of the Drifter  Day 1 thoughts: Gambit Prime is cool as hell, definitely a step up from normal Gambit. If yo… https://t.co/kxewaTDNPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[PREP BASEBALL: Lavaca 12, Johnson County Westside 0, FINAL  Jimmy Hall 4 RBIs. Golden Arrows are 1-0.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where was this guy radicalized?  #Trump should speak out against this #terrorism.  #yeahright #Hypocrite… https://t.co/mnDaIwIcZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golden Gate Bridge 🌉 and Alcatraz @ Golden Gate Bridge https://t.co/uFaTHojGXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryan_borucki you're my 1,000th successful TTM. also, my 1,000th in person from @TLutz37 collected last wk at… https://t.co/1EUAdEVA5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los éxitos de @ReinaldoPared en la actividad política sirven para reafirmar que su tiempo #ReinaldoenlaCalle https://t.co/zdSgT1KeiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girl Amy let’s NO ONE SLIP. Just some PSA for you ignorant mother fuckers 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wbir THIS is actually NEWS...and a very sad reality that needs to be corrected now!  Parents and our schools have… https://t.co/zhwjzee1PS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@firstrax @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Why don’t you go to Diane Feinstein’s office and get the green new deal pasted!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have words too, Senator: We are killing the environment. That’s REAL. We cannot AFFORD to do nothing and sustaina… https://t.co/c07xgaAlQ1]]></document></documents></author>