<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@CyborgPatriot @EthanVanSciver You’re working real hard to defend a bigot and a liar, here. Also- nice sock puppet account.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one part you don't need to over think.   @alexdopazo knows the importance of his.   https://t.co/dTP1MBCPwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Great auditon to be Secretary of State. Bravo for a stellar performance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They really made that fight seem closer than it was. Omar won it easy but the commentators made it seem otherwise.… https://t.co/BK6IPJeQVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parabatibe @irenepfvrr Irene se Pedro concorda comigo é pq a coisa ta feia p ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChonMayor @Arthur_gz @juanitovt @kekiquesada Hahaahaha eso vi 😂😂😂😂 lo hizo hasta hablar inglés 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also shoutout to @Jquick88 for getting up to the game on short-notice as I was putting out Tuesday’s paper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found a high school friend did an @amoebamusic “what’s in my bag” on YouTube. So weird two hs friends beecame accom… https://t.co/inJTvGKJfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[think about the level of their perfidy - our great @POTUS a man who does not take a DIME for his 20 hour work days,… https://t.co/RkpvgA8G9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahrosie__ Always look at the Silver Lining and he probably wants you back...!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dparamooficial te mando saludos, gracias por el tremendo análisis diario!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCampbellCBS @SilversteinAdam if Reigns is cleared for Mania, what do you do? Insert him into Rollins/Lesnar. Put… https://t.co/V4MVCEWfE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold seat #parks #winter #cold #ice #snow #chicago #winterphotography #itsamazingoutthere #weather #bench… https://t.co/GZ4nyJs43R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bnw852 @summershamrock @Kkloss00 @josephspencer00 @Kieran_IsAGod @BeckyLynchWWE Night to you to bud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Blake’s honors chorus who competed at the district II choral festiva.  They scored a perfect 40 out of… https://t.co/1lZIdeLReP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grantswilson @chipcoffey I agree Grant. Man, you guys started the whole paranormal show genre. I absolutely loved… https://t.co/zcvuB8Jam1]]></document><document><![CDATA[So is everyone going to go without acknowledging this young king’s wisdom or ? 🙏🏾💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Vienna Lager by @beer_works at @beer_works — https://t.co/fWHvS4Vsuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Ethan I was born in the middle and then we had a great day  My age is so much  I like to think that I ca… https://t.co/Gjo3CZ9Slt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaPaquin @HBO I didn’t know you before tru blood but now I love you for way more than that 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@js_tut I like to provide training like using agile methodology.  I cover a concept then add to that and slowly expose more complex topics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusieQFitLife &amp; I had the same doula for @TweetMaxBen2015 &amp; Xavier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite new releases @Bobby_DAmbrosio feat @Michelleweeks remixed by @JoeyNegro This track is DOPE! https://t.co/lHuG8VS1Ay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks so good man it’s about time you got it I know the wait felt like forever 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CourtneyGascog1 happy Sunday to you beautiful sexy lady from John in Manhattan ny 💓💓 💓💓 💓💓 💓💓 💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[This car is so bad I actually started searching to see if I was somehow using it wrong. Turns out newer Corollas ha… https://t.co/aHPMzqPKuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dominic Fletcher lines a single to right. I'd say the second time through the order isn't going well for Eastern Il… https://t.co/hfGfHDoYnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arXived_ @amyklobuchar Many people didn’t trust Clinton, especially swing voters. I don’t think Amy will have that problem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BellaInxs2 @andrsngirls AND that’s the reason we need to the electoral college]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lindsey Graham is that annoying little house Chihuahua that keeps trying to hump Trump’s leg! Hey Lindsey!! Get off… https://t.co/kMONAQqyUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutly love #saturday #mornings  . . #saturdaysnuggles @ Liberty Village https://t.co/tsXcelojTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing foosball, I make a bad goal after some really cool passing  “I’ll take it but I feel like it’s settling” -… https://t.co/Tq2DiDemvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hlcesl13 @Barbarajdurkin @no2wind @drwaheeduddin @ramspacek @bluesjack42 @EcoForester @jeroen1huizinga @IDirtlump… https://t.co/5ZqAnscrSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlatTaxFehlinge @yhazony @IngrahamAngle @indiegop @JackPosobiec @TGCwithJason @RaheemKassam @LilaGraceRose… https://t.co/9APRkqdZjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨New Listing Alert 🚨location! Upgrades! Premium Lot 📢 This Gem 💎 is a must see!!! 300,000 in custom upgrades in thi… https://t.co/RhdSM76P3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always wanted to be in a sitcom.  Coming to Netflix this Spring.  https://t.co/XLsSKahh2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tetris shows us that if you try to fit in, you’ll disappear. Be yourself, that’s what makes you unique. #MondayMotivaton]]></document><document><![CDATA[G'mornin. #LABoy #LosAngeles #LALivin @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/4KU75CGqhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmycfields @TheSpursWayy If roles aren't available due to vets occupying cemented roles, ATX makes a lot of sens… https://t.co/E9dWRNLW8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepSouthProud I hope he does not sign this poison bill, it is all for democrats and Illegals and nothing for cons… https://t.co/ImUEZugcQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago Bulls vs Atlanta Hawks para esta noche.  #NBA https://t.co/DHz58HWvFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad told me I don’t ever buy juice for the house but I’m always drinkin juice. This should shut his ass up for a… https://t.co/FSd9Q1DwsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My facial expressions went from Big E's to Kofi Kingston's in a matter of seconds...  #SDLive https://t.co/pQwxnYvo3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brhodes CNN is a great example of that Ben...  The  Democrat Party is upset that they do not control EVERY mass me… https://t.co/yKkFSDFuK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nwdouglass5 @MitchL24 @DouglassCoach @megdouglass32 @douglass_elijah @douglass_kaley @AQWomensBBall @AQXC_TF… https://t.co/WxgEM7D1yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amybchan How do crazy people like this get elected????  It scary that he represents people that voted for him... I don’t understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hazemania Devil by 10 Torr Distilling and Brewing at @rebarlv — https://t.co/b8wkLVdyvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeMiss975 Thanks for indulging me today.  They need to pay up for the @Phillies Fans. https://t.co/54PeB5hIbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck no, but I’d definitely put certain people on the position to make more money]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is someone special … Thomas “Tiger” Ziegler has been working the bar in Hotel Congress for 59 years. When I as… https://t.co/1iwlFEUMeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UberFacts He should sue himself for that pube looking beard... #damn https://t.co/APrxUIEsA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The asshole elders in this situation didn't report crimes because the perp 'repented' in front of the church...twic… https://t.co/XrHxLgoCh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze Just curious why when other networks falsely accuse and never say anything. The Judge is all opinion and… https://t.co/EWDjk3tfp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we look forward to Women’s History Month, let’s not forget what our women of today are doing. #justdoit… https://t.co/NLHb6xGueE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Are you stupid. Are your an idiot even TRUMP HATERS INCORPORATED DONT BE BELIEVE A WORD https://t.co/110dsc7iKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter Jacksonville should call Pittsburgh off for a second round pick for Antonio Brown right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michael_nielsen @PESimeon Local in what sense? (I don't mean to push you on this and am happy to stop here if you prefer.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Movie Spotlight March 1, 2019  Tom's Featured Movies For March 1, 2019  Versatil… https://t.co/Urxsi6Yb9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I look up, he's staring me down. Does he think he's better than me? I want to be better than him! https://t.co/p9uHV8WqLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DVSAEnforcement I done get why this stuff still happens people and companies just dont get it thay put everyone at risk themselves as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaudeBarlow These days Canada's leaders take turns trying to outdo each other with their stupidity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ben_davis113 @ChocOne0One @UnitedWeZag @marchmadness Idk about title, the metrics say they are average offensively… https://t.co/cZw5Bdzu9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliauci16 Ustedes son los más mentirosos y manipuladores del planeta, o eres el ser más estupido e imbecil , ós… https://t.co/IFv9txLkDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyNatasha2 Definitely beautiful! Defiantly perfection she defiantly is!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCB_Sara All good. We just binge watched Umbrella Academy all weekend. 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Turnerj555 @3YearLetterman @BernieSanders Someday, both your MCL and ACL will tear from one of coaches youth football players.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look to Video Gamers for Your Cyber Security Specialists https://t.co/78NwKuyGfA via @CBROnline.com]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreatScott_11 @BringBackTheBuz @NBA He made contact with his thigh and also didn’t give Kemba landing clearance.  So two fouls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have Wonderful Safe And Blessed Day On Purpose Everyone God Bless @ Baltimore, Maryland https://t.co/uM6uriG0KN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zzBuLLeTzz This is my #corgi, Doc. He is a sweetheart. #mypet #dogsarelove https://t.co/q0Hdj95KQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stupid ass motherfucker dude... and in the end youll charge to fix thier mistake for not taking care of it... fucking idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@citchmook @tony_thechamp @Benaskren The ref def didn’t save his life, but the ref did give him the fight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If you really are innocent, than why not shut the hell up until Mueller submits his report? Your c… https://t.co/sKPaFPih3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinksThinks If you are lining up wit the last one it’s  Muggsy -  Kemba  LJ           -  Kawhi Barkley   -  Draymo… https://t.co/7BIyysMCYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t  look like ice cubes to me! Nah I’m sayin’?! @ Cameron, Missouri https://t.co/IYLayNjkfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuinnyPig @mndoci I’ve met and interacted with what appears to be the physical avatar of @mndoci many times. My gu… https://t.co/jnYAfmHz1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrinityStClair ALWAYS, but it's kinda' hard to do via UPS or FEDEX lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamgregyoung I’ve been thinking about this (too much). The DNC is going to be forced to do multiple debates, both… https://t.co/S4CfTmgmqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingRicochet vs @JohnnyGargano from #NXTTakeOverPhoenix #Raw https://t.co/dnLeDs0NGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Utter bollocks headline from a mainstream news source. Not acceptable.   Please hold people to account for their li… https://t.co/QaaPWU3B6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shouldn’t you be working right now? Isn’t there anything they can find for you to do.?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The War Was Won Before Hiroshima—And the Generals Who Dropped the Bomb Knew It via @thenation https://t.co/a1NmpjTi9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badhopper @WildAcreBrewing @cedarflats @zappafaye @MIbeertaster @RJellyman @mtravis63 @cellmavin @beerhunter74… https://t.co/kg3CMNjfqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoreleiEllen Eye Eye Captain I can secure that hatch. https://t.co/OJVCkqFJR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Walace_Rocha @essediafoilouco Disse o torcedor do BAHIA, que nem estádio tem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuz sometimes that “what you bout to do”? Shit ain’t enough you gotta actually show em better than you can tell em its time to bounce]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jennie Garth is 46...still viable for a deep pour at The Peach Pit. @JOXRoundtable #JOXCity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STYGoc Wouldnt be able to now. A certain pop punk band from Chicago doesn't like other people using their name]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next Summit ,Xi Jinping and Kim Jong -Un  Should be at the same table for a durable peace agreement.  Think about it Mr President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess they saw their error in judgment. 🤦🏼‍♂️ @ Cypress, California https://t.co/MBUUQ2a1xc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilnerhotline @johncanzanobft Seriously, my first public question to Larry Scott told be, “Are there ANY performan… https://t.co/xguBMFzvf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mddr le message de Martial on dirait a qui sa daronne a dit “ Va t’excuser pour la bêtise que as fait immédiatement… https://t.co/BVQDoMJFe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m DEAD.. they asked Kelly if she had to send anyone else home without their luggage. 😂😂😂😂. She responded with a G… https://t.co/5s80sECMzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnrobertsFox @realDonaldTrump It is BS and you know it, tag still on his hat, pushed a cameraman and no video or… https://t.co/UKIcgxJJRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micronauta I think I am going to take the Technician’s License exam next weekend rather than waiting until I can a… https://t.co/WXtP3acY8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilevin This nasty asshole should be committed to an asylum, that comment is just insane!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrysRich_2002 No your records are still safe for now😉Good chance at a couple on the girls side maybe 1 on the boy… https://t.co/D3TVDIPWv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My healing magic is a practice.  You can be any faith and practice magic.  It is not evil by nature it is what you… https://t.co/cfTdaavY6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MurphPreds @eGOmarine There’s a guy that has reached a point in his career where he can literally do no right.  As… https://t.co/hxduU2PLiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cold weather can shove it. Can’t wait for warm weather and baseball season.]]></document></documents></author>