<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jonathanalter Isn’t this exactly what Manafort was convicted for? Inflating asset values to secure a loan?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgePaschall @GIR_atx @williamlegate @realDonaldTrump It started when Reagan sold weapons to Iran..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t all the Kardashian/Jenner bitches fucked hella dudes that were at that moment in relationships? Even some o… https://t.co/adxTPnDN3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockinRebel4 @CalimityF He said he knows it’s not the same don’t you get it. You mustn’t listen 👂 to Sirius xm nascar shut the fuck up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ClassicJeff @EaglesWinItAll @regdaddy10 I hope so. He seems pretty rigid on those things. They either need to giv… https://t.co/UEsl2vZsPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BalazsSimonBalu Still doesn't solve solar winds, still doesn't solve how you deal with nitrogen, oxygen mix in the… https://t.co/r2G57yIC7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not ballsy enough to pick an Iowa win tonight, as I think there are too many factors going against them right n… https://t.co/4RqPIf9T9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scifijunk @Jewelsquest Then the problems you refer to cannot be fixed with standards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've known ash for like a day and I've already shown her my fursona whew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes we instituted a Lutocracy in 2013 and again in 2017! Kumira kumira Thuraku #TanoTerror!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckySmirks @Jali_Cat Democrats haven't cared about the truth in decades. They spin lies into so called truth to r… https://t.co/rKcK8Tvego]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life gets you up and down constantly love what you have and treat them right because in a matter of blink of eye could be gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Danielle Limonez from West Town Bikes. Building bike equity, access and community in Chicago #BikeSummit19 https://t.co/zGttqz8Nh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just for giggles, I’m starting a little minibook project to supplement Skeleton Keys about animals that eat bone.… https://t.co/NLff59yGaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICE is sending hundreds of asylum-seekers to a private prison in Mississippi https://t.co/sKilBr1VAC via @MotherJones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pheykelly @joedeal_ @mathewrodriguez YES. She got hit by the demon at the end of the season then next season they’… https://t.co/5Cf2EeIfm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolfChannel Reports claim there are more famous celebrities than #RobertKraft caught in the Police Sting: Could it… https://t.co/Wo5uRoDkH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impactmontreal @985Sports @TSN690 @MLS @le985fm .. unless there's a hockey game on .. lol :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[This year we get to stay on the beach! 😍💕😍🏖 #beachreach #lagunabeachchristianretreat @ Panama City Beach, Florida https://t.co/S2Bv22Fvdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AvidComicReader @dregen02 @AccidentAliens No offense taken man.  I would never promote hate or harm towards ANYONE… https://t.co/nHrv34LgKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad I’m being my natural self. All of the time. Literally, I’ve been the same way for my entire life. I like d… https://t.co/Dm4symywxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[In other words if McCabe believed trump was a Russian puppet then he must also accept that pence is a product of co… https://t.co/kgUGmW5x1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of y'all with getting these fevers need to start getting vaccinated]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dang rower, so much gray/blue @orangetheory @ww_us #5amhustle https://t.co/tCv6271hO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 billionaires going to a strip mall rub and tug ... something big going down for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edkrayewski I’m not a Randian, and I actually disliked Atlas Shrugged and Fountainhead. But I could read We the Living any time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are too successful, it is hard for venture to be all that rewarding  Don't make enough money, too slow, not… https://t.co/6VgL0vz4a7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#almostnoline #rainyday @ Myungrang Hot Dog 명랑 핫도그 https://t.co/IvWdmBLs4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are the best Apple Watch band alternatives you’ve seen? I’m a big fan of @Monoweardesign but their red nylon one is out of stock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THNKenCampbell And what was your stance on Malkin’s baseball swing at Raffl’s head? Or Mantha’s hitting a defensel… https://t.co/Gl2Rurbikj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RewardingEdu @ChrisQuinn64 @StantonAlana @NowakRo @TheresaHolloran @cpoole27 @melanie_korach @CoachKCullen… https://t.co/PHvXdGHire]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could You Love Me https://t.co/lLrMBO2dRJ via @YouTube. Check out PDmelody music could you love me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was happy but also really embarrassed lol 14 PFC #3 😅 https://t.co/7Uu8Ou2UiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day One.  I have accepted a challenge to post 7 books I love: just covers, no reviews or explanation. Each day I wi… https://t.co/iKhyZkHWtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kica333 I’ve been pretty much off the grid all day. What did the petulant twat do just now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll be @rootdownbrewing today selling records and drinking beer, come by and hang out! @ Root Down Brewing Company https://t.co/qruh787pSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Balance in your life at school and at home will bring motivation and success. Don’t forget to practice #Habit7… https://t.co/o9NqztbgLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh Mighty One of Israel Our praises are here to lift up your name in honor and glory For all you've done for us Hea… https://t.co/grpwyKzoF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time after WMEA All Northwest hanging out with good friend and fellow Bach trumpet artist, Sarah Stoneback. https://t.co/RUGegIdKTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge save by @tuukkarask on Iafallo as LA had a 2-on-1 shorthanded chance  #NHLBruins #NHLKings #MetroBoston]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usatodaysports I like the idea. I think @SInow actually should do a special issue for Winter with skiers, snowboarders, ice skaters, etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I had a prospective ask me twice, "why do you say my website is not for me?"... after 20 seconds of silence, bec… https://t.co/XbArRY3v3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marinavibu609g @arcogarda @dykrh271 @marcosortega77 @BarryMeyer2 @atmanifarid @ZEYNAZERDA @grandesol2016… https://t.co/gikh8yjAwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Auuugh after weeks of seeing “unavailable”, I browse and find it available in 4K. You HAVE to work on this. It’s fa… https://t.co/TSjiV5f5AC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this the last page of #Jawbreakers book #2???  It ended so suddenly. I'm a little confused. It makes me think my… https://t.co/HULs0jQkKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next person to make fun of the Hex girls is gonna get a Mexican Grade A Hex from my mom that she learned in Turlock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Walnut Hill Station (DART Rail) - @dartmedia in Dallas, TX https://t.co/96aPhACOST]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscar Sunday or the only week of the year that the Sunday LAT is thicker than the NYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One ! !    https://t.co/92qDM8wrwo https://t.co/h4f1j3aWtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[People: "How you go and run 50k?" Me: "Drink coffee and eat chocolate bars...duh"  #ultrarunning #training… https://t.co/mRmeCvFPlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebukaemmanel @doublehelix @TheAuracl3 @11twiggins @huwlemmey Boston Marathon has rules around this as well IIRC, s… https://t.co/w5QjY1xVlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djt733 @FOXSports USC @ ND with the Bush Push. The Drive with Elway in Cleveland]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuamarlow5 No joke. One miracle run in 8 years doesn’t qualify for an extension when Clemson was literally abou… https://t.co/dLWKKl7nFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[This experiment has many purposes, but spoilers for you night owls, probably going to go this route for HASSP-3, as… https://t.co/xOESp2NbeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOS ✈️ SFO on Never a Dull MoMint (N937JB)  Flight is delayed 1h30m unfortunately. ☹️ https://t.co/XA9qq1aZV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume Brit! 1st memorable picture of you is when you were yelled at by Bill Clinton for asking a tough question, remember?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Sir,Personally what do you think of our president if you were not in Senate and Leader of the Senate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world won’t give this the justice it deserves but I sure as heck will! Incredible!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never begin change with the way things are...start with the way you want things to be. That way you wont talk yours… https://t.co/ULq6vvYFUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerHuckabee Pat Benatar, Betty White and George Foreman - while Pat Benatar is singing “Hit me with your best sh… https://t.co/GQIlE0CGMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RitterChris @chad_bowen @kevinwatson Yes sir. Talking with my church leaders last night, the first two plans were… https://t.co/45U1ykHNyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amarshallWHIO I had to book a flight to that little house down south.  😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think even the biggest diehard LBJ fan secretly would admit he's not being a good leader right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrossingBroad Maybe Tom Brady will think twice about that whole "Kiss your boss on the mouth" thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtracey Which is telling of the state of the Democrat party which has no real identity and yet also an oxymoron in… https://t.co/1glL82fiMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sidecar Orange IPA by @SierraNevada @ Swatty's Bar — https://t.co/pSxNZksb6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybonesshow @mrBobbyBones Pro tip Bobby...brush your teeth maybe?  The rest of you is flawless so, must be the halitosis?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night on Raw: no cheers *crickets*  Tonight on Smackdown Live: CHEERS!!!! #SDLive https://t.co/Nd7pBQcGDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManfredWeber @liliebayer @EPP @SPIEGELONLINE Better late than never - it took some time for the news in #Hungary to reach Bavaria...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freshman forward leads Faith Family past powerhouse Houston Yates in 4A state semis https://t.co/flzvrCrDRP YATES FALLS IN STATE  SEMIFINALS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp I’m not a Trumpster and I am not giddy. In fact I’m pretty pissed, both at Smollet and the media for preyin… https://t.co/ugop72z2qX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was going to watch a horror movie after the Leafs game but I feel like I just watched one. Full credit to New Yor… https://t.co/TK6KSjhHDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Big_Man_Mahan @Alex_Vice18 Better product. Better arena. Better attendance. I think that is what he’s saying https://t.co/iQvMOf86mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best gift you can give someone is your time, because you’re giving them something you can never get back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A furious (and visibly rattled) Premier Doug Ford lashes out at NDP for questioning his autism policies. Premier sa… https://t.co/BxKp7vFW6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mnewsince @SoncaGH @ABC “Pro-pandemic” is a good term.  Mostly I use “pro-plaguers” as a term indicating the end r… https://t.co/AmDJbf0bRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I felt that PT Anderson story about not saying a movie is bad. I respect that. But I also respect Spike Lee for mak… https://t.co/NQvECcjQXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@genebalk @typewriteralley My understanding is that larger, denser cities tend to have lower fatality rates.  So if… https://t.co/VGRvWSFVSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For God’s foolishness is wiser than human wisdom, and God’s weakness is stronger than human strength. 1 Corinthians… https://t.co/UADqoh6x4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikkikettle3 @MarthaStewart Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/XGCk15si7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bibbletron @Bungie 100%, not blaming Bungie at all. I just wish they'd implement something to penalize people who suicide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wellll it’s the annual UNC-Duke game. The only team worse than Cuse in my eyes #DukeAllDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinnertoSaint70 @matthewcerrone @coutinho9 @MattEhalt @SteveGelbs Definitely distasteful Ray]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mister_quint 😂😂 My last interview, my pants zipper broke as i stood from the lobby chair. Was f in sweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday March 8 - POLITICO Playbook:     23 House Republicans voted against a resolution Thursday evening that conde… https://t.co/27Jy85GlJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playan geometry  Remembering Black Rock City  #burningman #2018 #blackrockcity #instacollab #collab #remix #edit… https://t.co/VlRdwtAYQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Is Why You Don't See People-Size Salmon Anymore https://t.co/laJt4bqlar @jeffrey_ventre @she_maps @FsuGoody]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can do all the evaluation, development, scouting, etc. you want but at the end of the day you’re not going to t… https://t.co/WGs1gYuOcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who doubts climate change should be forced to watch @onestrangerock]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acampar. Aunque hayan -5 grados celsius en las afueras del Parque Nacional Zion, en Utah. Fogata, una cena nocturna… https://t.co/zOSsVa5oB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaheeres @miadventure @WOODTV If said ski mountain was getting ready to hold a hiring event that would put nearly… https://t.co/WO7XJoOAie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timinmitcham The people who need instruction on adulting are available for calling out on Friday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @Fatburger ..."Dee" from Miami at this downtown location is super friendly and super good at her job.."Thank you… https://t.co/M8aSMUOj4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zappafaye @beerhunter74 @thesushimaki @FestivalPlace @sake_tasty @ManvsAle @cellmavin @RealBMaxwell @wolv54b1… https://t.co/exRp4TpARM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social studies and science provide a compelling context for teaching reading and writing, and research shows litera… https://t.co/CKe6zTF3vI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Our military spending already has. We can borrow and kill to support the elite, but the working class… https://t.co/ZjPXqaZ5WB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet you keep following the Nazi Socialist left? Do you not know the history of the Nazis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wait to become famous so I can the convince the media to push anti-coleslaw agenda]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know what you're thinking It's just a storyline What's the big deal? The big deal is @VinceMcMahon has already ba… https://t.co/NIiOeThasq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game 2 is in the books. The Flames fall 8-2 to the UAH Chargers. Game 3 will be tomorrow at 2pm CT. Stay tuned for… https://t.co/o6bugob9zM]]></document></documents></author>