<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @KarenSLeonard1 @roads2 @AnwarManwar004 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Iluvinspireu @MelindaYoe @Jimmysimmonds1… https://t.co/MumEmrG7eK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl red flags:   -Is Proud of being a bitch -Doesnt care about health -Bad relationship w/ family  -Isnt nurturing… https://t.co/YcYeYWC9r5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenrart I’m glad I’m not the only outraged one... (also, that sounds fascinating, similar to what I study— I’d lov… https://t.co/pKp0gfLQ4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_waleedshahid @KanskeBra @SenFeinstein @sunrisemvmt @AOC @SenMarkey I actually think children should be able to vo… https://t.co/6N15htzgah]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOUSE ADOPTS AMENDMENT TO #HR1 TO REQUIRE  #RELEASE OF TRUMP’S BUSINESS  #TAX RETURNS ON TOP OF PERSONAL RETURNS  https://t.co/iIom67ga1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me minding my own business and suddenly remembering that's it's below freezing in March. https://t.co/k7xcKgyXxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all have something to learn from one another #KeepAnOpenMind #LearnFromAnother #BuildABetterTomorrow ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[An empty fridge, no running water and dead cockroaches. The horrible conditions of an Antioch home where two kids l… https://t.co/VkZs162usD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Jodie  I was born in the same face of a mess  My age is a bit annoying  I like to think about it but it… https://t.co/QWQv5DTQAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CillizzaCNN @CillizzaCNN unfortunately you work for a loser discredited news station YUK sad commentary on what is… https://t.co/lYoYT6Aaiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been reflecting a lot on mortality lately. A friend‘s life was cut short by suicide at 28 earlier this week. If can… https://t.co/1nPvcLtEPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnLadenberger @AnnCoulter @DrNikkiMartinez @CherylBlueWave @debfene @pam_brundige Scavengers and bottom-feeders usually do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLBStats He is or should be a no doubter Hall of Famer. Let’s get him in!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @SecNielsen,  Please resign, but don’t go to a nation without extradition treaties.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump “You the people”elected someone you knew was a liar, sex offender, adulterer and tax eva… https://t.co/oJfIiE6YL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Heung Min Son is in the form of his life. 2. Vinicius really didn’t have to drop him like that 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨ Chelsea Belle ✨ #cousins #cousinlove💕 #sd #sandiego #california @ Coasterra https://t.co/GWDZEXYsMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SupremacySupply @LoopGroupIO @SplashNotify @MelonMonitors @chefs412 @won_0925]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thebuljso @kellbell1024 EWW. 🤮 tbh I don’t like Brie Larson at all! She’s a hateful feminist. I don’t stand with h… https://t.co/IFUFx44kT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neo_mds @RealTristan13 If he cared half as much about ball then he does about cheating he might be at least a mediocre NBA player.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long Beach was beautiful! Can't believe I made it to the ocean - where I learned God loves me, and saw a random pie… https://t.co/pJ0me48tsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way Luke Combs talked about his girlfriend on stage last night is the way every girl should be talked about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m teaching myself spanish again before our cruise to cozumel in august lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dad bought some chickens &amp; joined a “chickens 101” facebook group]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you gotta go to work but you really don’t wanna #TheStruggleIsRealThisMorning https://t.co/IYpUHgjCKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaMaria_pasch I shall but you it will take me awhile to fly over 🍷🍷🍷😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 1862 Ale by @LandGrantBeer @ Eddie George Grill - CMH — https://t.co/n0ihY34kWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unbelievable! After seeing the news article, by the NRA, regarding @SpeakerPelosi and @GabbyGiffords. Now, this reg… https://t.co/xX6k8QqHwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched halloween by myself and I walked into the bathroom and my dog was hiding behind the toilet and pawed… https://t.co/46FMjVtHn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[!!!!!!!just trying to find someone to throw my love and affection at!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we are keeping it casual in an A-line dress from gap knee socks and @thefryecompany boots. #casual… https://t.co/zZYVLQCfK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[my philosophy professor is one of the funniest guys I’ve ever met... he wants us to complete a 5 question homework… https://t.co/MuaU8wYQXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joerexrode check out the end of the vandy ut game - UT was behind in the lst minute]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn’t get a chance to see it last night @RunTheRaceMovie is out now! I can’t wait to hear what y’all think!… https://t.co/VTyQTtiiIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It Exists: DOJ Finds Letter Ordering Scrutiny of Uranium One, Hillary Clinton https://t.co/tVSIO8lFZB via @thedailybeast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerSaidWhat @NeauxNegro This is very much incorrect. Solange just started getting her flowers. Her first album… https://t.co/760hAhe9Nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man was fatally dragged by a subway car in New York City  https://t.co/0LKNrEYkqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Footpath Thru -2 of 3 8” canvas paintings that I’m reworking. Cleaning up unfinished work. #acrylicpainting… https://t.co/I3atisvrV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing #SXSW this year but me and @sheistyler are working on a few 🔥 stories for @_theplugdaily to help you naviga… https://t.co/X3Z5Mpb3r8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so emotional today... have cried twice this morning over nothing; a deer scaring me and a car cutting me off...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brandyrayanne__ Literally me, I can’t watch it in public anymore bc I get so sensitive 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't post WIPs often but here's one! Can you tell I like this series yet? 🤔 https://t.co/UIUWq9yL0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next up: @MaricopaGOP Chairman @rae_chornenky. We love having Rae in #Ahwatukee with us! Thank you Rae! #LD18GOP… https://t.co/SLjbkGDZjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCWriterMom @celestyalcruise @MyVirtualVaca @CruiseCritic I like the size of their ships. Service was great, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING @ The Waterford at Valley Ranch Apartment Homes https://t.co/1xZ0xW5nGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Active learning presentation by  @JCCCtweet @JCCCfacultydev You are doing great work! #19INNNYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChynaJoanLaurer Congratulations to Chyna getting in as a member of #DGenerationX  I hope one day this women's pion… https://t.co/iWDLwYOKx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has got to be the busiest, most challenging semester of my entire law school career 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t get me started on talking about cars if your facts aren’t 100% because I will absolutely flame you until you… https://t.co/KrE23weBRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s an amazing feeling to be excited to work again rather than loathing it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Q. Who feels you cannot achieve what you do achieve before you do?? A. Surprisingly,  professionals, well as standa… https://t.co/0d65IQFWRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmc663 @dotCO However, you’re right one one issue...I AM FASCINATING...utterly. I’d like to warn companies out the… https://t.co/HK6092NNGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not LA but a few more and it could be 🤣🤣🤪🤪 @ The Cheesecake Factory https://t.co/U54Uv0gMLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camila3056 @jonasbrothers @afullsnack Omg! I can't believe we used to watch that video on repeat lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence @AliVelshi good news finally to share https://t.co/A7SrITsfdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blue States Band Together in Open Attack on Constitution: Aim To Completely Destroy Electoral College https://t.co/4ZuneLN2GQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revjamesrobison I love your TV show. I watch from Toronto,  Canada. You and Betty are beautiful people and a beaut… https://t.co/yaajdNhCOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was just told that a Trader w a Discord room of 800 people is sayin $VYST is over, and said about me that i was n… https://t.co/a83z5m93EP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolRcb @Bport_PIT LMFAO NICE PROFILE IN THE CORNER!!!!! Do you have anything else better to do than bully som… https://t.co/JRYR1AynqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSThisMorning @GayleKing And NOW that he is also financially bankrupt, what do these 2 do for shelter, food, clot… https://t.co/FAQBEy6Kbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColumbiaBugle @michellemalkin The chain migration worked to my family’s advantage, if not I won’t be enjoying this… https://t.co/wrhCkuHm2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[PBC ON FOX  our @rosieperezbklyn is in the house Great Girl I Miss her.  Its Fight Night Figueroa / Molina good fight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SbabeckaStacie @WhitAlmany Looks like a tamed herd you have trained this year @Tools_PreKTeach]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 @LindseyGrahamSC @HouseGOP @SenateGOP Absolutely Positively 💯%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "MSW"? What did you like most about that job? #SocialSciences #Saginaw, MI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angieecakes12 I was quietly admiring how perfect his skin was. He looked like a mannequin doll, it was unreal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Regardless, its a lot better then where we were with Obama ignoring the problem, Kim Jong Un threatening… https://t.co/8L1FzBqW3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird day, but good dinner! (at @Wendys in Austintown, OH) https://t.co/KDM0utG0t5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prnirvana @righty64 @RamblingPariah @atrupar Yes, we can agree on certain aspects of this, including that choice i… https://t.co/eOVCoZ0w3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Jose Antonio Vargas share is story of being undocumented at @NCRC #justeconomy conference. Powerful wo… https://t.co/2OniMF8EJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy21626593 @RLIGHT87 @abby_loftus @BJ_Stew @KyleKashuv @benshapiro Yes! A survivor confronting the man who chose not to help him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIVE: Yellow Vest protests continue for 14th straight week in Paris https://t.co/mVDF4fCaA5 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FromTheLabBench I can tell you from personal experience that @NOOMinc regularly references scientific studies and… https://t.co/vT7mYcxdqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you know an undergrad who loves the ocean, this sea semester is absolutely amazing. You learn a ton, you travel,… https://t.co/PEchnd374d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biggest pet peeve!!!                                     People who disrespects the arm forces!!!! #airforce #army… https://t.co/dCYKW2LhF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brevard Public Schools Teacher Job Fair 03/15/19 registration on the Brevard home page!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Puahashopgirl My years as a Hospice RN has taught me to never try to predict the future of life and/or death. It w… https://t.co/WKCoz9e9w8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherPhysioc AI4 Healthcare is a good one, but no specifically focused on marketing: https://t.co/0PNoMVCEmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad// I was looking through old emails and I saw these and almost started having a breakdown during lecture I'm so… https://t.co/96U8CnVtsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda depressing. But not surprising, I’m sad to say. The suburban area where I work is fairly homogeneous. Still,… https://t.co/gSD0U9VC1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[How old is Khloe Kardashian? She has too many coins to act like Tristan’s doormat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THD_Victoria @nyyroro @JackieGiusti @skfroude @DaveThd11 @mapmd277 @macateri @strainStrainmik @chadmetzger33 @tornillo_john 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samstein @mattgaetz I hope they bounce your sorry ass us code 18.1505 makes your threat today a crime.  Maybe you… https://t.co/bpfIgSiJuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[KFC by candlelight. Day 3 without power. It's a cool 50 degrees in my house. ❄❄ https://t.co/EN4OFFFy3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Thanksgiving. Seriously. I’m not a religious person, but I love Thanksgiving because it’s the essence o… https://t.co/UYMn2tRQJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just going to say that cancer is the worst. I am grieving the loss of someone who hasn’t passed yet but is not who… https://t.co/MgB7Sfr9Mi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_MrKev Jajaja me mama como manejan aqui aunque todos se quejen esta cm]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week is crazy in the greatest way possible! Gonna have tons of fun at work this week!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cngoolsby2014 @DreamsInColor33 Always praying 🙏🏽🙏🏽🙏🏽 with two kids and two dogs I can use a fresher smelling house lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adorbbsss_ @taiilor_ oop... I didn’t know she was letting the cat out the bag like that lol https://t.co/3Z14Sn8Xvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate the Day is your balloon and gift shop in Nashville! 615-613-3282 #confettiballoons #popme #balloonshop… https://t.co/qQ3twbBYKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope everyone is excited to meet all of the business jumpsuits I impulse purchased while watching The L Word.  It… https://t.co/lWhZdhMI5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitch please you can’t be sad if you got someone mending your “broken heart”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA I say it all the time. There are creatures (unfortunately more than I knew) who have fully mutated from hum… https://t.co/N2K1aPEAJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vowswithinhb Just need Stone outta there and full tank mode will commence]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait until the day that Saylor brings home an animal without asking, and I have to pretend like I’m mad at… https://t.co/6pLb0sIuTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing #whidbeyisland #camanoisland #quilt by #marydownes #quiltsofinstagram  #handpainted #freemotionquilting… https://t.co/V7JQd0mZVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @BarackObama #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass  #MarALardass… https://t.co/OH53u7fqF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sec201 @JohnFPfaff Just here to make sure you both know about this gem (for iOS). It’s $1.99 but WORTH IT. PS awes… https://t.co/Cw8ycK6zXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBReich @GAVAPeach Traitor Trumps MO. Create A False Emergency. Then Party Like Its 1999. Right? Traitor.]]></document></documents></author>