<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@neversaydie @BlackLabelNSD where do you guys announce the winners of your giveaways? I entered multiple giveaways… https://t.co/8pUhcvDMLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend tells me it’s easy for you. Yeah I invite someone over or go to them ... watch Netflix and randomly my di… https://t.co/VGobu6T778]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the #FridayFortyNYC for @HPPlayNYC on @TodayTix! Get tickets for performances next week at $40 ($20 per Part) #CursedChildNYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyMans_Ricky @NahNahBad @emmett_gg Spongebob pissed https://t.co/dGfzCuJsny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Tax incentive articles... without knowing the details of the Amazon deal, I think it’s impossible for anyone t… https://t.co/4cHDMIKs81]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back-to-back buckets by the Gators, on either side of a charge and travel by the Wildcats, and Florida had the defi… https://t.co/KHFeokWOVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACSOSheriffs @LivePdFans @IFlyOAKland Him: "Typical. Never a cop when you need one." Glad y'all are safe]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone gave you 1 million dollars in BTC right now, would you sell for fiat immediately (can't buy back in) or hold it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This photo, taken last fall, is now equated with @TeawithTolkien in my mind after a coworker said it looks like the… https://t.co/ODoqYsKQ7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHAME on @BernieSanders for supporting the abominable narco-dictatorship of @NicolasMaduro responsible for the deat… https://t.co/YXkWJZCFkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright, enough of this. What's next? #WWEFastLane https://t.co/SKjiZqksyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess what! @MrBeanStalker just earned 250 Fluffy Fills on Karmic Care Bear points for Galactic Level 2… https://t.co/EzHZtVsJY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone’s personal journey takes them down the road of self-development, great.   If they can share the experien… https://t.co/0EdLKBCJFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one made him play basketball lmao also... Free education, free food, free place to live, free medical treatment.… https://t.co/GTM1Yrk22M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emwesterb @LAFitness EMILY!! Message me ASAP I’ll take care of you make it super easy and cut fees down! I’ll take… https://t.co/7Pwja5603J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont want to better than what i was before. I want to be better than ive ever been.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@santorendon @AlvaroUribeVel @mluciaramirez @gusgomez1701 @rabodeajip @IvanDuque @MariaFdaCabal @PalomaValenciaL… https://t.co/Ky0DZJn8xs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kausmickey And what did/do you see as the principle problems of AFDC? Are they incidental - i.e. if in the event t… https://t.co/VKeskvtcua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Half_Ref I didn't have audio on so I didn't know but that's cool. It's like timber sports for knife makers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sq3Swf @MrB0033 @BinesVargas @PolinJess Haha...so sorry...I meant to tag her dad @sq1723 !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badrobot68 I mean I’m so close the gorge that it’s never not windy for me but I understand where you’re coming from]]></document><document><![CDATA[T pain new album is amazing! “Lambo in that driveway Gucci on that body!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikenedie @cyclone_cowgirl @zypisfy @yourmumspants @Cern_lXXl @tklforgiven @Heliocoptero @KotobaruSanSama… https://t.co/LVWlArPSgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The time I got Paige to mow the lawn @ Dover, New Hampshire https://t.co/SHGPqEJtII]]></document><document><![CDATA[Financial Aid presentation for @MadisonDistPS. #empowering the future @OCCollege students.… https://t.co/VMjqC9vzl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nikki_0422 @Phoenixnjpw @AndyNemmity Tried again today for tickets but had no luck I hope there will be a live str… https://t.co/motyCbQJ9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Dream Chasers! #NoExcuses  Check this out: https://t.co/eoVJmCb0MT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mistressmatisse @Maggie_McNeill @44ina4door Well. Having listened to @44ina4door all night, it is clear she has no… https://t.co/I0PMdkewRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE AMERICAN PEOPLE  KNOW THE DEMOCRATS ARE OUT TO DESTORY OUR COUNTRY...KEEP IT UP AMERICAN PEOPLE WILL VOTE REPUB… https://t.co/OCNLFQWpd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT ... That time I didn’t win the #SuperBowl with the saints but found my way in the #pic anyways 😳😂😳😏 #WhoDat… https://t.co/199NjmWyRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to Graceland University's very own, Ashly Gassoway #GUJACKETS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sonoma Saturday. #sonomaraceway . . . . .  #agameoftones #splendid_transport #visualsgang #igcars #instagoodmyphoto… https://t.co/FELWDg8BxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astanek07 @EdPiotrowski @VannagrammyLiz @jimmbsc @jamiearnoldWMBF @SydneyWPDE @wmbfweather @TheSunNews… https://t.co/nqOprsdVjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Night 1 shots from @BarWrestling "Threes Company" https://t.co/47ow41diJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out @BradleySoftball with some deserved recognition after the weekend power surge in New Mexico.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's @TimTebow at the plate in the eighth for the #Mets. Grounds out to first. https://t.co/z82jeHUp6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter That's Exactly What A Dictator Does. Spies On His Own People]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep your eye on the prize, my friends and Happy Friday! #happy #happyfriday #keepyoureyeontheprize @ Bridgehampton… https://t.co/qAKGZogRJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Makes Its Debut In the Live Video Space https://t.co/TBfqMG1Wl7 via @socialmediaweek]]></document><document><![CDATA[MJ played with one other all star, Pippen! If MJ teamed up with the 3 best players in his draft class like Lebron,… https://t.co/nN9wzjUIzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/tzQoSFvgCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LRYALL140 @Canes228 Better than yalls season just before that. So like what was yalls in 2017? 2016?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnMacDoug @RiceUniversity I'd say it also depends on the quality of the data it's being applied to, and, critica… https://t.co/MjSKrh0Mdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IGN @StevenDehler The Captain Marvel I grew up with was a man. I won't be going to see this movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Newest addition to the team! If you see us we would love to meet you. So say Hi!  -to Tried N True Home Solutio… https://t.co/wGHjbh4Q7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im bored af in my hotel room someone run some imessage games or something 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wait to become famous so I can the convince the media to push my anti-coleslaw agenda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andrew Atterson is inviting you to join Kids Earn Cash. I just earned $141.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a… https://t.co/XShEjpYEtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trust in your good work. Great things are coming. https://t.co/8l1sGgnBVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: SF Preps Basketball: Mission Bears upset top seed St. Mary’s, Thursday playoff results - San Franc… https://t.co/XBOvZaJqDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[7) Not only are our interpretations of the world often arbitrary, but we’re often overconfident in them. “Our ignor… https://t.co/L5FLtvpzKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vic Fangio on if he’s like to add a young quarterback: “We’d like to add good young players everywhere.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBellRacing brings his @ToyotaRacing #Supra down pit lane while on his way to win the @XfinityRacing… https://t.co/W8EVXSZCDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trollkashi @TfdGhost @1called_manders @IMPACTWRESTLING @ClevelandBrowns @WhereImFrom @RockwellMasks… https://t.co/tg83tHNfkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaiinHunterr Hey! I may be a moron but I know the English language. Seems like something you would respect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#recordoftheday #vinyl #vinylcollection #album #albumcover #glencampbell glencampbellofficial reminds me of traveli… https://t.co/tbf8iNiCqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The second I finish writing this piece, I’m popping on that new Solange]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Whoosh #LonnieJohnson's Super-Soaking Stream of Inventions” #ChrisBarton  #literacymatters #imagesmatter… https://t.co/4rHfhBhVhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve just been told that the B1G Championships are sold out here @GopherWrestling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariahCarey I’ll be great as a fellow ATLiean you preform  - A No No - Vanishing - Underneath the stars - Babydoll… https://t.co/EmKmjQV3WG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhhShay_ @maids @IrisTheMeme @zookdook @buratei https://t.co/cdCoAAAYEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not impressed with people dismissing them because they are kids - they were manipulated by adults, they are being u… https://t.co/dfwoVkViAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Minuteman223 Warm here this morning bottom dropping out tomorrow 2to3 inch accumulation for the weekend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a great day with great friends! #GTvsFSU #DidntGetFreeTShirts @ McCamish Pavilion https://t.co/X8jKPAaGVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody wants it too much. Always dangerous at #Oscars time.   “But that’s not to say Close will be crestfallen if… https://t.co/RJ1rGMBsD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anything to say for yourself @TTChelps ? @TTCchris ? This was called out before the fleet went into service. Need a… https://t.co/2Mzt62tCzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RabellRenee @Wblscott1 @bethtcoast Democrats have become asocial and nihilist...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always make time for an ice cream run even if it is cold outside! @ Wanderlust Creamery https://t.co/ADDQJw3h2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the realest MAN on campus @CAM_KEEPIT1000, bless up, the day is yours 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexkingham The Butkises adopting kids so they had workers for the salvage yard was the bit that got me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BostonKeith @TheSoccerGoose Would be interesting to see what did not make the cut.]]></document><document><![CDATA[u cannot be ugly and a bitch. u have to choose. sorry I don’t make the rules.]]></document><document><![CDATA[laugh and move on. Dog Grooming, Funny Dog Quote Art Print, Typographic Print, Digital Print Wall Decor, Bathroom W… https://t.co/LNRAd3BLdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[stretch marks are hot as shit I do not care what yall men gotta say give me a girl with or without stretch marks it don’t matter]]></document><document><![CDATA[submitting my first article for our newsletter today at work! super pumped😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing everyone a safe weekend! :) . . . #positivevibes #thankful #unicorn #owls #paintingclass #paint #art… https://t.co/ZWq5Yc605U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AutumnJoi Problem is mainstream media is giving him a lifeline by not covering this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MORE: @GovRaimondo spokesperson tells me ALL state offices are open in RI today because #PresidentsDay isn’t observ… https://t.co/HD2mnZde9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got up on time for the first time in WEEKS! Oh @Arsenal you're always there for me. #FuckYouDepression #COYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[How it feels to get the Dame 5s right before your game @Dame_Lillard @trailblazers https://t.co/RfzeIqXWEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shirleman @Han_Cholo I would say that’s easily the best Outkast song of all time, but hard to justify as the best… https://t.co/nliiEdnqNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out episode 7 of the podcast before episode 8 drops shortly! https://t.co/MlUctIMSO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol we send our own product south to be refined to be sent back up with markup to go to eastern Canada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToosUnderHigh @TheLantern @OutRInn @threesabovehigh @threesabovehigh is one of those select few bars I was talking about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@soniachocron Si vas a comentar mis tweets, lo cual agradezco, ten al menos la amabilidad de desbloquearme, ya que… https://t.co/293k2naohV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dog that drowned in the snow... (Backyard) @ Payson, Arizona https://t.co/JHIzfJCzQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheVOLColonel Yes..and which of the KY thugs broke Grant's nose during one of the many times they knocked him down… https://t.co/hpe0K5Nst3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul @roripierpont1 They're out of the country. THAT'S progress for the country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyTurrill I say “everyone in this class is your network. Build it. Maintain it. Invest in it.” @MaryvilleGame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anntopanga21 @JoshMatlow @JohnTory @fordnation https://t.co/aoih3G9Qgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiberalismReal @AOC @langeluntao I agree that the overpacked busses going into NJ from NYC suck.  NYC needs to red… https://t.co/pIPoErJtTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the #Phillies lose out in Harper over something stupid like an opt-out, I will be pissed. Probably the only way I’d see this as a failure]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know you’re probably never gonna see or reply to this but I got the police banquet on Friday if you tryna go 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alec Lewis with two 3-pointers in the same trip!!! @ShoremenBball closing in on tourney berth for first time since… https://t.co/3FA8YmCkHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Microsoft: The Path To Consumer #AR Is ‘Measured In Years’  https://t.co/cxmyhmXxfU # via @UploadVR Hopefully… https://t.co/BSDNmyquJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever listen/download a song and you're like "yeah pretty good" but then MONTHS later it comes on again and you'… https://t.co/LoUKNIcDpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much tax and tuition money did Stockton University pay the dirty #SPLC to falsely blame Trump for the hate it w… https://t.co/r6rjd8sozz]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔴ÚLTIMA HORA: GUAIDÓ RESPONDE FUERTE A RUSIA Y CHINA https://t.co/rQ4yjNPChS via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apex Legends is really starting to show its rough edges.  Hopefully a big patch is coming with the season 1 battle… https://t.co/4YxAZIrQ6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheVoice what about that past minute turning chair?? I always think that the director are at the trainers ears shouting “wait, wait” Now!!!]]></document></documents></author>