<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RepJerryNadler @WVGOP @Ilhan Guess that's not a issue when you have a foreign agent on your payroll. Come clean REP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewUpton3 Eggs sausage bacon and coffee is all they gotta add then bang they got breakfast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melicolor Quizás de primero con el tiempo te acostumbras a otras culturas ,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time, the Lions came ready to play. Here’s my recap of Bishop Ryan’s 68-30 win over Our Redeemer’s in the cham… https://t.co/GCWBKY3ILX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at what I've been up to in [Lords Mobile]! https://t.co/cQ5XuW0rzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 20th birthday bro, nothing but love for you brother @Sal_licciardi https://t.co/te0bx1z0yJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobNosbush @5787cdt @FabianArdaya Please refrain from posting this. My boss saw i was looking at this and threat… https://t.co/sOPEcD4EFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Samar3450 @Abisexy1212 Definitely beautiful! Defiantly perfection she defiantly is!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️… https://t.co/vwde4bz9DR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V_Rheault Body Removal Specialist--with cute pet dragon. https://t.co/p9QYVoDgPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theCarrieNugent @heathdwilliams Wait what movie is he in? He’s in TFA?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@owens1424 @classydirtymind Definitely beautiful! Defiantly perfection she defiantly is!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to get coffee. Paid for it. And drove off without it. Didn’t realize till I got to school. H8 myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to say it’s not a National Emergency if you’ve been casually planning it for months.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point idgaf where Harper/machado sign I’m just tired of hearing the daily rumors https://t.co/IoWMYlqSlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry Police lives Matter!!! But it doesn’t matter what color! We love them all. I don’t care what that hate f… https://t.co/fUzUzm5lnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very much looking forward to catching up with the awesome Pat Williams tomorrow at 4 pm on Behind The Law with Just… https://t.co/xTCXllYoAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjelliot67 There are a lot of security options out there. It is ultimately going to come down to what do you want… https://t.co/rKSl3LBxC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is Dolinde, half-orc barbarian expertly drawn by @Dewidiot Clearly, you should get #DnD character drawings don… https://t.co/QB0rJmQiON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night in town @agentajt got to hit in_andout_burger @ In-N-Out Burger https://t.co/YK4NiLddrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God I live in a city I can get around without buying a car I need instead of a car I want]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZCarr39 There needs to be someone at the registrars office or who ever records new births with the power to say ar… https://t.co/GxYyA9Vz8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[D-Wade’s statue in Miami should be him standing on top of the scorer’s table. One of the more iconic images in NBA… https://t.co/g5ONuLtO8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@granttruax Bud, his hand is starting to go up before I even reach step. https://t.co/2DtdsvWc7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrdenkpeclass @fitamerica @PE4Learning @PEgeeks @IAHPERD https://t.co/x4rRJeBtl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosayyLmao @SerenityRay9 @punmagnate @notviking Marzo = march  Mayo = may  L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayInslee 2/28/2019 NASA reports human activity has caused an increase in the greening of planet earth.  Video exi… https://t.co/fn3fCqXPxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tommy Beard is charged with kidnapping and accused of taking pictures of unconscious girls while posing as an Uber… https://t.co/WESfJpt3TH]]></document><document><![CDATA[toronto hit unfortunately the hottest team in the nhl st. louis blues with 11 straight wins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tundrawolfqueen @Hell_HasCome @ZombieAlertZulu @cspippin @dwaynecobb @deepdvr1234 @IBda14U @wonderfullone @ashau68… https://t.co/GiKJVdbKH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all departments, keep on craftin....for yourself.  #Oscars is just the icing on the cake! #inmemoriam]]></document><document><![CDATA[APPARENTLY WITHIN THE NEXT 160 YEARS WE MOVE UNDER THE OCEANS FOR WHAT IS COMING. THEY WILL SAVE US FROM WHAT IS CO… https://t.co/M1oKKUwqFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. 🙏 These players are our heroes. They are our idols. They are our entire freaking world in moments like these.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RedSox lineup vs NYY: Hernández, G. LF, León C, Devers DH, Castillo CF, Brentz RF, Chavis 3B, Lin 2B, Ockimey 1B,… https://t.co/YcTzTH3Hsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dia 4-5. Los Angeles, passejant entre el glamour i aixafant l’alfombra vermella abans d’hora. #primoscatusa en Los… https://t.co/tdWfq6ApZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattOswaltVA - Almost Famous, the end, Russell walking to William's room, answering what he loves about music? To… https://t.co/9vXt92Dj2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not only a boxing reporter. I’m a spiritualist, trilingual, a college graduate, an Army veteran but what I’m mo… https://t.co/HVBFxnLbYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDBank_US get your shit together. Your online banking is down every other day..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philosophrob @JosieIsTired In other words: She needs to be primary-ed hard next cycle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Son coming to visit requested pound cakes , ask and you shall receive. https://t.co/1wte0aFazA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalWakefield @snappingtitan @ManaByte ... it has nothing to do with defending it. I’m talking about the dates. H… https://t.co/cBPR9ecnUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[good job I am a winner I won 200 coins playing in Miami Beach 9 Ball! https://t.co/bCuEtRZQjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are Soldiers of Nigerian Army that have left their fight against terrorists in the North Eastern part of Nige… https://t.co/lHoxlr2j5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Brunella Craftbeer &amp; Gins in Hermosillo, SON https://t.co/mMvq3Zz5EO]]></document><document><![CDATA[FroKnowsPhoto is GIVING AWAY a CAMERA, LENS and MORE, hurry, get entered now!!! https://t.co/z29SIWzIrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethanyshondark Really - color me shocked. Trump GOP is hypocritical.  Noooo you don't say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xfinity i have to share this.  I have had satellite internet and TV service for the past 13 years.  I have had… https://t.co/Wgoz6nORFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParisHilton thank you for signing all these, I’ve had more but I didn’t want to bother you lol. Love you 💕… https://t.co/RT1QLQvBjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan Pulock arrived in the second half of last year and finished with 10 goals and 32 points. He’s now at the 30-po… https://t.co/336tymrmZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tu demonio 😈? Tu angelito 😇? Que prefieres que sea ? https://t.co/LCFLQo6ZPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qabaret At The Call  #Qabaret, #queer #cabaret #burlesque #Thecall @ Call Bar https://t.co/au57oTAMVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalCaribbean I planned a surprise birthday party for my wife, she had no clue the other six friends were joining… https://t.co/Nqo1vahMX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErasSociety @ERAS_USA I hope we will be represented @FHCCRS @AdventHealth @georgenassifjr Remains a game changer for our patients.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔 FINALLY FOUND THE PERFECT NAME FOR OBAMA 🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔 @realDonaldTrump @Liz_Wheeler @LouDobbs @marklevinshow https://t.co/aQlKHLHUGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheDevil2202 Para que no salgua caro ir al cinemejor miralo en tu cel jaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hombredeltiempo @sebasrocha96 Otra evidencia GFS modelo muestra vientos de componente N/NNW entre 925/850 mb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In reality I can do English good if I try, but stringing coherent sentences is so highfalutin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald I would pay ridiculous sums of money if I had it to have @ggreenwald replace @maddow on MSNBC.... he ju… https://t.co/bh5zbh5fvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atebbel For food biggest recs I have is Fire Ramen in Kyoto which is a great tourist trap and have a Sutadon/Sutam… https://t.co/ki8yMTtfHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tornado likely in the storm just northeast of Houston MS https://t.co/O8XKlw7FSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOXSportsDet @gordonbeckham @tigers @BrookeFletcher @AwningMarygrove Congrats on the job, @rleesonofficial. @wahles54]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoggyToasterino I’m in the same boat. Things get better I promise. If you’re feeling creatively clogged go do some… https://t.co/IEHlgjzsNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red.  Violets are blue AI can hurt workers  Or help them out too  #2MA @mit_ide @MIT_IIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most generous nation and people. Any garbage is direct result of Democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little uncomfortable with the whole, “Will Colton end up getting laid????? Find out tonight!!!” #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 more fucking day till I see @TeamSESH with my friends!! Its gonna be so hype!!🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_Pruitt1 @ISPIndianapolis Even better a visit at work from #Colts Mascot @Blue Wife will be ecstatic 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 66 of #Gymshark66 - here’s my 1st chapter &amp; progress pic coming tomorrow @Gymshark… https://t.co/0uDg3VAP2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TCNT Caller: "Do you know what time the @mnwild are playing today?" Me: "... no." Caller: "Can you look?" Me: "...… https://t.co/eHLeOJVO8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current Readings :  2/28/19, 07:25:56 AM Deg: 65.5°F R.H.: 91.2% H.I: 66.2°F D.P.: 62.9°F S.P.: 30.05inHg D.A.: 526ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who talks about others like they really exist , its time to exit my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one is streaming and I’m too sick to pick up my guitar or controller. https://t.co/iCtJJqMrLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me drinking the complementary water in the lobby before an interview https://t.co/IxW6UKm9oT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stm_Orange ça ne vous tentes pas d’essayer de ne pas synchroniser le métro qui arrête à H-B avec le train de 17:15 de @exo2_SJ ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are right, @karlie_sampson!  T.C.O.E.O. = Take Care Of EachOther!  #BeUncommon  #LadyVikingsHoops  #weareVILLAGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SIA wins Payments Canada’s tech revamp contract https://t.co/WW3c5swArr via @FinTech_Futures #fintech]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colbykobe84 I only like kuzma and Lebron. That’s just me. I miss randle. Right now get talent for ball/Ingram because I’m not sold]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t swallow the whistle. Screw that. We all want consistency. Call the game the same all game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Havent really really sang in a good year or so due to a herniated belly button so i been letting it heal for a long… https://t.co/QgVAFhPTXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They went to the bathroom like this...  so they could compare notes if you know what I mean https://t.co/hO7vE4vwou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @AOC You right wing hacks sure are afraid of her aren't you? Is it because she doesn't take the coope… https://t.co/HBkvZxk2Zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump JIM Jordan then famous coach who knew nothing.  Playing the righteous trump acholite. Power over t… https://t.co/7K0VDQ63WR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Wheeler @Heritage Was there something in the bill  that scared them on some “slippery slope” argument??? What the heck! Messed up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida fans still upset UGA beat out Gators for 4-star QB https://t.co/IimQH3Zmet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obstacles are placed in our way to see if what we want is really worth fighting for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FhSection @JaredGatewood Must've found a Duke Cheer sheet and changed the team names.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always knew I wasn’t going home. Kinda tough. Ain’t gonna fake it to make it. 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to really watch my shows before social media manages to ruin them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@townernation @jslovegrove @MegKinnardAP Making up for lost bbq during my years in the Pee Dee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachJohnsonPGA @JohnDeere Can’t wait to see your bracket and the trash talk 🏀🤜🏼🤛🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craltieri @inesanma @Crux From the three point line for the win. Now that the first meeting is complete, the next… https://t.co/uG80CzZnXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[at every urinal of the #StadiumSeries there’s a pic of a different Penguin’s player😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorettatheprole @RepMarkMeadows The Dems have made a deal w/the Devil. They want the Muslim voting bloc in their p… https://t.co/PKgNaD6gma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asinine.  1. Why would #JussieSmollett give his bosses a heads up to a scheme to get more attention and therefore m… https://t.co/CeNoZ9P5XA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ianpinky1234 @CouRageJD @Nadeshot That's not George Strait. It's  Keith Whitley.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we know as horses comprise two different components: A beast of burden from the species Equus ferus caballus b… https://t.co/MffXGdOKac]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know Britney Spears hasn’t been relevant in a minute, but this was not the come back we were hoping for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“so what would you do if I would’ve kissed you last night ahaaa” https://t.co/qnUcFI4lts]]></document><document><![CDATA[among the Rocco’s i’m famous for dealing with childhood trauma particularly well]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dickswingsandgrill #bonelesswings #saintaugustine I wonder if the #wingmonster would commute for some wings with m… https://t.co/MrVBlUNWaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HassNassar La orden:  -Hassan nos molestan con el vestido, crea una manera de hacernos quedar bien, y dile a claud… https://t.co/pvnZiN4q5E]]></document></documents></author>