<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Happy 67th bday Dad! Miss you every day. Think of you often. Your best quality was always making others feel loved… https://t.co/fEi5YeTWLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might've lost a bf but not entirely my best friend lol so why this shit hurt so much?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @seanhannity @FoxNews Do you think BMW might be interested in moving to NY since Amazon was turned… https://t.co/CkuK8ErScl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrows the day I start working out! Wish me luck because I am not ready for it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisneyFoodBlog ok so we’re going this summer to Disneyland for the first time ever, do you have a video for this o… https://t.co/1oPcWuVHKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[A packed house, eyes glued to the TV’s. UNC fans are filled with confidence starting this game https://t.co/hzNLIw5lOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je suis en train de jouer au 7e joueur sur https://t.co/n2Q4wRet2i. Joins-toi à moi ! https://t.co/p9OWZK0cVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[What?! If you don’t care about developing leaders, you don’t care enough for the frontline they serve. Magenta does… https://t.co/1SiHvbVayK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Ladies, if you don’t won’t to be kissed or hugged when being approached, introduced or greeted by a… https://t.co/bIeJhCcWkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any Houston commuter will tell you it feels like they're spending more and more time in their car. Now there are so… https://t.co/cOAP80wObK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont know why people wanna see Ja Rule fail so bad... wasn't that nigga on almost every record in the early 2000s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Can't click on any choice. Definitely no Bernie, Biden may be too old. There is a place for women but… https://t.co/kzZgK7Q5rR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramirezcraig67 @Anton47492193 @TonyaRBlue1 @JessieLynnJL @JessieLynnFans @BradHeyden @KFearri @RoverDov123… https://t.co/ic4Inxrrg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trish05014259 @Sammy_Markle And in the future, dont address any issues you have with me to include Samantha Markle… https://t.co/M1kLUJW0H0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RHinCHELSEA @thehill Anyone with this shit in their feed. https://t.co/OCDuUruqFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano You want the country to be a safer place? So do I. So do all “real”  #Americans. Join us and speak o… https://t.co/m2whJggY5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[This new bill is being discussed TODAY! I’ll have the live report at 6:30 am on @10NewsWTSP @BrightsideOn10]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time man everytime... i try and i try...pointless action after pointless action]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RyanBasford Trump is a treasonous liar who has ruined our Country for the sake of Russia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Possibly having coffee at 1am wasn’t my best decision ever. I mean, who does that? https://t.co/Y1KYmH248I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marcia has been trying out my new lanyards. Come see me at booth #637 at #cue19 for 3D printed pancakes, stickers,… https://t.co/o8PrDuujTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__ajaxx @SsssamanthaaMUA @RawBeautyKristi I feel like being friends with them is just like being wrapped in love a… https://t.co/0rNREGao31]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living with myself is great because I NEVER refill the water pitcher and I ALWAYS forget that I didn't refill it un… https://t.co/S1QD0ZVL3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was a great way to start off my day, but we still have a long way to go! https://t.co/sbqRjoh6ez]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is disgraceful! Who were these terrorists that disrespected our President?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly @focusbutterfly The Democrats are the party doing the lynchings without any remorse. They like to poin… https://t.co/M7zbKYFk8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard It's just plain old leftwing bigotry against traditional Americans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy planeando un viaje relámpago para este fin de semana. Estaré visitando Nueva York y Nueva Jersey. Y en honor… https://t.co/hmurl0g1R4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLatondress @spazuzoo @barryt30 @NGIinsights @CanadaFirst7 @MaximeBernier @peoplespca FPV #71: Is The PPC's Johann… https://t.co/QaWyExE5BO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods Hunny you’re grown. this is immature kid behavior]]></document><document><![CDATA[The key difference in JWR using “my truths” is that she is limited in what she can say, and that she can only speak… https://t.co/EtO1mi2kOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[To study abroad this summer in Spain or to take a higher position at work this April 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Podcasts that are worth the listen are HARD to make! I wonder how hard it was to compile @LyynR #TheHabitat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soul_of_Nowhere Teaching while you’re well is hard!  And handing out sporks is damn near impossible!  Hope your meds kick in!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just going to obsess over the new s’mores and butterscotch dishes for the next two days until I finalize what I… https://t.co/1Nh1WwrO8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llego Marzo! Hello March! Feliz fin de semana @ Villa Fátima https://t.co/qbrEGssHVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGAgirly @pjbowles4 @GeanineC @DaveSchreiber3 @ImabitcSumtimes @lbc360 @jonz970 @raducom @Serremmy @GinnyGinny_1… https://t.co/0JgLXiJBwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[NeNe always telling me about myself and keeping it a stack and I never listen🤦🏾‍♀️. As she says we only growing fro… https://t.co/P1eHSETX3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lil Mike and Funny Bone Live today pco High Scool. Come see them! Until 1pm. #livemusic @ Putnam City High School https://t.co/Hi91QKKBlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Peabody Lobby is my Happy Place ❤ #peabody #ducks #memphis @ The Peabody Memphis https://t.co/eZGKo4TzY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daddy's Nail Salon is open for business! I didn't even paint that much skin this time:) LOL I'm getting better so m… https://t.co/YLwRUfBeoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to always set the tone:  women belong in engineering! #InternationalWomensDay #GirlsInSTEM https://t.co/FsOvLUl2TP]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Qw21bWVxz1 Jennifer Nettles Bohemian Rhapsody @SplitSeason1981]]></document><document><![CDATA[(FULL) Marshmello Event | First Person | Fortnite Battle Royal https://t.co/1OJjKaUb2k via @YouTube #Fortnite #Marshmello]]></document><document><![CDATA[Small scale business crush in Louisville: @BeechBombshells 😍 #CNULegacy #louisvilleky #cnu @ Beechmont Bombshells https://t.co/1EXY8TKhPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tempe/Phx babes (or dudes if you’re down) I need a model for a free mani/pedi this Friday! Dm me if you’re interest… https://t.co/hDEvRkDJfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trump454545 Germany has been overrun by Muslims. They may be sorry they invited any and all refugees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cooked #dinner for my #closeguy . #pork #veggies #seasoning #sauce . @ Apple Valley, California https://t.co/oXJFGELmwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter Wonderland!  So love my view!  #gratefulmindset @ Park City, Utah https://t.co/Y72HworQpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been on this plane 2.5 and I'm still in @COSAirport https://t.co/JlJfvji4cq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamwintermute @ralkana47 @coffeejunkii @ladytian Pablo is the best ecporter of Llamas and llama based equipment 😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett You’re just an ignorant idiot. It’s scary that you have your finger on the nuclear trigger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newspapers Rip 'Imperial' Trump's National Emergency, Calling Him Biggest Threat Of All https://t.co/bxL8Qci8UE]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this drag queen drama!! I’m just gonna go quietly Stan @YuhuaHamasaki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just rooting for horse to put that guy down for good. The rotten bastard will get up &amp; beat him again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL at my snapchat memories from last year... its crazy how fast things can change 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonWaxman @nick_ramsey @nytimes You know this personally or are you assuming this based on her association to the @POTUS?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe democrats are blackmailing Cohen to lie.. Cohen is a lawyer right.. when does a lawyer need 10 hours of prep… https://t.co/YoKM2nChBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[why are they so cute? do they know they're killing us https://t.co/eNxDRinN4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[KILO SANTANA X DONT LOVE ME (OFFICIAL VIDEO) https://t.co/yrLML8Ggjx via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacandShauna @the_silverfox1 Hey sometimes that’s just as fun!!!  We did that for the NC game a few years back in… https://t.co/Qf5SWTc1mB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Bernie just needs to go away ! The Democratic party is going to hell in a hand basket. Oh Well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaDonovanTV @rtv6 Damn the parking meter gods up and at it this morning.... only 18 minutes in! https://t.co/YOLIlxCIUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine you’re a family of 4, you save for a trip to Disneyland for years and years. You get here, all excited, kid… https://t.co/R9MxgwWtdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @AkronWineGuru @thatsVeryKari @Dracaenawines @joneill55 @Julianna_glass @ccatmpt @cowineco… https://t.co/BZcgf2kAdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IDWPublishing Do the right thing #FightForWynonna history has it’s eyes on you! You wouldn’t just be saving a show… https://t.co/5lDYZJJnWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙏💕✝️Lots of love for my girl, @gabbypetillo , on her Confirmation day! ✝️💕🙏  @apetillo16 @MeyganThompson https://t.co/3k7vwIqZeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoDOT shout out to all the drivers we are seeing at each exit between STL and KC!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you ever think about the part in a streetcar named desire when Blanche says “deliberate cruelty is not forgivabl… https://t.co/MEDutSNBM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will always Love and defend Michael the same as He would do for Us! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come by the #discoveryouwellnessexpo  and get your signed copy of Life In the Shadows by RI author Emily Tallman! @… https://t.co/yw0e5ICOJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had my Face to Face interview with @SouthwestAir today.  It was great to see where the magic happens! 🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Upland chick "Gave Up" in a very big way.  I remember the time I also Gave Up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/uTtcwcjBZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tommy Westphal's new snow globe? @ United Church of Beloit https://t.co/hg83MGLAk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dustiebaby Gonna fuck shit alll the way up and go back to our “niggas ain’t shit” days 😢🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[💗💙💗💙💗💙💗💙💗💙💗💙💗💙💗Very excited for this beautiful blessing of mine our own little one , a mini version of us _jpinkyy… https://t.co/uE9OFfkt9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[This mans friends is always trying slide on me and it’s like 1) why 2) it’s a dead mission every trip ... if you kn… https://t.co/KdCTv1gYPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hello, I’m Gail Hailstorm, author of the book ‘You’re Dead. I’m Rich’ is just....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smerconish @TC34 can a non racist person do a racist act??? Can person tell lies and not be a liar??  Depends on who you ask..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Than you! To you and your beautiful wife! Y’all are so inspiring. Keep being great!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We lack discipline and self-control in all areas of life. We allow others to determine and control our happiness, s… https://t.co/kfUpGkgXLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rumbo a #SteambotTrip  #friendstrip  #Colorado  #denver en Denver, Colorado https://t.co/k3sBJFMk1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Razorsmack1 @luluHru @LadyNY4Ever @Not_Muted @tjkgolf21 @RPowell2011 @Serremmy @PattiSc08960854 @MAGAgirly… https://t.co/xxp9fI8hrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackoutJoel @Scampboi @wakeupwithlinda @RAICESTEXAS @CBP @ICEgov How do you know what they are planning to do?… https://t.co/RLEuZ30ATM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeisAlison @MKGenest I'm 70. Here in Alabama we'll honey n sweetie you into diabetes . .all with total Respect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[tenho certeza que o tanto que já andei nesse aeroporto equivale a 5 magic kingdons]]></document><document><![CDATA[Issa no for me, Dawg. Patriot needs to be (say it with me) DARK SKINNED.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susanhupp Starting to get questions - mostly from farms not yet growing but are considering.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ern draws a foul and will be @ the FT line, but he didn't look right on that attempt he usually goes up harder than… https://t.co/gHpPIXShjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being excited about the new Lion King movie then realizing we are going to have to relive Mufasa's death in CGI https://t.co/TuGhfB03pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC I know Lindsey Graham's parents died young and he raised his younger sister. Maybe the aunt helped them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[More good times with the family I get to choose! #friends #laughter #life #love #gramfam @ Humble, Texas https://t.co/7VDfTS9RZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KingBooks_ @jarpad Yep, it's already on Facebook,  that's how I found out about it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spend on fashion has increased from 2.5% to 6.5%—driven by social, more flexible working styles and more occasions/… https://t.co/zSA0dFRSeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[one door closes so more can open ✨✨✨✨ accept change https://t.co/qpfe28pJNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salmon and Asparagus for lunch @bodybuildingcom #bodybuildingcom @jimstoppani #bbcomchallengeseries… https://t.co/7Vm3rv30UB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trelonda Be Mad af at me but I be mad af at her too so ion be caring 😭 I love that girl to death tho 💕💕💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piIotjonez @Pjvibes Holy shit @petergilroy are you the neighbor called Peter???? https://t.co/pfZObJLLKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Evening  Family and Friends... I've been challenged by my Upline to sell 25 pieces of jewelry by Monday. Will… https://t.co/xsHZdr3RnW]]></document></documents></author>