<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[the jonas brothers are really getting back together. i’m literally going to pass out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[💕Dont forget to pick up your Valentine Day sweets at Light's Coffee Shop &amp; Bakery🍰💕💕Happy Valentine's Day💕… https://t.co/7sm89EKPjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I’m here right now. This is like my Disney World. @chipgaines @joannagaines https://t.co/jtOJ6xJXZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QTAnon1 No you didn't tweet that! It's what nightmares are made of!🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when tanning beds were cool? There were rules like you could only go a certain amount of time in the bed a… https://t.co/CRDAw76eW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccolbyrun I had a really bad experience w/ my eye doctor yesterday. Questioned why I was being charged to fix a co… https://t.co/pE1g01kQuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrangelyLiterl @pastpunditry @JaneMayerNYer And if anyone watches CNN, MSN, ABC, NBC, CBS etc. will notice they a… https://t.co/DnjZSGZ5wN]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Adventureous Spirit by Dan Gibson on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/mgFPzbENej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LKoennel @lsench2 @Curley_Liz @RHLeeESSC Proud to be in your boat @LKoennel #RelationshipsMatter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Born and raised on the south-side of Chicago, music has always been apart of carache029 existence. At a young age C… https://t.co/qov3a8RNct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y a vraiment quelqu'un qui pensait que ça passerait comme si de rien était....Hé ben]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel like i have more homework to do during spring break than any other week of the semester🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Btw we just collected responses from 150 utility professionals on this question. Interested to see how the results… https://t.co/sQ1JEQ7VQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dream is that they let me giddily toss the scooters into the gaping metal mouth of a giant grinding machine]]></document><document><![CDATA[SA goes to Cannes! Viva Pictures took 2nd place @48hourpalooza How awesome!! @JHB48HFP #48HFP #48HFPFilma… https://t.co/aMIhmRwbXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sayitdanniejay i adore my cat but i concur bc the thing i love the most abt him is his evilness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I have 100k friends who wanna help us get to a million!? Sub on YouTube and watch all of our awesome videos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keke_anders @EvaLouGrace @Michellealexg @EmoryOtto @aangelasommers @Sxmw10 @SylviaJHansen @annaeliset @olivia_bruce01 my eyes are closed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickyDavila Also her husband is a literal convicted felon- weird how that never gets discussed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Ya'll, I have so much pride and love for my Atlanta roots. I wanted to share my feelings for the city through a… https://t.co/xUhYocqELd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to be in my favorite place this coming weekend with all my favorite people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tampa, if you want to get up at 8am on Saturday, let’s do it! https://t.co/Cbalc6ImLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@we_r_Psymese @KoraKnight_Auth @Just4Me05 @dana_lacie @ilovebakedgoods @Twstdsistr35 @MistressBec @EmboLoves… https://t.co/WEmBTBdp9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brooke_Medina_ His words are incredibly arrogant, lazy and divisive. At a time when we should find ways to lift up… https://t.co/VeW9tlKdYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork @Doc_JJK Come on republicans. Look at this. What he says.  Can’t you guys get off your asses and fight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdBuchananWyo @renato_mariotti @politicalelle @TIME To the 🎶🎶Of 30 Million ❓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShirleenAllicot Good morning! Looking great! @KenRosatoABC7  Good morning! Happy to have you back😊@AmyFreeze7  Goo… https://t.co/046UHDxBYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Inauguration Day. Trump supporters. Picture is worth a thousand words, but all we need is 3.  FUCK… https://t.co/kh86uON4Eo]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have a choice each morning. It comes down to preparation and being able to roll with the punches when things do… https://t.co/6wR9Jl3afT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words written in the quilting.    I have did this with baby quilts &amp;... https://t.co/m11ZE45SMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I always do thissssss!! Every time I need to be up early, I’m up hella late 🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought I would see Ben Askren in the UFC. Here we are. Lets see how this plays out. #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[JOIN US TODAY in Annapolis for the Maryland March for Life and Youth Rally! NOW is the time to show our numbers, MD… https://t.co/ehCfljq9Jz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fat ASS would wake up in the middle of the night just to make some fresas con crema #cravingssss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gibblertron https://t.co/19QBxw2d30 would love to hear you talk about this on Throwing Shade!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristyStallsmit @Demandor @erikajayne So of course I dont. But you also need to remember that in his generation th… https://t.co/eJPjJ6eBiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ribozyme @aphillippy @nanopore I would caution any efforts to assemble across the millions of bases of centromeric… https://t.co/OtkKpLykQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh are you sleeping? Not anymore!  #crazycatlady #catsofinstagram #cats @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/3UUXGN2GiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your @Baseball_MHS fam sees you @gstrick_3 !! Proud to watch your hard work and dedication bring success at the nex… https://t.co/kKMBJvfr3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Keilet_FA @RedMeansGo33 @Sophisti88 @SteveKornacki You didn’t give the definition. Lol What does socialism mean?still waiting]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told Maddie that she can’t go to school again tomorrow since she still has a fever. More tears. We hugged and the… https://t.co/Prst5z4tgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aklein328 When I move we are going to Laguna Beach bc that’s what my dreams are made of and it’s only 1.5 hours from LA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow people are bringing this tweet back and it was literally a nightmare for me omfg let it die]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lpkelle @FanCentro @FANCentroTribe You have to see on https://t.co/c6SoneXNBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really not a fan of so-called critics shitting on others (some of whom unpaid) as a play on superiority, calling th… https://t.co/vFCV01ZV9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad to wake up to no snow . I really don’t care for snow . It looks pretty and all but it is Spring time almost.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMJewell @realDonaldTrump Do you wa not everyone to know what you have or have made.  Your friends might look at y… https://t.co/tn62XXi911]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweetie, I’m gonna need you to put those few remaining brain cells together and work with me here, okay?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Michael Cohen is a liar just think what does that make Donald Trump who employed this liar for over 10 years?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can i have one at my baby shower and do a keg stand? Asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyJoh06703615 @AppSame @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett No it was a paragraph. Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are the most annoying words and phrases used in professional and governmental/political discussions today?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatsVeryKari @ccatmpt @AkronWineGuru @SashaEats @Cbp8Cindy @FionaMorgan79 @Dracaenawines @simplysallyh @jay_eatz… https://t.co/i7RKCPDPBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DwyerAcademies @DwyerHS @sfarrell97 @WTDHS_Principal @Dwyer_Guidance @jkh_74 Fantastic young man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Audrey Kitch.. 🤘🏽🤭🖕 Justice has been served. Ppl! Always speak your truth no matter who the fuck tells you oth… https://t.co/o5GfTlVX0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Commerce, GA? View our latest opening: https://t.co/miC7LJtej0 #warehouse]]></document><document><![CDATA[For such men are false apostles, deceitful Workman , disguising themselves as apostles of Christ. And no wonder, fo… https://t.co/BnGvVz9Tdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The vendors are arriving and lit Lounge is going to be on fire! #420 #710society #lacannabiscommunity… https://t.co/vzZgtASwfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyRichter Take a picture and put it on the Internet. I’m sure someone out there will help you figure it out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrettyLuvBird Ready when you are 😭😂😭 the sarcasm that comes out of my child’s mouth 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BalanceforBetter Hilary Mercer, VP Pennsylvania Chemicals @Shell #HERWorld19 #shell #shellisagreatplacetowork https://t.co/CS1xxqmFxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[House GOP leader McCarthy slams Dem's 'blah blah blah' mockery of Trump administration accomplishments  https://t.co/eShSstUpMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ehernandez @Noelle_Phillips I’m wearing my #Ravenclaw robes. No shame. https://t.co/KTM3XH5Y8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Nick Cannon is a very nice young man, but for the love of God, why is he wearing the headwrap my Grandma wo… https://t.co/5hsIgbjXON]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn't matter how long ago those hurtful remarks were made, or if Carlson apologizes! What matters is that he h… https://t.co/eT4TbEYg41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 Cohen also said that Trump NEVER directly told him to lie about anything ....so which is it&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAFrench @mchastain81 @TIME You’re a sell out...Time is the worst piece of drek in the publishing world....you… https://t.co/4R9fwev6Pi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soniguer @RatheChristian @MaudeLafleur94 Aucune idée... me su fait rasé ça rendu au milieu du dos..  Ou p-être que… https://t.co/JUmPIbHCZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyBlunt @HawleyMO  Do the right thing. Block this sham national emergency, quit wasting taxpayer money on an unne… https://t.co/b0fRFRs5tN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NacHSPrincipal @NacogdochesHS From a former High School teacher...Thank you, Dr. Crespo.  It's great to see you ta… https://t.co/zFJKQDSCUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw some snowflakes. Melting at touchdown. @ Galloway, New Jersey https://t.co/EbnM8Aljyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetBlue Took a full hour of us being on the runway before we even got an announcement. Unacceptable. And it’s a de… https://t.co/p9VndZw58q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give me your 2019 #AAC most overrated #CFB player heading into 2019...  Mine- #Cincinnati QB -  Desmond Ridder.  Do… https://t.co/sxhgETqniR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Florence makes me feel way more confident than a normal woman should feel at 3:30 pm on a Thursday afternoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdkrantz @andylassner @theguydf @Eden_Eats Planning on listening to it on the bus ride home!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never forget how many people reached out to me the day he died. People I hadn’t heard from in years, months,… https://t.co/PZeUGr3X9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @RickGriffin @miliman12photos @always5star @CharlesMcCool @MadHattersNYC @MattsRoadTrip @RoarLoudTravel… https://t.co/LNoWdTzvI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SierraaaBadillo I have had a new prescription since September and I don’t wanna wear glasses (I’ve had contacts pr… https://t.co/k1oilIC7L9]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you for 10 days full of coffee dates, making me try Vietnamese food, forcing me to drive your manual car, alm… https://t.co/PoHzmPyfNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beginning Teachers Equity conference was filled with passionate and dedicated educators. What a privilege it is to… https://t.co/1TrmqsUigQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shameful, disgusting and despicable. I refuse to become endured to attacks on decency and democracy. #resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading back to the Big Apple!!! I had a great time in Dallas! 😍 https://t.co/zkmrNdCdx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job tonight KC Varsity and JV both taking 1st place!! @KCTIGERBAND  @KleinISD  @KCHStigers  @KleinCollins https://t.co/aWS8L5avPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bellanwa @YIAGA I miss you.. can’t wait to speak with you after everything.. stay safe]]></document><document><![CDATA[More specifically it's Jake in a cowboy hat screaming YEEHAW in her face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vivianibarra @JuliaTolliver @ElizabethCOCon2 @nameonrequest @GuidoLupaz @RJRHSimmons @BW_1970 @AOC @RepRaskin Yes… https://t.co/42AKz5cs2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throw the Scissors did Amazing Job at DI....You Ladies Rocked it!!! @ Bay Port High School https://t.co/qPCspVYSL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russellcrowe Another wildlife warrior saving the day for some sea turtles. Have a great day. Hope it's not too col… https://t.co/vhjSVPz6xr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffGordonWeb @sambassartist @NASCAR I'm so sorry your friend @sambassartist passed💔away @JeffGordonWeb I LOVE his… https://t.co/ovd9D5OXOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealdrix78 I'll take the money. True love would be nice, but I've given up on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For everything that was written in the past was written to teach us, so that through the endurance taught in the S… https://t.co/kzfsieHSEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is all too sickening!!  Good to see you back.  I have been missing for awhile or I have missed your tweets   Tha… https://t.co/AGnNVB1y6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback Tuesday &amp; Pine Straw is still the winner 😂 #politics🤑 @ Casa De Echevarria https://t.co/R6vCL8S1WL]]></document><document><![CDATA[As always thank you @TDFNYC  for helping to make #Broadwaytheater affordable. #Broadway #Theater #TheFerryMan… https://t.co/RMVUoYlSbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll give $50 to whoever tells me what’s better than drinking with your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[and if my phone doesn’t make the lock noise when i lock it i unlock it, turn the ringer on and then lock it again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[thought i copped a good deal bc it was 50% off but the cashier told me i came on the wrong day because tomorrow it’… https://t.co/thGkLj5YHe]]></document><document><![CDATA[me caga que los tipos te ilusionen bien kbron bajándote la luna y las estrellas y al final te dejen ahí sufriendo o… https://t.co/d5Xz3QCI2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Lots of questions why Cohen changed his story. Was he bribed, him or family member threatened?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I guess this fetus ... you know illegal “aliens” fetus ... is not counted as a person.... smh 🤦🏾‍♀️ sigh 😔… https://t.co/CebELSXVRX]]></document></documents></author>