<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Seriously... suggestions and thoughts appreciated. @ Winfield, Alabama https://t.co/JlYQQooy8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@molina_moprobs @RumpleMinze @lindor_truffles @AmiciMilly @_alainaknight @Izzy_Collazos @jmiket91 @annaeb22 Where d… https://t.co/ht6Ua2j6Ut]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cry...s/o to my mans for having this made for me 😭 #artbyjburt https://t.co/7sJs7PED2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Housing Market Will “Spring Forward” This Year! https://t.co/fBu8EAPFA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar @MorpheBrushes @ultabeauty What time will the show up on the website]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great picket line at the@CambriaMagMile tonight. Si se Puede!! @UniteHerelocal1 #ChicagoHotelStrike #JakeisoffRocker https://t.co/5lu76S9HNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@always5star @TBEXevents @CharlesMcCool @TheHusbandInTow @RickGriffin @travthroughlife @SashaEats @DanaHFreeman… https://t.co/t5qNzHAllx]]></document><document><![CDATA[didn’t know her at all but its been a couple days and has been heavy on my mind. so, so sad that a life was cut so short.. rest easy, KLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[New #BURBERRY  Dm @VAzFemFabFun @ Saks Fifth Avenue https://t.co/UWoPgxgGIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuuck my boyfriend needs to hurry tf up and come back home I miss him😩🥺🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[I DARE ONE OF YOU LITTLE MUSTY RATS TO JUMP IN MY CAR I PROMISE YOU WHOLEHEARTEDLY THAT YOU WILL LEAVE BLEEDING]]></document><document><![CDATA[[단독] 대형 화물선이 부산 광안대교 들이받아 https://t.co/wJp3FL4AAN via @YouTube https://t.co/Occnj8zm1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaltYPockets @HillReporter I am so tired of his Fugly face https://t.co/tLtLnBBWg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicheBangtan @SophieT I am so excited for #DarkPhoenix you have no clue how effing excited I am for #DarkPhoenix b… https://t.co/jzXlz8B5fh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This SC 8th grader was so thrilled to have this violin in her hands! TY @longbaysymphony for bringing your passion… https://t.co/KWw0wRNBaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marshallmarkesq That is more than an appropriate reference for him...  Why is it that evil/bad always lurks in the… https://t.co/5jver6MOBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in the elevator, and this couple is having an intense argument about Harry Potter.   Him: *holding up Slytherin… https://t.co/7bINPDUdgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Mr. and Mrs. Becker for sharing a cookie experiment with us today to teach the buoyancy and that scientific… https://t.co/vrOjv09KRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[An actual thing that just happened at the bar:  "Y'all have PBR on tap?"  No sir we don't have PBR  Longest pause i… https://t.co/gIjIyzOggR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahsanders33 @londonlibrary @DDeagleEdu Really sad I couldn't make it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wearepoweruk @SeanOnTheAir @BTSRadioUK @BTSonShazam @perrielmixers @SupportOra @CCabelloSP Hmm can ya guess what I want?😈😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all love talking shit about Spirit but American Airlines is actually the worst airline company to fly with ... let’s talk about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of goodies here today!! I didn’t even photograph the other things here!! Stop out 2-5!! @ Heath, Ohio https://t.co/IJWn12Nc2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magikalalpha That's what I thought. Whoa! I know your Long $VYST, and holding altho up so much.  Thanks for clarifying!  Congrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kenny was MVP in 1981, broke Baugh’s record in 82, and never made the HOF?  Please, he was one of the NFL’s all-tim… https://t.co/91OuK2hknU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mar 4 - A geese convention happening outside my PT session today. #birds #birdsbirdsbirds #geese #portland… https://t.co/k0T4CO3ou3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful balance, hydration and removal of #liplines using a combination of #filler as well as #wrinklerelaxer for… https://t.co/ryGeUZIynz]]></document><document><![CDATA[DECENTRALIZED GOVERNMENT.  TAKE THE ABSOLUTE POWER AWAY FROM THE PRESIDENT.  PERIOD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Melissssaa__ I’m already crying so I mean all I need now is to throw hand with @PriyaAnjaliPat2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas for @IPrevailBand  on the 27th, and @AwakenIAm  on the 28th of April 😍😍😍 HAPPY BIRTHDAY MONTH TO ME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning ☀️🌞😃 it’s cloudy ⛅️ and more rain 🌧 on the this evening so they say I hope everyone has a great day ☕️☕️❤️🥰😘😘xoxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert de Niro: linked to child sex trafficking &amp; hates Trump!   2+2=4 Evy the hate? Read on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigredwavenow I'm watching invaders from Mars and it's scary. Can you come https://t.co/EUOjd0Oq7t should be again… https://t.co/k2kml6MMcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerseyKidPicks .A 'good adult relationship' means different things to different people. There are many different k… https://t.co/gRxSU6tDlr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thatsSoPough The Poughkeepsie Performing Arts Academy!! https://t.co/nIX9XojyUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love teaching elementary kids on my birthday!  Birthday exercises together to equal my new age is the best!  “You… https://t.co/xXn76SJ57H]]></document><document><![CDATA[JESUS IS LORD IN ITALY......People of the lite.....family of God pray/reading &amp; piercing the darkness! https://t.co/toTpWvrkq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re bout to drop a 🔥 album but gotta bowl a quick strike #TakeSpare @ Bowlmor Lanes https://t.co/J2vMSnTLMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcarmody matthew mcconaughey                              Matthew McConaughey                      Matthew McConaughey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday #mocktail, featuring @stoli non alcoholic ginger beer and grapefruit juice. I am diggin' the color!… https://t.co/tjeqOZK9Dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beattheblock @mattyboy70 @davescherer And furthermore, I was responding to the guy after you, not to you. But if the shoe fits, pal...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDrPhilShow after watching episode 105, I'm only in it 5 minutes, I already want to lay the husband flat on his… https://t.co/aealnNBXKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @IlhanMN So many educated people talking a lot BS in the comments on our president and vice president. I suppos… https://t.co/8fCPllulpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Offer Has Been Accepted! Next Steps... The First 10 Days  https://t.co/y6YL5ZA4o5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Choose your words carefully..always keep in mind your ripple affect.. #powerful #simplechange = greater impact… https://t.co/rqisq2ybqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sylviakaydavis1 @FatJesusWV @Ironhorse76 @maddow Thanks. I followed you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day to my favorite person. We've been on so many amazing adventures and I can't wait to go on so m… https://t.co/0cPdh2AxeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you’re tall or have curly hair or BOTH &amp; isn’t going to break my heart hmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny, this is the same sad face he gives me when I’m still eating and he’s already finished his food...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayneMillaray @Sparki777 @howloften @ThomasMcAvoy14 @HERterus @cheomitII @theladykatie @WildChild69 @MaeVic3… https://t.co/VJrgLPlPr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heeeeyy friends! So sorry the edusistas are running late this evening!!! Let’s talk science of reading! Q1 coming up!  #EduAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobboBen i watched that ig video of u playing jenga like 5 times!!! Too funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days I am more wolf than woman + I am still learning to stop apologizing for my wild. — Nikita Gill ♀ ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀… https://t.co/VJ68mqeYdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[whole. body. chills. maybe it’s this terrible cold, maybe it’s #adriannelenker @ Metro Gallery https://t.co/bvUd1KNmfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved chatting with the lovely and talented @lashanalynch who plays Maria Rambeau in captainmarvelofficial which hi… https://t.co/2Ec5sx72IF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I personally think the criteria should be based on whether the fetus can survive without the host/mom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Make them more expensive?” Are living wages for their work too expensive for you? Low wages are a part of the prob… https://t.co/k6WelNsBmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @ESlaikeu and the random guy in the parking lot for helping rescue Bertha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyBaldwin Someone just told me it would snow tomorrow at the Hollywood sign. This is insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @arianakristin ! You are truly talented!😍 #somethingdifferent @ Cape Girardeau, Missouri https://t.co/4urCJ4QTeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my god I remember why that “saving words” excuse that Trump used sounded familiar. It’s literally a plot point a… https://t.co/rvJK5b4sa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remembering and honoring my heart is with you ❤️❤️ #ParklandStrong #MSDStrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh I hate when I’m swiping on tinder and I think “hm he’s cute” and then his next picture is him holding a dead fuckin deer]]></document><document><![CDATA[AJ, the way you speak to your partner is part of the marriage. Boy, bye. #mafs #MarriedAtFirstSight]]></document><document><![CDATA[#disneyland in the rain is my fav. ☔️ 😃 🐭 @ Pirates of the Caribbean - Disneyland Resort https://t.co/7JDe16ZxTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @Applebees discount drink for March is SO CUTE and DEEEElish! Who comes up with these things?! 😍🌈🍹 https://t.co/U7yQMIXCr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes I really wonder why I’m still single and other times I wake up with cool ranch Dorito crumbs in my sheets. could be it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LideFranks @jdnaa @liberal_party You know, hopefully, that when you say things like 'entitled zombies' any credibi… https://t.co/ASjlbzJPfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mccoymsutexas @MSUTexas Thank you! I have been trained well in MCOSME!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or you have a small business trip the weekend before and agree to call it good to “celebrate” (especially when your… https://t.co/f8cylEHIxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s your favorite season?   I am simply counting down the days until summer...   https://t.co/EIsJQ4qRbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#vss365  We #belong to the sky and the earth, the sun and the sea I to you, and you to me  To that touch that binds… https://t.co/zDE0mT1Rip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Mooresville, NC? View our latest opening: https://t.co/R1OztxuUSB #Sales]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats on the nomination @chefjgdetails! #SweetHomeCafe inside the #NMAAHC feeds hundreds daily. This is well des… https://t.co/bEneLU0tVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had some dry salty crackers... No food. No notice. You gotta pay big to mandate me tho...]]></document><document><![CDATA[In deep conversation. Cat + Beetle. #catphotography #TonkaTheNaughtiestCatInTheWorld #gingercat #adoptastray @ Cohu… https://t.co/UkEutp1Oot]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kind of Temple 🙏🏽 My kind of religion 🦄 #hilmaafklint @guggenheim #paintingsforthefuture #beforehertime… https://t.co/BKwdMMnVwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is so easy to fall in love with a stranger than it is to fall in love with yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t adapt to the energy in the room, influence the energy in the room.✨#goodvibesonly #bekind @ Santa Monica, Cal… https://t.co/VtbJv16nQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taxpayers are paying for that asshole to sit in prison for the rest of his life instead of just giving the sick fuc… https://t.co/mdbcuidw4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the positive outlook as we continue to wipe away  *shit that is flung in or faces , daily. Keep Hope Ali… https://t.co/W9dcyTXBJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir a Great shout out to my home away from home, SKY HARBOR ADMIRALS CLUB! THANKS for ALWAYS making us fee… https://t.co/xc5VAo9SrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elisaberryyy I didn’t even think of this omg My last snake I had was nagini :3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarMax Well she just got her permit snd we r teaching her how to drive the stick but when we brought it home she s… https://t.co/VIApRLi8lI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mellonee1 @creseda_hawk @GORMSWILDCATS @HappilyHamilton @jones_mjRMS @JStewRMS @RMS_Wildcats @RMSRELA Congratulations!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff They will want to misinform the public as much as possible before #MuellerReport is out. It’s… https://t.co/DB6WG8yV76]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stand the internet. That scary character on YouTube (whom shall not be named) is all in my brain now—terrorizing me!! 😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real IDs of Questioners at Bernie Town Hall Come Out, Showing CNN Radically Misled Viewers https://t.co/8DMPbhTwiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DorkyZoee @perksofbriana @YourAmazinTruth I got mine in ipsy awhile ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TGDsquad @mskitkat2u @IamNickGonzalez @GoodDoctorABC I’ll let you know tonite after the secret word goes public lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your mom is a theatre director, you sometimes wrap up your Saturday night curled up asleep in a glitter chair!… https://t.co/t3WlvRey2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto He needs to come to Alabama and apologize to the families that lost 23 of their own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraltofPDX @cnnbrk You are the idiot! Supporting the biggest con alive!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun weekend in Boulder with @ScheferAbby skiing at El Dora, eating healthy fun food and looking at housing for next… https://t.co/WFB7T4HFic]]></document><document><![CDATA[#theMpire #GoBlue #crisler #gameday🏀 #beatstate @ Crisler Center https://t.co/r8xE8HraY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marierossiter This time I just kept my mind on the medal. I had to have her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WonderWoman934 TRAITOR TRUMPS Tribute 2 ALL THINGS RUSSIAN. Bow. Bow. Scrape. Scrape. KISSY. KISSY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snuggle Up and Read at SWL. Thanks to all of our families for joining us! https://t.co/MalLOVvr7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mmmm white fish salad @ Brent's Deli Northridge https://t.co/xkPt4UBT9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Steve 🦚 I’m excited for our books ❤️ Otis Books @OtisCollege for bringing this dream to life 🌼 and thanks fo… https://t.co/Uo0Ro4XRdI]]></document></documents></author>