<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Reflog_18 Gordon didn't play to earn his ring, and Richardson is avg. 2.35 yards per carry in the AAF. https://t.co/03b1FXniEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost The sickening part of the @realDonaldTrump is the reason for so much hate and division narrative is the lev… https://t.co/usmaXJBf7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ham's acting city manager Mike Zegarac says Ontario is only jurisdiction in Canada that allows property taxes to fu… https://t.co/b68NxKmYfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing night at the Improv with these people. @erikgriffin @CourtScheuerman @chriswivell @hollywoodimprov… https://t.co/Ej8JNP4OST]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now this looks like a mighty fun time. Some of my all-time favs playing this show! Plus, Fishbone and Jawbreaker...… https://t.co/wMeduN8grB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonlietaer hola from Mexico! lots of food for thought in your Maclean’s ‘advice to Trudeau’ piece. We’ve got to… https://t.co/mGUvaAWSdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stpolishook @LibyaLiberty @IlhanMN I believe she questions the influence of pac money to support the interest of I… https://t.co/QOdtdKG7xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosDada Estimado Carlos, nos gustaría invitarlo a un foro de migración en la Universidad de Columbia. Nos podrá… https://t.co/Jhg8OIenSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luv2howl Hanging with wolves at Howling Woods Farm https://t.co/c932qdGn9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will have a new email alert up soon with the new bill number, but in the meantime use this link to send a messag… https://t.co/Oago7IapxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an effort play by Laughton! Keep pouring it on, boys! #LetsGoFlyers]]></document><document><![CDATA[My gorgeous anne_lukin warms my heart ❤️ every day! Love you!! ❤️ @ Providence, Rhode Island https://t.co/chb79RJJrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReinaldoPared es un hombre de conducta intachable #LosAlcarrizosConReinaldo https://t.co/bSfe0Wfp7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunDropLover69 @PatrickBushhhh @MarcBady @calebsroberts I just wanted to hear Birdland... https://t.co/vMfWOPC5Nt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @maddow None will, they are all dirty dogs with their tongues lapping at his ass😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[take time to smirk. This hilarious note from a wedding guest took off on Pinterest this year #hilarity #laugh… https://t.co/zO96klwcjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh. In my way too early in the morning, not yet caffeinated, stupor, I thought the announcement was that Sanders w… https://t.co/STqWNQS5jn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeoGlickman1 @NYCosmos @cmendes80 I am not fat but both my mcl are holding me back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lotion_Man @NJCAABasketball @efscTitans @EasternFLMBB Ok. But the past is the past post season is the post season… https://t.co/EH7rqSAH4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnTheRun_HM @CSeidmanNBCS All those idiots are overpaid . But Simpletons listen to them. Bayless, screaming A, Shsrpe, Cowtterd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re some things that a relationship has to offer that I miss but being single allows you to do whatever whenever]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is a chili 🥣 and BELT (🥓 🥚 🥬 🍅) kinda day - add 🧀! (@ The Bobbin’ Cork in Clarksville, VA)… https://t.co/PL5c7blmtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s hoping your morning commute is a safe one.  It was a bit hairy coming in at 1:30am on 64/40 between Clarkson… https://t.co/gwm0zdFOsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[MEL STARR DOIN A CLINICAL BEATDOWN,❗  #Current LIT-U-ATION: #DJMELSTARR  #ONTHERECORDLV #WELIT #DJSCRIBBLE… https://t.co/1SLQo12bEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza And the truth of the matter is that the Icon, Adolph Hitler, is idolized to this day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#harrierhawk Maybe That Red Thing will scare up a mouse... nikonusa nikonphotocontest #bwanabubbaadventurers @ Bask… https://t.co/egvgL53rsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Falleció el empresario sinaloense Jorge del Rincón Bernal; candidato a la alcaldía de Culiacán en 1983, icono panis… https://t.co/C36UE2PHE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I restarted GOT for the third time, I couldn’t wait for the day till I made it to season 4...and here I am aga… https://t.co/w23CWkbaQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rotten Tomatoes is purging Captain Marvel reviews on its site? Smh more censorship. If people don’t like the movie,… https://t.co/rxeDixmmW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it’s getting late at the club so you have to break out your best dance moves so you won’t be single on Valenti… https://t.co/YFWDP7QYki]]></document><document><![CDATA[New (FREE) 6-week online course I helped develop with the Program on Regulation, Therapeutics, and Law (PORTAL) --… https://t.co/XWW2fKfPeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Thunder’s abilty to get two bad shots instead of one good is the constant on which all nature’s laws are based.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you write, draw, paint, or do any other kind of art... what inspires you? What makes you get off your ass and make something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do they have the 👀🌴 #Issalook As always thanks again for having me @robcesternino ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[SPRING BLOOD DRIVE💉 Thursday, Feb. 21st Sign-up at PAWS Must have 70 pints collected and 95 students presenting the day of the drive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KasselMedia You know they are always going to give WCAL  / Open teams every advantage ! They also want that Good G… https://t.co/dmJ61WHEhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bustedlocker @ThePoniExpress Point taken-by that logic the skins have had some good seasons...hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion:   Females who claim their holding it down for their man while he in prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMontieth I think you mean he was bombarded by classless profanity all night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be nice if they would fix the receipt discount scanners. (@ Aisle 1 Fuel Station - @raleys in Sparks, NV) https://t.co/h5ZkFicuZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hearstruble @abc3340 Ever hear of the Iraq War?  How bout trump?  Think he’s the greatest thing since sliced bread… https://t.co/GeCLjcHGXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harrisons birthday in coming up in 4 months, I’ve been banned from going to both of his brothers birthdays this las… https://t.co/XdCZwz7oDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosewood3823 @LisaMcCampbell @kdogcampbell That’s awesome!!  I had no idea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With this crew I know things will be #lit! Bacchus bash 2019! #mardigras #bacchusbash #nola 🤙🏻🤟🏻 @ The Metropolitan https://t.co/6oimsPNp9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking pineapple juice and coconut rum tonight, desperately wishing I was back in Hawaii.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 I would not trust my daughters alone with @realDonaldTrump. I would hope that American standards f… https://t.co/Lz6zL6QF0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[The maturity my child @Earlburge03 showed in "waiting and learning" is beyond 15 years of age and yesterday, he sho… https://t.co/JKhv0In3l3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attorney for ISIS bride Hoda Muthana confident she will return to US: 'We are very likely to succeed'… https://t.co/pHUG74Gfm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decálogo de la derecha   Solo hay tres derechos fundamentales: vida, propiedad y libertad. El orden se mantiene al… https://t.co/k6auvwxLwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohanNDaCut @badlaxman1 @SportsCenter Ima just keep it real with you chief, once he gets paid, you REALLY ain’t wi… https://t.co/rnK5nek3xZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Para mí, no es tiempo de buscar culpables, sino de proponer soluciones. Lo que ha pasado era lo evidente con las de… https://t.co/aajwiMIz3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunset 🌅: Does watching the sunset 🌅 brings peace ✌️? Is the sunset really peaceful to watch? Both! It may depend o… https://t.co/1amQgpdY5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re scoreless after the first in the @NorwichCadets men’s hockey NEHC quarterfinal contest against… https://t.co/uBB2NJwfZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexLeeMedia are you no longer with CBS2 ? I enjoy hearing on TMKS but haven’t seen you on CBS in forever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First one wrong, 5/6 Bohemian Rhapsody first win! Sound Editing #Oscars https://t.co/hgdefKu7NM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @CBS19News It’s pure socialism and #SocialismKills #LiberalismIsAMentalDisorder]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diablos49 @IlhanMN On the contrary, she’s the only Democrat in the House with the guts  to be unapologetically progressive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi i will assume you were referencing legal immigration as reinvigorating America as illegal immigration d… https://t.co/iVjA6oU6y2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asian Americans may have an educational advantage, but they face a 'bamboo ceiling' at work: In a controversial and… https://t.co/uahMonPqng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEUniverse: @WWEDanielBryan: *kick*  @SamoaJoe: ??  #WWEChamber https://t.co/mGdAgvMR6s  https://t.co/WIXdx2dJTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope to get a response from you! I know you usually only respond to the trolls on your timeline. https://t.co/fTZppeIjj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatgirlondeck @breakingtco Would it be weird if i get a shirt that the average non-baseball fan would be like why… https://t.co/gKa5j8VzJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_McLaughlinIII Hang in there. It’s a long road. You will be challenged and go through a range of emotions. Just w… https://t.co/XBtkjBP2Sf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__sr7_ I completely agree ! He turned his body he didn’t do it on purpose lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Pictures Of The Day – 94 Pics #humor #chuckle #smile #playful https://t.co/E1jscHlxMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurieRoberts @azcentral @LaurieRoberts can never see a teaching moment or notice glaring problems with her pet De… https://t.co/fmJvxgshYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does everyone else have specific hats they wear front ways and specific ones they wear only backwards? Or is that just me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #BusinessMgmt job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Manager Clinical… https://t.co/6vqA9zRiIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Swagkage I never noticed how fucked up Itachi’s eyes were during his fight with Sasuke.. shit’s GROSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dame Dash #Issues A Sincere #Apology To Jay-Z, Jim Jones And More https://t.co/cmELd9nfDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[* @AB84 demands trade to contender with solid QB play *   Fast-forward to Josh Allen in Week 1: https://t.co/v8GMnCkCrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lynda_Zabala @rvr91696 @jensomnia @hotcheetotakis https://t.co/g4g6KCtozL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Green0101010 @Jim_Jordan @SpeakerRyan Ryan was a disaster and actually a member of the DS. He was instructed to dr… https://t.co/7FZZ040Zsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If not us, Who? It is time to stop the NYC crooked politicians from starving us #nyc #deepstate with the new wave… https://t.co/jB51uQ9wUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful downtown Providence Forge. @ Providence Forge, Virginia https://t.co/il4M8LM96q]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter made this for @YesTheory’s Thomas and he posed with it on their video! She flipped out when she saw the… https://t.co/of9RzCSGzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gu the fact that you played that Pizza Hut commercial was amazing, thank you ssoo much! Brought back so many memori… https://t.co/rUwyKZyV7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Russian sleeper agents in the White House IS THE ENEMY OF THE PEOPLE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today very well could have been the most disgraceful day for the Republican party. Your people representing you mad… https://t.co/dTsFBVUuhE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JD3Thousand @Whataburger Better get a couple more I heard that podcast boy gone need more]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottsauber @kc_dc And we are ridiculously excited to have you returning to share your knowledge with out #kcdc2019 attendees!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanl Last year I said something about me being a 40 year old man. My youngest pounced and said “you’re 42, not 4… https://t.co/b9V4yJtBtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RetroGameFix Looks like most stores, selling a digital code. Best Buy, Amazon, Walmart, Target.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump LOL - there is plenty if evidence of law breaking  - it is all in plain sight, you piece of totally useless shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A day of honor and celebration here in the city of Lebanon.” Mayor Jared Carr (LHS grad) @CityofLebanonMO… https://t.co/sZdHao3cww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyry5 oh hey I know that place!  the view is beautiful on a day like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mzrascoff @ryancraigap Affordability, at best. But price range offerings, market comparison pricing, student loan… https://t.co/5Ce03lIkqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtf @PapaJohns my roommate ordered @dominos 15 minutes after  I placed my order and his got here 10 minutes ago! https://t.co/jncPbGorNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hershey: "We heard you like chocolate. So we put chocolate in you chocolate so you could eat chocolate while you ea… https://t.co/TWfyavcJJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeenerJB That's a fair comment. If I'm reading sentiment correctly around why people like communicating via SnapCh… https://t.co/3zpTB7oslt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation @LindseyGrahamSC There is no emergency, and any claim that there is is a load of fetid steaming garbage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[70’- GOAL #AustinBoldFC. @LondonWoodberry with the header from a corner kick. Bold and North Texas SC tied 1-1.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say love is the most powerful emotion so while y'all be hating on me imma be loving on your momma 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is by the far the wildest thing I’ve ever seen in baseball/softball. Like, does anybody have a clue how hard t… https://t.co/B2rcflq1aU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shooting at VA Medical Center in West Palm Beach area.  WPTV reports a patient shot a doctor inside the hospital’s… https://t.co/bAazyqWMIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingboola And I like James but that brand of ball is trash in my opinion &amp; other guys are in the league for a reason...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra AOC grouping that together only serves one purpose, and that is to forward her own agenda here. She w… https://t.co/TYUw92UbO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my tract! Yay, data!  (And if I zoom in, I can see this was taken before we put solar panels on last year.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We are made right with God by placing our faith in Jesus Christ. And this is true for everyone who believes, no ma… https://t.co/Jbh6eMQkOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I get bad news and I feel bad about my life, but then I see gigantic trainwrecks like this. It doesn't ma… https://t.co/5r36TvwdQv]]></document></documents></author>