<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Nothing says “serious relationship only” like a bathing suit dating profile picture at rehab beach club Hard Rock Las Vegas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @shasaybel Quit associating with felons. https://t.co/89ehLlLXpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I must have missed this, but when did @CBBonFOX buy the rights to the great NBA on NBC theme music?  Watching the… https://t.co/kCVhIFDlfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Typical Leftist Liberal Socialist Democrat and Hypocrite ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[💋PYT APPRECIATION💋⚪️WHITE PARTY⚪️ 📅FRIDAY 22ND‼️ 🗣WE WANNA SHOW YALL SOME LOVE 💕 FOR SHOWING US SO MUCH LOVE‼️ 🚨FRE… https://t.co/w5qq6AQ5iD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kastelic13 @mw_faine4 @jbouch30 @NathanDensel @CoachMakrinos @coachrebholz Just got home from Josh’s AAU basketbal… https://t.co/Gub6amRcmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s tea  )         )        )     )     (         )       )      ) _(___(____)____(___(__ ( \   Kevin Knox put… https://t.co/zj4U4Cxy4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peiferlabunc @UNC @MarkZylka who is doing the March 8th event? Might have to go, it looks exciting. I had a Cajal… https://t.co/jq1VBZXGCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also what the fuck is wrong with the annihilator. It’s a horrible gun that does zero damage. A punch is more dps then that pee shooter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a little something from #2002 when I was #eleven #strangerthings #lies #writersofinstagram #poetsofinstagram… https://t.co/FUHrQR3PqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aprendan...  asi se lee un partido de futbol  #TuMuyBien #ClasicoRegio118  @migangelgarzam extiendale su respectivo… https://t.co/O5y1bpMIXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free Agent Preview: Anthony Barr https://t.co/dyEEWswUXp via @YouTube https://t.co/AiUylbfKkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BPucino @Howdy_Doughty @brenhillspeaks @JimCanto @katyb_spencer @MrLexJay @joshmccormack @DreaVilleneuve… https://t.co/KqYtgMU8r7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rdwrt @PhilippBayer @gmkurtzer @CentOSProject @SingularityApp Totally!  My point is it's not free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worth noting: @types mentions here (https://t.co/MtnPlVyJK6) that Flexport's revenue topped $500M in '18. One quest… https://t.co/GQ86zn2hFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Razorbacker24 @Austinh38887941 @BiGgZHRE @jknoxville @undisputed @ShannonSharpe 27-8-8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigMastersVK @TheSharkWins Okay. I'll track them for a month. Guaranteed they don't hit at or above 60%.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when I get a phone call in the middle of binge watching a show https://t.co/95KBFHHYhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sportscenter just showed a guy who has won his last 6 fights, all within the first two minutes. Man, that reminds m… https://t.co/DPnYi26K8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foggy #beach day at #isleofpalms @WeatherFlowCHAS @RobStormTeam2 @joshmarthers @arielle_WX @StormTeam2WCBD… https://t.co/LkuUthwzeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know something like this doesn’t mean much, but lyrics like this saved my fucking life. @KidCudi saved my life. https://t.co/r9ekiuCgrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nosleeprecords @Polyvinyl, @CIRecs, @epitaphrecords  But I promise y'all are 4th. If you would have asked for top… https://t.co/A2AJFvd9JP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So yeah I haven’t tweeted since my last birthday and good chance it’ll be my last tweet til my next one. Just wanna… https://t.co/qLYP9wv2lQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeTrumpEmergency #FAKENationalEmergency #TrumpFakeEmergency @ABCNewsLive @SkyNewsBreak @AJELive @CBSTopNews… https://t.co/pGzqkqQRSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus M. Trintingant should have been nominated. Losing only to Denzel for Flight or Pheonix for The Master.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaneRives @RickFF38 @jreed4401 we have Jordan making it happen in Kerrville! D220! https://t.co/L6NqHleOor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @PlanetFitness in Roswell, GA https://t.co/3BIaCypyd3 https://t.co/x1HOrnR0Bx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurtisCarson50 @CNNPolitics BTW, I’m sure you’re aware of this, but it bears repeating that smiling at someone as… https://t.co/8bXW8hDY4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clay_Mann_ @tomeu_morey This art has been next level, thanks for the hard work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeGymbeaub Should check both the boxes. Insanity.  https://t.co/tmog8CRg7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarrenSpeece @AdamMSowards @werehist @edgeeffectsmag @BackStoryRadio @InThePastLane @BFWorldPodcast @ErikLoomis… https://t.co/gIyAEkZxa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm looking for a staking deal in DFS..hit me up with all of you're offers I'm really good]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was bought two free drinks tonight hmmm going ✈️hot girl at the party https://t.co/AUkztqsVKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tempo perso i problemi dell’Italia sono tutti lì.. e loro non li vedono!! O forse fanno finta di no vederli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garciabanchs Deberias agregarle que tendremos terrorismo, no se te olvide que hezbola y hamas se han pronunciado en apoyo al narco regimen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@santiago4kd @Rayados Pizarro y Avilés, no deberían de estar en el equipo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is huge for us, thanks for everyone that backs it https://t.co/rwnLN7ZgTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re not allowed a day off right now it’s almost the trade deadline !! 🤔😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zacbowden @stroughtonsmith There are third party keyboards. I tried one but it made me slower. I had to think hard… https://t.co/31NEGfxZxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr @JohnCornyn I respect you Senator I feel the GOP or Republicans get beat up from the Democrats time a… https://t.co/msQdQEhW6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[SL  . . . . #mercedes #mercedesbenz #germancar#morninautos #soloparking #mercedesbenz #slclass #mercedessl @ Atlant… https://t.co/IxGqYXm4uw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting to visit Kurt Cobain’s Memorial in Aberdeen last year was surreal. Can’t believe he would’ve been 52 today.… https://t.co/00ABeX9yrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pray they all are found guilty some where this has to stop and people be responsible for their falsehoods]]></document><document><![CDATA[Season 2 of The West Wing is so great. Yes I stayed up all night watching the West Wing. #Bartlett2020 https://t.co/9ZDrbrDFvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karma A Bitch I Just Shot That Hoe Tho Bitch Stop Playin On My Top 🤣 #OnGang]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smh now you on the wave too Swizzy my influence is soo big https://t.co/BB7a1f4lm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Roger Stone Threatens Judge with "Corruption Central" Crosshairs logo from conspiracy site that also thr… https://t.co/le6UC7YnRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bellajane127 @krobinson_3232 @almostjingo @SpicyNoodles2 @Cara_TXZEAL @ModBond1 @salty_dawg69 @travlnjak… https://t.co/v4B5tWS0U7]]></document><document><![CDATA[LETS GO BLAZERS 🏀🏀⛹🏻‍♂️@trailblazers @Dame_Lillard @CJMcCollum @moe_harkless @bosnianbeast27 @farouq1 https://t.co/1mdTRRH8r6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pewdiepie Where do you see your career and passion going in the next couple years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Survey discovers/verifies/justifies premise of source org. Quell Surprise #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[My turn to rep @Ottawa_Tourism at the House of Sport at @RACentreOttawa. What a great place for our community!… https://t.co/IKZQGLySGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samstecky I used to read that publication all the time as a kid.  It's just sad now. lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshtpm Trump, depicted here in painting, praying that Mueller can't find 1600 Pennsylvania Ave.  It's the first time Trump ever prayed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PHLVisitorCntr For #ValentinesDay, we’re celebrating love right here at the Refuge, caring for homeless pets like… https://t.co/1dwWQbANp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[1BR/1BA #affordablehousing #incomerestricted #firsttimehomebuyer #starterapartment #coopliving #EastHarlem… https://t.co/jxZEapP8FH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you miss #FantasyFootball: 10 Things to Remember from 2018 from @TheFFBallers? I got you covered with a written… https://t.co/B7k0xHSMY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Hmmm Benghazi? Affordable care act? Birth certificate?  All sound familiar?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanna SAY Hi and I miss you @StephyBearrrr https://t.co/WBYPq9v2PR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like to call the #Watchers on #Facebook , they dont ever talk to me or share anything , So  I think it's because… https://t.co/CmzXw4ZUM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerryLaHay Hope it goes as well as it can. I'll get the Lego out and see if I can build a decent left leg. Logo Technics, the good stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BayDunks7 My brother-in-law is a teacher at a college. He says to the students, 'this is college, not high school.']]></document><document><![CDATA[@joethomas73 I do the same but smoke em for about 3.5 hours from frozen at 250.  Sauce- equal parts durkee red hot… https://t.co/I9Xkuu44Cm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomrichardson80 @kylegriffin1 Trump looks here like a detention hall regular waiting to be brought into the principal’s office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The upside to the Antonio Brown saga is my twitter feed today will be full of weird Buffalo pot shots from people w… https://t.co/ASXIp1SPNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checkout the Website , Link in my bio ..... Welcome to AnSiLans🤫🤫!!! @ Valley, City of Orange https://t.co/Frd4A6fz7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@labelladonna123 @notbuyingthat54 and the purpose of this again was?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge thanks to @subaru_usa for the media day access exclusive to subaru owners. #SubaruAmbassador… https://t.co/f5EamNseOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danileigh6117 What ever it is it will be better. Keep that pretty head up and all will be well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/Fr1va5Xi3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Roy Rogers to Infanticide https://t.co/BjtNbW0ekd via @AmericanThinker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrNoFollowers @MarkFossas @MrNiceGuy18_58 New 52 also brought the Suicide Squad back as a series also New 52 launc… https://t.co/1jvp6awnqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[On todays episode of Life:   Do I feel like shit because I'm 24 hrs fasted or am I finally going to feel deaths swe… https://t.co/IhdUETeFUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller @Eddieonfox @uhbroncofan @raider_rob24 the "Ben Maller Special" ala Kyler Murray..#ranchforthewin]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s beginning to look like that grey one might be in my not too distant future. Did a bunch of research on auto lo… https://t.co/MAG4f9lRCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh some comedy. I laughed way too long at this whole list. https://t.co/RsvhmD2y93]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sports is the most important training ground for future leaders.” -Arne Duncan, former US Secretary of Education… https://t.co/Pb2hiH3TLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexWattsEsq Aha. We did one of these in the states a few years ago and there were some odd questions. One that st… https://t.co/GG0bD6MBIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duffle Bag Ran.....One of the nicest lyricist ever on that microphone 💪🏾💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[They needed to vote on weather or not to be racist.  In 2019.  And it wasn’t unanimous.  Fuck this shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Cut Through the Noise by District 96 Beer Factory @ District 96 Beer Factory — https://t.co/Rbh8GY21WD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJoshPerry What if the Iowa caucuses were a true winnowing. We send our worst politicians there, and one by one t… https://t.co/gKDaYrDjaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The past couple of days I've been working super hard to afford a van. 🚐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggaz right in the same hood as they kids and won’t even think about pulling up but here I am on the other side of… https://t.co/G4hbOO9yeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Perhaps she can fuck right off and not tell me how to live my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timberwolves @OhioStAthletics @NBA @KBD_33 Never gonna forgive Ernie for not drafting him #FireErnie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go watch #CaptainMarvelYou will LOVE IT! Stay for end credit. OMG!!! #Marvel #AvengersEndgame]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @ToastyStickers for making my orange and blue controller into Goku. The cut out is perfect and doesn't go th… https://t.co/Bo2QfdhQp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @TrussElise New headline: Far Right Camara Person Intrudes Into 64 year old Nathan Phillips Space, Almost Knocking Him Down!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@949Game2 @NYFC @NashvilleSC New York food company is beating us?? We must really suck]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/CbpGn1Ya4H Esto cada vez se pone peor. Los padres de Ian Carlo Poveda y Eddie Salcedo pusieron en su s… https://t.co/XW6z3PgOnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[In position for @SanJoseSharks v @NHLBruins on @NHLonNBCSports following @TBLightning v @BlueJacketsNHL about 7pmis… https://t.co/ALyKJcxJkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT  SELFLESS LOVE IS ALL ABOUT..😇 IF YOU CAN CONTRIBUTE ... PLEASE! RT❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueUvino It took me a long time to watch that movie. “The Boy in the Striped Pajamas” as well. Much easier to talk… https://t.co/vnv5jXgplB]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s official, New Orleans roads are wayyyyyy worse than the entire state of South Carolina. Good God]]></document><document><![CDATA[These wilson snipes pass thru pehlam bay park but are a bit hard to find.from last year on the orchard beach puddle https://t.co/fAgL6qq3Hy]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s unhealthy how much I love buying baby stuff.. thank god im not pregnant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tax Refund day lunch! #nafnafgrill🐫 😎😍 @ Chester County, Pennsylvania https://t.co/7eKJNXf9MP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCM @OliviaAustinxxx @OhMelissaMoore @xoxoashleyadams @MissJessaRhodes @wildgirlathena @char_stokely @daveenadavis… https://t.co/5lTFPBczIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@don_fishh @AwwDudeItsAlex @CodyDrake_ @donoooo watch Donny Harmon check twitter for the first time in 8 years and… https://t.co/EtFMQPbvaj]]></document></documents></author>