<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[i landed here like 20 minutes after this... thank god everything’s okay🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC All the Trumps never had to really work.... their only challenge was to try and cope with that big Silver Spoon stuck up their ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phoenixkhos @TrevorBland7 @Sean46013855 @SocialistRA it’s just boring lol don’t you understand that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitter world. Have a Blessed and Wonderful Tuesday  " LOVE LIFE " Blessed to be Blessed https://t.co/f4XCiXFcY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost The douchiest of all douchey things to say. Pick a party dkbag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vargasmoni @AirbusSpotter @EtihadAirways @SacrementoCond1 @SanJoseSharks @NewMexicoUTD @Baines_Simmons… https://t.co/9hUsvl4okN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trusting God releases anxiety and carries us into rest. (Today's @ourdailybread )]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelstrahan @TheHumble_21 Agree 100%. Can’t wait to see LC21 continue to make the Pro Bowl while the @Giants br… https://t.co/I3v5egI8uQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonMezzera @WWE What’s the U.S. Champion?  😂 😂 You know it’s funny I’m not saying I agreed with the call, but I di… https://t.co/8xWJdEomuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day to be an Oak Hill Golden Eagle....  Girls BB state champions Caiden Lake diving state champ Janessa Hasty… https://t.co/yrGjVNCqD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[من يقف مع كذبة فلسطين و الفلسطينيين هم مغفل و موالي لهم ضد الخليج العربي، و يكون وقف مع ايران ضد العرب.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/ZCRWLq9zR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpencerFernando @Jimmy33478435 Meanwhile the poll I started a couple of days ago with over 600 respondents so far… https://t.co/KU36o8Qz8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scarylawyerguy I love all this bullshit two years before the election.  Wait, listen, research, vote, than vote again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second part of my lesson from a child speech at the Prison To Power Youth Event last week. If a man is right his wo… https://t.co/N5XfTGyUBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pchopz_ Gonna suck to see him go, but on the flip side. It's fun having a top 5 talent on your team even if it's not long term.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at my Twitter timeline today, it looks I’m gonna have to add the word “Jonas” to my muted list. #DiabetesTwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJayapal We have a single payer model that is run by the government for our veterans. It helps to provide horrib… https://t.co/JN4z5C3FKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RuffinAngel @G_Sapia_Ruffin @DAVIDRUFFINJR @DeDeTillman @SonsOfMotown Return to Sender...luv ya fam... Sunshine &amp; Rain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesdpitley @CocktailsCigars @Racingwelfare Well, it’s gonna be tough for me to answer that: https://t.co/HcBwqc0Eb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at what I've been up to in [Lords Mobile]! https://t.co/QipOm6kTx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait for one of my niggas to get married so we can do a bachelor party!😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TanyaDonelly Hahaha.....Belly 1944:  the boogie woogie kid from the bad home who decapitated your dolls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows So is DOJ going to investigate the people investigating a PERSON and not a crime?]]></document><document><![CDATA[8th Grade Mentors @BataviaMiddle work August til June tutoring students,assisting school staff as well as volunteer… https://t.co/jeQuMFPR8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go @TerrierWHockey !! #WinTheDay | Women’s Ice Hockey Terriers Capture First Beanpot Trophy Since 1981 https://t.co/pi0v65bhuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only free democratic elections are not inside China, but Tiiwan. China has a central communist party with XI sh… https://t.co/wxMozBo24g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asvpxrocky and @tylerthecreator made a movie at iii points last night!! https://t.co/4rSeJy9GBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFixerESQ @SpurrWVUA Amen!  I thought the same. I mean no Popeyes, no Mapco rotisserie taceto. No Baptist hospital cafeteria. Geeezzz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some are great - some are terrible. Which one would you choose?   It’s been fun creating with this small kit. I’ve… https://t.co/vSZP7MuR5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frames from computer-produced film “A Computer Technique for the Production of Animated Movies” 1964, Ken Knowlton,… https://t.co/gNo5w9BLue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CredentialedRSS Yeah not planning on using this stuff. Posted mostly so people are aware that it's some toxic stuff!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBenSwain @uhhlishhaa Saw Goldwire try and calm everyone down. That was VERY close to being an embarrassing loss… https://t.co/ZMVbE8EqT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The yard when I got home...&amp; it’s still coming down. #vegas #snow @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/RIajOWtLAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is so worried about a Philly/Boston first round 4/5 matchup...people...INDIANA is going to slip to the 5 s… https://t.co/qKarZyMPTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #SwitchCorps, support The New Bloods with DUSK and Tonight, We Riot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Gran fin de semana para tod@s!  A nosotros, a los #hardbuttocksteam nos espera #ViñadelAjo !!!! en #muñoveros ¿y a… https://t.co/deFwZGLMLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill These folks need to get off their horses and buggies and understand that we have spaceship! Future economi… https://t.co/8bKLtyKPnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legend. Gonna pour out a root beer (from a frosted mug) for him today (while eating a Big One combo...despite the t… https://t.co/MJ01mngYOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s real out here - saw two cars turn around bc they couldn’t make it up a hill]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to Pastor Rod Parsley @rodparsley for these kind words! What an honor to receive this from a GENERAL in t… https://t.co/qRSEWX7366]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpartanMatt8497 @dodgersnchill Yeah man, I’m not buying anymore World Series tickets 😂 nah I’ll probably go again... 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr In other news, you’re going to prison. #lockhimup Jr. and Sr.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcgillu @McGillUPhysics Climate Change Joke: #Trump proclaims April 2019 Climate Change is Real Month @POTUS… https://t.co/ayzF6KbfEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennLahmers Yessssssss Jenn don't worry I'll be up for you smart talented pretty lady  and the fox family your the… https://t.co/Ll6psctqBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIP tickets to @lilbaby4PF @YellaBeezy214 with tickets to @BIGNEECHl ‘s pool party after 👀 @SouthPadreHUB… https://t.co/xtswAVeTpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YishaiThau @DiscussingFilm She deserves the eighth? I suppose I don’t disagree.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encuentro de los grandes empresarios con el presidente de la Republica de Nicaragua, para inicial otra vez el dialo… https://t.co/mofbiPR6tC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the umbrella mdandersoncancercenter! #bootwalk2018 #endcancer @ Cypress, Texas https://t.co/94ExdYYZf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kind of rude to make fun of someone’s drink when they’re standing right there, don’t ya think @Starbucks? Especiall… https://t.co/IvTD5elcCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComicContext And that's why Alan Alda was recast as Hawkeye for the TV series.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cisforawesome I’m not saying Orlando is bad! I’m coming back to visit in a month! I love Florida, but based on my… https://t.co/rDyfPGq5ee]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a small dream to one day be a judge on a foreign reality performance competition]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hellsbabykel @Cosmopolitan Sis is s you dumb? that man is an NBA champion making 16 million dollars a year please… https://t.co/ydSPS8EJq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't get CAUGHT without Coverage  #Bossnhugconnection👊 #GOOD&amp;SEASONED👅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Big_D_411 @ctanner3 @RL9631 @bigb1rd @SeanCashman5 @luluHru @TruthMaga @Lexa_Merica @Kjseili @AlohaHa59067534… https://t.co/kCv7Cz1FYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentines Day Dessert course 1: lavender creamer brûlée @ ZINC https://t.co/e8I4yH37o9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinBrakeNews @JusticeCanadaEN @ONAttorneyGen @SusanDelacourt @WendyMesleyCBC @SustainNtwk Has @AndrewScheer inf… https://t.co/I3wcPUBYsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodrigoPlata5 I’ll prefer to listen to someone more keen like Hendrix, Morrison or the kinks, Elton John or queen… https://t.co/F8UQVYs0WH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodmorning Family and Friends. Be Blessed! @ Browns Summit, North Carolina https://t.co/FSSQUuNwJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EEMKing1 @bielzebuddha @USCongress @USSenate @US_HouseOfReps @nytimes https://t.co/GKywXyYv6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @jossandmain I've never bought anything from you but somehow got added to your mailing list and you've been ign… https://t.co/zG3gPjCfXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE GROWL!!!!! I do not own the rights to this  “Finally” #ninetiesmusic  #housemusic  #independentartist… https://t.co/8sFValT33T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stankintony @RyanAFournier 😂 My friend, they’re all narcissistic celebrities... and none of them are here to rescu… https://t.co/JN113YudJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning beautiful souls 😘❤️🤗  Crazy hair, don't care!!  Been a touch off for a few weeks and lost my focus a b… https://t.co/RibdLwpw2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenidraRWoods_ Kenidra sorry your having issues. But Im glad to see your smart enough to get some help. Many don't… https://t.co/FQgVwNY1we]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BNightengale @MikeTrout can’t forget about signing with those @Phillies once they get @Bharper3407 there will be no $$$$ left for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harden has been playing really really poorly this quarter. Idk what he's doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jtruzmah @IDF Not one adult.they are taught to attack Israel. The adults need hunted down and shot for this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge congrats to @A_Reid81 @HighlyReal__ and Kennedy Cronan on representing @WeAreSouth_SB as part of the All-Tourn… https://t.co/4m8vcX5k1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hickory Ridge High School - @hickoryridgehs in Harrisburg, NC https://t.co/j8sbE0perw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This episode made me laugh 23 times. Listen or you’re a big ol bitch https://t.co/6uHwsMGfJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHAQ hey shaq where do you get your golf shoes from?  I am a size 18 and nobody makes them  I know your size 23 is… https://t.co/gj07VhCjFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Collins on the disappointment of not advancing: "I was PO'd. I was angry...That's really it. I was pissed."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaniRemigio @spainprimero Juasjuasjuas...ni de izquierda ni facha.....soy un redomado 😝😝😝😝...facha, claro😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews He's not super concerned about immediate family when he separates indefinitely them at the border.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parkertm @mattyglesias 2) any political questions about whether what they actually *mean* when they say "Medicare… https://t.co/N9lO74Uhfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Big Doinks by @fairstatecoop @ Chuck and Natalie's Place — https://t.co/EG1xzR1a6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[saying "and if you wanna film it that's fine, but you're missing out. and let's play.... fallingforyou" before pres… https://t.co/b7vg13ZijM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephen90045069 @stevenmosher @milkchaser @pcampbell001 @priscian @JamesRider3 @RushhourP @ray_langella @AltUS_ARC… https://t.co/6REClEn7R4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie @MMFlint Yes Mike, get on the bandwagon for the DNC anointed, because, old people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday @SeaTacAirport. Kind of expecting to see @theCarlaMarie and/or @WorstAnthony]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcoGutierrez @realannapaulina @POTUS @RealLatinos4US @realDonaldTrump @MarcoGutierrez If you need help getting o… https://t.co/AHFUTtpzO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My god spanish 1 isnt real. I “studied” for the exam by watching 4 (four) bad bunny music videos and got at 100]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: @shelbywhippets 61 @gobluestreaks 59. #10 Whippets upset #6 Streaks advancing to face @TheSailorNation for t… https://t.co/rcyBKlb3sQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RLStollar Thank you brother for sharing and for the work you're doing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HanxFingers @UKJBB @MandyxMuffins @_Kitty_Wampus_ @TwitterMoments “...until such alien is subject to an administra… https://t.co/jHxeWUl0Lw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kdruckenbrod @MarketingProfs Yes, I need to tell my team to add it! They should have included it when compiling the list for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TermitesBeGiant That is definitely an issue in Midtown. They think it’s a pedestrian plaza. Good point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toyota Kia Vero Beach the Latin Connection Eddie Rivera and Moses Cantu come check us out. Se Hanks Espanol... @ To… https://t.co/mZysrt4y3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vsnaryxo lmao I’m glad you liked the stickers 😊 I love you too. Anything for you my love💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[It may have been cold and wet and a 4 hr drive but it was definitely worth everything to watch @Harding_SB today. G… https://t.co/KZBl5jVGNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Bryce, shithead reporter over here, can you tell us your thought on the fans of Philadelphia? Tell us about how gr… https://t.co/I9QBzx4jfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson Thank you this is what. People don’t understand we can not live in the past]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porque la Revolucion Avanza y Nada Ni Nadie la Para...  #AvanzamosPatria https://t.co/RZtrDYrh8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[All That Remains The Crofoot 3.7.19 . . . . #AllThatRemains @ATRhq #ATR #TheCrofoot #Pontiac #Detroit #metal #WRIF… https://t.co/6Sbw28Pajm]]></document><document><![CDATA[So all the marvel shows are canceled @netflix and y’all want to up the plan prices https://t.co/bKlIBdTpS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Photoshop Can we get an update on iPad Pro release date for photoshop?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TEXASMONTE @CrockettJusten @yellatus @jemelehill So you’re against upkeep on roads, fire departments, police, etc?… https://t.co/mtEu8XhgMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol All of these articles are great pieces of writing. But there is no sign that the current Republican Pa… https://t.co/FZZYRfVUOP]]></document></documents></author>