<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Me: gets hate for kicking jaclyn Ant: gets love for a video THAT I FILMED ITS FINE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSoberOwlie Yes you absolutely deserve care. You are starting over. You could have not made it back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And in this crazy life. And through these crazy times. It's you, it's you. You make me sing. You're every line. You… https://t.co/gPco07FYV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ObamaWhiteHouse Stop lying about what is going on you dont just find an Islamic man in the middle ofColumbian jung… https://t.co/kf2K3KKaFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm a bubble in a soundwave A sonic push for energy  Exploding like the Sun sleater_kinney "One Beat" waa rocking… https://t.co/bWsx1CIoi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day one of my trip to Santa Fe has been quite the whirlwind! There are about a dozen restaurants I walked by that I… https://t.co/A5uFsr1SAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Can’t Buy Happiness, But You Can Buy A Bikini 👙 &amp; That’s Pretty Much The Same Thing! #bikinilife… https://t.co/2Gz0HIOohC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amvetsupport @FLOTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse I do not believe you are even an American; identify yourself, do it be a coward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr Wow, I check you out on my FB page and no video there...They won't let me upload a video either. I… https://t.co/F3i9rR2zgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Killeen drives ain’t shit to me omm  I can do them hoes in my sleep... will be back veddy soon #BLOOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsiaRChapman I think you’ll find an agency more comfortable given your trust level right now. You can explain that… https://t.co/3IOtuVwzMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inagarten I can’t wait! I always tell my family, my best friend is Ina Garten, but she doesn’t know it! Ha ha ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hay días que quisiera vivirlos a toda, maso a tal punto de ni poder recordar que fue lo qué pasó.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericaNewsroom Dear Friends,  I am a former Soviet attorney, please read my No. 92 -- Ripping the Mask off KGB Ac… https://t.co/9hXPnVDBi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a voicemail from my god momma and she was all pissed I didn’t answer... little did she know I had been at wor… https://t.co/r1hoSFJx9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man is old school Italian. He would give him a verbal warning 1st! Then Forget about it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oakland come through. ❤️ @BeSteadwell wrote an amazing musical that I am apart of 🌈 come see it April 10-13th at Mi… https://t.co/YYfEOyTjla]]></document><document><![CDATA[It blows my mind that people try to cheat a charity system for their dogs health care, skip out on a bill, but have… https://t.co/YrGAAjp1ZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiNurse @luvlambs @patchfarmstead I thought raccoons or foxes but we deal mainly in possums here so not sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“best actor” . . words what are they even #Oscars https://t.co/o2FRCB3jAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bergenstables @Gatorkitten @Kimbchr Living the green grass and weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally have been sitting at the library for an hour and have not gotten anything done. Why am I like this🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I can bide my time. I can fight to get another chance. I can make sacrifices. Magic isn’t gone from this world… https://t.co/1DuCmzC0VB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand aggravation if someone jumps in your mentions and start coming outta pocket and being disrespectful bu… https://t.co/vqpCfqJe1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[More proof of just how little our government officials know about EVIDENCE based treatment for autism.… https://t.co/CP42QNh8Xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[$23 billion = how much more funding predominantly white school districts receive compared with districts that serve… https://t.co/oYxAigyxUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[mas pera, se falam que não foi com a marina porque não tem provas, como sabem que foi a gioh que contou, sendo que… https://t.co/NDcJVYFfpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helpme_Rhonda_ @MrsChrisBrown89 @missjournalism THANK YOU, some people are really dense..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AZChiweenerPop @yzest5121 @SpectatorUSA @realDonaldTrump @20committee @spectator https://t.co/5aeTQAnxYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to all and especially Meredith O’Neal. We are very proud of you! #RunMeredithRun]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I ever get to become an influencer  the first brands I would reach out to would be @odoreaters and tinactin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @toriewilliams22 and all of the girls that made All Region! https://t.co/TFNJbiKava]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished rewatching @OnMyBlock and I can’t wait 3 weeks to know what happens 😩😩😩 #onmyblockseason2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super proud of this little lady!! #dmf2019 #nowtodistrict https://t.co/Xk2NGRVVkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gun Restrictions Have Always Bred Defiance, Black Markets https://t.co/iscpprsxOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puta madre! 😭, he keeps creeping back. You can’t be my friend nor will any of my ex’s be my friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSugarballoons Iesha Trotter, I remember only a couple of years ago .,, look how God is blessing you...QUEEN!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sweet Caroline” 🎶💃🏼 @ Fiji University of Arkansas https://t.co/TijjoRGPQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little things matter!!!! #choices #whatareyougonnado @ Knoxville, Tennessee https://t.co/n4h9OKhLAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dorianwarren Ignoring antisemitism helps White supremacists. White supremacists don’t consider Jews white.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙌🏻  • • • 🌠 #spiritual #faith #faithful #toptags @op.tags #god #grace #pray #prayers #praying #amen #believe… https://t.co/JLqPuLLSOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao this fits perfect with my sister with her damn Ford Explorer 😂 but it looks nice tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ServantLeaders #BartsPIE #TUProud @CowboyBart333 @quntut13 @NovaO https://t.co/8TckRzi1lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmRenae1218 Yes please!!! I’ll send ya a message the next time I want to. Maybe next weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por que todo mundo no Brasil celebrou Valentine’s Day no dia 14/2? Véi, dia dos namorados no Brasil é só em junho 😂… https://t.co/NKzRfnNXjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phil_Sledge You're making it very difficult for me to enjoy my chicken sandwich....🥪]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can catch me here all day not thinking about anything school related #hiatus #bestpictureshowcase2019… https://t.co/nGUj4r5Lp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bibi_Camilo Luckily I am able to work from home. That way I can lay flat to help]]></document><document><![CDATA[Typical post-snowfall shitshow in the #MeadowvaleGoStation parking lot. First few rows work well and then it all fa… https://t.co/ntDB1ByqY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics So judge ordered Stone and his attorneys to STFU, but he has shown us what a media whore he is. Any pu… https://t.co/eGs9n8ttr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw this short cover by alexander.ivy on guitar and loved it!!!!Rock on girl 🔥🔥 . . 🥁 + 🎸 @ New York, New York https://t.co/qt2oFDOiTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still in shock that my first year of college is over in less than 3 months like wut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slow start to the day. I’ve been at work for like an hour. I’ve ate my breakfast and just tucked my blanket in.  I’… https://t.co/8horPd93lH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek In another story; Rosenstein says this assertion is factually incorrect]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s pancake Sunday! The kids love my pancakes. It must be how I add the milk, eggs, and mix together. 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Stratford Community Center https://t.co/tMoIaWThUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omar, Trump envoy Elliott Abrams clash in fiery exchange https://t.co/nkMW7e530u woman has got go!!  Nothing she be… https://t.co/3mhioQRaRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gif just made Powerade come out my nose and idk how I feel ab it 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really !?!?! runningwithroro #stopeatingmyfurniture 😳 #youarestillcutetho #blairpack7 @ Salem, Virginia https://t.co/cbH0OZFZIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶...In dem indian wedding, Dem old ladies singing See how dem young gyul wining  Mor tor Mor tor Mor tor 🔊🎶🎶🎶 @ For… https://t.co/x3lmqyg4ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book talking to each other on this minimum day &amp; it is just making my ❤️ so happy! #booklove https://t.co/sP5fiHA4jQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift’s career is so fascinating. I would die to sit in on meetings with her team. I’ll sign that NDA! I jus… https://t.co/PfbGG7pmGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#brunchsohard #losangeles #kimonobrunch @ Water Grill https://t.co/r8JnjeMZtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SWardArch @only1joesmith The building wasn’t, but the art was relocated so the historic relationship between colle… https://t.co/GcgfgFglWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elevator Pitch https://t.co/41QH6SkyAV via @YouTube Vote for my project]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajwarr31 @OnTheMetra He handed the conductor his 10 ride and I just... nooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ingakokic I swear to god I was looking through old ass pics of us on my computer yesterday and literally was think… https://t.co/rLElznx7ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was such a hard day and it’s taking everything in me to wake up tomorrow and do it again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GH_obsession @mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 @SpeakerPelosi I agree they definitely need to take a look into Diane Fei… https://t.co/kh6bPhyowU]]></document><document><![CDATA[and all the evil spirits who wander through the world seeking the ruin of souls. Amen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 Yes! I have always thought this from the beginning, that his mouth looked just like a sphincter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ONE more week till I’m laying on a beach in FL and let me tell you it’s much needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[why can’t I be like @solarmahone and have my fav celebrities follow me too 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Musical selections at the LGA Shake Shack as I'm waiting for my breakfast sandwich:  -All Star -Changes -Paradise C… https://t.co/IdEC76rzzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good character is not a prerequisite for actors portraying  characters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy how the president can get away with saying the rudest things ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too Fresh ft. @iWillSmith | Painted using iPad Pro &amp; Procreate #artistsontwitter #BlackTwitter https://t.co/fgVuyQuiAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[like I’m not even procrastinating I just physically cANT KEEP LOOKING AT THE SCREEN and it always kicks in at the w… https://t.co/QFHTCiRbqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just signed a petition: Don’t let Mitch McConnell kill democracy reform. Sign here: https://t.co/9D2zPA2E0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResistanceGold1 @WendyTruong3 @kneadinghands @OwenGoyer @Schutz_14 @MissMaryCovfefe @TheStaukBox @R2017Girl… https://t.co/uvpZ3mAUHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren Amen! Civility &amp; morals are sorely lacking in many of this group's souls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fascinating article on the rapid changes happening in Saudi Arabia under MBS, from relaxing social norms to the ris… https://t.co/BkQrQWCPj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a pretty girl.  Please share.  Adopt ,pledge, foster, rescue.  Hurry, she needs a home right now.  Urgent😢💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheugs @SamHeughan @barbaramills1 @sarahjaswim @LaurelSchuett @MauiJANderson @pjl24 @GHJNancy @ladybay8… https://t.co/QgRpBkpDT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[melinda is on the little mermaid ride but still responds in seconds when I tell her i’m sad 🥺💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[mis amores ya no aguanto mas...voy a dormir..😖 estamos con uds.. cada hora que ustedes esten el #ApagonEnVenezuela… https://t.co/01kAV2MDbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been trying to convince shane we should get another puppy, but i saw these pics of this calf this morning. Hah… https://t.co/YXTBakSwen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BartCrow here’s to the songs that I play...and the love that music saves. #bartcrowband #dearmusic #txcountry… https://t.co/IwwX0wwxMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Tuesday everyone!! · This past weekend, some of our brothers and pledge had the awesome opportunity to attend… https://t.co/lni7HJpQzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRafter @Ollie_Cycles Would love to speak to a firearms expert in law enforcerment about WHY that is. Four ppl: th… https://t.co/sqjKOjvpdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouisWTPromo @Louis_Tomlinson @Louis_Tomlinson @Louis_Tomlinson @Louis_Tomlinson @Louis_Tomlinson @Louis_Tomlinson… https://t.co/1nzW4kqgb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black &amp; whites are the best ❤️🎵 @ShayMooney @DanAndShay https://t.co/hclImWyEP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for spring in #newhampshire ! Sick to death of #winter  Go check out the amazing #christy (links in my bio)… https://t.co/JErE69rVD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still PreGaming 🦅⛹️‍♀️ - Drinking a LazerSnake 2019 by @3floyds at @grain_grape  — https://t.co/UUpUTtZKT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What started as simply putting my clean clothes away has led to a full bathroom declutter. Bye retainer. I won’t miss you #amianadultnow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discovering really special places around my new home = magic 🌲 @ Northumberland County Forest https://t.co/UEA37CVszD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pushed my button for @DentonArnell! #TheVoice https://t.co/uPl7rFUHAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My neighbors freaking walk by every time I’m outside smoking a blunt like y’all are making me feel like I smoke too much go awayyyy lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got a reminder email about my flight on Saturday. Airlines act like I haven’t been counting down the hours f… https://t.co/5sXbxqUREZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grandma and Mom ask me to do this for Shanel Balogun all the time. I clean the dishes out of Shanel Balogun's room.… https://t.co/LnQ0bv3aD5]]></document></documents></author>