<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Hey Onion Field, Stop lying. Republicans obstructed the investigation for two years. Crooked DonaldРђд https://t.co/Ovr1d9jemq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miriam_Junne De qu├Е se trata la noticia o el tweet? Me tiene bloqueado la persona del tweet que hablas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You dumb niggas really sat up here and tried to educate me on the prison system like  one IРђЎm not really Smart  TwoРђд https://t.co/ynGhCQn5z1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AmericanBornHockey @USAHockeyArena @USAHockeyNTDP @usahockey @NHLРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћРђћ https://t.co/Vy5JQR72o0 https://t.co/9lvVuGSVKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AAstrojet @seanhannity I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quincy HOMEРђд https://t.co/x6TiaZ7ye5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TorriesNoseJob You have Sasha fans who thinks she's the be all end all and better than everyone before her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runningwolf1978 That's awesome!  I have 3 all rescues they are strictly indoor.  They get visitors too lol,  neighborhood cats tease them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyberMikeJ Not easy with 5k vendors all saying the same thing standing shoulder to shoulder]]></document><document><![CDATA[@locknesss456 Better hit the store and stock up on bottled water and charmin !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@p_lewandowski1 Me @ GodРђЎs design of these animals https://t.co/hUil72GFbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPD66Pct  N.C.O sec " C"  YELLOW  bus  with expired registration has departed to pick up children .­ЪњЂРђЇРЎђ№ИЈ­ЪњЂРђЇРЎѓ№ИЈРђд https://t.co/lG42jxEWUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to make the stock rich-guy criminal toolkit to be so distastefully risky, so unpalatable of caught andРђд https://t.co/7kXbQ15BdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[allstarbagelmanasquan and #beethoven #saturdaymorning #kiddos @ Wall, New Jersey https://t.co/jBnblLtet7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspan WeРђЎre taxpayers asshole, we already pay for it. I trust someone was in the room taking notes plus a translatРђд https://t.co/g1Cpc63Fze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandadeelion2 I think my man JT said it best with Рђюwhat goes around comes aroundРђЮ. People who put love and happinРђд https://t.co/gu76EXEoZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because those things occur does not mean White Evangelicals approve of such. There main concerns was pro-life, pro-Рђд https://t.co/QJOGT6uqAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrwells82 Nice catch. I wrote that while doing 32 different things. I knew Rauch had done it, but it was that horrРђд https://t.co/9ZdFSJ3PX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well a lot of the details on most of your tweets are bad, so just go ahead and bounce the whole account]]></document><document><![CDATA[LetРђЎs see if AG Barr will do the right thing and let the public know how corrupt Trump and others crooks are, or heРђд https://t.co/qKjEz8pM4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man owns 2 stores, but uses security cameras on only one. The cameras help him catch 90 shoplifters. In the 2nd sРђд https://t.co/ahNtQm1u8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronLemingNFL Yes he has, and he might save what little respect Chicago fans  have if he owned it publicly and voРђд https://t.co/pAZpC8DLHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюI think what Nathan and I are trying to do is use Cernovich and PosobiecРђЎs own tactics against themselves, but doРђд https://t.co/OTBJpNamgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cay_B_ This dude as always been a clown. I am glad he got the showing he deserved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So IРђЎm messing around with credit karma and all the cool info it has and they have a tool that finds your emails inРђд https://t.co/dwNJlQKedN]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #screentime summary alarmed me. Thats a lot of fucking time each day but what blew my mind was how often I pickuРђд https://t.co/VGJIz8He9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[LF scrims! Our team is finding our identity, and we wants to take the next step before qualifiers. DM me if interesРђд https://t.co/UxCt0VRcNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every new business that has opened on our Main Street has been a huge celebration. We are DELIGHTED to announce theРђд https://t.co/Rip5mgP4vR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing РђюnothingРђЮ isnРђЎt always nothing. Staying focused, requires strength.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jake_burns18 CanРђЎt tackle n undersized like schobert. Fast and dynamic playmaker tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCComics @BRIANMBENDIS @NickDerington @Walmart Will this be collected in trade paperback? Or is it available in CaРђд https://t.co/1Nv4wrzPf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah yes, all those poor people doing poor people things like trying to survive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFLDraftBites  who will the @raiders take with their three first rounders?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judgebeats 5-7 dollars over a period of Time adds up  ItРђЎs one Thing if you live by a metro  Also over longer distРђд https://t.co/jOdXzLzC9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/5/19 Wabasso Schools 2 hour late.  Buses on plowed roads only.  #rabbitpride]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come into Grand Central before the St. Patrick's Day Parade. Doors open at 12:00 noon. #stpatricksday2019Рђд https://t.co/SC3ywwEPJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[last night a man told me an improv show I was in was Рђюlike watching Rick and Morty onstageРђЮ and then I blacked out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1bigbeer @RealMattCouch Actually itРђЎs a Jack fruit from either the island of Borneo and Sumatra. Orangutans love them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinson_ramon @DeAndreHopkins God Bless you both! Appreciate what you both do for kids in SC and beyond! #MakingADifference]]></document><document><![CDATA[See this my point I donРђЎt get it see when Becky does it u guys  love it but when Ronda does something cool like turРђд https://t.co/VSxxVeVDwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Pursuit  I'm gonna go make a Sammich.... anyone need anything from the fridge  ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @davidmweissman Is there an Рђюall of the aboveРђЮ option?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@93wibc @93wibc The image you are using suggests that the student committed rape. If he sent inappropriate texts, tРђд https://t.co/CGs40Ch02P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePreztle @RSAtroxJal The Blue dragon panels really hit me from when getting good enough equipment to fight BluesРђд https://t.co/H8ioL70lY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends The 25th Amendment was created to be used when it is needed. It provides the PresidРђд https://t.co/f6TbCWWJVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha am I the only one who wishes terrible things upon themselves in hopes that if they happen you donРђЎt have to go to work??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there any female rappers interested in discussing anything other than their vag?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny, the same thing was said when @jimmerfredette played Рђюnever gonna seen anything like him in a long timeРђЮ is nРђд https://t.co/cknvjnapgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Perhaps if Republicans had the gonads to address this issue when they were in power of both Chambers we wРђд https://t.co/wPMOG2MMHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timberwolves @DeltaDentalMN Uncle Drew didnРђЎt just make that!?We got next!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This continues to be the best thing that pops up on my feed no competition]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking Republicans donРђЎt want the truth. The party is a sham. It has zero credibility.  #Cohen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who is coming out of retirement  @JasonWitten #82 https://t.co/VMVxtSfuwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I donРђЎt like to dog on refs... especially in basketball, but it is disappointing to see a set of two referees win a game for a team..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSPhilly OG Daily News Live from the late Рђў90s-2000s was the best show on that channel and they ruined it. The fРђд https://t.co/iPaDbSdcHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This absurd claim that we have A shortage of truck driver's,Been hearing this all my career. In A driver's eye's,I question the motive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathanstitus @SkySportsPL @GNev2 Its Mou with a dye job and Souness clothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be up some shit and still where comfortable clothes IРђЎm not a extra nigga when it comes to clothes but shoes is another story ­Ъўѓ­ЪЉЈ­ЪЈй]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buckingham_meg thought of you when I read this.  Here in Charlotte they are looking at building a second rail oneРђд https://t.co/7WjYNpvLvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @SenatorSinema and @SenThomTillis for introducing this bill. IРђЎm hoping @Repbencline and @Reploucorrea wРђд https://t.co/0Ygwhr7rmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaineРђд https://t.co/QosjsRdV6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my sister's (on left) last round of chemo!!! ­ЪЎї­ЪЈ╗ I cannot imagine the pain, emotions and things she's beenРђд https://t.co/XrYttN8nKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Storms...by His command and His peace they are silenced. Just a little declaration/prayer the Lord gave me this morРђд https://t.co/xTy831kbH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Burns Family Artisan Ales https://t.co/GF8z9OXhYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A nigga will brag to someone about who YOU fucked just as a conversation piece. You cats are lame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephynb @nytpolitics We are definitely not taking about the same thing.  Did you have a late term abortion becausРђд https://t.co/mAnocKjo95]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @LindseyGrahamSC HAHAHA!!! Keeping us safe, right Sean? Art of the deal!!!! https://t.co/oRseEHzKSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuLuRoche Funny how he just wants to pump money into the military industrial complex while ignoring how we are reaРђд https://t.co/7MRSS50Gbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nodaysoff#andis#wahl#barber#barberlife#barbernation#barbers#barberlove#barberworld#barbering#barbershop#puertoricoРђд https://t.co/B5GRwBcDuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter playing Metal Gear Solid IRL.  #MetalGearSolid #IRL @ Columbus, Ohio https://t.co/2ayfhEkqji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhakiBlueSocks WHY DIDN'T YOU LIKE IT IN THE FIRST PLACE!!?­Ъце https://t.co/DJQcdLS3dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay. I found Brooklyn-99 and IРђЎve watched 7 episodes. I like it. https://t.co/HB5KorkfPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedManShow @BCampbellCBS @BCampbellCBS twice in one week... LetРђЎs Go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RanesHook @VHSRevival @bonkersasscin @badmovieman @skipbolden @cinema_strikes @TrashCanDanpt3 @DamianHempsteadРђд https://t.co/3wafv5qqB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaGrubbsPhD @Ashadahya Josh Jesus didn't say follow Christians Jesus said follow I for I Am to take ya to I FaРђд https://t.co/5rLkIqLjDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fun just never stops. #icebucketchallenge @ Lafayette, Louisiana https://t.co/BeKJrUTQyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reason #76 of Why I love Twitter. It helps provides reflection points on a Saturday morning. @FraserLearningРђд https://t.co/lkdkgpA3me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HombresDesnudo2 Kiero aljien con kien pasar estefrio no avra algien porai disponivle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kporzee You're gonna be a great combo with Luka and win NOTHING. You wemt through the tough rebuilding years in NYРђд https://t.co/gSpxzdNSvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sidneypegula @MichaelParthum @TJSamer @Burgmania @KevC_Sports @Stuboyar @billsequipment @leoroth @NicholasMendola @kilgore_ed Rick Azar?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pburkevt @BFA_Athletics @BFAStAlbans @AmericanCancer Special moment and game for a great cause. ­ЪїИ­ЪњЌ­Ъјђ­ЪњЋ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@orctilate1 @BrandyShemal2 @Conservativ_Cat @shinypok3hunt3r @cadester22 I wasnРђЎt expecting this  shiny clamprel exРђд https://t.co/lASS2HopuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago #fashion Show post video. Previewing. @tridence . . . #fashion #fashionblog #fashionblogger #chic #modelРђд https://t.co/828QdZ1hmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come join the Freshman leaders and @PVAMU_CAB Monday as we present a panel discussion addressing Black Mental HealtРђд https://t.co/PKbL052F19]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of these two amazing kids who are both representing #KoldaElementary @ccisd in the #CBScienceFairРђд https://t.co/cqaao098zk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSRaleigh is the 0.2 degree tilt being tested or something? I've never seen this much beam blockage before https://t.co/JiTFrLCCYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReBourneAgain cant wait to see bone soldier isimori vs thunder liger for the title should be a hell of a match]]></document><document><![CDATA[Itz like LA ex up in here!!!.  The line up of #birds in the air awaiting clearance 2 land on my window sill and graРђд https://t.co/YyAnottnLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricRaskin The fix is in.  They already have created a special belt for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto The Jews are screwed again. Young dems will embrace Islam.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffReidUP @GREATBLACKOTAKU @KSAMANNY Bro. I've been here so long. I rememeber when the Insiderz were Kevin Nash (Рђд https://t.co/NsX06Lhj4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Treasonous Obastards ObamaРђЎs ClintonРђЎs Clapper Brennen Comey Lying Lynch Holder Evil controlled AmericaРђЎs PresiРђд https://t.co/sgREsTJnPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Also pretty slick. DEMS said you couldn't get anything done when you had majories. FALSEРђд https://t.co/9XzTHM9UBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: how many times have you watched that tiktok today? Caeg: I donРђЎt know Ev, How many selfies have you taken todayРђд https://t.co/DaxEtV7WbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SnowboundPlaylist: ­ЪјХMush, Mush­ЪјХ  (I'm gonna run, I'm gonna try I'm gonna take this pack right to ya All my heart,Рђд https://t.co/zGO4oH2DG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed this! If you know a teacher ask if you can go read to their class. It was a great way to meet the kiРђд https://t.co/4Sctxr4HYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace @PhilipRucker ItРђЎs clearly a very small tool kit.  He has two tools....hate and fear]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson Hey Tuck! Can I call you Tuck? Anyway, just keep doing what youРђЎre doing! Once you find yourself inРђд https://t.co/s38wVa5Lth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another pop-up show!!! Next Friday, March 15th from 5-7pm, lululemon of Lake Forest is hosting РђюWelcome to SerenityРђд https://t.co/4iKSb4zDN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Btscott5 @iamthemanuell @BTheLastHope @aka_stretch @ColbyHillegass @DemetriSmooth @Megadon23 @goknickstapeРђд https://t.co/62mGK4AOdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @DonaldJTrumpJr Show us one defense .  And you know he lost a lucrative film deal because of that, riРђд https://t.co/2rfuZ3qRIE]]></document></documents></author>