<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@khalisa_rae Thank you. I’m going to watch a lot of Juan Gabriel videos. 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaghateParthFC_ @LaghateParth #HBDParthSamthaan ❤️ The colors of rainbow🌈 May your life be colored with joy,fun,ha… https://t.co/ruFGPEMj7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is into everything but so very cute!! @ Mullinville, Kansas https://t.co/XmLX9PtmN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe What is going to happen is that Trump's businesses will be in jeopardy. SDNY will find criminal behavi… https://t.co/k9YNHtzLN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the first time in like two months I’m not surrounded by snow! So thankful for being home 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love connecting with people. Regardless of how shy I think I am, it really is a high for me. All highs have low’s… https://t.co/9wEy6RB5kG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr Canaday’s, my work hubby’s, birthday and he shows up on IXL! Happy Birthday!! 🎉🎊🎂🎁 #CCESProud https://t.co/DCeIVcrztR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume Journalism is so dead, people commenting on your tweet do not know the difference between reporting and c… https://t.co/R1FSRORuVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyAd53451729 @FCSOTherapyK9 @OfficialLivePD @LivePdFans @LivePDNation @LivePDK9 @Christina_Roof Is it raining where you are yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m finna delete my crush on all my socials because he don’t pay attention to me...🙄😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tara Hills CA Wed Feb 13th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Chance Of T-Storm Lo 55 THURSDAY Chance Of T-Storm Hi 59]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love when these hashtags collide! So grateful for you, Sean! #JoyfulLeaders #CelebrateMonday #ThePepperEffect]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only teams I don't want the Nuggets to face the first round are the Rockets and the Lakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AFStoner Yes! I left for a conference yesterday and had to scramble to put A’s together before I left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Isa54v5 @Sacraestvita @testisfidelis @_BLACKCATHOLIC @StevenErtelt @CatholicVegSis Good night https://t.co/QRZvksFl1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @AdamRuins about weddings. I should let my brother watch this. @Shippyfunsports maybe you should tell your family to watch it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on vacation right now (yippeeeee!!), but I have a problem... I was on a plane when #TheBachelor aired! 😭😭😭😭😭😭😭… https://t.co/MC02diwzgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Be w/ the Unseen 🌻 , You Be w/ the Unknown 🤷🏽‍♀️ . Hair: @_konceitedbeauty on IG 💕 . https://t.co/GGAzYgYWl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylornloving @JLOV34 I love you sweet girl ❤️ So very proud of you for always following your dreams!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it comes to spin, @soulcycle &gt; everywhere else. Don’t @ me on this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Guadalupe: broken clouds, 17°C 45% humidity, wind 4kmh, pressure 1018mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of control? Feeling helpless? Got PMS? Stop suffering! Call (626) 447-0679. Treatment is covered by PPO ins.… https://t.co/jMa7cngd6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got a $175 coat for $52 😎😎 It was improperly tagged and I don’t feel bad for taking advantage of that mistak… https://t.co/Kdf3CzrLmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanBJackson1 @1wingCoachB @nasapl @fit_leaders @ddelaughter @tyarnold18 @NickHoltvluwer @DrChrisLongo @MrRileyjo… https://t.co/h1qsyxkOr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone please tell me why I wake up at 4 am every morning and today have songs from White Christmas stuck in my he… https://t.co/7TMFKFk9dr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my girls! These two inspire me! Signing up to be a switch leader was one of the best decisions I’ve ever mad… https://t.co/4du9H2uvRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HealthySnack : Veggie Pizza : Hummus and Greek Yogurt Veggie Dip with Cucumbers and Radishes:  . ………………………………… Gre… https://t.co/Hux9z37OD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally how do i find ppl who have the same interests as me, im so aggravated and lonely lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I just lost all my shit!!!! I can’t  even form words right now!!!#AStarIsBorn #BradleyCooper #LadyGaga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed are those who keep his statutes and seek him with all their heart— Psalm 119:2 NIV https://t.co/fkbTGPZMhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Icons in the middle of the street   Thanks to #the_kitti_kitty for my paint job and to #birdlambro for this bomb ph… https://t.co/qR8C02qR8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[The place was gorgeous last night at 3am, but today in the morning light, I mean, COME ON. Willie Nelson still isn’… https://t.co/76aifsUmKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody in LA:  Me in LA: PURO PINCHE COUNTDOWN CITY. YEEHAW VIVA LOS SPURS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenDuckworth, sign the Rubio-Sinema letter to join @RepSchneider in the fight to protect #Medicare #PartD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @AdvertisingLaw Or our senators, @RandPaul 🇺🇸🇮🇱🙏⭐️⭐️⭐️ #WWG1WGAWORLDWIDE  TRUMP2020… https://t.co/mkHW0K9Tj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SpeakerPelosi: Oppose the Trump admin's proposed changes to Medicare Part D to protect people living with HIV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LexyBandera Tooooo many memories. Tooooo many inside jokes. It was the sorority I never thought I wanted]]></document><document><![CDATA[B4 | Gomez reaches on a fielder’s choice. Brumfield up with 2 outs, runners on the corners @CoMoSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people feel that Israeli funds have corrupted America-why should she do something she doesn’t agree with if it… https://t.co/XUvdbA4GiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAIT THE @JONASBROTHERS STILL FOLLOW ME ON TWITTER AFTER ALL THESE YEARS I AM : EMO 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@earthriseset @G_Paknowsbest @Cha51brolll19 @chefrocky413 @rockkitten86 @DawnHoad65 @CunningSq16 @tjbogart33… https://t.co/Hh4DKQkSQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucretiaPruitt We should downsize. I’m not certain that we’re ready for that. Maybe the same size house with fewer bedrooms?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedDragonFly19 @robin_ked @bedevilme666 @Sequencer16 @SealeyGerald @rkline56 @SpriteJ11 @LucyLovesTrump @Tankinc… https://t.co/aP6qi3xl2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retail needs to evolve into experiences that brings in a human connection in the midst of a digital world.… https://t.co/30rA1KCxS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸Con Sue Photography and Design🇺🇸   🇲🇼Like our photos...Follow our IG 🇲🇼  🇨🇱This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 🇨🇱… https://t.co/qQOs37Z0aI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love these ladies! They feel my heart with joy and my brain with knowledge! Happy Valentines ladies! I hope you a… https://t.co/qL5rAKRv1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a pleasure to serve on the United Way of Allen County Advocacy Committee...great meeting today looking forward… https://t.co/8MM2fB8CfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think there’s a band onstage! #corrosionofconformity #atl #atlanta #shortgirlproblems @ The Masquerade https://t.co/gGY6JcpdsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[matcalvani did damn good with surprising me at work!!! #loveyou @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/pUp1gmIHaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[An unimaginable day for the 17 families in my hometown. We will embrace all the families in their grief. Unfortunat… https://t.co/5DZCB2vV4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @blaizeshiebler_ miss you and our freshmen year days 💗💗💗💗 https://t.co/Mnbpifnveb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz you are one truly BIG ASSHOLE.....I sure hope your house is clean before you call someone out for wha… https://t.co/oVFJQ8BCg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think you're a bad parent watch the Neflix Documentary #AbductedInPlainSight Guaranteed to make you feel bet… https://t.co/KwAc3IgU77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotorheadRyan This one hurts a little and I didn't even know the man....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great things heard during ATD sessions: "...moving from tokenism to action" #ATD_DREAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Sloane Toyota of Philadelphia in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/inWZBUJFHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many retweets to get @VancityReynolds to come to my cousin’s bridal shower July 20th??  We’re a fun people I pr… https://t.co/oIR0X7UtRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m Alive!! Thank you Lord for granting me another day!! Something we forget that waking up each day should be the… https://t.co/sQg3b2rNnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conebonez69 @AOC @grist Well she did say " She is in charge"! Spoken like a 15yr old president of her high school junior body! Oh geez!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms Ina (Kadiatou Diallo) on her UA100 nomination for being the brand and taking care of all customers, specially yo… https://t.co/Ra4GkuAOIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrezood Share one thing you learned from @paco_olivas3 about solar power! #FLO #forcredit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dang. #blacklist trying to make me have nightmares of bugs coming out of someone’s mouth and throat. 🤮🤢🤮🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smugorange Happy happy birthday!! Enjoy your day as much as this hamster is enjoying his cake https://t.co/dsB7NoaKrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[No drama here. Only a ckassy natural looking enhanced brow. Absolutely undetectable as a tattoo or permanent makeup… https://t.co/GW9FMMjP6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nor any other @UPSers safety is a concern at @UPS! Company spokeman Joe Brown will make shit up, HR @MikeArndt99… https://t.co/5gyBKKKyOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramblingwithdan @hmgivingsoul @wishboneandvine @FionaMorgan79 @AkronWineGuru @thatsVeryKari @SLBriscoe… https://t.co/N0Y0e19Ldt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel I would like to see her hypnotized on national tv and admit what a fraud she as nd the rest,are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseball Family weekend! @LaelJLockhartJr @m_skinner9 @FHSLockhart @roy_skinner4 @klockhart5 @UHCougarBB… https://t.co/RpWlT3ZIUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are so many good reasons for students to study abroad. Developing global competence for personal, social, eco… https://t.co/FYixRLiqbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can do whatever your little heart desires as long as you are genuine to those who surround you. don’t judge oth… https://t.co/v3kU1O32Tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@AZCardinals' own Big Red was out with the @GlasserFDTN and Laveen Youth Sports to teach kids sports + life skills… https://t.co/P3yidyZ1wh]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I can saw is Lust is a real thing. Prayer for me. These Negros down here. Lawd!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why these type of “men” most of the time end up with daughters instead of sons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I only cried once today lmao I mean it was for a Spand for 15 mins but I mean that’s good for the first day right hahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Search me, O God, and know my heart: try me, and know my thoughts:  And see if there be any wic…… https://t.co/kuscCsHn0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my vanity but I’m really debating if I should cover the top with lewd anime stickers. I have so many just si… https://t.co/5dW8GbBHgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does hatred of @realDonaldTrump make a man step out in a god awful dress and look like he wants to be a woman?… https://t.co/XaUUeTx8Zq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessieJaneDuff @AnthemRespect No way!Hoda Muthana denounced America! She was working with the Terrorist yelling fo… https://t.co/9j3tVthLSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@analiafranchin @cardinalijuliet La canchereada de Charo amiga x plis 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@knyzen Are you getting a copious amount of emails from them? I don’t know how to turn them off!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow voy a Madrid en Marzo y mi amiga de PR se acaba de montar y otra amiga que vive en Londres me acaba de escribir… https://t.co/AsUoUo1apY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics The office of the presidency has a different meaning to trump..The White House is trump’s largest pers… https://t.co/461ZJ3CBSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Storing Health Records On Your Phone: Can Apple Live Up To Its Privacy Values? https://t.co/3rmGQTx2kI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDOTCommish was excited to host members of our transportation committees today at @myTDOT Region 3!… https://t.co/4CaPRUtNwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @richard_mccune for that lesson a long time ago. Long live #SVLEscargot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace great interview with #AndrewMcCabe today!! Glad I stayed home today!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought the ghost in my house was gone, but it literally just turned on the dryer &amp; everybody is asleep 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucy took Buddy home for a sleepover with Stitch (pictured below😂)  and the house feels so weird. Miss a Buddy. 🐶❤️ https://t.co/zwfwN2eJ7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is happening this coming Friday. It’s won’t be possible Saturday because of rain! @ Pomona, California https://t.co/LRER9sCDCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[A leader who puts country over party no matter the consequences, and who is genuine in their approach to all sides in reaching solutions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What !? I was 🎤 singing Moves like Jagger one minute then the next song that came on was that one !!!! Whatttt?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day another #smeargle #pokemongo #gosnapshot #photobomb #sanjose #dtsj #dialga @ San José Museum of Art https://t.co/s8msxopjlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join Merida in being your own CuPig  #ValentinesDay2019 #singlelife  Donate on Paypal link for your custom high res… https://t.co/9s2KnMhIrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maziehirono Please hire a vocal coach. You sound like you’re the teacher on Charlie Brown shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mintyysquid Dude. Same. I had a cyst rupture on my ovary last night and couldn't lie down without screaming and cursing everyone out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StuartEmmrichNY @LizziePaton What it was pond green and accessorized with a flash mosquito/midges net. Nothng comp… https://t.co/9rse1grRrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh! The places they wanna go! I hope they get there some day! Dreams do come true! #DVMSFAM #DVMS143… https://t.co/1yiYmO1NlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just read an article where @JEFordNCTOY stated "We need to give careful consideration to the words that we use and… https://t.co/m2NiDkRfrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[So for Valentine’s Day nick and I sent each other gifts and we both sent chocolate covered strawberries. 🤠👌🏼😩💯🏄🏽‍♀️ #telepathy]]></document><document><![CDATA[You literally are trying to put women back to the 1950’s but we won’t go back !]]></document></documents></author>