<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @EricTrump Come on boys don't have a hissy fit. You're all a bunch of lying, stealing, treasonous,… https://t.co/ZVHTZe9Zwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @mattbbs3 I don’t understand his reason for this tweet.  Is he happy our nation is so divided?  An… https://t.co/VAYIifxosG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @LordMinion777 and @Foxtrot44 for liking my tweets and being such great role models for me. I’m so grateful to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's so much scarier to open yourself up to new people though and to tell those people you're doing poorly or you'r… https://t.co/tiKR3fqEZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WitchPlease was my reaction when I found out that smoking cigarettes, even just some nights, can cut my life short… https://t.co/gQqcBQnnUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting this really cool diet of coffee and adderall and I really am excited to being to better myself thanks for the support]]></document><document><![CDATA[SNOW REPORT: Dusting of snow in Ava! ❄️📸: Teresa Tost #mowx #kolr10wx @NWSSpringfield https://t.co/N7x2cX7zMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear if I ever get cheated on again I will do some savage shit as a big fuck you]]></document><document><![CDATA[✖️📐Angles📏✖️ . Appointments available this week at @hairetics_salon! ✨ To reserve yours, please visit my bio and ta… https://t.co/ihJ7vkto5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m with her! You are already perfect.. but if you are looking for a real world answer... they just have good photo… https://t.co/eOK5aqtzvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moral of the story: Men can’t take decent photos @gabriellebeech https://t.co/zsQyPEpmdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brunito690 @RealJamesWoods We'd welcome them. Salt of the earth. We like rural people in #Florida. It's the citidiots ruining the state.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClevelandClinic Walk away the pounds program created by Leslie Sansone is the best walking program.  Even idf you… https://t.co/EDKknH9HU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP #GOPCrimeFamily Are #RussianAsset paid in debt for #RussianElectionMeddling #GOPTraitors cutting safeguards li… https://t.co/JxBrmGZKVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @alexisperno and Chloe-Amelie Aikman @plantpop @PlantHighSchool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah hi, Zach is it? Girls work just as hard for an opportunity to play sports after high school as boys do and whe… https://t.co/MvqxSDNvZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAG4All @winstonCovfefe That’s funny. I never watched.  Never will. I think most ppl never heard of Jussie Smollett]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know Your Rights: Police Encounters with El Centro’s Black Lives Matter.   The community is incredibly engaged and… https://t.co/C0nFZ8oqbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If they tell you what you WANT to hear and not what you NEED to hear ... that’s not ya best friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[gen said i’m not allowed to have choc milk after dropping a whole ass half gallon at the grocery store 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[i walked into Ulta and saw everything i ‘absolutely’ need... my bank account won’t be happy with me pretty soon 🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family: Where life begins and love never ends. To our followers celebrating today, we wish you a Happy Family Day!… https://t.co/LVhmkaVjsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomthunkitsMind I appreciate all the hard work that goes into these articles, sometimes I think they give this lunatic ideas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4th Graders are hard at work on their habitat models! #PBL @PBLWorks @ApacheIS512 #science #MakerEducation… https://t.co/NqQc7PjILk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation @realDonaldTrump Trump followers are a bunch of fools if they believe Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doomedphantasm1 She also went on Neil Cavuto on Fox News during Obama to attack him from the right for not using t… https://t.co/BdiRogodEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend Larissa Parson, an AMAZING movement teacher is offering an afternoon workshop @BluePointYoga on 4.13. Joi… https://t.co/IHT5ORJhKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Def gonna hit up the lingerie shop Allie showed me.  Kris and I have our anniversary coming up and I’m not about to disappoint 🤷🏻‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other day, I shared my love for @PeterThomasRoth 's calming face elixir from the #GreenReleaf line. Today, I wa… https://t.co/MwSm7XDri5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Girl✌🏽Alyssa Milano: Democratic anti-corruption bill is a power grab in Congress — for the people https://t.co/JgiEhfj03s via @usatoday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ry_Madden @nkcusmano @USL_HQ @select_america @SpursOfficial Such a freaking LEGEND that Nina]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elvis has just left the building #Pens win 5-1! #LetsGoPens !!!!! https://t.co/QsLn1Y0uLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obedient, Affectionate, Stubborn, Loyal, Clownish, Intelligent, Strong Willed, Friendly, this is my Molly!  Now obe… https://t.co/d2DDrEEhCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at Waste Management? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and i… https://t.co/dgWaUeTf6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[📽📺📻📜 This is literally one of the best suggestions I've heard in quite a while... things like this could help us he… https://t.co/NspHbrNf2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think he needs an ophthalmology and psychological consult — the eye part, i am happy to do that probono (i’ll be… https://t.co/V8C3qxGO5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[BUT DID SHE GET THE PORK CHOPS SHE WAS TRYING TO BUY?! SHE HAD COMPANY COMING OVER AND SHE CANT SERVE THEM AN AUDI… https://t.co/8ql7PY8XnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGingerMinj DM me if you need to chat. I went through this with my dad last year.  Here to support or just listen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Megan_burns4 and @kayjay1152000 are not allowed around my mother anymore https://t.co/lBM6qv33kB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was really trying to give winter a chance... ya over that sooooo where’s summer at]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donholley0 My younger brother would answer the door naked.  After a while they avoided his house like the plague.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeshmatAlavi @Twitter @almostjingo @drawandstrike @DebbieAAldrich @HNIJohnMiller @LVNancy @CarrollQuigley1… https://t.co/jFT5vEDSD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eedwardsellis @ThisCantBeLyf @ThunderHeadFan Brilliant, brilliant strategy. I hope you enjoy that permanent republ… https://t.co/80W47wzvOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk if I ever told y’all this but I went to a concert and this cute girl was walking around asking for papers and m… https://t.co/yLRA61WwCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scshepard @FOX40 It says, “chain controls - 15 to 20 miles ahead.” It’s where the checkpoint is passing Pollock Pines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Actually we are all popping popcorn over here as Cohen is about to testify and reveal everything a… https://t.co/fCHUxmWzBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I get for not retweeting those dumb pictures 😫😭😭😭💔💔💔 https://t.co/qc3wfl5sZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leave it to me to be leaving for a trip in 2 hours and STILL not be packed.... Kevin might kill me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dailydaysspoilers Tuesday February 26th spoilers  #days #dool  @TMegiaAI10 @1CaseyMoss @missyreeves4… https://t.co/uB7Iyd3PaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebfromPA @HenryScarf Okay!! I really will stop!! This is just too too funny! But it's so sad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TracyJan I won't read/show this article to #Kaia, lest she may feel that she's missing out on the pooch pampering.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiaipassa great presentation at @CRT_meeting @ron_waksman @biljana_parapid https://t.co/vMzPdysvuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep being strong @khloekardashian  regardless of anyone else’s shenanigans you are a strong ass independent woman… https://t.co/DDDslqSKQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[si te quejas de personas hipócritas, asegurate de que no estés hablando de ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FullNam48149098 @BuntyKritty @andrewperezdc @AOC #NoHateTurtles #turtlesHateMitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or does it seem tonight’s episode is going slower than usual?  Not complaining just seems lately it f… https://t.co/Oldp5uYs5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me trying to hide the excitement for this seafood tower. 😍 🙌🏼 🦀 @SaltineNash https://t.co/P60hhosJ5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[my housemates: me *coming home ready to rant loudly about my day*:  https://t.co/3Mk1SGBXi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaycastruita @soyrocioliliana @alejahdro Y yo llegue a decirte a ti 🤓 y loo subí y @alejahdro me dijo también Hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner It just kills me how smart he thinks he is. He’s an idiot and so are his kids!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rapIineaus So happy to see you back 😊 Hope you are doing well and taking care of yourself 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[#snowyday#Winter#beauty#nature#Brooklyn#NYC @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/LUlNH9H0Ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@growingupzee Always up for stunts.  P.S. Sometime would love to hear about your stem cell therapy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckyUF @LoriMoffet @4thegatorgood @Rob_Dodd @C_Robbins97 @CJ_Clarke1 @SeanSteed Ayeeeee!!!!! That’s what’s up!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG! STOP This! @indivisiblestl @jenesq2 @MO2ndDist4Chg @LaterUSA44 @JolineAbba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyrsfaith @blessthefall @SLAVESOFFICIAL @capsizeband @GlassHouses_ GOING]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lessons learned: never underestimate someone’s ability to not know how to wear pants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just want a car to build already so i can spend all my time on it :\\\]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TankSchottle Tank, I love your positive spirit. I love your genuine care for others. You have a beautiful soul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prettybOiRad @justinalmanzar No fuck you both ... I’m hungry &amp; no one cares]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is not "good" just because you say it's good.  You're selfish and your kids will suffer for it.  Why not help th… https://t.co/8QEBGa4Frs]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Jose Reyes is a dirtbag, I’m not surprised by this behavior.  2. Don’t call it the ‘World’ Series if everyone ha… https://t.co/OErFJVEYIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NISDRhodes Captain Marvel #rhodesspringbreakchallenge https://t.co/MQ00EbysfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tadster48 Yeah lol.  They like to sit under the tree and wait on them to come to the ground for seed.  For awhile… https://t.co/fV6LIxZWJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear diary: idk about you, but I swear I always feel like a bomb or something. It’s like people can’t be around me… https://t.co/5mmPGE3Sow]]></document><document><![CDATA[أهلا بكم جميعا يسعدني ان أرحب بالمتحدثة بإسم الحكومة البريطانية في الشرق الأوسط وشمال افريقيا  أليسون كنج في هذا ال… https://t.co/VJMlrr5g86]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dog. OMIGOSH this dog! Dog of the resistance chillin at @Safeway #portorchard https://t.co/9BfrLGURWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[A whole fucking hour of Peterson? Wtf?? This is when I’m gonna get suicidal]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bonjour @Souriswingette  Best river cruise I've ever taken: The #NILE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe how some people continue to talk about this man as if he’s normal. Stop expecting him to do normal… https://t.co/jIFO0Fcjgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we keep God first, everything else falls into place. #WednesdayMotivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved watching that show and him in it.  It’s a shame greed got in the way.  Money should never be before people.… https://t.co/vbZHC1xrsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Más libre que nunca ✨🦋 #sigoreciclando en Brooklyn Bridge https://t.co/6nzvKCBu8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn Honestly sir, you’ve underestimated our intelligence. People worldwide understand all too well what you… https://t.co/Infl8DDjvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my older sister Lydia and my mom! We’re planning our visit to mom and the farm for this spring! But when the… https://t.co/D9s51sEsRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people can be on every thing else on their phone and still can’t reply to a text. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilxplum literally the one from the show 😂😂 rookie mistake tho i ordered it friday https://t.co/WJ0wXcr4ew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I signed some copies of #thelostnight at @shakespeareco on Lexington Ave. One could be yours! https://t.co/IqMxdLeue1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies, you’re adored. I’m inspired by your love and tenacity. Women in gaming and esports are girls I dreamed of h… https://t.co/1WY8y8MaWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allophile Thanks! Thought of you while driving this. Pictures for days!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for spring? 🙋Now that the snow has melted off we have flowers and gardening on the brain.  It's a safe bet to… https://t.co/Ivqorrd0PS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Us next year to whoever moves into Forest 124 @Breanna_Doss @haley_priddy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Until you spread your wings you will have no idea how far you can fly 🦋 @ Cocoa Beach, Florida https://t.co/wzL6LMWFhE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maggie’s face when Meredith tells her she wants to go on a date with Deluca. A MOOD. #GreysAnatomy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best grilled cheese in the city! #idrinkgaybeer 🏳️‍🌈 🍺 https://t.co/yg039Ae1Le]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have never been able to hide my emotions because I wear them on my sleeve. My facial expressions will show how I… https://t.co/wYSdlx0VRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstoryTina @Vaw511 @SenSchumer @senatemajldr Clearly you are too stupid to understand laws of the USA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday SHISTAR 💘💗 #legalorno  @_roxyroxx https://t.co/dIFnKvOvi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gilsimmons Yup, crazy weather!! I really missed having a good snow storm!! Good Friday morning Gil!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strong words from a strong woman. #internationalwomensday #iwd2019 #strongwomenlifteachotherup #strongwomen… https://t.co/AMWOzXgmoe]]></document></documents></author>