<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@CatholicPierogi The kids have such a good time learning how to do this. It sparks so much creativity. It teaches t… https://t.co/srcuIxglRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beauty and the beast X Romeo and Juliet  @Camila_Cabello @ShawnMendes @bazzi https://t.co/4gRhTmJgh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I tell y’all, I can’t wait to get my hair done in a week &amp; a half 😭🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[i keep saying “it can’t get worse than this” and yet, somehow it still gets worse]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope this takes him down. I'll never forgive him for how he treated Barack Obama or for being a craven, partisan,… https://t.co/ua4Besxn0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HausOfEse @kellycloonan @catiepetunia @MaddowBlog how the hell does he tie his shoes like that??]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is an appreciation tweet for the bold genius who took a boring flavorless cucumber and soaked it in saltwater… https://t.co/ZBmWjvjGPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s only 2 teams out 112 teams in AAA in the state of TN still playing today This is what these girls have drea… https://t.co/TGFE3y24Jw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel was a superb movie but when @nodoubt’s #JustAGirl came on during that fight scene I nearly came outt… https://t.co/3g1sJZFZo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @CynthiaMcFadden Nice story on older women; it would have been a great story if some women of colour had b… https://t.co/ZB2XZPnRQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiallOfficial Bravery behind the buttons but spineless in really life 😕 What happened to manners, morals, and kindness?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anaheim district to offer dual-language immersion at all 23 schools next year – OCDE Newsroom https://t.co/p0nMAQ9xgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[True he always said I was his cross to bear... then he hugged me and laughed @ Moms House https://t.co/MCUIwHBIIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also I don’t have therapy this week and uh not to be dramatic but it makes me wanna cry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher and I would like to wish you all a very happy #InternationalWomensDay @ New York, New York https://t.co/GQjMTV5sLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basic traing.  Brother flights TI was not trying to be a mean unkind person. He was there to help push us. The thin… https://t.co/DRD2JU94bU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jury Duty Post #3: I am mentally and emotionally exhausted after this experience. I am sad for everyone who has eve… https://t.co/0ZnypXnDzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be helpful if at least one thing in my life could make sense for me right about now 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a great day for sledding (and snowboarding, tubing, tumbling)! 🛷🏂 @NBCConnecticut #NBCCT https://t.co/jUYTUbw2gH]]></document><document><![CDATA[wanna know something annoying, people only focus on the pittie part if they’re mixed. lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[If BET was smart they would start their own news and focus on the voices of the black community]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings Respect Chairman Cummings! Respect! What an inspiring speech!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when I got to New York I went to the statue and I said, “Lady, I promise to take care of you and your ci… https://t.co/NKd1hb1ySr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy(s): Wait how did you find out? Girl(s): We're girls.... we find out everything sooner or later.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LissetBeauty Hey go watch my video, https://t.co/lJSrp1guv8 I got pretty good content. Hair, travel, how to, vlogs… https://t.co/Gtmu3sgg5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewdelly @cavs @PeakSportAUS GREAT TEAM WIN @matthewdelly THAT WAS A FUN ONE TO GO TO CANT WAIT FOR MONDAY’S G… https://t.co/gOxwyHBtrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know why laws don’t reflect public support for gun control? Because the public doesn’t support #GunControl. I n… https://t.co/JN2szM2NuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quicly threw together this video about cruisin' down US1 in the #Floridakeys.  It appears I inadvertently made a… https://t.co/01dLcWp7g0]]></document><document><![CDATA[PA Governor Vows To Sign Gun Control Bill ‘Immediately’ https://t.co/SiI3XYQMEX SCARY TIMES IN PA!!!!! Wolf should… https://t.co/MqtVvlFfEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robin_schuh @CressidaCowell @SkypeClassroom @ChatterPixIt @Seesaw @Altitude_Moose Love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a good idea. We have so many boxed and single note cards to choose from.  . . . .  #honeypaper #stationery… https://t.co/o25JkwJn1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I WILL DO ANYTHING IN MY POWER TO SAVE THE PEOPLE I LOVE. DONT EVER DOUBT ME.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom Return the money for you failed train !! The money isn’t going to @realDonaldTrump personally.. it bel… https://t.co/YGkrfX2OH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone have the Vegas odds on what piece of furniture AB is going to throw off a balcony when the #Steelers refuse… https://t.co/CjfXrJOdb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣😂😆 How we roll at TES  #pajamadayiseveryday #socalwinter #brrr @ Temecula Elementary https://t.co/xC9GtK0YDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This left wing crap has to stop. Illegals voting in our elections must be considered foreign interference and we as… https://t.co/wfM4I7nxpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlsBoy ...or been through the parent pick-up line to get their kids after school.  It can make you stabby. 🔪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Middleboro, Massachusetts https://t.co/2mmSwEo0qW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fire her. Take her to Court and prosecute her. This is a minor! Zero tolerance of abuse to youths.!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m upset bc the juke box @ morry’s doesn’t have gasolina and all i wanna do is shake my ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first #MVInterim and #mvclass trips experience on twitter....amazing experiences all over the globe and also her… https://t.co/KARFGWwBjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Crocs are CHOMPing at the READvolution School Field Trip! Let’s go Canes! #READvolution @SycamoreCreekES… https://t.co/vL03zxoAtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said INTENTIONALLY GRABBING SPACE JUNK SHOPPING FOR PARTS OK. SMDH OK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Morning @RadioLunchbox had me in straight tears! This mans enthusiasm is EVERYTHING! @mrBobbyBones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee is MY Valentine! #goodmorning #writingcommunity #valentinesday2019 https://t.co/oGNrIyrtrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McBittypaws I was being being controlled by a guy who wanted me to be his pet and had me pay for a lot of things f… https://t.co/30GHcdkqD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Starting reading 1984... scary how much you can see parallels to today’s world]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Guess what...the problem was resolved with your idea...from 2 to 3 months ago.”  As a consultant you don’t always… https://t.co/9Mm58LjpEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN see that julius cole black mercedes benz ml 320 vyz 4852 targeted krymena with smg uzi on richmond virginia ha… https://t.co/BawhJGzFD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todo lo que vamos a construir juntos es fenomenal 😘😍.   #love #FENOMENAL #dreams #pasion https://t.co/thO8oZb4F9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MtnDogBoy @pegasusbelle @mad_liberals @realDonaldTrump @CarpeDonktum Nope... Stewart and Linda Resnick own Fiji. I… https://t.co/m37vLxqvYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[When one of yo gfs catch you slippin  *side note: I use to babysit the lil girl in the photo and now she and JoJo a… https://t.co/kxxRYNQgFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicanInBoston2 @morningmika Too busy destroying Ilhan Omar for 3 weeks now. I hate them both. Sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comradekelley the train did come and at airport now! hopefully no more delays....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninadobrev  have a nice valentines day with your most appreciated beings. you have an angel and you are a pretty a… https://t.co/dAzyMQD5kR]]></document><document><![CDATA[yo the internet so ruthless mfs rlly in herb comments calling bro g herpes mfs just don’t give a damn 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they live on our tax payer dollars as we all know government just spends our money. Got it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze Why are you surprised, ?? you created this problem and others like you with the same mind set, Did you th… https://t.co/jVE7mInkrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz RepMattGaetz sticking up 4 the Orange Pinocchio will not put U on the right side of history! Being an… https://t.co/BjwcrWDFgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_musoscribe @thebandGHOST Very good interview here in my opinion. Shit is always going to happen. Look at all f… https://t.co/UgI7qaDUER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_onlyydess You probably sat in the back and was squinting instead of opening your eyes 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raydaleshamaine You? ME!!! I play my games and mind my business. No drama unless you make me have to put my 3DS down. 😤👊🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go visit India! It's so filthy mainly bc of overpopulation. We cant pay the price 4 Irresponsiblity by China, Indon… https://t.co/9X8rUsCXTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanVallyD This was true long before their petty and ill-mannered treatment towards Tavares and the Leafs 😛 they a… https://t.co/YmClTyAzP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jschwabish @urbaninstitute Hey 6th floor neighbor! Thanks for sharing the pics of the new community. We (HFPC) wil… https://t.co/KOGpmJaetN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronBlake You know, some people lower your IQ by just looking at them....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all VA Tech is always annoying. Everytime I hear their crowd cheer, for some reason I get annoyed. #Wahoowa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JazzJennings__ watching S5 Ep9  Hooray!!!! It’s so nice to see you guys get some good news, you’ve been through so… https://t.co/ZvvSlLs2rB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way back when I went to a car show in Paterson. #car #cars #carshow #custom #customcar #lowlife #lowcar #paterson… https://t.co/xRQPyKVzOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dale621 @xwingdma @ex_harvest @wad3mullen No, really, any mention of the Gospel?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heather Ahlstrom Kosec crossed OO. Time 02:05:19, pace 06:17 min/km, est. finish 2:46 pm https://t.co/Ts3LP8Jpud #Birkie2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice piece in Coach Cook and the program he’s building, Kirk. Go Toppers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i touch my bump all the time!! the baby can feel that you’re touching it and it’s comforting to them and if you hav… https://t.co/vAWICk4jSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏👏 congratulations @TuSimpleAI on a $95 million Series D! Arizona continues to raise its profile as the best locati… https://t.co/Kb5jn61SDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, St. Joseph, do assist me by your powerful intercession, and obtain for me from your divine Son all spiritual bl… https://t.co/FpaxzvwJ5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamcbest @jennifrancoise @realDonaldTrump The apple don’t fall far from the tree]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VVP_KGB @SReganBratton @glennkirschner2 @maddow @NBCNewsTHINK @MSNBC Unfortunate we all are ! That is their strate… https://t.co/sw39sc5IQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoperfidoDario @radiomitre Y cual es el problema de llamar las cosas por su nombre? Todos sabemos la historia de Eva.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can not believe @Colton just chose Cassie over @caelynnmk.... so disappointing. She 100 percent should be the nex… https://t.co/67yiwJZsCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HATE when people won’t let me speak. I’m already doing what you asked, please just hear me out so maybe we can fix this problem. 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s nights where I literally stay up till 4 am painting pictures of scissors that REALLY make me wanna drop out, ya know? 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EreborOsahon @Dangchick1 Not cut in the literal sense. More a wound of the heart. 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate nobody and just want all to know the truth and not be deceived.   The Lord is real and is the only reason I… https://t.co/WooVLTXSdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antoniaterrazas So if I’m understanding what you’re saying: that sexuality (maybe gender) can be ‘seasonal’ as in… https://t.co/v2bwGJBA3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd love your help to bring my project to life! Check out my classroom on @DonorsChoose https://t.co/nhJSyrGZnS… https://t.co/79J97RGPUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Digalo completo..Vamos bien porque vamos todos con Dios Nuestro Señor y su gran poder por los siglos y los siglos Amen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to get this show on the road ✈! Going to Indy to see our Emmy! 🎉 🎈 🎂 #itsherbirthday #auntemmy #uncletuck… https://t.co/hccpEnP5YM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some friends of mine do number among them, alas. #FriendOfTheDevil @GratefulDead]]></document><document><![CDATA[The horses don’t understand why they have to stand here 20 feet away from where they used to stand and they’re tryi… https://t.co/v0tkk5dZC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattLucas Wow that is crazy. Sometimes I forget how homophobic the world was. Qe are definitely the generation… https://t.co/Tb9Cq4gOcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a BAD man!! #idriselba elba @ Mulberry, Florida https://t.co/xNcInp2RGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch You keep looking for truth from this https://t.co/8oZvkOqhCU isn’t there.Hasn’t been for decades.She… https://t.co/KwjTmngdme]]></document><document><![CDATA[My apologies to Micheal Strahan for misspelling his name. Obviously it was a typo. 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IyanlaVanzant Watching from Philadelphia with some wine 🍷 &amp; a good Philly cheesecake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheilamac46 @Dzana1407 @WhiteHouse Pres Trump has 6 more years folks &amp; it's going to be MAGA !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump @RepJerryNadler Nadler is another Pelosi/Schumer puppet and should not be a chair of anyt… https://t.co/Z1UG7fmJpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParticipACTION Hey @Jdkennedy54 how about we do some hiking at Hilton Falls and Rattlesnake Point ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are our tanks. The 4th is in the process of being cleaned and set up https://t.co/zF4gsGuNME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomArnold She Just trying to find a way to stay relevant but I know with half a brain is listening to her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wyatt, Waverly &amp; Wynonna 🦆💚 #cluckbackatit #fluffybuttfriday #weeklyfluff #love #chewy #welshharlequinducks… https://t.co/M5QGXrgrg5]]></document></documents></author>