<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Now I wonder what implications this could have for Bible reading in public school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll always root for you wherever you go @NickFoles .... 💚 (unless it’s the Giants or Redskins)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get the free book, Work the System: The Simple Mechanics of Making More and Working Less. https://t.co/Y3poByH6Vn via @workthesystem]]></document><document><![CDATA[In snowy Boston for an Executive  Briefing. Headed home tonight. #viewfrommyhotelroom @ Boston Harbor Hotel https://t.co/iMQn358R9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Fountain Hills Festival of The Arts in Fountain Hills, AZ https://t.co/KfRp8DHA26 https://t.co/EtqS2uubtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE: The #CoquinaClutch spells the end for @reymysterio, and @SamoaJoe is STILL your #USChampion at #WWEFastlane!… https://t.co/1xtUXCrZPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Mrs. Matsis for inviting us to your Biography Bottle speeches.   The kids did a fantastic job!   #dvlions  https://t.co/rJyf7fejmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tasty hazy goodness - Drinking an Astronomical by @wickedweedbeer @ The Local Draught House  — https://t.co/dwTG4bX8FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the Oscars coming up, we really need to discuss the elephant in the room. Bohemian Rhapsody was fucking awful.… https://t.co/k2AHDA3jZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter Storm breakfast run! (@ Jumbo Donuts in Whitinsville, MA) https://t.co/fG3NLTSqub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Public service announcement: @Fi_Contextual is a total intellectual badass. 👏 https://t.co/LCirPhTMlS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost   This little pig needs to be removed now Nancy control your little pigs kick him out now]]></document><document><![CDATA[The show #ImpracticalJokers should be called #ImpracticalWaysToGetYourAssWhipped.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#yellowpainting #yellowart #paint #painting #jaunes #jaune #californialightandspace #abstractart #minimalpainting… https://t.co/vpq63tgpzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for your love, care, and dedication for us and our little family. I can’t ask for anything more.. I love… https://t.co/6zczBtqKOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lock this little fucker up he’s a disgrace to our catholic community! He disrespected this Native American Vet. He… https://t.co/rjhuObinYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about you @stormewarren @buzzbrainard @MCSiriusXM @TommySiriusXM down in Tennessee with all that rain! My… https://t.co/Pg1H4ifu0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CASMF @marcuslemonis @TheProfitCNBC @CNBC @hellobensgarden Immediately in our Ben’s Garden Soho Store- while suppl… https://t.co/7hHLuArqzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Morning Walk, Less Sitting Can Lower Blood Pressure for Hours https://t.co/wdrcOk0TTz via @medscape]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marco Rubio, you stand with Democrats on this, I believe you stand on more with them, you're not a hundred percent… https://t.co/KV3yyFIvvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew48815892 @ScottMLibrary @IngrahamAngle @senatemajldr @RandPaul When will it@be? After the system collapses?… https://t.co/VoMEiUUpoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Business owner fights to save 'last LGBTQIA+ black club in NYC' https://t.co/fqjvgGodfA via @nbcnews  My pal… https://t.co/yTHQUsr32F]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Credentialing Specialist - https://t.co/dWMBVQet81 #hospitaljobs #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave_Matter The program is close to turning the corner. We'll have more experience next year and should win a few… https://t.co/1wIsHlfNJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jaden Guidry 6’5 WG / TJ Ford.  Long with good wingspan. Has a set shot but he nails it from deep over his opponent… https://t.co/XczyHwn2Sk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fight for education is happening right now in Ontario.  The families in our communities need our voices heard.… https://t.co/oJW4Q7DSTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[MADRE MIAAAAAA😍😍😍, ese sentimiento de con solo ver una simple imagen se te ponga la piel chinita no tiene precio, e… https://t.co/A6Tbknagyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Clinton Student Athlete Alyssa Leblanc and the Lady Gaels Basketball team for running a successf… https://t.co/zn8JeVQNCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think hik punching his own teammates in practice are better stories but ight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si no quieres ahorrar no me compres las entradas para los Parques  de atracciones.        If you don’t want to save… https://t.co/93UyTWx9C5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmm, he’s saying it will be an  executive agency of State government under the direction of the Governor to provide… https://t.co/XyHQXQmkPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBeatWithAri @JoyceWhiteVance What shld have been earth shattering was the recordings the NSA had of TRUMP collu… https://t.co/57PQA73oDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I can play “Grazing in the Grass” by Friends of Distinction ... and, some here enjoy it ... my mission here is… https://t.co/XZ8f40cZ6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaithfullyBP There are Christians - evangelicals in particular - who try to shout down this type of factual statem… https://t.co/GSmrW59ZDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Džænæty čæštyšyg |Tears in heaven @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/daFgRvQK1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisJudy9 @erink_mitchell @JeremyMercer_8 can u two pls quit egging this on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAFrench Yet abortions are still happening so all of that really amounts to nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthonRaptor @ThoreauSquad @PaulRoundy1 And while DELMARVA may not exactly be a center of progress for such things,… https://t.co/ZJalmmHk81]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great multitasking here: walking, talking on the phone, ignoring reporters, enjoying a coffee and hating on Israel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s Evan? Ryan’s brother? Jesus Christ get the name right. https://t.co/5bT5NDZAh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HayzeJuly @UnicornFor3some As a client it let's me know that I don't have to go through life alone without human t… https://t.co/ltkAw2mHUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine : @POTUS apparently has not been informed by the CDC epidemiologists about the Incidence of Drug-Resi… https://t.co/A07nsorxTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carleigh1985 @DWeeks41 Paid to  beat him up ?  LOL!  Lucky for him he had no clue were the camera was  so no one c… https://t.co/rCdcugrHno]]></document><document><![CDATA[I truly enjoyed visiting with parents individually. It allows me the opportunity to listen and learn.  This evening… https://t.co/DWtWCyoTDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ New American Tattoo Company https://t.co/XuK15Or0pg]]></document><document><![CDATA[His problem is that he doesn’t perform during the regular season. Philly is the only team he hasn’t played belowe a… https://t.co/VexTX3pIX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sorry that the #Warriors got rocked by Houston without Harden.. #disappointing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cortez0818 Hankins back to the RAiders . Richardson is a FA - teams can start talking today.   Somebody at ESPN su… https://t.co/8XiYYxec9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really in depth article that I too have seen played out in real life.  The words stand for something or fall for an… https://t.co/lJYGzPlOj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aspeaches_ Lol the only people I guessed right were the gay guy and the old guy 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the other semifinal game, Capital leads Baldwin Wallace 33-25 at halftime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is very simple  Muslims by religious law want all Jews dead. There are no exceptions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul So are you saying that Donald is fibbing? Ahh nertz. I just started to believe in "it." C'est la vie.. https://t.co/twgRiMP072]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at the house. Wind knocked out the power, so having to start a massive file transfer over again. (@ Wes’ Livin… https://t.co/8eeHu2bunr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertolongoria @10APG @JavierAquino7 P.D. Hoy Gana TIGRES!!!!.. La U la U la U.... abrazo incomparable Roberto!.. 👍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m still a rockstar, I got my rock moves!” #badass @ Colonial Life Arena https://t.co/1ZQCCgUumk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kariyyahh @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/fdKWidzSRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@branson2_kevin @usopen Lendl and Wilander matches were always epic, along with Edberg and Becker.  The 84 French O… https://t.co/yHiPRpBnXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oMvkvrv_ Hi, We would be happy to assist you. See our innovative work here: https://t.co/0kK0depliy… https://t.co/RSM1vu3oBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichLesperance @AspenSnowmass @BehindTheKnife @MadiganSurgery @TopKniFe_B @DrHasanAlam @HBuMoore @ExcelsiorSurg… https://t.co/G0Kn1hWQc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, there it is, the most delusional nonsense I've heard all day. Saw this posted in a fb group and honestly thou… https://t.co/hHCdkMzf53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit @cristinalaila1 @realDonaldTrump does not need electoral votes from NJ.  Perhaps DOD bases in NJ sho… https://t.co/k84SL4ssTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nealhgentry @Medium @susie_c It’s not an attack on freelancers. It’s an atrack on companies abusing the $ benefits… https://t.co/KkbKg4Pe4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweettruth2me My word! Delusional people given over to a reprobate mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetNation He seems like one those guys thinks he is smarter then everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[But you know what this means, we're getting Batista Vs Triple H at #WrestleMania! #Raw #HappybirthdayRic]]></document><document><![CDATA[💛 Just another Saturday 💛 @ Southern Pacific Brewing https://t.co/5tjSKSC9ug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseyABC13 @abc13houston @TomKochABC13 @MayraABC13 @ABC13Elita @ElissaRivas13 @CourtneyABC13 @CharlyABC13… https://t.co/O4AQyWGWpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimomal77 @NorbertElekes Foreign aid is 50b, less than 1% of the budget. A drop in the bucket, and it gets a retur… https://t.co/HxyQZ6Cm6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlancheKnox5 @nightsun94 @Dinagarcia1932 @RepJayapal @MoveOn 🙄, your taxes would go up 100%, if you even pay taxes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitaniaMcGrath oh, I know why. what pisses youoff is that I’m comfortable with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[This team doesn’t deserve a tournament bid. Too inconsistent, scoring is an issue for long stretches 1-2 times per… https://t.co/IISRJZZKXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was nominated by @gus26 to post covers of #7books that I love: no explanations, no reviews, just covers. Each tim… https://t.co/y13XTNIJly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaBoots @StarvinLarry How extensive is the screening process for refugees? Background check?   Citizens must ques… https://t.co/4VYdZHQsEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[With that win by the women, Auburn Men and Women basketball teams are 5-0 against Alabama this season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florence wins 59-45. #basketball #hurricaneflash https://t.co/gv4sDGXGiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VomLXiKZZM Que Piñera lleve ayuda humanitaria a argentina ,es mas cerca y el pdte es intimo amigo..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've gone old school.  Morning coffee and paper delivery.   Now have a print and digital subscription to the Arizon… https://t.co/Buuz1qRtTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acupcakemess @JameyBaskow This is where we disagree. He was going after the puck and voracek changed course and hit him high]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Labor and Public Employees Committee meeting is still going strong, at 9 pm! This is what democracy looks like!… https://t.co/i7W6iWRV1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmDwarf I think it’s too small to be from a Saturn V. I’m thinking an ICMB of some sort. Maybe @mhanham knows?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuckMyGamecocks @coreypowell23 @CFBEditSupreme2 Do you really think Clemson didn't have a good defense? They were… https://t.co/1cKwaHkiWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my wife skjeik to join me for the first night of #threadx @ Kona Kai Resort Hotel &amp; Marina https://t.co/aiVQ9j4ieB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wedding time for some fantastic friends! @ Ray’s at Killer Creek https://t.co/UDx34Hi0jJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trendchasernews Whatever happened to the dentist who blackmailed Michael Jackson?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eeeh...what? Does he not remember the punches? Can someone please show him a replay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m literally freezing at work right now IN CALIFORNIA!!!! Imma snuggle under all my covers tonight imma sweat]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @Coach_Hopkins Zone: If do right, no can defense. https://t.co/ggyNhBcmn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come help us educate and inform people and policy makers on how government decisions or indecision impacts northern… https://t.co/U5QRgXEOl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recién me entero que el @ClubPueblaMX cambio al Ojitos Meza por Chelis. No tengo nada contra el buen Chelis pero por favor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@middyraddy @wutevr4evr_ @rfpcrawford @goobisgoofy @sabouring1 @Jimmyv221 @mayrabella101 @AnnCoulter https://t.co/oJOCBbH74b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul HOW CAN YOU ASK FOR OUR SUPPORT WHEN YOU DONT SUPPORT OUR PRESIDENT?? BUILD THE WALL!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SluggoDoug Isn’t this what you have to clean up in the Temple of the Dog? #TitleChop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daniel_T_1985 Check out Doug Lewis’s video! #TikTok &gt;   https://t.co/wnOZmjkrK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the #Steelers decided not to trade AB and he retires , would the they still eat the 21 million in dead cap space?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeachVonT @yaoiluvr @CarnivoreCrypto @hargrump @Veganella_ @jadeo09 @GodZo0 @SBakerMD @Dave06031956 @skinny_keto… https://t.co/PO6j5SXCBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_iglesiass Oh ok. I have a beach pass, but I still pick up my trash sometimes ♻️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thefloridarose @Ranal55 @FinlayDave @DamianHempstead @getsprograming @anozierich @Siwgth @madlycool @michelanna… https://t.co/7CJxYtLF31]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venga dinoslfa a ganar #olamorada💜 en Estadio Olimpico Saltillo https://t.co/li7ChlCyki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh all that trailer did was make me want to see Jon ride a dragon even more]]></document></documents></author>