<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Mysmileydog There is nothing in the world as great as a dog for therapy and loves...I miss getting mine..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido TOTALMENTE DE ACUERDO VENEZOLANO NO DEJES LA CALLE🙏🏻🇻🇪🙏🏻🇺🇸🙏🏻bd RECUERDA MADURO NO ES NADIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom and I were going to leave for an east coast road trip and fly to Boston the day after I graduate... but we just… https://t.co/xEZtVPbC9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SummerSelenite Imma BISEXUAL activist (grins)  Also I spent a short time working as a digital assets manager at a… https://t.co/Be75wZBoB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarimmerman @UTKSIS Thank you for joining #UTSMW19. You did a great job! We continue to be so proud of you in @UTADPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great pickup of @CGasparino on a possible Biden presidential bid! https://t.co/UWpb5z54Ut]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am not #shambhala.  I do not like their policy on drug use.  I do not do drugs except for medicinal purposes, ie… https://t.co/fYJn5PJGE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my fucking God everything about this movie. No noms? Wrong. Major league wrong I say kiss my ass mister oscar th… https://t.co/Urt4raIvwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garysonnabend4 @GoBowlingdotcom @FS1 @PBATour I give away autographed photos on my Facebook page, you should follo… https://t.co/RgIANcgO7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope we don’t run today because my legs feel like literal flat chicken wing bones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Complete the form below for your chance to win $2,500! The winner will be announced on Monday, March 25, 2019. https://t.co/usq62QbwXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happydoggies 🐶🐕🐾 #dogpark fun #maxine #maddie #mia #dogsofinstagram @ Spring Valley, Nevada https://t.co/wK6CtnyMkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreeeBird1978 I also got invited to a unlimited pancake dinner tonight, so I;m really happy happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalvaCambranes Wow didnt know that? Guess the reunion got pretty heated]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ez4u2say_Janis @WalshFreedom @Barkforlove1 I heard one mention about Lavrov being in Russia (Maddie maybe ?) durin… https://t.co/wUWF8H1bJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Strange Matter Coffee Co. in Lansing, MI https://t.co/O0wjIKlvs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[BTCS Elementary Robotics Teams Rockin’ some robots at the VexIQ TN State Tournament.  @VondaBeavers]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; I am soooo happy I’m off tomorrow!!!!! Cause I real life can’t stand Monday’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was our moment of celebration for being able to name all the letters of the alphabet w/o Miss Megan’s help 😎… https://t.co/Cv63ZkoJIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Running water in the cave. We didnt get to explore inside.  #2019SchnurenciaAdeventures @ Indian Cove Campground, J… https://t.co/U0xzvKLzpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @CillizzaCNN @ForecasterEnten #Schultz will be the one who does it for our sweet POTUS to have 4  more years!🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart These Republicans never do the homework that is required before blabbing their "facts" and opinions! T… https://t.co/MulSKAXLuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We the people see all the players and motives behind this corrupt, treacherous, hypocrital committee!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d @Abis25669315 This whole thing with North Korea is just an overpriced photo opp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Des Moines is a Top 10 State Capital to Live in, according to WalletHub. For all of my out-of-state friends, now is… https://t.co/K8ZqkFE5Wo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieSymes414 Try Kimes Ranch! I have the lola’s and absolutely loveeeeee mine!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SenGianaris I’m ashamed to have you representing my neighborhood. I don’t think you get economics and how the Ama… https://t.co/FH16QduWdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jannarden Yes - and @Burrowsdrums gets an A++ in #YQG for how he supports musicians and non-profits and charities.… https://t.co/PkBFcTmKSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learn to deal with the valleys,the hills will take care of themselves.#borrowed 💜💜💜 @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/RPY3vpRefC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbell17 @thewomenofcoun @AshleyMcBryde If I had more than 10, I was adding Shaun Cassidy, Andy Gibb, Jim Croce, Ph… https://t.co/1RRgVK2C5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett You can’t blame our president for what he did! He is kind of hypocrisy… https://t.co/CeDQA8Fd09]]></document><document><![CDATA[A magical moment at Traffic and Conversion Summit #dj #events #eventprofs https://t.co/hks4BIWvg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARONFOX WAY TO GO BRAD MY DRIVER DIDNT WIN BUT THATS OK  LOVE THE WAY YOU REPRESENT WITH THE AMERICAN FLAG OOO RAH SEMPER FI 💪☝️👊🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do so many shows have to have a musical episode? Please don’t sing the entire episode]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so DEAD. Sophie got baby bean it’s first pair of vans!!!!!! I AM SCREAMING we love aunt soph @Sophie_McCall_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind I am amazed at how this judge doesn't see this sentence as a racial, elitist, #WhitePrivilege moment.… https://t.co/DBArRygKmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sammantix @YTWFXX Yeah but why wasn’t that pillow fort from season 2 an option......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life will always try to make things difficult for you, but every time you overcome obstacles, you come out stronger.🙏🏽💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[“To reach your goals, you have to be able to articulate them and the value you bring to the table, then share those… https://t.co/E0C6pUAQxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, If it aint broke... or should we say, "wenn es nicht kaputt ist, repariere es... https://t.co/cDLph6nMG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: frat boy has said that he originally messaged me to join him and his girl for a night💀😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just found my dream job with @tartecosmetics but it’s in NYC and not Chicago. 😭😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of all my years of being apart of @NevadaThespians I still can’t sew a button.  With that being said don’t tell… https://t.co/xxYZYOkJvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Receiving a login code via SMS and email isn't secure. Here's what to use instead  https://t.co/0frpD99iPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T__E__S__L__A I didnt want to believe it..still dont, but I do! Now I just dont feel like we are moving at high sp… https://t.co/c8fDOanLLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl in my class took my seat but I can’t even be mad bc she brought her yorkie :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luckily, we were through in 2 hours &amp; it was definitely worth the wait!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsrox 🙄 sigh... I knew it! My question is but WHY would he do this to himself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well you’ve lost your constituents by going along with the non emergency!]]></document><document><![CDATA[im a firm believer of “everything happens for a reason” good or bad. cause honestly nothing is worth getting out of… https://t.co/toqjiS5uTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Halfdeadghoul I will allow it only because you have some DC experience on ya resume lmaoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovEvers And I’m sorry, I forgot to mention the obvious.  This beautiful AMERICAN grandmother is dead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soon as he seen the other dude so was talking to he come come hugging me 🤦🏽‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@margenotmaggie @abc13houston Oh how did I miss this part of the story. What was the purpose if you don’t donate th… https://t.co/MmMD0hoXuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamcarolla I’m sitting at a sports bar in Baltimore with a total of 2 other guys at the bar.  Katy Perry, followe… https://t.co/8ycnD3oRfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey all- Anyone with an active dog on the #southcoast want to have an energy filled walk with their pooch, please j… https://t.co/XWVK0mi0Ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist I think it is the Republicans who are unhappy with Trump who we will need to convince to vote Democrat… https://t.co/80EOkOVGPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Professional #REALTOR®  working in #SilverSpring🏠 #MontgomeryCounty #DMV #WednesdayWisdom🤔 #WomensDay 🌺 Your… https://t.co/4g88RpqVgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure if I should be #TheCatInTheHat this year for the millionth time... Or should I try another character. I have material. 💁‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @CarolsakelCosta Hey there, Don. It’s Sunday morning. Shouldn’t you be in church?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say this with 100% seriousness: forks are a terrible tool for consuming salad and hands are THE WAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not all sunshine &amp; rainbows, but a good amount of it actually is. 🙅‍♀️👐🏻🌞 @ Statesboro, Georgia https://t.co/mDyi6mUzfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[dudes will go from “i love you” to really not giving a single fuck ab you and that blows my mind. teach me your ways. lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TonyTEEE Yea but I love deep conversations you not going to “wyd” me all day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once again on a southbound Amtrak. This time heading to @AmerUrological for a Data Committee meeting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love when ppl put me in their ‘close friends’ stories lol i feel honored]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Trump was asked what was his favorite Bible scripture was and his answer was “That is way to personal… https://t.co/9BnvrzaQMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theejamieson Lack of hotels around our arena*** lol we have plenty downtown which is less than a mile 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is going on, I know you don't need that kind of attention here but we have been waiting long enough. We were v… https://t.co/tbr1bMmirH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobbeeeRob @MrRob_Educator @itsBTerrell @TeyaSophia @Malinda_Hodges The lady in black is my mom 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Nintendo eShop Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Bel… https://t.co/QxMh4DtmhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuning into #oscars aka the Ally &amp; Jackson Maine concert https://t.co/Xil4tx2Cgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheV_Quadrant Why dont you go and fight against terrorists who are inside INDIA? Dont deny the facts. Worlds known… https://t.co/ZgEvgWEJfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[You won’t see/read this in the corporate news. Take this excellent economics crash course from Prof. Michael Hudson… https://t.co/05LB8ygw9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@user47 @VikingCruises @masterpiecepbs @VictoriaSeries River cruising is a LOT different from ocean cruising - diff… https://t.co/SkjAbp94kQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When ppl ask why I’m so dramatic, idc maybe cuz I watched this growing up lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPaigeWWE Just finished watching #FightingWithMyFamily and it was one of the best movies I've seen in a long time. Biggest fan !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today our AIMS dabke troupe had their debut performance @heightscrawfish festival! @hisdaims @Mahassen_B @sarinakeller @QFIntl @HISDChoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's personal. This exhibition is great. Not to be missed. A message from 747 Seminars taking off daily from… https://t.co/XYALOrPfzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have your @jonasbrothers every hour this am @963WDVD ⚡️⚡️⚡️⚡️ #Sucker 6am, 7am, 8am, 9am 💣 https://t.co/oX8UQ6DvKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[💔💔💔Feburary (February) on YouTube now let’s run it up!!!!!! 👩🏽‍🦱: dajahreshae._ 🎥: @westleysnipes19 💔: @........🧔🏽🖲… https://t.co/BCXGOpUNVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so excited about #CUE19 I've already started packing up snacks to keep me going as I plan on attending every se… https://t.co/QvbZ51o26V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to put you in a coma like I did to my bitch ass cousin. I’m so done]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mauriciodubon10 Dude!!!! What did you have?! The Flu or gastritis? Or appendicitis? Get well! We need you! 💙💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[4/6 Demonic- they are ambassadors for Satan and are the forerunners to the Antichrist. They often preach in the Nam… https://t.co/7ewaKMym3k]]></document><document><![CDATA['My wife needs a liver': Husband in search of donor for sick wife https://t.co/M460DOPR5s https://t.co/L3Ikrjz4iE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is because of friends in high places period, @therealroseanne created the flipping show, unbelievable.  He almos… https://t.co/9yNQVaC5wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I managed a whopping 20,000 steps exploring Chattanooga today! @ Chattanooga, Tennessee https://t.co/pCfwv6aJYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[is my quizlet freezing a sign i should go to bed or do i keep studyingggg??]]></document><document><![CDATA[BE BOLD! BE BRAVE! #gameday #firstthingsfirst  #ultimatefootballexperience  #mycoachstacy @ Tempe, Arizona https://t.co/0bYz3Cu5Vl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 8:30 am on a Saturday and I’ve had a full conversation with my employee. BG is ready to play. I can’t stop smi… https://t.co/NUQ49B2Vvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chantal89058922 @ChrisT0_0pher @TBLightning @86Kucherov Oh it’s really funny! 😂🤣.  Get those tissues yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[windmill windmill          🤚      😣/     _/||     _/¯  ¯\_  for the land 👋     \ 😩        || \_    _/¯  ¯\_  turn f… https://t.co/oiDysm6o2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many of y’all are actually able to still follow your ex’s or old partners on social media without any problems??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pechanga security sprinted over because they thought something was wrong with me but i was just dancing LMAOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌸⭐️ #quotesoftheday #quotestoliveby #deepthoughts https://t.co/PqgubOjd2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelLeForestier Moreover, psychology is asking fascinating questions! Unless you believe that the mind is unobserv… https://t.co/VdYxIUxllK]]></document><document><![CDATA[travelling increases movement. A 3 day weekend all the more. #fitfriday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1007TheTiger @LukeBryanOnline loving it ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ thanks for playing ❤️❤️ What Makes You Country ❤️😍💙❤️😍💙❤️😍💙❤️😍💙 https://t.co/SgIObbqNb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsadDaDrummer @LewisBlum @AxTheBevTax @ZionBaptPhilly @mediamancomm @PhillyDailyNews @phillygaynews… https://t.co/oDhIxnfBPP]]></document></documents></author>