<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:37.6°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yvonnewingett @Dlstoke @SenMcSallyAZ Hardly a spoiler. McTrumpy has never taken a stance on anything.… https://t.co/4jxePNlnOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doozerblake Oh wow. I thought they all pretty much had the same menus. Been going to Mi Hacienda lately but I’ll h… https://t.co/n4XDpzQALk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/UIMocZXo3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soy de esos que no se va hasta que no se rompe todo y me sacan en pedacitos.  #picoftheday #ootd #mexico en Saltill… https://t.co/xIKN7OCSpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t care if you take 9 hrs to text me back i’ll text back right away cause i’m a little bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me surran esos gays que son los únicos que... No joto no eres único ni eres especial. Si tu mamá te lo dijo no cuenta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gah damn between Cartel beat and Kt rapping, I’m still stuck on the first song. This hoe too hard 😭❗️❗️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a Blessed Sunday.    .  #faith #blessedbeyondmeasure #teambefitt #sundayfunday #smile #blessed #blessedmama… https://t.co/yRUdWjnFol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blairzach10 I’m gonna have to disagree with that there last sentence young man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dave_christison Had to check if it was April 1st.  This question is a joke lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:25.5°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[DCeased Comic Pits #Zombies Against the DC Roster https://t.co/I0FZEvTtuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaclark1313 @Kellie_Lynn2013 BUT watch Infinity War first. It helps make sense of stuff. https://t.co/E8h8EEns5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nike @nikestore @nikebasketball is there a way to keep the lights on the adapt bb continually? If not will there b… https://t.co/YlQBAAyhnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tim_Barreto I think the “Green New Deal” needs some work, but this guy saying MTA is excellent is either a sign of… https://t.co/8Dbum8SMrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bikesalsa I tend to prefer the Atlantic side as a general rule but Tampa has always been great when I’ve been here… https://t.co/p14lBqtX0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Name something slower than the MBTA after it snows in Boston. I’ll wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RPPNoticias y @canalN_ en vez de invitar como opinólogo a Altuve deberían preguntarle como es que no ‘habían irreg… https://t.co/xf4Jah2r11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you lord for another day of life for myself, my family, and my friends! I love y’all! 💪🏾🙏🏾❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally back from a quick trip to Gainesville. Just in time for playoffs, baby.  I'll be covering No. 4 Woodsville… https://t.co/lQxDNVl8f6]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@instagram if I get 10 retweets will you permanently ban the caption of “Missing ______ a little extra today”.   I… https://t.co/QIUWkClCoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity I'm outraged about White Supremacist Nationalist @realDonaldTrump supporter #ChristopherPaulHasson  wh… https://t.co/dtHamRbCAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm literally debating the dumbest dude ever and about to be late for a date lmao what am I doing with my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very courageous and forward-looking plan to increase #housing affordability in Minneapolis. I had a chance to mee… https://t.co/s9uAEDvTcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winestainedlens @Awk043 @TheRickWilson You're right. He didn't eulogize Strom Thurmond, like say, Joe Biden, who is a Democrat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@szantz @Timmy2x_ @MikeBlock611 Heat? You’re like a little twitter gnat. Wah wah knicks wah jets wah wah hot takes wah 😢😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn’t matter if the spelling is a letter off...  It’d be a swing and a miss if we don’t get #Speghetti trending a… https://t.co/xLX5XU5uTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEGraves dude you got a big issue. Don’t get me wrong Carmella is an attractive woman but you have a family why r… https://t.co/M0mTGxSDXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always receive a lot of questions asking if VR will further distance us from society, and the more time I spend i… https://t.co/YmlzhgmKDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Burnet Lady Dawgs are headed to the Girl's State Basketball Tournament for the 1st time.  A team loaded with ta… https://t.co/VlhKJwLxcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Escucha AFTER - Leonel Balleza de Leonel Balleza #np en #SoundCloud https://t.co/k3jvrfiEV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Marching Music Day!!!! #march4 #highschool #drumcorps @fox43 @DCI @DCACorps @USMCDRUMCORPS https://t.co/9RZEvjOL0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacOnTheMic All the negative Murray talk may be true, but don't act like you actually have been in the room with h… https://t.co/txcfU0PRUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[See what happens when you lose faith? You crumble. #stlblues #JesusSavesOReillyScoresInOverTime https://t.co/FWjMzwkr6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danlevene The board in their wisdom (sic) chose to send ChelseaFC on the SarriBall road. With the ban for the next… https://t.co/kryWGZyu94]]></document><document><![CDATA[1920’s paper used as insulation in the walls of the former #stagecoach stop building and market in Stuyvesant, soon… https://t.co/t00qIuUYy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyBoyInTN Okay.  I just spit water all over my phone. https://t.co/XvwR0Hv8wK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how we started #ValentinesDay at the Rahlmann household! #KrispyKreme #love #family #doughnuts @ Be Our Gue… https://t.co/HTseqzm5DN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@habermetrics If Kuhnhackl/Ladd/Martin/ is healthy Ho-sang can’t play unless he plays instead of Dal Colle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen, @rickbrewer... We agree humanities can provide a well-rounded education and support so called #SoftSkills.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBar59856057 @SGirardau Yes. You will allow the voters of Minnesota to send their representatives. And you will… https://t.co/oizr5UnArv]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you miss your Cali peeps... but you don’t miss SVPGMHCBM. @kellyp7 @vegasjeff @jennantonia #tbd https://t.co/6OMS1FjXpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Fe por rata”. Nunca dije que @ENZOSCARANO es candidato a gobernador #carabobo. Cometí un error al escribir y obvié… https://t.co/7pAb2TyaKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJRAnderson @BrocNessMonster I thought about getting my first share of Vlad or adding another Rendon but stuck to the script.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my talents is laughing while actually panicking about what the fuck someone just said to me.  #HappeningNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That's murder! What has our country come to when we protect illegal children and kill our own? Tho… https://t.co/xV1Ge38rwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should be training future coders like skilled trades. Skilled trades people are trained by people doing the work in the field.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_littlemissJ__ @SexytotheNorth Always first. If for no other reason than someone else can't have it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmozymoz Yea, I guess he’s a good dude. He did kill his ex, though. I mean, I get it. She was sleeping with his da… https://t.co/bcm1tCIv9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandro211 @Mr_Boffin @The1stBAT @CBNostalgia @MikeSchmidt09 @mrjafri @delvin_cox @GeekVibesNation @GeekToMeRadio… https://t.co/KL89FHLKa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp You disgust me. You’re nothing but a deplorable Trump apologist. You’re fine with a bastard who rigged an… https://t.co/dqLuKmJ8hD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NonesuchRecords @EmmylouSongbird @RhiannonGiddens @wyntonmarsalis @jazzdotorg @KenBurns @PBS I am so looking fed t… https://t.co/4atSyGuTce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash Get real, stupid question, you know they do, stop asking start forcing them to stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebM32 @brennan_bloom @JohnHillbery Lol nah G. It don’t matter how bad dray is. They got KD AND Boogie]]></document><document><![CDATA[No fucking washer no hot water no gas no food I’m moving back into mommas fuck this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanWrightRNG @headdogpound @BrandonHuffman @KTPrepElite @coachnatesmith @GregBiggins @adamgorney @HamiltonESPN… https://t.co/y6jEsq9FAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love listening to @phoebe_bridgers b/c it’s like she’s trying to make the absolute saddest music possible and ya… https://t.co/HVGdvExX5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amariedauwer @EricTopol It is! One week off a year! 😁😂🤣 #hcldr post #HIMSS19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allsweaty OMG..... I'll trade you my youngest son for it??? Congrats!  I am sooooo jealous!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[By my count, Conway had six road games longer than JI’s longest one (not accounting for excessive traffic, as I’m n… https://t.co/vriRC5Jbsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I shaved my mullet and posted a picture on Sunday. Since then; 2 graduate schools have contacted me taking me of… https://t.co/oM7j08fvmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The libertarian fantasies of cryptocurrencies https://t.co/UPXm7rEpEA @martinwolf_ | Kinda prefer large rocks myself.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeccaIsAweirdo I wear a pink thong over my tight jeans all the time on the #nycsubway #mta #newyorkcity #1train… https://t.co/97Z0eQ5oZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[1610-1650 E Elizabeth St 1610-1650 E Elizabeth St, Pasadena, CA 91104 https://t.co/UytiPSL9Xt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confession: sometimes I have more fun creating &amp; curating Spotify playlists than I do actually listening to them. 😬🤷🏻‍♂️ #spotify]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garyvee @problogger @kevinlee @neilpatel #WilliamShatner/ aka "Jim", his cast + crew and that of the #StarTrek "Ne… https://t.co/pUs7WMZqzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Design #3 has been in the window drawing people in for weeks, and finally a gorgeous lady is taking It home! ♥️… https://t.co/nQoWBs27f2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guy at bully’s bought dinner for me, Ryan and my dad. thank you good sir you are appreciated 🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJQuinnESPN Based on the video, Kraft’s release significantly quicker than Tom Brady’s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCompWiz @QuilterAmerican @savtheusa @JudicialWatch What’s it like to live in total denial]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🚨🚨 PUBLIC SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENT!!! ATTENTION EVERYBODY!!! 🚨🚨🚨 This Friday... IT'S GOING DOWN!!! In Greenville, Sout… https://t.co/EyaOl7NLE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck the world news they tll it all wrong anyhow so i ecsssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssscccccccccccccccccccccccccccccc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeLoweReports @WGNNews @Skilling @WGNMorningNews Pink sky at night sailors delight, pink sky in the morning sail… https://t.co/GoWoCjEQ1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShankyMcWidleft @savageedits15 Pretty solid. Expect to see Demario McCall mainly at RB as opposed to H-back. Dobbi… https://t.co/1lR7KmODU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sucklingpig and #fishmaw w vegetables. #chinesefood tonite at Grand Harbor in #Burlingame near SFO tonite w ocean… https://t.co/JXZXqXhPoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay! I’m with her. And her. And her. And her. And her. And her. And her....]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the dividing line between "this person's playlist sure has a lot of Van Halen in it” and “I’m definitely in a machine shop rn"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My future children will grow up with diseases that were eradicated in the 1900s because of you essential oil humping moms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen Holy shit you’re like Tobias 😂😂😂 https://t.co/c4hau8103t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump We have to begin calling him "bubble boy"! He's living in his own "bubble" of made up "… https://t.co/aDn189ydso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lakers are sorry af bruh it’s getting so irritating at this point man...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muy de argentino mediocre festejador de subcampeonatos criticar al Real Madrid porque Messi juega en el Barsa. Como… https://t.co/k9EveqIMnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Kid’s new obsession is The Lion King and I asked him if he could say “Hakuna Matata” and he just says “Matata”… https://t.co/UK43AltOXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to welcome @lilliamichelle to the Cairn Guides team! Lillia will expand our hiking services to the Denver/Gol… https://t.co/FrvFhz82PE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jarrymanna bruh the more I listen to Gleam the more I grind 💯🔥🤟🏾 sheesh there’s no words that can comprehend how f… https://t.co/SAqdiwym9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jammer_Volts But if we’ve been practicing our greater summoning spells, should we still try and see what we get?]]></document><document><![CDATA[No offense SmackDown Nah all offense to SmackDown but @BeckyLynchWWE looks better on Raw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this great deal I found on Beat the Dealer. https://t.co/9yh8tf9DO0 https://t.co/X9mNJqCNil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keelinjack @rosebeefe I'd be happier if folks would stop with the apocalyptic predictions and, like, do something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timbhealey It’s all about the $$$ not fielding the best team possible. Same old @Mets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well been here an hour already 🤷🏻‍♂️ when times get busy. You gotta push a little harder and a little earlier. Star… https://t.co/c1dVzvkeU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[En mi corazón dueño tus ojos yo quisiera probar el dulce sabor de tus labios rojos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dave &amp; Buster's is hiring in #Cary, NC! Read about our latest #SupplyChain job opening via the link in our bio: Receiver]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some Sundays are better than others #rogue #callaway #theharderiworktheluckieriget #titleist #indianwells… https://t.co/EHwTW6czjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dancing and fake fighting in the mirror right now.....  Don’t fucking judge me! https://t.co/5a9Tq1XMlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComicsintheGA @JackPosobiec Perhaps intimating that Stan was concerned with quality and integrity above all else might be...a little naive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekMcPhee @Texas_Eric1 He stated this during the “fisa” release conversations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning Anthem and coffee!!  Can't wait til The Division 2 comes out!!! https://t.co/JwBaBeGswj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travhaney @NashvilleSC One man’s skid marks is another man’s Meowth coin https://t.co/zcjaIPYLTm]]></document></documents></author>