<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Celebrando la nueva posición de Alfonso Terrazas @Soonerzo como Director Internacional de Ventas Para… https://t.co/I7XaH17ok7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of #worrying about our lack of #privacy and #data being stolen and used against us; we should make complexi… https://t.co/1qxq8N1FKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little mood for Kate’s senior session. Wish we still had that borrowed couch. #seniorportrait #portraitphotography https://t.co/3z4nHquOrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClayTravis There was a cornhusker qb a while back that moved to safety in order to play in NFL. Terrible post on your part]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super hot thong over my tight jeans #1train #newyorkcity #7train #3train @VSPINK @7FAM @TheShops_ColCir… https://t.co/3bwm3Hdpwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Night America:😴 time to recover it's been a long 5 days have a blessed night @ Texas Holy Smokers Bbq https://t.co/1UORyZDHZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait for the price to drop on Play Plus DX Pack so I can finally pick one up https://t.co/Jc8hov1loS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheMcCarthyFiles coming up at 12:15pm ET with @LaughlinSXM @mike_p_johnson and myself on @SiriusXMNHL   Among the… https://t.co/bTQqTTH98E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mariazelzel Zel , te ves preciosa espectacular y súper sexy en Tribuna te amo 😍😘😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hamdogg are you still in Atlanta? How much is an uber to Ft. Lauderdale?]]></document><document><![CDATA[*billie Jean comes on  Gavin: what band is this again? Me: ...Michael Jackson? Gavin: ...... Me: .......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THV11 His parents should be ashamed of themselves! I guess they take him to the klan meetings too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MFollowill Do you think JJ has been mentoring JB? I really see awesome similarities in their play and vision.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s still time to register for a great race next month! We’re proud to be a sponsor of Ella’s Race on March 16!… https://t.co/5qZGLxW1lA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A true warrior stands his people“ . PC- @skipiozor  Best photoog definitely check out his work  Contacts- honeycol… https://t.co/wOLI5h9M7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to smile today? Just find a .@Coach_Leach video clip and you will!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briebriejoy 1.  Statistics show that Blacks are being disproportionately targeted for police stops in Castile's ar… https://t.co/dZjxWekj3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro I fear that too crowded a field plays right into Trump's tiny hands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@elayna__c @twitter.com/Sailing_LaVaga needs this #ShortyAwards!! And I voted to help bring home the W! https://t.co/RiMeMAM8qP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emphasis on: we still have a ways to go.  Thanks to the women in this video (and many others in and outside of the… https://t.co/ZpnLkTeNgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nayibbukele déjaselos Nayib que gocen su momento por que el pueblo se las cobrara con creces]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Natalie__Currie The only barrier really is the limit to your creativity. So many implications for coding in the classroom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eeshtaferr @chuuzus I know it’s like “just don’t pay attention to it” but every time I see some shit pop up I can’… https://t.co/85NP2OOT2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perhaps my favorite loci to teach in the classroom as a systematic theologian are Trinity, Atonement, and Grace. Am… https://t.co/e3v7CYPA7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DEADLINE @TheAcademy because it was about the awards and less about the dumb monologues and dumb bits they normall… https://t.co/SbaIcLPJJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylviaJonesMPP @ChiefBordeleau Sgt Leanne Smith, her supervisor, Sgt Constantine his supervisor have refused to in… https://t.co/HeZxLD49Td]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photo collage. @mipic_app pic.motivation  #photo #photography #photographer #graphics #graphicdesigner… https://t.co/aX93I2BlP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewScheer Stop your lying, you know that the issue is far more complicated than the simplistic view shown here! #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minnesota Meatheads Never Cease To Amaze Me.  As I Am On The 3B @MetroTransitMN Bus Headed To @CityMinneapolis Down… https://t.co/NV2oVqmw5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deppykats @Butterflies7779 @Caramelicedtea @Indigostarr777 @TheEllenShow @Oprah @OWNTV Well, he’s been dead for 10… https://t.co/zDY7xGvYti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyC1926 You’re welcome @AshleyC1926  just being honest every time I see you I’m like wow I love to meet her]]></document><document><![CDATA[First ever state wrestling team title for the alma mater. Congrats guys!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDavenport_NFL Adam Humphries 10-14 million?!?!? https://t.co/DiG4aeRvbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I come back from this loss in my trading account... I will give everyone $0.10 each]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todo cerrado en #WashingtonDC ☃️ Extrañando una playita 🏖🇨🇷 https://t.co/n0dwAXxunE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielhuntgrad1 50% of your followers liked this tweet. That's impressive and if the trend continues you'll be a K… https://t.co/ncp2jHu0R1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Music Label Spotlight February 26, 2019  Celebrating 15 Years Of Cosmicleaf Records  Side Liner… https://t.co/MfvqpjBUbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of yall dont know the difference between ‘Okay’, ‘Ok’, and ‘K’ and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBC @guardian @nytimes @postpolitics @SenWarren @BernieSanders @PBS @ABC @NPR @maddow @latimes @USATODAY @WSJ… https://t.co/ArlX0Eierg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@batmanpopfigure got us tickets to see @VHSNYC this eve. Twas a Christmas present. Got to meet them and now, lookin… https://t.co/8FWfgNhkcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then maybe throw in some Zora Neale Hurston for a more modern (and female) take]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nephilim_Girl Thank you! And you're right, it is exhausting. Worthwhile if it means even one reader connects to it… https://t.co/TKqp7QlS0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StPaulResident I just put it all back in the street, further down so the plow takes it the next time they come around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonLaCanfora Thank god would be a shame to see him in Buffalo . He would look as a Lion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The day I lose a race to a taquache that has a dropped truck is the day I’m selling my car]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaythaAlhassen @jadapsmith @jordynwoods Only you can take tabloid trash like this and make it into a worthwhile le… https://t.co/XlJus7EjSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life's greatest lessons are most often learned during the lowest periods of our lives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeattleFaithful As I explained to my Uber driver in Vegas last night when the topic of Seahawks came up: they love… https://t.co/IrE7my2S1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diannaeanderson I think the organization is supposed to be universal, speaking all languages. But it is odd the on… https://t.co/W2fPE1EBZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hsrayat  Hi Harmel, great to connect...looking forward to your tweets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! I just realized #CWLForthWorth is just a couple weeks away! It’s gonna be good to see everyone again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Piano Guys (at @PeaceCenter For The Performing Arts for The Piano Guys in Greenville, SC) https://t.co/ylzRgsUkwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twin Cities will reach the most snow in any month, by this weekend! Looks like this year, it’s nothing or everythin… https://t.co/psBXwqedf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steven_A_Gerace @AndrewSolender @realDonaldTrump Jesus...this is your idea of doing great? 40% approval ain’t great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best thing about eating two bagels a day?? Feeling like I can drink myself into oblivion knowing ALL THAT BREADS DOWN THERE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielTurnerPTF @RyanAFournier It's because she knows she will be embarrassed. She just want to say she put some legislation forward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PowerTaking @letters4trump45 @GenFlynn @DonnaWR8 @DonaldJTrumpJr @dbongino @AngeleStar11 @cindy_nurse @j_ankrom… https://t.co/lU9yLCp8vY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraBoman @APinv Trust me, if I could I would but #AgencyLife keeps getting in the way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your New Jersey Luxury Employees coming back from vacation? https://t.co/YGtbxLFBBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DodgerFoodie @suejo825 @nerdyDodger Pre-season Sue Jo steak party at Taylor’s! https://t.co/eWRZ14cyvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone seen Icetray?  Playing like asstray!  @FastEddieFear @Awesemo_Com]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yes I said @MaryseMizanin is an icon check the resume The original longest reigning divas Champ The 3rd most su… https://t.co/OFSOndkBo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[See that smug look on my face? That's me having the last laugh internally at everyone who picks on the #EcoBoost… https://t.co/rwsQysUZkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meeegmason @kaiteasley @ash_lain16 Nonono. It is. Just some inside jokes going around is all]]></document><document><![CDATA[A casa dia que passa e fica mais perto eu fico mais triste. Não sei lidar]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a lot of free agents still left... kinda surprised Jose Iglesias hasn’t been in the news at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estimado @liebano acabo de leer tu artículo "Evaluar, ratificar y rectificar" y me pareció estupendo.  Lectura prog… https://t.co/svU9RdJerW]]></document><document><![CDATA[How the criminally underrated Arky Vaughn looks in the Pyramid Rating System. https://t.co/XGZR1Ckbnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[District basketball tournaments (@ Gerald R. Ford Fieldhouse - GRCC in Grand Rapids, MI) https://t.co/S3A8FYQf3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shemale434 I love beautiful cock big big big big big big big big big big big big big big big big cock I love]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Honey_B69 @AnnaAnn_imlive @GreatAssBigTits @iStan69 @TheDirtyRichard @EroticTemptress @sexx_freak @jopower666… https://t.co/xwpHB75EJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students at Culbertson Elementary programming "Rad the Robot" with movement and music. https://t.co/39WefWwwYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAstate911 “A hard job! God bless him for his service! It is a stressful job that takes it’s toll!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me crazy but somehow I don't see it as a "smart reply" to wish someone a happy Easter more than a month in adv… https://t.co/HR0Y1H9les]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennaPHL17 @phl17 Drove through that at 5am. At least 7 cars wrecked. Overpass was frozen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have lost a hero I have lost a friend  But for you darling I’d do it all again  #newyork #StVincent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to watch the NWAC tournament tomorrow. Tournament time always brings out the best in everyone. #FutureDawgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last evening in Tempe. @ Tempe Mission Palms Hotel and Conference Center https://t.co/QJao4UGsVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost Fake news has messed up lots of people, he is honored in Israel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jazzlove1995 @cindy_wilk22 I would of tuned in for a episode or two as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANK YOU @katkinson702 @Nicole4Nevada @Senatorspearman  @MelanieScheible @YvannaCancela @DallasHarrisNV… https://t.co/z0fLhhRWpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that's MY President! @realDonaldTrump #MAGA #Trump2020 @VP #prolife  BOOM: Trump Just Wiped Planned Parenthood… https://t.co/PjAUdOFs3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying The Long and Winding Road de Yusuf @YusufCatStevens #PaulMcCartney https://t.co/2mvdphy7CQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Prayers for you my friend.  I hope you get back in saddle soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: @browardsheriff has just cleared the scene, now getting a better look at the home that caught fire. House s… https://t.co/IMT000kSbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianWCollins Christian loves the song! It’s just one of the hosts that was being a jerk about it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@powertoimpeach I expect it'll show up on @wikileaks if the Republicans try to block it.  #hobomessiah  Enjoy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hunter2baseball @sam_vinograd @realDonaldTrump You better research it and get rid of that cognitive dissonance. It… https://t.co/C0YjLyG0nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to trip about Shone’s fucking up but I be fucking Up so I’m straight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austin! A cidade mais incrível do evento mais plural, instigante, diferente e ousado que existe. em 301 Congress Ave https://t.co/RYhvKpg0hJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Colton_Stock I know the towel boy at the Oscars and he said it looked pretty real from the sidelines]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing family I haven’t seen in YEARS is making me feel super grateful for this opportunity ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haworthia Attenuata Concolor, Haworthia Fasciata, Haworthia Reinwardtii Zebrina succulents + heat pack included in… https://t.co/6fPS9OZGUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are protein bar wrappers made of the noisiest substance known to man?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @THEMiaIsabella @DominoPresley @Britney_Amber @TweetRSummers @angelina_wild @tsjessy @xJonelleBrooksx… https://t.co/x6DZiEgwnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pelé: "Messi sólo chuta con una pierna, sólo tiene una habilidad"   Leo 👑 #10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InesArrimadas PERO QUE NO A LOS JUDIOS NOS MARCABAN CON ESTRELLAS AMARILLAS Y ACIAN DESFILES CON ANTORCHAS? QUE EN… https://t.co/n8ciLce1IW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men cannot be women. Women cannot be men. “Misgendering” is not a crime and is not real. It just hurts your feelings. Get over it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Please stop. We are not as stupid as you have proven yourself to be. you are being accused, along with your BF… https://t.co/cIDBN0mUd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows #How does Meadows keep a job . He’s a Communist. You will never decide what happens to my body or a… https://t.co/cl3SpuWVhB]]></document></documents></author>