<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump u should checkout @wearethe22 See what this awesome nonprofit is doing to prevent #VeteranSuicide etc. in Arkansas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch @TomFitton No shit!  What can We the People do to put some fire under those asses??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samstein So CW says this will be problematic for Senate Dems? Only if they don't support it. Are there any Dem str… https://t.co/9UpAUvflAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Policia_HMO @HermosilloGob Calzada de los Ángeles y calle Dr. José Miró Abella, por Las Quintas. Alrededor de la 1… https://t.co/pUf8DTOLyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Seattle Seahawks player Anthony 'TJ' Cunningham killed in parking dispute with neighbor, police say.… https://t.co/72mF0LWBYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[No mimosas were harmed during the enjoyment of this brunch with my friends @Realitychekkb inga_1gfz #mimosa #brunch… https://t.co/zo9wIH5nTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So is a lobster bratwurst a bratwurst stuffed with lobster, or lobster meat made into a bratwurst?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #demonhouse, and  the first commercial for for Chick-fil-a. Um, irony much? @GhostAdventures]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyallyPetite Meghan and Harry could have a girl. Meghan and Harry could, they really could]]></document><document><![CDATA[The air fryer is so great for warming up food! Mmmmmmm @ Partment https://t.co/srUe0JmHrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ridick44743357 Voy a platicarles los chismes horrendos que han inventado de mi; hombres, principalmente.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We support you sal, you do what you want. Haters gon' hate no matter what.]]></document><document><![CDATA[today was also opening night for our show in Palm Springs. #damp #forever #goodnight]]></document><document><![CDATA[ if you are winning, no one cares. His comments regarding sex scandals in athletics seem to apply everywhere. Peo… https://t.co/CVP1r4qkPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anxiety started when they had us popcorn read aloud so you never knew who was next]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this for her! Definitely well-deserved she’s been great for Vegas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrassrootsSpeak He’s turned into such a liar and despicable human being! Better follow his Russian money! Probably… https://t.co/RL0PkIYbfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to go to bed but I can’t stop watching @QueenSugarOWN. Season 3 is 🔥.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZooWildlife @j2tyco @FOX10Phoenix Sooo glad to hear nothing will happen to the animal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man is saving western civilization  He loves his country with all of his heart, fighting hourly to save it fro… https://t.co/n0gbB6QLkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man who owns the tattoo shop next door complained for months about our patients being too loud. I am currently unab… https://t.co/DjBNGr5hVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbagump324 I had a coworker once who told me that he could use the n-word because his girlfriend's son was half… https://t.co/yB4hHrqhHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a great presentation.  Thank you for sharing and visiting with our students.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ADXC9IsDZT “Butterflies” by Christina Perri tells You My Immortal  Truth. Nobody fights for Us, for Me… https://t.co/z5F768lcqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can thank AOC for the loss of Amazon.  New York thanks her, read the billboards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaarreaza @NicolasMaduro Me cago en tu madre maldito hijo de puta malnacido]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bed at 10, up before 6am...I'm so tired.   He is so excited for more wrestling. https://t.co/hM1vl0MrfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nopallixx Nah I’m good. A little rattled but I’m good. No one was hurt. I’m gonna borrow my mom’s van and take the… https://t.co/67OaDYqkkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelindaYoe @debratankersle1 @Peeperpea29 @Jimmysimmonds1 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @FRISEEMYRIAM @MyEngland2016 @Iluvinspireu… https://t.co/4uZPbvnDYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna go &amp; go everywhere, which means I have to start staying longer at work.....😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hope ashton irwin had a wonderful day today and is surround by nothing but love and happiness 💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends The analysis from the peeeepeeeee tape came back.....you got the clap... https://t.co/nAHoFOH6n1]]></document><document><![CDATA[G R O W T H . There’s a reason why the people have their eye on Tampa. . #Repost @watersttampa with get_repost ・・・… https://t.co/XAkbBp9bXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do guys pull their socks up over their sweatpants?? it’s NOT a look]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maruthf @DominguezHills Thanks @maruthf I was so happy to share this news with you in the hallway :) I was like no… https://t.co/O7PefabTrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The common theme running through the student panel is caring! Teachers, they do notice when you care!  #CougarLC @pfisd @msedillo22]]></document><document><![CDATA[The idea was that to the degree that we have knowledge of the divine, we must have changed our own character from h… https://t.co/iflxcb4ZU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“you weak ass hoe it’s been like 36 hours” how long did i really expect to conceal how soft i am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snap Sale NOW! Click the link in my bio OR dm me for direct sale options! 🔞💦 you don’t wanna miss my #FuckVdaySale… https://t.co/pE199GX2C4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Katherine and Principal Valdez take time on this Fun Friday to celebrate Read Across America Day and Dr. Seuss birt… https://t.co/vJDRsZhCyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveableLines Thanks for “hearting” my pitch❤️. Your Agency’s award list is remarkable, congrats! Unless u say oth… https://t.co/4o8YoUbSxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenTedCruz please advise our president. He does not have to comply with Nadlers bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[While that is true, she should’ve ended things with Roy. He kind of sucked anyway, but once she started having feel… https://t.co/DHokwU8SnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Navyw1fe @robreiner He’s a lying fascist con man. If you are not afraid of what the president is doing, then you a… https://t.co/H0NumowgwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton #VoicePremiere just enjoy watching you and Adam goofy around]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_lydthesquidd hasnt texted me back for legit hours. ATX what have you done to her 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[So last night mimi told me she was feeling herself like girl 🙄😂 she get on my nerves lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddShe72716015 @SpencerBoyd @jimbobsgrizzly @LVMotorSpeedway Your welcome Dutch!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starbucks tea stays boiling hot for like an hour y’all.... in related news, I burned off my tastebuds 🤷🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/DcArOLLXN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pac12Network @SunDevilHoops Thanks @dequonlake and @1KingZ4 ! BUT, keep it rolling through the rest of the season! 💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[ever since i started listening to 5sos about five or six years ago is when i started to pay attention to the drums… https://t.co/ypXKtVimAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here are the results from mayoral survey on racial equity @cueChicago https://t.co/C4ayRVT7LO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scaramucci @AOC Awe and you Guys Loved her So MUCH !! You Just Got Bitched Slapped !! Suck it up !! That's Sociali… https://t.co/MShO2Ytb10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idkvinyl @toxic_webber @PointNorthBand @chelsea_hutzler @Kaitliinxx Hey there! So much joy in this post because I… https://t.co/IoIlEcnYH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know when you work out and your legs feel like jelly after? Well the driver side door of my car froze shut whil… https://t.co/oJ8eAprPVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zakqwy No plans as of yet. Holography would be fun, but jeez, the last thing I need is another hobby that includes a bunch of equipment]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WomensHistoryMonth #FemaleComposersOfColor #NoraHolt #LenaDouglas  Nora Holt has a bit of an exciting story. She w… https://t.co/6zpqtrpZzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmallcageGG @psiangelic @HandyRed @MistyYo72777051 @MichelleNorby1 @sue_childress7 @SueChildress5 @deedawson66… https://t.co/kGsR2ZbdYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleRLyons How about those Tech softball players too? 24-1 so far!!🥎❤️😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so here’s the thing we have a climate change denier in office and as the original song states in the Year 3000 w… https://t.co/HQba9mTnK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraRose220 means . . . a great education, love, joy, friendship, great teachers, learning, memories, laughter… https://t.co/3FQWcaThXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @markfromhalsey I believe him, not sure former FBI director would lie on national television with major net… https://t.co/X7lnpIeOBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok but Adam Schiff pretending he has friends - let alone republican friends - is making me laugh.  https://t.co/eCDEJ5i81N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess I’ll start wearing concealer again so people will stop asking if I’m feeling okay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jali_Cat @beaglebabe48 @Ilhan @IlhanMN @SpeakerPelosi @senatemajldr @GOPLeader Wish Washington reused coffee cups, not the landfill kind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How am I getting sick but asked about ice cream and I’ll always say yes 🍦 #icecreamaddict]]></document><document><![CDATA[When stories of child birth are shared... they elicit this reaction https://t.co/wC6a5zKx79]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growth doesn’t always have to be on a physical level💭  My absolute favorite thing to see as an online coach are the… https://t.co/3opNNPEZgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChauncyRutabega @Bharper3407 Because he wants to be a dodger and apparently is a dodger according to @MLBINSIDER_ it’s a done deal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders You believe in abortions, lies, selling out your supporters, when everything is free WHO pays you ar… https://t.co/SmOQ7PnopL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McguireScotty @tillinghastpat1 @BreitbartNews He wants his rights? What rights? He's ILLEGAL!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFreeze @ABC7NY  Its Mook's 3rd birthday today! 3/10/19. https://t.co/cJUxuK5Ur6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko Anyone surprised by this??? I'm not. Not one bit. This is evangelicals' guy. I wouldn't be surpris… https://t.co/6Cnoa9AyA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Depauper8ion Only NERDS go to school. I'mma be a cool kid and stand out back just outside of school property and s… https://t.co/ccL0aHOOwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mujer en el camino de la nieve. #centralpark #ny #love #lovewhatyoudo @ Central Park https://t.co/MnSM4UTGVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know your company has brilliant marketing strategies when this is the signage one sees when departing the train… https://t.co/0olZ9fHVRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to take a group photo of the cleanup crew after last night's event like 🤪  I can't describe the amount of gr… https://t.co/eYFRHfRldo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsBravin It's true. People confuse dowry for bride price. Even saw Betty Kyallo doing that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my favorite days in elementary school were “Reading Day” where we could come to school in pjs, bring pillow… https://t.co/cUeEjohUZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sauk banned the use of cellphones during instructional periods this year and while kids still find a way around it,… https://t.co/pcXHyKlPQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. So so proud of y’all for coming together to make an impact! I love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ho-nestly can’t wait to tell you...There are some I’m just SOOOOOOOOOO eXXXcited about!!!!!! 🤠📬👏👏👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I miss being home, but then again I lowkey hate McCurtain County!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMoochers @cspanwj @RodStryker THE DEFICIT IS NOT DUE TO SPENDING BY THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION. NOT ONE BIT. IT ID… https://t.co/aNJi1H6zLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh...YOU GUYS!!! If you missed this production, you missed a great show!! Hats off to the cast, crew and everyone i… https://t.co/6Ljk7MYc9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost freaked out I thought I misplaced my ring. Then I remembered I put it in my robe pocket so it wouldn’t get… https://t.co/Ch4ReOVsya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell yeah I want the sun, moon, &amp; stars. Why? because it’s what I deserve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lpav02 Oh I believe this is only just started. This decision will be argued for a long time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love all my babies so much..... #CleoMarie💞 #LadyDiane💜 #JacobOliver💚 ##NalaMufasa🧡 #OscarBoy #CrazyDamnCat… https://t.co/RH35iypNYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_HamptonU alumni out supporting  fellow Pirates @TasiaGrant and @Skeeshea at the Columbia screening of… https://t.co/9Cj0GqrEXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IWeatherON Hamilton Catholic school board posted no buses but schools will be open]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OlessaStepanova Not sure if everyone catches some of the things you say or do...but you crack me up every day 😆😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY MOM ✦ WE LOVE YOU @ Backwoods Crossing https://t.co/pfPYALf3JI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abc13houston I understand totally why you would be upset. My opinion is there is no greater gift than to donate yo… https://t.co/yHIE6fPvHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cartoonsbyhil I once said if I got married I’d serve chicken nuggets and I still stand by this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brbird @WCTH_TV @hallmarkchannel @SCHeartHome #Hearties @hallmarkchannel , Amen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tfitchlove Lmao I know which one you’re talking about😂 he’s not that bad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working and laughing to another great literature marvel (that includes pooping convo) by @AlyssaMastro44]]></document><document><![CDATA[New day, new city. Hello Dallas! Celebrating Sandow Birk, Elyse Pignolet, Paul Mullowney, and Harry Schneider at th… https://t.co/WHX2O3E2Kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GatorCosplay @_makeshiftwings Rounded carpet needle and a stiff toothbrush works great!]]></document></documents></author>