<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@acoyne As we've heard, until the verdict was in the DPA was a viable option so what was he interfering with when h… https://t.co/N14EacpqlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillLastra Your boy Menzies is always trying for 3 when he only needs 1 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great day in NCAAB. NC State still perfect, Clemson looking to take two from UNC, FSU 1st loss but then bou… https://t.co/h0jv0AedNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know Charles Bronson, Lee Marvin, and John Wayne used to be considered sex symbols?  Yikes. Did people also… https://t.co/7W6u28aoVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The awesome love shown thru our Lord and Saviors gift of everlasting life thru the blood of Jesus Christ is infinit… https://t.co/JD9du3f3aa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@braddewhat It was a human like form but I couldn’t make out exactly who or what it was. Jarring, but it was that c… https://t.co/coGO9Ru40Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ftbragg Joshua is moving in.. yes, slut her to Cheney's air force crews girl.  I don't know why but people always… https://t.co/uE9CUltRyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna have @RealKindMeds421 on Deck for all this weekends wrestling live streams and VOD so should be some high times]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @DonaldJTrumpJr Numb nuts, Obama cut Black unemployment by 7%, Trump cut it by 2%]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are 3 kinds of drivers in Fresno.  1. Me  2.During the day have no clue what the’re doing drivers   3. Come o… https://t.co/g5R4jjjsrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarryFromCBus you guys face the winner of tomorrow's centennial/bexley game]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defending #Farrakhan! Live from Saviours Day 2019. “I am satisfied and honored to have the privilege to be a Studen… https://t.co/YrB62D45T2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is new music Friday are you going to be a part of that? @Tinashe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesGHudson2 @Lrihendry What you call an oversimplification is the Democratic Socialism Bernie Sanders and others… https://t.co/TP2HQfPQyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose This is bull shit Dearborn is a joke Muslim Muslim fu .k Muslim keep pushing and someone going to die]]></document><document><![CDATA[@molly_knight @darth by a landslide, it’s @9Artemi’s Riziy (mr_riziy on IG)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shboot @NomadicNative @REZ_woman Oh no 😂. Stop making fun of Tuba. I'm from there too!! 🙊😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PullYoHoe hit up my boy mario fire w the cuts 🙅🏻‍♂️ 🧢 https://t.co/aTXDEMVBJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without many chances left to improve their NET rating, Rhoades keeps preaching “get better after a win, get better after a loss”. @VCU_Hoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar An honest assessment of the situation, Yashar, would have had people fretting three weeks ago that Individu… https://t.co/nUpNJm36e0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seafood Pairing! heidijeank @sanfordwinery @terlatomedia @rae_322 @LettuceJobs @lettuceeats shawscrabhouse #wine… https://t.co/VmEOoKOq9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfElMohtar @ut_caee @GeoInstitute Our recruiting day, too. Good luck!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Black &amp; Blue Hill by @southerngrist @ West Lake Tap Room — https://t.co/jQLPof6w9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Why is it without looking at the TV, that the voices questioning Cohen attacking him and trying to protect… https://t.co/rkYel33ElF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KXAN_News Lawless officers can only exist where there is no effective supervision. Chief Acevedo is going to addre… https://t.co/obZoFvP8hp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alfranken Please come back! Maybe as independent because the Democrats hung you out for slaughter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[iPhone Snowmotion #detroit #iphonexsmax #iphoneslowmo @billmcdad @freep shinola tigers @ Detroit, Michigan https://t.co/GorEg13Dyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @TheDemocrats how much longer are you going to keep silent on this biotch's anti-Semitism? You need to strip he… https://t.co/cHz9chgsMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez responds after report accuses her of 'Green New Deal' hypocrisy: 'I also fly &amp; use A/C'  https://t.co/Q2zfQjiijA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcindychu I worked in Food Service during college, always ti 20%+  If you gave great service, that's what matter… https://t.co/bbDMHxRKO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[people try to compare running miles to boxing lmao i don’t care how good someone is at running it’s different in a… https://t.co/IUCkHgjWtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find interesting properties on our website ! 🏘️ Visit https://t.co/bqzmXRUQeW and get back to us with your feedback… https://t.co/iFdPiDlfdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows @DineshDSouza Except it wasn’t the Dems theory.  It was the US Dept Of Justice led by Trump appointees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don’t see color” is a dumb statement. It’s ok to recognize someone doesn’t look like you. But to not associate t… https://t.co/XoPquSIWhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being in Chicago with the lack of snow with milder temperatures got me excited to ride my bike again.  Then, I land… https://t.co/BJEp92hGX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this day in history, 03/11/19. In 1708, Anne, Queen of England, Scotland and Ireland (pictured), withholds Royal… https://t.co/FaiqSGTsVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowledge is a function of perseverance.  Wisdom is an understanding of life.    Yep, in the mood for dispensing so… https://t.co/HDHB7rbisH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warhorse.  Ride w us today at AER Road Atlanta!  In-car live stream, link in my IG bio https://t.co/qC6OgMxfqd  8AM… https://t.co/CsPgRFthrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así fue el aseguramiento de una persona que amenazaba con lanzarse de un puente en #Ensenada Mx #México ,trayendo c… https://t.co/omnnv1heQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OkSoMikki We bought two for the kitchen and one for the front door but goodness it’s like 4 rows and they have the… https://t.co/MDR2jDCJFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Squat is out of the way.  3 for 3 and lifted with confidence.  1st: 90kg/198 2nd: 95kg/209lb 3rd: 97.5kg/214.5lb (T… https://t.co/uOgnMcqSpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[How anyone doesn't understand the importance of Hyman on this team is crazy #LeafsForever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DSports24 @tcraigschilling I thought Ronnie was doing that tomorrow.  Is he on the PA tonight?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertliefeld I tend to agree, though I'd add Marv Wolfman to the list…  artists and characters really]]></document><document><![CDATA[And your attitude is exactly what's going to get Trump re-elected. Please stop the nonsense. I am a moderate Democr… https://t.co/sXXDfsEExe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The song is good but the fact that they’re all singing high pitch and not using real instruments 😪💔 it’s gonna soun… https://t.co/TeQHCBDzaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ford You still support Tucker Carlson!?!?! You approve of his obvious bigotry, racism, misogyny and now his approv… https://t.co/M4Ij3kbyA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for coming to the special event at Reign of Terror Haunted House tonight. See you in October #BestHaunt https://t.co/qyK2BYm5Ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mco_xxviii @MsJayLee22 @jdstalnaked @judyohtweets @lauralaxla @of_ramblings @MrsTyler78 @lovethat4you… https://t.co/ny8uEpqfJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blancagarzap Buenos días Blanca, que tengas un excelente jueves. Saludos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What even are “Illini?” Are they the plural of “Illinois,” and if so how can they possibly fight?]]></document><document><![CDATA[First run of the year without gloves! I see a possible shorts run this week! #Runner #RunChat #LessLaundry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmfb Good Morning Football from Roanoke Virginia @nateburleson @heykayadams @PSchrags @KyleBrandt @MattHamilton25 #GMFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐺v🌲Another Sunday done right 🏀 @ Maples Pavilion https://t.co/i6aRm7N3bh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkYuhnke @MeaganFOX31 @KenClarkTV @SamBoik @chrisparente @DutraWeather @DrewEngelbart I love the “JibJab” App. W… https://t.co/83UMfa4N4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @lucianocadenza takes over the terrace this Saturday you’re going to feel like @miamimusicweek has started ear… https://t.co/wjC2tVJ82b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Edwards Aliso Viejo 20 &amp; IMAX - @regalmovies for Captain Marvel in Aliso Viejo, CA https://t.co/T7G6G8c2PA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first @reba Promo shot circa 1994! #fbf #StongerThanTheTruth https://t.co/QPtcUYMSPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TKhatesyou On a secondary level, I'm upset about how bad white dudes are at photoshop. You'd think we'd be better, but naw.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kidgolferman @RL9631 @AnnThacker2 @mymynags @SweetKat111 @MarshaPatriot @Joanne1776 @JanetTxBlessed… https://t.co/7yORG1ckay]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not saying that the almost 25 million that they freed up is to go on a run after @LeVeonBell buuuuut...TheAlmos… https://t.co/NFB50PwYbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phil_vee @stevendschmitt @universalhub @BostonBTD @wutrain @CityOfBoston @BOS311 Your beloved parking spaces will… https://t.co/0Y0neq79FB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And now as I'm running out of rounds As I'm falling to the ground Can you hear the sound Cuz I need you now  I don… https://t.co/UTXT3EOkiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[每年都会接到不少辉瑞药厂请来的中国医学专家在费城开会，如果论外科“手艺”，中国医生比较熟练，这个可能，因为是拿多少病人练出来的…[擦汗][擦汗] 但是说治疗癌症的技术没有中国先进，这个呵呵了……不知道谁在进口谁的霸标药物?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sylviaduckworth @AlishaZ143 @SteveSilbert @mospillman @Rob_Dimeo @Cbustamante2222 @lgonzalezteach @mcoutts81… https://t.co/7EMv7SpbUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simkinsjourno What is it, a single shot rifle? Stop milking the trigger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GIGABYTEUSA so who do I need to talk to about getting my motherboard repaired or replaced? I sent it out to your R… https://t.co/wo0GmQ0wM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of people are "clueless" enough to not even know that women were ever involved in software and hardware from the very early days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mikey and Nicky (1976): Great performances and a fantastic script.  #film]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike6miller @arkellsmusic They’ll write you a doctors note for work the next day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch If they know of these improperly registered aliens, some possibly illegal aliens, why haven't they i… https://t.co/4hYNkEjUoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to see my Mighty Delta Eagles making the Regionals in @IHSAA1 basketball.  I'll be cheering you guys on.  G… https://t.co/dgh3ePBfEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m of a similar opinion about bringing some fun discovery back. My worry is that the alternative to loot metering… https://t.co/WO9gToJiDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is the blonde behind Cohen making faces rolling her eyes and shaking her head?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should be a financial analyst. I can gauge market confidence based on if casual acquaintances who are clearly doi… https://t.co/UwrIf7tZso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Libro 📚: Una Vida Sin Obstáculos  Autor: Erick Torres Disponible ya 😊😃💯👍🏻🇺🇸🇵🇷🇩🇴🇨🇴🇲🇽… https://t.co/BVw0aeADMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Saber” es importante, pero el “hacer” es un plus, tomen nota porque su Hiram yo soy...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shell acquiring @sonnenCommunity. Oil and gas making a big push   https://t.co/gCZvg7VWeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are playing Remix to Ignition at the barbershop and I am like https://t.co/irrBTaa6Of]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Vexing @JMHanksHigh , find out who will be representing us at @VEXRobotics internationals, best of luck to all… https://t.co/pMYPMkRgy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftShewPolitic What I’ve read is that the focus is on him to see if he did indeed stage a hoax.  Not that it’s be… https://t.co/fnD8IKsW2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[You put me down when I bought my first new Cadillac and when I bought my second one last year. I lifted you up and… https://t.co/caeBUyNhs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobsansevere NEVER FORGET: Obama Declared THIRTEEN National Emergencies While He Was President, And MSM Looked Oth… https://t.co/BbXYCMyj7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett And all racist, ignorant whites have enabled the degenerate who followed Obama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSteelCrew Come on @WillieMcGinest football fact Good O-Lines make avg RBs look Good, a RB can’t stop in the bac… https://t.co/le3Cr1zupN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrafthouseSF I’m a deaf movie lover who thinks you’re the best theater in the city. I would worship you if you had… https://t.co/pd6VdD2sl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[..live from The City of Brotherly Love, the interactive Facebook platform will feature eight outstanding bouts, inc… https://t.co/Tyc1Rqlg9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt to @musichallofwb June 2012. My first time seeing @feofficial live. I took this pic of @phontigallo singing “T… https://t.co/6hrJW6qvoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalkerBragman She had her chance to support  those policies in 2016. She chose not to and play it safe. Sounds lik… https://t.co/xE1sC0EQfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con qué finalidad? Si vas contra un equipo amateur... Solo arriesgando a una lesión]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBTA_CR Thanks! Is there something wrong with the GPS on 586? It’s been off/broken a lot lately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndeeCurt That comes as standard equipment with the syndrome. What can I do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[New vlog, go check the link in my bio, please and thank you! #TuneInTuesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rock_andor_roll Best of luck. You did nothing to bring this on you.  Enjoy your 18-22 months the best you can.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Father, Ephemeral Son, swan feather, telescope: the semitones between us are rhapsodic lairs.  Life on Earth is fle… https://t.co/VbjKNhJ1XY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_T_008 Fellas, go follow @BingingWBabish learn how to cook and bake, your girlfriends will be forever grateful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was great to see @DRIPresident at the @IADClaw Midyear Meeting tonight and to talk about the exciting upcoming… https://t.co/LkPLADzOVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Kain1 I’d like to Meet U &amp; Ur FRIENDS!👍🏼😘#RodSteelOfficial @Daniel_Kain1 @aussietrbl @JuanLovesCock… https://t.co/kv0PTN1ukH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you struggle with hate, grudges and bitterness? Don’t miss tomorrow night  on “Overcoming Hate” God didn’t call… https://t.co/17UQJrehtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theashleydlc Keep your head up Ashley.  It always gets better before worse.]]></document></documents></author>