<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Mis amigas nomas me ilusionar y luego me dejan vestida y alborotada 😭qué feo? 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iheartraving What about the pants on y’all’s insta stories that look EXACTLY like little black diamond’s??]]></document><document><![CDATA[the killers opening with mr. brightside is like fall out boy opening with sugar we’re going down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailySignal @AbigailShrier Fundamentally unfair. As the mother of 2 female athletes, soccer players, it would most… https://t.co/RYUa43POVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJWSCOTT I like your vision. My drill Sgts let us watch black hawk down the night before graduation, so...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano To be fair, there are some REALLY dumb people out here. How else did we get in this mess?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had 2 anxiety attacks today and no one would answer the phone and i honestly felt like i was dying :( i hate living alone sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lacroixoficial it absolutely fucking is I Should have just watched the movies but I’m a dumbass bitch !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielhowell  The internet support group mug came in the mail today! It’s super snazzy and now I can bluff being a… https://t.co/yDDkaNWu7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[As soon as I walked outside today my eyes started watering and my nose stuffed up. #WinterIsHere my dudes https://t.co/gKiCreAph0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it!  #BoringOldTrump is going down in flames and this plane crash is gonna burn for a long, long time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior @Vbarnett323 I heard this was only round 1. There will be more names.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She said "my floor looks like hopscotch" I love that she even knows what that is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am outraged!  We should ALL be outraged and DEMAND the @SpeakerPelosi @HouseDemocrats @SenateDems DO SOMETHING so… https://t.co/oIzmzLO6UW]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my Valentine ♥ #ILoveMySister @ J Butler's Bar &amp; Grille Lewisville https://t.co/A91rpAYxpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @TedCruz has an idea on how to fund President @realDonaldTrump's proposed border wall... Make El Chapo pay… https://t.co/LjAD3l4y2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[19 Feb 356 Constantius II issues a decree closing all pagan temples. It was one of several anti-pagan religious ref… https://t.co/SbLErd5Kzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not exactly sure but I know when someone acts different but I’m just gunna mind my business]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so severely dehydrated today that I couldn’t eat or drink until like 7 pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLAssociopath I would argue that the importation of said horse was permanent, not temporary. Therefore this law do… https://t.co/lKWmCwiCYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #YasLizzo on @TyltEnt—Lizzo is an icon in the making https://t.co/acm0A68VLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[this will make you giggle. How To Cope If Your Candidate Lost The Election. All these silly animal photos can make.… https://t.co/KNt4q9jpcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be on @WOSUAllSides this morning at 10 a.m. to discuss #GC2019 and the decision United Methodists face over wh… https://t.co/KUX5XreO2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump, why not just stfu?  No one wants to hear your rants.  No one.  I know that the pressure of… https://t.co/2rNmKtzDTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonnyMoriarty @uclaVIR @pryce227 @SIRRFS @SIRspecialists Awesome! @womenirads]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s my birthday! 🎂 And here is my bday weekend schedule. Where will you be joining me? #birthdayweekend #djelizamay https://t.co/cNnZ5J0rdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like who in the fuck... opens a restaurant that’s so understaffed that the hours we were supposed to have for our s… https://t.co/MIJ7lbZ70t]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more I collect, the more I appreciate my mothers taste in antiques...loving the blues! . . . #antiques… https://t.co/5hibldJ2sI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solid advice from @MuseumHack on how to improve your @facebook! 👍https://t.co/qP8a0dpQgs #musesocial #marketing… https://t.co/50MvQzWPox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idobiradio I’m excited for Friday too. I be jamming to @wearetwinxl ep album before work and after work on that day]]></document><document><![CDATA[To top off how shit today already is, I went to take a shower and someone apparently doesn’t know how to flush to t… https://t.co/7fkH5PZvVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like as soon as you announce the pregnany the baby decides to pop out too. 😩 I’m not ready for this y’all but Mama bear has to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to make such big changes for my life and I know some of them are really gonna hurt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[EPIC INTEL DROP! Shadow Warriors &amp; Master Spooks How Trump's Praetorian ... https://t.co/GhuWhXJeW8 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we just fast forward to summer? I really don’t care about the warm weather. I just want this game 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[99.9% sure I unplugged my hair straightener before leaving my apartment this morning but WHAT IF I DIDN’T??! Also,… https://t.co/dr5Oz4Ewp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonmarkluckett @SenJeffMerkley Clearly you know very little about our beloved Senators!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s hilarious cause this bitch really thinks she’s right 😂😂 go ahead and believe whatever you want to sweetie. I’m… https://t.co/SfKFVv3WMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PenmanshipVids I love ya! #freehandart 😘🌟💚 #TaraAnnMoons https://t.co/8GFwk4B7Th]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I am going to say is that #JussieSmollett is a famous person. If authorities want hate crimes erased in order t… https://t.co/yjBCQv6DzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okkelci The lady was super chill so I wasn’t totally mortified! But yea... not ideal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I totally get it. When referring to Donald of Dipshit President, I often refer to Donald + Dipshit as Donald Dipshi… https://t.co/LuAB7OzNtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InjusticeN0More I hate animal cruelty I went vegan 6 years ago after seeing how the meat and dairy industry treat… https://t.co/fomcisxKv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening panel at #NADOHE19: It can’t be in the moments of trauma that you decide to show up and ask how to build trust with people of color]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words can not express how much I love cooking with my #princesshouse #vidasana #cookware !! 💗💗💗 Hands down one of t… https://t.co/IkOcyksDs2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't had a period since May and I've had it twice in the last month. I hate my uterus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SemaCiel0101 @Havenlust @AmandaRay02 @AForce01 @AnneScottlin sunshine on this Monday morning to All 🦋😎☕️🙋🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/MuHOXnHt5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s by Gods grace. all things through Christ Jesus. no weapon formed against me shall prosper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[kinda crazy how a famous celebrity can cheat on another famous celebrity and the gossip can distract everyone from… https://t.co/mFd2NaYPk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissKrys65 I skipped portions of that episode for obvious reasons. I’ll never watch 😫. The tumblr photosets were enough for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_Copperfield @Chloegosselin Happy Valentine's day to both of you and your team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate filipinos so much omfg was he supposed to b CLOTHED https://t.co/q1uSPv5o0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop this. Stop. This is becoming a joke because ego's need to be feed by certain politicans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow #OhMyDad When I was a teenager, Dad would answer the phone when boys would call saying Hello? Yes. Cl… https://t.co/rywa2uF4ZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico And since we know @PressSec lies pathologically, like her boss, whatever she says, the opposite is the truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secularcitizen2 THESE beings are NOT CHRISTIANS!!!! They a clearly demons from hell. That are masking THEMSELVES a… https://t.co/jxDJdREx4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell Congress, “It’s past time: end the federal prohibition of marijuana.” https://t.co/xHDUe3bhbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The money they have waisted on this crap they could have already paid to BUILD THAT WALL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think squirrels always go back to the same tree at night to sleep?]]></document><document><![CDATA[the 12th house, by its very nature, is hard to describe in words. i feel whenever i turn to verbal significations,… https://t.co/UwH6Xdev69]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a face for radio today!  1pm with johnfugelsang @siriusxm channel 121 1pm #style #fashion #influencer… https://t.co/d9fXDyNv79]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know about you guys but this just angers me... #lgbt #LGBTQoftwitter #TransIsBeautiful #MartinaNavratilova… https://t.co/3UuOzGGwvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kimbers05 I went to Books A Million to look for After and they didn't have it. Looks like I have to order online.… https://t.co/mwEKKXNv4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLE_Online Awesome! It would be so neat to build a pocket version using one of those tiny viewfinder CRTs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙💙 Rich Family Poor Family 2019 Part 1 – The Rich Priority  Matius 22: 37-39  A.Tuhan adalah PUSAT hidup kita.  Tuh… https://t.co/OxozUp9Jz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hodakotb This is brilliant. Thanks for sharing your kindness and joy with us. #happymonday 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SenGianaris introducing @SenWarren: “we are here in Queens tonight Bc we stood up to a giant corporation here.”… https://t.co/3StSNKFnMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice game sky_manek nice win ou_mbball - way to pull out a great second half!  bradymanek #35ismyfavoritesooner… https://t.co/f1TneoHL3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mhenderson33 His bathtub was sold several years ago. Saw it, just looked at it and thought okayyyyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a beauty! Sickening that his family would leave him.😰 https://t.co/MgBbAip1BQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rosh Chodesh Adar II Din din at the ‘New’ Mexikosher (@ Mexikosher in New York, NY w/ @bradnpx)… https://t.co/OjlqxRmX3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of saying: I don't have time, what if we said 'It's not my priority.'? What aren't you making your priori… https://t.co/CJCjAxbU8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morey2200 @CaptainLeman @JLSigman @Paul196510 @MuslimIQ Now that's a gentleman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The most important brand metric? How you make other people feel.” - @kaiwright #followthefeeling #favoritebrands… https://t.co/sDVrgLOlTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#enjoyinglife   #lovingtheweather    #goodfoodanddrinks @ Mambo Cafe https://t.co/kRz1L5H1BU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Double-clic si tu aimes voir ton Herbe? Mary Jane’s où tu peux sentir et voir ce que l’on a en boutique!… https://t.co/6r6TtbOiv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never thought I'd be clearing out drawers to make a dedicated drawer for WIRED controllers in 2019 lol. https://t.co/fBKulBWpqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any thought or mention of the lyrics to Carole King’s “It’s Too Late” and I’m weeping]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be an adult, they said.  ... I am trying, I said. https://t.co/ZDboJiFxx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[As BERNIE SANDERS talks about lower health insurance premiums and lower prices for pharmaceuticals, President Trump… https://t.co/G0xuVxoEln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saltandrockets I think it would have been too obvious if they foreshadowed it. Any menacing look or moment with hi… https://t.co/FO5fHOax5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GPBmadeit @DEADLINE So excited and happy for you and the success of this project! Congratulations! 🎉 🎉🎉🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FurburgerMayor And haven't you noticed it's getting thinner and thinner? He can only achieve a square "do" during… https://t.co/ZlAJZvCGea]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still confused as to why adults don’t get naptime every day like toddlers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren I agree with you. This is important. Please talk about healthcare, teacher pay and education, veteran care… https://t.co/iceSqvI90g]]></document><document><![CDATA[My full name will never ever fit in my Twitter handle and I have decided to never ever accept this and move on with… https://t.co/NTzLTp3IIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny how some people be hitting you up on their convenience and later say you should be lucky. Ummm nope nope bye bye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you date me, I’ll get you on time to everything and spoil tf out you. Just a heads up fellas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crossing my fingers for no Polen or Yogurt. Stay away from this ski resort you’ve interrupted enough 💁‍♀️#canem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M_Bipson @coeshmoe He was already divorced and spending summers in Mexico by the time we met him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesPPierce It’s unconstitutional to abuse or attempt to manipulate the constitution to usurp a duly elected pr… https://t.co/QZM6wuzhGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I say “I will have crawfish this week” over and over that will speak it into existence right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MassPLAN @MassSierraClub @KatyEiseman @craigaltemose @rsullivanWMEDC @MassGovernor @AlexBMorse FWIW, my take is we… https://t.co/eg9ji2sorp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it when dutch bro workers leave little notes on my lids. It makes my day 100% better ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to just be a student and not have to worry about also doing this completely on my own. The landlord/insuranc… https://t.co/WbF9BXLfj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Statesville, NC, check out this job: https://t.co/kR0H1PeD2O #Marketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever whisper product advertisements you’re scrolling for to your phone? Yeah, me either..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders @Bananas4Bernie There is No Room At The Quad.  I'm so excited that I'm shaking.  And getting on my c… https://t.co/RmBsMQSyip]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was really contemplating today and I really only have 2 real ass friends LMAO everyone else &amp; just acquaintances]]></document><document><![CDATA[The plastic ban has already been a boon to weavers known around the country as “mamas” who have seen increased sale… https://t.co/PVSVm7mmxC]]></document></documents></author>