<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’ve waited for these accounts to line up for years @smotus https://t.co/SunLVv2k1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silly individual mistakes at the back costing us goals again 🙄 #coys #thfc #nld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gbnf4life @Mimirocah1 Trump is stupid and criminal in plain sight. https://t.co/6u57TTxMct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spf8298 @tony_chapman76 No different that football playoffs in some the mileages teams are traveling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrickrazzi She didn’t know. When you know you know. Bill and Harvey didn’t abuse Oprah. Remember that people can… https://t.co/MZxhbP4uS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know its NEVER A DULL MOMENT when the #GetFreshCrew is in the HOUSE 16 X AWARD WINNING EDDIE KAYNE SHOW EVERY S… https://t.co/TfjuK2tUZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlancaCamachoNY @oc2gman @KamalaHarris @JussieSmollett Another pandering fool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting to think the 20 minutes of sleep I’ve been getting every night isn’t enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harryhstamper1 @hewitt449 @VP @WhiteHouse @POTUS my bad ! lol Thank you Dr.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas look at my pictures and think they finna get some girly girl on some soft shit like no I’m a whole lil boy out here 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newswithnatalie @boston25 It’s unbelievable how many lazy drivers don’t clear snow off their rear windows. Acciden… https://t.co/rX16uMCCQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sports Protocol podcast 5: Game Preview Michigan Wolverines men's basketball vs Penn State #wolverines #mgoblue… https://t.co/cZssEibvwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best sign of the night last night from the Wisconsin student section. https://t.co/6t0mw9Hv3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning #sunsetbeachnc @TaylorYakowenko @SarahLucyMurphy @MMoore_hoops https://t.co/s9OPIRAgqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobanMarjanovic Thanks for holding it down tonight. #HereTheyCome #bhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[If even 10% of what is being alleged is true, Jesus did we miss all the red flags #LeavingNeverland]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dannykanell Puh leaze.. Any team that wants to win would take him.... This is all about supporting each other as o… https://t.co/9tiAe8xcOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Williston Horse Country in Williston, FL https://t.co/vSlILcBjMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spadeaudry @rcallimachi @c_mcandrews The mightiest army can’t defeat an ideology. Bullets and bombs can’t eradicat… https://t.co/EYlG75G0Ki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronson828 @krispekitty @joan39455649 @MollyJongFast @mattgaetz Get fu**ing help you tRump cult loon !]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd intermission:  @SsuVikings 0 @NorwichCadets 3  🚨(NU) E. O’Neil 🚨(NU) A. Hulst (A. Rossini, KC Herne)  SOG: Vikings 7 Cadets 29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiteracyBatman @SimonBooks @Hypable @BookRiot @simonteen Thank you!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The latest @BSNNuggets on what was potentially the biggest win of the Michael Malone era, Denver’s inside track on… https://t.co/bs9Cd5Nlwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reic5Jacqueline @suarez1116 @kings_favchild @60Minutes https://t.co/cuAhVpBj7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[2. Alucard, de Castlevania y mención honorífica a Destin Faroda de la saga de Tactis Ogre.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que bailaaaaaa😊😃😊😃 @ Mojito Latin Cuisine &amp;BAR https://t.co/Eby4A81rRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Team_Onion @JeffGordonWeb 3 Forever but as much as I booed that 24 car in the 90’s that kid who’s not a kid anymor… https://t.co/9w7pPVx6Vn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexJettXXX That one I saw on your page with the nun looks like it'll be pretty damn hot, too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CranedoBaggins I know you're all about @KristySwansonXO and being timeless... but #jenniferconnelly is a smoke show in #AlitaBattleAngel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Airbnb should have aired a commercial right after Marriott's Bonvoy spot #priceless #AcademyAwards]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/iZFqCv2wXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lukewarm Christians I'm Begging You To Watch This https://t.co/hFZOtW4gsr via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alfre_acevedo @Cruz_Azul_FC @jesuscorona01 @EliasHdz08 @pablisaguilar @lacruzazul @orbelin90 @jona2118… https://t.co/xTivihpShV]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Time favorite player each sport  COPY...PASTE...EDIT...GO!!  NBA: Ray Allen NFL: @tae15adams  NCAAF:… https://t.co/yFTkaAmWsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWETheAlexander Alexander question about Bobby lashley the camp in wwe my sister super hero big dog wwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going to keep shouting from the rooftop that The Witcher series will be more famous than Game of Thrones (ASoIa… https://t.co/ooAEGkkVZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The person that shot Gabby Giffords didn't he have a psychological problem🚫 https://t.co/BTUrW7usfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio Amy, if you act like a few to many drinks in a bar,or like you would talk in The Army, I was in The Army… https://t.co/B939dwNebX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since that match was dedicated to his next kid, will the kid be as disappointed in @mikethemiz as Miz’s dad was in… https://t.co/bi3dq1fost]]></document><document><![CDATA[One hundred and forty-five days, I'm counting Tryna hold on but the time goes slowly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Platoon Berlin by URBAN ARTefakte, via Flickr #laughter #snicker #smile #absurd https://t.co/1QcqdsM4gc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexisgoldstein @AOC She's got guts...hopefully her ethics stay with her]]></document><document><![CDATA[9. GLaDOS: You can't go wrong with this smarmy AI. I still haven't got a piece of cake. https://t.co/zKnGfZvonf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really I'm just ready to go home. I'm ready to sleep. Idk why stars have to align against that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GSUniverse Watch the first 3 series of this list every Saturday night on @adultswim - https://t.co/N3KfqrOoRU https://t.co/4oKWnEN9zH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncampea @MovieMantz  Peter Farrelly pulls an ARGO and GREEN BOOK upsets ROMA for Best Picture!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ya, but you know when bitches toes hang over the front. That disgusts me.”   😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Note to @netflix ... our family just discovered @OneDayAtATime.  I grew up on the original and love this one even more. Keep it alive!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imAaronMoore @kaylersmith_ @Uwaine @CynthiaHennecke @RobertShelli @TCIIIESQ @michaelcard82 @PDeSant15 @Dantej21 Sh… https://t.co/SgnIeTuFCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Building relationships and improving culture is not always easy.  Try these 5 strategies for conflict resolution. https://t.co/779PiAVMjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the special services support team at @Delaware_SPS, chosen for the March #Powerof1SPS profile fo… https://t.co/n0xQkYMyIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@46Sports @freebymomof6 @RileyWildcatsBB @JalenJennings11 @YouTube Like it. Just saying these film breakfowns are the best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having had the good fortune to work with @GFennig I know he is the perfect person for this role, and is someone who… https://t.co/IUv06OsdK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone put the P juice over to the baby 🍼 👶 ( my screen shooter not wrk n now ... be grateful in the morning .… https://t.co/0eTq4g2cqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good To My Earhole, March 9, Part 1. #itwasagoodday #jamesbrandonlewis #hermetopascoal #artpepper #dave… https://t.co/BYanNLVchw]]></document><document><![CDATA[You say I am loved when I can’t feel a thing You say I am strong when I think I am weak You say I am held when I am… https://t.co/WWVlJ72uVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Part-time Psychology Instructor - https://t.co/bRA5UOTatz #NACADA #HESM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love @CapgeminiASE in action https://t.co/kDUQn4pckt @CapgeminiNA @Idean delivering #DesignThinking with @Nafirious… https://t.co/8mpNUj73Gu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are you not at @BarLuchador RIGHT MEOW, friends?!? Everything is 1/2 off until 10:00!  Also, next Monday looks… https://t.co/q7r0ho4gCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Is there anything in there about how to help Florida deal with seas rising from climate change? Project… https://t.co/BKAFbvUfTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have gone 3 for 3 on writes this week.  Can I get through all 5 days with songs I love? We’ll see....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SabresProspects It's also relative to who's doing the picking. Nylander at eight has the potential to be a big disaster.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chance05297385 @kstew4444 @CBSSportsCBB Let’s clean it up guys.  There’s kids on this website.]]></document><document><![CDATA[work   wərk/noun 1. activity involving mental or physical effort done in order to achieve a purpose or result.  VMI… https://t.co/OUHBCWBKuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[But he knows the way that I take; when he has tested me, I will come forth as gold. My feet have closely followed h… https://t.co/OHiQ4HyrQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warmups are underway between 1.@SuffHock (18-1-1) and 9.@brewtownpuck (8-11-1) @travjax71 @LoHudHockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s only two.  I’m really good at one.  With NO one having the ability to stop the first.  I’ll get those billi… https://t.co/y6fmjAhE0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFLonFOX @Ravens Offensive weapons aka @AB84 and @LeVeonBell #RavensFlock #FlockNation #Birdland #Baltimore #BMorePositive]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMO - the greatest skill that we can teach our kids, to optimize their odds of future sport success, is the skill o… https://t.co/4SYwZmYTo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerrythornton1 Get rid of the people that you don’t think that they’re going to get rid of, free up space, trade a… https://t.co/KqEXWd9sRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueBloods_CBS @CBSWatch It would be fun to watch "el familia" on vacation in the wood's! :-D ROFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickDriscoll10 @KEGsCards @thehill They absolutely do support Assad. It's pieces of shit like you that want to tur… https://t.co/n7PV7qZpQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope I never become lost in the sauce like Steve Harvey. Chase integrity before chasing the bag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @fams2gether @ACLU @CBP If they were not here illegally they wouldn’t be separated!! Oh yeah, you D… https://t.co/XhE3Q8109Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ll all think I’m mad, but one of my favourite things is driving around during a nice snowfall. ❄️ Pictured: My… https://t.co/dT03p78lhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[White Ghost Berliner  Weisse #whiteghostberlinerweisse 4.7% ABV This is a sour, but it’s not one of those sours tha… https://t.co/kLFU3FQIsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fabmar2018 Sorry fab. I'm a little older than u. U shld respect what I'm telling u as I've given u the proof. If u… https://t.co/OJU4FWzTaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unfortunately, you ALL have same core beliefs taught to you. It’s the behavior that is abhorrent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edwirthwein I was planning on Saturday but they moved game. Need to get you your bobble head]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brumblesmagee @Jordan_Kuehne Yeah they are pricy up front, but when you dont have to buy a new one for a decade, it more than evens out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new car being blessed by The Cornerstone Church/Pastor PJ. This was right after our church, particularly after o… https://t.co/CHILZYg3Tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los Djs también tenemos nuestro día y lo celebramos en casa 🐻🎧🔊🥁🔥 #DiaInternacionalDelDj #DanceRoom #Dj… https://t.co/pWi1zEAIx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He definitely changed the attitude in this dressing room — it was pretty bad and pretty negative,” said Vince Dunn… https://t.co/EBqJUM1T0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most liberating realization in advertising is that nobody really knows what they're doing. So you just go do what you think is right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Duke/Carolina day. Two fond memories growing up in the #BullCity. On this day, such a buzz in the air. Everyon… https://t.co/YkV8Gv3ThG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMagicDaily I hear you but the officiating not being great is a damn cop out,bit sucked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ret_paratrooper @TCBILLS_Astro I can tell you with all certainty that OBJ wasn’t in the same convo as Watkins/Evan… https://t.co/Ys1XqpIaTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@t_gidwani @RSAConference @JohnHultquist Will do! Thanks for the connection]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Might Regret Becoming President https://t.co/QBve6aPKZD via @YouTube. @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to @GunLakeCasino on the bus at 8:30 am.. Hope to win! But I will have fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReginaKing HUGE CONGRATULATIONS.. Can i say still hear Huey and Riley 🌹🌹❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for a much needed fun and positive afternoon! #speech #improv @ Okoboji High School https://t.co/o2zbTBMLMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricBoehlert It seems only common sense to me that at some point the Feds might get involved.  If a state is corru… https://t.co/5XVWBSyma6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevilleD35 Also I’ll say it does 175. People are fired up for it, lead woman etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The CEO @Tribus @ericstegemann is telling his story at the @ohiorealtors Broker Summit. Always awesome to see Eric… https://t.co/0vbSxP5CUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicRoccoXXX @BoysdoLukeOn @nickcapra @JonGaltXXX @BoysdoLukeUP @new_gaywanking @Novin_SafadoPR @Os_melhores1 @paupratodahora SPECTACULAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntonioAttolini en Colima y en todo el país .. chingos de asesinatos, robos, feminicidios .. de todo .. jajaja cua… https://t.co/tP7PzfLjGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Travellers meet more people... those experiences and serial relationships of intensity. are themselves a burden. -K… https://t.co/hllU129480]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HawleyMO how did that subpoena work out for you? Lol, loser! Just another white male giving the Republican Party a bad name! Sad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinnowWalsh @Medscape @theheartorg I really enjoyed the interview and your story.]]></document></documents></author>