<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[i’ll never understand, maybe a couple years ago but... now? nah, shit is for the birds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a twin sister @midniteblue71 and I think twins are inseparable no matter what the distance from state to sta… https://t.co/WqOvoOLivD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brrr.... My outdoor gym (tennis courts) started off quite chilly this morning. We swept the day... ANYWAY! Love my… https://t.co/9RGJ2U4sFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yvresse69 @Mary12976830 @loa717 @sylvainreynard @JDT19 @EffieKammenou @E_L_James @pamlangworthy @CawleyFranca… https://t.co/hrOjL4tELF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHeartRadio @markluckenbill  other side of me  ❤ @CMorneweckMusic halfway love 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence Trump's maturity is at the level of an amoeba's. https://t.co/uZJYky8NXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven't seen it yet, but you guys feel it!  Someone WAS messing with you, but not any living being on this earth!!… https://t.co/9TZdEjFnwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamjeramel Wala jud Jem. Pati abli sa bag pasulod sa mall nga murag unsay gipangita ni guard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on Lot 35 Stone Harbor Blvd #LenoirCity #TN  #realestate https://t.co/wfKoFTF32E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelindaYoe @MrShikharMisra @Jilliemary @karenslinn43 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Peeperpea29 @MyEngland2016 @FRISEEMYRIAM… https://t.co/Obm4XL5AZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MTA #LIRR Deborah Chin must own up to PTC debacle and our train safety failure. Why does she still have a job?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los leo. El mío fue este lit —&gt;😂 adjunto evidencia https://t.co/AZpXVxLHZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vickrdz17 Aguas Vicks te van a responder: "tu cállate la vicky"  jajajaj 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m concert addiction and my bank account are really battling to the death]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I love being from California. Why I’m in Texas rn n I see hella trucks w trump banners n this van just drove by… https://t.co/olbTKgXz6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pathryn34 No I think it's more emotional to hear that from Dean than his dad!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[May I ask you what in the hell is wrong with all of you people you see this and you can't even stop your car for a… https://t.co/M3FEfDZFLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart SINGS when I find common music interest. I have so many feelings and thoughts about the songs I obsess ove… https://t.co/hzIn3JQdYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Dana girl 😍😍😍 #chinesedwarfhamster #hamsterlove #loveanimals @ Durham, New York https://t.co/uKejsG1YJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to do my homework at a normal time so I can sleep early enough to go to the gym in the morning tf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caesar wrap with no chicken add humus from tropical smoothie ur fuckin welcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyAller @FJNunez7 @nerdlunch @TallyMacShack @CarrieQ82 @Stephen_Kubiak @laflynt @NoleNurse00 @SpinksThinks… https://t.co/sknSKjFTDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may have a few driver era tickets to give away for the Philly show!! Stay tuned ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiiNii_Rose You can order online if you’d like. https://t.co/4IRnWBVrP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So ly’in trump which statement is true, the one gave to the reporters or the one you are now givin… https://t.co/kpV2W6Wy1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a responsible adult with a steady paycheck and I own my own home.  I also exclusively purchase @starwars Band-Aids because wtf why not?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter era más cool cuando a todos les valía verga lo que escribieras, fuera ofensivo o no 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was weighed at the doctor and I’ve gained 10 pounds in the past 6 months 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[“i like to go night walkin, to see what this life’s about”   the man @yesjoefox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelUnderwater @JillLum1 @MoreRealLove @Mousefan98 @Odin_twt @GrantonGranton @sjreidhead @socr8ive @dogfishicu2… https://t.co/W0fz8iOFAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SluggoIsLit Nancy. I love you. It's so cool to know there is someone out there who understands me.   Never change. XOXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I was not prepared for rain” I say as I run back from the fitness center hiding my phone and ear buds, completely… https://t.co/okXgMoIGrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[And tbh too much Paris as well (with a dash of Kim) https://t.co/ki4oZaeOjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoAizen90 It's okay I knew it was going to happen but, you still are never really ready for it..... Her memory wil… https://t.co/xjYZEeV5Cg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNCastaldo @RyanAFournier Oh Heck no Twitter! Don’t share anything I write that has to do with God! Right!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am at the Mounted Patrol Barn getting ready to help introduce our two newest horses! The horses were purchased wi… https://t.co/pc78U6p67b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbuHafsahClare Salaam. Unintentional word play but a good one considering I am in health care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asthma More Common in Opioid-Dependent Patients https://t.co/FHSP0AL8up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eveewing Wait. You’re telling me the light on my phone isn’t a night light for when the overhead lights go off due to lack of motion?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton PLEASE don’t ever make my heart beat that fast again that was NERVE WRACKING. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debarian05 I do have the cantina music (Jabba Flow) and thanks for the info! Bye!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto @BrianKarem I always feel safer when he’s golfing. We know where he is, he’s relatively contained, and… https://t.co/sv6HOQGCjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swedish humor. #BorderWall @IKEA @IKEAUSA @verom1976 @atheenieweenie https://t.co/AhfVfzyEJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueBloods_CBS Another great 👍🏻 episode,emotional &amp; certainly well acted!!! 👏🏻 👏🏻 👏🏻 👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 year ago today was my last day at Forever 21. I’ve lived 2 lives since then 😅 Time flieeeessssss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama So awesome to see girls and players in wheelchairs also!  #inspirational]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickRockbeats 🚀  https://t.co/wtSCp3QhG9  #rickrockbeats #RickRockBeatsTheAlbum   #RocketTheAlbum #RickRock #dope… https://t.co/Ag8rUVPPsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTalkCBS YES I HAVE, TWICE!  I NO LONGER DEAL WITH HER. IT’S SAD, WE’VE BEEN FRIENDS FOR OVER 40 YEARS. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thinking you’re the person who needs looking into. They are comedians, you aren’t that’s for sure.… https://t.co/Ao6LUaD4Yg]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most well known families and they all act like sixteen year olds when it comes to men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you and special thanks to Ambassador Oris de Roa and Sofia Machado. We hope to see you @virginia_tech @vt_lci… https://t.co/1IvQJEvBsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black belt Putin shows off judo moves with Olympic athletes #BuzzVideo https://t.co/iEAW0qxPj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi @JunoWillEatYou You look like an idiot here. Lets just open that mouth in the shape of a butt hole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that everyone knows this bitch is crusty af 😂 ghonarreah ass bitch @JennaWillingham]]></document><document><![CDATA[just saw a guys twitter where the only tweets he has is replies to women calling them sluts/cunts/bitches and makin… https://t.co/cBivc5hn8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[alguien tiene una foto de los power peralta sin gorro ctm?!?! #GalaViña19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did I get a message from that stupid after school app last night? I thought we cancelled that in like 8th grade]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ArtsAdvocacy ⁦@TheRitaMoreno⁩ asks members of the House Interior Appropriations Subcommittee when can we double th… https://t.co/wdUsZc84Wv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students in the Jefferson MS Reading Enrichment and Arts Cohort for High-Achievers (REACH) program solved mysteries… https://t.co/rH0yzixfY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorriefencil @MaryJo44966098 @Heevenlee @kellylgordon @ErikaGlagowski @KathyM1214 @JustForFun16 @Darlene0528… https://t.co/ckxRf3kfsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home with sick Caleb. I don’t know exactly how many “The Land Before Time” movies there are...but I have a feeling… https://t.co/l4vGWuZOij]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only photo I took on my 22nd Birthday 💋 #NewProfilePic https://t.co/fezDifCyB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life of a PE coach: it’s 9:16 and ive been doing lesson plans since 7:30 this morning 🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[7. contributed to the bullying and harassment of a 12 year old with the actions they took today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Phillips1 @SpartanJessica Some years it’s March, some April, sometimes even May. I have a feeling this may be… https://t.co/8b8rQcsC7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I unfollowed one of Brian's coworkers wives on FB and I couldn't remember why, so I crept around. Then I remembered… https://t.co/vfmxWFG3ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer ...and this, immediately after signing a monstrous farm bill, giving his district another huge “social… https://t.co/NTzedFziBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my brother talking Brian: “Are smoothies healthy for you” Me: “They’re healthier than Milkshakes but Apple J… https://t.co/B91vGOoSqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got to see LeBron pass MJ to become the 4th all-time scoring leader tonight in person and I’m just so blessed to… https://t.co/iAelOBZ6DO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on Mothers Day gift guide! Please let me know if you want to work with me! #bloggers #PRrequest #bloggerswanted #BloggersRequired]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a friend that texts me just to leave me on read after I leave her on read]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need you to be 100 with me at all time and we’ll be happy forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to the newest episode of my podcast, Fundraising Secrets Show: Episode 44 7th Grade https://t.co/k1r3dfx9Tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KalpitValesh @bennyjohnson SAME PURPOSE!!!! A wall is only a higher and thicker fence, should be easy to grasp (ph… https://t.co/u6urOFdi6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know my 2nd video on YouTube is kinda long... 17 minutes 🤦(sorry!)  However, it is a bit more funny than the firs… https://t.co/hTYwSjXeae]]></document><document><![CDATA[and Kuwait trailing the Sultanate.  “The reason so many expats are leaving Oman is because the government realises… https://t.co/72gfrEPJF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im excited the house is empty. Lol its a half ass get dressed day for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it’s David Wright bobble head day at #firstdatafield you’d think it would be #DavidWright not an imposter wear… https://t.co/W3WsO35dFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandradibble @thatsdebadibble @ScottDibble @tomdibble @tylerdibble @woodward_dibble  Hi, this is me, Jamie. Do you… https://t.co/BNWZPtShS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know anyone looking to buy a condo in Oak Park? Check out this awesome vintage modern flat in the Harrison Arts Dis… https://t.co/PqawR0VMy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am very honored to be among such terrific journalists awarded @PolkAwards — accolades however should also go to… https://t.co/vRpXA2vLSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerseyGirlAnt @creditkarma @VZWSupport For real.  I sent a dispute.  My dad explained to me, because he’s really g… https://t.co/Cz20DKpJFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahardtospell @pascallisp @mcmansionhell calls these the “Pringles can of shame,” and she is correct]]></document><document><![CDATA[mark my words I WILL make movies. The kind that make you feel, things you don’t want to feel, things you do wanna f… https://t.co/4YR7lA3rNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bozinc94 That’s great. Actually when I saw this I thought now that jacket is different.  ❤️❤️❤️❤️. You go girl!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to multiply your entries tonight for Saturday’s $25,000 Love Of Money Giveaway! ❤️ Win Cash or double… https://t.co/9rcG700CWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the absolute pleasure of getting such an education from Nancy (the owner) while at @_TOOC_ Laguna Beach, CA o… https://t.co/KfpZrfUKX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Hmmmm is this like 45 saying "there are good people on both sides"??? https://t.co/OhDdtX3MKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antoniiguillen @galbanus Don’t tell me u be sucking frat boy community dick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senoraMThomas @rickwormeli2 I agree! There are always consequences in life at some point; but giving kids hours of… https://t.co/bJVHbdm0Ta]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO glad I’m awake right now bc my mom decides to have a loud hissy fit at 4am. Why can I hear that from across the… https://t.co/9gmqCSpKap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Painted this myself at with Alecia @PWATAlbanyNY 🌍✊🏾❤️ https://t.co/E1tiqt6GpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will see people love people who do not love them back. Bishop Ken Carter during morning worship. #GC2019 #MTSOatGC2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE TRUTH ABOUT WISCONSINITES WHO DID NOT VOTE IN 2016... 300,000 Wisconsin Voters ;Turned Away; Due to Voter ID La… https://t.co/504NghLdYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolynryan @R_EvolveEchelon Hell if I were alive then I would have walked in on the whole cabinet when they were… https://t.co/5MyhrO3HhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldenlily2017 @MercuryPoMo &amp; I say, “Good luck with your move &amp; look forward to seeing you very soon indeed. 🍀😘🐶🐶.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeddraASmith @audiojoe13 Why did y'all let me drink that much tequila??? https://t.co/vKkyOoA3fV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbyhiddleston I hope you have a great singles awareness day this February 14th Bobby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people think all that matters is their appearance but the truth is your appearance doesn't matter as much it m… https://t.co/n0Ukpa6DSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took the book #valeriescateyescream on a little #gilmoregirls adventure. Do you remember that time in on gg when th… https://t.co/NmJoIwIjG1]]></document></documents></author>