<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Mi abuela de 76 años, es buenasa del whatsapp, pero le envío algo y no me responde, sólo procesa la información, se… https://t.co/YXKOjTWoAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Table ronde avec des entreprises et organismes québécois participant à la mission en mobilité durable et intelligen… https://t.co/WqiAqaNKvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I #LoveMKE because our community can connect in ways that we couldn't before the @thehopmke https://t.co/qU0pupTN8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great day visiting classrooms at Belleview Elementary with Mr. Hood #BelleviewWildcatsinAction #Engagement… https://t.co/Q4yNa77dY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MFreemanvegas @CityOfLasVegas https://t.co/gtIKF67fdn please stop the construction at Pittman wash. We need people… https://t.co/yyqrgypg6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrNikkiMartinez Girl you know better. He can only say, 'its day 129 of the Trump Impeachment hearings'...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for a great session on supporting #ELLs at #NABE2019 !Over twenty years ago I taught #SLIFE students and… https://t.co/xXYxdJAimY]]></document><document><![CDATA[just started watching Temptation Island.. who tf would agree to do this? Idgi?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love watching stars win Oscars when they don’t expect to win. It’s adorable, powerful, and just a beautiful moment. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiskersCrowley @jimmy_dore @LeeCamp @RealTimBlack @RonPlacone @miserablelib The real life Justice League]]></document><document><![CDATA[State Robotics Competition Let’s Go West!!!   #bluedawn #golddusk. #vexrobotics #arkansas @ Arkansas Tech University https://t.co/USoKruDYlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Can I order your “Fuck Trump” shirt from Kathy Griffin and a pink vagina beanie? You’ve gone to the dark side.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy how different my perspective has changed on certain things as I’ve matured. I no longer feel the need to… https://t.co/otQ5ibPqKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_sowers @6abcWeather Chuck Starr has a house near there! Tell him to give you the keys. (You might have to sh… https://t.co/k58rZvmY7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simonphillipson @CxxPIPxx @Bigshirtlesscol Thanks for putting in the apostrophe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatNeal @mostafa @realDonaldTrump It’s because “his worshipers” can easily demarcate good from evil.  Apparently,… https://t.co/IzyFt7QAeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing a wonderful birthday to my other half! Happy Birthday @lee_ttaylor #LoveYouTillTheSunDies https://t.co/MDmq1UAkZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill She keeps talking about what the Democrats are but I don’t hear her talking about with the Republicans are… https://t.co/sVkpesRApF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arrest report shows that Wickline was released around just before midnight last night. He is due in court 3/25.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPol I love county fairs. We go around Ohio, to all the fairs for the harness racing and good ole fair food!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For my birthday/the start of #WomensHistoryMonth, I ordered myself a mug with this dope picture of @AOC… https://t.co/0cAam5sWKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a treat to hear about the amazing women featured in #ShePersisted from the author herself! Huge thank you to… https://t.co/pxrmUq6tve]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Honor Flight of the season 🇺🇸@HonorFlightDCA @HonorFlightNet https://t.co/vWnjUnCUr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Suntimes Ummm Tiffany, you have no choice regarding the matters of your murdering husband.  He is now in the custody of IDOC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG, At least get your dates straight. Your a malicious family. Karma!!! Scary what's coming your way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off the grid with my Love!    Happy Valentines Day ❤️ @ Unahala, North Carolina https://t.co/cZrJFWyOx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieMorseNews Good morning yes is very cold out there getting ready to leave to New York next week so I hope the… https://t.co/1jIeq2NhwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnbcrist Can’t wait for tomorrow night in Baltimore! Let me know if you need any coffee, craft beer, or food recommendations. 💁🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[being successful and/or going on big tours does NOT make you a sell out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hands up (or down) if you’re thriving @ New York, New York https://t.co/UhxiFULpzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[- - - - - #photosbymarietta #cinematicphotography #pregnancyphotography   #maternityphotographer… https://t.co/mpBU6aGOyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week and every week I am grateful for my community. It takes a village and I appreciate every friend, family m… https://t.co/mwg4ylsT3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtmendozahn @SDIYYY ✍️  it was predictable ...daily ... rolling on the floor laughing and winking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanted to mention that I ran into  @KateEminger in the don today and it genuinely made my whole day 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for hopping on @Vliveofficial and joining ARMY in the countdown to #HopeDay! Rest well after your amazing… https://t.co/iMGat40LBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing story by @ChristopherAve on WWII hero John Kriegshauser from St. Louis and the Englishman keeping the memor… https://t.co/L6Gslf5LDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never understand how random people with ZERO mutual friends find and add you on Facebook. Don’t they realize how creepy it is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote on Worlds Best singer!! #TheWorldsBestCBS @vonnielopez  #TWBVonnie #MyVote]]></document><document><![CDATA[do little kids at gigs ever ask you weird questions and you just kinda blank cause same]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MojicaBenjamin @dcpoll @realDonaldTrump there are idiots...and then there are complete idiots.  You are the latter… https://t.co/5M9zNzzWO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[All jokes aside Irina Shayk is beautiful and her a Cooper make a cute couple.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaRealChrisCo YES—and we can follow it up with a fashion show/shopping spree in our already established fave sections 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your Sunday Funday is really your Friday. Waiting for @98official to go onstage!! https://t.co/9xTpllFaED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tradingPolitics @latashamarie13 She’s gross and it looks like she’s a parent. Gross]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar So you're the stupid one. Dim-witted, no chin whelp. you are going down  boy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevonBumpkin @TheSims @SimGuruHouts @SimGuruKate I lived this build! It gave me so many ideas for my current build… https://t.co/VHS7bmmvpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to start my commute home. Not gonna check the #KentuckyBasketball score for a while... 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickSnowRemoval Where oh where are my snow removal guys or gals???? Major snowstorm and they are nowhere to be fou… https://t.co/fbBaOHZeRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mccuaig_nikki @JazzyFitz_ Who even are you??? You probably drink your yellow gatorade while you eat it too.😑🙄🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to have a friend that’s close to me that I can escape to.. I really needed this night away from my room]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old train car. I am thinking of renting it for a party. I think it would be pretty sweet.  . . . . . #oldtraincar… https://t.co/dM9MQsyibb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USPSHelp @USPS why are you not responding to my URGENT MESSAGES???? We need serious help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delanadapr Ya van como 5 veces que le tira a #SNL...  Pero que se acuerde de cuando lo hicieron el "host" en el 20… https://t.co/s98HXbzmv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[of the biggest U.S. buyers of medicine, Medicare, is prohibited from negotiating prices directly with drug companie… https://t.co/XxGNCLmL28]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep forgetting to post the next day of my counting and it makes me so mad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris and I were walking through a store that was basically empty , then two workers came up to us and asked if we… https://t.co/pmAq0cn1ym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Is there any way of ‘getting rid’of all those ‘alleged’ tear gases and gases Madura uses against his pe… https://t.co/0pJDNsN0EE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should just unfollow you lmao you piss me off a lot just because your tweets are conflicting as fuck and hypocritical as fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright folks carryon. I’ve had these conversations on here SO many times. I’m tired. 🤣 Continue your chatting but… https://t.co/mgdIHA4XyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually haven't missed a day of my March art prompts. Time to jinx it XD   #artprompts #doodles #dailydrawing https://t.co/ht3CFOMRUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crazymom50 @lucyRoseReedus @linalan96 @emikoko896 @annedo55 @ldavisusa @Donnams_ @wendy_talmage @JenYeager6… https://t.co/kwsmtkDcfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACHSChoralMusic Such a great win for Chaos and so exciting that PX placed as well🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beckyspadea @Jim_Phillips1 @barchenbeer @OmahaLyftTodd We are hoping Todd and his wife Amy join us and that’ll we’… https://t.co/NgIiZcOwG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can hear my parents watching forensic files all the way downstairs.... I’m scared]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP #GOPCrimeFamily #GOPCrimeFamily #GOPTraitors #GOPWarOnWomen #GOPTaxScam #TrumpIsARussianAsset… https://t.co/BLiIG9N92b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theabimaria Extinction island is a subculture of the survivor mainland culture yo! 😂✊🏾😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[My students using litetacy stratgies and math problem-solving skills during Mrs Senter's circuit board lesson.… https://t.co/EDsZPd76sJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump At least he didn’t get five deferments for BONE SPURS!! CHICKEN 💩!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And another high speed rail project in danger @Bdereyck  @BentFlyvbjerg]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Eternal Love❤️#UniteAnuPre   #KasautiiZindagiiKay #KasautiiZindagiiKay2  #AnuragBasu #PrernaSharma… https://t.co/rTppl4YHZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved using @Seesaw activity “Classroom Compliments” today to promote #kindness. Kids took a selfie, then we rotate… https://t.co/1xa17ubAy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder @realDonaldTrump Of course he did. He probably told them to do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What about those meetings with Russia, who was helping the Trump’s because they are such banner money launderers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York Post : Adam Schiff: Trump should have to testify under oath. https://t.co/24V0Dn9QiH  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IfIWasABillionaire I'd work hard towards total transparency and honesty in Washington and everywhere else!!… https://t.co/g56V5UrJik]]></document><document><![CDATA[More garbage caught than cod: NGOs call for emergency measures to protect Eastern Baltic cod https://t.co/rsJnULKkVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[There were lots of hugs and tears this morning as 150 National Guard members were deployed to Afghanistan. We'll in… https://t.co/EdLjCRk4HV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSabs12 @raf_tyler He a great player, we are blessed to have him here at BBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[STUPID IS /WHAT STUPID DOES!  I BET NEW YORKERS SEE HER IN A WHOLE NEW TYPE OF DESTRUCTION!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christinkallama I'm pretty sure that's actually Richmond Heights. There hadn't been anything near St Louis on that… https://t.co/d1JLxwzIl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only is AOC un-fit, but she is also a fraud liar. In for the money, she really has proven that. Took a million and hide it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 🤮 that’s the most disgusting thing I’ve heard today 😜 https://t.co/VURH8b0z4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYinLA2121 @laureldavilacpa These sex-deprived old conservative men, demean ppl who have a healthy sex life,then t… https://t.co/7znuRu4pIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill Baldwin is such a special #BarLeader! He knows how to run a legal services program. He is compassionate and ge… https://t.co/oiq2wGgoz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's always a treat to meet online friends in real life. Thank you @Alex_Hirsch for saying hi!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to announce I am a freshly-minted Level 2 Google Certified Educator! @GoogleForEdu https://t.co/rXM3V0t5y9… https://t.co/dsm47jzuXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to work with @marklewismd and a wonderful team @Intermountain to start the #ColoCareStudy under the lead of… https://t.co/d4kBvejgt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @GovKemp You should be setting your ass in NY taking care of your businesses not representing US citiz… https://t.co/MkGKUezjeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I take the 405 daily, and that’s an everyday thing I swear. Latinos always work for their money 💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheMaskedSinger Peacock is Donny Osmond, the Bee is Tina Tuner, Lion is Normani from 5th Harmony, and the Monster… https://t.co/a4UwB0vd78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow what a warm Monday!! Im so glad to tell you today temperatures will NOT be that warm with highs in the low 80s… https://t.co/dIYXKGBjOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeed Probably not going to believe any of this because I’ve worked at 2 movie theaters and none of what was sa… https://t.co/7m6oZFpwjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@srsinger40 @funder REALLY! IT IS JUST SICKENING TO WATCH! SNL IS THE #1  SHOW ALL OVER THE WORLD! AMERICA IS A JOK… https://t.co/I0x5J6ODEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some things just fall together beautifully... Taking EMH | Stanton “design liberties” with our swag bag contents… https://t.co/ffvmv5MMUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 for mature audiences only *** Photo is censored 📸 @VanErotica  ✭ https://t.co/OphxzecMIj  #linkinbio #photoshoot… https://t.co/o6DPxtpT0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mjsongbird @JikookiesnSuga @HaiISagan @Ramirezmmrf @JenniferMascia I did say he was abused as a child. I think you… https://t.co/pyK3HAXyyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicc_seitz Seriously!!! I miss having e board and then getting ready and going out every Thursday. Now I’m in bed by 10 pm lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day!!!!  #healthequity #healthequityforwomen #valentinesday #happyvalentinesday #women… https://t.co/lC0RhtM40e]]></document><document><![CDATA[#moreglam #officephotoshoot #lovethatcoat #fauxfur #redleatherpants #nailartoohlala #taxreturns #surroundingme… https://t.co/tHVZWzEcC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 miles and 10,000ft walked yesterday, 8 miles cycled today. I ache. I feel 90, not 19. Netflix and dinner in the… https://t.co/puZxfPT1lf]]></document></documents></author>