<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Reading and loving (and about to finish) GIRLS LIKE US by @cristinaalger . This book is utterly spectacular. On sal… https://t.co/OyjmguTklF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 Be sure to watch our new video 🔬🧪🦠 @ Peterborough, Ontario https://t.co/4OBICD9dBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psalm 118:24 24 This is the day that the Lord has made; let us rejoice and be glad in it. ESV https://t.co/jIbyMMKnlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My AAF Power Rankings after week 5.  1. Orlando 2. San Diego 3. San Antonio 4. Birmingham 5. Atlanta 6. Salt Lake 7… https://t.co/oeNdLFsEVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doodisgirl Proverbs says “Charm is deceitful and beauty is vain, but a woman who fears the Lord shall be praised.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[When she opens your snap, and you think she leave you on read but she just getting a good picture]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you like taking an express train that actually makes all the local stops and comes to a screeching halt in the t… https://t.co/Tdpn0mgzoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been an honor and a privilege to serve alongside such an amazing group of individuals in showing our community… https://t.co/qr92AeSoDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VTVcanal8 @VTVcanal8 : Bolívar, en Angostura( 15 d Febrero d 1819)”El sistema d gobierno más perfecto es aquel q p… https://t.co/lr3Tqmyvn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My supervisor said he was on a “seafood” diet anything he sees he eats and I broke down laughing, I have no standards for jokes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouieNester Yeah I agree. One of the other angles shown did show the ball still in play but I think this angle pro… https://t.co/CvltGKNxLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c3convertase Just get through today. Tomorrow will be ok. Like you said, you'll fight if need be. You're so close.… https://t.co/arq4qqppd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_NoiseWaterMD Hell, Justice Jackson never even took the bar exam. He had a successful practice, became SG and the… https://t.co/voEOYhZi14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Tower Mobile Home &amp; RV Park https://t.co/mVCqSnbKvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time to make the rules of belonging to STEM more visible: https://t.co/SU75DT1TsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the most kid gloves approach I’ve seen @donlemon take toward reporting something so uncomfortable for him.… https://t.co/ysjannnqMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppStateJen @ESPNStatsInfo @UNCisFamily That’s what wire-to-wire means. It means the same team led the entire way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pontifex Well enough assuming the nature of a faith not based on merit, reward or even  helpfulness, being the ide… https://t.co/oBf0uy0jq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianeMariePosts Not mentioned are the consequences of the large installations/institutions under PPP management of SNC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“who the fuck needs coupons to mcdonald’s? who’s that fuckin poor?”   -Matt https://t.co/cbOnQStdWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nooooooooooo😓😓😓😓😓😓"Kim Kardashian West slams claims Khloé will be the next Bachelorette"  https://t.co/hN1E4GD8y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just referred to the contents of my granddaughter’s diaper as Mr. Brownstone. He’s been knocking all day. #abouttime]]></document><document><![CDATA[To add onto that a little bit:  I’m just extremely thankful to finally have a job I can say I actually love. I’ve b… https://t.co/VGjCHLTXNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fake vs Real • • • P/C @amairanyc &amp; matthew_belknap @ Sip Matcha https://t.co/19vsbUBDcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[In such a small town, why is it impossible to run into the one person you want to see?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garyvee Fire the GM. Should’ve traded you to the Lakers while you were healthy.   (Rest up and come back stronger, homey 💪🏻)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just enjoying the intellectual conversation @YogscastLewis @Sips_ @PyrionFlax https://t.co/yIe6uD31TZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BooksieWriting Signed up this morning only it won’t accept my email and password. Reset password multiple times an… https://t.co/D0EmC275zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife’s super power is getting into any bathroom that I am in. It matters not where we are or whether it’s locked… https://t.co/lH58nkfFyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any chance we can get the spring game back so we have something to look forward to??? #Cyclones]]></document><document><![CDATA[This beer is so #swag #daydrinking #beerme - Drinking a Here Comes Your Mango by @BrewRevOtt @ Evergreen Brick Work… https://t.co/pLDOJNpJEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brooklynsbeat In this scenario I’m the equivalent to a Monta Ellis truther (trade D-Lo bc he cant play with Dinwiddie)]]></document><document><![CDATA[It might be my first year as an exhibitor, but it’s my 15th @therentalshow in a row! Looking forward to seeing ever… https://t.co/nykNNZEM49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okwaterwellman @jessicawilcoxOK @bsheff87 We had a 250 Big Red. That thing was a rolling death trap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[✔️CLASS REGISTRATION FORMS Students are reminded to turn in their registration forms for next year as soon as possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got Jobs like this waiting for me.. 75 thousand to 120thousand a year is more than enough when you have no kids.. I… https://t.co/24kpiEZiQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right. But we don’t ding the ‘27 Yankees because black players were banned from MLB and there was no free agency, n… https://t.co/iM0nmu5mMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanTheTerrible So riddle me this, u don't reminisce in your mind about females u use to have fun with,  I have ex… https://t.co/Va1ynKyDEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good move Manny on signing a contract that will put you in one of the least hitter friendly parks in baseball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickieV @USATODAY I love @DickieV but I find his outrage interesting, in light of his previous support for Rick Pitino]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barchenbeer Yep. And you don't even want to know when the one after this is. 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[US trade deficit now at 10 year high. Trade deficits aren't inherently bad, but Trump mistakenly insists they are,… https://t.co/BIDj6yArIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just some dudes riding down the highway blasting Hit Me Baby One More Time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s because the “fans” that go to the games are rich band wagoners. OG warrior fans remember ROARACLE when lower l… https://t.co/Nk8MLbJSz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn, @kennyloggins killed it on #snl tonight! Looking spry. https://t.co/HwkNVLpzfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisrdavi @jeremytache @FernandezAndreC @PaintCornersPod Dude his whole person is Cano like. Stocky, left handed s… https://t.co/ITdZrHM9gK]]></document><document><![CDATA[How's the hammer it's about to be dropped you f****** with my triggers,,,, and I'll press on thou Easy Button,,, an… https://t.co/xKchzcFaLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[United States citizens will need a visa to visit Europe starting in 2021 https://t.co/itq6CTDqrg via @CNNTravel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Killer performance from @ladygaga and Bradley Cooper on the @Oscars2019Live_ #brilliant]]></document><document><![CDATA[That I’m happy to see Tviq play a Mei should show how over the 3-3 comp I am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrkambN @lillyt72 Sorry you don't think it is a great barometer but considering it came from a US based organizati… https://t.co/hcDmYnlDoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not gonna lie, if I had enough space for them to run and they had a super gentle temperament, I'd consider a wolf-dog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bedell_lyss @n_holland1 @Fabletics Call bank immediately and talk to fraud department.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tylerguilliams1 @LZyl23 They never won a championship without him, and he NEVER missed the playoffs. The NBA is ju… https://t.co/cAHpus4Eqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveMess10 @PaulTenorio Because TAM is pooled money whereas DP spending comes from the ownership...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onlyonejj22 @therealpattman Except, we do. We need to see him ball against everyone. Good and bad. Beat the bad teams and the good teams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance When? The black people in this country have been waiting 300 hundred years]]></document><document><![CDATA[7️⃣5️⃣7️⃣ ‼️  Darling Stadium/Todd Field.  We all play at the same Spot... there’s no “Home Field Advantage”  😭😡😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleRempel WTF is wrong with those morons? Not enough terrorists here already?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fateswarning @joey_vera @realrayalder @MetalBlade @brianslagel LAST NIGHT IN NYC WAS AMAZING!!!!! CONGRATULATIONS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THAT_DEJA @BaybeeDee Yeah these hands are Rated E for everyone so she fasho would’ve caught em]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASoloski @MakeBelieveFM Yes! They are stand-alone audio plays, not an ongoing serial, in case that matters to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sidrosenberg @bernardmcguirk3 @RobinRoberts @bernieandsid @77WABCradio Sid, why do people lack common sense today?… https://t.co/bExS4jNnKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagicJohnson @Lakers STOP GIVING UP ALL OUR DAMN YOUNG PLAYERS FOR NOTHING!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Molyneux made the same pro-immigration argument as @LPNational in January 2007. It’s fine to change your mind, but… https://t.co/QGg04uSGJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyMountain10 @krisscottxxx @PornPros @TheMattDreads 😎👍🍾 https://t.co/JBtKpqvcMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton #VoiceBlinds congratulations on Andrew, you have the other coaches scared!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the #DenisonStingerettes #Officers Contest awards yesterday! Officers-Platinum sweepstakes Best… https://t.co/M3muJu9Bq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Layering of Texture / White Chestnut Royale / Very Seasonal Structure / Essence of Winter / Respect 🤙🏻😌 #nyc… https://t.co/sylxge8imK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gzuckier @HillaryClinton @GabbyGiffords @lucymcbath @SpeakerPelosi And its nobody's business what guns I have]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEY! YA TALKING TO MY GUY ALL WRONG .... do it again and I’ll stab you in. The face with a soldering iron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alythuh I feel like being on a direct path to a strong future is all that keeps me emotionally stable]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all the women out there, especially those who have influenced me to be the man I am today. miriammanriquecansino… https://t.co/ckhCk36mWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinRayGolf @APinv @PGATOUR @15thClub Justin, do you have the median distance to compare to the average?  This i… https://t.co/ltcWXr95yZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scdavis65 Check out @lisasharper 's recent thread on this. Must've been reposted in my Twitter feed 50 times. And… https://t.co/Q9m1IYfIh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff #shiffisupshitcreek @DNC #accountablitycomingforcoruptpolitians #DemocratsAreCorrupt]]></document><document><![CDATA[$154,900.   📍 Elida, close to everything!  🛏 3 bedrooms, wonderful master suite! 🛁 2.5 beautiful baths.  🍽 Fabulous… https://t.co/AIa5ES1USP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update!  @Eryn_NotErin has placed as high as 40th in 4 matches. She is now hooked as well. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham @BillyGraham @ICCSyd Praying for you!  Preach the Word in season and out of season!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judithdont @HeatherMarsee @CodeMan1104 @Iagos_Children @prattprattpratt @ChristineCaine @StephenAtHome God Hates S… https://t.co/DwwBekyOzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[United at the rock with  @UTFacultySenate president Misty Anderson. Cold hands but warm hearts for a welcoming clim… https://t.co/mMTey2ielZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gormsby @StreetsMN This morning two cars couldn’t even pass each other on Grand. Literally twice the space going t… https://t.co/1seYVsgasH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MolonLabe6969 @theappeal @shaunking Did you read the article or just skim through it? Did you miss the part where… https://t.co/g2ETIGGfLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My health killing me slowly, but as long as I’m in good terms with everyone, I don’t fear death. Live life to its f… https://t.co/39mHsnrv5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiverHawkHockey I may be in the Dallas area for the Revs season opener, but I’m still paying attention. Win this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPost_Brazille @briannnnf Just on those items alone! However Rutgers can easily squander any opportunity like thi… https://t.co/lSWDQknVSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCreasy2222 @CatholicChroni1 @StefMNicholas That frankly is exactly what a Mormon does with the Book of Mormon.  T… https://t.co/F86qSuwAAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiverAveBlues The SOB should have retired so we could have collected insurance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thesis committee meetings today and I’m very nervous. Hoping to set my graduation timeline in stone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohort B blended learning mentors, tomorrow is your day! Woo hoo! I can’t wait to discuss purposeful planning for c… https://t.co/4krMqGu5zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottWamplerBMD That a downside, but the upside is more Corey Haim in a wheelchair and Gary Busey before he went i… https://t.co/Kmezq8JZM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyThriller69 @KamalaHarris you dont like kale? and OBTW , it's Fanta Orange]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara @Mimirocah1 2/  his eyes] A wall? [Again, El Chapo doubled up, laughing] U S:  Yes or No? G:       We… https://t.co/eA7yDv1XCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MANOLOCADAFE La copa que se corria era en honor a nuestro tío, quien fue uno los propietarios más emblemáticos en… https://t.co/xu2F8WXZ5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Dot_J It's like trying to fight water, when the water has no idea what it's talking about]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronOKelley @Grant_D_Taylor @h_a_thomas I think in the scholarly world it’s the legacy of the historical-critical… https://t.co/QSHUisUYgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4sqms @GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @POTUS That’s right, we must clean house. The wonderful Americans have been… https://t.co/s9123bAvHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't recommend this highly enough! Brilliant! ✊🏾💪🏽👍🏽  #Legend #BlackHistoryMonth]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a ride, finally put my suitcases down and spent 4 years with one team and I’m beyond thankful for the teammate… https://t.co/25vHNhfAT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonyElectronics I would not have bought this if I knew the content providers were going to abandon your platform...]]></document></documents></author>