<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AlexandraDarya4 I still have selfies on my phone with bitches I don’t even know but we were so excited to see each other 💀😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markiplier Chica you're being such a good girl! Tryna make your dad feel better! Feel better Mark!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Are our farmers happy?  Are you going to compensate those who have had to declare bankruptcy?  Or, do you even care?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattyArquette @splcenter Now that you know, it was a made up lie! Where’s your apology. Wait for the facts, not wh… https://t.co/BcUJLJgoZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Desesquerdizada Ei, @brunocovas, vai ter assessor de rock e sertanejo também?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg✨and then there are those #dreams...I just can’t win. So real, even you were probably dreaming it too💕✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods James I know u know a lot of people up n the higher-ups can there not b something done 2 get rid of… https://t.co/jcZGH9ahv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are some tips on growing out the nape of you hair? (The kitchen) That’s the only trouble I’m having with my hair right now 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fun time behind this door and then for some great shopping after. Thank you ladies for letting me join you.… https://t.co/Hs4Mi4RllO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today In History March 4th On This Day In… 1865 - US President Abraham Lincoln inaugurated for his second term as P… https://t.co/b5OJxVvGjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why don’t we hold bigoted country music/radio personalities accountable instead of comparing two women that hold si… https://t.co/TC5IHxsalJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[(More “Shibirenai” translations later today. 6AM without coffee is too early for my second language skills and fighting auto-correct. ⚡️🏹🖤)]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DontMindMeImJustWatchingArrowAndShippingOlicity  🚢❤🎯👓💘 #Arrow #Olicity #OlicityWithdrawals]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does my jacket look like some headless man standing in the corner of my room]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of y’all never watched harry potter growing up and it really shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Misty_Lee @Ruth666 @Paul_Dini That would be magical. 🔥🔥 https://t.co/HKoP7k1u1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dacheteur @andylassner @joanwalsh @TuckerCarlson Your a good Liberal Zombie steward,  they must be so proud 🤣😂🤣😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im legit still listening to this remix. Idk if its the arrangement, the vocals or how I had to mix the instrumental… https://t.co/LUpVmFnvm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, so @BTS_twt 's comeback is mid-April.... Imma be in Korea mid-April... Does this mean I get to witness this first hand?! 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're not in the feed, you're not in the game. - @BenSmithee #DigitalMarketing #IJOPhoenix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@friezeartfair paramountpics You know how a painting begins undulating before you are swallowed up into a new dimen… https://t.co/40xNvLI7qF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting really tired of watching people throw cheese at their fucking babies. #cheesechallenge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cause trust me I would rather be fat and happy than work out and diet ANY day of the week 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[isn’t your sweet 16 supposed to be the birthday that every girl looks forward to because it’s going to be the best thing ever?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodNotesApp Dear Goodnotes team, I have emailed a diagnostic. My version is currently 5.0.14]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the ONLY candidate that mentions @HillaryClinton and the #StolenElection]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t understand why you would fuck up something so good. You had it made and ruined it for nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurenmzabel @mrdonut @GirlsWhoCode +1 I’ve mentored for @GirlsWhoCode and found it to be a consistently great pro… https://t.co/C6oZpiRR0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t had this much fun in a long time! Got to see old friends &amp; new ones too! Thanks guys!!… https://t.co/8nKhgj2n2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 My friend always tells me that "white people" are the cancer of the world, I still want to believe that… https://t.co/jHW1LTroSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3: I love to start conversations with these two little words... #leadupchat https://t.co/VK0gUbx9Ca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spend like 30+ hours studying for an hour long exam. Like wtf. This is my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamballam honestly even if they didn’t. just go whenever. (also here they serve all day breakfast so i literally g… https://t.co/pmQi2KxXrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithboykin That's bullshit! Him on his bike! Riding ! Doing nothing wrong! Fuck you! Fuck her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bobby saved the day and got me some sustenance! #tongueisstillnumb #hurtstoswallowanything #iwantchipsanddipsobad @… https://t.co/IL40MfCKYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a POG Whipped Dream by @cellarmakerbeer at @lupulo_sc — https://t.co/VWRwUfOLYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matmenpodcast Cant stand Owens! No personality, nothing to look at, what’s the appeal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allahs_SonOfMan @TS_SCI_MAJIC12 @Pontifex Yes I Am. And will never use that E Why? I fucking hell have three of 12… https://t.co/XN4nfaUCae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely so Paul oh, if the guys already down kicking and is just cruel and we're above that my kindred spirit :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Rehire Nadia Bjorlin: Days needs to rehire Nadia Bjorlin ? - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/WfXt9CTc7r via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Australian tea tree oil better help my face because this shit smells TERRIBLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I promised to never be that girl that does the holiday appreciation posts about my S.O. or always post about them b… https://t.co/sS4Le9gMlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsarcasticass1 @rawls_juliet RKelly far from free. Got off the first time because of technicality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJusticeDept Wow, nice catch! Hope assets were frozen for the victims.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was obsessed with libraries and reading as a kid. I once told the Librarian on a field trip that I wanted to be l… https://t.co/j9hkRKZg2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[An extraordinary, beautiful and challenging course - what a wonderful day #twobirdies #playedquitewell… https://t.co/97q85xgRnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the Oscars and doing my taxes.. so far I can’t decide which one is less entertaining.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gimetzco Yeah, im not enjoying it either. I only turned it on because a twitter friend said he’s having a lot of f… https://t.co/xusSdPNMn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XxCinthiaXx I will cry so hard if Rue goes home tonight. But I have faith that she will be safe because our Queen… https://t.co/4d2MTC6m5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[But ask me why I’m not surprised this story started with a focus one of the BEST women-led STEM Ed companies and en… https://t.co/w3gUaQ8HHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @GOP @realDonaldTrump Your dad Donald is killing us. Your family is making a killing. The other 99%… https://t.co/dlAGb7mEuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[To say we are excited is an understatement - we are ECSTATIC! @MaxwellCougars is a special place filled with amazin… https://t.co/hPncFQiQ0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who gives af about international women's day lmao what a joke of a holiday imo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 10th birthday to my free spirited granddaughter #granddaughter❤ #birthday https://t.co/rFfAOtVSKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never forget the Halloween party I went to .. a guy ran out of the bush dressed as Beetlejuice and I damn near… https://t.co/pr7uhpxcx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Megan_Dollar @CoMissourian This vertical design is fantastic, you did a great job with this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow @JJA1958 This lady needs to go.  She is very dangerous to America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell do these people actually believe what they are saying?  or are they doing it for money and their 15 minutes of fame?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TarynLovesYou_ @uhkent @cait_lh I love this! You can use it for so many things, I’m totally stealing it 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[girls really act different when you tell them you’re bi... like no bighead, i do not have a crush on you. if i did, YOU’D KNOW.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do ALL THINGS with LOVE ❤️  —— follow: @adriannacdavid &amp; @CharitiesAngels #dailydoseofDad @niathenote… https://t.co/lnuh4ZoDOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@growingupzee I know you haven't been  complicit with Trump!! Is it the nip?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acwheater @WXMegs I think it’s in the 1-3 inch range now for Des Moines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerTonight Please ask HANNITY to pass you his hundreds of leftover ties.  You need ties, my friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PrivateDancer #ErosGuide #PhoenixCompanion #PhoenixEscorts  #preferred411 #LizzyLoungeMembers #BookNow… https://t.co/g6cumWiHtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a turning hell #canpol when @CBCNews churns words to a “case”. Shame on @CBCNews .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isabelaamp @DionJunior4 DANGERRRRRR y’all need to pin a disclaimer to your backs. 😏😈 watch out world!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@huldaah_ @jaimeb_11 @Chinyere_Jason8 @JazzzzyS Hold duh, this plan better go through. I  ain’t waiting no more😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDallFL @Barry8892 @ThomasBoswellWP @JasonLaCanfora https://t.co/06Q5jeGqGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marksanders1958 @SenWarren @realDonaldTrump Like wat sitn on his fat ass eat n fast food n golfn hes a disgrace]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blocking the whole Kardashian-Jenner Klan was the best thing I’ve ever done on here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@destroytokyo @Granddad_Sr Mary Elizabeth Winstead should be in everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait! Going to be an amazing night and free pizza will be provided!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It absolutely KILLS that I’m not in ATL for these races this weekend. @FoldsofHonor it’s gonna be a fun weekend out… https://t.co/Hku6zuXYdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Christy_ Well then I’m sorry you feel like animals aren’t sentient beings. They are and they have desires t… https://t.co/nhRZJv0hB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KennedayTS Yeah but they're watches look brand new I suppose I could take a look again but it just I don't know I'… https://t.co/CIZY0sLodl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stillsie @kathygriffin @sxsw Beautiful?  Dude, u are seriously blind!  FUGLY is more like it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You spent $811,929 and your son almost died to “ultimately decide” against a follow-up vaccination or other immuniz… https://t.co/mrQcVAMFQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[STOP YELLING AT ME, TOY SOLDIER! I'M RUNNING AS FAST AS I CAN 😭😭😭 #PrincessHalf https://t.co/twDtmlXs5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsElementary__ @FoxNews Who cares what @Judgenap says?  We all know he's a never Trumper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With a 5  inch height difference,  fitting both of us and a circus tent into a selfie is harder than you'd imagine.… https://t.co/VBWbecEV4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be Humble! 🤦🏾‍♀️🤣 How do you expect somebody to bring dinner to the table, if you don’t even own one 🙅🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out I’m going to be a godmother this year to baby demon 😭 https://t.co/7cqjqEdr91]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy President's Day! "If your actions inspire others to dream more, learn more, do more, and become more. You are… https://t.co/U2LRPaakMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my #eyelash #eyelashesextension #lash #pestañas work.  #eyelashes for everyone come see me #teaminga… https://t.co/EL7FwYdMSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[drank #travelgnomesofinstagram  #happyvalentinesday @ City Tap Dupont https://t.co/1GvR0Rzz6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaigeForExample Can you say if you don’t sign that I don’t work here my lawyer will be contacting you? I just need… https://t.co/OdgXBZYNK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if we had a magic genie and we could have a different colored skin? What if you had to take all of the baggage… https://t.co/urhssQYVpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diletta1972 @BoyGeorge Hello Diletta...I'm just beginning my morning but thinking of taking a lil nap.. before I start my day...💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryKateCabac I wanted to wear that to @erinc_118 &amp; @reid311 wedding, but didn’t want to steal the spotlight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJnz1 @PlayingPolitix @lynnkthurston @Haven_Resists @KAmorphous @mbryan002 @acupoker @tngsmama @runrosierun… https://t.co/VYwdq3pAP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JadedCreative you have no idea how that word has stuck with me and inspired me ! You would be my inspiration guest on Deal or No Deal !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks bitch ❤️❤️ I wasn’t angry for those 30 mins before we opened lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChangeHisHeart good morning 🌞😊hope you are doing well and having a good day so far]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lil_AaronR Thank you!!! It’s hard being away from you on my bday but it’s okay because I’m proud of you I love you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump   Everyone should call their Senator and DEMAND they support our President in keeping our border secure to protect us‼️😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KadyRoxz Lol I could’ve been my usual self but I figured alittle motivation was better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry for the rant but she got on my nerves!!! I wanted to say something too but I was too busy worrying about my food order 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last but not least. My fav pic. Thank you @JoeFlacco for everything. Love u always 💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoltarianFist Have an affair tonight! Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight. https://t.co/D30OFvedLZ #us #uk #nz #ca #dating]]></document></documents></author>