<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[3/7/2019 - 09:33 Temp: 38.4F   Hum:  89% Wind: 3.0 mph Baro: 30.258in. &amp; Falling Rain: 0.01 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeELtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwon  congrats!! good for you!!! I am not even mad at you!! you heading to my second team Niner!! that rent is goi… https://t.co/d0vKqquVps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews dear mr president—please act your age]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I got the call that today’s gig was cancelled we pulled into a very unassuming general store.  Upon entering i… https://t.co/4qXr0eaf5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darla32234 @dfausch21 @qanon76 @realDonaldTrump @KimStrassel @WSJ https://t.co/3DyTpkb4u1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYMetroVets @warsnotover I struggle with being optimistic, daily. So what I do is make sure I atleast help 1 perso… https://t.co/U3IKBHKpPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyBrown088 Everyday your breathing is a good day! Remember trials are for a season and a reason. Keep your head up young man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisyearsgirls Uhh ... I don’t work in agriculture, but even I know that won’t work! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Differentiate organically” and your students will work harder. #pbl #EducationForAll #studentchoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 It's the same political party that doesn't know it's ass from a hole in the wall!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol it’s funny how people trip of social media like y’all gotta understand it’s fake ... me and mines getting it in the real world 💰💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a late night of drinking &amp; eating I had to get one in! @nateberkus @jeremiahbrent mrstracyrobbins… https://t.co/jPl6gAazAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnastasiaFrost Я бы даже за тысячу этого не сделал. Передай тому мужику, что он дешёвка ;)))))]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝😍😘 @latinas At porn!… https://t.co/DWEfavjqel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoSacredCowsGOB @WalterGeorge6 @Nostrafartface @AdvanceHumanism @Lily_Bell82 @neithskye @kenserlore96… https://t.co/pbWU9NwfWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_mollycaitlin_ Couldn’t even get through the top 25 but homeboy is dead serious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Welshy_Who @TJSutton04 @BeckyLynchWWE @RondaRousey @MsCharlotteWWE First of all, Brock Seth ate not even more wort… https://t.co/ngwVS7AZSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sewneo Little things become big things when we polish our spyglass of attention and have the discipline to appreci… https://t.co/3Jo8IDFZvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamCoatesTimes Actually read the emails and you’ll read an entirely reasonable response from Murray. This is an at… https://t.co/QskjG7sbTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heyyyyyy @SoundersFC fans wich style jersey should i get authentic or replica?? https://t.co/UoRQ52xpKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[You cannot escape “Wagon Wheel.” You will be assimilated. Resistance is futile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the logic here: https://t.co/jjJAfZJHRm  Sanctuary cities/states for Illegals?- Yes, fight the power!  Sanctua… https://t.co/GpMkrd1adY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PKSubban1 @PredsNHL Gotta love how much Hockey players appreciate their fans. Love these videos. No matter the team or player! #respect]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't been as active streaming lately, but I'm about to go live with a new session of #finalfantasyxiii on… https://t.co/2JJyWuS3aL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 7 y.o. found a floss stick in a bathroom drawer and asked what it was for. When told that it’s for flossing, she… https://t.co/9BW9KKORs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adverstine Hot debate in my office about this last night. Did you see Ridley's BTS video for it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rebuke of @JudgeJeanine issued by @FoxNews for her comment about @Ilhan. https://t.co/F740tvNlMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We live in a simulation where someone turned the absurdity meter to 100 just to see what would happen https://t.co/rHd7hBj0xP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardinals Live has gone from a decent #fanwithsources to a cocky piece of shit real fast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SundayReading on #NittanyEpicurean features @ShangoBistro @BuffaloSoup @BreezyBurritoCo @naantasticgrill… https://t.co/wlh14eJkxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lakewood, NJ. Jewish police allowed to patrol "their" town with no repercussions as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#zoe concert :) @ The Cosmopolitan of Las Vegas https://t.co/chYjJvTHlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the first few years I’d go down to South Street to find relatives postering the neighborhood for witnesses. I w… https://t.co/nL8F8CtLko]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t know David Otunga was in Madea Family Funeral, seeing the movie now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Thought to Think About - “USE THE GIFT OF WORDS TO HELP NOT HURT” - #ToddCPittman  #Proverbs12:18 #LifeAndDeath… https://t.co/lsa22KFdG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday March 1 - WSJ The 10 Point:     The U.S. and North Korea traded blame for the failure of their second summit… https://t.co/NTBp3PQTz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonasFortune Also, follow up: we’re going with all of the reporting is false?]]></document><document><![CDATA[COMPROMETIDOS CON UN MEJOR PAÍS, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York metropolitan area https://t.co/rM2bfnYvq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This post is from the beginning of the car buying process. Bets on when I’ll be done?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeburkejr @BuckeyeFou I bet the TTUN football would like that. End the trail of 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying for you, Mr. Trebek!  I have watched Jeopardy since I was a kid, and despite the low survival rate, I know… https://t.co/8WhBoMSxJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diagon Alley!!! @ Wizards' World of Harry Potter: Diagon Alley https://t.co/T666mMF0MQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryjesus19721 @Heeclifpreven @libertylatina @marcorubio So you left your people and country like cowards, and the… https://t.co/oIpCpXX2KD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ethan_3x @Afrocentripetal At least my mom loved me enough to not name me Ethan ffs 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently at @BMSupdates we would need the aero ducts just to channel the water. 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackhakimian Hi Jack, We would be happy to assist you. See our innovative work here: https://t.co/0kK0depliy… https://t.co/9zye2r7q2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp Hate crimes don’t exist a crime is a crime period. Your obsession with never trump is what’s sick]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grant Hightower crossed 1 Mile to GO!. Time 01:49:22, pace 09:18 min/mile, est. finish 9:07 am https://t.co/OgVQXMtueh #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shows how little they really understand the mind of middle and working class taxpayers who have come to rely on the… https://t.co/RNWv3paZns]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have so much work to do to prepare for a perfect summer.. all new sound system in my boat, get all the safety equipment, tubes, etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The need to choose between a free R Kelly or spend the rest of the time in the dark]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlacklistTrader Bro you want to spend the evening going after me? Unfollow. Easy does it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mehdirhasan @IlhanMN @leezeldin Does everyone now have Arab or Africa names? If so why......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenrogers6abc @6abc Good morning Karen! We are tired of winter so we are getting in the car today and driving so… https://t.co/0g8V7hxDjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Venezuela is being torn down by a mafia style President who wants it all and wants his followers to ter… https://t.co/kXryAnb78y]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling when you were up til 1am working. Then woke up at 6:45 with ur toddler https://t.co/4tkvb3D4gY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ladies and gentlemen ... The Orange Bloviator of the United States - Donald Jumbo Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's one of the sources for that Wikipedia entry: 50 Years of AC: Vanilla Is Licking the Competition… https://t.co/Vci3kCOr0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@readingwinds @jcravens42 @CORLibrary @wccls Sorry that I had to leave early and didn't sign out, but as a… https://t.co/oa8rTEonNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sipping @daouvineyards here @mastrosofficial  . . . #marcosestrada #wine #vino #romantico #steakhouse #restaurant… https://t.co/WH740Aycej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackGirlHockey @FisherJillian Love what you're doing here!!! Any way I can help let me know. #catfishjake]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bayard Cutting Arboretum, Great River, N.Y 3/2/19 #longisland #longislandny #iloveny #landscapephotography… https://t.co/IaOUVBgeHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Palate Cleanser Harp Lager @bjsrestaurants @BeerInFlorida https://t.co/uhACxmJtTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[If have nothing good to bring to someone’s life, don’t waste yours or their time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mormonger @spiritskyes @generalzuo @nihilists4jesus We stan repentance! https://t.co/pIlVR5vjqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PilotSunny787 So sexy #GenevaMotorShow #TopGear https://t.co/xM4TR2vOmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Collins Carpet Cleaning located in Lewiston, ME for the business taking home their new 2018 Ram Promaster… https://t.co/9AjgrobHj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate you dad! #jaxthepuppy #pittiesofinstagram #dogbath @ Clayton, California https://t.co/cNR2auTc2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamiesusskind Also a long time Apple user, but once a year when I teach in Miami I am given a Windows PC. Equally… https://t.co/NRbogm4iuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ja rule is like what Roy Munson was in kingpin. Now u don’t say to took a “L”, u jus say u took a ja rule]]></document><document><![CDATA[“More than 500 architectural firms pledge to design carbon-neutral buildings. Right now, buildings account for almo… https://t.co/nWMmrsjAuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLastRefuge2 @RealMattCouch Dear diary the President Trump doesn't like me he doesn't call on me he doesn't take my messages]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last area team remaining in boys hockey is #2 seed @TigrHockey, who plays #1 seed @Oronoboyshockey on Thursday, Feb… https://t.co/jlOM6GImNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hop Suds by Old Coast Ales @ Old Coast Ales — https://t.co/IXvZCpEvVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no comment at the time. Jesse Smollet taught us to wait for all the facts. Which I intend to do now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Healed shot of one from a couple weeks ago.  Let me know if you'd like to make an appointment. Your design or mine.… https://t.co/h83NCWQEdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only because you @Catioz cannot speak any other language does not mean that there are MANY educated Venezuelans tha… https://t.co/qPqi5Y6s9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tieruhhsten You’ll be straight, I promise you. Celebrate yourself until you got a S/O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjoyitac Cuando post prandial estoy en 180 y con insulina activa no me permite corregir. Si pongo que voy a comer… https://t.co/lzcFzipFsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you do when your kid brings home a new puppy?  Head out of town as fast as possible! https://t.co/jLtiGka3uW]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Image And Scripture is courtesy of @youversion Bible App) Do not love the world or the things in the world. If any… https://t.co/NHK4VAHmAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ltdsoltd @TresaBridges @SSG_Davis_Ret @Birdseye1 @CarolGarofolo @intelligent50 @Whichsideareuon @Muttonchap… https://t.co/AETyMEHZ8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, Obama is going to be at the UNC/Duke game tonight? But the baby boomers on my Facebook feed are all saying he… https://t.co/Gxif2hwA5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Jon doesn’t finish this bum then this card sucked. Also Dominick Cruz is such a dousche.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buy a #NewHome in #California  If your #Negligent #Builder #Lennar screws you, trust me #Government cares none!… https://t.co/ne1uYp3WDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Thank you thank you thank you please continue fighting for us middle, low income people who work hard and pay… https://t.co/dcj3DdThDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google over here telling me to expect rain Friday I’m like google...your mom expect me to make it rain Friday cmon now lol #funny #humor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mothers don’t “own the womb where the unborn babies reside.” God owns the womb where the unborn babies reside. I ge… https://t.co/APytZ7Vcfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like calling your bae and tell her to come home from work for a noon day quickie!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@e_mcclee @kimberlymontse1 @BernieSanders Blame for 70 year old challenger that didn’t take Corp cash not the entir… https://t.co/s9vC6iNkMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iliveonthe @RationalDis @PrisonPlanet You realize that the vast majority of terrorist activity in the US has been… https://t.co/TJ4Im1aQul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joetar996 Same.  I move we adjust work hours to 5am - 2pm.   I’m done by dinner]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you need to borrow money, let me be your last option, not your first choice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DZMMTeleRadyo @alvinelchico @DorisBigornia sir ang iboboto ko Po ay yung octogenarian na si aswang...este afuang..… https://t.co/MFSE0mzt1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[WITH THE FLOW. I have very little control without a flight booked already, so I’m loose and flexible as hell. The e… https://t.co/AI5gIP4lgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Thinking) *Starbucks always gets my name wrong but I’m sure they’ll gey it right this time*  Barista: Joo-On!! Ord… https://t.co/9xKpzWxuBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charles_Mace @NSF_ENG @Daniel_Wilson92 Wonderful news - well deserved!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epsteins took the 5th when asked about whether Trump engaged in sex with minors]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone you know is expecting a little one soon, here are a list of names I highly recommend 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carloslopezjone @silviamcasanova @lopezobrador_ @IATA Es un capricho del pejelagarto el haber cerrado el aeropuert… https://t.co/NBCFni8dFi]]></document></documents></author>