<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This 👇 is more important than a "border wall".  https://t.co/jBaoJI0VKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMikeBloomType @LianaBoraas @paulasleson The #RHAPBnB is back!  Just those casual comments from Facebook...it's al… https://t.co/c2y29QrhOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frenchypupp @JackSEO6 @DavaStarr @lll_sin @Shaylashanaee37 @jessiedoll2 @omgshuddup @thisisweedies @SageDuchess… https://t.co/jeh3NQlHsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[No more slacking off this, time for growth #gains wise &amp; #money wise 🤞🏼💪🏼👊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 I can just see what a GD mess she'd make out of the U.S.! Imagine! NO EXPERIENCE &amp; NO BRAINS as ambassador!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Answer the knock!   #ifinallygotitright  NOT!  #GodsTheOnlyOneWhoAlwaysHasItRight  I am His, so that’s why… https://t.co/UFqeTzAjT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @BreitbartNews @RedNationRising @chicksonright @johncardillo @larryelder @townhallcom @RitaPanahi AO… https://t.co/YZW8qZF9IG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris51161 VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥https://t.co/vaAT1XmggR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SanjayAzadSln @BJP4India is insensitive &amp; do not care for poor Indians .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday Sweat! . . 👉🏻Cardio - Stairmaster 30min . . 👉🏻WOD x3 Sets 》Squat Rack x10 @ 70lbs/70lbs/80lbs 》Plank for 6… https://t.co/nBEXH2Fwqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derPlau thought of you today during this talk...data science, and how Tableau can bring value both during modeling… https://t.co/qrCXObccAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the most snow that Killarney has had in the last 40 years!  I’m thinking the water levels will be high in t… https://t.co/rK4cEeSwqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatgirlnj Happy International Women's Day! I am so proud to be in an amazing group that you're in! Yay Women... we Rock!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyDntShootEm Hey lol can I get the keys to go get my drink nigger lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@until_today If I was handling your PR, I would have gone full white lady ‘Can I see UR manager’ on they assezzz.… https://t.co/qZL6iFT6Bl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love each and every one of my friends. They are all a blessing sent to me to help me through life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack @junogsp7 I like other countries. Let’s take Britain. I kinda follow them but I wouldn’t presume to know enough to vote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign if you agree! #notolls   https://t.co/LX6qF2uWhr @ Greenwich, Connecticut https://t.co/6PtMU92OTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashaEats @DivaVinophile @VisitSeattle @_drazzari @GailBenzler @jflorez @GrnLakeGirl @SeattleBlgrs @wawinereport… https://t.co/ksN9lAdEXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We are praying for the people of Venezuela. Then there is this..... https://t.co/pueNmuX1qU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ty fuckin’ Segall! What a goddamn joy to see him and White Fence in such close proximity. @ Ottobar https://t.co/gCdMVrUpLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro The idea is out there. Pretty sure the Dems will eploit it anyway at this point, no matter what the President does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome site to see the entire @JohnLongMS campus out cheering on their fellow Longhorns who are headed to compete… https://t.co/ORymS7WnwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up late wishing I could relive my labor. 😭 most beautiful time of my life ❤ bringing our daughter into this world w… https://t.co/D9Jk7Q9u8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KlepkMichelle @MikelleWilliam5 @crystal_wilky @IrelandDr2 @krsimp22 @DrPFrance @MrsN_VB https://t.co/ZhbjfFxwsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[P.Terry's is coming along!  Can't wait and hope it has an indoor restaurant and not just a drivethru! #pterrys… https://t.co/UTkSeBaMYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamonEmbry  I'd be honored to have your follow !!  #ArmyStrong #MAGA #VIP on #TEAMMAGA IFB #KAG2020 #BackTheBlue… https://t.co/gcdZ4zdEwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Takeaway from the symposium on heated tobacco products: a need for a clear and cosistent public health message on t… https://t.co/NupQeTAHin]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t condemn the violence or bullying but Jordan and Tristan both deserve the hate 🤷🏽‍♀️ they both fucked up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elowennicole It definitely isn’t. It’s not like you interact with people on there. Also, where else will you find… https://t.co/fYamqw2CFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouVersion Since we have been united with him in his death, we will also be raised to life as he was. We kn…… https://t.co/SVOunXGWbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[My halal guy is in Egypt for the entire month of February and I rlly miss him wow https://t.co/icpLdZzGeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeTheKings music has gotten me through the darkest times of my life. I love everyone of them do much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieAngusNDP @OPP_Indigenous Will you be coming to Toronto to discuss this book, and where can we buy a copy? T… https://t.co/NGRlobStiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right in the #Thunderblink feels 💜 #TheGifted @jamiechung1 @Blair_Redford]]></document><document><![CDATA[That look when you realize you have school today @hoffmanrich @News12LI #notenoughsnow https://t.co/Lcg2Y9BDmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find Killer Shooting Neighborhood Cats With Air Rifle https://t.co/uu1oi7J4to]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Dems didn't have their double standard, they would have no standards at all. They have no morals and they ha… https://t.co/da023HWbRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to say for such a surprisingly good season, this last episodes is quite a let down! I just don t get the cas… https://t.co/DBtpjPBcqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@normsworld @Markus4Ward2 @LubinskiTeresa @mariarizzo @TrusteeDAmico how far reaching can we get this tweet?@TCDSB… https://t.co/j3Dp7CO2Ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOGChristina I was going to get this for for Christmas maybe next year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patio weather ✨ (@ Axelrad Beer Garden - @axelradhouston in Houston, TX) https://t.co/OGJYUp8u97]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nacholacriatura Gracias Nacho, please escríbele a la Bachelet por favor tu q Tanya gente sigues. Callada cómplice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Realitytea Im moving to Coffee4josie@coffee4josie please Follow me there. Ill FB. Separting political and HW thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️☕️ A good cup of coffee is like a nice, warm hug. Thanks for the hug @cremacrema @ CREMA https://t.co/FOT5Jsrbqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t just need painting,  you need @koFitness90. 🏡 👨🏼‍🎨🙌🏻   ✅ Local neighbourhood house painting. ✅ 12+ years… https://t.co/BmqUPUfdk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VYHgVV5oiZ “The 59th Street Bridge Song” by Simon &amp; Garfunkel. Let’s feel groovy today, Loves. https://t.co/hI85BYkCn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prohollins Congrats!!! I've been thinking about applying for the program. Let me know how it goes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goku622498 yes but my group would be without the crazy religion rules, and my sewing creations that everyone HAS t… https://t.co/fo3kqZ0ten]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IfYouEverMeetMe  please don’t ask me why I am so quiet, don’t tell me to relax or loosen up. Don’t judge me, you k… https://t.co/KsEhfdVU0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST REDUCED!!! $375K Beautiful move-in ready home on over 1/2 an acre in Schertz! Single-story living with no step… https://t.co/GxUsRnM5zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting little nugget after JFAC's newsy school budgets today: Lawmakers rec'd extra funding for education/outr… https://t.co/TvuPmaQ1is]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Are the 10 Cleanest Chain Restaurants in the U.S.  https://t.co/xpOq7TRsIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not shocked! What is shocking is Congress is giving this liar a chance to tell more lies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come, make us gods who will go before us.   - Exodus 32:23  Ignorance and fear create the gods, enthusiasm and dece… https://t.co/TzbA2GKl6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[//. If I Had A Dollar For Everytime Someone Tried To Tell Me I’m From New York Or Jersey Id Be Rich I Stg Mfs Don’t… https://t.co/bFkdKxWFKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fancyTaniii Girl omg you dead ass!? Omg sis I thought she was dying the way she was going lord]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheBeat That nonsense DOJ memo was written during the Iran Contra investigation! It’s BS and was written by Raegan’s handpicked lawyers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am freezing I have to stay warm but not too warm...so I pulled out the dress socks. Warm but not too warm yknow? Bu… https://t.co/3biRsgvuxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoesingLoretta I hope you have shared this with legislators and your Dept of Insurance. This is wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found this from Josh Groban that I had never seen and thought about the Parkland families. Wishing you peace and ho… https://t.co/mC0CjZ1IVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing one of my favs featured in the @Tennessean today. Much deserved accolade and respect to Susan and the e… https://t.co/ceLSXF8J36]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liverpool  can kick your butts dubs  #ManchesterCity  @ESPNFC #PremierLeague #watfordfc  #football #goal   #arsenal… https://t.co/mVYsiqpLoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HolmesCarolyn23 @DrIanWeissman @lhugar @AmerMedicalAssn I am so sorry,that is just so sad.Prayers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deolebear @networkindie @JenniferMlottUK @MlottersNation @JenniferMlottNs Aww thank you so much! https://t.co/kIeZaKUXhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TarsesSimon @mchastain81 I love Apollo 13. I can watch any 5 minutes of it and be happy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edited these and they turned out better than I expected so here u go https://t.co/PiDPshVT2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone took advantage of one of my friends and I am furious. https://t.co/y34qWnT6YO]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can anyone hate, hurt...not love her?   She’s the sweetest @bernardokath 💓💙💙😍 https://t.co/ET9YjORwZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jojoh888 Makes you wonder what the heck they put in half the country's vaccines to make them so triggered by truth]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re far from perfect! But things are great for us ! Happy birthday babe I love you 🥰🥰🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉 https://t.co/WQGiypYytB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I not shocked at what happened to @khloekardashian ? It’s definitely sad 😔, I’m just not shocked. It’s almos… https://t.co/cEk6VyPdjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherChilders @KyleBiedermann @POTUS @FoxNews How can we help Texas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my boyfriend drove down to SoCal for his birthday weekend. We’re staying at his parents house for the first… https://t.co/duiD6IgzTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight at @tsacleveland youth group  Youth pastor: So. What do we know about Peter?  Student: *shouts* O he is a h… https://t.co/pbkWU74IYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeuFutur has a new review of @jonnypolonsky's new Unreleashed album of demos and rarities.  https://t.co/yyzWRID2yS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wellness Design Antique Garden Doors https://t.co/Rj8mzYaQpD https://t.co/D4qE75NDVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winn-Dixie Mid city, looking festive. I go to winndixie to buy sale items: buy one get one, 2 for, etc. Bought a Pe… https://t.co/siOExkktWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ekbufalo Después de leer que al Carnicero lo aprueban como candidato en la UE y ONU, las piezas del rompecabezas d… https://t.co/C4HQLisUkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriDisneyLove @spadergasm And it just reminds you of how serious this disease is. And by your same logic of joking… https://t.co/n4xQXSytLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Unload As… https://t.co/cZTQXvEi1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[We already got to see Jumbo’s 🍑 In the photo shoot - i still consider myself blessed beyond belief.]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️ disease informational posters @DelmarHS_Bleile @DelmarHS_AP @DelmarSuper https://t.co/Basgv9mzGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half hour of sunshine, laughing, exercise and relaxation...during a day of omg why are we all having to explain thi… https://t.co/PUNogBegHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LamestTurtle77 My all time favorite. Now you will forever be disappointed in every other series you watch ever again ..... EVER lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[How’d this random white girl get on the list? If it’s that easy, I guess I’m a rapper now too 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this supposed to be a Bill Cunningham stand-in...? I don’t know how to feel. #onthestreet @NYTStyles https://t.co/KzvKKUlLdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateCasey 4 way tie between, LVP, Dorit, Teressa Guidici and Vicki Gunvalson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @marcorubio (Little Marco) this country has zero stomach for sending our military into that hell hole. Enough.… https://t.co/ECO47K0Bb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too many pets: Overcrowded Bay Area animal shelters beg for adoptions 😪 https://t.co/JP3SqH4q2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[so where are the sisters-apparel pop sockets , and why are they not a thing yet?  @jamescharles]]></document><document><![CDATA[This beautiful and enchanting table runner is going to be in our next sale!   Comment MINE when you find your Vinta… https://t.co/dRqb0RRPZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did the IRS has to text me at 1 am about my tax return!? Like couldn’t that have waited until a decent hour! I… https://t.co/frtQQFWsZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely everyone in my house is snoring...💤💤💤💤 except me...cause...insomnia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump But U give the news media so much 2work with!U give comedians more material 2 work with than they'… https://t.co/AD59BvQ7O7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @LandOLakesInc experience at #sxsw lets you share your take on food. This tweet also helps send a meal to… https://t.co/G8dBhbnA9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[NWI Dunkins need to teach Indy Dunkins how to run a drive through like I’ve never had to sit and wait in a dunkin d… https://t.co/wPfj8dalqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fleccas @VANS_66 @PacSun Haha. I love @VANS_66 i hope they just moved him locations. https://t.co/Fwdf0OYHF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLastWord   If lies are not lies then laws are not laws.       Secretary Nielsen lied to Congress today. We can’… https://t.co/kxPQXEaqie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WG_Burton So do you think that Jussie Smollet was working for Obama or what?]]></document></documents></author>