<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[evidence of how SoCal my dad is: he said “I got these new shoes but I have to wear socks with them &amp; as you know i hate that”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now the grout, next the unveiling. #lovemosaic #recyclewithmosaic #glassonglassmosaic #mosaicnightlightcomingup @ I… https://t.co/JPqf3AnXE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Brandeis International Business School Alumni join us for an evening of networking and mingling with former classm… https://t.co/xsV6nM2EoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure I'm not the first to wonder if @timkubart is part Tigger. T-I-double-guh-er, of course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes and this will all backfire when these idiots in the house or the far lefties campaign for President! What goes… https://t.co/ObprSa2FTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love ❤️ him and his #focus. With one hour between school baseball⚾ practice and travel baseball practice he choos… https://t.co/xwkqgCUZUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kids I babysit when I picked them up from school today and they had a valentine with a gift card for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby's first ear infection. 😢 At least it explains her discomfort and sleep troubles. #poorkiddo #ElenaRuth @ Marti… https://t.co/TC3jp8Uy4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnELTenney I often refer to it as just that Hell. Unfortunately they have the French bread that best makes my ch… https://t.co/SuTvRH4Sui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting BTS tix was an absolute nightmare, once again. I had to buy tix off of stubhub and even that was a struggle. 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[💚💚💚💚💚uno más 😎😎😎😎 goooooooooooooooooool  Santos 3-0Marathon               9-2  💚🇳🇬💚🇳🇬💚🇳🇬💚🇳🇬💚🇳🇬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Loudon #TN  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/jYIfJIrOdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YazzieSays Thought about getting some of these and the other ones they minted too...so I can make jewelry out of t… https://t.co/nXin0yYTp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s dumb af and wrong!! 🤦🏾‍♀️ how you not gonna let the biological father who is doing his part claim his OWN kid… https://t.co/mNvA02DDgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaredmunson Here is info to donate: https://t.co/9kMeVHkdPf Books have to be new. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[the jonas brothers reuniting has 10 year old me screaming. and 19 year old me screaming even louder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NYC Number 1, top global city in tech. Acess to a deep talent pool &amp; center of commerce  🗽🍎 🌎]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand Glen Close was trapped in a cult when she was a young girl. She should relate to the evil of Scientolo… https://t.co/BC9bpRJ6qk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jax_persists @BarbaraLevinbb Don't worry, I will be more than happy to introduce you to the real, kind, compassion… https://t.co/JxY9vE6hh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone needs someone to talk to I’m here 👋🏼 just putting it out there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Total failure from @nhl for not showing the pregame number retirement for Iginla on their Center Ice package!!!!… https://t.co/2nFEMIjgLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Richmond International Airport in Richmond, VA https://t.co/ewcvjhqFxX https://t.co/TMzk30ul73]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear if people observed me an my cousins from afar I’m the way less dramatic one compred to them lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenniepryce @dadyo32 please tell me it includes their genetic merit and not just their picture!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get your heartbroken on Valentine’s Day https://t.co/nBKZ97fvLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horny? Lets cam! hit me up! sheilamariestore@gmail.com https://t.co/2qKtRwWOEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@countingpulses Jump up and down on your bed, not off a bridge. Please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codeofvets Madison is a fighter and with the glory of God she will continue to make progress.  #lifeisbeatiful 👼❤🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[JV/Freshman Tennis Tournament- we are thankful the 🌞 finally made an appearance! https://t.co/NPIUUGRs3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #OklahomaCity, OK #FacilitiesMgmt job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: Manager, F… https://t.co/5SlahFf5dK]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIRTY EIGHT // I can honestly say I’ve never been more content in my life. 🥳There is something to aging and realiz… https://t.co/JcWkegtyXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pchdotcom Omgosh that’s a hard one .... I don’t know if y’all  (PCH Prize Patrol Team)  has ever been in the state… https://t.co/cLxXmhG4zV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wedoonlinefina1 LIKE I TOLD THE LAST ACOUNT.  THIS IS ACADEMIC MISCONDUCT. https://t.co/AjhFedkXBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love doing #scicomm but I desperately miss being in the field. Solution? Grab that cheap, last-minute, one-way ti… https://t.co/i3JrrLP6y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night’s #makeup look for the Scout dinner. #latergram #blueandgold #cubscoutmom #boyscoutmom #proudmom… https://t.co/YkGXEk92VB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuschwitzMuseum @ChaosKitty24 There’s so many beautiful, engaging, baffling, endearing, amazing, indulgent, educat… https://t.co/QX8wzTokX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who is representing Arkam Asylum in a civil mock trial regarding Cruel and Unusual Punishment at Comic Fest t… https://t.co/7DPNHtigCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[HIGHER FURTHER FASTER !! IM CRYING !! PLEASE GO SEE THIS MOVIE !! #CaptainMarvel]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really think information pushed by Planned Parenthood,Politicians is wrong in calling all abortion by one word.La… https://t.co/m9MhtovwUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing I love (not) more than working allll day and coming home to take a mediocre nap, just to wake up with a fever. 😊😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need to take a minute to say how proud I am of @IAmUltimatePred. For standing up, for speaking out, for givi… https://t.co/SKGiGzBiiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[iron veiled plebeians with too many followers Humans would be better off led by the blind]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just stepped in a big ass puddle cuz i was looking at my phone 😫  GREAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkipperChic @DonnieWahlberg @NKOTB I can’t stop watching this. It’s so funny 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 year ago today, I met the most amazing man ❤️ I’m so glad he approached me at the bar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting work done and eating at my favorite place. @ Oasthouse Kitchen + Bar https://t.co/CA9zDCo2fc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackGirlHockey I was happy to see this handle exist. I’m a long time ice hockey fan (Go Flyers!) who has long bee… https://t.co/4B6RdqD39z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liz_emmmm I agree! I rarely get symptoms, but when I do, it’s heartburn 🤦🏻‍♀️😂 other than that pregnancy has been… https://t.co/TpXlJayH9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Stone Delicious IPA by @StoneBrewing @ Joe's Station House Pizza Pub — https://t.co/sd7bCqIRw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[FLOOD THREAT: 3-6 inches of rain possible through the weekend. That’s the amount of rain we normally get in a whole… https://t.co/CzYRoW7GSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Awww shucks she did beat you the first time by more than 3 million votes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought that P.M. cannot get a pardon from SDNY. Is this true? Also, is this was a conservative favor by the judg… https://t.co/ozyLoz95aa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for @hartfordcourant to put @UConnMHOC on the front of the sports section. Third huge win at home last nigh… https://t.co/GDnIDQUnKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyPolice are looking for 1 of 2 men who stole a car with a 5 year old boy in the back seat in West Philadelphi… https://t.co/ucKCEVZy7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is advocating murder because of how someone communes with God. Vile!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow I’m late posting was in the hospital Day #7 I will post everyday until I get tickets or my health get… https://t.co/ZWxq59BhcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day!!! @ Soldier CreekElementary School https://t.co/qYtQRSC0xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Callie390 @emmap72002 @TeenMom @ChelseaHouska Well Adam is changing again it's hard to get out of that deep hole h… https://t.co/8Vdy9NessQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wangawoman @beamondiv I’m HOLLERING!!!!  Twitter is not READY!  I’m SCREAMING!!! #YouWin #Insidejoke #LifeandTimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really can not fuck with light skins, they do nothing but annoy tf outta me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei @JaxsonAgincourt I am going with BOTH are #Liars and all bets are off on why the meeting was cut short… https://t.co/6qhuQ5gpYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randi_hubbard @OkaWolfpack looking at different Virtual Field Trips for her kinder classroom #CotsenELC2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[DILEMMA: een levenslang gratis first class vliegen of altijd gratis eten in restaurants? Wat zou jij kiezen? Ik zag… https://t.co/fQ8lsy0Yiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Yes he is but everyone that follows him is corrupt also. They are afraid of flooding power and money. They… https://t.co/aJEFheXJv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite things, I present to you. Some are old, some are new. Some are shiny, some a royal purple hue. Without… https://t.co/1yVBzkYz8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TayJaneGC @GeneticCouns There will be lots of processing going on in your head this week - enjoy! ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliantinaFans @barbara_lopez21 Ganaste barbie te lo dije ayer que eso era tuyo felicidades 🎊🎉🍾🍑🍑🍑🍑🍮🍮🍮♥️♥️👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻… https://t.co/7tTSSv29RS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My day: @PB_Kingstowne ✔️  #LTB #PBKMarchMadness   @Starbucks ☕️☕️☕️ #caffeinate #momlife   @DuckDonuts 🍩🍀… https://t.co/rQU9eyzrmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have an occasion? This is your dress 😍 Graduation, wedding guest, or Easter! It’s under $60 and runs TTS! I am wear… https://t.co/HP73D6w5Lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vBsVqnIji8. @sengop. I suppose that’s how Clinton felt, nice that ya’ll were so forgiving with him 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone: are you working on any special projects this year? Me: I’m gonna buy a @Starbucks bagel from every store i… https://t.co/ts3EQll40F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some folks hate and envy is stronger then common sense.  This will ruin you everytime]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TRUMP2020 @realDonaldTrump @VP Looking forward 2020.  You will continue to do a GREAT job for our country and the… https://t.co/IcAj9jtZAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[41-year-old Joseph Sisemore faced a judge this morning. He’s accused of having sexual intercourse with his daughter… https://t.co/5rMyPPegi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatScarletMoth That's so amazing and inspiring! Yeah my husband is back at Riot again and I'm currently doing the… https://t.co/8G8C3Fb1IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shyaannnn same!! usually my chin and cheeks :( i hate forehead acne cuz it's where you can see the easiest cuz of the wrinkle lines :(((]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tantramar Most people that I did advertising campaigns for I’ve found want to advertise what they want to see rath… https://t.co/MHcrEUop6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude, I’m from the back end of the Pong era..  was a Space Invaders Master on the Atari — until my neighbor got a C… https://t.co/3rYehsVA49]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to be at #movethedial to celebrate #IWD2019 🎉 feelin like a BOSS today with all these badass womyn and f… https://t.co/lbOZnBYYF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[People ask me to watch there stuff when they leave. How are they sure they can trust me(a complete stranger)????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eloncomm @W2OGroup @KetchumPR @WeberShandwick @gs_comms @taylorstrategy @FinsburyGlobal @Fleishman @EPCo… https://t.co/XL5tRiFP2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dutch_disciple It happens to us all evan!!! 💕💕 always here for you love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[De saco cheio da galera passar pano pra esse cara. Não é de hoje que ele faz merda e sempre é convidado para os eve… https://t.co/jCObkNrMEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pgh_law @PLB1931 @ElizLanders @SpeakerPelosi @VP @GOP @IlhanMN @SteveKingIA @davidaxelrod @davidfrum @DavidCornDC… https://t.co/YtGm73WwDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate it when my stomach sounds like a creaking door from a horror film]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyContentSucks2 What does cleaning your face have to do with being gay? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickyDavilaH Y qué pague la multa eso dice el código de policía aprobado por Santos tomen pa que lleven.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bf was talking Spanish in his sleep the other night so long story short I think I’m going to invest in Rosetta S… https://t.co/ZYGBCnC59B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living on one of the busiest highways in this town with the county snow plow shop literally a 1/2 mile down the roa… https://t.co/PMFqqJ9DYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[smirk with me. funny sayings | Tumblr #laughter #chuckle #grin #merry https://t.co/1G0AWp8IYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[💪🏻 Five Fabulous Females on 🔥= Fearless, Fantastic &amp; FUN to FOLLOW 💪🏻😊🙌🏻 Thank you @Cisco @gerri_elliott… https://t.co/sLCxPNeRdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReingsPalak @Reignsgirl2012 @HypeSista @IAmTravaughn @sarthak_khavdu @ImGabyMtz @IJoybanks1947 @pjtownse1999… https://t.co/0wQHBvi5T4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Screaming “ i need weed “ in the middle of bourbon street did not help me acquire weed tonight Incase anyone was wondering ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump jr, just saw you on Fox News at CPAC. You’re great and you be in line to run for President when your d… https://t.co/81sUfUNNRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jentechnology @CoriOrlando1 @billselak @LAMBRADLEY Super fun.....and done! #CUE19 #CUEYearbook]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StefaniaL1 Buongiorno Stefania. Grazie e spero che avere una buona Domenica anche te cara amica.😘❤️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 me too.  tho I don't think it would look good in the context of this testimony,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shoko55mmts I'm choosing Hibanni for Pokémon Sword, and Messon for Pokémon Shield. (Sorry if you can't read this.… https://t.co/Pfm607pm4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I resonate with your dad’s statement bc I also attended boarding school between 2010-2014 in Flagstaff. There were… https://t.co/9F8r4M43v0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@georgedrascon and i taking on NYC together is gonna be iconic. Be ready for the cutest IG pics]]></document></documents></author>