<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Me and my girl plan to stay to the end  Hope there never comes a day where we better as friends We in a marathon we… https://t.co/ROYKxDyh7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safetylawyer1 @smerconish @CNN @cnni @JoeBiden @amieparnes @sunraysunray @Sen_MimiStewart @hiltzikm @DiDimond Penc… https://t.co/68UbqHWrlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA https://t.co/XqkJUw5k5J https://t.co/3hYnqD2Z1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[the first thing I’m doing when i move into an apartment is getting a cat]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think it’s a coincidence that Year 3000 and Kids of the Future were on the same album? The Jonas Brothers we’re… https://t.co/jVSPmCBr4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoniLove love the show. Please be advised that there is no such word as supposably, the word is supposedly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therookiedad @lunchboxdad Haha! I’m glad mine are in school. We have about 3 inches and now that the sun is out it… https://t.co/sVRmyH6oJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spivcom @ProudResister @realDonaldTrump You’re a fornicating imbecilic moron—hell—let’s compare lies!   How many p… https://t.co/LmXujw6off]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st place! 💪🏼💙🤼‍♂️🥇 #perrymeridianthorntonstrong2019 #FWC @ Perry Meridian High School https://t.co/iNgNz8l5x2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a photo from September that my friend took professionally outside of Chain Reaction and when I look at a phot… https://t.co/sBufeahV26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanTonelson @twitchyteam California's high speed rail succeeded in doing what it always was intended it to do- it… https://t.co/Oc5KI0L0N7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my man was having a moment and I just start crying out of nowhere and he stops everything and lays me on him… https://t.co/RTNOireANq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorRomney It’s ppl of demonic followings, it’s killers of babies, God’s creation, &amp; they all will have to answer to God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m re watching ‘Narcos Mexico’ and every time Diego Luna comes on I just wanna... https://t.co/qEsz9gwX5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day of learning with our teams! #collectiveefficacy #teamworkmakesthedreamwork @wareitis13 @RandelJulia… https://t.co/XTKQ3qvcyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s a DAIRY cow. It’s her job to produce milk like this. Her utter can hold up to 40 pounds of milk and that’s ou… https://t.co/p7EXkyXFuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to take some zzquil so if there anyone out there that’ll like to confess their undying love for me .. it’… https://t.co/HrYu2zmJ8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s time for Mikaela to take one of her oftenly-practiced, spontaneous road trips to the beach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh good so our recycling isn't even being recycled that's good to know. https://t.co/6PI8HV6x9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little Valentines Day fun on my Avaya Vantage at work. https://t.co/nJe8Pov2GK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Julian Castro was in charge if HUD Ben Carson now heads that department. He found 500 billion missing from this dep… https://t.co/ZVktFB2wml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anne_theriault @Drunk_Austen Think of it as a humility block (quilting reference!) for an A+ tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I take a shower at night I think, “Trish, you are going to be so pleased with yourself tomorrow morning.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume @howiedubz Oh sequins, shiny objects. Oh golly bright colors I can look at. Neato. Goes with the Jimmy Ch… https://t.co/9bCFvCjY2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pay attention to how this man speaks. Beyond the dumb shit he’s saying. Watch how she can’t get more than 5 words o… https://t.co/GEzBYEShXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_UnSilent_ #NPD #narcissist has a strong familial  genetic component. Just sayin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at all the peer to peer recognition for February!! Time to start all over and do it again!! #1549proud… https://t.co/UoDk7kptMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natalieast I don't disagree. But want to point out that when bloggers add a disclaimer that something is "not spon… https://t.co/elag6D4E1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanReynolds The person who recently dragged you down has gate-kept what is considered “real music” for over a deca… https://t.co/78nvFBv7ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alert Call Congress 202-224-3121.@amvetsupport @VetsUnitedMarch @naretevduorp @joefaz @george_capen @Brasilmagic… https://t.co/gexXqtJpGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau This voter who supported you is deeply disappointed in the recent conduct of your government and wil… https://t.co/5BsZ7RdSJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burk_molly @Logan_McCrummen Plus they’ll be able to see you anywhere in Harry’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Metrolinx  says trial of “kids ride free” in Barrie line , led to a 17% increase in weekend ridership- resulting… https://t.co/Qn0PoqEo1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the 7 day book cover challenge from @MsBPope ! I’ll post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations or… https://t.co/7ZGtASAamw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eyeslikebadu As long as the are no hurricanes or tornadoes. A lot of communities limit where you can put them, if at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@academicfangirl @221Bcrow @LoveBug54 I would assume the escape room is really heavily geared towards the more casual fan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just my saw my first @WTofficial concert and it was such a dream come true. They played my favorite song the heart of everything 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always regret leaving my contacts in while sleeping. But I’m too lazy to take them out. Plus my nails suck]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my @cofc student @leahcimpham for his 1st published writing in the forthcoming @antholegacies! His essa… https://t.co/6aOU2Dlroe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carpediemeire @Primabl_ @ExploreThePrime @FolderRed @RoamingIrishman @AOAOxymoron @Abfabtravels @StromfieldAdvs… https://t.co/ev4NBRCEeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShamrockGen @ggirltalks As a conference planner, I want to know who’s new for research/speaking on diversity and l… https://t.co/RTDkpe9L0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is energy , BreathE careful. @ San Francisco Bay Area https://t.co/1eOF4qG3PJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@HowardSchultz kicking off his talk with @DylanByers at #sxsw. https://t.co/h1R7PiVXNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[best spot in la to edit photos &amp; question if i’m good enough to be doing so lol https://t.co/3KxwENar07]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great way to start my morning! Sitting at a large roundtable of amazing people at @PPact Planned Parenthood Latino… https://t.co/dECdnOQamm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost pitaya.photodesign with repostsaveapp    ・・・   🎥 #Repost @paola41703celia with get_repost ・・・ Commercial vi… https://t.co/ZIcnvPA0wr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zomabroc @ProudResister @realDonaldTrump I see those who attempted a Coup being indicted n sent away to prison for a really long time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Court orders judge to reconsider his decision to deny a name change for transgender kid. https://t.co/tg4Zjlzmls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Francis39847829 Denuncian, pero el Gobierno FrenteAmplista tiene mayoría, sabe?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valley residents about to take off from @NatButterflies toward the border to highlight the border wall’s impact on… https://t.co/lrsEqpdQwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from  @Mmatp to post covers of 1 favorite book each day for 7 days: no explanations or… https://t.co/wZkLWzTC87]]></document><document><![CDATA[glad y’all gave me the go-ahead i rly cannot go back to the doctor to ask his opinion, i was just there a week ago… https://t.co/PnCKCvKkCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[...not even listening to music in my headphones is drowning out my dads snoring rn SOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pregaming the week: Sunday at Space with Frank Orrall @ Space https://t.co/Ytak8NUxMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ciara_anna #NicomaineAt24  HAPPY 24'th BIRTHDAY MAINE! GGOD BLESS YOU MORE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning from Colorado’s legalization of marijuana @bunkybun @BlakandBlack @lilith2u @KittyBhagat @ChrisFDonahue… https://t.co/tl1YWkJwfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahouraxo @gl3nnc4rt3r A few years ago I would have said this is impossible! But with the Orange one in office I d… https://t.co/EFT0Ut7kkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look what came in the mail!! @EAST_TRAUMA #donate https://t.co/PEnfyTM1r5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisWeekABC Well, first of all, there is no defense.  And second, the Republicans should be defending the Constitu… https://t.co/mSbERfgDLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO MIDDLE NAME: The Complete Collected Jack Reacher Short Stories by Lee Child is only $2.99 on #Kindle:… https://t.co/J2Li2khWyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[And people asked why I voted for Kevin de Leon instead of Feinstein again. #GreenNewDeal https://t.co/DP2katDS0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s currently an hour into my 9 hour shift and in that first hour a customer made me super uncomfortable and i ref… https://t.co/sjNhbAQo1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@welcomet0nature Sadly, this not nature; poor thing is trapped behind glass!😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliima @DonaldLawrence @kanyewest Stop being judgmental@charlima. Who are you to decide when or how another per… https://t.co/f2X6RMC7GG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerrySu13121981 @beatamk Czepiasz się. Uważasz że dwa "homiki" mają większe prawo wypowiadania się w sprawie rodziny?...]]></document><document><![CDATA[If grapegatherers come to thee, would they not leave some gleaning grapes? if thieves by night, they will destroy t… https://t.co/AEZHqM32zF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Nature is always full of surprises this is a reflection of the #sunrise on the #frozen #pond . The strip you see a… https://t.co/tSNqJmksOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity So we knew this would happen.  More immigrants heading out. To U.S. Democrats say no wall. What happen… https://t.co/neBsIzaMlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring forward that means spring is almost here!!! Happy Monday Loves🌸💋🌺 @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/1tCXa8AVrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoudenSwain1 @ndaustin @RobBenedict @Innocuous_Flop @BorjaBorja1 @Billy_Moran See you there...for both shows!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ow, my bunion!” Is something I just said because I’m apparently now 87 years old]]></document><document><![CDATA[And trust me on the fact that I did care and love you like you were a sister to me but than you decided to attack m… https://t.co/eDjSnouJJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbaradye921 Why dont you take her to register and then when it's time to vote take her with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedcruz you worthless Skally wag! Now you KNOW I’m a Constituent! @JohnCornyn VOTE FOR H-8. It’s time for both of… https://t.co/wg3xALORGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m warnin y’all now. From personal experience, don’t let her drive your car...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IgniteMyFuture’s lesson “Drone Delivery” presented by Learning Leader: @estrickteach. @DiscoveryEd @tcs_na… https://t.co/rVhttDFGaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next time someone says #fanfiction isn't real writing, remind them of the fact that people like Shakespeare did… https://t.co/tot7LVU9gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌇Con Sue Photography and Design🌃  🏙Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌆  🏙This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/2eRtK1jRUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soaring into wind makes a happy Prince 👑 #autismmom #autisminspires @ Mountain Creek Vernon Peak https://t.co/8HafS4ifay]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I asked my mom about going to the lake and she started blowing up about finding an internship 😕🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[the fact that the night king just made the dragon a wight just pissed me all the way off]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT’S COLLEGE THURSDAY! ————————————- Free yoga all day for College students with valid LOCAL College ID! See you so… https://t.co/gP34Ql0xoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop trying to fix us, fix me and you. Cause we don't need fixing we just need someone new.”  - @benjtrillado]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let go of: ~ the fear of failing. ~ the quest for perfection. ~ doing it all. ~ comparing yourself. ~ I’ll be happy… https://t.co/ncxvj7CEZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tulilam PiS uważa, że nauka jest gorsza od pedofilii! Zauważyłam, że ci, którzy protestują przeciw LGBT bronią ks. Jankowskiego.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcfunny @urbanx_f @drnik614 @SueQuez @RebeccaLardner @doritmi @jsjohnson_mdphd @mmelgar09 @Just4TheCause… https://t.co/mEGG2ixzWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayBVB @ChrisABiersack I've made some life long friends thru the group chat we all met on the official bvb group ran by Dan and chloe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Mentorship Monday!  Super Proud of this One @reeonmone Reeona Curseen. She has continued to work hard and purs… https://t.co/Y1gLl4LKn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[OneHunnid Music LLC Presents  Young Hevn: I Use To  Between Blessings Coming soon! #musicians #upcomingartist… https://t.co/XbmHNi5gw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraNiven @ruthhill74 @hallmarkchannel @hallmarkmovie Always love seeing Barbara Niven and have for years!!! So… https://t.co/A23ikYUK1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will always cry watching Billy Elliot. ❤️ #BillyElliot https://t.co/tvOmFQ5p9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonasbrothers @ElvisDuranShow @elvisduran @Z100NewYork What a wake up call! 😃 Happy Friday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HappySeminarian Yes! Granted I did not have the best taste in men two years ago.  Honestly, it’s not so much a pro… https://t.co/YWwcLlPTBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @GOP @SenateGOP @HouseGOP tell me again how your party cares for the elderly, the poor and the sick. But… https://t.co/e9ynIzWgDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Espectáculos Bonanza Tijuana presenta: GLADIADORES DEL VOLANTE: Demolición Total el próximo 31 de marzo en La Monum… https://t.co/1JHd52uFUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly—Trump Tried Every Possible ACTION To Work With Congress—EVEN A GOVT SHUT DOWN—STILL NOTHING—EO Is What’s Le… https://t.co/kjbPG6vqPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kindofmiserable @reynoblewrites @gerardway OMG. I’m watching this immediately]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusanSmythSL @MountWolseley Lovely enjoy...Sunshine in Ireland Wow....😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell Congress: Stop the sexual assault of migrant children and women under Trump. https://t.co/58T8Yjhy0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s your responsibility as a consumer to check your labels...there are no regulations on beauty labels...check to… https://t.co/nWXhzIPfuM]]></document></documents></author>