<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[.@SpeakerPelosi: Oppose the Trump admin's proposed changes to Medicare Part D to protect people living with HIV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Women’s Day everyday! 💪🏽👸🏽🙋🏽‍♀️#womensday2019 @ Pineville, North Carolina https://t.co/4Vle094wyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RewardMyShoppin @AcadiaNPS Was at the lobster festival last year! What a great and a delicious time !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 years ago I was prepping for the best baby shower I could have ever imagined.  One year ago we were prepping for… https://t.co/AylvCpSgsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UserBrice @sllkres @realDonaldTrump Huey Long was a governor of LA who was assassinated.  Also coined a dictator b… https://t.co/0I7YnBj0P5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4 of the book cover challenge - 7 books I love. No explanations. No reviews. Each time I post, I’ll challenge s… https://t.co/YUBlSvtQm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just went through 5 years of unread emails. This is the first time I’ve had 0 new messages since I created my email.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CallMeAlhaji I would have been in that video if it weren’t for your intricate leg movement 😤💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4YrsToday @AltFawn Evil Demonrats😈 KKK dont believe in God ! https://t.co/zXLi5JGhYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! I’ll be joining @foxandfriends at 7:15am ET to talk about the Dems inability to denounce @IlhanMN’s a… https://t.co/gj4DT8jzpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have been working on literary essays for a month. Like step by step from reading the story to outline to finding… https://t.co/wUBQHuL7LL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby at home: *loosing my mind*   begging for someone to help  Goes to baby sitter for a couple hours:  *crying hys… https://t.co/CGJlVy0T9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a goal!!!!! When I tell you how happy I am for Andreas you never no idea!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I do a “guess your age” quiz they think I’m in my 60’s... wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC weather is wild I'll be wearing a thick jacket scarf and fuzzy hat and some people out here with short sleeves… https://t.co/c3Uby0NGGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#red4ed 🍎 #fightforeducation #everyonecounts @ Texas State Capitol https://t.co/YrRdEKqwXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lolll. Add this to the list of why I should’ve seen that my ex was fucking psychopath.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you realize people don’t get this platform since they keep retweeting their own replies and not understand why… https://t.co/vThLtnbfJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My job while I’m in with the president at any event is to try to capture the most storytelling photograph.” Excell… https://t.co/TWgwBMmvGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EileenS71495521 @ATXBengal @realDavidCahn @thistallawkgirl Plus I think you would get the idea pretty quickly if s… https://t.co/kQAvVIzqjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomthunkitsMind She is a disgusting creature that feeds on lies. She is NOT a Christian because she lies so easily… https://t.co/qfD4xwIAsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM CRYINGGGGGGGG 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take the time to do what you love! I have worked so hard all week getting my book launched. I’ve started before the… https://t.co/mLajc7nsvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[These gorgeous Depression Glass Objects are going to be in our Thursday Sale this week!!!  The PREVIEW has started… https://t.co/c1PGSp2FWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscars In Memoriam Snubs Include Stanley Donen, Carol Channing, Sondra Locke and Verne Troyer https://t.co/QHZLsTe02t via @SFGate]]></document><document><![CDATA[I eat some weird shit for breakfast but this crap is nasty, it's smells. https://t.co/rbyddTjtKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[last week I was having a conversation about sports with a prospective student and his mother goes: “no offense, but… https://t.co/5OuFkFHbp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like everything else she has said, it is not thought through. I'm tired of talking about her, but we have to becaus… https://t.co/82muxTtDl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@komonews @ConnieKOMO: @UPS has a rumored system outage affecting many in Seattle. They're blaming the snow for mas… https://t.co/qm7aPFh59W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusiB348 @rickkinley @brit_ritchey @geekhomestead @patchfarmstead @Pickwickshephrd I didn’t mean food production.… https://t.co/6FR8tLxFKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating International Women’s Day in a pretty cool spot #HappyWomensDay2019 https://t.co/lLEVQIO4x7]]></document><document><![CDATA[They have Trump to help them heal, from all the crap the democracts feed them to keep them suppressed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benFranklin2018 This is one of Putin’s plans to destabilize America. Trump is helping him along in every way. It’s terrifying and reviling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Americans keep listening to Crooked Hillary Clinton; they deserve what they get...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Protecting Gotham is tiring work.  #batman #Tishtopia #fiveweeksold #daddydressedme @ Novato, California https://t.co/LRrwjPGAra]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you doctor sends you to @LABCORP and the lady at the front desk yells at you through the glass “YOU GOTTA SIGN… https://t.co/EPhi65SP0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reasons why I would travel to the most isolated place on this planet are quite extensive.  #The39steps… https://t.co/X1p1irUSXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can officially say that no one ended up in a better situation after doing some foul shit to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinnieBoccWGHP @WCAX_Dom I just wore that dress at our movie premiere! What a timely throwback. 😊 MISS YOU ALL and… https://t.co/ZOpdc53cfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unproblematic?? She really made a song called “break up w your girlfriend, I’m bored” she really married someone fo… https://t.co/lRK62p3SgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hazelnut is actually better than French vanilla but y’all ain’t ready to have that conversation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilibellmia @LadyRedWave No it should not!! Dang if my tax dollars need to go for that. One man one woman was made… https://t.co/UEjbQOn75h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWTravelChat @KaraDiDomizio @wildheartedblog A2. Yes. I lived in Togo from 2007-10 and during that time I also vis… https://t.co/gWicSmM2Hc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ange_Amene They are gonna have to do it. Frankly she needs to be put in her place]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristieGolden I don't like wine, can I substitute some Rum Chata instead?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lamenting low appearance of law enforcement agents in Oyo meanwhile in Rivers they don't want to see law enforcemen… https://t.co/HiEvOKGWWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comunicado de John Bolton en el que advierte a las instituciones financieras extranjeras que “enfrentarán sanciones… https://t.co/OrYn9TDFVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiatoSM @PPLosAngeles Congratulations and thank you all you do in the community!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gah my iPhone screen is being touchy with this dang baby lotion I have on my hands]]></document><document><![CDATA[This verse of “Come and Find the Quiet Center” rocks me every time I sing it. Every. Single. Time.   “In the Spirit… https://t.co/vhtni7Qp1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi...old white guy here...remind me why @ImAngelaBassett didn’t get the @TheAcademy Award for What’s Love Got to Do… https://t.co/kZyxYjwWBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael to the docs when picking out the sperm to father his children: I want a HE-HEE and a SHEE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunset #chisosbasin #bigbendnp @ Chisos Mountains Lodge - Big Bend National Park https://t.co/IG9XguKURr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my favorite human❤️ love you more than anything, even Nutella. Have a great day babe😘… https://t.co/6myDtvDZ6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimpsonRasheem ur family is such a blessing to me. i’m thankful for you guys &amp; the bond we have 💘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lori Erickson representing @SPPS_OEL and school based early learning programs all across our state so well. Thank y… https://t.co/hXQYhCYYQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am watching the #3rdhourtoday and love it.  An entertaining and #diverse panel and great content!  I would love t… https://t.co/J5yhylOfKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferNBC4 Thanks Jennifer i met you a few times with the rescue puppies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Night 2 of making myself cry. I decided to watch My Girl and I will never get over Thomas J’s death 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ibyshire Nevermind. It took me longer than necessary to realize this is just French toast made using banana bread.… https://t.co/yhzaWWx95T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi You and your democratic thugs are destroying America!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#stadiumseries #wewon #finally #flyers @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/stwAunu8X8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me:                                The garbage:                          ↗️my mental health↘️      ↗️… https://t.co/xZNrX2jHhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to forgive you for the way you left us. I’m trying to forgive myself for not reaching out often enough. Happy birthday Pete Malet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bastilledan Eh, I’m still sick and have a bunch of tests to grade and then report comments to write. The joys of teaching! How’re you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up to $3.9 million! Looks like it's finally slowing down.  44 days to go! #critters #criticalrole]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Democrats want to control America but it will never happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $60 Spotify Gift Card Offer    Enter Your Email Id And Complete A Simple Sign Up To Win $60 Spotify Gift C… https://t.co/JIoCQu9dLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trent_PhD Man. I wish. So far this is my only complaint and I kinda knew before I got here but now I just cannot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wheels up on this #delicious #duo in #march2019 more info to come but be warned @whitneysmelton and I will sex you… https://t.co/ontqQtHMey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulieD55 @CharlieD2749 @HillaryClinton should be in panic mode because if they go after our Oresident for somethi… https://t.co/vgnYpiW1lr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slider Track &amp; Field is ready for Day 1 of the Conference AA meet! @SLIDER_PE_WSMS  🏃🏽‍♂️🐎🏃🏽‍♀️… https://t.co/bYiTcLssic]]></document><document><![CDATA[something I learned this week: you really are as happy as you choose to be]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is getting out of hand! I feel that anyone NOT born in the U.S. should not be allowed to run for office. Peopl… https://t.co/kv8xedfos7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the Monday after daylight savings is also the Monday after your birthday and also Mercury is doing its retrogr… https://t.co/Hk9TME3DB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might not be sure of what I want right now but I’m definitely sure of what I don’t want.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday's @CITGOiaOLLE STEM showcase was pretty awesome🙌. I met some young @aliefstem entrepreneurs!… https://t.co/ompYXwktAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharronBaron I really liked this design so hard to have them!! happy you like! thanks for saying!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @AustinWalker82 on your promotion to VP of Public Policy at @STLRegChamber. Couldn’t be more proud… https://t.co/eP59r1SnRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having your day ruined at work &amp; having to finish your shift is honestly the worst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crissfresh @GeekDudes Technically it isn’t a voltron wannabe when it predates voltron by 6 years in japan. So tech… https://t.co/YIYQu3hJET]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched @_maddienadine11 snap story like 20 times... I’m about to cry, my heart cannot handle]]></document><document><![CDATA[love you so much Austin💜💜 thank you for all the great memories https://t.co/2q48UcPFUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Preston Lakes, Frisco, Texas https://t.co/Ms8z88zPkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marlett29 Your right if they aren’t doing jack shit or even trying to better themselves by going to school or anyt… https://t.co/iScXDaKbs2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassandraSeven Impossible to hide your identity once you decide to join any social   format]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dune_Tatooine @ponygal1986 @HamillHimself @MaraRanger @YodaForces @maka_gh @CassyC2107 @anne_lindor @RossowDoris… https://t.co/QOcKNeIUOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Microsoft Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/k7ADrVdUJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #FortSmith, AR job and click to apply: Associate Financial Analyst - https://t.co/1dQ6m9rg8u #Finance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand Take guns away ? Let’s take your reproductive parts away to STOP YOU FROM MURDERING BABIES it is les… https://t.co/7YJxOmCvzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeDavisRB Happy Birthday Blessings Mike! Congrats on another trip around the sun!✨💫⭐️🌝🌟 #27]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pray POTUS shuts down  asylum until laws are changed. I don't know why he hasn't!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winellroad Haters gonna hate, Kate 🤷🏻‍♀️ Just brush those haters off https://t.co/9uNKrytN1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss Iceland so bad!!! As soon as I got there it felt like I had finally arrived somewhere I was meant to be like… https://t.co/tOybAcretU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lefteris_VR @tushy_com @ParisWhiteXXX @BrooklynGrayXXX @NaomiBluexXx @StacyCruz_Xxx @jewelsvalxxx @MissLacyLennon… https://t.co/gN60rz7Klv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scarbsteve @shannonrwatts thank you for bringing reaity to this sentimentalmoralityolympics]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@bizzabo found that nearly 70% of professional event speakers are male. Today they’re doing something about it!… https://t.co/vlCxZgTM9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManuelBartlett @FelipeCalderon Calidad moral... https://t.co/Zhnsw9kjuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DeepThoughtsOnYourDeathBed My cheap ass brother in law never did pay back the money he “borrowed”. Bastard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an awesome time with a room full of rock stars today at the @WomensNetworkMO luncheon.    Loved serving as you… https://t.co/AnL5aNYkQA]]></document></documents></author>