<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@1ChocolateGypsy @idrispayne @amanialx Mannnn the poop shoot makes me laugh every time @Pace93til]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pb6980 2019 cutz at hairtwothere #barberconnect #razorsharpcuts #hair2there #barberbeast #razorsharplines🔥🔥💈💯❗️ @… https://t.co/aNNINatiuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyBReggae Too commercialized. The problem is conscious artists falling into this trend. It’s the new thing an… https://t.co/pDIrArUFd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Step back just a few years and getting a message out nationally meant paying $100Ks to a newspaper or TV station, l… https://t.co/z3i2nZDl3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3dTanny @alienslacker Love the support for the FTC team. I help out Team 94 a FRC team. Great programs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In One Politian and Police. " A Secluded Area With Hundreds of Units is the Future. I believe Like People Should li… https://t.co/HytHeI8ioT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crumley_kevin @ChadNJensen Those later round QB’s are a mirage. For every Russ Wilson there is 75 Charlie Whitehus… https://t.co/phIUxwFIXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/kb1rfhYSgf Verizon Wireless Customer Service 1-855-431-6111 is ours #Verizonwirelesscustomerservice… https://t.co/J5NX04jd3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the ever did the Running Man moving what republican asshole could we get to fill the Richard Dawson role?  That’… https://t.co/hX5p84ngix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delsina363 Na, the dude is a perv. The fact that you defend a man associating with little boys is beyond me. https://t.co/gJlbWF4umy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good bye Nike swoosh this ]! @ Newport Beach, California https://t.co/rcy6ljaOOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poll: How do you feel about the Browns signing RB Kareem Hunt? | Browns Wire via @thebrownswire https://t.co/PWBKkgtCHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[DRC breaking news -- UNT  wide receivers coach Joel Filani is leaving the staff to coach outside receivers at Texas… https://t.co/CeuAXY3Jmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your pastor uses a Lord of the Rings analogy in closing. @davebjornolson https://t.co/r5rRwnkiX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifesafeast @_thisiscarter @jpodhoretz @IlhanMN @JewishWorker The problem with attributing this particular antisem… https://t.co/BDaWwQtd49]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hbo brought out a whole choir for their #forthethrone blood donation event here at #sxsw @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/CYo6TmzKR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski Trump's July 4th buffet table: Quarter-pounders, KFC and Diet Coke. Embarrassing to have an idiot as POTUS, sad! #HoldTheDate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@el_diamante3 I know for a fact @andyblarsen and @E_Woodyard will do a better job than that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreamShakeSBN @SpaceCity_Scoop @UHBigRedHatGuy Can you name 2 players still on the buyout market that would play m… https://t.co/cSsJ2Mep3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReignOfApril I totally agree! GDT won last year so him presenting Director was happy coincidence... but Samuel L.… https://t.co/KqnkHOqFIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[of a girl wears a watch and it aint a rolex shes no good its either wear a rolex or dont]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love these Gals! #Friends #ThisIsForever #HT500 #WayBack @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/h05z1EUzqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then he should put out plans for the young people who are too young to vote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crossbar for #Avs captain Gabriel Landeskog with 6:29 left in first period]]></document><document><![CDATA[May I present the latest member of the @GroundhogClub....3 year old Emma from New Jersey! @weatherchannel… https://t.co/faTElDXyMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta remember the guys with the good advice @ The Artistic Home Ensemble https://t.co/uPe3AJ3uvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's the aincrad style. - (@BrycePapenbrook) Kirito | Best quotes in episode 03. #SwordArtOnlineAlicization #Toonami]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow More likely, senate republicans against Trump are actual patriots!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#repost from nuestrabellezaus  -  Ashley was ready to hit the buffet to celebrate her victory as Nuestra Belleza US… https://t.co/FCWahjKleI]]></document><document><![CDATA[grin like you mean it. Bwa ha ha haa...they don't call me Jerk Magnet for nuthin!  ; ) https://t.co/eJMuZXzSiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R439878 The guy was wrong. He lied, as a conservative do you speak out when the Prez lies. This guy fooled people,… https://t.co/1aBgAt6uKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the profile by @MikelleStreet, Fame reveals her Drag was borne from “the mother [she] never had.”   https://t.co/l5tC73nYiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 9 year old just got double connect four on me #dadlife #amaro #connectfour @ Connecticut https://t.co/nQirxmuBnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RheaRipley_WWE @EddieOrengoWWE @MiaYim If she is the HBIC what does that make you now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@verizon Verizon, why are you not doing anything about the crazy amount of spam calls your customers are getting!… https://t.co/ouPIiII5eT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every priest that puts ashes on people's heads today either raped a kid or knew priests raping kids. #AshWednesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine walking to your car on a warm summer’s day and out of nowhere this giant mf start flying towards you]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread made me cry. THIS is why I want to get into social work. THANK YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobMSheehan is a fucking star. That is the primary takeaway from #UmbrellaAcademy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been playing a lot more #Starlink today. It murders the #Switch battery, but has great gameplay! My only thing are… https://t.co/JV3H0Ym1Ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought into the hype of an ⁦@away⁩ bag. Big mistake. I was wasn’t allowed to board (held at the gate for 1 1/2 hour… https://t.co/1GTjTKy6EW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ Ayton. At least try to block the shot. Jrue just goes right by and hits a lay up on you? Wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Au 5 à 7 de la 9e édition du Rendez-Vous des Entreprises de #Gatineau de la @CCGatineau. Nous avons de supers entre… https://t.co/liiQFQUSxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just want to point out Melo averaged over 20ppg in FOURTEEN STRAIGHT SEASONS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traderjohnt1 @ShawnG927 Lincoln was a Republican and that is the truth! Democrats have birth to the KKK!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonTrombetta @giantswfan Not Vernon and Jenkins. You only get back 18 million or so i you let those two go, I dont… https://t.co/RfHtajQICw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy came in and #stood next to me he is #sevenone feet #tall #bigfella @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/Esqy4UF90T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Running becomes so much easier when you’re not thinking about every step of the way every step of the way! 🏃🏻 🤜🏼💥🤛🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vwinstonv Y tú qué haces de amigote del asesino MADURO pase avalas las muertes de su pueblo.   Que mal q mal]]></document><document><![CDATA[And this one of the strange things about @Twitter.  Mystery purges.  i've been following @JackiSchechner for years,… https://t.co/sYtz04jvD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moochiepoodle can we pllllllllease have a sit and a beer at target field this summer????? https://t.co/C2Xe4Zm67F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent my entire day editing digital photos &amp; I’ve decided I’m only shooting film in NYC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: ICYMI: Home Depot hiring, a moneyed Grab and Kitty says Hello to Hollywood - San Francisco Chronic… https://t.co/k0wBsYe2aC]]></document><document><![CDATA[DON'T FORGET: Lejeune's 21-gun salute on President's Day is set for noon. The Globe will stream it live on Facebook. https://t.co/8sCuSeQAbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConceptualJames Since grey hairs generally don't recolorize, that may just mean you are losing your hair as a resu… https://t.co/yWNrL1LqHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kelsey Berreth’s parents spell out a possible motive in new court documents filed in wrongful death lawsuit.… https://t.co/hGLggyGbdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤷🏼‍♂️ ... #IAmHere - Drinking a Dadgum IPA by @RahrBrewing at @dfwairport  — https://t.co/40hOJpQeXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there is any method in the way I take pictures, I believe it lies in this. See the subject first.  -Bill Brandt… https://t.co/yHZfuCOGvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love being at Metropolitan High School. Great Town Hall for their 10 graders. Look at the students with perfect att… https://t.co/6LM8urRz7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Enrique_Rojas1 Yo no sabia que existía ese torneo Don, cuando fue la primera vez que jugaron y quien quedó campeón?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A really delightfully awkward sit down with Beck, Jim James, Vanessa Bayer, and others on this Jenny Lewis thing. It’s so great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump FIRED FOR LYING    AMAZING   THE PRESIDENT THAT LIES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KendallGPace I don't believe #txed teachers lack motivation. I think districts lack sufficient motivation/rewards… https://t.co/tBEJbhxvPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning family: And once the storm is over, you won't remember how you made it through - how you managed to su… https://t.co/D0zwoMuaTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the brighter side of things today. @NoahKahan released a new song 🖤🥂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to put the city on my back 🚫🧢 #NewProfilePic https://t.co/0hEGFdH2eZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well she left Bond Suss Racing in Denver NC making the longest tow to the NASCAR KN West Series Race at the Las Veg… https://t.co/OvZAbuCon8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews That's a very blind sided view of looking at it. But expect that from NBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmaustinyoung @jeffchu @UMChurch Is the disqualification in the sex out of wedlock, the abuse of power or both? (I… https://t.co/5whyqv1MhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happend to that guy who was speaking down on black men for not standing up for the gay community...still ain’t… https://t.co/zoNWxnjLK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like a Boss!! 🤣😂🤣 @realDonaldTrump , the reigning “Troll Champion of the World” 👑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when Rove thought Romney was going to beat Obama? Fun times, fun times]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VegasBorn: Gerard Gallant walks out of press conference after getting upset with media.   #NHLBruins 3, #VegasBorn… https://t.co/FCbIWprLJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk how was the movie last night?  Glad we could help point you in the right direction to get in :) https://t.co/ox2TV70H1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[It could still be Logan Wiley in the second game. Just going off the notes, fam.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to refinance my car. That interest rate and payment just too damn much. 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ratatouille is 12 years old in case y’all didn’t know https://t.co/zcBVjhgsQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[the best is yet to come don’t forget god always makes the right decisions 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex_wiley - Tangerine Dream 2 (Review) do you agree? Who should I review next? @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/8jLfhwLCr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I'm sitting next to Smokey and some friends. They don't know who Diego Rivera or Frida Kahlo were.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was briefly in the SF Chinese New Year Parade tonight when I really needed to cross the street and no cops were looking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 66/365 of “The One Year Uncommon Life Daily Challenge” by Tony Dungy and my reflections...  “Love is patient an… https://t.co/dnxEm2RArn]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Houston: light rain, 53°F 100% humidity, wind 19mph, pressure 1016mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black people were considered outcasts in the eyes of Ghandi and considered us as "untouchable".  https://t.co/NvIteR4idJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanBarreiroKFAN Down south by the Dells now, don't have eyes on MN weather like I did in Duluth. Did the weather t… https://t.co/pCbS1uiQdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felt pretty good to stream again. So good I wanted to update my background a bit. This will be my new background an… https://t.co/0GRCtEPfEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dreaming of that next big trip, but need a little extra cash? List your place on @Airbnb, earn money while you trav… https://t.co/YRA6vVA7mw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 90th birthday to the Morrison woman with the most sass! So wish I could be home stuffing my face with ice cre… https://t.co/sR8Yl6fGHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chadsh11 @deleonmels @ayemandamonreal Might have to join that bet of yours]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 word: "Rivalry"  Bryant: Molina's response to his St. Louis comments 'caught me off guard' https://t.co/huHdCBkRnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieTheCommish @I_Am_Turton @StevrayFl @CarlosOCSC @smokeyflarez They should never ask and just do it. That’s jus… https://t.co/JtkxvOMZyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd pay some serious cash to be able to walk around old school Disneyland in VR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UMichWTennis Living that Michigan life #Goblue 🎾☁️❄☃️🌬 https://t.co/rATBmEnZdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAndyFee @PresConoley @LBSUAthletics @halpinkr @ShaneyFink @lbsumvb Amen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonRFloyd I don't believe I've ever heard a German showtune... I plan to keep it that way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DIGESETT No es que lo van a presentar no es la presentarlo ante el MP y una multa ejemplar mas carcel]]></document><document><![CDATA[More than half of #bootcamps are career-preparation programs, while 35 percent are shorter courses that are less fo… https://t.co/euzouFvnyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Pilots win in OT with Quinn Green's 20th Goal of the year at 3:09 of the extra period! #NAHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was playing with the random in apex and sent a friend request ended up playing 5 games with him went  11,11 in kill… https://t.co/WiB9PEtV0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNRadio_Ali So making it so sub-par schools look better is different then just giving kids inflated grades so they feel good?]]></document></documents></author>