<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Sterling_65 @charlie_savage @DefendAssange I’m not sure I understand this comment?🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so thankful for my friends they truly help me through the toughest times...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make it 11 straight wins and an @A10MBB regular season title for @VCU_Hoops! The Rams opened the second half on a 2… https://t.co/ucygOFlGaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_Mealor I can’t believe what my ears just heard! Marry Summer......you are killing me! Ugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lamar University vs Northwestern State! Go Lamar! Keeping up with the scoresheet reminds me of HS! Lol @ Montagne C… https://t.co/CGbVZifrnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And because I’m a huge nerd, I tried my best to do her glare:  Kit Coleman was a pioneer for women in journalism, l… https://t.co/2vuGvZq3db]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marthamaccallum : Andrew McCabe has clearly contradicted himself when he said President Trump might be agent of Ru… https://t.co/Yp8gI5vKLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exploring in Tinker Town 🤖 #wearemg #VEXRobotics https://t.co/a2hFAHWKzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@minda33 @BizballMaury Yes. This doesn't always end well. Especially for women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spettypi You are an absolute apologist for Trump. Hated your minimizing of Cohen’s relationship with traitor Trump… https://t.co/ATiMl1E9H9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @andersoncooper I beg U, DO NOT trust gov w/your healthcare. Woman w/Wrkrs/Comp w/severed back waiting 2 years… https://t.co/mTt21x1AoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s going through someone’s mind when they tweet 💩 like this? Hi 👋🏻 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenluluthepug Woo Woo Lulu party hardy Happy Mardi Gras to you and poppy,have fun but be safe at your party😂😂Don… https://t.co/RTTY4QLBCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi prima se quedó a dormir y me acabo de despertar con su alarma, mi cel estaba en silencio, checo mi cel y tenía 7… https://t.co/D4LwRQZNYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday❗️😘 Beauties At The Beach 🏖  Potter’s House Women Retreat in Destin, FL:  22 of us... 👀… https://t.co/3OcXWxScMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjkm_717 @washingtonpost @realDonaldTrump Everyone’s favorite President would NEVER. Holy heck 😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como van a quemar 2 camiones con comida y cosas que necesita la gente? PANA QUE TIENEN EN LA CABEZA, NO TIENEN CORAZÓN?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A quick update from Cody Howershell about the #whiskeyrescue of the wayward @GlendaloughDist cask. As you can see,… https://t.co/JgHznQTpgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #SteveJobs! Check this out #DataCenters in #TysonsCorner #Virginia! You and I built it. Largest centers in the… https://t.co/4k8wDXK48h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro, Sabrina’s vibe was so chill. Honestly left a huge impression. I love that 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrKarlButton Maybe next year. I've already invested money into a trip with my family, so I'll reserve next year. H… https://t.co/TtJOBzvngS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosieOhDonald @pianopsycho2 @AOC *your *cerebral Doing better with punctuation. Remember: no space between the wor… https://t.co/rXIXPGf2zQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[voopootechofficial Rota Kit is the first spinning vape pod kit which with ergonomic and aesthetic design you can sp… https://t.co/Jy34XX7hie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenoritoCruz What if you made a video About how birthday parties were invented because the other day Cesar was asking about that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlushTribe @eyeroniclashes Can my entry please go to @xoBrittanyox91  please you would love to win this please!!… https://t.co/Hu6Dj2zkCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. Happy Monday to you. I hope everyone had a great weekend. https://t.co/U1ApYJivwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait for GOT,Winter is here finally,didn't know if I would be alive to watch the fnal shows,what's the word o… https://t.co/ffOmlBwLm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @realDonaldTrump @CPAC @ACUConservative @SalemMediaGrp STFU PLEASE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wind plays music through the window crack  Whistles and whine and sings back  A cold and wintery tune  About lo… https://t.co/TMDi4Obtqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation God Bless Them! My heart breaks for his family and friends! Thank you for your service and that you s… https://t.co/lyhmQYssot]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a meeting today with a couple who have been married 60 years,  husband says,” The reason I would go help my fath… https://t.co/14AfJbcHHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my god @NiallOfficial is at this pizza place in east Nashville??? Ummm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuddyPrinceton @realDonaldTrump There is no way that a wall can hurt the USA. I feel if someone does not want a wa… https://t.co/90qL3BGfkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get here EARLY for #RPDR11 with barbiesaddiction and stay for our sparkly new night VANITY! with madamejeuge servin… https://t.co/PHwFbTE0ZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherryl_holmes If you have sometime save sometime to stop by the #techbytes Room 229! #IBS2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelleFriedm2 @SarahPalinUSA Again you are wrong . Do some research . Trump said several time he was talking abo… https://t.co/kknzCckpmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resulta ahora que la #izquierda se cree dueña y única defensora de todas las causas sociales habidas y por haber de… https://t.co/i4iieghlfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 I watched cnn today for about twenty minutes and they believe there was Russian collusion. Bobble heads in agreement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PnPCBC @melaniejoly What about the whole buying-a-violent-dictator’s-son-Canadian-prostitutes thing, @melaniejoly? #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be a seeker of everyday magic 🍃🌞 #goodvibes #sunrise #nature #morningrun #reflections #sky #view #photooftheday… https://t.co/fo67dby68s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Very funny :) thank goodness for our Constitution. If you don't like it Russia and North Korea wou… https://t.co/WtYAojRsg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto @griviera Don’t bother asking her, just contact a divorce attorney right away. I will guarantee that th… https://t.co/E9W15Wd4dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation Curious.....how many calories does Deputy Carmack have to eat a day? Shep runs him like crazy 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda wanna sell my second shelf but I’d wanna charge probs somewhere between $80-$100 because of the original pric… https://t.co/tXtMqOq8A1]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dreams came true! @nellychillin came through with the juice💛💛 https://t.co/Tw9KYKTpst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Erie, PA? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/rdyhJp6tf3 #CustomerService]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing I love more than spending my Valentine’s Day getting hit on by a 34-year-old McDonald’s employee.… https://t.co/wV0cYge8Uh]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ladies and gentlemen, the brakes are pretty much shot on this plane and maintenance is coming to replace them. We… https://t.co/eAKe7NaTMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m old enough to remember when @mattgaetz not only threatened a witness through Twitter, but also made his presenc… https://t.co/XKfzWNtXWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pray for those who are considering having an abortion, that they might allow their child to live.  Our babies are t… https://t.co/l1AfJsSfci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Thank goodness - no more GOP complicit line of questioning.  Correction - no real questions asked - just badgering of the witness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phoenixfire2912 That's cause we know miss Jenn likes her some beers and some cas!!! Lol❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Subscribe to #MajorMusicTV on youtube link in my bio. Weekly instrumentals, beat making videos and pro audio gear t… https://t.co/be9R3IYHkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start your day with the best forms of nourishment. #readingcompanions #LoveYourPetDay https://t.co/9hukkOYHRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s like some flight or fight stuff but instead of those two options I was like “HIDE”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aftershokz is celebrating 🥳 until March 1st its customer happiness team by delivering happiness to all of their cu… https://t.co/YwN4YygyGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win a trip to Manchester to watch City take on Spurs Exclusive to CItyzens, sign up for free for your chance to win… https://t.co/JEluN2QmOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[ayyyyye who goes to UCLA and is willing to let me see Megan Thee Stallion in their place 😭😭😭 PLEASEEEEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mark_Lapping @elecporcupine @Biggybadass @therealwallbie @NicoMartelle @stradlemonkey @Brooksidefilms @BrianCBaer… https://t.co/UIvzGo8NFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing everyone a happy #PresidentsDay!!! @HempsteadTown  offices are closed today and will reopen tomorrow at 8 a.m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SD2usingmyvoice @JustJared @SamHeughan @caitrionambalfe Where are you getting this?  Cautiona was there with her f… https://t.co/i1Ch9v6nrU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxSportsSA What channel is the HS Girl's Final BB on and what website if my dad does not have that channel?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to hangout with high times growers and even test the flowers out this weekend I’m super lit 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every now and then I realize how lame I am and today it was buying a coffee just to make sure I can stay awake for a 7:30 movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillWineBanks I LOVE the idea.  ....but I can’t use my antique cameo for an earring. 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@everywhereist By far, one of my favorite movies. Their chemistry was fantastic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop talking about Abducted in Plain Sight and I think that it’s starting to affect my relationships becaus… https://t.co/a485874LP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 @saotaylor @MichaelCohen212 Already putting ur defense together?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw @Ebonyactor in this amazing play. @ MTC Theatre https://t.co/nlPn0kjzKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe this just happened!! Ryne Sandberg autograph right when we walked up to the stadium ❤️⚾️💙🐻… https://t.co/6jJeLz84H9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The days I work I want to sleep in, the days I’m off I can’t sleep longer than 6am...W. T. F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went out of town this weekend and I really missed my kitty (full grown cat, all adult animals are babies haha) Binx… https://t.co/ibZ0Ibiqb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they want to pay that amount over 10 yrs and call it a goal. I don’t see myself affording to go 100% solar/elec… https://t.co/ls2TSPVkN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HATE every unnnecessarily nasty person commenting on this. Please, help the rest of us out and learn to be civil… https://t.co/NG0eCfFik3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows @prayingmedic My gosh he wire tapped the President.  Seriously, I would not do that to anyone I tap… https://t.co/DLwQP0X527]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you even a parent if you haven’t endured a long car ride alone with a baby screaming in the backseat that you can do nothing to help 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's a sweetheart. Thanks for sharing him with us. By the way they used to be a website that was nothing but pictur… https://t.co/ug49FBaktb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MDeskaTTU @cd_davis93 @RoundRockTim @KingBobbyWdlnds @dkdeberry Why’s he all squiggly? Was he on ‘Dr. Katz?’]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @Roblox  the trio bicycles as finally convinced before pinky plane elisette boat lorna jet alana lilianne and… https://t.co/zF8TFG6U1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @WarrenBuffett on @CNBC this morning. Yesterday talked at length with my dad who will be 93 years old this… https://t.co/qTknViJEcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes You call this shit news? You obviously know NOTHING about the medication issues in MOST jails today! But,… https://t.co/OK3fXiBuAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leland: “mommy what’s your favorite color?” Me: “ yellow!” Leland: “no mommy, your favorite color is black”  Oh🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@umfufu13 Can’t tell you, I placed an order for two dresses on 1/22 and have not gotten them yet nor do I get a res… https://t.co/vosqGqfYfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drag queens will get you ready to be the center of attention...we’re attention whores 🤣 #dragme]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad really just called me to ask me if I wanted to go to New York with him this summer 😭😭😭✨  BITCH IM CRINE TF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foresports You always do such an amazing job!! One of my writing idols and your support for all these gifted stude… https://t.co/eCp3xUHszi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@always_nicole_ The Dragon Prince! It's a kid's show but there are some... innuendos lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't be the only on that finds it #ironic that we celebrate the #NationalDayOfUnplugging with a hashtag. 🤔  ✨ Fo… https://t.co/2dtmnlg9Rk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Working together, Boston can become the leader in promoting diversity and inclusion in development.” -… https://t.co/DoXU1MTvy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump The Dossier was started by the GOP, in primary.  So why do U always leave that lit… https://t.co/0wu4INKneh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dikte17 @GrouciDjamila @moonriver365 @TheBlueHouseKR @DrPyo I am with you We need global outcry!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot to turn the bedroom light off and both dogs are so comfly asleep and if I get up they’ll be bouncing off t… https://t.co/4NtosJeR3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegan food that is beautiful and tasty. 😋 (@ The Butcher's Daughter in New York, NY) https://t.co/gsxG3TXre8]]></document><document><![CDATA[its nasty how easy some girls are, like you guys really have no respect for yourselves and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was followed by cuddling up on the sofa to have tea and watch a romantic movie: The Addams Family https://t.co/X6HpMLN66Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KUTVHolly @KUTVRon @ChaseThomason @jennyhardmantv @KUTVMary Happy Valentine’s Day!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoviUpdates @jonbonjovi @jimmybuffett I wonder what song they did together?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamGolbach Got my 3AM hoodie 🤟🏼 wish the phone case was in XS Max!! 😍 https://t.co/AK3Vy3wdPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some takuache truck tried to race me omw home rn and got smoked 😂💀 My benzo not working properly and he still got g… https://t.co/5Yeq8Ynj1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my fav cousin love you so much❤️❤️ @nicole_heinz https://t.co/mkKSD0xPvv]]></document></documents></author>