<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[FREE VA Home Buying Seminar!  #Veterans #veteransmatter #homebuying #homebuyer #mortgage #VAHomeLoan… https://t.co/yhsyPDlKy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep hoping they'll keep showing their asses like ;that once again as in 2016 they R completely misreading the Am… https://t.co/3hufg1XFJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two weeks out, my friends! Make sure you preorder your tickets, as prices go up at the door. Head to… https://t.co/7SuEifPrKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBigCat @darrenrovell Imagine going to Indy and getting a free beer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Communities like Gates, in Marion County, which has tripled its tax income with just one pot shop.  More freedom.… https://t.co/8ZnLezAybb]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to give life in prison for hurting animals because some.people pets are as important as people and they wou… https://t.co/9rOD6KyCD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[TALES FROM THE LODGE: An uneven but sporadically funny horror parody. Takes a turn in the final act that didn’t exactly work for me. #SXSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #FullIrishOyster experience - Tonight! Connemara Turf-smoked kellyoysters #Clarenbridge Bay Oysters - finished… https://t.co/HeVsJG04aE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact they didn't do so indicates they know Cohen is at the point of having nothing else to lose by telling the… https://t.co/6l7MA78zN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasie @MaryCarstensen WHAT HAPPENED HERE  THIS IS A NEW " BEHAVIOR  " WHO WOULD HAVE GIVEN THE DIRECTION/ ORDER FOR THIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcHochman Channing Tortoises crowder because he can’t jump but can be in water]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Peanut Butter Porter by @fourdayray @ Whiskey Business — https://t.co/M6fxQOBpk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words wont express how I feel about this Beautiful woman whom has walked into my life and reopen my eyes from what… https://t.co/wKuP10CcdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew from the start @JussieSmollett wasn't being completely honest about what happened. I believe something happe… https://t.co/5Y0ipGIYpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noneal510 Sounds like you have the perfect skill set for some Summit outfits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT @brhodes And you've done nothing but condemn the President as you have since he was elected.  Get ov… https://t.co/2YgKHhwkUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[El Monte’s Herminia Estrada suffers a second round pin loss to eighth-seeded Ariah Barragan of Imperial HS of San D… https://t.co/RVqNeMo1Oh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone please show this to @POTUS this little kid has earned a WH visit. Just look what this kid pulled off  #MAGA… https://t.co/B64YH72JNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please someone use this. I want food.  Here's $100 in FREE Postmates delivery fee credit (good for 7 days). Sign up… https://t.co/OneBAFcCaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[5-5 for the girls today with a few rbi and some runs... lots of hustle and energy.   It was a good day.. https://t.co/UezPFjXXYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorldStarDave how the tides have turned in just two days... Analyst talk about the clutch gene I see you 👀... Amazing game winner bro 💪🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One ! !    http://www.oceangrownseeds. Trup is DELLUSIONAL! https://t.co/9PmgvtdNZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s see if @AnnCoulter is still in charge. #artofthedeal #worldnewstonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoga was great. I don’t always look forward to it but we always leave feeling refreshed and focused. Nothing better… https://t.co/FiTkQtJrkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC peeps always trying to look out for each other!!! 😱🤭. But you know there was still a few assholes that still ju… https://t.co/hICiXHcNWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boyroshima @quill_monger @BloopinDoober @ButtBoob Allahu Akbar indeed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lemonpeppah @Kyoko__Hana YOU CANT BUY OFF BRAND LEMONCITO https://t.co/zE9A3HULiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshCavaliers @WalshCavsWBB Congratulations ladies on winning the regular season GMAC!! Tremendous accomplishment… https://t.co/jVl3NkHCkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Network2Networth Nationwide #DavidMims @det2la #kNOw2NO #Detroit2LA Sent You #CastingCall March 9 #BMFCasting No F… https://t.co/ceUm0vaY9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT I’m glad Kim apologized and dealt with the abusers.  Oh, he didn’t?]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@KnoxvilleFire looking out for someone in north Knox who didn’t heed their advice to turn around when the road was… https://t.co/8VluFnlXMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[...If you reside and/or are visiting the Atlanta Metropolitan Area ...Join me at The Velvet Note on March 1 2019 (7… https://t.co/gPjVNDZMVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1fragmentedmind Thank you for being here and posting this extraordinary gif.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, here’s some news: Not everyone speaks as you do, nor do we allow others around us to use that slur.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @jdebona And Hollywood people are defending him saying ok he lied.  Lol lol their delusional hate has no bounds !!!   MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dallyd31 @VoiceOfFranky @RickAnderson So not Abacus, whose owner Bruce Anderson's daughter works in the PMO and an… https://t.co/f3mHXIbdjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So if he’s that good he should be able to walk on water  like everyone thinks of him]]></document><document><![CDATA[This first kid on American Idol is easily the best singer this season!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pic courtesy of the great @W_i_l_l_i_a_m_L who has provided outstanding pics all season long. 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys Basketball Section 9 Class be game Marlboro over Ellenville 16-11 at the end of the 1st @GoMHSDukes @Marlboro_Mayhem @suptbrooks2015]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brent_Brown1 Crawfish boils are fine. Maybe not the drinking.... For old times sake ya know?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a local band says “this is a new one” as if we knew the old ones...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luckyboyleshon Sorry I was busy trying that portrait mode. It’s no joke! 😂 Haha kissing your good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun game! Lowest grade at the end of the term in Physio has to make their next son/daughter Rhodopsin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Food_2_Die_4 @SpanbergerVA07 @WhitfordBradley What I read on high speed rail is that our geography is not as condu… https://t.co/uHnZaHN97w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bryce to the Phillies means buckets at brick house 162 days this summer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TzahraF @evansscribbles Don't let suspense become excessive frustration.  Many a book has been permanently closed… https://t.co/Vn6x35DuZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prostitution should be legal anyway. Government just has to figure out a way to tax it and make it safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodMusicPlug @Music2Blogs Check out @ProdHybrid playlist. Dude is young and talented. https://t.co/1k02KJXCoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freezing cold here today. #dreamBIG @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/u0ngAfsigU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BDisgusting I wanna see IT Chapter 2, but i don't wanna see claims like this, because i think about...... https://t.co/diLJjHZieV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoiseStreetDept @AbigailKBOI And let's not miss that high rise bullbar (forget the technical term) that no doubt m… https://t.co/2OFpT7wTwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danorlovsky7 @dh_simba7 @OhioStateFB The past 35yrs only 20% of NFL QB’s come from top 25 programs.They have a hug… https://t.co/yzcIfZRsfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to our amazing son @jordanlukin We love you so much!! #proudparents 🥰 @ Providence, Rhode Island https://t.co/gwyjD4zMES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiGicmka @PhilduranJ I thought so too Laura. We'll see. Sparks will fly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharkvoice we are “enjoying the broadcast” from Cleveland! https://t.co/CF9uAGafJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do be wanting friends on this here campus....but this phone go both ways sis. Don’t get me wrong I’m a very fun friend though 🤷🏽‍♀️☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woooot!!!! I’m not sad now, @masonramsey IS coming to Austin and I have 2 tickets now!!! https://t.co/9QyL2M92i8 via @TicketWeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rlamartini @LelenaPeacock @StefanKertesz @Enough212 @emergVictorious @beyerstein @WhosAGrumpyBear @headdock… https://t.co/W2ZODfCHHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[USTFCCCA Assistant Coach of the Year, Women’s Track &amp; Field, Great Lakes Region. #ustfccca https://t.co/chMmhWlrYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn You should assume the rich exploiting the poor and widening the gap between, makes life more miserable for the majority.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddiestvshow had a great time at the Hollywood Reel Independent Film Festival opening reception tonight.… https://t.co/9b53R1MXFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyEichner   This jump from funny person on Parks and Recreation to action superhero has happened once before. I… https://t.co/wcTzvyjwnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning from the Master Sommeliers. One step at the time! https://t.co/PQ4g4Rv9bG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT PRETEXT FOR WAR - the IQ of the Dumbercrates is amazing LOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anna_Chetti Congratulations! Now your bed time is pushed back to 11:45!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Souvenir poésies ; par, Marc Cantin ; Unique à partager entre amis.. https://t.co/kPYM6jUSaN #marccantin #poetry… https://t.co/7mgikNZvHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been playing Micheal Higgins “Daybreak” on my parents Google Home for upmost 20 mins now and I still haven’t… https://t.co/1b2yDovbhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirandayaver @realDonaldTrump We are a nation of immigrants, but we are also a nation of laws. Obama said that. He… https://t.co/XpbenieIS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaaahhhh this bitch just fucked up my eyebrow! Not eyebrowS... just the one..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopCulLibrn This is ridiculous. They’re lucky you’re being nice and not calling them out by name publicly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow the link for info on Hatha yoga for children  https://t.co/qQ9IzbZAsF   #SadhguruInPhilly #Sadhguru… https://t.co/0tlygu5MRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp @jack @Twitter Stop whining! You set a record with the lunatic’s speech yesterday. The longest ramblings… https://t.co/gpwgh2Cr5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday from my client @spur_themoments! #btsSCK #wavyhair #amtrakfriends @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/GToUbQkzXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow this @ButlerMBB team is setting new levels of embarrassing. Not a good look at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArashMarkazi Can’t believe you went with the del taco over the McDonald’s tho. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando de Formación de Porteros se trata!@memovelazquez7 @rulosalas25! Saludos Memo! en Cueva Zuazua Club Tigres UA… https://t.co/b96hO05Bar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eye2winner @WalshFreedom @amyklobuchar Again, I like her. I just don’t think it will happen. I could see Biden run… https://t.co/DvO7fZig3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XboxSupport I'm still having issues with the menus and store taking a long time to process, most of the time. Have… https://t.co/ap1Ixda11C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC The GOP know full well about climate change.  The reason billions in tax payers hard earned money used to move… https://t.co/KKdgVPBrc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank You Jesus For Life, Health, Strength, Grace and letting me live to see another day.😇🙏🏾🙌🏾🛐✝️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow day. Stay safe. #artstudio @ Action Art School https://t.co/FkcpmPZ5eQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeilHellegers I've always known that there was more to you than meets the eye https://t.co/Q1AO7WzJ75]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s unfair she’ll be slammed by liberals for this very reasonable position. If ending the student debt crisis is t… https://t.co/u3WiySl3ML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pramas @DGS_Midwest Sigh.  I dumped the boxes but kept the content. Never expected for them to have value in the future.  Alas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsmejjwarren I hope you and @markismusic will FB/Tw livestream the worship! I’m in need of worship and 🏳️‍🌈❤️ community!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gnels22 @Lovell54 Sounds like a good time to go to McGovern’s and watch the wild]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I through away an Apple Watch box and I literally just watched the trash man search through it 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanBehlke11 @Jordan_Ueltschy Mack declined the Raiders monster offer, wouldn’t resign]]></document><document><![CDATA[books  pros: more relaxing then tv. also more options.   cons: there will never be another season]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awww, now the #ISISBride wants to come home because "seeing bloodshed changed me" Too bad, baby girl. When you call… https://t.co/0kwSHMBneP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fur babies. #vanessacarlysle #pistachio @ Hyrule Castle https://t.co/mkPQ4saLSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImEddieMoney I'm listening to a slew of your albums I downloaded on a thumbstick for my car stereo.  My favorite s… https://t.co/TY0cNOaFDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mesovorticies in the eye of Typhoon #Wutip. The longer evening shadows really help enhance visual contrast of bande… https://t.co/dFkjF8Zztt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Absolutely. She is the real thing. She speaks for the non-wealthy American worn down by decades of co… https://t.co/hJnmQuWymQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[as you can see it working because grammar is rather difficult at the moment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice to know still living rent free in the old ball coaches head after all these years!! #vols]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cubs @SloanParkMesa @ARizzo44 Bryce Harper’s rolling over in his grave with $330 million]]></document><document><![CDATA[A joyful celebration in song, Dawson's debut @ GCCC, PB's b-day and the word. A pretty awesome day. The clock didn'… https://t.co/Jghd3GzPvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate #Carnival2019 with @fogorestaurants on @greatdaywash https://t.co/ONtlyCVYip]]></document></documents></author>