<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@freedm4all1 @funder Not sure what your point is. Are you saying the media should stop all coverage of Trump rallie… https://t.co/WdUlhVkZZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#blue💙 #flowers #orchids #phonephotography #phonepic #samsungnote9 #saturday #like #love #instalike #instalove… https://t.co/7SaUG1bEVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesPPierce @barkingink2 #TraitorTrump loves #ConManTrump first, above all else.👆🏼DonJT is a #SummaCumLiar #KremlinAnnex #RESIST #ETTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashlynntheurer I'll support anything if its sacrilegious. You know it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awelab1956 What do you think Dale?   I think it would be a remarkably good 'move' for @jennycohn1 to be invited by… https://t.co/Vv3sYoJE6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itvnews She has not changed her view@s, a definite threat if allowed to enter UK.  Doesn’t bother her to find a se… https://t.co/kUZWRgOXzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 79 of #backgroundtobestfriend  Start of my weekend! All of my amazon packages are coming in. Starting to crack… https://t.co/OS60wfOoW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoccerByIves It was suggested I reach out to you for a story I'm working on for the @indystar. I'm looking to talk… https://t.co/KTrboMNcC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing up I’ve always felt like a burden..I felt this non existent pressure and I couldn’t live up to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Best And Brightest Of This Year&amp;#39;s Minnesota High School Hockey Hair https://t.co/4yQbJq4doy via @deadspin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me tonight for this powerful testimony from a dear friend &amp; sister in Christ! He never wastes a hurt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malroark @ImpossibleFoods Ooh it got your stamp of approval, must be good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[isaac said i’m not allowed to go on a diet or go to the gym. i’m just tryna get my body right before the wedding. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boiarski They are so deep, drowning and still can’t see the light of day under the criminal orange mans spell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyrasofar @laurenp16 Totally not offended by this at all 🙄 I can show you better tacos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @KatyTurNBC The deranged man interviewed by CNN while under the influence. Doubt he knows]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pregnant women are human beings, not a mere “host body.” These human beings are entitled to reproductive freedom, w… https://t.co/LYpOQv5t1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tizzywoman @MadelyneRants Abortion was made legal for one reason only  - because they have the right to control wh… https://t.co/r1HfDXDpZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperEliteTexan Who advised you. If parents go get money from them. If your school go sue them. The rest of us owe you nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I see your hand up, I’ll get to you in a minute so put your hand down and stop wasting ATP” lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[two spros, quarter cup of drip &amp; a ciggy — the barista is present —]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Push back harder. The object of 2020 is to regain the presidency, not groom new media stars. Far le… https://t.co/uNf4p8mk4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abhiprofen It's always been cool really. As soon as you meet him and talk with him you are a fan!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing the excitement makes my day! Anything to make our teams more efficient and to bring visualization to the wor… https://t.co/8u8ROR5BuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afd1369 @JacyFranklyn @CREWcrew Well the people did speak in the midterm elections so I have hope keep spreading t… https://t.co/23mwRSPS1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nous à la CAQ avons bien ri des Québecois.Nous avons été élu sous de fausses représentations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I hung up real quick bc wtf you know ?? My dumbass too, but whatever. And she was off all weekend so they didn’t… https://t.co/3MXh9v0cpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's lunch: leftover traderjoes shawarma chicken, avocado with #everythingbutthebagel seasoning, and my trusty f… https://t.co/ezw42F6Pzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elysium1313 Right?!? This chronic typoist really needs a way to edit tweets. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is getting ridiculous Twitter! 😡 I am here and I stay! Earpers NoChill Fight for our FAMILY! None stop!!… https://t.co/aaFBaWfwuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what this tweet has built to @bmb_mellos Halfling Wild Magic Sorcerers]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so crazy how much shit has been stolen &amp; broken when I have parties.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DIY Budget Bathroom Renovation Reveal #laughter #giggle #smile #amusing https://t.co/DeBMLcjGfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[People tweeting Trump folded with Kim Jung Un, Nope... he's just waiting for a chess move..! He's studying the board 🤨🙏👁]]></document><document><![CDATA[A     Beautiful                       Love! Donald .. Malania .. Barron          💓💓 💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sweatyaf  .  👉🏻Cardio - Stairmaster 60min  👉🏻WOD x3 - Leg Press x10 @ 90lbs - V Squat x10 @ 45lbs - Squat Rack x10… https://t.co/bJ1AIYLyJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be taking bout some “I don’t like all that king and queen medieval type stuff” okay watch something else than reali… https://t.co/pZPfBsgz51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prosecution is directing rebuttal closing at Jesse Torres ... you left her like trash, she couldn't be identified b… https://t.co/EAKNJC0N4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDORIANGRAE No. I dont really find her work as an actor very interesting.  Allison Brie is the superior brie imo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manchmal, wenn man der Schlange den Kopf abschlägt, wachsen zwei nach. Sometimes, when you cut off the head of the… https://t.co/z66juZJJIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putin Vows to Target US If Washington Deploys Missiles in Europe #BuzzVideo https://t.co/xC4zBIR8Rt]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m not even there and my heart just started racing like crazy https://t.co/V3g4g9ffUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister For some reason nothing and no one can take him down!!! Enough already!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meu sobrinho: - Eu acho que é uma boa ideia você pegar gummy bears pra mim pq pode ser que eu fique com fome e não… https://t.co/bf3QE9k9gM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing my long hair. Ignore the eyes, one word: risperdal. #schizophrenia https://t.co/V3tsDy7Ssg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylinLong So darn proud of you!!! Just the beginning! Can't wait till next year 💪☝️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone for the love of God help me find a place to live?!?! https://t.co/Qj1QS2VuUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Sports Ecard: Not only do REAL women watch football, they cuss the HELL out of... #laughter #tee-hee #smile… https://t.co/6oDFWeoGbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricaMarie1988 @KyleClark Yes. The pics are mine, I took them last night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChicSavage1 @MethuselahsB @DonaldJTrumpJr @JordanSchachtel https://t.co/1SDTRrCnSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Met_CindyFitz Same happening here right now Cindy in Burlington, Ma. All the dirty snow is fresh and whit again L.O.L.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He who is faithful in a very little thing is also faithful in much; and he who is dishonest in … https://t.co/qa8RIRoQdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[What better way to return home from a short absence than to be picked up from the airport by a friend and immediate… https://t.co/UJqQ8cGKRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's one for ya @TUMBBHoops fans since it feels like it's been 97 days since we've seen The Owls in action...  Wo… https://t.co/95ylowKN2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathyWurzer @WRFWFM @facebook Thanks, Cathy! And thanks for the tip about the @WRFWFM Facebook group!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find Allies for ur @SXSWEDU idea  @cultofpedagogy No mvmt w/out the first follower- #SXSWEDU #SXSWEDU2019 #SXSWEDU19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do preteens/teenagers do “tbh?” so much?? Like are they really going to tell the truth 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyVirtualVaca @magee333 @VisitSanya @MadHattersNYC @always5star @suziday123 @FoodTravelist @TouringTastebud… https://t.co/tHwOeJhhum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani It is obvious Cohen is Lying 🤥 for Dems to help him cut his jail sentence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The MSM would be praising her for robbing America blind, the person that got elected, that is putting America First… https://t.co/aXB2hvyY7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doakfsu Yes.  When it rained so much a week or so ago...the water rose to the street.   Scarey driving over it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The purpose of this life is to love and be loved. . . It’s that simple.  Two Qs for you in comments today:  1. How… https://t.co/EZ5f1hNTt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it that when I’m on vacation I wake up early, but when I actually have to go to work it’s the hardest thing I’ve ever had to do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Try as you might Hillary wasn’t brought up on any charges, you are such an old fool!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElkeHansen7 @barb71 @laker477 @OldSmokeEater @TeriHentschel @thelastmilehome @iAmBoomerStrong @FMedic921… https://t.co/17aSKJTmuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such great show choirs throughout CRCSD! Congrats to all that competed this weekemd. Special shout out to my guys o… https://t.co/rRjbNejIyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally have to stop myself from RT sappy shit all the time, my relationship has made me soft 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthernerSays @Sostraveluk @thethirstytales @FoodTravelist @MattsRoadTrip @radiantwanderin @GailBenzler… https://t.co/4wsutNUv1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an OPA (Ohio Pale Ale) by @jackieosbrewery @ IDFWY — https://t.co/tKolmpB9d0]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ hey WhatsApp me I lost my contacts   A man who has never been on your WhatsApp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jumping into the weekend like ☄️ . .  Shot by the brilliant @justxusha  . . . #lululemon #highfashion #jumping… https://t.co/gl9NCoudMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes people cut you off for no reason and that’s perfectly fine. Move on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maricopa County has allowed more non-medical exemptions (NMEs) for vaccines than any other county — almost 3,000 in… https://t.co/7St2ayu0nF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealSweetT @JaidenWoodbey Thank you for your additional information.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett should be charged with making a false police report, required to pay back all public service funds… https://t.co/NpICkb008W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just pulled a 6 page paper out of my ass LMMMMMMMAAAAAAAOOOOOTIMETOBLACKOUTONMILLAAAAAAAOOOOOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdavisHPS Looks good! Thank you for the work of many on this. #HPSProud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaForFlorida @RoryDiamond @wideanglefocus OR, plan B. Keep them up all year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Call it what you want but we want a break economically... not just the rich....@KarenMoscato #capitalism #wealthmanagement]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Theo realized he could text @mmilky400 on his tablet! https://t.co/hCwwbPrich]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBlackHippiii They cute as hell as puppies but after that ion want nothing to do with them lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another fine evening coat look indeed! This is so fantastic @Fendi #MFW2019 #RTWFW19 https://t.co/50F49FVSyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job today @cluzniak presenting how the “Pythagorean” theorem works at @ArcherSchool APA Meeting! We had a gre… https://t.co/LIdSh7jZsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outlazymedia @EllenMcManus4 @fashionsizzle1 @tommyxtopher @SenFeinstein Climate change can be a non-political thin… https://t.co/AHKWdf4Egn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Could he have a headache?  Maybe he has to suddenly go out of town?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome, even if the “e” is missing @ Red Robin Gourmet Burgers https://t.co/7WnagOgscz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t make no sense, a team should be able to keep up the same with a player out no matter how great they are in my opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[actually understood EVERYTHING i read for my patho readings. 😭😁 kind of a big deal to me, I feel great. 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks alvintroi302 for my Lush bath bomb to celebrate my Dean's List announcement! I feel like a mermaid right now… https://t.co/ELaRQ0vSBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it’s only Tuesday, even though it feels like it should be Friday - but you smile because you heart hoops are g… https://t.co/xmCP3AmuzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @Cbp8Cindy @thatsVeryKari @suziday123 Good morning!! How's your day?? I'll go for run today,  not too bad out!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nettaaaaaaaa post pics of women who inspire you in celebration of #InternationalWomensDay #IWD2019 https://t.co/7xsgEye5oB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janelle_2310 @dougpike32 @MLB In certain cultures, this is a very high compliment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F5_Jackson Lost my dad 4 years ago to prostate cancer as well. The pain never ends but neither does our fight. Let… https://t.co/FzaEFId7xA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gonna be wen I get off work 2night😂😂😂😂 @ Amazon https://t.co/lj8yhRHEAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Urunderarrest I have a sinking feeling that AB will be a Steeler in 2019. It sounds like the GM is trying to prepa… https://t.co/jA6dD3Ed0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta love soap opera’s. No body works and nobody is ever in a hurry. Why can’t that be me????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradleyRBloom He's a spoiled, rich elitist who pushed it down Bernie's throat that he didn't like the idea of bein… https://t.co/uj4Q5BOdyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freddie24495909 @Timodc @UrbanAchievr And, America's classified information!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is #exclusionday across Oregon. 💉  If you don’t turn in your child’s up-to-date vaccination documents or exem… https://t.co/kkZDYp5vZa]]></document></documents></author>