<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Sunday are made for amazing moments!! #sxsw2019 #hometownhangar @ Speakeasy https://t.co/AyUORmxdr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darlainky @occupied_stall Or,20 times longer when your job keeps harassing you 3 hours after you left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ames, Iowa 2.21.19 :: @needtobreathe #acousticlive @ Stephens Auditorium https://t.co/8pPC1NlaOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘If you are not going all the way, why go at all?’  •  Having a broken thumb has limited the amount of time I’ve be… https://t.co/Jb6AuoTPL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ochreandsalt @Alyssa_Milano I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quincy… https://t.co/E19DNT7ToS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kremlin Barbie and queen of nepotism @IvankaTrump has no business being in the White House, much less leading advis… https://t.co/JlEKS2GYHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literary agent Jon has just been dumped.  He's too vanilla, too boring.    A client calls for a meeting.   Research… https://t.co/jxJHDwTeZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zjones20 Gelo did get into trouble but had a chance to bounce back but got arrogant and it has cost him. I think h… https://t.co/3qh7hknk4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Padres (35 years in SD) 2. Red Sox (MA native) 3. Boston Bruins 4. USA Rugby 5. SDSU football/Basketball/baseball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RDSmith1025 @inyokutse @dannySWISHperez @Gogogoat_HN @RVREFXRM @shelbs2032 If its not socialism there, its not soc… https://t.co/Vdd5FRqrNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a cowboy fan don’t get me wrong but I’m 24 years old and I haven’t seen us win a damn thing since I’ve been ali… https://t.co/ZNem4lIgP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Metro North - West Haven Station in West Haven, CT https://t.co/Ke8Ahnm5hP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEHernandez25 @scott_pianowski That thing will be packed opening day... but that’s it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnieYuTV Not looking good for Yu, Annie! ☹️❄️❄️❄️ Sorry- but hope you have a nice weekend anyway 👍 https://t.co/T4EwMOzkbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatzorro Happy birthday bro’!! Hope the next 12 months are filled with wild and unusual coffees courtesy of @glenlyoncoffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll never shut up against crimes against people. Good people are my favorites. Bad people suck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC first of all at any @Walmart @WalmartInc the main position has always been the cashier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eight step drop, no play action, burner down the sideline, touchdown. #MadBomber #RaiderNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redpainter1 @IvankaTrump @IvankaTrump is just a box of rocks! Bad genes 🧬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtwatts1 @Decreevy @davidfrum Did it occur to you that the CPAC audience was composed of demented folks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[when the boys are kind and respectful and kind just chilling all weekend and i’m having a good time. &gt;&gt; officially drunk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had @AB84 played with past teammates like Jack Lambert, Mean Joe Green. , @JeromeBettis36 , it would not have come… https://t.co/HKIID54ckW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terryatthebeach I got my first block... she said all I put out is hatred towards brew..🤔 https://t.co/y5Wx3T88ea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @bencnn Should we treat them the same way they treat their hostages?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magaxxoo @ata2dtoo @LilyNCali @Jim_Jordan @DevinNunes @realDonaldTrump @LindseyGrahamSC @TGowdySC @RepMarkMeadows… https://t.co/e4gHILOOac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compare that to Acquaah, who is 1st in scoring, and 3rd in steals at 19.3 ppg and 47 steals. But to each their own I guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pruebas de la presencia militar cubana en las Fuerzas Armadas venezolanas   Aunque el canciller cubano negó este ma… https://t.co/SehJAgssPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody : Min. Wage should be $20 an hour.                                           The government:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finebaum @KySportsRadio @CFBPlayoff What a damn JOKE....Did you see the offense #UGA put on display last night??… https://t.co/YjAd4CNDKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaxleyRJR @FlaccinOff @wncaudill @UofLSheriff50 They should wear helmets like that all the time. For one they’re s… https://t.co/QzeWFlopWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[this guy across from me on the train is reading the first g*me of thr*nes book and he just SLAMMED his fist into th… https://t.co/QOfC8Y2yBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@withamorxfaith I eat my spaghetti with flour tortillas. Spaghetti tacos fucking rule.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dunno bout' y'all! I feel better.  His human suit… it's, so, so, lifelike.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idek how I feel anymore. Sometimes it’s like fuck it idc other times it’s like come here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReasonNDecency @Timcast You think Trump is successful? If you define success as gains made on what was gifted, Tru… https://t.co/Yifw1Pqeld]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VoteGustafson @GustafsonMeg10 for All-American and National Player of the year. The Olajuwon of @ncaawbb https://t.co/H7Nby9NgMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skiers and snowboarders are probably going to like this forecast. For @denverpost:  #COwx   https://t.co/Yy0R34vHTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oliverg2014 @blairanton @secupp @michellemalkin Try posting something remotely on point next time. This is just st… https://t.co/gb3ddjXl8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frbragg. St. Croix bitches knew I was police.  Yeah but you fuckers know I'm human.  Bet Larry lomonacho 8s wonder… https://t.co/L47sbwshtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k8macqueen The bars in my area have done their normal bar crawls, not just this weekend, but last weekend, AND nex… https://t.co/CIYJaFW8gh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlgarces @NicolasMaduro @jguaido yo dudo que regresa a Venezuela en las próximas horas, creo que correría la misma… https://t.co/0bPI8pZbvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Megs_ISU @VOlthoff Wife put me in detention twice this morning as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Ya el presidente Guaido abrio las otras posibilidades, la intervencion viene pero se deben cumplir pasos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByCommonConsent @nihilists4jesus @sug_knight @bayoulejeune @bagofcats1 He came to bat for me, I come to bat for him. That’s what friends do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Next Coast by @GooseIsland at @bwwings — https://t.co/2Yv5UzPfrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1kevinkerby That was a genius statement. A Laker fan being a Laker fan. https://t.co/bMDSSihyeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s do something great together… @ https://t.co/EKqZvk5SFx https://t.co/Cxh090UQm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iankimbers Hi Ian, We can definitely help you in design and development of your website at an affordable price.  S… https://t.co/CM1bidK3B9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpaceLy You @JeremyStuD @NAMELESS @SaintsNato gotta find one for the one time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinmcleckie Some some reason, I don’t think Trump will be keep on taking down a firewall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonboSports Ronbo is your live radio app down?  I can only listen in on You-Tube now I used to like the radio app. https://t.co/Dv596s2T1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ EL MOMENTO, LLEGÓ PAPÁ EL PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/p8xYgz9zmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A day in the trees 😊🌴 • Photo cred ericajsd ❤️ • #BotanicalGarden #Rainforest #Trees #Garden #Greenhouse… https://t.co/BJGXiqRXJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@filmcenter @KinoLorber Lol. It’s not something I’m ever conscious of doing in the moment. But I was amazed at the… https://t.co/GmNtLTPaRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cajitacruzada #anniversary #gift #loveart #bearandpanda @ Monterrey, Nuevo Leon, Mexico https://t.co/gPYWTLuHI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hotdog6969 We need @hotdog6969 google tennis translate then developed soon so I can understand what you mean 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏡CLOSING DAY🏡 . Thank you, Larry and Alicia, for trusting us to sell your home, and then help you purchase your new… https://t.co/J0IqZg16xD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best political reporting in the U.S. comes from @michaelshure.  He appears every night 9pm @i24NEWS_EN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tarkus_Chiefs @MattVerderame I didn’t say that at all. I said I know a credible source told Matt that the Chiefs will release Houston.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Debwrightjones @sweetromance God Bless them all an for you sharing with all of us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jay_quigley @AnthonyOgogo Very nice words Jason to your fellow boxer. You are a true gentleman and champion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Hey Mikey, I thought I heard you say you had something on Trump? Chirp, chirp, chirp.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VABVOX Perhaps he should examine his life and make some needed changes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve come to the conclusion that me and coffee just don’t mix. Beyond the digestive distress it puts my body throug… https://t.co/FNcvuawxyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ABSOLUTELY Love my Birthday gift from my niece Celeste 🔥❤👀 https://t.co/8TppYrE8Ri]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CasSauce @Tjonesonthenba Breakfast in the 801  Old School: Ogies Cafe (3515 S Redwood Rd, West Valley City, UT 841… https://t.co/lNwiq7uKeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barballan1 @AnneGolfRules She is the best.  Just having a little fun.  😊😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[What kinds of changes would you like to see in Oakland Public Schools? @oaklandmuseumca #StandWithOaklandTeachers… https://t.co/2tDxHfayvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish I had more time when I went through #Boston recently, all I could manage was a pic of traffic @ Boston, Massac… https://t.co/f8RP5b1JWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikemad75 @MattGinellaGC I respect that Mike. Hope you can work it out. Maybe walk tee to green and ride green to tee box?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tim Cluess, Rickey McGill and Iona College 4 straight MAAC Championships #Dynasty #Legends]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’d rather have the committee doing what they do then having to depend on one player every night.” - Lou Lamoriello on @JoeandEvan #Isles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARonFOX The many individual car setups and time of race has some like @CBellRacing leaving 2 tires in place. B… https://t.co/Fj9YUraamF]]></document><document><![CDATA[nhl pick for mar5. boston bruins, columbus blue jackets, new york islanders, pittsburgh penguins, winnipeg jets, na… https://t.co/8bjq8LJ562]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ playoff mode “ we’re having technical difficulties here . Let’s go rockets 🚀 https://t.co/gAOZn9tmCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary #DoesThisMakeMeOldAstrosTwitterNow? https://t.co/Q7ixgfvwoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The turnover that lead to 2-0 goal came 20 seconds into a 2:07 shift for #CBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattBenzWeather This has definitely been a winter for the books. No golf anytime soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/ss9k3lHWOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Miami skyline from the cruise terminal. Miami aka the Cruise capital of the world. #iPhoneXSMax… https://t.co/R6XtMtgs0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new Meister Watch Ambassador.. @ Meister International Watch Co. https://t.co/RY2Mn2EKNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve been busy! Congratulations Ricky! He has been promoted to ASM at our Medina location. We are excited to have… https://t.co/aPjCnRwQ2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fleccas @VANS_66 @PacSun I wonder how she would feel if someone took her son away from her when he was four years old 🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catapult_x @ReverendSleepyG @_blackgenji_ I have a complex about semicolons resulting from childhood trauma incurr… https://t.co/ONojgK3rhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This hurt more than anything else that I could think ever matters today. #RIP #JaniceFreeman 😢😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need some braids?! She’s hella dope, Don’t sleep on her work! HIT HER UP NOW!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to go to work wearing these shorts and no jacket ... it’s raining as fuck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell WHEN WILL YOU DEMAND THAT NADLER RECUSE HIMSELF FROM INVESTIGATING TRUMP   PEOPLE AND BE INVESTIGATED… https://t.co/m7Ufh9nyJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyGirlboss Twitter isn’t public house owned or dominated by me, or you, but it’s not owned or dominated by Dona… https://t.co/uYx5XWLdhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @realDonaldTrump Tehehehe hahahahaha hahahahaha!  It’s gonna shit itself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why You Need to Cut the Excuses and Get to Work https://t.co/JP5AgyGaaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The US struggles right now with infrastructure projects because we’re in this spaghetti bowl of decision making, sa… https://t.co/uBDv81AVqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are headed off on day 2 of the @WaterEdFdn Lower Colorado River Tour. Last night we stayed in Lake Havasu City A… https://t.co/7sOfygznKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here for #AlitaBattleAngel. #Alita (@ Regal Cinemas Gilbert 14 - @regalmovies in Gilbert, AZ) https://t.co/9RCw3BURiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyORonquillo I was literally just thinking that. Yesterday at work when we were at the barn, I took my coat off… https://t.co/nx9WVjAzvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vikesmn24 @b_heintzz @skolszn I think it’s just a reflection of how bad @espn has gotten they employe him to basic… https://t.co/PPiIm2M3tS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I can’t imagine what type of healthy relationships black gay men could have if they didn’t spend most of their… https://t.co/E7VzciUrI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arielhelwani Cain should not be the main event on a new network debut. Did they don't learn this the last time they tried with him??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love ice cream and really appreciate that Columbus is now home to several awesome Mexican ice cream shops, includ… https://t.co/CNTqFH6CG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am truly honored to be a part of your journey. Congrats my brother   Friendship, Morality and Brotherly Love @ Ba… https://t.co/mV8Egn0lu5]]></document></documents></author>