<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@deaconcruise @WeStandWithEvan @yanksteel @licantropo_max @UnimpressedTX @TxsleuthUSA @JebSessions @WalterLapp… https://t.co/CdIKeykrnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithFoulke I usually watch old Red Sox World Series highlights when that happens]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UK via #Germany claimed my Grandfather Zarins body after they assassinated him.  Killed him then dragged his body… https://t.co/euu3VLWEj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting on the back porch sippin' my coffee daydreaming of sitting on the new house's front porch sippin' my coffee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mehdirhasan @IlhanMN accountable because they don't but are quick to create headlines when Democrats are expressin… https://t.co/ls8GoPOl2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Mary Poppins Returns song made me cry during the movie, made me cry right now, so beautiful😍 #Oscar2019 #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brain after I go to bed at 9pm hoping to get 10 straight hours of sleep but instead I just wake up at 2am feelin… https://t.co/NR9LqBe6Qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday we spent the morning in a vineyard and the afternoon finding the shooting locations for Scream. Guess whi… https://t.co/NIbPHQgnPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 things our brains need: -sleep -brain food -water (lips chapped, drink) -exercise (kids who played 15min b4 test… https://t.co/FiHBx2R37v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized I’m wearing a @kyliecosmetics lipstick and the @jordynwoods X @TooFaced  gloss...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m feeling some kind of way. @Phillies, you could have at least told the kid he was going to be catching in… https://t.co/Lx8iBHrE4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@establishmentno @nightOwlbookLvr @Melody7473 @hockeygrandma23 @DrWhoisin @MarilynLavala @hungryturkey007 @TheMarv6… https://t.co/n3pNSqQ1ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MossyWill66 @Patriotress @bbusa617 @TiffanyATrump @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @KamalaHarris @SenKamalaHarris… https://t.co/Dki6z85EPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deplois_J @BrandiceSmith Just keep praying. Miracles happen. He’s not completely gone yet. God does some amazing things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC schools will be closed tomorrow. I guess I’ll be doing food prep for the week tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennFredFOX29 what about the rainbow flag the peacock flashed ? Donnie isn’t gay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senior night - we are loud &amp; proud of our @UNMLoboWBB especially our seniors #GoLobos https://t.co/uWblwRByyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging around #rattanfurniture #rattanswing #casualluxuryhomefurnishings #coastalchictrends #thebestindecor… https://t.co/puDX4y1Yvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[i want the vamps to take a nice little break and then come back to the states so i can see them finally 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[How This Expert Made App Gets Complete Beginners Speaking A New Language In 3 Weeks https://t.co/uHLIPq0EI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greenpeace founder rips Ocasio-Cortez's 'blathering insanity' and green hypocrisy. She goes on defensive. https://t.co/41UYZA56Hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayBeeAFC @firstpinkchaos @6ixxbreezy I’m about to hop in now just to get my bearings about me 😂 see how much I ac… https://t.co/Jq8aLpI9fH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FL_lewoo @SenninSage @DivineSten @Ilhan There you go! Party over people! Lol! Yes, tell all your democratic friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElysiumFields10 @MeenaSrinivasa5 @6state @bjemec @BRCAinfo @FawnHoganMD Shout-out to the SisterHood!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamAllen_1 @realDonaldTrump Agree with you Graham Allen. Presisent Trump is exactly who our country needs to MA… https://t.co/mP0ksCYhy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is new Thelma oh, my older female rat. over the years she has learned how to jump out of her cage while I'm cl… https://t.co/iM2TLP7UNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏝💚Thought About Training?💚🏝 👇Here's your Chance, Press More👉 . Spring break is right around the corner, summer too!… https://t.co/URJfWToozY]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/f5BmZ6wITO Necessary trip? And Sharpton gets a ride along...why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can get behind this as long as that includes protecting the most vulnerable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could tell 15 year old Heidi everything is going to turn out great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we helped edit a peer’s sentences/paragraph in writers’ workshop. I observed lots of helpful feedback ✏️… https://t.co/I1V4h8R6xf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheBachelorFinale  Colton: I love Cassie   Cassie: I don’t love you   Colton: I think you can love me   Cassie: https://t.co/kq7vPMGo4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarahmony @knucklesr98 @The_Giant_Irish And we love you!!! ❤️❤️ Literally every time you directly interact with me… https://t.co/SmqjZlBXNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Sunshine! 🌞wishing everyone a wonderful weekend 🙌🏼 don’t forget to call and reserve you Spring color s… https://t.co/9DCftTVOsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diamondslil @79Aspen Oh that's fine,I easily confused 😵too easy I gotta go over shit 50 times to absorb the information lol 😀🤣🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring break#beachbum#lastspring break @ (@ George Bush Intercontinental Airport in Houston, TX) https://t.co/ezcRijdQLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg @andy, @BravoWWHL just flirted with a possible Real Housewives VS Desperate Housewives moment... Current mood:… https://t.co/939tPnuZuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I exfoliate with this coconut oil body scrub twice a week and it is amazing. My skin is beyond soft 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey this is really strange Mr President Trump! People who never stood up for you and kept their mouth shut are now… https://t.co/8oo4ZEiipO]]></document><document><![CDATA[A NEW THREAD FROM @jennycohn1 7/ Like Brian Kemp in Georgia (the most notorious vote suppressor in the US), the ine… https://t.co/xug1JKygKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unrelated but related who wants to host a party where we dance and drink and eat to Queen songs?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[beemanpam Bella being silly yesterday! I’m shocked she let me pet her for a minute (then she was gone!)… https://t.co/Rvd9L0X0JJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir - I never got drink vouchers this year! 😥 Any chance you could hook a girl up for her bachelorette we… https://t.co/80EHSZ4rv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I resigned as the Chair of the VBDEMS. While I’m proud of the many accomplishments, the harrassment and false… https://t.co/YuZdUXhnAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's 44° here in Michigan; so naturally, as a Midwesterner, I'm driving with my windows open and my jacket off #PureMichigan]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Goddess' sake! Are we already living in the Republic of Gilead? Eff that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/mQ4kski7lf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#coffee #onthewater also  #everythingelse #saltygirl #pasco https://t.co/igQ3WBflxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimLangevin @RepDonBacon @mega2e @Reuters @moflatley what about the safety of aborted children??????????????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Two households both alike in dignity in fair Verona where we lay our seed from ancient grudge break to new mutiny… https://t.co/J6tzfpasDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maconodom I was SHOOKETH my guy, but honestly not surprised in the slightest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I really miss my friends. 2 years ago today 💔 https://t.co/3U59RHEcG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roywoodjr I understand the owner of the Stardome treats comics well and I don’t want to devalue that venue. It’s j… https://t.co/WiEJEM5btI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soon after, he engineered the Brussels suicide bombings, which killed 32 people at the city airport and a subway st… https://t.co/2BFjvtD0SP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly going in and out of the hospital once a month and changing up treatment regimes is the most annoying thing… https://t.co/0MzwxY4iwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent strategies and commitment to ensure that students will come to school because they know we want them to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ParklandStrong #MagnetGame How truly sad it is that this is what our children and grandchildren have to face. Not… https://t.co/sqgpG63uZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wonderful day! Thanks @FortHuntES for inviting us! #outreachisaaesome #museumed4lyfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciation post for my fav wild child. So thankful for a bestie like u 😚 #nofilter https://t.co/Tbw9UHi1Qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackMitchel29 @AwlesAntonov @AnnaCAAlves Good morning Jack. I wish you a very special day with much happiness 💐😘🤗🍃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland It's cold outside: Here's a quick guide on how to stay safe during deadly winter weather. https://t.co/HcSkoDoyCB via @HuffPost]]></document><document><![CDATA[I unlocked $20 Rush tickets for #SeaWall/ALife at #ThePublicTheater on @TodayTix! Unlock here: https://t.co/HID62Vhb3A #TodayTixRush]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week better not get in my face or I'll drop that MF #HappySunday #HappyMonday #HappyTuesday #HappyWednesday… https://t.co/C4WzsSZ87m]]></document><document><![CDATA[north forney indoor percussion🖤 wgi dallas regional competition #breakingfree https://t.co/W7bbei2Fba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drcynthiahoward Woah! I really like this idea!! Stepping into new better habits. Thinking writing doing. Pretty so… https://t.co/ugT9WKZAVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisagemeni You’re too sweet 😊❤️ I’ll do another sketch of her, but more detailed next time 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flaparia putting this in my phone for when we visit FL. Menu looks fantastic. Can't wait to visit from MI. ❤️👍🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tionna46923058 @bankroll_bigz @trapicana_k I know they fuckinnnnn lying 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[about to say fuck it n just get a perm since I want curly hair all the time so bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOTH RALPH AND JESSIE WOULD BEG TO DIFFER HANDS DOWN THE MOST LOVED AND SPOILED DOGS ON THE PLANET 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dee_ford My son lives down the street where the suspect was hiding.  He was away from his place when the police fo… https://t.co/Xoe9DshoOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hwy 37 westbound lanes closed at Atherton in #Novato. Right now eastbound is open, but that could change depending… https://t.co/EkQR8e0qaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradhoylman Try the eye drops. I went to pick up a prescription and it was over $50 for a small vial.  The dr exch… https://t.co/LDhu7dA6ML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BayleighDaily @rachieswin She literally never said anything about you??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[For anyone who was wondering, yes, I will be accepting gifts today for my half birthday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our March dancers of the month! We are so proud of you girls! ❤️🌈☘️#francesleadancenter… https://t.co/vcqKKXJC8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remind someone she’s admired. Share these words of Jesus with her today: https://t.co/eg7ViWZf2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good job to the Comets on getting the W tonight! Friday action coming up for Sectional Champs.Shout out to Marcus f… https://t.co/Wd5o0PhLAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatTech1121 @CorbellElem We love our DLC @NatTech1121 and IC @Corbell_IC !  Thanks for a fun PD!  The king cake wa… https://t.co/HEvD4fyhpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came home like a Cinderella from the ball. One shoe on, one shoe in the passenger seat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just call me an optimist 🤷🏻‍♀️ #safetyfirst #SombreroOut https://t.co/Gtk5sLUrmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Netflix Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  C… https://t.co/1z1hTY5ZRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of y’all bitches wanna be like cardi b and that’s where y’all fuck up ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Kamala goes with the flow. America IS America, BECAUSE of our HISTORY. Good, Bad, or indifferent.… https://t.co/jLLxSV6ziJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benscoalum1 @TuneZanotti_206 @SandyDarity @HiveMindMilitia @kzshabazz @BreakingBrown @tonetalks High number of Haitian Republicans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is going to be Emmalane 😒 I already know 😂🥰 @LaneKodie @desfrvr @iamlgndfrvr https://t.co/FoDhovvsZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Collections Analyst" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about these types of oppor… https://t.co/dDElqXPjyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will not be participating in bump photos because gaining pregnancy weight has been extremely hard on my mental he… https://t.co/J9kqQxVQI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[That girl from dating around fucked up when she let that fine ass papi firefighter leave🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually leading. Allowing me to be vulnerable without feeling like a burden. Consistency with want US to be good n… https://t.co/SinJwwPXiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green New Deal | I Was Wrong About Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez https://t.co/6SGrN2ka58 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[People need to open thier eyes and see what is happening right in front of them. Where do they think these women sr… https://t.co/up748hVjdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Numbskull430 Thanks! I hadn’t seen this video before. Definitely adding it to my toolkit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCPolitics @JamesPindell I like Biden but I fear there are some unrealistic expectations here. Been a long time s… https://t.co/dJ1RYyHpmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved #CaptainMarvel. They’ve hit their stride on interpreting the comics for the big screen and telling a good s… https://t.co/QKcHYtqpQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I wanted lasagna, I’d have my mama make it.  ⬆️ My thoughts on deep dish 🍕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats only care about illegal immigrants and their kids they could care less about us they’re gonna scream and… https://t.co/yEJ6HTrAfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking Jurassickening @SUEtheTrex @ Field Museum https://t.co/s4UxIYNJB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helping out the honeybees. The food mix is one part sugar and two parts water. We mix boiling water in the sugar un… https://t.co/PwPnwPekNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[if the girl is aware that the man is NOT single... sorry but there is some blame there 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document></documents></author>