<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Que podemos esperar de un personaje político (@VicenteFoxQue) vende patrias y que su cambio fue más efímero que un… https://t.co/cbNuLgUpti]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn’t stop  #fitness #fit #fitnessaddict #fitspo #workout #bodybuilding  #gym #train #training #active #strong… https://t.co/rQsFb6Smqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought half gallon of half and half, carefully calculating that wife and I would use it by six week expiration date… https://t.co/ka9BdbQGxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpsAsianChic That's for sure. A good book on that to read is "The Rape of Nanking". Similar incidents occurred… https://t.co/KfLDYcVBbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is a sad day for pizza... my coworker just told me that there’s a box of pizza in the fridge that’s been ther… https://t.co/LWV4fYUjAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Managing Sea Level Rise in New Jersey in a World with Climate Change @ Princeton Plasma Physics Laboratory https://t.co/mzQ8AKtpmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump He does negative things, he gets negative coverage. It’s simple.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTedAllen I have two black Maine Coons also! https://t.co/q5ZfLiNTVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @MistyEwry to post covers of 7 books: no explanations, no reviews-just the cover.… https://t.co/MUdU0vvjNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnnadershahi Pretty awesome! That's definitely an encounter you'd never forget]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeSington It's Trump's hair.  You know it is.  He has confounded them.  They are in awe.  He pulled off the grea… https://t.co/bnMZV6IwuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The level of Corruption the @BarackObama Adminstration pulled off with #FakeDossier #SpyGate and n… https://t.co/9wwAPoNEpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods The perfect example of The Failure of The NYC BOARD OF EDUCATION, just the facts ... #DeathToSocialism]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayer: Lord, show me the path you have chosen for me that I may do your will and be happy in this world and celebr… https://t.co/jUn89NK0fW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbrownsports @EricSully1037 Lol the Hawks are 2-3 in those 5 games. Gtfoh. He can put up all the stats he wants bu… https://t.co/4TvH7u4yo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealRyanCameron @IndianaMBB And a great win. If we win the conference tournament, we can achieve some redemption.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wichita State led by 16 at one point in the first half, but let Memphis back into it. Anybody's game in the second half. #Shockers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nedryun @JustaGuy1225 @AOC Of course! That is the foundation of socialism. I get rich, the peons stay poor and nee… https://t.co/88IPfajAUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My newest piece of art for my collection gingerrogersarchives #ginger #gingerrogers and #fredaastaire original auto… https://t.co/xYdUxn1wEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbaAdventureNY @PicoMountain Must be nice to escape the crowds and ski the baby brother in the shadow of the beast! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleighM919 @BIG1059FM @iHeartRadio @PaulCastronovo @CastronovoShow @Heather723 @ibToast @AD_Strider Whoa whoa wh… https://t.co/8dxtbzplDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's to a long-standing relationship. @Phillies @Bharper3407 https://t.co/UwyAYnb3vz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vigocarpathian @_waleedshahid @hmcghee @sunrisemvmt @AOC @SenMarkey Let’s say you get rid of Feinstein, replace he… https://t.co/scdEaEV4Ct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 down. Day 2 ahead.   Go get it @Roger_Dodger60  #ChampionshipSZN https://t.co/toONGh2yNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ted13Cox @Ken_Rosenthal No hate from me. Just truth. I couldn’t care less where he went. The Cards are my team and… https://t.co/rFCc2ROb17]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson something big is changing in my life with these magnets.  It may sound odd but if you believe anythi… https://t.co/7OT6ZxREdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dreaming of #cuba #gaybear #instagay #beaches #hairy #italiangay @ Oshawa, Ontario https://t.co/e7KvBmY9RJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Norman Brodeur Spanish painting #love #artist #art #world #painter #paintings #beauty @ Irvine, California https://t.co/2rErCieYdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__taralynnx Nah you don’t have to participate, it’s encouraged but not required]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calvinjburke Wait... what am I missing about Aurora? I grew up with her family/brothers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AirielleUrias @DanielMarquez99 I can’t wait to be back with all my WTX peeps]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is the first time all year of college that i’m crying about the amount of work i have.... can we go back to first semester????]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3 getting to start off with a class meeting that helps to meet my Ss where they need me. #KidsDeserveIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week of home games! We need #RamFam to come out and support!! #RamHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! wasn't expecting #ManUtd to make it through today but somehow they persevered. Not sure it was a penalty but I… https://t.co/cVkI3eqrxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael47309670 @CNBCSuperRich @CityofBevHills @BeverlyHillsPOA  You can take the girl out of Rodeo drive, but you… https://t.co/VC6fvSbQ8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nic6879 Yeah. I just got home. Roads are AWFUL.  Not leaving again.  I hear there’s this thing called the sun, tha… https://t.co/sxIItAj7Ud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuciaRendn4 Some people really need to go back to Facebook. You look great, don’t change it. If they have an issue… https://t.co/6skiA83I9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to all of my friends and family on my social media. Only #80skids will get this……… https://t.co/FFU9mZeSnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to have our 4-4 ARB back.  Welcome home Gambler Guns!  Thank you for your service!  God Bless..... https://t.co/rUpMXx1rAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick experiment with some new brushes in Procreate. #illustration #calledtobecreative #modernartwork… https://t.co/9tF0xPKqRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the HARDEST Parkour Map in Fortnite...  [DO NOT PLAY!] https://t.co/6RlP5sLql8 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizva9091 It’s one of the most amazing things. I’ve done it in MK twice and it’s the best thing ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought a new out of socks today with koalas on them and I can already tell these are going to be my new favorites.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gratefulmaggzzz Nope, more often than not it ruins the original esthetic of the work. 🚮]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% of what I post is for me God does over an abundantly more then I could ever ask for so...I know sharing is car… https://t.co/QBK7w6xykl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey moms do you have concerns about your child’s esteem or them being less than the incredible person they are beca… https://t.co/XDanAWQgWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You did not "tune" that guitar... you had to choke the damned thing into tune.. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadLeistikow One of the best articles I’ve read @ChadLeistikow well done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericfisher A woman on my flight’s iPad rang before takeoff (it was loud and in Spanish, she was old and white) and… https://t.co/LqnIvIKteo]]></document><document><![CDATA[NetFlix/TV Station in LA California on Lockdown after report of person w/deadly weapon.#BreakingNewsNow… https://t.co/snfkIKfHaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Just got news on our news channel tonight duke power is going up double digits,being on fix income… https://t.co/2Z9lhooaEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @KatTheHammer1 Send her to Gitmo. She’s a terrorist sympathizer if not an accomplice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defying gravity with this Glinda wannabe! #wicked https://t.co/nXvRnGwxWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottwatkinsTU Well you basically have to be Dk Metcalf.. and there was a 6-5 253lb Tight End who ran a 4.51. They… https://t.co/HDJGZR1umh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnfilteredSE @secupp Limited government doesn’t apply to national defense you idiot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If by chance, Trump wins in 2020, it’s worth noting that @AOC will turn 35, 1-month before the 2024 election, and w… https://t.co/VAORncDSVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@9coacheswaiting @TomHeartsTanks @CPTDisney @RPG_volley @armyguyJustin There was a giant one in the back! Like find… https://t.co/dJH6R3IQVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Metalpanthers thats what I mean tho, stars can do so much, you can't be having bums on the bottom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pokemasterjon We won’t discuss the 7 clips of the wingman 😂😂 to pick you up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the snow fall on Mt. Sterling, it strikes me as odd that I'm about to purchase new swim trunks for my son.  @Kentuckyweather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASavageNation Michael, God is great!  You are a prophet of our time.  It is why I still listen to you even when my… https://t.co/Fkohv1kdKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisWeekABC @MarthaRaddatz Senate finds no direct evidence of collusion between Trump campaign, Russia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just called my son to check on him (I’m extra) and he getting a slurpee @ 2:40am 💁🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honey your so beautiful I'd love to eat your dooty anytime for noreason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevDon That should also include excessive amounts of perfume, cologne and/or aftershave. Some people seem to take… https://t.co/e1FLpkeaMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarimarSanche14 Muy buenas noches 💤😘😴🌙 ya para ti Marimar y que descanses cuídate mucho y hasta mañana.!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a southern meal done right this afternoon with my forever date. #friedchicken #macandcheese #ibcrootbeerfloat @… https://t.co/Q1BaxDmUMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve said this from the start of this bs lie. I wonder how @RobinRoberts  feels right now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#repost thanks for the support fit2massage Checkout @lazellc316 Classic Man line of unscented or scented Classic Ma… https://t.co/PJEp7CvjyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so glad that @ChynaJoanLaurer is finally going to be in the WWE Hall of Fame with DX. She deserves it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly METALURGIST are the BIGEST COWARDS in the WORLD.  They will not ACCEPT O’KEEFE’S $100K CHALLENGE of ME… https://t.co/qFIpfll2k0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one bothered by the fact that a fatty joint≠blunt? Please put some respek on white owl, Backwoods and… https://t.co/VB5ezt7ws6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CattleParker My biggest love/hate relationship on the farm. Worse than any ol onery momma cow for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The roar from the crowd when Longstaff’s goal went in was something else. #NUFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stockton High School Seniors Keep Gun Violence Victims' Voices Alive https://t.co/e5XFpBlUdU via @FOX40]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Listed in #Eden #UT. 4033 N Juniper Ln! Please retweet!  https://t.co/6aI633SHAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[CUTE  FAGGOT  LOOKING TO  HOOKUP WITH GUYS  FOR  SEX. I'M JAMES DI MARIA FROM WEST WARWICK RHODE ISLAND. I LIVE AT… https://t.co/YGTUDAixhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Hey Ass Face! Get a brain can’t you see you’ve shown Americans your true racist bigots! Or are you really that… https://t.co/5GcsxilQS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#macemonday🤓 #tothemoonandback @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/pI1KzXKO0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got tickets to the Rockets game next month via my job!! And what does your job do for you? #nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[No excuses, make time. It's your life!!! @ NAS Patuxent River Drill Hall https://t.co/tFCLXPOhyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slade ungh What normal 14-year old is hanging out with soldiers? This doesn’t make any sense. Just do non-problematic stuff, Luca!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out here being a badass #queerlatinoscholar super proud to present part of my research agenda on Queer Latinx stude… https://t.co/xF56mK9Ebt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pero esto no se agota con la salida de Maduro. El restablecimiento del Estado de Derecho pasa por desmontar el anda… https://t.co/aHpWaMECVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 7:00 AM CST, 5 SSW Sitka [Clark Co, KS] COCORAHS reports SNOW of 2.00 INCH https://t.co/pPq2chyiUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haslametrics @CBB_Central But bubble teams are constantly trying to prove they belong, and losing to a very bad team does move the needle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Satisfacciones de señor que hace el aseo: limpiar una ventana que parecía imposible de limpiar.  #TriunfandoComoRuco 💪🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halak is 3-0-2 in his last 5 decisions with his last regulation loss over a month ago (Jan. 19 vs. NYR). Jones is 1… https://t.co/pWua8G1P3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birmingham Iron QB Luis Perez doesn't play around! It's been a blessing watching his growth in the game since his c… https://t.co/vGsRSdoKXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Voodoo Ranger Liquid Paradise IPA by @newbelgium @ Acres Green — https://t.co/XD4Car13LT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmomahony May God Bless you Jane! God is enough! I promise to pray for caregivers today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 years ago today i saw Lorde in concert and it’s still the best concert i’ve ever been to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseySlaterTV @Mark_Baden So cold out that they are still encased in ice 🥶❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeMall83 @MrRighTNoW_818 Nonsense. I’ll let me speak for me because I don’t want to get in the weeds over what is… https://t.co/0Jjg0OR5iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saferprint @spiritdance33 @CrossTiesBook @RulesBenitez @jj5barry @carolyn660 @enriquillo2 @SophiaPapadop10… https://t.co/j2ZeTeyyIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidPingalore Don’t sweat it, Ping. You’re new, you’ve got heavy shoes to fill, but you’re getting better, every… https://t.co/faNYxxnKVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briannekimmel Been trying to tell my brother @dahveedgh this. Great story :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Comic book news”  Is happy a comic book movie might have bad reviews   Come on now. Stop being pathetic 🤦🏽‍♂️🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ghansen711 Conference of empty seats it’s amazing Larry Scott can survive this being so bad]]></document></documents></author>