<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[wait it’s saturday .... they don’t have work .... why are THEY up !?!?! lmao insomnia runs in the family i guess]]></document><document><![CDATA[missed dinner, if I drove to McDonald’s or pchop right now would you come with me (serious inquiries only)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Time to open an investigation and find out whose Pockets were lined with this money]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwint @MarianBrandmai1 @DeepStateExpose She’s definitely a very sick woman. Sick sicker than a woman with some men… https://t.co/mKaahbqqfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd be delighted for this to be the national anthem performance before every home @UHCougarMBK game! @TrentonamoBae… https://t.co/3RBuy7ac1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdscientist Bottom blue is Snowflake Garland. Middle blue (the turquoise) is Amish Butterprint.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Hateful bigots that are able to ignore the truth when they actually are able to see it as long as i… https://t.co/JsRfxWF3kT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisamurkowski @POTUS If your  praising Trump for ensuring America’s interest than why would you vote against the N… https://t.co/go1H81CamV]]></document><document><![CDATA[During the last few years of Momma Ann’s life he did become a godly husband. But his years of infidelity and abuse… https://t.co/YOW3ppME20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremynewberger Is that a quote or is she sharing her husband’s word salad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC there is no such thing as Islamophobia it is a made up word you idiots us to try and shame people to accept it… https://t.co/3zKJSPCRZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pray against gang violence and crime, standing against the demonic forces behind them.  (Ephesians 6:12)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kleaverkiddo 1) I never claimed I'm a poc- cause I hate the term and think it sounds like a disease. 2) Meet my fa… https://t.co/8k467U1cwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m also strongly drawn to Virgos but they are actually good for me. It’s them damn Aries lol 😂 we start some damn trouble]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Biden is an embarrassment and part of the swamp.  Does he think acting like a jerk helps his popularity here in the USA?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndieWire Congratulations to Rami Malik #Bond25 #Oscars2019 You would be Amazing!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Apologize all you want. You did it, the investigation will continue, and we will see wh… https://t.co/3WSx9EMv3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cryptonerdRSA @alexdunsdon I’m just not one of those dudes whose entire philosophy is to invest into other dudes w… https://t.co/Eze0Imgmm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got to tour the Somali exhibit @MNHistoryCenter tonight and hear Osman Ali describe how difficult it was to get t… https://t.co/jJaM2XmFiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MONYRODRIGUEZOF @GoezTeresita Es con los papas!!! Los Niños solo repiten lo que escuchan!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeVargas I am so blessed in my life! I may not have lots of money, but I am rich in so many ways!🙏💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenJoBubble @dnvrsangel I have a little Irish too. On my mom’s her ancestors fled Estudia Spain, looked for somewh… https://t.co/uV65CyzL7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adam_Karpiak @k8bischHRLaw Your birthday is the fake birthday I enter in all online forms. Mine is coming up soon.… https://t.co/s5OYPm6mK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I were a cardinal a lot of popes would be dying under mysterious circumstances until the vote went my way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m obsessed w my fiancé like I have to tweet it atleast once a week 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse .....reviewing my loyalties here, at home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But when the kindness and love of God our Savior was shown, he saved us because of his mercy. It was not because of… https://t.co/vhpdkuSfDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiracleLoveinc had one amazing event last night with #wigsinspace @DarcelStevens !! Had a great time with this… https://t.co/e9TWcZr5Oq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FunFactsFriday I never wore those shoes again 😂  #bts w/ mr.stevenward for a @ShyGirlMagazine publication!… https://t.co/ayNjJ1dX7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daveweigel 1/4 w/die of heart attack. HC won’t tell U it’s muscle knots. You accumulate knots U whole life. Press… https://t.co/kQym71YuKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 Shister Sophomoric asshole Shit for brains. Should a would a could a. Simpleton  Need I say more.🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow Just curious if you're aware of this? Someone is posing as you on FB, luring people onto their page w… https://t.co/0PP7U2rsJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why buy one #LGV40 or #LGG7 when you could get two! Stop in to @TMobile and get all the details today! #NERules… https://t.co/wbPEvo9Z8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Willis is so sweet. One of his favorite things in the world are mommas dirty socks. Well I got to work the other da… https://t.co/biswmtE2DM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is the right one  I was born in a new year  My age is a good thing  I like to see you too much]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psycho_jello "at least I don't spend my entire life *high* looking for some cosmic oneness with the world!!1!1!1" - fake Davy to fake Peter]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m actually in love with my after baby body this time around https://t.co/aR9qTjxQBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite Mabrey 😊😏 Congratulations on an AMAZING career. I literally have never seen anyone work harder @mmabrey1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Voodoo Pils by Glover Park Brewery @ Glover Park Brewery — https://t.co/1iaP6XA0E2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great working with you ladies! @SarahBalkhi @AdrianneDiCarlo @nelliearsenio #DigitalEdu https://t.co/19NbDnFwyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Dr. J!  Thank you for serving OSU and Cbus so well! @UWCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally no one:  Facebook PSA: uhm just to let y'all know ,they're guillotining ppl in whole foods every Wednesda… https://t.co/eM6EAXjZtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ILoveBeinBlack Fake. The toddler has the flour thoroughly covering its face and hair with his eyes spared like he… https://t.co/K0Xh4UwT2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 He was also sweating heavily according to ppl who watched his speech.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Th paparazzi shots...hmm...🤔 @mirandalambert https://t.co/HJZvYuKqlZ via @people]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took my rings off yesterday I forgot to put them back on, and my hands have felt so naked with out em😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solecito mio.. 😍 😍 #BTSGoingToMexicoCity  @BTS_twt  @bts_bighit  @BigHitEnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seuss week. Character Parade. #pandas @PboroElementary https://t.co/DEvBmUQtHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CACCOT1   Hi....are you in search of app designers &amp; developers? We are here and happy to assist you in developing your dream app]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I’m not tan enough and yet I really can’t be in the sun anymore cause my back is burning 🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[wait.......i’m seeing the pilots 3 times this summer. okay okay i can dig it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Scott and Laura ❤️ #imarryu  #marriedbymaureen https://t.co/s6lo5wbJlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[appreciate it! Don't take advantage of it. via Cassey M. on facebook [sphotos-b.xx.fbcd...] https://t.co/d4T273Ff7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow wee I wish I could call off half the week, every week and not get fired... Must be nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast Right !!!!  Sex trafficking children it not a good look NFL ... kneeling on the field not excepted.… https://t.co/fn7mmZJorL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moment when you get SWEET deals at @VictoriasSecret and when your order comes, you get 1 out of 9 items and are… https://t.co/txTQ1XoUS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Compliance Surveillance Oversight - Capital Markets" at U.S. Bank by asking for ref… https://t.co/IbwmtQaLZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[It kinda sucks when your relationship with someone ends. Like what am I supposed to do with the year of memories we have made?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VaughnHillyard @CHueyBurns @brithume Suddenly grilled cheese doesn’t taste the same to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone on earth is engaged and i want to know why and how do i join the club]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cetihwnayr @TeeRooCruise YESSS THESE ARE GOOD TOO! I have so many options 😬😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile new ads are spot on for selling a feeling &amp; experience vs. A product. Well done!! # https://t.co/craJOL6cME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinezR2015 @Alexander_AISD @Janeth_UK @lmartin_12 @RaveMiss @enrique_febres @NunezMath @MsDFigueroa10… https://t.co/lH0ASJUNHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cute mystery boys at the airport are like coffee shop mystery cuties X10! No general idea of where they’re from or… https://t.co/On5XaAudIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an awesome list!!!  Just like they passed Obamacare and congress doesn’t have to use it. SHAMEFUL!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stoopidemiks @luhshawnays @brendita_gomez @voguemagazine She's not a meatball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregGutfeldShow Greg, I wish your show was live to kick in thoughts about Trump at CPAC!!!! It was priceless!!! Ca… https://t.co/clDlbQIGxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone at the lunch table is talking about their feelings  Me: fuck bitches get money]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @MQTGirlsHoops are headed back to State! Final score 47-32. https://t.co/02o4NTR904]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want To Throw Your Ultimate Dream Party From Party City? https://t.co/eZaknt7EYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would spilled the free salsa over her head because guac is extra and I ain’t dumb  she is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah Bramer crossed 10K. Time 01:40:14, pace 16:52 min/mile, est. finish 10:06 am https://t.co/w40YZ2gOWg #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissagorga So good to see you stand up to Theresa. Just know you did everything you could to have a relationship… https://t.co/8fE8A4iVPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy how you trust niggas with shit just for them to throw it right back in your face🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔 I’m not sure... but if they’re using a double they’d be smarter to just hire @LauraBenanti #benania @StephenAtHome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Therefore if thine enemy hunger, feed him; if he thirst, give him drink: for in so doing thou shalt heap coals of f… https://t.co/UAySAamFpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka This guy has a mouth like Jabba the Hutt   It is all over the place]]></document><document><![CDATA[Letting all my @ArenaNet friends (who likely won’t get any sleep tonight) know that my heart is with you and I’ll h… https://t.co/LLtqhE9FlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to make a successful 2018/2019 movie: have the main character hit their head]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PublicLisa @monabenach @EllCeeGee @EKGenest Of course the alternative is going out in Syracuse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shirfire218 @JDaIey @BobOldisTowel That's so cool.. Shirl..😃. ..I dont know anyone famous from my City only myself… https://t.co/2o2PM6jwbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SantosTechCoach Opening a #STEM school is basically my life goal/dream!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nationalpancakeday #citizensvegas enjoy fluffy pancakes on Tuesday March 12 @CitizensVegas @sbeCollection… https://t.co/BpjNgFb7XQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to collaborating and learning today with my #CobbInTech team. #CelebrateMonday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenMab87 @HoarseWisperer @Girlsday312 @GothamGirlBlue @ghost_ready I am extraordinarily well aware of internaliz… https://t.co/tn4GepqZJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Chance to Order Your Chef-Crafted Valentine’s Day Meal! https://t.co/UsQ0cAbE18]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaliBugsyRiz @NickiPavek @WCTH_TV @hallmarkchannel @brbird @erinkrakow @LoriLoughlin @JackWagnerhpk @HuttonPascale… https://t.co/MdHuuJePvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyhughes Upcycled ding-dongs (from a feral colony, adapted immediately to the indoor life) https://t.co/6R58067M2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheryll1950 Right! We have IQ tests, too bad we don’t have maturity tests. There are some adults who shouldn’t be driving. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluejaylover49 0300 EST, right? Headphones for me or the Flock will raise 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been watching Barefoot Contessa and Property Bros all day, because what else is one supposed to do when they’re sick?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tmoorehutch4 Love having you on the Board! Thanks for your amazing advocacy Tamara 💪🏼💪🏿❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petridishes 1)  it is time for coffee  2) *I DON'T WANT TO BE A PIE  3) I'm picky about **[that sort of thing]  *L… https://t.co/q7sOwMkJDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had a dollar for every time I say “sister” “hi how are ya” “we don’t need her” since watching Jeffree and James I’d be rich]]></document><document><![CDATA[I make danny the biggest lunches for work lol , gotta keep my hard working man fed 💓✔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selfie_podcast : Yes! Please talk about Trader Joe’s products! Love them and need to know which others I should be using!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisee_p @__KingBritt This is all crazy. It’s super weird that he would think those men wouldn’t tell when they wou… https://t.co/30JvWODS05]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jupo1182 @YahooForde @PeteThamel @DanWetzel @wwadelsu Yeah, we though that about @Mark_Schlabach but ESPN just put… https://t.co/n68LlJZOqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emergency room nurse, Hannah takes care of people all day, yet she couldn't stay home to care 4 herself after the b… https://t.co/eM6dCE2COA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you live on or near Forest Valley Drive? I'm hosting a Forest Valley Drive traffic management update on Feb 28,… https://t.co/TQYZnfTAER]]></document></documents></author>