<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[A wall I’d happily pay for myself. #ITMFA #sociopath #shamelessliar #illegitimatepresident #malignantnarcissist @ U… https://t.co/58ctpeUoP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica This boy needs sn old fashioned ass whoopin'. I presume his parents probably won't properly address… https://t.co/miKKFw7caO]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you pay more than $30 a month on your cable hit me up I'll get you everything.....6000+ channels plus all the ex… https://t.co/YYC8zCW2Qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunrise #beachlife #becoachable #bemybest #bettereveryday #gratitude #delraybeach @ Delray Beach, Florida https://t.co/VD3KxXxAmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the director, cast and producer of Boyz In The Wood... including Tobey Maguire!?!? https://t.co/78dFbPIaqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now why would u want her not to run. She’s the gift that keeps on giving. Everything she does backfires. Don’t ruin… https://t.co/rCeKbGySd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm more on the Powderpuff track after living Anamaniacs style  during college #mirth #laugh #smirk #playful https://t.co/VBTmQ5oW5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve watched organizations change their team name four or five times.  Once you compromise your brand it’s never th… https://t.co/j3hPBP9Cf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMReporte @michelleriveraa Luego entonces, al menos parcialmente le tomaron el pelo a @AlfonsoDurazo porque SUPUES… https://t.co/kOJKTxH7DI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #LeavingNeverland doc is a lot, you have to feel for these former kids. And I want so badly to shake the parents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisVui_ @bettenono @USARugby Thanks uso! Proud of you too g! Keep grindin for your lil family 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Browns Good news 👀 Report: Jadeveon Clowney rejected Texans' offer for contract extension in 2018 | Texans Wire vi… https://t.co/d6G4bs8X8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come enjoy these specials tonight with me behind the bar @MuttsPlace https://t.co/duucpha0QB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to my 3% brother @NameOfTheGame96 in the SoCon Tournament🏆‼️ Lead them Brodie 😼 #ItsComing]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only good thing to happen from Trump declaring a national emergency to build a wall would be SCOTUS unanimously… https://t.co/jUW9sSHmSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at @CHHSPirates this evening for a non-conference ⚾️ match-up between @highschoolot #2 Fuquay-Varina (0-0) and… https://t.co/kgQg1IUdOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolSm01864194 @Franklin_Graham Or like today when Trump took the word of a murderous dictator who had his own br… https://t.co/tfisqsr8da]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamselby @Amtrak We just cleared Baltimore. Finally moving again. Now approaching an hour late.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IttyBittyTurtle That’s what someone told me! But I really want a Bully 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beautyrest available at your local @stlmattress in beautiful Washington MO! Be More Awake! #sleeprules #washmo… https://t.co/QpBPM6TCGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3X8QHhdhwmEATkC @cclslibrary @hiwinds4 @castingcrowns @amazonecho @FedalAnyone Yes @andknowles1 https://t.co/VMZx9p6gYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A veces quisiera ser una persona normal en Twitter... ósea desahogarme y escribir todo lo que siento, pero me acuerdo que no sirve de nada 🤐]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When I open myself up to the vastness of my own ignorance, I can’t help but feel a sudden suffocating feeling. I h… https://t.co/ySnVTLNiDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being Sick Is The Worst Son I Be Feeling Like It’s Over But @shesthegoods being a doctor so I’m good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHarns Why didn’t the Big 10 fine UM for this? I thought that was the precedent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are at the break inside Najafi Gymnasium and @pcds_mbb leads  29-19 over Glendale Prep. Ty Rodin leads all score… https://t.co/JU7iEwNPRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Life is short, and I’ve shortened mine in a thousand delicious, I’ll-advised ways, a thousand deliciously ill-advised ways”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any time you can work @PajamaGram into the lede of a politics story is a win for journalism #lol #ctpolitics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checks "art of the deal" for chapter on negotiating with a terrorist regime, finds none. Gives up and decides accou… https://t.co/QJemNA1odd]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Grandmother effect’ helps explain human longevity https://t.co/0n4xmJutfY via @statnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soyfdelrincon Excelente programa Fernando! Mis respetos. Por favor sigue informándonos desde Cúcuta. Espero que en… https://t.co/02jqezBszB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatholicHerald He was a #marxist, which is incompatable w/ #Christian religion. He stated that St. Pope John Paul… https://t.co/YEtWBSJYGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto #WeThePeople: we R Sure the majority of people that voted to elected @AOC are wondering now WHY ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliDahmash What would you say if you knew they had to first follow/unfollow 7 million in order to obtain those 1 million? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day 2019! Explore powerful words by women &amp; illustrated by women from around the 🌎!… https://t.co/y59EVRgRwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Betcha she got to listen in while Trump got NatSec briefed in the dining room...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I topped off my my 22 bowfront tank and the flow from the sponge filters made my java moss look like a Christmas tr… https://t.co/YM0Jc2fjvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS: Folks are busting down the door here at the Liberty Cinema 12 to see LEGO Movie 2 at 9 AM on a Frida… https://t.co/SBU5tiiaLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s legally impossible to be in a bad mood when Sly &amp; The Family Stone plays on the radio.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rgarzatr disfrútalos, la felicidad casi siempre está en casa, en familia]]></document><document><![CDATA[If what I put together in my head just happened... I can’t be mad, good job honestly 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been waiting for an AJ Styles-Randy Orton feud for a long time. Used to book the hell out of it on the old EWR. @WWE #SDLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Austin_Police if you are aware of women who calls herself “Clara McQueen” as I women of Austin have heard of. Plea… https://t.co/2MWb38GuvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoonable i’m usually a sucker for safari and safari-adjacent 911s, but yeah, for some reason i think this one looks like butt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we in the field of competition ima compete with my closest niggas the hardest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, yeah, yeah, enough with the birds, back to the booze. Negroni Bianco from Negroni by @gazregan.  1.5 oz gin 1… https://t.co/ehdAO6jrI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWBoyd I just have to pack them - we’re hiring burly men to carry them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Whitesnake Masterful job Whitesnake, this song Rock's!!! I'm afraid you snakes may of come up with another hit her… https://t.co/89qS9n8lNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDilanianNBC But the Attorney General cannot. And it can be subpoenaed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley You damage your credibility and integrity when you demonstrate you’re willing to take this tragedy, the… https://t.co/tphEGAwXQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great heavy bench press session for lunch today! All using my SlingShot, hit 350, 365, and a 390 pound PR. Put the… https://t.co/3ogKiUOw48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffMacke @BrianSozzi Let's bring back the 1970's.  They were popular when I graduated from high school in 1974.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattihb101 @DonaldJTrumpJr The only thing fake is all the crap from the left n main stream media....FAKE NEWS!!! BUILD THE WALL!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacobs71 Honest question: Am I the only one whose skin crawls w Nate’s fake swag act? Somebody please tell me why… https://t.co/NW4TNDPKoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritAirlines flight was supposed to take off right now and no one has even boarded yet not a change in flight st… https://t.co/TizI2eqbR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 45 #100DaysOfCode Day 11 #JavaScript30  Continued Wed Developer Bootcamp with v2 of YelpCamp.  RESTful routes t… https://t.co/sMXEKWJNKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT! LAS VEGAS! Anyone who already bought a ticket or buys one at the door tonight gets a friend in for FREE!… https://t.co/c61U30FphO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BionicBlonde @mchovden1785 @raymondtberle @JRubinBlogger I expect his next residence will be in the HAGUE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi @speakerpelosi #speakerofthehouse #NancyPelosi https://t.co/u79s4YC9rG]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you were to get a tattoo right above your genitals what would you get]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexd0rame @JohnnieGuilbert messsge me. I’ll buy you whatever Fortnite toy you want 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dailystrategies @seattletimes Sorry... It is a woman's right to choose....whether you like or not.....I don't want… https://t.co/ADEYqdlaeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOOO IM NOT READY 😭😭 BUT KIKE I AM READY!!!! BUT IM NOT READY FOR THE “SOON”!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikemayerMMO He's a guy with no margin for error. Hate the 'stuff' and really hope they bring someone else into camp.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyBunzy @vincedemello He'll say something stupid just as soon as Hannity comes up with today's game plan and ge… https://t.co/0eVoccJygm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s called not managing your money! Spending more than you make will put you in that situation. People think that;… https://t.co/4nOQ6XIiqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[எரேமியா 32:27  Tamil Bible:    27 “எரேமியா, நானே கர்த்தர். பூமியில் உள்ள ஒவ்வொருவருக்கும் நான் தேவன். எரேமியா, என்… https://t.co/fagbjwytk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[With many players starting to sign extensions in uncertain MLB economic system, #Brewers 3B Travis Shaw said he is… https://t.co/rrK8IHQdm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone tell Terry Crews to stop responding to everyone who gets mad at him on Twitter and also that I love him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[canny wait to get hame and volley ma wee sisters cat straight oot the loft windy, aiming for a two field personal b… https://t.co/41FvTWmQQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[“They normally call people like me ‘turkey people’. We bring a turkey at Thanksgiving...drop it off, and we leave,”… https://t.co/JSWd1THTik]]></document><document><![CDATA[#macmiller #nprtinydeskconcert @vincestaples at @tabernacleatl on the #smileyoureoncameratour #vincestaples… https://t.co/KyhU7T9re0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrozenSicleGirl I don't have that crazy one eye twitch Emoji so I thought I'd send this instead #NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte https://t.co/r8h6gjjOK8 @Pirates @RMUMBasketbal @DuqMBB @WVUhoops  @PennStateMBB @OhioStateHoops… https://t.co/O1KY2tdheL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_brandonh78 @CoachMirabal @CoachKWils @coach_cristobal Congratulations and Go Ducks  🐥🏈🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreddyKrave God I love your work, such an amazing artist, photographer, and model!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrystyneSantos @Ramos418Ramos @snezana_stajic @dmd62607 @norazimbardoya1 @caubel21 @jburbano17 @MattKeatinghd… https://t.co/4p8CjQxOAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[There will always be a distance between our view of our self and our ideal self ... but the self that God is and wa… https://t.co/mj6K2mDAcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Dan, AOC was recruited through a casting call by a group calling themselves Justice Democrats which is ob… https://t.co/O4vEYHTfzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diva_prince and you spelt “you’re” wrong. also the day i compliment ben]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sir_Clampsalot @_OGfeeq Can we all agree at least that Zion is the best player in college basketball?]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂 @MohamedMOSalih don’t even text me before coffee ☕️☕️☕️ I just can’t even.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the shop from 12-6 today. Then home to hang out with baby girl till she gets sleepy. Then #APEXLEGENDS till i pa… https://t.co/KAvDRMzIvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soft capture achieved at 05:51 EST, 04:51 CST, 03:51 MST, 02:51 PST, and 10:51 UTC. Hard capture complete at 06:02… https://t.co/wpppapGJb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManyHatsMilles Ok that clears that up, thanks.   I was at a JC game last night where a clean cut little guard shou… https://t.co/Jxl1rklvm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Después de unas semanas, tuvimos que dejarle libre el penth house al personal de intendencia, para que haga la limp… https://t.co/g2bg7bVx4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vlindelof @ChampionsLeague @ManUtd I got nuthin'!  Amazing job, everyone!  Now, get HEALTHY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a direct result of the use it or lose it budget process. Government procurement personnel cannot take a vac… https://t.co/RGz27tMrrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukecombs if this tweet gets 500 likes can I meet you at the show in Knoxville tomorrow night? Driving 5 hours and… https://t.co/jy62m5onTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alaric_Uno I'll lace you up on some tech bro.. you can take some with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost Munich Police: The 2 killed were private individuals..No Israelis or Palestinians involved, and too early f… https://t.co/w3q6y72nRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fstoppers When I travel, I make sure to have internet access in my condo/hotel and I use a VPN service for securit… https://t.co/TcAeQBrpCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its time to get out and be social. Wish me luck lol. Those legs tho🦍 — #6foot6withlegs #legs #fashion #event… https://t.co/oxPpzT0dk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the people insinuating there is something between Gaga and Bradley Cooper are insane.  Any dude with a pulse wo… https://t.co/zHiJXHEaN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a couple #BernieBros #BernieSoBlack #bernie2020 https://t.co/jonerQNfxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know Politicians are known for kissing babies but watching video footage of Creepy Joe kissing little girls disgu… https://t.co/65MwGTL76Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larrywbrown @KeithM_Photos That’s a new one for me...when I get back out East I will see what I can find!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForumFZP @I_Lendorf @JanZaryn @IsakowiczZalesk @KWyszkowski @Zebrowski_NSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mgafni @sfchronicle @EvanSernoffsky @SFGiants just because we didn’t get Bryce?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nehemiah Benson 14 points and 7 rebounds to lead @LEFalconsHoops. https://t.co/FBrLk6MO1I]]></document></documents></author>