<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[super inspiring convos!  @sxsw #supportingfriends @carinvvuuren @tiffaniestanard @alessandrab_617 mlaxros… https://t.co/wJ72v54vsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natalietaft I would kill for some cinnamon butter buns right about now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTS_twt 😂🤣🤣🤣😅 I think it still needs more air.☺️ #iHeartAwards #BestFanArmy #BTS #BTSMap_Of_The_Soul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt Hixon of the Hawkins County School District told me that they have exceeded the number of emergency days and h… https://t.co/hC8QMLqSIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[walking around w a coffee in my hand automatically makes me a dumbass who can’t walk through a door. that’s just th… https://t.co/ri97WBM9ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachjamesygolf @Titleist @SrixonGolf It’s been a while since I tried a ProV, but I would say it’s a bit firmer. G… https://t.co/ORZjtEPk9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow kicks off the spring GOTR season @TSGABulldogs and with the support @Academy gives to @GOTRKC our girls wi… https://t.co/RAqMhGEZkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Evans #GA  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/OqzVU7g5yY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xoxoxMinnie @SageHillfarms It looks like an eagle dressed up for a halloween party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannity: We now have damning evidence on the 'deep state' https://t.co/3Em2589GpL via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending #internationalwomensday with my professional mentor. She’s the most caring, knowledgeable, hard-working nu… https://t.co/0VC2EEveSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny thing this is sent to me now it's what many say and that is wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessings continuing! All is well!  God IS good ALLLLL THE time! AMEN!!!😁🙌🙏🏻☝️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL @HollyNiotti @realDonaldTrump 🤣 Are you kidding? There is no explaining the Dem “logic”! They are crazy!🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosaDeliadelos1 @DavidHarris707 @JudyMcAferty @aryservant @judysix6 @OfficiantR @ITGeekCT @disciple96 @myrnabob1… https://t.co/JMYdwHPo5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that's a powerful duo, EA want to see more of that this season.. #HAHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to me and mine (new @ArianaGrande album) https://t.co/SqagGs6ZKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hay Bozo California is the 5th largest economy in the WORLD, not the states, THE WORLD! California… https://t.co/6zOtYtn0ut]]></document><document><![CDATA[What qualifies as a severe thunderstorm? @NWSGSP only issues warnings for storms that meet the severe criteria. Che… https://t.co/36sb6lo75I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrZuhdiJasser @Presidency_Sy @VickiePolitics Real classy @samadhouse You might want to review your profile. https://t.co/eQ7cRfbb8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Use my code: Brittany15 for warm, fuzzy, feelings in the form of felinaintimates 😌 I've been living in their lounge… https://t.co/ImR2TlJgWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anne_theriault I’m in my last days of my last semester of college but realize I haven’t been to my literature clas… https://t.co/KSlq0EZKn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@artsharo672 @sun_shine712 Are people in Minnesota really that stupid ? I think she was elected by fraudulent votes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ms_Deathwish @KingdomKarrie Caught them sneaking out between cage bars in the beginning (fixed that) but wanted to… https://t.co/406XDc2tAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Just another way of having his followers do his bidding. I never in my widest imagination ever thought I w… https://t.co/3bworHHgns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MillenPolitics @DonaldJTrumpJr No.  Only the ones that preach socialism.  Listen to what he said. Wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okc_sports @CFPExtraYard @OKCPS @Big12Conference @Phillips66Gas @davidfholt Thank you so much!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tb to baby me and one of my first shoots with kouroshkeshiri ✨Brought to you by disappearing eyebrows and my *sign… https://t.co/cvMtl2BW5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday !!!! New Week New Goals! These past few days have been a struggle for me in staying consistent with my… https://t.co/KkGQZRyYj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also just found out one of the “homies” that use to be at Igbo camp got arrested for attempted pimping and human tr… https://t.co/wjNXf99I2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom-“ I was thinking about giving up talking bad on people for lent, but then I remembered that we would never h… https://t.co/P2A1mbwsRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fit_life360 @TravelBugsWorld @Adventuringgal @LeonandTash1 @suzytheexplorer @RoadtripC @loveGoldenHeart… https://t.co/xbpNWlUuH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Interface2019 kickoff success! Lots of learning and laughing does a brain good. We might not have come in first at… https://t.co/56xE0FHqYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌻I guess twitter should see my photo shoot too 🌻 https://t.co/xJjCJh7fUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much @ASUCoachCharli!! You make #Pac12Hoops special ✨🏀 https://t.co/rgi6DVXk2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner with Sebastian 🍣🍙🍺🥤 #sebastian #sushi #asahi @ California Sushi and Teriyaki https://t.co/e1KAT8OAfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[MORE LEFT LUNACY: KAMALA HARRIS https://t.co/JAtL4iwo0e. supporting legalization of prostitution. WHO KNEW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Sunday morning of hill sprints and knee lift/hip mobility work.   #trackseason @ San Diego, California https://t.co/s4OHmP7GcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I'm obsessed 🤭🤭😁😁 elalfaeljefe @ Mamasushi Passaíc https://t.co/oFQgTjPmTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dreamboat Burlesque is this Wednesday, Feb 27th at @thestarlinernyc ✨! Take a gander at this gorgeous cast we’ve go… https://t.co/czroEItBfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, waiting for Darby to get home with food so we can watch more Umbrella Academy https://t.co/vUNtaAOc6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starstrickenSF Oh!  I so happy for you Sarafina!  My sister lives near there and told me about Wine Therapy cruise… https://t.co/3dolp8ORgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 in Vermont on our brewery tour. The weather is cold, but sunny. The beer has, of course been fantastic as has… https://t.co/InWaFRf6Dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The goal was to read one book a month 📕 Then the goal was to read every time I found myself wasting time on my phon… https://t.co/UGtiA5eMdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! Thanks, friends, for expanding my world. #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/UyAm8aZAp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love of my life by queen is such a precious song I can't stop watching it on YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[❣️Life wouldn’t be fun without  my favorite Galantines❣️  • • • All my love to family and friends near and far who… https://t.co/igkmIvCAeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarrionTrilevel @Lilitrubie @leezermae @NomanTwd @GrumpyRue @MommaKro @47young1 @AlyssaLeann @drfredrick71… https://t.co/GzzE9WM7C4]]></document><document><![CDATA[A ver si en el 2020 se nos cumple el deseo de ver a @laorejadevgogh en @ElFestival de Viña del Mar. ¡Ya van para 13… https://t.co/YznqFfZxl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I realized that was the last night before leaving San Fransisco. #sanfrancisco #mykindoftown @ PIER 39 https://t.co/w6OPqK77Hy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this program and love to see a woman of colour in a law enforcement leadership position. #CrushingStereotypes… https://t.co/0tcgDrkKWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATX787021 @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows Michael Cohen was offered a Coverted Job at the Wh as White House council. H… https://t.co/CHi8NdUy6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesignationSix @leeleeb50 I don't eat McDonald's anything. I can't stand the smell of their food.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly one of my favorite things about having a boyfriend now is introducing him to all the Asian foods and snack… https://t.co/eUbpUXgCXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anton47492193 @TonyaRBlue1 @JessieLynnJL @JessieLynnFans @BradHeyden @KFearri @RoverDov123 @petergraigs… https://t.co/a9gsA109T9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m actually crying okay it’s not funny none of this is funny he just wants to play]]></document><document><![CDATA[What did old white people even do before being obsessed with cops was an entire personality]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a slow #PageSpeed becomes a performance issue for #Retailers https://t.co/18GGoRFcLX #DigitalMarketing https://t.co/5MXL4Adevm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiSportster48 lmao how am I just now seeing this? and yeah we truly did]]></document><document><![CDATA[The J Bro’s are back, they’ve had sex, and it shows! DAMN 🔥#suckerforyou]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pay little attention to what these folks say.  The DoS words and deeds will define her. She is a remarkably astut… https://t.co/jcDbKoo10P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading Time 🙌🏼 #FMSTeach #LusterELA #readingteacher #iteachmiddleschool https://t.co/LrkCPUK0zQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @AriMelber He already broke the rules and was warned. No 3 strikes for him. "Lock him up."]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Band Steele  - The Lineman [Official Music Video] https://t.co/nAjSJYPFHr via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralHospital @MauriceBenard # happy birthday sonny corinthos may you have a very enjoyable day.💕💕🎂🎂🍨🍨aka  maurice bernard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The health benefits of raw cacao are fantastic: it can improve your memory, reduce heart disease, shed fat, increas… https://t.co/hpBe5c4HP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sent @ChrisWebby a snap so you need to add me boo Beautyaddiction 🔥💔💋 https://t.co/j27JNFNORs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ESLKOnPurpose #HappySunday In order to go where God is positioning me, This MUST BE MY POSTURE!!!! https://t.co/fHBi66WQqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my anger issues have come so far.. lmao but nothing wrong w a little relapse from time to time😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Schiff is a dwarf alien!  He is just downright strange looking, acting, talking!  Typical Demo, I'd say!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Muna962 @colpan_m_alli @SylviaV74759384 @Viviane6677 @angela681417 @gabryluce @enriqueiglesias @merta_aneta… https://t.co/XymEgwejHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching someone slowly drifting out of your life is so sad. On one hand you are going to fucking miss them but on… https://t.co/Vgv2JOvNBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[💃🏽🍾🎉🥂🎊🤗👏🏼😁❤️😍 #stonebridgeschool #instagraham @justindhess @ Stone Bridge School https://t.co/zB6Ao3IjMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbrady_real_est Lol, I'll bring you a bag when I get going on it ✔️✔️✔️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smollett's 'Empire' dad Terrence Howard breaks silence, doubles down on support  https://t.co/EGeToPe0Yr Sorry Howa… https://t.co/ftWo3IeGMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹💙 l PROMISE TO MY LOVE 💙🌹 Jerry Maguire - Hard to say I'm sorry (Music Video) https://t.co/tcmBjybqk3 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremiahBrent My time is when I go for my morning swim.  It is calming, I get exercise and is a time to reflect and plan my day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up in the middle of the night just to think &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe @JamilahLemieux She needs to run because he hasn’t changed. Hope she hasn’t sent any suggestive phot… https://t.co/QX4r2wXnzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mthrtckr @LRESPTA @BethFisherIFT @Principal_LRES This is so cool! I love the name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of me really wants to go back to working in amusement parks. Part of me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachgilford713 It’s usually not as bad as you expect.  Dealing with the stroller and luggage situation is usually… https://t.co/w9ahZH1WWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jobs make kids feel important and empower them to co tribute. 😊 @ConsciousD #iheartCD #JoyfulLeaders #CEunited #SEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Spring!! 🐇💐 @magnolia #T2847 #HearthandHand #TargetStyle https://t.co/gkhRrqI7Xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slowly waking up. I've had a lot of fun. But not ready for the real world. Bags are somewhat packed, slowly getting… https://t.co/nS4L91tIyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[You, @LoraineForLA, and I! ⏰: 6 pm  📲: my Instagram story Auravasquezofficial  Tune in!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the amazing opportunity to meet @RanaAwdish during her book signing at #CCC48!! Can't wait for her talk at… https://t.co/4LYdXSC35e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing the Happiest of Birthdays to my G dog from here to SLO!! Thanks for being a part time ram and a full time f… https://t.co/Livupq3WFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We could build walls like Israel if they would give you the money . Crooked Dems]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nach zwei Jahren hab ich es auch endlich in den Bolivianischen Imbiss geschafft! Die Salteñas sind etwas americanis… https://t.co/YW3v96yhq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matiasyisabela_ El día que no pasé eso 🙈 dejó de ser Daniela, así de simple 😂   PD LO BUENO QUE ASÍ ME QUIERE LA GENTE OK NO 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Courtney  I was born in the car  My age is really pretty I like to see them and then I gotta go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Well a court of law didnt even prosecute hillary for all her many many re orded ille… https://t.co/M3lS2Jpkro]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019.. WE ARE GIF GHOSTING. THIS IS THE FUTURE.   911 SEND HELP. KINDA SCARED. https://t.co/pQxFv5bv9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your fans love you.. the fuck outta here. I wish I was workin with &lt;k followers 😒🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liqour license just came in. Yall come take a look at the Four Aces Saloon located on 1201 Lincoln Ave. Robstown TX… https://t.co/vFt3DWXeey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously crying right now because they are so beautiful, thank you @kyle_park 😭 can't wait to get them into a honk… https://t.co/OM7UEefUlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terramazing NO! You cannot leave me alone in a world of toxic masculinity and twitter trolls. I cannot allow it. P… https://t.co/bkO4g4aS1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IDoTheThinking @uhshanti @HenryKraemer @kristoncapps @DavidKlion @eb4everyone @SFyimby @henrygeorgepgm They did? W… https://t.co/TnSPX4udOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I misread a situation and leave before the guy I’m kinda interested had a chance to make a move? You bet!]]></document></documents></author>