<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Just got back from the tax guy. He says the tax code is more complicated than ever and married filing jointly tax p… https://t.co/5IjUGi9hKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lowes @HomeDepot  You have a responsibility to your consumers #RemoveRoundUp from store shelves or suffer… https://t.co/joJkvJUFEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so funny what people think they can get away with saying online. In real life you’d get these hands💯 #sorrynotsorry 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving for airport soon. Got all my stuff packed, and a very slick outfit planned. Big THINGS ARE HAPPENING.]]></document><document><![CDATA[but her future manager hears and is like, be my star but mariah/billy is like "nooo i love being exploited for my v… https://t.co/fYRUlKc6Ay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tulsa's deficit is four with 1:10 left. Memphis has the ball out of a timeout.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“iPhone Notes From a 3AM Insomniac,” is one of my most beloved poems &amp; having it accepted for #publication by… https://t.co/YpHP123BNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me to hyper 4 y/o: why don't you do some push-ups 4 y/o: (does two push-ups then stops) my arms are not meant for t… https://t.co/MR9WtFLa9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every diva should have a pair of red bottoms. ❤ Check out this Christian Louboutin Choca Platform Sandal (Women) fr… https://t.co/daA8kiGDJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanDietitians @mvmntcoach @ChristianTams @YogurtNutrition @LoriShemek @ESodicoffMD @DietitianOnline @Wendi_Irlbeck… https://t.co/ryGFILU7sf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just in time for Valentine’s Day 2019 ❤️💋 #IChooseMe https://t.co/hTI9zPzEzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strong landing for New Years resolution to stop undressing like a 4 year old, which when it’s 4 degrees and there’s… https://t.co/Zab4rOQCBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣@AOC  she just called you a Democrat Socialist 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 #FoxNews https://t.co/aTwCkhoHCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait, it’s been almost a month since I’ve seen my guys and @FlyWithDale.  #LINets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilabachrn Did you mean to tweet those to me? 😉🤣🤨 These were in my Timehop today. https://t.co/Vxkwz8L8n4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenSPLATT i love this so much, thank you for sharing your incredible talents]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DetJoeLocus @KathyDutton16 @OldSmokeEater @laker477 @WarriorAllways @DarleneG64 @Gramma_Nini @mrshhjones… https://t.co/s6jnD2JshJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samstein He only affirms what I’ve always believed, @mattgaetz is a disgusting individual. #LockHimUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe I’m finally an occupational therapist. Hard work really does pay off 😭💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[They don’t got my number sooooo no problem there 🤷🏽‍♀️ https://t.co/mbS6jK8FNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning everyone my dad just called me to recount a ridiculous dream he had after applying CBD cream to his “third eye center”]]></document><document><![CDATA[The daggers he sends to my heart when he knows I’m not working from home. #jonah @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/ssC4nCB9DC]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all know this is his vanity project he’s a one trick pony when there are so MANY other things to fix!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Audience question: what can you bring to the table as a female senator? Diaz: mentorship to support young Latinas.… https://t.co/Ow2ifNQvaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alysson4CK You can contact him through the website I posted at the end of the tweet :)!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So grateful for the meaningful staff development this morning with @MPS_Reagan @ReederRocks and @RohwerE. Thank you… https://t.co/GaaNpzRbdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So great to see Capital named as Platinum Member again for 2019! #bestmanaged]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KillerMartinis Yeah. You know the little mermaid story? You can have legs but it’s like walking on knives forever?]]></document><document><![CDATA[made most of their profits by buying and selling goods. In the words of Francis Bacon, the purpose of mercantilism… https://t.co/idZP7uz52U]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥰💃🏻Solicita #CuandoTeAmé de @julionalvarez en tu estación de radio favorita. @ChulasDeJA @EEnrique_F https://t.co/1WZfyEcxtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJonCryer @JerryFalwellJr Kudos!  You got that in before the wrap-it-up music started to play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING DALLAS COWBOYS NATION💙💙💙💙  HAVE A BLESSED SUNDAY MORNING💙💙💙DCB4L @ Valley Ranch, Irving https://t.co/l61071s0PB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tpgarlick @marushk20073410 @alllibertynews @justinamash LOL. Republicans confirmed over and over again what losers… https://t.co/rtpLLZJwuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebKurenaiValo @JohnPtye @dbtjenn @YoshikiOfficial @PBS @ThirteenWNET 😭 I hate missing it... I mean we'll probably… https://t.co/lXfhBomEdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[And when all the glitter fades there’ll still be stardust in her veins... ✨💫✨ Sometimes all you need to do it put o… https://t.co/LECQezLRBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you going up there? 👠 #ootd @ Thai Town LA, CA https://t.co/8TfupUv3YQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@129grey_madder @BeautyBind That’s wonderful, Jojo!  Keep up the good work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoHeels @StubHub Well since my husband and I didn’t win tickets to Monday night’s game for our 41st wedding annive… https://t.co/mskzvwv601]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be like Rahmaan and sign it!  Calling all Charles Town Residents and Property Owners!  Come down today if you have… https://t.co/gwqfCGBwX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lodan03 @DonnieWahlberg @jordanknight @dannywood @JonathanRKnight @joeymcintyre @NKOTB HA HA HA HA ! I showed my r… https://t.co/UghqVQVnld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like ships passing in the night, 2 district baseball coaches nod to each other, while shoving fast food in their mo… https://t.co/GyO6a65Wbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming in on a day off to celebrate this incredible woman! What a career inspiration you are, Dr. Elta! It will tak… https://t.co/BnLlpherMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u got there right before the artist comes on and u wanna shove ur way to the front ur a BITCH, some of us wait 1… https://t.co/2fWeweisZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I consider mornings to be sacred time. For example, it’s not even 5am and I’ve already gone through half a box of K… https://t.co/dbINOpNeB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhhhhhh love the ide of the YT timer! I already do station rotations with Google Slides but use the Class Dojo tim… https://t.co/wDxZZhTGZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MZHemingway Another critical reason for the problem with journalism. https://t.co/wXQD6yilC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day Amore💋♥️ Moments spent with you are my favorite💫 https://t.co/mSoTR1HHE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tami_Henrickson @knickRocky @Derm_girl98 @PMOmaha2017 @SheliaEubanks1 @dollbaby312000 @MLB2MLR @JolineBradshaw1… https://t.co/St3yb8OtaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabryluce @enrique34142823 @colpan_m_alli @enriqueiglesias @merta_aneta @angela681417 @Viviane6677 @vice_elisabete… https://t.co/raz3frVSCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanKemp66 @KamalaHarris All these “strong women” aiming for #2020election 🤣🤣🤣 ALL a bunch of liars… https://t.co/Ia1fj3PUjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 @normangoldman Wow, you mean every elite's vote would count the same as a minority person. What's is this… https://t.co/xmhXz76i0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColtSgleAction @ArthurEASC @bdomenech Cough! Cough!  And that’s why 22 vets commit suicide daily @buell003… https://t.co/SfAn6tZXJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to California by @nickcarter on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/H8bk81lEVy https://t.co/w7zvskhyfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[11 He came to that which was his own, but his own did not receive him. 12 Yet to all who did receive him, to those… https://t.co/W6JsoDIntF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard Mitsuta Chow’s had retro games and a pink staircase. Had to see for myself https://t.co/ik0PeQSfl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KKay7777 Im on Coffee4josie @coffee4josie for hw stuff and tv from now on. Trying to separate hw tv from politics.… https://t.co/Y5eUiYSUkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I just say the teaser clips for this song do NOT do it song justice!! 👻🎙♩🖤 The entire song builds, creating a v… https://t.co/F3G7kznf6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me this Saturday morning listening to my dentist preach a sermon (I wish I were joking)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj Road Infrastructure is aging and there is no argument that it needs updating...But our President only sees… https://t.co/4pqjzxHLGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tutte le volte che vedo giocare Vanderbilt in casa cado vittima di un disorientamento spazio-temporale. Sembra che… https://t.co/RYxLobRD9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Buzz Feed for recognizing my girl crush on Amy Santiago. https://t.co/qqtlbUvmr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabyGo2014 @loveGoldenHeart @PapaPorter1 @gerrinnesmac @ChristiWalling @jill_magnussen @kalimullah2 @YanaNaumenko2… https://t.co/vyYPqFPkC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, WOW. Im getting mad Suspiria vibes from the trailers music and it’s directed by @AriAster I’ve been waiting for… https://t.co/hctboo025l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fok_julie @KathleenBenzin2 @ElsaSk8s @whitesnakeione1 @lkrol68 @cadoyle62 @WSnakewoman3 @marieboscia @kupfgirl… https://t.co/keBnJl9csB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MihaiTrofenciuc @AnastasiaSMihai @harris_1961 Pictures from last week, walking up to the Getty. https://t.co/imptBEqd5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEOrive This also happens to be, hands down. my favorite Billie Hiñoliday song, though — worse things to be hearin… https://t.co/uIWL4rfmf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett u could instantly RIGHT this wrong by reaching out to Trump supporters!  U have been lied to about… https://t.co/dJJgkmBpMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaggieVA44 @HSIGlobal @HSIAfrica Let's focus on spreading real live footage of this evil. I know there are so many… https://t.co/sb8EOpoHd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobNelsonABC7  All night Long @ToniYates7  LOL! They got it it in the end “Kool &amp; The Gang Celebration” lol!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManuelMirabal_ @sharklatan @Pulandres @ProfeJuANTONIO Tons pa que quieres el Apple Music]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite kinder projects to do this time of year!! ❤️ Inspired by Jim Dine’s artwork. 😍 #mrsreadysartroom… https://t.co/zSJp4uZyur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMitchellELA @mraspinall @SteeleThoughts @HostBrian @ShiftParadigm Thank you, Jenny! I’m proud to be mentioned!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just found out my dad has gucci slides ???? shocked and really confused]]></document><document><![CDATA[We aren’t perfect but the amount of respect we have for each other is so big and I’m so grateful for having someone… https://t.co/fNE3M1qrHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEFTIST DEMS RETURN TO THEIR RACIST ROOTS TO BOLSTER SAGGING NUMBERS. THEY NOW SUPPORT ANTI-SEMITISM, LEGALIZATION… https://t.co/bsOAVV4KH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsHoskins_PMES @ronclarkacademy @mrronclark_ @jmyersnps getting slide certified would be the best PD ever!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know you see me down here fighting these tears. I know you know how badly this hurting me 😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our hibachi driver from an hour ago just walked into the bar as our friends Uber driver. #WiscoThangs @rachellynb  #bdaynight]]></document><document><![CDATA[No she didn't! She politely told them the truth!   Show us the unedited video of the entire exchange. Where is it?… https://t.co/TvqFxLPknc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comcast internet is entirely vital for our small business but I can’t help but feel like we aren’t a priority to y… https://t.co/rom2qGf9hM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful 4 generations of happy loyal customers! We missed you today Paul, Robin, and Jamie! We are so blessed to… https://t.co/7dMlr60zPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TLMarkides 28. I 💜 book talking these titles and getting in the Ss hands. My most reluctant readers often find the… https://t.co/KtCivESgsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj How many thousands of years did humans live on Earth without Electricity? It is only in the past few hundr… https://t.co/ptJUrWjdPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who has ever had to block off unpaid “on call” shifts for a retailer is screaming with joy reading this. Gre… https://t.co/6YT2gqLiXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the second deadly fire this month in which homeowners went back inside to look for pets.  @WGME   https://t.co/UNVqrCIcHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, Representative Cummings, for your heartfelt and wise words yesterday.  The United States people are hono… https://t.co/2sgR1i7iIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost I am looking forward for your book Mr  Cohen compared to trump you are an angel  and if i had anything to… https://t.co/FvUe7fohWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redpainter1 @susanfaiola But was there wine?  Please say there was wine.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Meeeeeeeeeeee!! I hope it wins "best cast of crooks,thieves and liars" and instead of a statuette the… https://t.co/orQsWtkJSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLCanes And to think she started out like this! https://t.co/tsE4zD4Pdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plagiarized from peri.home #todaysagreatday #casualluxury #talenteddesigners #hospitalitydesign #lovinglife… https://t.co/oNRgFLikn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a Ripp off. It’s not lifetime!!!! Cost too much and get too little. Don’t get them 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agentjenlove @tclaybuck @johnlepp @mcahalane @funddiva @benbisbee @thattomahern @spjoyaux @NonprofitAF… https://t.co/pyUDq3d57n]]></document><document><![CDATA[my highass conditioned my hair 5 times bc I kept forgetting if I had done it already lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police say the acquaintance, only known as Ariel, was found with Sariah in Greenville, MS about an hour ago.   It’s… https://t.co/twaGsOdpM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Regal Cinemas Montrose Movies 12 https://t.co/qQgQwxQa44]]></document><document><![CDATA[this world is not a competition. lift people up instead of putting them down. there’s room for all of us at the top.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#amjoy Wow, so many trolls this morning - and mostly a new crop. Thanks so much for boosting the #AMJoy hashtag, we… https://t.co/NoRvow9idr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ramkou @EddieDonovan @adriaanbacker @realDonaldTrump @doj @FBI Agree. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cute children’s boutique in Charleston hiring!! Apply online!! https://t.co/Wxl8JCgcmk #jobs #boutique #children… https://t.co/l4ZzgSwpy8]]></document></documents></author>