<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[.@crojasphd .@theworkerslab was Amazing...from Social Services to Authentic System Change. .@AllianceNews… https://t.co/MHdE0PdhQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an awesome experience!  I highly suggest everyone see an outdoor game.  Start to finish, an unbelievable event… https://t.co/eAQhUjEdRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some how my Twitter screen background is black and I like it! Easier on my eyes @JitneyGuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Urunderarrest It's like a person who thinks that ppl who fart are gross, yet everyone farts🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do any of y’all in Eugene/Springfield know Dr. Pilar Bradshaw https://t.co/lnapTjOM3j She’s active in the Youth Sui… https://t.co/grxmjZqACQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- I want clarification  C- many including Z have paid in full for life for what I have done.  I have helped many l… https://t.co/ocde18QXnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Après un creux de vague normal c’est reparti pour #District31 #intensité]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wounder who signed the insurance claim for my death https://t.co/pfBRAgvkk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikenedie @PolyRhuagh @AwayFromTheKeys @Cern_lXXl @Glad2bAtheist @zypisfy @yourmumspants @PrinceOfAtheism… https://t.co/TCeEqB3RBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigjimmurray @FelgerAndMazz those offsides and pressures are related... he relies on that jump in order to generat… https://t.co/VsNbgx7Z8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[So close, just have to keep an eye on the prize 👌🏻#lawschool https://t.co/SVLgaSOfbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thought of having to re-download dating apps just made me throw up in my mouth. Maybe I’ll become a monk?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daylight Savings Time tonight. That means many of you will now be using the same clocks I have since November. Welc… https://t.co/L3ioNhMd5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[TheDIM-O-RATS cannot even read how Trump ran his campaign.  He controlled the Media, in fact, his fake media is sti… https://t.co/2QHAhdJN0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoga ramen night. From time to time, we get together outside the yoga studio.  Didn't like the ramen the first time… https://t.co/1YAjmLMvdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of my Canes fans, check out my first article on the Canes recruiting. Let me know what y’all think. https://t.co/5h3VkNwfHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST ONCE-JAMES  INGRAM https://t.co/h0W0N1BKsO via @YouTube great song!RIP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Varsity Boys Basketball 🏀-2:40 remains- Northwestern 35 West Lafayette 35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mandalorian_Ren @LA_Karma1 @cpw_Numenor @D_resists @BusyBrain_Very @minhtngo @Calais_Brit @ReaperKat @Dobieblue… https://t.co/Ji2N5M3wq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows I’ll say it.. Meadows continues to do racist shit! Birther narrative, well send him bac… https://t.co/hz1qpc46rF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiallOfficial On the other they ate alot of nice people, jut like you that help others out . Thanks Niall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A proud moment for a gun. That’s such a stupid thing to say. So stupid. I weep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MacLeodLisa apologizes amid controversy over prov. #autism program.  She writes: “I apologize if my comments made… https://t.co/lPyTKJDreB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another one of my all time favorite album's. Good night gonna listen and drift off to sleep. Here’s an album for yo… https://t.co/Vfxdn6irpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepRobWoodall SOLUTION TO BORDER WALL PROBLEM During WW II the Treasury Dept sold War Bonds. SELL Treasury WALL BO… https://t.co/8T5tKiuGlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckonSports @ShaneSchleger @WSOP Was worth it. Def have a good voice for the booth. In fact the first time I play… https://t.co/BriPTfxvzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vibes! #windyday #windy #hairandwind #saturday #march #likeforlikes en Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/HaqjYVLrjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShanHalligan @SaraKronenberg They picked a nice spot for it. Hiawatha left on time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLaunchMag This is when they grew up &amp; showed a much more polished image from their original look, which I loved as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Morningjoe #Quinapiac poll most unreliable. Wasting breath as #Trump will be re-elected and your pathetic group will assist. #WitchHunt]]></document><document><![CDATA[We literally have 3 second best players on the team in Bledsoe, Middleton, and Lopez I can’t get enough of the Bucks😁😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier At the same time, @DNC pres candidates are demanding a return to paper ballots that would be easier to commit fraud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dance 3 isn’t a joke.... I’ve stretched parts I didn’t even know could stretch 💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weather report from #franklininstituteofscience #philly #vacation #family #weather #fun @ The Franklin Institute https://t.co/qxtiYyB3Uv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep, like it or not Biden was an outright racist about 40 years ago when Bernie was already getting arrested for so… https://t.co/c34yGCmI5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MileHighReport If he hadn't had the injury its 100 percent yes. Now hes questionable..... they probably wont.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasJTobin1 You're in luck!  The extraordinary form,  which uses the 1962 calendar, has that preparatory season… https://t.co/kECGndkCv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Memphis Grizzlies coaches sharing a moment. Cool. #SacramentoProud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenrussellmiami @GillianDJohnson @CoconutGroveBID @MiamiDadeCounty In many places there r light poles/wires hangin… https://t.co/gFkaG4boYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OmniAirCon C-V2X certification workshop is underway. Thank you to @Qualcomm for hosting. https://t.co/uEmDt8cqN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapeAir why are you guys price gouging? $319 for a 40 minute flight from Boston to Martha’s Vineyard!? That’s ridiculous! Robbery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m actually amazed at the people who watch and are excited about the sycophantic Oscars ceremony. Get a life!   (I… https://t.co/2OaOYlmoqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie Unlike the dazzling complexity of this schmo. https://t.co/t4QZ3sOc4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[All night, I want to hold you, all night I'll never let you go. https://t.co/ONxTcrDVLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mindset fuck these niggas and these bitches too where the money at so I can break loose ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reporter:  Why do you believe/not believe these people?  Trump: Sean Hannity told me to  #NotMyPresident #Treason]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because I don’t care if they win or lose, I’d start selling off limbs for the Titans to go snag @AB84...but I’m bia… https://t.co/PdhuJ6wjSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancy_dav @CheriJacobus @Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler Wow Nancy. Those are some mighty fine Christian values you are… https://t.co/ctCkfXpxV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derikv @GOPoversight @GOP So he lied first time got two years for lying now he's going to testify AGAIN an your re… https://t.co/w5wrbvbfvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I released Nación Bajo un Riffle on Soundcloud in 2018. It’s officially out on everywhere. Check it out on Apple Mu… https://t.co/oIvjcSeymj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think us should sue California for being such a fag state sorry minority state with chinks wops and dagos and other shits that live there]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drank 4 hurricanes at the PAX South Twitch party and got black out drunk. @Diction and @JessiwanVonDerp took care… https://t.co/A484AUOwrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveLaMont1 @CastronovoShow @PaulCastronovo @Heather723 Then yes, if it is brought to the table in separate bowls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@G0ldenstatemike I’m the same way. I think I’m still scarred from when I was a kid. My mom would always do that shi… https://t.co/FIp7hGdJUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red, Edamames are green, Postharvest insects squirm eternal,* In silos of dried bean.  *Many dermestids d… https://t.co/itz5RVcRMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mv2jsievers @ArgusSports I’ll have coverage of championships tomorrow and will update Friday results page once I g… https://t.co/nHyzF4Gvyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many babies are being slaughtered daily because of your beliefs? Taking guns away from law-abiding citizens is… https://t.co/0bL5Y6JAjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iLikeRollins @WWEDanielBryan No it that would either be AJ ,Ricochet or Seth Rollins]]></document><document><![CDATA[#foofighters #walkingafteryou #acceptsurrender #guitar #gibsonj45 #gibson #acoustic #acousticguitar @ Los Angeles,… https://t.co/jZiuofN7uX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karma79167154 @JimCarrey Jim  Carrey has US Citizenship. I doubt Jim will go broke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCoronell @Univision @StateDept @NicolasMaduro @NicolasMaduro ya no respeta esta igual a los dictadores de cuba fu… https://t.co/zT0GeNy2lv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 Yes put Trump at the end of his name! That will enlarge his asshole several times!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachCooney10 @atlbaseballtalk I’d love to see the tiebreaker and play in games..... however then the WS would be… https://t.co/p96NQsbW9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Derek Frank - SoundCheck LIVE Take #15 at Lucky Strike Live  #derekfrank #soundchecklive #luckystrikelive… https://t.co/BdgOAH8Z82]]></document><document><![CDATA[This series, I think, is a vivid look at where he came from and how his father greatly influenced his personality.… https://t.co/YLTX7g2fs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benarmishaw https://t.co/57A125Bzv1 okay but the whistles are a nice addition]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diamond twist on a classic signet ring ⚡️ #aligracejewelry #ss19 #silver #gold #diamond #signetring #custom #ring @… https://t.co/Wp1c0HV3OM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyson_jominy @MotorTrend @mrcurt4ins @TimWJackson @eviljefferson Thank you Sir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abratton225 hey, that emoji looks like our matching tats, let’s get a new one soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poke_gotips  youtube deleted my account i am new to youtube only have 5 sub i post random stuff i don't know anything  help me out guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCW @heaathh_xO @AlexisStockdeez @melissastark @Melanie_Collins 😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The Pits by @GaragisteMead @ Garagiste Meadery — https://t.co/NUpUaC2tFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexkinsella @srlake Nice, love the @focalsbynorth mobile showroom concept.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is what I have always understood to be the essence of anarchism: the conviction that the burden of proof has t… https://t.co/Whfn4pk7Xt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashlee__willis @linnymarie4 @fred_guttenberg What does dementia have to do with law abiding gun owners? Oh it does… https://t.co/wHnIWtOjDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TS7Track3 Ya boi is never one to pass down food. I’m actually jealous I don’t have a grindr hookup that brings me food. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[A dallasstars hat trick!!! By my new gf complexionaestheticsdallas fave player!!! Best. Night. Ever!!! #GoStars!… https://t.co/IMykSdaaZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good way to start the flight! - Drinking a Breakfast of Champions by @bangerbrewing at @bangerbrewing  — https://t.co/MXz7xPLWZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lalaboo62 @tmbracken2 @kdawgswift @expectdelay @Public_Citizen @amDC_novi So your saying you don't understand how… https://t.co/p5lv3wcTJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[maybe it's a sign I should stop laying around so much, cuz I've been getting walked all over]]></document><document><![CDATA[My TWN app says theres a snow squall warning for Wellesley but I cant find one for Waterloo Region https://t.co/uvDBVTOGR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Simmons is pressed about the Knicks online (he usually jokes on us and pities our fanbase) then KD and Kyrie is… https://t.co/gWdOucAfSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister just texted me saying she had a feeling something was staring at her while she was in bed... but when she… https://t.co/INKkxhU1JN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAutumnWind80 @lopezee I wish I could donate my Mack or Cooper jersey to bring him up with the times]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time at the nflnetwork today, shooting spots for their 100 Year Anniversary and talking @AEWrestling, wayne.g… https://t.co/Q8rYTP5OBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEgames @BlackBeardGuy So many when he was partners with @andrethegiant at one point and when he went up against… https://t.co/jVCI9fk4yi]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@FoxNewsSunday  .@FoxNews  .@larrykudlow  Fox News Sunday, has Larry Kudlow on. I sure hope they gave Kudlow, tests for drugs and alcohol?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty disappointed that #TrueDetective didn’t end with Mahershala Ali’s character saying, “And that’s why you, Ame… https://t.co/bfoDyfc2PU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilaGraceRose Job 12:5–6 (NKJV):  6  The tents of robbers prosper, And those who provoke God are secure— In what God provides by His hand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gbvitrano @totofiandaca @Ginetto I love this...the world united with QGIS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/bBHKnKgpQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow Here's a partial answer (do you have 26 minutes? if not, pass it on):  https://t.co/y2afehK1te]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ramblers went almost seven minutes without scoring. They trail at halftime 26-17. 16 minutes left to right the ship… https://t.co/rLRTA3Mrgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bryan_Lidtke They didn't systematically tank. David Robinson got hurt and the team sucked. They got lucky in the lottery, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[La entrega de boletos de la barra será en el bar Mantarayados a un costado del estadio BBVA de 2 a 4 pm antes del r… https://t.co/MHDdhtmocR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not that it matters but I def blocked marshmello. He’s so annoying and cocky and I cannot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this hilarious there's something wrong with you. Such a cute idea for pop up cards! https://t.co/0TD8mCkrYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my start a million years ago with @SanDiegoSockers and walked away with 2 championship rings. Seeing the reacti… https://t.co/650MUUSurA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamonBruce You wanna act a fool. Ok let’s see how you like it in Buffalo with a running Qb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@futbolaldialagu Raymundo parecia mas al Tuca Ferreti que a Caixihna, ya nomas falto decir "callese carajo"]]></document></documents></author>