<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Last night I took a picture of my dinner with the flash on and later the restaurant owner came over and asked if I… https://t.co/dMBB1hR9Cr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmohorovich therefore, academy voters less than enthused to give a movie surrounded by controversy much recognition. Whether it is good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse @DineshDSouza @DaveinDiego “Truth is incontrovertible. Malice may attack it. Ignorance may deride it.… https://t.co/5vjRAVSofV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cajunhossman1 @RealJamesWoods How is this guy not in jail, also every file he ever worked has to be reviewed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍Desert Rose-Shaped by desert elements both physical and spiritual, Desert Rose is a variety of Barite, so it carri… https://t.co/Uncg5tpEJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I predict 30 days - that’s all.  Not enough. Also should be a large fine for misuse of resources]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best thing heard on this holiday so far: “Pablo Escobar built his own prison motherfucker...” true that. https://t.co/Q2z7piSfG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @netlogxTeam #sixsigma class just got weigh better @FionaHippo just showed up (well she made me happy) https://t.co/qJL4GK9WJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[A guy in my class is in the computer lab and procrastinating so hard he’s stressing me out like you don’t even know what’s ahead of you man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Biden "Chester The Molester " Medal  .... He's  so Proud! https://t.co/1vR3grX1ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[#datenight #cheeseboard #wineflight #lent #lentaf #pumpkinravioli #hehadfilet #hesgoingtohell #imnot #eatlocal… https://t.co/r9WTXrfmT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a Gemini and that’s why I get to the shower and then I’ll be home soon so I can get you to come over and get i… https://t.co/chWeGx5yA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Use https://t.co/AcB6YQZwxJ and they'll reward both of us with a US$20 gift! https://t.co/BWRK1UV4s6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey media. Please research the actual job history of @IvankaTrump .  @CBSNews  @NBCNews  @ABC  @CNN  @MSNBC… https://t.co/bg68Bx5Erh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday is usually my best day of the week. I like when things get going. ✖ https://t.co/CH9EVrl62R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GulfCoastDawg Somebody knows what happened but they aren’t telling and it is sort of refreshing to know that it is… https://t.co/FzkOEJ5KMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prattandwhitney #PW4000 powered aircraft refueling the @prattandwhitney powered #F35. #WearePW #Avgeek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strive to do different kinds of things becuase they evelate us eventually.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t give Ariel’s parents enough credit bc they have done so much for me and I’m not even their kid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's the direct link to our #podcast tomorrow morning at 11am EST.  We're replaying our fantastic interview with… https://t.co/Fg3DUJRbbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I’m introducing you to Power and JAB. My mom’s long-standing, beloved nickname of “Power” comes from our soft… https://t.co/VFRb6SJ1db]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loraineballard @Q102Philly In Delaware its moderate or heavy sleet showers 😉 https://t.co/5fpVaI39uL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all pussies &amp; your “I’m gonna say this,&amp; then mute this post” shit,STFU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This excites me to no end. First stop is #Israel then we'll be heading to #Breck in early April so keep the snow co… https://t.co/ofA4x3NA7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BellaDonnaGagn2 I know, I said I'd call you but I am beat&amp; off to dreamland! I will  try to catch up with you 2morrow , ok, sorry!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelsayy921 It’s one of my favorite things to eat, so I always make wayyyy too much so I can eat it for 2-3 days!😂🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BangorYMCA do you offer babysitting classes for tweens/teens? Nothing local is available and it might be a great o… https://t.co/CKuzcdUB0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pennsauken's Anmarie Lebron stays loose before her match against Parsippany's Sydney Petzinger in a 100-pound girls… https://t.co/V3squaK8pQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real #NationalEmergency! ##RESIST Trump’s #fakenationalemergency on #PresidentsDay! @ Raleigh, North Carolina https://t.co/BoAbVRF6TD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geeanem @MiniWineGirl @SteveKubota @YumchaAddict @LisaMRomano @OfPainters @JeremyPalmer7 @Oberreimer @nineov… https://t.co/J5duvG4hSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was Going Go Have Drinks Tonight  With Myself. But I Lied Shawty Said come Over She Will Make us Drinks 😊😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC By taking Air Force One on a trip to a country that doesn't have an extradition treaty with US?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing from leadership in Butte County and Santa Barbara about the devastating loss experienced with wildfire. Gre… https://t.co/FZIFThH1Yy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Willow is ready for our Reiki 1 students to arrive! The altar is set. The house is buzzing with positive energy! @… https://t.co/SBhjmelcDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repjohnlewis Keep up the fight!! We appreciate it and happy birthday! Thank you for all you have done for America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bitch really went to go sleep in the break room for a HOUR until she got off! 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow #RussianDoll on @netflix is damn good TV, thanks for recc @nifferty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk: Elon u scared the wits outa me again. I'm a REAL REGISTERED NURSE who gets emotionally involved in the p… https://t.co/tllvdLVzDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[An example of something that bugs me is a person of color can make a post and say “only a face a strong black woman… https://t.co/7STDty9LFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. In so many areas involving difficult conversations on race, class, gender equity that require self-reflection… https://t.co/h7XFG8fFI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MommaTNYC @Kx7xxx @NYWFP @SenSchumer @SenGillibrand @AOC I’m not looking for an argument and don’t feel the need t… https://t.co/877rWWEQlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump and GOP promised economic growth much better than Obama's. That's not what happened https://t.co/XD2vAdG0CW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everNeverTrump @ida_skibenes Thoughts: I'm glad I live in Oregon, The Dr. should be reported for breaking patient… https://t.co/4NIwYaV9mU]]></document><document><![CDATA[... *pokes a @DaemonX * I know it’s last minute, but whatcha doing tomorrow? (What? I admit, I was considering wuss… https://t.co/WdFfTdj2Mt]]></document><document><![CDATA[MURDERING NEWBORNS and aiding and abeding illegals couldn't have anything to do with it right Cuomo!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙏🏽😈 #prayforthewickedtour @ Valley View Casino Center https://t.co/hR8TzhNGHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great move Amazon - AOC is an idiot.....especially not good for people of NY!  AOC Blasted with Massive Billboard o… https://t.co/eW38YF00lY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to work with a talented group of studio and office leaders @SmithGroup San Francisco #WomensHistoryMonth2019… https://t.co/43aen4xCEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porque gastar en una dependencia como #profeco si no pueden solucionar el abuso de @NaturgyMx Para auditar básculas… https://t.co/mX6pWzQt6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jarredamato Between the World and Me is also an incredible audiobook. Hearing it in Coates own voice is incredible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[{Hold The Mustard}  #ootd #ootdfashion #style #mystyle #fashion #njblogger #zara #zarastreetstyle #sweet&amp;spark… https://t.co/dkUkCYcr2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don Sweeney: "I don't know if we're necessarily going to do anything else. We'll continue to make calls."]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the most disturbing tweets I have ever seen... that is saying a whole lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#capturebaypath On the Freedom Trail in front of the 54th Regiment Monument. Embracing history. https://t.co/EbivSL37rl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yungkreflo That shit was so fucking stupid at this point I’m fucking upset!! They sounded an looked stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Kingsway Community Life Centre https://t.co/BWy1sSpsFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I am nobody but I do understand and I won't play their game anymore https://t.co/eW6srZztLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations #DAG #4brothers @ Tavern on Broad https://t.co/FXaS0vi84A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@njfarmerwife @valrhonausa @CupCakeLady1313 @CMANGO @DannyLeBlanc24 @dega_boy_87 @4judyblue @Pixxydoodle… https://t.co/Ah1Ape3fsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I make wayyyy more bands as a young scholar 👩🏾‍🏫 and cultural critic and executive director than I make from music.… https://t.co/SE3vj7sx56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DangMattSmith Me: Go thru 20 damn surgeries. Esp. my 17th 1 which was I had to wear somethin' called a "halo" on my face for 4 mo..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fully funded 😊 Thank you so so much for the donations for my sweet kiddos!! https://t.co/TldBYtq2Ux via @donorschoose]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaNenaDeBrigard Ese par de fichas, llevan su izquierda y su odio en la democracia, hasta en el último rincón de su… https://t.co/he8oMs9XQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nuestros ganadores del concurso de deletreo en español, Marium Zahra y Uriel Duarte, muchas felicidades 🎉 gracias… https://t.co/NPAqofDQ15]]></document><document><![CDATA[catch me dead (or single) before i fall for a guy who wears sports jerrseys as everyday fashion]]></document><document><![CDATA[The presidential suite didn’t appear on a board agenda until after the College spent over $100k on architectural dr… https://t.co/cMkE7yovo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson I was right agin , ROSENSTEIN needs to be "FIRED" @seanhannity]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of the Jonas Brothers getting back together I think I should sing Year 3000 at karaoke tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OlisaEloka22 That is why the Bible says that you know them by the fruit they bare. You will know if there fruit is good or if it is rotten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gem 💎 of the Desert  🌵 Best Kept Secret #travelphotography #traveldesert #thankyounext #travelers #california… https://t.co/PxCPQXMmVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timehop just reminded me that one time I went to a school dance with a guy who smelled like Chic Fil A. We never talked after that dance...]]></document><document><![CDATA[5) At least this time the driver was arrested but we will see where it goes...I'm just sick of the dead victim bein… https://t.co/06ZEwlQRay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CblGuyChris What other sports are they neglecting on basic espn channels? They paid $1+B for the right2air all UFC… https://t.co/BxtnRipGo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to organize to win in #NC09 and take another bite out of #GOPVoterSuppression #GOPCorruption]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chronic pain is something that has changed my entire life. I don’t act the same. I don’t walk the same. I don’t bre… https://t.co/6IrxF8XXA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was hoping the snow last night would have been enough to have work be cancelled today but no such luck 🙈🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cajegroup Amen! I dedicate at least two hours every morning even if it means getting up at 4 AM because time with… https://t.co/DgZ3ifnPCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a Crooked Web We Weave by Monica H Thomas #booktrailer  #bookauthor #bio #summary  #Book amazonbooks… https://t.co/hSHWjt6p7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomselliott @RichLowry @JRubinBlogger This woman has proven herself to be full of C***.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gladysperez805 @soyguu4 @CidEloisa @Carlos20203084 @1Fashionisima @BebaDril7 @barricada_azul1 @matygarcia… https://t.co/Bq7w9y2Z8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Buenas tardes! Les deseo un excelente domingo familiar... aprovecho para agradecerles sus saludos y felicitaciones… https://t.co/y07IXdxD1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our introduction to fact families was tons of fun today!!! #fielderpride https://t.co/0Uo4UQLSnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willpenrievans Replace the words in your tweet “Francois” and “UK” with “Trump” and “US” and you have written my tweet for me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh wow -  feeling the love on a story I shared in response to another heartwarming wedding moment. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimKilbane @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett This will go to Supreme Court. Will not stand up...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just spent 10 minutes looking for a loaf of bread that was right In front of me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhyllisDelfin @JohnRMoffitt This goes to show we're on the Virge of becoming a police state country. Too many zeal… https://t.co/OCa8be93Pl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending all the healing prayers to you welcome to a club none of us what to be a part of but we are now warriors an… https://t.co/7AMX7UTpF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[📱🔌 Do you ever take time to unplug from social media?  • I’m just coming back from a couple of days unplugged and I… https://t.co/12NuhfoHyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Grateful Hearts,💕 Good morning Gracious and loving God,🙌🏽 Thank You for waking me up this morning.… https://t.co/FzvBwEui25]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ex told me to get ready bc he’s taking me out to my favorite restaurant and won’t take no for an answer 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smile - got that #FridayFeeling ? #TGIF @ZooEcomuseum @YourMorning #leweekend #arcticfox #SmileOn https://t.co/4QqqD4mcm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This came out a whole lot meaner than I intended it to be. For that I apologize. I've never been cheated on but I'm… https://t.co/eCJjrzliwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Evening🌷 *https://t.co/s88lSmxaKS Shop my *eStore 24 hours @ Blackshear, Georgia https://t.co/5hXfmN5BXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessxcajustxne you with the PB &amp; J before the trip &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody was real mad when she got home from the emergency vet last night. Truth be told, someone’s still mad 24 ho… https://t.co/tzfqVE9BAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi princesa si se mueve mucho será que va ser futbolista como los papis 😭😂😍🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@writementor Bluebeard + TUMBLING A 16yo elite gymnast’s Olympic dreams are at risk when she gets… https://t.co/ydaYJPgarS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHarris707 @d_ast777 @Jj051301 @SeptemberJulie @ArleneKowalczyk @TheBread_OfLife @carmelitequotes… https://t.co/TmE75PMn5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrezonKing There are some podcasts I want that I can't get with stitcher and music sharing]]></document></documents></author>