<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[You ride around all day smoking weed &amp; don’t have a single lighter in your car https://t.co/AY7myFrmAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning world..... #verseoftheday #believer #loveandlight💫 @ Lake Arbor, Maryland https://t.co/hPX4UtA2rk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have like three outfit changes a day so if you see me looking different ... mind your business]]></document><document><![CDATA[Custodian, Rita Favela works to makes sure our Computer Labs are continually protected from bacteria at The Corral!… https://t.co/OQCFOdIPpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 Good. He’s not done a damn thing except collect his check.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genesis 3:6 (KJV)  And when the woman saw that the tree was good for food, and that it was pleasant to the eyes, an… https://t.co/f9sRCABwuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was going up the stairs @ work and the wind literally PUSHED me omg i almost fell]]></document><document><![CDATA[So those Hoax allegations were false and there was no proof( I’m guessing that interview with those brothers wasn’t… https://t.co/pa3TXpCZXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertalanmorse Love you my co creator of our amazing daughters and oh yeah five grandkids]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m 12000 percent over all of this injustice happening against POC. Im 13000 percent over white DUDES getting off w… https://t.co/xXlzw6Xqp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[my 21st is legit the next thing im looking forward to just in case i can't go to vidcon]]></document><document><![CDATA[amazon limited edition New Jersey Barbie doll !!! @barbie #Happy60thBarbie @ Amazon Books https://t.co/SWIK1mRgof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelBalcom1 @realannapaulina Teachers aren’t supposed to be armed. And realistically if a gun were properly sto… https://t.co/wZLBKrMT6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack @Zwoodbutcher “Stupid is as Stupid Does” quote from a famous person Forest Gump!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations friend on having your precious little blessing! 💕💜👶🏼 @amberly_405]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frankh511 @CoryBooker @KamalaHarris Apologize....never. But their credibility tanked. And that’s hard to do when u start at zero😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[NCA All Star national Champion Premier Cheer Sabre’s small senior D2-B #ncanationals @ Kay Bailey Hutchison Convent… https://t.co/rB33oyvbvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles I have never been so heartbroken and felt like such a failure as I have trying to get my hands on you… https://t.co/S7vJ5IEEFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[this just fucking infuriated me and broke my heart all at the same time]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏🏼  I second your pledge @AyeshaRekhi.  Change happens when people commit to it and speak up. #GenderPledge… https://t.co/yEtmpSGzQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDept @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo Failed  presidency. Proof yet again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitchyTeam Does she not understand there are two other co-equal branches of government? Dumb as Rocks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep watching this and thinking if that girl in the vid was me I would fucking die omg 🤧 I love him 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FallonTonight funds for my son to pay hospital bills https://t.co/SMjiti7fK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Garvgraphx @boston_jon1982 @adamcbest Please spear a thought for all who won't make it back home]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved Captain Marvel, I was already crying a minute into the movie during the intro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aptly_engineerd Maybe @MeghanMcCain is crying because someone else ate all the donuts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate that my apartment has literally no sound proofing.   Why can't the people having conversations I am forced t… https://t.co/KbLzE9OtcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kieran_nee @zarawesome Absolutely this. Big companies have whole expert staff to make sure they are following best… https://t.co/vjQ5gXVCHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheerFessions1 Four fantastic teams!!!  But don’t count out Infinity Royals as well!  #Apple #Proud]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a way to cap a deal - @naiopcolorado 2018 Deal of the Year, @gaylordrockies in @AuroraGov.  Congrats to… https://t.co/Z2GiMse9RC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilevin In this day and age why shouldn't a woman be able to  shoot his dick off? Oh yeah, we can!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a very nice time supporting the school and district at this fun family event. So happy I got to run Sofia’s fir… https://t.co/hbNbChsVQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tremendous speakers at @CPAC2019 ! @charliekirk11 @RealCandaceO @michellemalkin were on fire - getting ready for 20… https://t.co/z22umHsydj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not even try to steal my chewchew, lady. #rescuedog #schipperke #cupcake #dogsofinstagram @ Pittsburgh, Pennsylv… https://t.co/WwNnc2sdE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[what’s in my #imperfectproduce box? swing over to my #youtube (link in bio) to see what #fruits and #veggies i’m… https://t.co/kSnJZnkf2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think dropping your phone on your face hurts, try having a cat knock your yeti off a ledge and the corner of th… https://t.co/Bn8Va21TjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tawm23 DUDE!! i am just figuring all this out - how do i know which ones are the best??? i am having a crisis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HornyFacts I had to know what the hell this was. HornyFacts? I'm not trying to be a jerk, it's just so strange. Ho… https://t.co/Vmoo9aB0lc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun how the over weight fat girl thinks she is fit and knows what she’s doing with exercise and form lmao!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 @ellievan65 Fake Fart Fiend Fucker Freak Fat ass  Sorry I couldn’t help the last one.😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cocopomapooh @hallmarkchannel @IamLaceyChabert @brennan_elliott @AllOfMyHeartTV @BGrossbardProds Absolutely! #AOMH4PLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump do you know what UNCONSTITUTIONAL means? See you in court buddy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter for a chance to win the Santa Rita 120 Hours in London Sweepstakes now. No purchase necessary. Must be 21+ https://t.co/wglFEYHAg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JellyRoll615 I’m so very sorry &amp; will keep you &amp; your family in our prayers 💜🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days you just gotta sit on the kitchen floor and cry it out no matter how much your cats think it’s disrupting their dinner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t walk up my ass if you don’t want to be hit by the door I’m opening ;) not being metaphorical this just happened]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp... Who wants to prank call Canseco first? Lol https://t.co/9HDzIjN1aX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski Run! Run for the exit!  It's loaded! She likes to masturbate with it!  Think of the germs on the bullets!  Run!]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be fair I think we were LIT that night because I don’t remember this either!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finchfrii @Indiana_Beto My God, I don’t even recognize my country anymore!! Corruption, Sleaze, Racism, Human Traf… https://t.co/fYlobewoB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a scale of 1-10, how bad is traffic on "Spaghetti Junction"? I voted It's bad on WSB. What's your vote? https://t.co/wXdSlnJqSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wildsunshinesky @Ibelievthehype I love this scientific disproval of this theory!!! Science wizards taught you well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @KimStrassel @WSJ Day 3 of your fake National Emergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bucket list ✔️  #badasscaptain #StacyPink #scubadiving #scubasquadnation #badasscaptain #Stacypink #bahamas… https://t.co/o1GwTfDvAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have officially entered the freezing cold, sleep deprived, waiting for my 3:30 am flight, grumpy part of this trip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got tickets to @whydontwemusic here in Kansas for my daughters first concert. She's so excited. We are so read… https://t.co/t8YhfrDnH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The devil attacks when we’re the most vulnerable. https://t.co/4N8YOGenqB via @GregLaurie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parker_krupic Hi, we specialize in Design and Developing excellent Mobile Apps for both iOS and Android platforms!… https://t.co/7gGIHQcyme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_a_ronRose Meet Mordecai😂  Morty Morts Mista Mista Morts Morty poo poo head Mort Bort https://t.co/EkneFvBpKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[YAAY!! 🙌🏾 Let the equitable implementation planning begin! #onwardtowardsequity #cleanpowertothepeople]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rahatheart1 @DrMarthaGulati @somedocs @TChanMD @SamRRazaMD @DrKristieLeong @heartdoc45 @Heartdoc530… https://t.co/4hdsCX2VJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torontomike On it! Has @lievefamke received her assignment yet? Pre-printed name tags this time for the regulars?… https://t.co/KSWeqrA5tW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FandomIl I wouldn’t know what to do with it but it would be so cool to have one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nanigranados_ No! Haha I was obsessed with the Beatles and then the Jonas Brothers were introduced to me around 7th grade  🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[For reference in case you needed a reminder. Please bring them back. @Target https://t.co/ro7oIjc50W]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will be Paul once Tim converts him @paulplemons0 @dan_clemons @southman91 @Yoimstorm @KaylaGamble122]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickoleraskey I don’t think I ever said that you supporter the wall. I just generalized Trump supporters and Trump… https://t.co/7rSjBYS9mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why did democrats give Jordan 5 Billion for a wall but not the US?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, Nashville Predators play against "A Bunch of Jerks" from Carolina 🤭😉  (cc: @canesfan25 ) https://t.co/koae72DmYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep giving vets freedom boners and they keep buying me drinks I love America]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just read news about #TomassoCiampa will have surgery which he will be out of NXT Takeover NY 💔😭 #GetWellSoonTomasso https://t.co/KIpnJmcr67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EugeneMcCarty @Acosta @POTUS And U seem 2 admire that behavior in the leader of the country - which speaks volumes about U &amp; UR ilk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great team performance in Nashville what a free kick from the skipper @stephhoughton2 and @lilkeets deserved that g… https://t.co/fA1z928vM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Twinning with one of my best girls! #GreatMindsThinkAlike @GrangerSign @GrangerIPSD204 @GrangerPTA #FutureReady204… https://t.co/O9vQKQje6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElizaFx @kckabay @OhNoSheTwitnt I also had 4 vodka sodas this afternoon so yes, I am an overachiever 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao I just know somebody from Toledo gone where this as soon as the weather breaks 🚮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnOberg Thank you for sharing. I would never know that pigs are able to solve puzzles. Thank you for your tirele… https://t.co/JwWrg3njVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody:  Me: New season of @GhostAdventures starts Saturday!!   @Zak_Bagans @AaronGoodwin @BillyTolley @jaywasley https://t.co/zz0eD0xucO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notbrianfallon He's a demon. Gotta be something different.  Could have his something normal for his name when he's… https://t.co/5HqgCihNms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt Nathanson Night Two #philadelphiayoureinmyheart #singshissadheart #tla #cheesesohard @ TLA https://t.co/4QgHT1BGD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dean_R_Lomax Yeah, oops. I was so excited about extinct creature ‘coffin birth’ that I didn’t bother to look up wh… https://t.co/xW90mObpfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Candace Owens. As to be the craziest one of all. Twitter do your thing!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaSpillYT omg.....she’s always causing some controversy to stay relevant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piccilover33 @ninjatamgent @chinkydoodles @rebekah_wells @ivykimberlyn Ummm, maybe?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else single &amp; wants to stay that way but want to go on a cute date as friends today lmk I’m down 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariecountryman @QuietManc @bunkybun @Dennis_Lintz @haloefekti @lilith2u @BlakandBlack @deeshanger @Communista2… https://t.co/7Lf0d4G80T]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fucking 9th grader slide up on my Bev’s picture😭 y’all my baby doesn’t look that old now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn’t that be something huh? #hustleup babes! Let’s go make is happen. #2019 is ours! I need a re-set! Time to a… https://t.co/lA7uxTZ04b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottwarner18 I get it...super hero, Superman, flying, kryptonite, saving,cape, bald bad guy.  Looks fine to me.  Sweet dreams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#motivationalmonday surround yourself with amazing and talented people; watch, listen and learn... @JeffGordonWeb… https://t.co/kXyfrBKgYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson  Really enjoyed what you had to say on msnbc. You provide such clarity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuscadineBLine We saw you guys at your first time at the Grand Ole Opry and you were amazing!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HAStarsRead1 @shallweteach3 @KDGhoustonAP @MsRiveraEla @Menard_2016 @MargauxTeaches Thanks!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Kardashian’s are taking over my life. I just had a whole ass dream about them 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think more like she's tired of the constant questions. She went with the majority. So they need to leave her alon… https://t.co/D7L4QLVyzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaston_films Lupitas performance as well as what you had to think about after the film was over]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up this morning and pet Jasper, and he didn’t move, even when I shook him a bit... I about lost my mind. The… https://t.co/3MwZk8KSQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tweet 2/2: 3) expectations matter, kids rise to the occasion 4) relationships matter and his teachers and aides hav… https://t.co/YKSf3g1ymp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si ok, pongan sus albums en spotify please, para poder honorarlos escuchando sus discos.]]></document></documents></author>