<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Bellaknowsitall @landorosario Ya are so happy about making it to the 2nd round in 20 years. Lol go ahead and celebrate that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Music of the Millennium” Like (or Retweet) That? S2 E4 of #WaitWhat with @KimoraBlac on @WorldOfWonder’s… https://t.co/maHYGSHK0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[From each according to his ability, to each, according to his needs. Karl Marx, 1875 (who was constantly broke, b… https://t.co/IQCXIp1PZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reutituti3 With this smile am sure all is good and went out happy from there lol 😜😜😜😜😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamMoeller Have there been studies conducted which looks into root shear during the winter in the NE and whether… https://t.co/64tGyltgy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMSeiki @BC_EHS Unfortunately I’m not sure! Since I’m on the island now I’m not sure what @apbc873 Public Educatio… https://t.co/IvfdOaRDui]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so dismayed at how so many people are rallying to discredit survivors and to defend Vic instead of thinking abo… https://t.co/q9tMInRVzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dude was tryna get my attention for MONTHS but I kept curving him. Was bored one Saturday and decided to accep… https://t.co/ofdVuG49VL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anything is possible when you put in that work @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/faEyjvAhfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the thing about All That. I loved it. But why reboot it, especially with kid actors these days that just are… https://t.co/uo1LoCBAgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSeaboldt @bkparallax Thank you.  KKs so far in this guys head it’s not funny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rexglacer Guns kept the world free in two world wars and guns are the only reason we are free today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonBream That's why I continue to live in Wilmington NC we still have that southern hospitality here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump How can a person love a person they don’t even know?   You guys are a cult.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarshLichblade @terrycrews @realDonaldTrump “Outrage” is the new way of dismissing any kind of challenge to your s… https://t.co/G67cu61kfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilyseh @IlhanMN @staceyabrams @HaleyLive @KatieHill4CA @RepKatiePorter @RepPressley @AOC @RepJayapal… https://t.co/AZI6hCb28j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorSmith1102 you being serious?! Keep puttin a hurtin on some baseballs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This what the lying, phony, cheating,corrupt, treasonous, greedy, self centered, two faced, anti American, repugnan… https://t.co/MAIBlZstca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephynb @nytpolitics I’m certain we are not talking about the same thing. I’m not sure what you’re getting at. Yo… https://t.co/Bo1FcGgFSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC #Facts and well said ..show what they think of everyday working people..smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dead in the middle of two generations I’m lil bro and big bro all a once]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMisterChef @Xbox @crackdown Agree, the up close details blow me away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddyNews1 @JimCarrey Donald Trump never liked Sen. John McCain and claims that  McCain isn't a war hero, in which… https://t.co/bb6u0dhMzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come out to the pentagon at 8 to support us as we play in the ELITE 8!! 💙💛🏀 @ Sanford Pentagon Basketball Academy https://t.co/267kcAOaUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t blame AB one bit. If I was in the situation he is with the kind of leverage he has, I wouldn’t want to go f… https://t.co/NE8aN2S6tl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@herenowhere3 What would have necessitates a hearing?  Feel like I missed something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She accidentally killed three people, Soledad. There was no evidence that she was speeding, driving under the influ… https://t.co/mQsC603DHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Khan Younis needs to be leveled completely at this point .....nothing productive is coming from this hot bed of ter… https://t.co/fIMi1Smh7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whstancil Even if it’s narrow several high folks will be caught up in it.  He’s already laid out the predicate con… https://t.co/K4zZdiQeq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the end, The Series May Be On The Way Out, but it will live on forever in our hearts.  And if whatever comes nex… https://t.co/adI7Bd22f8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my baby boy simonvicsays! 💕❤💋😘😍🤗❤💕 #randomVegasTrip #lastMinuteVegas #spurofthemomenttrip #vegasbaby… https://t.co/7XdCdUigwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RGreggKeller @missouriscout Lol Stop It! Everyone isn’t getting a “call” I love Dave but one day y’all are going t… https://t.co/GvgSPiGIAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rooting for Spike, Blanchard, Ruth Carter and team If Beale Street tonight. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annakripli @grandeshorny @ArianaGrande Mine would be:  1. GIAW 2. Everytime  3. Better off 4. Goodnight n go 5. Breathin 6. Get well soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice to see this finally out! Neurocognitive Aging and Brain Signal Complexity - Oxford Research Encyclopedia of Ps… https://t.co/7DgspbgJyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kavita1010 @JoelRRenner @AlHopper_ @katyb_spencer @DreaVilleneuve @joshmccormack @alysonshane @ScottOntiveroz… https://t.co/dtRLZHWlAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Odio a Petro, Odio a Uribe, Odio a Duque...Odio a todos los politicos de mi país, fin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daniela Alvarez Contreras crossed 5K. Time 00:30:01, pace 09:40 min/mile, est. finish 8:23 am https://t.co/Ef82ojlBvP #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re here ask for Beemer. 9132615368 Bbehm@smkia.com https://t.co/oYaprlCZEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samuelson rips into a fastball by Rhodes but hits it right at Cerillo in left. Rhodes gets out of the inning only a… https://t.co/TcqSWKaXjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariofraioli This seems insane following an era in which biggest “household name” distance stars (Rupp, Farrah, et… https://t.co/TJb2NdgxqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NituPerez @patriciajaniot @carlaangola @NTN24 @jguaido @Diego_Arria @napoleonbravo Ya firmamos más de 120K… https://t.co/OomOVGmkRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldn’t be surprised if “July Me” decides to see The Lion King on the big screen once a week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanMetzl your segment on #MorningJoe this morning was straight up REAL TALK! This is what I have been saying… https://t.co/grLeH94xH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This graffiti has been up since Saturday in the Denver’s Clayton neighborhood. The homeowners say they want to leav… https://t.co/NS4SE30NnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Michigan #PureMichigan #MidMichigan #Potholes 1 out of 1,000's of them here  , I hope  New @GovWhitmer makes sure… https://t.co/FlL7zbq9gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisFox5SD Don’t mess with the long arm of the law @JussieSmollett 🤣😂 https://t.co/QxWNFS7GnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great season opener didn’t meet my goals but Top 20 in the state for class of 2022 in 3200 @RNC_Sports @RCHSBulldogs https://t.co/xmVKuWf0S8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHSommers @clairlemon @Quillette I don’t get it, why are you so connected to Quillette? Are they paying you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol so I try to wash my comforter .... it’s so big for my dryer. Now what do I do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lengthly, proper set from @yottomusic in San Fran tonight. Man is a presence behind the decks. AZ is in for a tre… https://t.co/c6HYWsr0E0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nmknmk Hi Neil, If you have any plans to hire a resource from an agency to work on your project remotely, we would… https://t.co/VOfQEFb3FX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCPSSuper proposes no longer giving 5 paid holidays to administrators who work 260 days a year. Jcps has 235 admin… https://t.co/CmVUyQVaLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uhh… #mariomaker2 in JUNE?!?!? That’s too long. The wait begins. #nintendodirect]]></document><document><![CDATA[The US House passed the bill to terminate the emergency declaration on border security.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadPergram Don’t worry Chabot is to stupid to ever be president, if you voted for him are you a little embarrassed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home is wherever I’m with you @ Hamilton, Ontario https://t.co/jtxdnZF9vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_thacalm Which is why Luke Walton’s job is in question. It’s more than likely because they were in small ball agai… https://t.co/UGvWV0dRvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Billy Bock by @shortfingerbeer @ Kickoff — https://t.co/LbanODHmgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our long national nightmare is over #Bryceharper signs with the #Phillies https://t.co/joYOrjMn32]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #TheDonaldLibrary Burned down ! He lost both books ! Hadn't finished coloring one of them ! https://t.co/rvdCnABtsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝🍭😍😘 @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/aiEUwdSONR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THE_METAL_SOUL @Alberto_Mega4 @medranoazteca La gente de santos lo odia por su culpa se fue siboldi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been wishing other men “Happy Valentine’s Day!” and everyone’s getting a real kick out of it:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the fuck!???? Are we defending drug dealers now?? Nah. Couldn’t be me ever, never ever. I swear some of y’all… https://t.co/mVGfpvOOLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because the reality of real life situations, esp end of life of stuff- is something you cant learn in a textbook. Y… https://t.co/zMxQZlXB0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish today’s USD WBB #SummitTourney game was on WatchESPN (free with my cable) rather than ESPN+. Regardless, Go Yotes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProperOpinion @terryschappert @StudiosShelly Liar! Washington was at LEAST 6 raccoons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ciela7990 @Eliecerdrum @nikolibertad Y tu como sabes que no lo hizo, a caso le pediste un informe? tiene que pedir… https://t.co/134ryQr5QD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdoukmas @haymarketbooks @aimeelevitt @Chicago_Reader Interesting! I’ll take a look @sparklebliss]]></document><document><![CDATA[The shower tunes you so choose can really be the make or break in the outlook of your day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep reading complaint after complaint about this yet people in a position to do something are doing nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epl fan boys have to get over themselves. Not a knock at you Keith. Celtic plays in Europe and can count on at leas… https://t.co/VjBTZjFxhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frups1 @washingtonpost Article I sect 2 clause 5 allows the House to pick its own speaker. It is also sole judge o… https://t.co/0ngDbhDu92]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever since you caught that out there bug, I’ve caught me a ‘round here buzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Desperado9025 Hey, a NJ town tried to fight this. Got sued and ended up paying for the whole thing. ISIS was seen… https://t.co/VT3wiemBSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJmountexplorer Far from it. I watch other leagues on a regular basis that have it far worse.   And it isn’t close… https://t.co/iGYmJHfpcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAstrocomm @theresphysics Also, we have more useful things to do than beating our collective head against that wall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soon whom ever it may be will see that I am me always will be me, all my friends and family know who I am and will… https://t.co/UlV0qe2gPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @ManilaUp_Mag for this lovely featured article &amp; interview on me 😊🙏❤️  https://t.co/OOsgHZ8zub… https://t.co/krE8hwtte8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fabulous day for a little ski de fond...except if you forget to brake! 🎿 ☀️😎 @ Parc régional Val-David Val-Morin https://t.co/5C6CEbO44d]]></document><document><![CDATA[solo! honered to work and create #music #indiefilm #scifimusic #percussion #compser #reggae #latinjazz #latinas… https://t.co/5lP6hH8gdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strahan must be gay .. every day he has a queer guy on his show  Strahan &amp; Sarah https://t.co/YwFtQ6z3pR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching BBQ Pitmasters and they’re cooking chicken to 170 and prime rib roast to 140-145...]]></document><document><![CDATA[To ensure affordability as it grows, Houston needs this to be implemented ⤵️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanCFowler I like Avery Johnson...... as a basketball athletic director... can we give him this position  @Tide1029fm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@team1885 - Thank you so much for your invitation to join your Alliance.  We are so grateful you recognized our pot… https://t.co/RI1fdOFC1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @starisbornmovie for the second time, I’m truly happy and proud to see @TheRealDiceClay do such a good job in his role.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaClinton @IlhanMN Your comment about Trump regarding white nationalism is a goddamned lie and you know it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a quality thread and I encourage anyone in a serious relationship to apply these.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @KristinGiannas @swilsonwtsp @LaurenNKowal @KendallKirkham @AmieDillaFirm @JSalomoneTV @WFLAAmanda… https://t.co/90G1rMqQ4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished #KingdomHeartsIII, and what a great game it was. As someone who’s played every entry in the series si… https://t.co/XeDqY50xrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Chilis Grill &amp; Bar in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/aSCARpForP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RorateCaeli When did reform become right wing? We desperately need reform. #reform #movement]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chulopjm @DoomsRay_ This is all kinds of lit only right as we chicanos embrace Japanese anime culture]]></document><document><![CDATA[this lady just yelled at me for no reason so uh catch me never leaving the house ever again :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamRichman @andrewzimmern @ChocolateRoomBK @FranklinFtn Like the Philly @franlkinft shoutout @AdamRichman! Think… https://t.co/dRm5KMYBCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter The next time you take a pic with a human trafficker, smile donnie. https://t.co/1uAyhJpWkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anotherseminole Unlike what that other coach didn’t do for years...... can’t wait for WT to prove the haters wrong!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evansilva I want to know is Juju ready to come out that slot and face the top Corners. He could be a bust on the o… https://t.co/47CItAjOPM]]></document></documents></author>