<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JoseLey38103628 @nataliefitzie Agreed! Everyone must feel accepted. If they don’t, they are hindered]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimdonovancbs3 @StormeWaves42 @Humility2014 😂😂😂 truer words have never been spoken!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonohueRobin @DCZooWalks @CharmCityPanda @VandyViking @kariek @aleftie @FamousBabiesC @FONZNationalZoo… https://t.co/1oviXBm42s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in Sound Pony pre gaming and waiting for this line for Hippie Sabotage to go down. Fuuuuck waiting in the cold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaiannaqueen woah woah woah, tell them u got a man &amp; to back tf up😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yankeecannuck @PinkSparkleYums @steve45220 @dennisdiclaudio @MugabeJonathan @nypost U need to chill out. If u need… https://t.co/lllUL7zQU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatsaiToo @GenixDJ @EL_Waves @iBluestone @REALMAORLEVI My hope has started to faaaaade https://t.co/bZxFNBPAm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianeLong22 @GroupHomepage @ChrisRowland9 @kidgolferman @KilllerBee777 @karen_erotoo1 @KatherineWolfr2 @harjo111… https://t.co/wkHLPvvc43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwelijournal have you announced all the scholarship awardees for the NYC #kweli19 conference?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you drive like a dick ima personally go out of my way to piss you the fuck off 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would throw myself in front of a train for Klaus Hargreeves #UmbrellaAcademy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ask_Spectrum does it typically take you almost a month to apply a web payment?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SoulSunday: You hold the power to your destiny! Never let anyone convince you that you are not enough. Continue to… https://t.co/xA5JSt5cZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I call my mom and even if she is teaching a yoga class she will pick up the phone..... ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @RepAoc I am excited for the United States of America to have you in the position you're in today. #GirlPower… https://t.co/GL3nQckHfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPDONeill ON A RECENT TRIP TO MIDTOWN MANHATTAN, I APPROACHED A GROUP OF MTA OFFICERS.THEY WERE WEARING BODY CAME… https://t.co/T2ixx7RC7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Animated GIF popular on Instagram today is WordArt that says "your cool." Makes me wanna lose my cool, or should I… https://t.co/7VULyb4umQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is really amazing and I’ll be there soon for I love Dubai  and thank you for posting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta be tough to be so corrupt. So much criminal activity yet to do and so little time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[White woman tears are one of the most resilient and pervasive tools of white supremacy pass it on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeakerCarlie @IowagirlinSoMd @PeakerTees It’s hard not to smile just looking at that tee; such memories 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep. Doc Stewart has blocked me too. These pro-vax doctors are sure pro-censorship!  Check out Stewart McM (… https://t.co/y1ZYyUpzWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out with the Legend Olympic gold metal winner and UFC Champ @HenryCejudo what a class act !! https://t.co/vcZOZeMGTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @kayleesticker for your POY nomination and to @MadisonAnglin05 @AnnaLowe44 @sophiagrace115 and @marlie_t41… https://t.co/7BQ8vp6FnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay &amp; #WomensHistoryMonth. You’re welcome, feminists!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HornbergerLogan I don’t know her married name now but we called her Miss. Summer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@everythingloria Awww! So cool! My Twitter wish came to life! Yay! @Caissie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinLEddy1  HELP AZ HELP US.  WEAR WITH PRIDE.  TSHIRTS Large $23.99 ExLarge $24.99  Check or money orders payable… https://t.co/9ptNBv98Da]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABaskerville10 @NBCPhiladelphia Something real bad  happened between these families  May their soul rest in peace]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 weeks from today I’ll be fear and loathing in Atlantic City. #BachelorParty https://t.co/EjC9xF7b3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeeneLaura I sign up for them even though I hate them, thinking I’ll be enlightened or meet people. Well usually n… https://t.co/cLIfuGVoG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @FLOTUS Why don’t you fight for stopping the separation of children, including babies, from parents? And i… https://t.co/vbmsa1HeBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pardon not mentioning #MiddleEast .  I assumed Men in Black will help. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PureBob It is too bad that I do not live in San Diego. My family will rarely eat anything past 7 so we could just… https://t.co/eLjv0Ys2q0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will NEVERRR ask someone for a bite of their meal or just take something off their plate to try it out of respect… https://t.co/jirHpMqJte]]></document><document><![CDATA[I officially left Vegas 90 days ago and in the 3 months of being in Texas, one of my biggest dreams is coming true!… https://t.co/VG8nFayBOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to allow yourself to have time to yourself so you can figure things out]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #surgery day! @drmeganjack is @schnittplastics in #delraybeach and doing a #mommymakeover today! After finishi… https://t.co/L5D5fs6AsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrCoachRidens @jack_dunlop @UofSC Thank you! I wanted him to be a @Mizzou Tiger. He says USC felt like the best fit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think sometimes we forget that God is for EVERYONE. While we all have free will to make our own choices, He made… https://t.co/AmFcDHIn5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JKalczuk Oh, I forgot that one...might try to catch the end. https://t.co/dm4mOcMVM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[THREAD @amjoyshow 1/ THREAD: I’ve been thinking recently that there ought be a higher standard to qualify to run fo… https://t.co/wctw1CVDt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse Reported &amp; blocked them all.  Why can’t Twitter catch these bots?  I don’t get it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bi gave u great numbers yesterday in a must win !!! Bron was like 8-23 in the most important game of the season y’a… https://t.co/bjKwNrWWYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elyssifer @gantisdant yep still have The Morality of Capitalism i brought it to school with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see @helenstravels/@Sociality2’s panel “Tomorrow’s Perfect Food Narrative” featured here! Will be live twe… https://t.co/ROPcAkF6ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[God really removes people and shows you people’s true colors boy i tell you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barriemaverick @GOtransit @GOtransitBR You are fortunate.  It’s a long slow commute from Barrie to Toronto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreciselyAlyss 🤚I have 100% done this before. Usually with sweat pants over yoga pants or leggings. Two layers of… https://t.co/ReJr60e3JS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is your presidency and you are doing a wonderful job..God bless you my President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm still so upset that "ready for ya" and "smoke and mirrors" aren't on spotify 😪😫😭 #demi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajplus @IlhanMN I am Black. You have a finite amount of time to get issues we voted for during the mid terms. Focu… https://t.co/FkJ4BSwFqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who love when you beg for their appearance are lame af. You either going or not I’m not about to beg you. Byeeeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going all in for AD, a player who might not even wanna play in Boston longer than a season, does not sound good to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark my words... I will own a small farm with lots of cute animals one day]]></document><document><![CDATA[One litre of maple syrup will last nine Canadians approximately five days when on a trip to #laketahoe #dropsleft… https://t.co/XkmnRFjsAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. My thirteen year old is a black hole.  He eats more than my extra large husband.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Friday and I work minutes away from @citybowlssouth . Today is a good day!🥝🍎🍓🍌🍍❤😊 @ City Bowls https://t.co/d55CH73VoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[my older brother legit just fell asleep on me 🤦🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/yj8hufwjrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll choose my best friend/s over any male any day of the week. it just be like that all the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dangchick1 @AnitaThom57 Crime doesn’t pay Manafort! Now do your time, all of it👏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeeCinny2 @Kokomothegreat In all seriousness...WHY is he so vain!?😝 https://t.co/3dtngHxIZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dazzlecarol @cas_33 @allyemmerson @lucretialive @lusciousvixen @feromoon @jaguarlogdrum @Jetemetet Hello and good day ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everleaffan The same here 🤬 @MStrooo6 go and fuck yourself.... What you have done to your dog is inexcusable 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA['Greta' is bloody good fun thanks to its stellar female cast  https://t.co/L16aVt7BP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This made me happy and I hope it puts a smile on ur face too @dragonsandbees]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nesha2325 @BreakandEnterTV The girl in the photo is not Soon-yi Previn. As an aside, Woody Allen wasn't married to… https://t.co/arx2AJN26K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the pleasure of attending Disney’s Fairytale Weddings Showcase today with BooBoo! What an amazing day filled wi… https://t.co/IcbnHgxxld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why I countine to drink startbucks knowing I’m lactose intolerance and it makes me hyper as heck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSwitchCTR @kat_lau @julieroginsky Although, I think that's an issue for more than just Fox, too. The other networ… https://t.co/6rKCCIqTuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be with a man that makes you feel so secure in your position that he can have  friend thats a girl . #Iwantthat  #myman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kc712 I’m so sorry. Praying for you and your children during this difficult time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thefoodiespace #kids #momlife #food #sis #love #enjoy #caviar #sushi #sweetdreams #thirstythursday #soda #pho @ Th… https://t.co/ilpWK9wsI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many great #WorldIADay nuggets being shared all over the world ❤️ That's the power of a global event! #DesignforDifference]]></document><document><![CDATA[teen posts and quotes | life, posts, quote, story of my life, teenage - inspiring picture... #funniness #laugh… https://t.co/fUIpH2XV8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fortunately I am not Superintendent,  because I wouldn’t have school when it was cold  and raining. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikkikayser1 @BoulderRamblers @walk2connect Thank you, Nikki! It was really fun - three days of learning and conne… https://t.co/d6m8RqFEjZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Oh Aaron (Feat. Nick Carter &amp; No Secrets) by @aaroncarter on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/tnwCuVeGUz https://t.co/OlDtJhR8jJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash What’s up with McCabe ratting out rosenstein on 60 min?  Sounds like McCabe is in big trouble.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Is In The Air... My Mother's Azaleas Are In Full Bloom. #ChildhoodMemories #ChildhoodHome #LittleWoods… https://t.co/VfgyYd6REI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Freshman Congresswomen Did Their Damn Job At Cohen's Hearing. So Proud of Them!! #InternationalWomensDay… https://t.co/zIydCnz7Bm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itskaitbabe @AdrianH018 @hippyjohnnykat @gabriellaleef Well it's understandable that you didn't know. I said you'r… https://t.co/TCGE4C6E2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1madwoman1962 @MelindaYoe @merabethjames @SuezWillson @monicasloves @WoodsCher @JackConnie @CathyBawden844… https://t.co/fqx3a2Gr4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bresciap32 @YaGirlYani You thought I was bad with thank u next... You haven’t seen anything yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[remembering when Disney World was my playground for six months 😭 . . . #dcpalumni #disneyworld #hollywoodstudios… https://t.co/VJkxkx2LZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving a dog is not the same as leaving a kid. i don’t think pets understand. parents can FaceTime their kids. I h… https://t.co/RtqENoDSsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jiveDurkey If he recalls who was sitting there at the time...my guess is they are kicked out of the club?   Don't… https://t.co/CBTWcLpBhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmataconis @nooil4pacifists @ericinva @JazzShaw https://t.co/H09FjnzVQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe the Jonas Brothers are actually coming back!! I wanna go to a concert and do a _ years later thing… https://t.co/1s8OUwtggg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahgrafferty, YES, YES, YES!!! The build up was SO worth the wait! 🔥💋💥🥃❤️ #darvey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh In my family we have so many from different race.I'm Mexican,and we have whites,blacks, Armenian,Japanese… https://t.co/A8LNJyQyRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonEsterman @Jamie1074 @WalshFreedom More attention to@mental health might help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiecouric @AmericanCancer I am 53 and finally going to be screened. Primary appointment in April....schedule scr… https://t.co/aMAuAwy6Bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ordered the special and the waitress said, “just so you know it’s a lot of food.” I didn’t leave a bite, bitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tonithecat32 @1gingerbeauty @buddy_gizmo @deborah26449389 @fluffybasil @Kathlee54272830 @ToughGuyMankas… https://t.co/F59tmvIdHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol Nevertrumpers are the enemy. Flat out. Screw you bill Kristol. . Your   nonvote counts for a vote for trump.   Fuck you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a pleasure hosting our UWG alumni today. It’s always good to see our former members of this program. Looking f… https://t.co/NQ7SZyrjkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Associate Manager - Environmental Services" at Aramark by asking for referrals. It'… https://t.co/a0aSNJcdhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherrig108 @BeatriceLacy @Backpackjohn1 @Ariatnachantal @happy02013guy @Jonatha97947998 @BarbaraWatley @LudMarx1… https://t.co/c8vp61vInQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohitsmeale i LOVE hearing 8d audio + rain that shit gets me in my feelings]]></document></documents></author>