<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This pretty much explains why everyone is like “why is our Slack so quiet?”  It’s hard to use if you don’t know it’… https://t.co/MZ4Pk7caIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too bad que #LaVoixTVA soit un pro forma.  Ce Davide a une voix formidable]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rodando🎬 #latin #tvserie #actors aquí con dos talentosos actores #actor #actrices #mexican #🎬 #🎭 en Miami, Florida https://t.co/iQeMc1Nzee]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are looking LIVE at the Iowa State Capitol! #iowa @ Iowa State Capitol https://t.co/k81bV8ZtmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHolmerr @WesternMastery Problem is someone who tells you they can “sell” anything.  I can’t sell shit...but I… https://t.co/hFkeYGtUaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CriticalRole @TitmouseInc @jennifermuro Im pledging 100. Because yall deserve to make this the best it can be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna know the workout @BeckyLynchWWE does because I wanna grow up to be her. Better late than never.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job is now open at Enterprise Holdings in #Kent, OH. Follow us and turn on mobile alerts to hear about jobs li… https://t.co/i8P5x85Lh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[DRAX THE DESTROYER RUINED RIC FLAIR’S BIRTHDAY AND NOW I’M GLAD HE DIED IN INFINITY WAR #WWEAtlanta]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can start to smell the #scent of the #litmosphere that is the #backroom at goldsoundsbar I am #soexcited to be j… https://t.co/hYxjv2vfCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to our advancers so far at National Qualifiers: Julia Scott, Szofia Wiksell and Emily Fischer. More advanc… https://t.co/74VttrvMug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubncheryl  👀👀👀 this is what your text was about huh? I thought you were talking about the Bryce Harper stuff.… https://t.co/CL2altxqAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[A minor point, I know, but calling out racism is not, in fact, racism itself. And if you think somebody is falsely… https://t.co/0yrU8vds34]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregLandsman In addition, we have numerous analyses that show which programs work and why, and why other programs… https://t.co/6llaeK9u0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m very lucky and blessed to have been able to have seen Sonny play in 2012. Such an inspiration]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mez_merrill @robmitc69885060 @goodenough_fu @BEyes60 @CityofTwoRivers @frances_van @Mark_R1_5VY @johnnyrockhill… https://t.co/EhTQnq8tBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seasicksheep No need to apologize at all. You have given me great alternative information. Much appreciated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX @danpfeiffer The entire GOP is "what is wrong with American politics," especially @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You all can see plump Trump receiving a similar reception and tipping $40 after buying 3 tacos. Right? Right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Judgenap @Judgenap You don't know your right hand from your left! You are a disgrace to someone who should know better.  Enjoy the swamp!]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAVE YOU PEOPLE HEARD A ASSININE  THOUGHT BY YOUR WEAK PRESIDENT THE HIS PART OF GOVERNMENT ARE TOP SECRET OVER CON… https://t.co/mJsQOSYy5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another beautiful day in Miami with nikkiberryman #miami #usa #southbeach #southbeachmiami #florida surfcomberhotel… https://t.co/13zqeEytpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithOneShot518 @GailSimone He's had it a couple times in continuity. It's never really worked out for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmBradWalker @BRIANMBENDIS Don’t think I didn’t consider sneaking out and seeing it solo, but the wife was genuin… https://t.co/LP6bcT7liP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaneFromTheBurg @CWUAthletics The coaches poll on Nov 18, 2018, before the the playoffs and the National Champions… https://t.co/iAEiDaS7Pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HBSAlumni @keylargofoley Awesome article. I think he says what everyone thinks the first time they step foot on ca… https://t.co/X8JuQvymDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready for a fucking beer hopefully one more night here in laredo then drunk tx bound lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when 53-37 after one quarter a score you’d only see in an All-Star game. Now that’s just a Warriors-Nuggets Wednesday night game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tavern Brown Ale by @Alewerks @ Shield's Tavern — https://t.co/AwkOosOvTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lassialanen @LaceEmPodcast So @HockeywthHannah, you’re ace with rankings: Hughes/Kaako is like Matthews/Laine or S… https://t.co/Ib0zuj2QBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[we need to be educate engineers about green infrastructure. widen the tool box. more tools in the tool box. -craig… https://t.co/tonoFB6oHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Super70sSports I saw some tweets after Spurrier was drafted and they were predicting that he'd beat out John Brodi… https://t.co/b098YQVQox]]></document><document><![CDATA[I 100% know this ain’t serious, only posted it to illicit reaction, &amp; it still fucking worked. 🤢🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aquí está la Perrona @clubleonfc !! @murallaverde https://t.co/QN4M8pVPxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all better stop snitching with this shit and just slide on niggas, like if we really mad, SLIDE THEN!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rotocop_ATL @MrDane1982 HRC may have said "super predators," but BS actually voted for the crime bill of 1994 whic… https://t.co/QVVZPVWKyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robovie Nano Robot Kit - Miniature moving robot set https://t.co/it6TcW1zxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirstenPowers You are useless and despicable. I hope you lose your job and get cancer, stage four.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieSLalonde Also, I might have been speaking more about #cdnpoli than #onpoli. The OPP story is absolutely disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost all people with a few exceptions, that associate themselves with Donald Trump will eventually be conned, mar… https://t.co/g2ZiZHpvPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another of Trump's way of telling the scientific community to take a hike! Trump admin is the anti-government!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, is that Biscayne Bay? Fowey Lt House as you exit harbor on the right? Yes, I shipped out of Miami more than on… https://t.co/ZfNE1fKCtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apex_dfw_wx @_CTWeather @RickMitchellWX @GrantJNBC5 @NWSFortWorth @spann @JesseWFAA @wfaaweather @StormHour… https://t.co/3VNo9PsVVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralBPeddle @SalvArmyIHQ @SalArmySouth @CSB_SA Our marching spirit is alive &amp; well in Seattle! https://t.co/2Msm9auGf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MckKirk Interesting. It genuinely has me intrigued. And stealth is my preferred play-style. Far Cry was largely mo… https://t.co/QjryMYgR21]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine there was a “nut man” super hero and his only super power was slowly eating almonds while staring at your family]]></document><document><![CDATA[secured tickets for @tameimpala  it was tough everyone, i waited 15 minutes before 12 in the waiting room, even red… https://t.co/PBNKWazyZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AzorcanGlobal He shouldn’t even be considered. Oilers need to stop going convenient and actually do a real search.]]></document><document><![CDATA[to listen to Eric Holder's comments about stacking the supreme court to get back at Trump, that pretty much solidif… https://t.co/NIBwvLklwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blackintel1 Nothing to do with race,,,, more about knowing who are allies are in that part of the world 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers to my angels ❤ #alwaysinmyheart @ King's X Bar https://t.co/Enq0WrV8kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever just wanna stop talking and cut someone out of your life cause you know they would be better off without you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You write and think like a 3rd grader.   Never has America been so embarrassed by a president!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool (although blurry) effects on the flight to #YOW. So much for the window views. #flight https://t.co/9iaKQjycSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great distinction. Helps me think about how to approach particular stories. Some require building while others just… https://t.co/MBo2tcIK2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElliottZaagman @sdonnan @AngusGrigg About seven years too late for this public affairs tactic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me watching what the Dodgers and Kings are doing like https://t.co/UxdxQDu9fs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom’s care packages are the best care packages ❤️ love ya @delcopops https://t.co/tdWOyU7DKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CGurisattiNTN24 Si destruyendo un edificio creen que vamos a acabar la cultura traqueta y facilista, estamos tosta… https://t.co/eg4qWSobp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit I rock. I don’t genuinely believe that very frequently, but for right now I rock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExactSpy9060 I understand the difficulties of multi and zombies camos are on entirely different spectrums, but the… https://t.co/LSDoRUMKJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTSKILLS I understand your reasoning, but you don't think clubs would be willing to try it out. At the younger ages, it might work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carver County Parks-Maple Syrup Open House March 23, 2019, 11:00 a.m.-2:00 p.m. Baylor Regional Park, 10775 Co Rd 3… https://t.co/qFQqw75cii]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Beechmont Baptist Church in Louisville, KY https://t.co/vgPLuRMrxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trevorbaptiste9 see you Thursday and Friday ✌🏻 https://t.co/opw3bij1bz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCMcrush here’s me single and friendless five years later https://t.co/ZbmCBYejTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[How would the theory of separating land lease from buying housing as a way of bringing down housing costs without c… https://t.co/fsJv4CcyFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AMEN and God bless WORLD have a great night don't forget to SMILE @DennisJBolt 🔱⚡BOLTIBOLTZ CAN'T STOP WON'T STOP… https://t.co/vENrExqlxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra No shock on using that card. What about the mob going after Kavanaugh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crusader120 Yeah. Haha scared my son when that went in, I was livid. Whoops...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@El_fur_ez_Back @ChrisRifer He also pointed out the inequity of Territory (implying both size of territory and dept… https://t.co/glld3FhMbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SAWohlfeil @SpokesmanReview Yeah I caught that too. And the SR is still owned by the family. Journalistic ethics for the win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Respect cops by firing them when they question you, I guess. https://t.co/FC5dmV0I7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Treuer in his new book The Heart of Wounded Knee comes to celebrate the water protectors at Standing Rock. He… https://t.co/DXyCahQndy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBPM The one I went to with the party the other day was the Palomino club. It was fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Russia's OPEC+ production cuts don't cut it.   It didn’t even manage to reach its 50 kb/d modest target – the cut w… https://t.co/ObOeQMAhkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperSensFan88 @Aportzline @monstershockey No sarcasm, he’s one of our brightest future stars. If he’s coming to OTT you’ll be happy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ang sarap balik balikan ang kahapon.   I love you Maichard 😍 hanggang sa dulo.  #ALDUB43rdMonthsary]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ‘Knipper Kar’ is back on the road today traveling our beautiful Commonwealth &amp; headed to Western Kentucky!… https://t.co/9QP2nbhosQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dante -Atlanta, Ga #malemodel #themodelsoftkmgmt #tall #young #handsome #casting @ Scottsdale, Arizona https://t.co/r5kiQesY9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the record, this isn’t edited. The taser genuinely sounds bass boosted in this fhjsakskak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real Men Read Volunteers #handsonbroward @ North Side Elementary School https://t.co/aOecRAefVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PittsburghSport @steelers If I'm looking at speed I'd probably put Adam Humphries from TB slightly ahead of John B… https://t.co/8t19dMXHjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC ITS DAMN TIME WE THE PEOPLE BE GIVEN A SEAT AT THE TABLE OF WHAT IS SUPPOSE TO BE A DEMOCRACY AND PUT AND EN… https://t.co/iVFLZdXWXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaRTubbs my best friend and i kind of just go whenever we need to because my doctors are mostly garbage and we… https://t.co/5k2rTCivQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is on the move, and that doesn’t necessarily mean life, health and happiness, and I’m ok with that. It does mean joy though. Always joy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Wrestling World 🌎 Is Mine Weather Anyone Like It Or Not!!!!! #mykingdom… https://t.co/cvy8YTQdCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming in Saturday’s @HoustonChron: @UHCougarMBK has earned its 'GameDay' moment https://t.co/L5KPRfz0F1]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is that a @netflix show has a better script &amp; acting than Aquaman with a $200M budget?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Erik Prince (founder of Blackwater and brother of Betsy Devos) has been a vampire (not the cool kind) bleeding taxp… https://t.co/cXOVDbJAhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Tlaib And Rep. Meadows Have A Heated Exchange During The Cohen Hear... https://t.co/2FnvDXmOfR via @YouTube.… https://t.co/q1VBQMLUff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleClark @billdirects check out all these C- beers. @theWXwoman invite him to the next basement party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinTobz Yes you did. Thank you. That’s how I will say something important from now on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCurtisAxel Ah but your Pops made the people believe it was. #Kayfabe brudha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarieAl @farjad99 @Turki_AlOwerde @RealthingUlli @B0RedS1 @305local @Alkofide @ceasere @awwadsalotaibi @travlnjak… https://t.co/PWeTGhOMMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wonkette @DoktorZoom Yuck, sounds like one organization is more worried about being kicked again in public by the… https://t.co/5wWZRsXmEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurahbaeza @JesusIntonso @jmesa77 @ritrejo Tienes razón. Se le estaban saliendo los pulmones, pero eso ya era tuberculosis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clutchfans Harden needs to sit a game or 2 for rest. Start watching his minutes as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The low number of AAs on PrEP in the US in practice and clinical trials despite the higher risk should be seen as a… https://t.co/CKPy2IIHtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[UofL needs a fresh Chris Mack recruited roster with kids who actually act like they give a shit out there...]]></document></documents></author>