<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[NBC10 First Alert Weather: Brace for Snow, Rain https://t.co/6dX5u7EIyH via @nbcphiladelphia hope you enjoyed the n… https://t.co/BQbOXRoREy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to these young ladies should be in the leader news this week or next..#piratepride #allcomingback😊… https://t.co/aDacJvDaav]]></document><document><![CDATA[@serenaadrianna That nurse was tiny to I was like well here it goes ....lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO TENGO INTERNET PARA VOTAR PERO AYUDO CON LOS RT @ShawnMendes #JFCShawnMendes TwoOfUs DIA 13 SIN ARISTEMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hola y feliz sábado mi querido @pabloalboran Hoy estamos a exáctamente un mes de vivir una gran noche llena de emoc… https://t.co/7gx8B3jzqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathan_ht pues si, el pasado se deja atrás, pero los recuerdos no los puedes eliminar y algunas veces llegan sin ser llamados.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#newfav #muse #muze #artistProfessorShaun #artmodel #artmodellife #womenandart @ ArtCenter College of Design: Graph… https://t.co/RlLl5jeEYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be unavailable today  by text or phone.  if you need to reach me today Facebook instant messenger is the best way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanna wish @PeterScanavino a very Happy Birthday! I hope you enjoy your day]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Friday, #March15, tens of thousands of #YoungPeople across the country are #striking from school to demand  RE… https://t.co/1sBCCYqxiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, all!!! Hubs said it was delicious but looks like I have a few recipes and methods to test out now, too! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday #PresidentLincoln #LincolnsBirthday! #Tatiana December 2015 https://t.co/kerteIg7Jw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I set a timer for 15 because I’m making rice and if I never turned it on:) great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickFoles @lululemonmen Louann Landolfi @louann_landolfi  @nickfoles @lululemon Looking good Nick...your phila bas… https://t.co/1wGTJGWCz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm merely exhausted just talking about this weekend let alone going through the motions. Resting is definitely nex… https://t.co/3NMiVnAVth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillieJeanTV @wcnc This is where taxpayers money get's wasted.  He shot the gun that killed a man (any questions?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@staceyabrams Stacey, babies and education, it must be one or the other...]]></document><document><![CDATA[She doesn't QUALIFY TO SPEAK OF Jesus ... STUPID LIBERAL .....https://t.co/MsyNSPVVGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harambevan @BYU It’s always on this jacket and I would dream of doing this without it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m conflicted about this “Social Media Awards” that BET is having. I’m not sure exactly what kind of opinion to ha… https://t.co/F21vokZ525]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need y'all to put some respect on my mans name he is pristine at making thoughtful songs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum @TuckerCarlson @JennyCraig @SamsungUS @Bayer How can any corporate executives be ok with advertising on… https://t.co/tTf0N3VTvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffzentner I think Chads were typically youth pastors with frosted tips and/or soul patches and distressed jeans,… https://t.co/EEesQabWcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well said &amp; very true. Wise words &amp; actions do speak louder than words. 💜🌻]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I hate and love this story. It’s sad and beautiful and a big mess. I  don’t know what happiness is right now after… https://t.co/7bWkXOp3co]]></document><document><![CDATA[The static on @ClintBowyer @SpotterBrett radio is driving me crazy and stressing me out #ClintsMyBowyer #Holla #Daytona500]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @SFGiants and @Bharper3407 today... #bryceharper #sfgiants #phillies #dodgers https://t.co/7uygXQtVUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is mike  I was born in the middle of the night  My age is literally the only thing that makes sense  I like… https://t.co/2W3HM544Ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryLandrigan @CSAHQ @BurgartBioethix @DrNancyGlass1 @HarrietHopfMD @EMARIANOMD @AmyPearsonMD Snuggles are always… https://t.co/QPZal8VBcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like this tonight 👉🏿EXTRA 😉 @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/KOlfZeUogz]]></document><document><![CDATA[AHHHHH. I ordered the black classic hoodie and am so freaking excited. I absolutely love this design 🎉 thank you so… https://t.co/lJJ4FXx7YR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrickesque I'm calling you a racist. Jerk. Just kidding, love you. PS ~ I am not in Georgia. Weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First night not sleeping in bed with Brandon in the past 3 months ☹️ probably not going to sleep well at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HahaT2130 @NO1GifQueen @mammajane2 You might be right. I just think he is low key.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHoffy68 @commie22 Ahhh screw the haters @MHoffy68 and I’d rather keep you in Florida anyways!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ilhan Omar blasted over latest ‘anti-Semitic’ tweet about Israel. https://t.co/oDCC9iz5Z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabryluce @Viviane6677 @angela681417 @Alcioni5 @roberta_lanzoni @evakoosiglesias @PucciaPatrizia @ElbaklySami… https://t.co/8S7BoGkSku]]></document><document><![CDATA[{Eli}  Giraffe lanaandwren   wrap and bonnet from gingernpicklesknits   #jenniferrittenberryphotography #jlritt… https://t.co/gEgTTTUlnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My lady is taking me out tomorrow and it’s a surprise, the last time she did a surprise she blindfolded me and I hit a pole lmaaao]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the answers on my test today was @rihanna birthday 🙄 told her happy birthday on twitter and still got it wrong 😭. Coulda got a 90 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun little tidbit from my first open mic. It's not great but I had nothing written and fully improvised for me. Tha… https://t.co/oU2LTkq3HC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alix_iconic Right?! Crazy! At least we can look at his follower list and get an idea of who to avoid]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d hate to think that the highlight of my day today will be this gloriously perfect mashed avocado I’m eating atop… https://t.co/LdKirbWWdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steelers @mvp86hinesward Happy Birthday, Hines!!!  I hope you have a FABULOUS day!!!  And a wonderful off season!… https://t.co/3xQb6ajOls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lopezianos, están seguros que ésto es es bueno para México? Están conscientes que ésto hará crecer la economía?? Av… https://t.co/piLpiOYFUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[when your friends post those “i wish i had friends ___________” tweets https://t.co/vqBzMkM6gT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The strongest creature created by God in the world, not the lion, not the elephant, not the tiger, the girl” - spo… https://t.co/6YBZzUr9hH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#POstables I introduced my niece to #SSD a few years ago and she has become a devoted fan. Last weekend, for her bi… https://t.co/MqKUZOz5Qj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smoking gun.  All this talk about one doesn’t look at a more nuanced story.  I’ve had that conversation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would someone please tell me how that fucking idiot dressed himself and got to the studio? Holy shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msm_021498 Aquí no es como NYC. El tren es una mierda y para yo ir a sitios en el tren tengo que llegar al downtow… https://t.co/tHlJAdkwjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seh Thankfully not today. Yesterday was rough. Scary as first time with major breathing issues and throat getting… https://t.co/CwLUntg04e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelle Malkin speaks at CPAC 2019: full speech https://t.co/963o4QvFYq via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MzCata1 @AllAboutDaTea And Erika ‘s husband’s lawsuit and his mistress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyQerim thank you for speaking up for sex trafficking victims today on @FirstTake @espn 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still wanna do a swap box with an online friend....I haven’t done one since a Christmas gift box swap I did with… https://t.co/LeLoqMH8AG]]></document><document><![CDATA[anytime a woman does anything she’s a “ bird “ woman can never win lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @BreitbartNews @JxhnBinder More reason to build the wall and CLOSE the border.  Let them enter through the legal way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FeedYourFandomEntry https://t.co/477gVsjIGs ❤️🧡💛💚💙💜💘💘💘 Ends 7/31/19 ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaniKind This show gives so many of us a reason to fight Dani, with people like yourself who embrace ya with open… https://t.co/KVSij9I5op]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy has a sweet arrogance similar to that of Netenyahu. He is on the wrong trajectory and needs to be held to… https://t.co/CTbIznlxP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating a great start to 2019 in good company &amp; proud to be a part of #TeamElliman🎉🎈Woo Hoo #DouglasElliman… https://t.co/JTyftR8e1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! ❤️😎 @ Hooksett, New Hampshire https://t.co/XNS9ULPmKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing vulnerabilities is what strengthens relationships with those near and dear to the heart. Don’t be afraid to… https://t.co/MataPwMmBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evangelical blasphemy. The glowing orange human equivalent of Satan, a man who displays and embellishs the seven de… https://t.co/4TH37bV7SU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earpers are FAMILY We are here and We stay! @SYFY @IDWPublishing fulfill your commitment to #WynonnaEarp Put our ca… https://t.co/WBZKdk1a8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcelaFeudale @AngeldebritoOk @ulisesjaitt VOS TAMBIÉN MARCELA? Es el colmo que spoyes esto!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Algemeiner @benshapiro Hopefully it will take aim at those who think there are fine people among Nazis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m walking around the streets of philadelphia. let me know how NUFC does plz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been asking the same question all day. #patriotsSuck #NFLFavoriteChild]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump  America's right is to the free press, what you are doing it against what our country stands for. SHAME ON YOU!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all the fans who came out to support us tonight.. not the outcome we wanted but we will work to get better! Go 🍊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cozzzyboyz @spacermase @Sirius7dk @TheChrisMosier @rachelvmckinnon @joerogan Not how hormone replacement works.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girllllllll today went from cool to what the hell to ok time for bed fuck off 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished two quick signs tonight for the game this weekend. I need this semester to be over so I can put some more… https://t.co/5FoFhaXF7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday! Hope u are having a wonderful day! @mf_peaches https://t.co/awx6LU50Xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoonPie The Moon Party needs to work across the Horizon and share the sky!]]></document><document><![CDATA[MBB: Falcons maintaining working margin on @ShawBears...@Tyre_Gathright scores and is fouled...He will shoot FT com… https://t.co/ctK6tg7X3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every single day you should wake up and commit yourself to becoming a better person.🙏🏽💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[slept 40 hours out of a 48 hour period but now I’m up and showered with a coffee in my hand on my way to the apple… https://t.co/bD1x5qVDOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnipesAcademy Chorus students sang last night at UNCW’s Caterina Jabaro Opera Symposium, featuring baritone virtuo… https://t.co/NEjeuw5T3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yawn. The Mueller report MUST be a doozie. You're pulling out your old song and dance routine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a lot of compliments on my dress tonight, ima post it later , feet hurt to bad to walk over n get it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancy_hamm1 @GodFirstGina @phillyeaglesfa1 @AsiaTater @ashleynhinsley @robertdunlap947 @G1rly_Tattooed @go4itbas… https://t.co/PzeHZGOQkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember seeing this rover being tested in public out in California on the beach. They fenced it in and brought s… https://t.co/PFzpsUGyIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahh. The person who doesn't like Kamala's laugh supports Beto.   I still abide by @Bravewriting's Great Kamala-Beto… https://t.co/GJxUu6GUX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need everything in my possession to function properly and to its fullest capacity. I will not drive a car if some… https://t.co/i7yryok1g8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraniteShoalsPD I’m Now following you! Can I get a follow back? #NeedFollowers #IFollowBack]]></document><document><![CDATA[You reject all who stray from your decrees, for their delusions come to nothing. https://t.co/7FXHRaYnuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Oh boy. Another one of those. Let's see how well her publicity strategy works. 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andersonj Congratulations, Jeff! I am so excited for you and the family! 💝🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m_millsey Agreed.  If that happens, my meltdown will be worse than Chernobyl. ☢]]></document><document><![CDATA[You do not and should not judge someone if they do or do not report sexual harassment or assault. You also should n… https://t.co/yKO3r3a5EJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't exactly storm out of the room when it's a mountain of crap. #hoarders]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ReadingRecoveryworks #❤️myjob From Early Reading Struggles to Bowdoin College: One Student’s Story in RSU#34 – Mai… https://t.co/5zgPqMCmg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already flipped my calendar to March tonight, cause I am very over February and very over winter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rodeo time. #friedoreos #friedreeces @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/h24AjbM7cO]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd grade Levites carry in the Ark of the Covenant and place in the Holy of Holies. #parishtabernacle… https://t.co/f1IfLr7fmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[No worse feeling than not being able to make it to the gym on one of my nights to go 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[VDub loyalty remains! Congrats to Brett Bogovich! He purchased his leased Volkswagen Jetta!  * * * * #erinpresley… https://t.co/3mbIgKKdhS]]></document></documents></author>