<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AyyE_Redd Sis do favor Oprah &amp; the way this BHM is going I don't put nothing pass nobody... So O coulda been wylin for real 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨🍃Artichokes are ALL THAT and MORE!!!!✨💚Whenever they are on the menu...they end up on my plate ☺️. 🍽 . . . ✨💚… https://t.co/2yBW6hctFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flushing out the leggies and kickin’ off a new week with a boost of inspiration!  A 45-minute #trainerride on… https://t.co/6jjSzcwEpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roseannlanglois @RTOdyssey Who's on the team?  All Wonder Women I'm sure! My money is on girlfriend. 💪🦸🏃‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 philosophers set up a booth on a street corner – here's what people asked https://t.co/sYU9Udqwb6 via @ConversationUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Awinston77 I’m not getting involved in this drama bullshitso leave me out of it I’m just a fan of Aaron Carter who… https://t.co/CSCW0yHJgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLo im a student at the University of Miami at the baseball game and i would love to meet you! you are my everything!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking some Splash to work today! My mood and energy has turned completely around this week,  and I've already lost… https://t.co/hAsr5H5o8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woo hoo!! So happy to work today with the night shift, brought me lots of memories!! #AgentsRocks #PurpleLife… https://t.co/M8ay1xHkHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[kinda tilted that it’s snowing where @elissuhdude is and i’m out here suffering from a sunburn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnpavlovitz @Denise04359537 As amusing as an anecdote this is, it is such a sad commentary on what this country… https://t.co/HcHjy49NMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved getting these sweet thank you notes from @kathrynsmithhi1 ‘s class! These made my day much better!! https://t.co/nX0REyTxfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump watching you right now- chubby, disheveled and lying the whole way thru. Bad look for a US Preside… https://t.co/WWqSEuUFUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Squirrel judging my attempts at "exercise."  #urbancritters #walking @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/XlYZ0mwGJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren One man..first off he is a desperate pathetic kid yet again...and all combined u liars jump all over it… https://t.co/qaxNTa5XCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna watch 13 @Victorious episodes tonight! One for every year @Bharper3407 could have been with the @SFGiants]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy in this moment. Surrounded by smart educators and learning @GoogleForEdu in Austin with Google and friedtechnolgy 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would check on him.....but I don’t actually Care.  🤷🏼‍♀️ #hesadouche #hottytoddy]]></document><document><![CDATA[And 🙏 like it's going out of style. #TGIF #ADED https://t.co/2GsvyNBVJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[ooooohp homegirl dropped a bombshell on colton about cassie and caelynn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not trying to kiss my own 🍑, but I’m probably the most stylish female at the gym 😂💁🏻‍♀️ Allll thanks to my… https://t.co/JrD45LjQSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like how Antigua have Good Morning Antigua. Is there any show in Dominica that's similar ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karidlane @DancingQueen_DQ @LinzStanley @amlehr @Atrias @besandler @ru_thompson @BrianaDeCoster @Allyson_Floyd… https://t.co/uug5farHlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaBertrand @kimgard728 Does this White House know what nepotism is and conflict of interests?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyMartinCo3 @RuanAntunes7 @Lynette_50 @KingsPlayszz @pizzalover4189 @mfourie64 @dm_stp @CJG_Pokemon… https://t.co/U6zNLqX67w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Challenge accepted! @kelly_hipp challenged me to post the covers of 7 books I love. No explanations. No reviews. Ea… https://t.co/SycoLmiwii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Khanoisseur Awh! I'm enjoying myself Dad! No troubles!!! I live our comfy couch! 😁👍🐕🐶❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@englishelf79 @jayvanbavel That’s why you’re there to teach them otherwise!]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you for this tweet because without it i would never have realized that elon musk and i share a birthday and b… https://t.co/2FqlLPaJld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crazycost @CW_Arrow Hopefully, they'll pop in once and a while as guest stars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica Now that’s just not fair... #ThePowerOfMelanin 😌 https://t.co/fPCUvxsvm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realized that @16handles is on my way home from Chelsea Piers Gymnastics, and since they have a new #vegan non-sorb… https://t.co/W7AD9ZLZPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was 13 when I saw the Jonas brothers in concert and I have been chasing that type of joy ever since]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitch6632 @GeneWillis I feel like trains/subways are touristy in **some** locations, but buses are not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally noticed this during the Oscars! So cute. 😊 https://t.co/EaDxUKLFpA via @YahooEnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baileysouthside Bailey has told the battery/condom story multiple times on the show. No wonder he’s into old ladies #senile #GripeList]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spike told it like it is. Face it, Hollywood despites you. And, you can keep blabbering, we all know you are a raci… https://t.co/eNKdnYFlP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuteAnonMan1 That’s funny because I have really needed your services today. Let me grab my whiskey and sit with yo… https://t.co/ySuwq8A4RX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenryTContreras "We are star dust,  we are golden, and we have got to get ourselves back to the garden." Not my wo… https://t.co/1qPEOWAjU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y se llegó la hora 🤦🏻‍♀️ #TheWalkingDead  fuchi caca fuchi caca!! Tan chevere que estaba viendo los Oscar @TheAcademy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A woman in harmony with her spirit is like a river flowing. She goes where she will without pretense and arrives a… https://t.co/u9hxRvYpwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: not to go on a vegan rant or anything ... also me: *goes on a vegan rant*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffFlake @JoaquinCastrotx You are now entering “No Man’s Land” going againt the US citizens wishes. We the People… https://t.co/aeOTyNtsNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[we all want some mirth. #funniness #chuckle #smile #hilarious https://t.co/64hUxuAWhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me to my kids: nah y’all gotta go sleep in your room  Me at 10pm: *peeks in the room* hey you guys can sleep in my… https://t.co/ClrV8zlumN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT and #HappyValentinesDay2019 to my better half @Shawgr. We haven’t changed a bit! Here’s to many more years of… https://t.co/vgVSJSxvQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickyberwick can you please give my son @TyRyan27 a shoutout he’s a big fan! He named his dog after you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breathesgelatin Is this as in....  let's not scare road warriors cuz we want them to vote for the 2020 bond?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m finally watching “Won’t You Be My Neighbor,” the documentary about Mr. Rogers.  In the first week of show, the… https://t.co/dlWBflg1Af]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h3h3productions Reading the replies to these tweets is legit grossing me out. If they were accusing any other man… https://t.co/TZJRpiem90]]></document><document><![CDATA[In short, James Calvert had appropriated and had put into practice the truth of Galatians 2:20 and had identified w… https://t.co/cFHUMAvOI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews Maybe if you EVER had original ideas; were an independent thinker; and had a… https://t.co/gpN1kOT9N6]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the age of fake news, here’s how schools are teaching kids to think like fact-checkers https://t.co/C0RsIKPNkE via @qz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scarbiedoll @karonliu N tried more new things because they came out of the box. I kid you not. Add a toy and it wo… https://t.co/Z66Q2vIoa7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandyCain79 @catturd2 @LovToRideMyTrek Lol the sad truth is there are few that can wage war as females or male.  H… https://t.co/V6n19A4ghh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are my allergies acting up so much? 😭 itchy eyes. Sneezing. Runny nose. It’s annoying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thvnderrcvnt Shit tay I miss you more than you know.😭😭 come to Seattle!😉 I’ll be back in June to see you and the baby though.❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BB19KEVIN I add you to my prayers on hoping that you will remain in total remission from cancer and that you can t… https://t.co/Byz1mIDfch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out #NaiaNickz in her baby Tesla. @ Palm Beach Gardens, Florida https://t.co/CqVmYnTrE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipPulley @wcsRNHSspanish @Schoology Thanks for sharing! I got some great ideas from your sandbox course. #schoologychat]]></document><document><![CDATA[the most shocking thing about pushing people away is who lets you and who fights you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When karma rolls around im not gonna even feel bad. Im tired of her always throwing things in my face. Being angry… https://t.co/MzLcHtzjsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertMaguire_ @realDonaldTrump @60Minutes Too BAD, So SAD !!  #ImpeachTreasonousCorruptTrumpTraitorPenceNOW… https://t.co/jwc96pMlnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unbelievable:  AOC Threatens to Put Moderate Dems on a Primary ‘List’ If They Vote With GOP https://t.co/LZb4XCgCNs via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m keeping it that way then boom when my kids dad come home 16 hour shifts here I come]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zerogspot Two of a billion stars it means so much to me like a birthday or a pretty view]]></document><document><![CDATA[CatVideoFest is bringing its 2019 compilation of the latest and best cat videos to the Portland Museum of Art March… https://t.co/QI4IW7Snpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamMinyon @HillaryClinton @CoryBooker My God people how completely lost are you.  Hillary is a terrorist.  She is… https://t.co/Ro7r6N2Olu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewrsorkin Rather paltry :5 million: devoted to queensbridge job fairs and NO JOB GUARANTEES per yr article....puhlease. cc: @Nas]]></document><document><![CDATA[proud to say i’ve come to a point where i know i can make it in industry!!! TO FREEDOM!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talk about what you gone do when you see me, I’m waiting on you to come get me 🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gunner_20_W I am simply supporting the argument that if you are familiar with how much fencing like the type you a… https://t.co/8ySORedtbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhunt84 Schoology AMP! I love playing around with all the features...time to implement!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saraGG14 @TamiGoveia I helped. I don't want to take all the credit lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who knows him already knew this, but now it’s official: our superintendent @pkdiff is the best! I’m proud to… https://t.co/L8LngmHzsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deadl1ghts @mulatttoo @hamadrryad @BroderickHunter Well duh it’s the governments fault, but you can’t do shit abou… https://t.co/M95MLWONeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that iCarly episode when they basically ran a sweatshop, what was that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello @MassGovernor, @OregonGovBrown, @GStuntzie , @NatlGovsAssoc Scott Pattison, and @SpeakerPelosi Wendell Primus… https://t.co/fjivmkNYYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby is 2 months old today 😭 spending my Friday night cuddling and loving on her because I know she’s never goin… https://t.co/GJoAJAfp0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunrisemvmt @SenFeinstein #raisingradicals. These kids are spouting exactly what their teacher has told them is “t… https://t.co/mDiqKp5fdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday! #rest #spokane @ Spokane, Washington https://t.co/Vqy2tcmWun]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone on here called him Matt Klencrap haha, it’s no Ruin Tomorrow Jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister You make a great point! 1st thing gop evangelicals bring up is that God only blesses those whom bles… https://t.co/RAUj4a1eTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhollowMyNuts @Sputnik22 @RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump GO PLAY ON BORDER😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1987emb You gotta learn to meal prep the healthy food. Saves a ton of money]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyEGoodman Very fair question. See previous tweets https://t.co/aQDRmEX7UQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @pattyinNY Next door to Manafort. They can discuss who has the best chance at a pardon in 2021.  Which one will survive until 2021?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday feeling 🖤⚡️ . . . . . . . . . #venicebeach #tgif #friday #losangeles #travel #travelphotography #throwback… https://t.co/YJ7ZZzYdc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Texas... 😔 If you’re available Wednesday, show up!! #NoVeteranLeftBehind 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y esa es la mentalidad que nos tiene donde estamos! Moentras sigamos asi, tendremos muchos Chavez, Maduros, y tanto… https://t.co/BOAQQwf0FK]]></document><document><![CDATA[And to think that 4 months ago, I fell in love with you while you wore a Pikachu costume. I am soo incredibly happy… https://t.co/LZilN3F4xs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Sage is modeling her New Mermaid Tears Jewelry Custom Designed by her sweet Valentine!! Sage gifted me wi… https://t.co/xH9Q2Bok6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mix - Summer Walker - Girls Need Love Lyrics https://t.co/PlwtF6XsN1 via @YTCreators]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneak peek at my Fat Tuesday flash for tomorrow! First come, first served from 11am-8pm $120-$300 @mplstattoo @ Min… https://t.co/wQRNmaDj8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[My classes this semester are TRASH! I can’t wait for this semester to be over]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MSNBC As I’ve said before the problem is RWNJ Netanyahu not with the Jewish people! The extreme right wing of any… https://t.co/T4VFCfzjhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#earlymondaymorning #bookrelease featuring #WRPbks Author Jean Grant, A Hundred Breaths https://t.co/mscnfxO2V4 via… https://t.co/FLQNa4bwpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[What about the other border?  Remember we also have a Northern border, you don’t think bad characters don’t come th… https://t.co/VthwCMq1aa]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎼 March is Music In Our Schools Month #MIOSM 🎵.  Celebrate by making sure your local school supports Arts Education… https://t.co/PyT1MMnvIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT Photos from 2015 @BayouClassic74. My first and @HBCUGameday first Bayou Classic #hbcu #football… https://t.co/ETCUI43LYu]]></document></documents></author>