<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[All Trump has to do is unseal all redacted memos and conversations of politicians of both parties. Let all the worl… https://t.co/O0N3qdezZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[When did #SXSW⁠ ⁠⁠become this ultimate conference of #politics, #highered, #science et al.? Who are the  attendees?… https://t.co/OCygdVxL4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CsaundersTalent @DJagello0115 @RASports Been watching/helping coach Derek since he was playing flag football at 8… https://t.co/jGqc1MnrPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Director of @NASAKennedy speaks on a big day for the US space agency ahead of the first test launch of the… https://t.co/KxgB67ikQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retweet. This is how they want to shut (the people) down. How many are Trump supporters? Coincidence?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jake_burns18 You're on the horizon of the Viper and the Mountain... Brace yourself. I've been rewatching leading t… https://t.co/nGAaTXJVQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The end of AOC’s response here, please inject that straight into my veins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @magee333 @Julianna_glass @Dracaenawines @cowineco @thatsVeryKari @hmgivingsoul @simplysallyh… https://t.co/yxGcgELCms]]></document><document><![CDATA[63 Chevy Impala cruising Van Nuys Blvd. #cruising #lowriding #lowrider #63chevyimpala @ Van Nuys, California https://t.co/fxIFJ7l00N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the mamba mentality grind 24/7 destroy my competition eradicate them. Not is a literal sense just that I wil… https://t.co/HaA6T4O4Oe]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ He didn’t even have to go to the whip”  @MoveTheSticks out here killing the #dadjoke game. The rest of us are jus… https://t.co/wZCT8WJjHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittanyrennerr @THINKiWONT ...whatever... Um... Would you...? ...😉... https://t.co/tysMBzgFma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best think about Rick’s send off episode is seeing The Punisher and Michael Burnham.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 23:   **Today's Progress**: Began learning/working with Bootstrap today.  #WebDeveloperBootcamp #ColtSteele  Co… https://t.co/ff6E4dXgD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enriquelopez_18 I have a lot of shit to do before then too, 😫 but then it’ll be over when break is here 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great talk by @A_Izquierdo1 #CSULBBUILD #CSULB #GoBeach https://t.co/JKfToPGdua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferinNC @tribelaw No, I think he’s a Trump supporter and it was evident the way he treated the prosecutors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cgnitmar1 Has its own the real YORKTOWN of history. She went to YORKTOWN high school? But lived in Bronx ? She game the system ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some beautiful playing at yet another early morning #WindEnsemble rehearsal! @HPRwildcats @DeodinoWildcats… https://t.co/vm2PoOll2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that was fun!  #mardigras #mobilemardigras #joecain #raisingcain @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/sy2rfv24t9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Spring 2020,   MLB network host:  “Astros closer Craig Kimbrel now averaging an astounding 104-108 MPH after s… https://t.co/ErwXCZPzoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting at the @SanAntonioRodeo for Jon Pardi!! https://t.co/dozvZWAUux]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephietweets Yes he is... and some how this prick less prick made money off of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @realtrumpweathr @realDonaldTrump Trump lives in your head rent free. I love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaileeSteinfeld a murder is a god damn slutty fucking bitch sliding into groupie raht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyLandry1 My daughters Goldens love routine.  The routine of waking up, walking, and eating.  They do things on their time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate Tennessee, first of all it’s Tennessee, they low down they dirty they some snitches]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keselowski is so good at managing a lead. Good race today! #FOHQT500 #NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #Oscars you forgot this man in the #Memoriam Segment https://t.co/fNf1Dj9UvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinMyers541 @AKidFromKent @TheLydiaCruz Naw, sticking to the rivers and the lakes that were used to]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch this all the way through. This is why I’m a #proudalumni #BeBlue #DSMHometownTeam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoeSargi @dmasterflex000 @KazzyOfficial Wtf is there pen15 in the background]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go ahead. Try to find a bigger fan. I dare you. #Wahoowa!🔷⚔️🔶 @_mdiakite @UVAMensHoops https://t.co/T2W9QqnH2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGComedy @SpeakerPelosi @JussieSmollett Do you always thank her for lying?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cameronmoll I agree that no.2 is most likely, and it will have to be accompanied by some kind of mitigation of the… https://t.co/YDnuZbze9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramirezmaria844 😘lindos sueños Maria duerme con los angelitos ✨🌙✨👼👼👼❤️✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Folks I'm sick and tired of being called a racist and other names simply because I am white and love America, that… https://t.co/I74jMBGRYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at AMC Loews Roosevelt Field 8 - @amctheatres in Garden City, NY https://t.co/468GYjPpu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@culttture @thecjpearson @donaldtrumpjr Laura Loomer a journalist.....lol.  No chance!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girls. #penelopethanhthuy #golojuhs @ E Patisserie Cafe https://t.co/V3xbrXUPUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[He has a new Fox series called ‘Proven Innocent’ - first view was very good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's involved in helping drug up your children. In reality causing them to defy you. Causing them to overlook respe… https://t.co/5DyFZztpn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FSU winter/spring sports:  Men’s 🏀 20-5  Women’s  🏀 20-5 ⚾️ 3-0 SB 9-0 w/ big wins over no. 8 LSU and powerhouse Oklahoma.   #Noles]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine dating me and then boom we just last forever and we’re both happy asf. wild.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCS__Athletics vs @shhsbballgirls tonight in the 1-AAA Championship game from @BooneAthletics on AM 640 WXSM with… https://t.co/CJKU6bMs9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zakc00p3r @JoeBleedsBlue you think I haven’t had her added since like 2016?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByRickBrown Been through the same thing with my mom for the last 10 years.  Don’t hesitate to reach out for help.… https://t.co/kSgUd1A0Si]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT to the last time the boys hosted a state playoff game in 2009 vs Wesleyan. Tied at 46, with 4 seconds left, Jr… https://t.co/j9cFgibMRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smichie24 @kutzmarski "FAKE NEWS!" Exclaimed every Trump supporter in droning unison like zombies]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s still time to get snag a gift for that special someone. Check out our #ValentinesDay Collection here:… https://t.co/TozHA7XNsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂 Cold! Random Thought..if DDJr were to go to @LSUfootball ...Offensive consistency and success will follow. Love… https://t.co/kO4wsteAAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timcast False statement that socialism has never worked. I advocate a mixed economy where the commons provides the… https://t.co/eYi88Qli6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd fly or stand 🇺🇸 with Sara anywhere! 👩‍✈️ 🛫 @DCLabor @AFLCIO @CWAUnion @AIL_NILICO @TxBldgTrades @TexasObserver… https://t.co/f497BI2WeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @TheDemocrats Wow! The "leaders" that call out racism, bigotry, and all the isms, are stumped on this? I'm shocked!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGirlInPhilly @TollManJoes26 I did the stuffed mushrooms, chicken parm, and warm apple crostada with vanilla ice cream]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the extremely interesting side-effects is GingerWoodWorks is that my little two kids have become extremely i… https://t.co/QxsdXWfGrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Malcolm I caught the very end of Grahams show on here 3am -5am can you tell me the name of the last guest he had on… https://t.co/JkYdKSHUhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pq se tarda tanto el gobierno federal en desembolsar la ayuda a Puerto Rico #federalgrants #grantsattorney… https://t.co/Ul0Af7zNO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abby Goodrich, out with an ACL injury, cuts down the net for @GbbFord. https://t.co/WVsCXusiZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sin blinds you. Sin finds you. And sin grinds you. https://t.co/a3QMdkpVkK via @GregLaurie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miami Herald: Alan Dershowitz suggests curbing press access to hearing on Jeffrey Epstein sex abuse.… https://t.co/WLuCiJ9U8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veronicamariez2 @yelgeb @shadur @simms3710 @nickiknowsnada @SLReaves He got what he PAID for. https://t.co/Zm33mkgJrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish each and every one of you the unbridled and pure joy i experience with my friends.  In many ways, i am the l… https://t.co/p7PuEMThDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your kids start screaming in a restaurant and you don’t take them out, then shame shame]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Incredibly) special guest alert! 🚨 @chrisamsart is the lead singer of @favoritestates, debut album this year after… https://t.co/6CzNV0cKYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Bernie Sanders had a show for every attempt to run for presidency we’d be waiting season 4 rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come to think of it. influencers are genius. we SHOULD get paid to promote your brand or company. I was working for… https://t.co/WbNZ7F3zQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is going? What are they doing? When are they leaving? Where will they be traveling? Why are they doing this? Ho… https://t.co/dTFpAjBEai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving the music in #sanantonio this year. Great show from metric and #emilyhaines @ The Aztec Theatre https://t.co/XKT7CMNOlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day back at the gym was so much fun. I'm getting back on track with goal of being 200lbs by 2020  #fitness… https://t.co/UcUinm3y4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 18b Pale Ale by @hopnutsbrewing at @hopnutsbrewing — https://t.co/s6Zt0xF1Rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Direct Client - Looking for #UX #Writer in San Francisco, #CA Check full Job Description:- https://t.co/CPf45YsjxB https://t.co/i01irvdP9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveShd Only recently did they enable it for iOS and Android, but you can’t use the controller with it. Should be… https://t.co/xLrFtNe2xC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@io9 This article makes me feel like the author has a personal vendetta against Ready Player One for some reason. H… https://t.co/WZFZTazc34]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise You’re entities to your opinion but try and defend this https://t.co/oDiZjp43ZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day ima get to do that cheesy thing where I talk to my kid through my wife's belly and I can't wait]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tarastrong Sending you birthday wishes Ms. Strong. May you be blessed with many more. https://t.co/N7pBbVYifU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go!   Congratulations to a team that knows the meaning of fighting until the end!  #ElmwoodTough has been ea… https://t.co/eLwJJh8RXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frang4u @CurlingCanada @McDonaldCurling @CurlON_ One person from London. Rest not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT Green deal or no green deal. This feels like the worst possible reaction to children trying to learn abo… https://t.co/hP9m2ynsD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@21SBcraM @EdBouchette Yes, MarkyMarc. Fire the GM in the middle of negotiations and with free agency and the draft ahead...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LombardiBeau God Bless you on this Journey.  You are an uncommon man going to an uncommon place so happy for you.… https://t.co/rBW2Dt3300]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Kent state gun girl being a poopy pants is the funniest shit of the week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corby_aroma @FlorentJAYB @KWABdexENA @mickluf92 Damn. Hope de gal b ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Handsome_Jake_ Not that he would be bad but I want to see him in a lumberjack competition]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPaigeWWE   today is the day, fighting with my family, is coming out. #RealPage #LoveYou #HappyValentine’sDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marc_benton @tlindlahr Stopping Tejon to relieve bladders in an hour. Gonna charge for 5-10 then head up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oGSanch @RageOutland @Censor @CallofDuty Yoooooo those maps were ELITE. 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAtlantic @amandamull and they donate all the profits to legal aid for the people jailed for selling weed, right  right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@germanavilan Muchas veces es mejor hacer silencio, sobretodo cuando se ignora por completo la realidad. Las FARC s… https://t.co/FR0JzyKpSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinBuffalo oh man Kevin she's a heartbreaker- so when do you enter the NRA? LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[First trip of 2019 - South Carolina. “Travel, because money returns but time does not” #vacation #traveling #travel… https://t.co/7DSNSZGySJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@demisxxual found her in my recommended. Really good stream so far. Good luck on moving out @shikigamixo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because the judges don’t fall into what u think the judges should be, doesn’t mean they’re not fit. A huge fra… https://t.co/zTZovXzZA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derya555 @StateDept @FLOTUS So, you are a judge now. I'm sure you are just as pure as new snow. I'm sure Muellere… https://t.co/mSc6Kkn3Ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Contentious Matter by Perennial Artisan Ales at @perennialbeer — https://t.co/rOBcg5dBD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My soul thirsts for God, for the living God. When shall I come and appear before God?” Psalms 42:2 ESV  We often c… https://t.co/Ek7T2oap01]]></document><document><![CDATA[He still won’t clear 10% in an election with minorities. Meanwhile, the people who voted him in are demolished in a… https://t.co/pXL6t6Fftz]]></document><document><![CDATA[In an industry dominated by Netflix and Amazon, this streaming startup found a way to win @mbcheng15 https://t.co/tsgtRMAAKc via @Inc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alberthdz09 @cesamo70 @lopezobrador_ Si este es el lider? Nos conformamos con poca cosa.]]></document></documents></author>