<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Jennmoxley @unccharlotte @UNCC_News @publicmediaNC Appreciate the kind words. 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TracyHa61896525 @WadeN43 @TalbertSwan @JerryFalwellJr @AOC Were you going to give money?  At least now you can don… https://t.co/gUpG0d50VN]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wanted 3 weeks for this ace family video and it’s only 27 minutes ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[More freaking delays on the @NJTRANSIT_NJCL Another disabled train. When will this end @GovMurphy WHEN. FEES ARE AT ALL TIME HIGHS!! WHEN!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS THREAD IS MAKING ME CRY ... low key  Erick  would just tell me “bye woman “]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FifisDream @DougDavidsonYR Yes! An anniversary gift from Christine, or a welcome back gift from the GCPD, delivered by Rey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m annoyed that people seem shocked that solange would put out an incredible album]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MissMendonis as per our educational conversation last night...take a look at the attached @cultofpedagogy 🥰 artic… https://t.co/CQavdFOw7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[woke up 22 hrs ago to start our trip back, finally on our last lyft ride home 😩😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GalentinesDay — sparks the same joy as a birthday or anniversary. 💜 https://t.co/RRx7rs9hga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heathermpierce it won’t work as you might have had planned, he’ll try to railroad you with being his personal assi… https://t.co/56dWHMXNRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[De vuelta a la radio hoy arranca a las 11:00 A.M. por La Primera 104.9  1190 AM TiempoRealconClaudiamendoza. Vamos… https://t.co/gPGnsxJuLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[are you feeling alright? cause i really can’t tell sometimes. i wanna know what’s going on inside your brain… https://t.co/aGlfuipnrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcbridemelissa This was so awesome loved seeing you two together off screen and the bond yall have ..family is fam… https://t.co/XNsXkaslmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to go to the zoo, museums, concerts&amp; play laser tag but everyone else wants to get drunk&amp; high&amp; catch stds so whatevs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drmattcarlson @nikkiusher @hiddenla @realDonaldTrump Based on my Mtl political scene of the 2000s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barb_avon @CalPLogan They're not all talented. Let the untalented writers price theirs at 99 cents and free and th… https://t.co/bl0ge3dmNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandra_gallega @cc122ar Ojalá ,todos los mayores tuvieran ,una hija como tú ,que sin conocerte estoy segura que er… https://t.co/8xbsXbgyNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[i cry after everything now arguments, sex, driving. idk why but. i’m extra sensitive rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited for this concert coming up and to take cute pictures of my sister and her friends in Nash. They’re j… https://t.co/Hv9QyMFGmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a big difference between IF and WHEN. Check out this video to learn more.   For more information on how to… https://t.co/k4aspP2izM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoneyBaggManz Like there are so many situations that I was in.... fucking gross]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m probably more excited about NYC than I was for Mexico freshman year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait til you see the decor I’m using at my place!! So many mermaids and ponies and Senpai]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Grounds for Thought in Bowling Green, OH https://t.co/pkdms8zs9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was honored to talk with @crackersnjuice about the way we can best be church. Thanks to @JasonMicheli and… https://t.co/9HJLVm1p67]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to leave this world knowing I tried my hardest to love and care for everyone around me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why couldn't we get a Urban Outfitters, or something at Cerritos instead of Lauras Boutique 😫 Her things are way ov… https://t.co/o8bsGKKchG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me voy a aventar el documental sobre la gente que dice que la tierra es plana]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Keats_Shelley Ode on a Grecian Urn https://t.co/znzjxhjF3f  #beautyistruth]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For the representation of African-Americans in math departments to reach parity with their 13-percent share of the… https://t.co/R1dTlGVEfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandyceClifft @SRiggsWDRB @JudeRedfield @KeithKaiserWDRB @mmarshallWDRB Happy Friday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kudos to writer of episode. Needs serious raise. One of best episodes this season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YandersLaw @Matty3Thompson @loganapp20 @IceHaney3 @mlexartini @JadonGilpin @LatreMorrison @ny2lasports Congratulations @Matty3Thompson !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_A_Rama_SFF 😔 Sending good vibes and prayers to you right now, Jay. https://t.co/WEJ7CCWdPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh You’re a waste of time &amp; space &amp; oxygen. Please delete your account.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sledge_harris @gregorytangelo The thing is is that the community accepted LGBT activities. It was live and let liv… https://t.co/KpOhrgE44s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to the Danish American Center for hosting today’s aquavit lunch where we ate all the tasty courses and drank… https://t.co/3Sgol0ZAIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morganoliver06 I’m sure you’re saving a lot of money that way, though! I had to do that for a year a few years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sinmersaw so many people from Instagram and YouTube at Flower and Garden today but was too shy to say hi #yayanxiety]]></document><document><![CDATA[a true friend will support you through everything and every decision you make, even if it’s the wrong decision. a t… https://t.co/JVYbyT7fmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its been a long time since I've taken a step class - I sure do miss teaching them! Great Y memories with good frien… https://t.co/wOitm3npp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Intercontinental Hotel lobby coffee shop makes a really good latte!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#georgetown #nationalharbor #fairfaxrealestate @ Arlington, Virginia https://t.co/0o19bqH34f]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I knew I was going to be dropping near a whole grand to go to Dallas for SOMEBODY ELS’s Batchlorette party.... I… https://t.co/R7g1XHQdlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyle_scanlon04 @tgshepherdvan @bodgei @LetsTalkTigra @ootcscenes @angelt18 I has a warm lap https://t.co/6e70Vo74sV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Sweet 16 today and I’m loving this month’s treat! #myfavorite #beaconstweet https://t.co/AFMUP3Ls0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasHumor Oh wow. It’s actually national chili day? Coincidentally for us, that’s what’s for dinner. 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night at the @sanjosesharks game in the @sap suite! #gosharks #sap #lifeatsap #bestrun #sapariba @ SAP Center https://t.co/8cILvgYFju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Susan83283200  Arriving #InStyle  #TheCsrpenters  #RichardCarpenter  #KarenCarpenter 1978 🎶🎹🎤❣️💞⭐️ https://t.co/MrBSArYnBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#riseandgrind @jahova33604 #goodmorning #sundayfunday @ Crowne Plaza Tampa-Westshore https://t.co/PTDoTm5IjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conquering the alphabet. Today: her first "s"! #MilaLovesLetters #ProudMama #ThisIs3 https://t.co/ppA6WUm3W1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RogerTaylor and #BrianMay are sitting in the back...#Oscars https://t.co/swnWWHI4uG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less apologies—just pay women what they’re due and stop harassing us, hey? #SorryNotSorry #MeToo #TimesUp… https://t.co/egi5UFoNQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nahroceo @sunnyshaw7 @LDozierSHRA @ndcohen2 @barbarafields_ @TiaCalHFA @TinaBar11012713 @AkersTina @bmorehabc… https://t.co/7xiHTnu9Te]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperGrobanite @Absulutlyluvly @bisexualspies You can't scuba dive either, cause it says, "Thou shalt not have in your bag divers weights."]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure every ER sends 2-3 Doctors to take care of you as soon as you break in. #theresident]]></document><document><![CDATA[No hay #beso más tierno que el que se recibe en la mano acompañado de un perdón]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCoker13 @nereid_niobi @pattty_k @cornish1969 @Sarahwaugh20 @FreshSpellbound @kitchen5203 @FireGoddessB… https://t.co/FtEobJ4v7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone for learning with us today! We are thrilled to know that the SALT model has resonated with many… https://t.co/X0gAPlm8R4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reecealann That's a good point. Never heard someone point that out. I can't explain it. I can't get myself to not… https://t.co/8u4P0U4EsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahlofolino i thought this said friends and i was like,,, hwat r u posting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important topic for educators. How we approach this topic impacts students’ future understanding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starellla honestly I am too but I’m traveling this summer so it’s basically up for it🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman No and no.  #NoBernie we need strong, VIABLE candidates. He and his Bernie bros don't make the cut.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the thing. Store-bought sandwich bread with butter (salted) and a thick slice of cheddar cheese is God’s gre… https://t.co/qi6NipWbl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yngridssso Sim. Alguns artigos falam de pessoas que não tiveram alguns grupos de alimentos apresentados a eles qua… https://t.co/SPUeYIGe9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me estreso bastante siempre por las tareas de ese maestro neta lo odio🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silent037bob For about half an hour then right back to smelling like a dog. 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jockosims @dredis92 Happy Birthday! As always, last nights episode was a tearjerker. Um still crying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jake just told me I’m starting to sound like my mother when I sneeze and I’m just going to get my nose sewn shut be… https://t.co/eZOdFDz73x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FanSidedDDT When I Came Back To Twitter And Kofi Kingston Is The # 1 Trending Topic #WWEChamber https://t.co/Sc1PeluD4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're not anxious about a roller coaster but anxious about how many people are here https://t.co/n9xmCZVoWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need [redacted] to come [redacted] me until I can’t breathe https://t.co/QC3uIZ98aY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bloodysunday #neverforget #march #justice #justiceforall @ Edmund Pettus Bridge https://t.co/J8oXdi2uiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[One good night to sleep and all I dream about is my new car being stolen and me frantically screaming at the hold m… https://t.co/vnFfoTnlUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitRECordJoe O Brother Where Art Thou? and Betty White in Lake Placid. https://t.co/29eIeQsuZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading back to Florida next weekend for @PlaylistLive with @AdobeVideo. See you there 🤘🏼 https://t.co/1QfIHHyOCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CABLENOTICIAS @JuanManSantos Fuera fuera fuera. El presidente que más dÑo le ha hecho al pais]]></document><document><![CDATA[𝑊𝘩𝑒𝑟𝑒 𝑑𝑟𝑒𝑎𝑚𝑠 𝑐𝑜𝑚𝑒 𝑡𝑟𝑢𝑒 💫🏰♥️ en Walt Disney's Magic Kingdom https://t.co/7xWekZWOaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adamqab @HuffPostCanada @YahooFinanceCA Not all medical marijuana is smoked. My husband just started taking CBD oi… https://t.co/J3tXcLNt5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[And honestly I'm just venting anger so I do to screw up my cutting. Everything right now is overly frustrating and it hurts my head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandioncam @xprincesslula Yes...you are unbelievably gorgeous have you ever experienced a transgender woman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forced to watch the Oscars (K has it on) and they just played off the Makeup and Hair winners. Because they need to… https://t.co/vX52bzUL1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI: YouTube the video Loco by MGK when you’re baked, you will not be disappointed 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealBasedMAGA @team2usn_gp Let’s help that 52% return to their country of origin so they can have the Sharia Law t… https://t.co/2iaTTCamYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just spotted @mariemorincan’s delicious single serve cheesecake &amp; chocolate mousse desserts @Walgreens in the… https://t.co/JNRnqOfAKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmHarleyJay It is. No one likes you. Also HI MISS YOU WHEN ARE YOU BACK DINNER NEEDS TO HAPPEN CC: @JaymeLake]]></document><document><![CDATA[YT ppl sweaty follicles and bref on me. Guess who doing a DEEP clean 2nite]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fabulous Friday Drink #rustynail #liquor #scotch #ink #lamy #pentelbrushpen #superaquabee #sketching #watercolor… https://t.co/QmFGt7iL7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the pole is spinning we're cuttin' at Victoria Barber Shop #WomenSupportingWomen #womenempowerment… https://t.co/OsmUFNFtQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7026saki @KrawlAmerica @TN_Jeep_Girl @steelecreations @hawkeyeinmd @Bobshankland @wve1022 @Legendary1941… https://t.co/S7Flvesxog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Born a military brat and saw every awful tattoo.  Became a nurse and saw how awful tattoos age, AWFULLY… https://t.co/LZUe3T73dS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElieneC3 Hi Eliene! Thank you so much. Hope you have a very good day and a safe one!😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RatesDaGoldfish @TheMettaVision @A_affirmations @RuvvyMyLuvvy @CoriSigma @NatsRallyCat @cocoa_dot @landis_melinda… https://t.co/VaGEdk542l]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Menu at Rowland High School Delicious Shrimp Tacos! 🍤🌮 #WeAreRusd @NutritionRUSD @rowlandhs https://t.co/z0yHGbgPZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GangstaNerd @AP She just want support for their children. That is reasonable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metsfanmurph1 Lucky you’re not married to me. There would be no doctor visits. No medicine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a cold is kicking your ass, slap some eyeliner on your tired face and power through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How you finna ask me for something &amp; don't reply for over an hour. I'm taking a nap it clearly ain't important.]]></document></documents></author>