<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s Monday, new week, time to grind 💪🏽 @ 10 Fitness https://t.co/CyWU3H3TTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched #FightingWithMyFamily recently. It’s really good. Funny and heartfelt. @RealPaigeWWE @StephenMerchant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rams supporting Rams - @CSUSoftball is crushing it!!! Congrats on a weekend sweep! https://t.co/oVtzNLM35Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro You looked so beautiful and your father walking you down the aisle is perfection.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuffBills53 Lol I'll have a Pepsi straight up.  I hope you're having a great day. 😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toniboyy @LakotaMan1 @unixdoss Yeah, I know. I’ve dried many children’s tears and tried to explain cruelty to them… https://t.co/xidnspWuL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelsie_morgan4 Isn’t it the worse thing ever, I just sat and cried last night ugh 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took the book#valeriescateyescream for another fine meal at Mori Tepan Grill. Shared some ice cream with the people… https://t.co/5B7MNNhsYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance @NicolleDWallace @matthewamiller But plenty of obstruction of justice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ruvirivlin עשרות מטעים נעקרו, יהודים רבים אבדו את מקור פרנסתם. ובבית הנשיא, שתיקה. אין קול, כי אין קשב.  עם ישראל… https://t.co/mqPialb47w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahh welp.. it’s been almost two months now so I guess it’s almost tattoo time🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Josh's plan to trap a Leprechaun! This is getting pretty intense over here :) @Millertcher https://t.co/joobg9mD7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker be having me dead af I swear all we do is talk shit in Spanish 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence I’m a viewer and if everyone responding to this tweet is....you’ve got 100 beat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlanderHQ If i didn't tell her, i could leave today, California Dreaming on such a winter's day... such a good song!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve noticed the @BuzzFeed YouTube stars are getting personal channels and hopping in the comments. Is this a talen… https://t.co/VyWAsBp7sv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Eyespiration at @PIER39 San Francisco #tulip #natureisart https://t.co/sCZfkoRToe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TimesSquare #Manhattan #NYC (@ Times Square in New York, NY) https://t.co/Yt1b4weOj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Hashtag Marketing campaign can Dramatically Boost Brand Awareness and help you build your brand.… https://t.co/yQaWYGkvU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstherThePig Right back at you beautiful 🐷❤️ your smiling face always brightens my day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t have to talk to your best friend everyday......give eachother some space]]></document><document><![CDATA[The entire EQAO program and testing should be cancelled. It’s more a measurement of teachers than students. I never… https://t.co/EoGCgUt85Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance @SarahHuckabee  for lying for such a horrible man https://t.co/SAwv1E7U98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adesign_thinker @DT_DC @JoGolden @DesignForDC @sarahbbrooks @AshleighAxios @adesign_thinker -DM me. I am happy to… https://t.co/vLwlh8VnFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyways I made awful tips because we were so slow, my dab pen cartridge broke open inside my serving apron, and I n… https://t.co/DAFraKdPqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everytime I apply for a bartending job in LA.  Them- “what’s your bartending experience?” Me- “ I bartended at 4 am… https://t.co/bVKP97C7Lf]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve started using “vive la resistance” too much in my everyday life.   today i walked by a bird dragging a sock aw… https://t.co/XyYBfGaRMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@useitorloseit4 Yes,had a discussion about that the other day.i don’t believe for a second they killed him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF are these ridiculous articles being brought to be put in the record. #CohenHearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FormerDirtDart @ellievhall @SeamusHughes Except he was no longer a diplomat when she was born so the exemption wou… https://t.co/5INr1XsxDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yess girl this playlist is amazing!! I’ve woke everybody up at 640am 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻😂😂 @danni79jo #sorrynotsorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished my pre-employment screening, had breakfast, now going to scan a million documents and then I should be don… https://t.co/NcmLB8f96p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian Yes . He’s not going on a talk show.  Good luck Khloe ! People are mean . She needs to just be qui… https://t.co/5tDj4yrfpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[karlis gma was trying to find the plug in for the vaccum and said “i dunno where to stick this, up my ass i guess”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savannahmillion The creative team probably found the tweet and thought it’d be funny for social/asked author of tw… https://t.co/x5WynbvQJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robin_McGraw Yea some people have families and some don't.  My mother got pregnant with me so she get her hands on… https://t.co/JhRfhvUVII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans @travelchannel The. Eye episode is intense. Loving every minute of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wBiancaMartin @NPRinvisibilia Isn’t it so cool?? Like straight out of a fantasy novel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilyseh @charles_gaba Indeed, it will not stop abortions or when it does, it will create unhealthy babies born in America]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy can barely handle dressing himself but thinks he should choose what a woman should do with her own body...… https://t.co/fb6ilJdzIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSSacramento What do you expect when human sprawl keeps pushing them out of their native habitat. Now Newsom is f… https://t.co/nrOMZGdD3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sit down Prince Caleb. Drink your  beer.  Obviously, you figured out that I am the Eternal Dragon and you want me t… https://t.co/DWu1rw7Qmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[No such thing as too much @kyotoroaster #DarkSide #Coffee #MondayMotivation https://t.co/bgW0ifwcHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[to my bestest friend in the whole world.. happy freakin birthday!!! i couldn’t be more grateful for a forever frien… https://t.co/246ukBBGSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Republican leaders stand up against them.  Most of all stand with our Republican President.  Then fight against… https://t.co/d9OGpBAytk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canadian Labour Congress Lobby Day   A very successful event - it was the largest day of lobbying Senators and MPs… https://t.co/JVGcqLe7TH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let there be peace but we are killing being hateful with words we all wanted someone to listen care for us the only… https://t.co/SWEcrgGOh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ebony the medicine is deep in your locker you will find it (grandmaaaa) 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m excited about the blues festival 3/9 but sad part is I DONT KNOW ANY OF THE ARTIST 🤦🏾‍♀️. My mom wanted to go s… https://t.co/pzR11KgJYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonMarduk lol Wow! I haven't not been called a chick for a longtime. I am use to other girly names like baby lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I’m hungry late at night I tell myself” well if ya ass was sleep you wouldn’t be hungry #growingupblack 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenHowe I don’t have a problem with women being a superhero. I have a problem with an actress who attacks men to p… https://t.co/JUIOcP13oa]]></document><document><![CDATA[So nice to see blue skies yesterday. #blueskies #glass #lightglobes #belovedcommunity #behilife @ El Centro de la R… https://t.co/mfqYIiZByL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not preaching,not bragging, etc. I hustle. I’m young, I’m broke. when I meet a homeless or seemingly so person I as… https://t.co/XHUp0wIjAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelseyleslie13 @notsoMcCool19 Just with my parents for two weeks! Lol was gonna add Greece but decided against it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialSPGB @GovMikeHuckabee Show us one place  where this Utopian concept has actually worked.  The only way thi… https://t.co/d09khPcEXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate your birthday with a cute baby meme card. #BirthdayCard #Meme #hilarity #laugh #smirk #playful https://t.co/yZjKfpFoP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gentle Yoga 🧘‍♀️ 9:30am and Restorative with Aromatherapy 8:15pm Tuesday’s at @YogaCureLife #yougotthis… https://t.co/HDk0IEJ2py]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this!!!  I remember doing this when I went to school, but with single periods where I teach there isn’t enou… https://t.co/8Jqq4lPIP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted to shout out to all my Facebook fans! I posted this thank you on my storyline because my friends have grow… https://t.co/EU8lflW45w]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moat around your success is the hard work and difficulty. Most people lack the discipline to compete with you.… https://t.co/BEziBgYtsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vaaaux @vin_440 i started laughing even though i was so pissed off. his eyes took me tf out he was so confused 😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[i rlly watched this for like 5 mins trying to see which one they missed a spot on....]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 years ago and still the best advice I’ve ever received. Grandma Debbie is a real one 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put the wrong word on my Instagram story and I’m definitely not fixing it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Just WONDER WJAT RAND MAGIC NUMBER IS ???? HOW MANY AMERICANS have to Lose their LIFE, THEIR BLOOD SHED B… https://t.co/buanWWQ5dT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KnoxSchools did yall forget that bearden is a school? and the neighborhood right down the road from it can barely… https://t.co/6NEnAk1tlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grabbed a breakfast biscuit and some necessary reading material from @detroitfuturecity. https://t.co/d06ZsuX8wB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radiatoryang I think @GammaSpaceTO / @DMGToronto could be on this list too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @Fabletics By #KateHudson! Use my personal referral link for special savings! https://t.co/TuUX3Csp5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning reading while breakfast cools down. @misswalkerclass https://t.co/IEQC4ER2FF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmudd19 @FantasticBeasts The back of my head is photobombing you. 😂 Great pic of you! Really enjoyed both of your presentations today!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught you!  These two fur friends where playing on the kitchen table chairs.  This is the look I got when I caught… https://t.co/y2wVP7H5HP]]></document><document><![CDATA[CC I am surprised that you can see all these indictments all these guilty pleas! And the fact that we all know Russ… https://t.co/5Mya6VMgpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 100th day of school from these “100 year old” third graders! 👵🏻👵🏽🧓🏻🧓🏽 #FHHighlights https://t.co/N8ED10LsYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmSteveHarvey Hey tweet a Terrific Tuesday morning to you and your Family]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was a baby in one of my classes today who smelled SO nice, like baby head smell mixed with lemon tarts, but t… https://t.co/7YjFAJEbhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahNRO I'm awake too. Insomnia is insanely frustrating, but I'm so used to it now I've resigned myself to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speakers can benefit from chatbots to enable the audience to share feedback on the presentation in a fast, and in a… https://t.co/k7tq7ThPYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StumpforTrump Just look or listen to this evil idiot! What a shameful pos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotherCussr @LMHPhotog @PowerRangers If it’s bitter I don’t think it can be saved. Maybe go buy a cake]]></document><document><![CDATA[While we would all love to see some more of the beautiful babies @chrissyteigen and @johnlegend make, may I say tha… https://t.co/d6AuQ5CX6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraGruener @AllysonApsey @Matherne_Edu @TaraMartinEDU You are connected with everyone! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ZumbaWithATwist is live with Dance Instructor deme_dee on every Tuesday night 7pm-8pm beginning March 5, 2019… https://t.co/FKB73IZj8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my #magichour #abundance #candle from @gaywitches please notice the the circulating #money attracting #14k… https://t.co/nmdzavMsOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite book...Pride and Prejudice!! ❤️📖🎉 From now through March 31st, post a #shelfie on Twitter or Instagram… https://t.co/PpJ6dwhYok]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all I drove the the gym in 6in of snow at 5 am - someone give me a medal. Or a cookie. #dedication]]></document><document><![CDATA[This vibe tho...😍 @KitMercerXXX @mandymeadowsxxx @SteveHolmesPorn @ayyrrae https://t.co/kdrSc3Ur4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get BTS to Seattle - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/46jWsFrRmW via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[The day I remember to get my hot sauce for my eggs in the morning they don’t fucking have it... I’m pissed 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my little dragon hatchlings. Sunday, they might grow up top terrorized some adventurers!  #painting… https://t.co/vER7Nacm6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Valqurias4 Infeliz. Besta fera. Ignorancia pura. Voce nao viu reforma fake com recibos farjutos? Voce nao ve o abs… https://t.co/oAt98RKcYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CriticalRole @chamonkee @TitmouseInc @jennifermuro Just hit 1 million!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshgroban liked my instagram comment so the rest of 2019 is cancelled so I can recover]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missyslaymaker @JMyers1971 Right? Here daughter take this sack of BCP because you are going to get raped... huh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pkamla1 @Sadafsultansaif @ChristiWalling @BabyGo2014 @Light4ASD @gerrinnesmac @DansoyGomez @SathieGounden… https://t.co/ipzw7J1EHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barcoholic27 @SiegeMiami Miami is unlike any other US city. Huge Hispanic population who loves football.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realmiketeevee @realDonaldTrump Maybe not white supremacy ,more like white stupidity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LyonHeart85 @AlexHuttonxo I know. That’s the point. He’s a really good man. I’m just chuckling because he thought… https://t.co/4ChXJdzavs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Cookies #HISD #BJCC @ Barbara Jordan High School https://t.co/WsnmxBDBHi]]></document></documents></author>