<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[That ain’t dolphs chain look how tiny that shit is. The real one bigger than a motherfukr]]></document><document><![CDATA[That tax refund gone, sis. Good thing I held on to that refund from the other tickets. I'm ready for the U.S. Tour… https://t.co/XkMFZQPwrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wild #flygon @wizardworld #pokemongo #pokemon #wintersoldier #milesmorales #comiccon @ Oregon Convention Center https://t.co/vMfCxkl1ql]]></document><document><![CDATA[El WR @jjarcega_22 quien terminó la temporada con 1,059 yardas jugando para Stanford..  - no tuvo un solo pase pant… https://t.co/kD7Z6nACXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Row for 20 mins and then some body weight exercises. On the slow road back from broken ribs! #brokenribssuck… https://t.co/K07DtZd95A]]></document><document><![CDATA[A @UniforTheUnion table sits empty at the #ANCanadaCongress But it's OK, we know you're at the Sting/The Last Ship… https://t.co/FkelrDN9MF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacksonville State getting all the rebounds. Murray down 4 with 6:15 to play. Morant going to the line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two inspiring speakers at today's Bright Futures Conference...... @CarrieCaruthers and Sara Stipkovits. Thank you f… https://t.co/OHmkDl2KWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristiangranat1 @TNTSportsLA Si q lo se y me parece estupido, no es una guerra es un deporte entiéndalo d una vez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgchamp 5(one shoe)+19(Dude wearing 2 shoes and 2 wrist straps)x2(only 1 strap)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DepSecDef @VP @DeptofDefense Thank god somebody is finally taking the Klingon threat seriously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianlaungaoaeh @sednanetwork Thanks again so much for the invitation Brian. Fascinating evening. 🇺🇸🙏🏽👌🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left to right.... - Drinking an American Presidential Stout W/ Peanut Butter And Jalapeno Jelly by @AZWildernessCo… https://t.co/pjyRK9S1uQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girls gonna know how to change tires and oil.. kick a nigga in th nuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @OversightDems Why should anyone believe Trump?  If lies were electricity, Trump would be a powerhouse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Netflix is taking the vampire diaries off on March 1st !!!!!!!! Guess who’s going to be watching the vampire diaries nonstop until then??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joannlund You may be districts away, but Im just a phone call if you ever need anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get tired of thinking about how other people feel I'm about to say fuck it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Murder, She Wrote S12E13: Jessica consults with Daredevil to figure out a sticky situation in a nightclub. The nigh… https://t.co/z2qTkijcHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp You are delusional of you think Trump doesn't lie constantly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@condrab It's completely heartless and disrespectful to the patient and their family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyJKoch Now it's what is evil is good and what is good, evil with these awful human beings.  Not voting to keep… https://t.co/qphgMlaoLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roywoodjr But that’s what I get for doing karate with Mr. Charles at the YMCA 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know, I went on a rant. I can see the failure of the party and another Trump 4 yr term]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the great event @AmandaYen8 and team.  Love the partnership with @TMobileTruckLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisWFMJ Some imressive numbers from this storm.🤤 https://t.co/2DDS72xWgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByNickFarrell OK I can agree, “it’s close,” but measuring up WVU with Pitt isn’t a good sign for WV. Pitt was in i… https://t.co/37iW7NtSyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Diva, Sarah Brightman.  #sarahbrightman #diva #hymnworldtour #hymntour #hymnsarahbrightmaninconcert @ Viejas Ar… https://t.co/FjyR2WMrbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattMoscona Bad stoppage for sure, but for a second I thought he went out in real time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2:01 left to play in the Bayside girls basketball championship...  Parkside 52 | Easton 50  #DelmarvaSportsInsider #ShoreHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impudentearworm And when the service ends and it’s time for the Bible class, most of the fathers go AWOL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you heard ‘#Doubleup Teaser’ by Frank Finesse on #SoundCloud? #np https://t.co/TevsRHN3wT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLHay @TheOfficerTatum No lie. Lincoln freeing slaves was an attempt to contradict the South. While the southern s… https://t.co/fYvNeTDT8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rubinafillion @AOC @SenWarren @SenSanders Cities are curtailing library  building hours because lack of use and in… https://t.co/9T6JCYb5Py]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zenzurzb24 @DiMontPlatinado @Garyjayuk2 @classylady2206 @sssnnooooppp @jaydeefung @bionicanadian @samyliam19… https://t.co/hBTCURdl1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Democrats thing is disgusting. In favor of killing babies, and now they want to protect Child molester. We have… https://t.co/XXwFN3GBE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickelberry_9 @wayveeeb @thejayharvey14 @brandonfrankl18 Congrats kings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working hard @ Red Lion Hotel Orlando-Kissimmee Maingate https://t.co/1SLkdE5cJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BillyIdle (#TheWhite x #TriangleMints) bred by seedjunky_jbeezy over at raylanfarms during her flush, advancednutr… https://t.co/vHT8UuesVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chingonmatthew @TheBeaSmith @Metallica @KirkHammett I’ll stick with “let’s go party” with Marty Robbin’s version if yew puhleeze 🐝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelpollak @SociallySherri @tedlieu No such thing as a moderate Dem anymore. They have  all been brainwashed and g… https://t.co/VNJnktISbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredChieux @turoczy Relatively AND with little to no help from the public and private sector.... Imagine what coul… https://t.co/pVWmRsj9Kj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnonHeel @buell003 Yup and Amazon usually has low prices and millions of things they wouldn't have found in brick &amp;motor place. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corylinkous That is, indeed, my dude. Keep up the great work and thanks for the photo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanHigginsLive "My Dude" -- he respects those @umichbball fans that supported him !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Only1SeanSmith @JimGaffigan You’re a good egg Jim! Sean, you’re almost there! Speedy recovery👍😎 https://t.co/2pkpuK0zwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wear this because I try to hold myself to a higher standard, not that I’m better than anyone; but I’m trying to b… https://t.co/WZOBbbd5wZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Champions! There is no buddy like a brother.  Maxwell and Mitchel congratulations on your season! #ByronBears… https://t.co/ozLol6KSyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BestBuy @GeekSquad This dishwasher was supposed to be installed 2/18 but a scheduling error occurred by your staff… https://t.co/WypovQLgu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[POUR VERY CAREFULLY! Nice fruity nose, very hop forward, medium to quick finish. #DrinkCraft #DrinkLocal - Drinking… https://t.co/wbZY1F43PK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craysounds_ @KayzoMusic Need to know where I can get all the furniture in this pic omg everything is so nice 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews I hope he gets it and it teaches the lying media a lesson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose This is newton Iowas little cia fbi cointelpro mk ultra hew jfk files left over sitting in a murde… https://t.co/x2oU31i4sw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARonNBC @NBCSports @NASCAR @DISupdates @amsupdates @dennyhamlin @joeylogano @KyleBusch @mattdracing… https://t.co/q7Ob0yFvc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Indian diplomat and strategic affairs expert KC Singh remarked that hawks in Mr Modi's BJP and the Indian es… https://t.co/bNy9JKwEKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamonFoster congrats buddy! So happy that you’re a Steeler. Love our O line!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a day! #NationalPolarBearDay and #NationalStrawberryDay https://t.co/ocsM5SThOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[What keeps you motivated? There are some days that are harder than others. Sometimes you feel lost and start to los… https://t.co/udbkFfrhup]]></document><document><![CDATA[The BEST student job on campus! We have fun planning FREE events to all MSU students. Plus you’ll get work with me… https://t.co/bLy4ExNSDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callherdiana @MoneyMakingMakk Nah I’m jumping in ya ticket. U bout to cop a crib in midtown. Stop fronting lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KLChouinard To be fair, you have to have a very high IQ to understand John Collins dunks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FleetwoodMak Oh ok. Well, time to be still is necessary and important. Glad you are investing in yourself in this fashion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if everything in my life fails, I will still love you! #rootedinstrengthca #thebible #nomatterwhat @youversion https://t.co/6cXJV4Zph1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMek i’m waiting for them to try that shit on me........big mistake, trust me....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just made it through Greenwood and did not hit one red light! https://t.co/e4df5n3PMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buck-Tard the #Dog said #GoodMorning 🌎 have a great day!! @ Waterford Township https://t.co/CRZCaFxu46]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gingerfreakb3ta @saskquo @IanDunt @KenClarkeMP My understanding was that the main constitutional purpose of the ma… https://t.co/kI9Ef7rGd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks again to 🎶BigTime Radio🎶 Vegas BTR International on Twitter for spinning my Duet single “You Do” featuring D… https://t.co/XVN5gF53GJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joroe40 @Chris_Hawkey @60Minutes They make a consistent effort to not talk politics on the show.... If you disagre… https://t.co/Fq0Htlzzkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[|| Stay Up || @ Rawhide Western Town &amp; Event Center https://t.co/xieEMuvm1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Sir, for protecting our country from an invasion of illegal (mostly criminal) aliens. The dems don't care… https://t.co/0ulOybZ4Zu]]></document><document><![CDATA[No worries, Austin. I just lit a “Blake Griffin MVP conversation” firework and shoved it up the NBA’s b-hole. They… https://t.co/YiKS9j2nHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of our listing on Lot 19 Highland Dr #Gulfport #MS  #realestate https://t.co/UA90OLiaUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best dual-sport athletes in #OleMiss history died today of natural causes   https://t.co/tpp129nmdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bkantha1 @SoleFoodAlerts @thehypekitchen @soleheatonfeet @SwiftCop @TheSiteSupply @InfiniteCooks @pingpatrol @TheNorthCop @AMPoll13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StuartMorrison1 @CoachDanCasey True but all WRs were blocking.  He needs to be on his horse on that run fit.  LB s… https://t.co/93sx61r1j2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Way to act like a real politician by distracting from the real issue of you choosing to live in a complex with… https://t.co/vTUmVdTgRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DalaiLama please let me know if you are receiving my messages Mark Wengler]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wendler34 @A_dmg04 @TheRealSckank The flaw in this logic is that he shares his Dew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is cute. #hilarity #lol #smirk #merry https://t.co/5viq6Colqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everquestion @nowthisnews @OG_JOHNSON84 Unabashed racism in its purest form. https://t.co/iRKNEYTUVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muslims Are Systematically Trying To Take over The World That Has Always Been Their agenda! Taking Advantage Of POLITCAL CORRECTNESS IS HOW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of my fav people in this whole world just threw me the best birthday dinner i could’ve asked for 😭 wow i feel loved]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Bull market hits the 10-year mark. Will it keep raging or will bears spoil the party?: In early 20… https://t.co/zzOaWHcuGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not ordering a cloud macchiato in a grande is just disrespectful. ☁️☕️ @ArianaGrande #arianagrande #CloudMacchiato #Starbucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I injected all of these and I still got the flu. Plus the vein in my arm collapsed and now it smells like fajitas https://t.co/UJjHRyhvBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a feeling their kids might look a little off #GameofThrones https://t.co/1E8r1NMjE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just want to say it’s not easy taking photos as it may seem. It’s not all about pushing the button and letting the… https://t.co/WMgX6BT1ML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@huntasha @NextBestPicture Agree on the first 2 but still have to see Roma. As of right now I'd want The Favourite for Best Picture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oye @TigresOficial Centurion esta libre, otra bomba para la siguiente temporada. Y a chingar su madre Damm..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Book Deal - a spot in Late Night shows with Stephen Colbert 🤨- a Star 🌟 is born in Hollywood- a full hour of 60 minutes -]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE This shows just how great #TheMan is.  She is so good at every aspect of pro wrestling. She can talk… https://t.co/7hsHquiUAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sloppy first have zero perimeter defense Blake carried our sorry asses again #Detroitbasketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @FoxNews We are blessed to have one of the best negotiators in the world , in the process of making… https://t.co/FkHaERxNVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Bourbon Barrel Aged Old Mad Joy (2019) by @GreatRaftBeer at @guitarsgrowlers — https://t.co/UX32tkh7XB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half the posts in their AMA are statements of hate for minorities. Austrians should know better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im never gone forget when shawty cheated on dude and all he said was i should’ve loved you better 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisneyCutie11 @chellemybell22 @clark_gasm @Eva_Tramell_ @katzz77 @coolcam101 @RobinRashell @gigirules7 @kitawny24… https://t.co/cl5xR9ooKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a lier nor do I hide from the truth. I just believe in something more than myself. My problem is I a cared to m… https://t.co/fZXlKSMscK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffgreer_ Maybe not shooting s contested 3 with 3 minutes left ! Just saying !!]]></document></documents></author>