<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ShaquitaTPUSA @exposes_racism @ShuaEli3 @redpillblack @Tree_of_Logic Point to lie? Said who? lmao dare me? I'm sur… https://t.co/6KubgOmAWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatchadmiller @hulu And it’s impossible to not see how much Cheers, Seinfeld and Friends (for a few big names) we… https://t.co/1x5jsSQNK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoHWFanClub Good morning ☀️looks like you all had a fantastic night 🥳 https://t.co/k8U2GyJJ7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Alexa, what’s in the news?” That’s all you have to ask to get @KMOV news updates to your @amazon Alexa. Here’s how… https://t.co/SmdZJ5KmDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who in Las Vegas sells desk calendars with a events and Las Vegas key dates marked on them? I had one last year, bu… https://t.co/7aA8tWoKXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonvigil88 @Rebelredbird I predicted 15 wins before the season. Looks like my prediction was right on. That Grim… https://t.co/jcal0Wwjfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel Honest answer? trump wouldn't know an honest answer if it was pinned to a porn star's a$$!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating my birthday at bookends_and_beginnings listening to authors’ works-in-progress. 🎂 🎁 #authors… https://t.co/bmnRf2WflA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @CynthiaSchwind for this giveaway! I will be reading it this week over Spring Break before adding it to my c… https://t.co/fHuKW4oXPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot get over how good the Lemon Meringue cheesecake is at the Cheesecake Factory 😩 #1billioncaloriestho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Chase bank for sponsoring KBIS and supporting the design build industry by partnering with us to provide… https://t.co/XBJIOFu5Sj]]></document><document><![CDATA[A reading list for #BHM and beyond. https://t.co/uFvZResw4I via @blackvoices]]></document><document><![CDATA[FUCKING FAAAAACCCCTSSSSSSS I WAS JUST LISTENING TO THEM THIS MORNING READY TO CRY BECAUSE MY 1D CONCERT DAYS ARE OV… https://t.co/vccf9KaWWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClayJoh05842749 @MiniTiger I’m not excusing what he did but calm your ass down with the “white hate crime”.  We do… https://t.co/PAQwefodFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heyyyy long weekend, I've been waiting for you!  . . . #longweekend #longhairdontcare #everydaymadewell #totewell… https://t.co/c32RLMU1po]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rtraister Glad you're not falling for that BelaRUSE https://t.co/XS4CkA9GFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[fresh out the shower i try to grab some lotion off my desk and now i smell like a starbucks frappe. FYI: coffee creamer is NOT good lotion 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris #MediaWars #GovernmentShutdown was a #media showdown! #TSA #ipaintfree #feedme #uniomstrong… https://t.co/RzlifehIzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[to this day these are my favorite pictures anyone has taken of me..✨ https://t.co/QdN6yckA16]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been writing online for 12 years, but my career as an author officially begins now. ✨🥰 This is a dream come tr… https://t.co/tpHhKZdtMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[These quesadillas I made with tortillas my abuelito gave me from Mexico are really a religious experience]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz cumpleaños a mi!! en Gastronómica food park https://t.co/yc7ttYl1kf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawsome872 @MyPeakChallenge @SamHeughan @MPCFitlanders @Sheugs @GHJNancy @sarahjaswim @LaurelSchuett… https://t.co/n8ilU0cEPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu amo que aqui onde eu moro seja rota de voos, eu sou apaixonada por aviões desde sempre, e antes de dormir eu sempre fico ouvindo eles..]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my ISP Scholars. Today we are participating in #DLDay learning a new platform called NOWComment. Digita… https://t.co/H4E3c5KGDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmmteach Similar to this @mburnsmath decimal addition idea in the blogpost, “What if we gave the answer first?” https://t.co/TghYotbzs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abducted in plain sight is the most disturbing documentary I have ever seen .. #netflix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stockingframe  @lastbookstorela @thepalladium with westhunder @ The Stocking Frame https://t.co/j6fo3S1XRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 9 · Annual Bel Air Yard Sale - Saturday Only - Nextdoor https://t.co/pb8dNtkmka]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don't know. I would go as hard as you can. Theses red hats really don't care. They want to see this moron… https://t.co/DNhl4aTAn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a real congestion with this joey that couldn't keep his eyes open and refused to leave the pouch. @ Debbie Do… https://t.co/I6VExTtdql]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just went to this well-known book store in Montreal. Went to the POLITICS section. All they have is anti-Trump prop… https://t.co/hecS5tykgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A letter to my followers and those who see my tweets because people they follow like my tweets: i promise I’m not crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EscapingSarah Yes!!! I love oatmeal raisin. I made them with chocolate covered raisins because that’s all I had on hand. So delicious!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamjaredhopper “With God before me, who dare be against me?” I’ve heard Joel Osteen recite this passage so often a… https://t.co/W3L0k8P5E9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool! CA gives Drivers' licenses to illegals. Hopefully the Dreamers in CA will vote for Trump. Democrats voted aga… https://t.co/vJ8lf3awq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AylaForTrump If i have to respect the koran,you can eat my bacon,my bible says its ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredibly proud of you @KeyshawnWoods1 and your @OhioStateHoops brothers❤️!! #family #nevergiveup]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Unfriendly people are selfish and hate all good sense. Fools do not want to understand anything. They only want to… https://t.co/a8i8l6KWw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivaVinophile @FionaMorgan79 @GailBenzler @joneill55 @SideHustleWino @Starofthesea007 @hmgivingsoul @simplysallyh… https://t.co/X52sEqT9Hr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice, well deserved standing ovation for @chriscoons. Thank you Senator for your decades of support for… https://t.co/LNaQhOlW1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for the flight to Keflavík 😍 #GlobalJourneys #JourneysIceland19 @agnesscott https://t.co/3PYsUwHWRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Artist Hard at Work in Warner Hall @ Cloverdale Citrus Fair https://t.co/VctAF9CJfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had 5 people now ask me if i went to crush this weekend… NO AS A MATTER OF FACT I DID NOT GO TO CRUSH okay 😭💔… https://t.co/sDy9tDzJQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[So... rollover headed east this morning...now major accident heading west. Seriously El Paso!!! Is life really wort… https://t.co/DXMtLJGvoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maribelraura Yo me fui más joven a Inglaterra, a Alemania y a Estados Unidos. Buenísima experiencia, aprendí muchísimo y me lo pasé genial.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Probably because he doesn't have a "store".   Bahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny this picture pops up on my fb timeline from 6 years ago heading Mariah's junior pro championship game. Today… https://t.co/sWMSbSUtzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson Fight back!  Dems want all conservative personalities , radio and tv silenced! They are going to go… https://t.co/asmJ4Y3DOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @JussieSmollett did this, he needs our support. Because, this is not a regular thing to do. There may be a menta… https://t.co/AdeVJ4QeM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next 3 mornings are 6 am mornings and the next two days are 18 hour days... “I’m excited I’m excited I’m excited”]]></document><document><![CDATA[me squeezing around the barricade thru the back door of The Basement to pee in the pitch black bathroom after drink… https://t.co/gX0TTL9wFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelmacinsac @joncoopertweets I believe that also !! https://t.co/HZXCvRHelX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrassrootsSpeak Pardons would be my answer.  Ignorance, stupidity etc have to rate up there too. Your point is int… https://t.co/rnddlWG9wa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queen Elizabeth II is not a Priory of Sion, she is Satan, the Devil. Geraldine Manning https://t.co/i8jkrp8dVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisterDeanLong @Long_Twins @JarrettLong2 @JacobDeanLong1 Happy Happy Birthday, Guys!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the daughter of two librarians, things like this usually hurt me on a spiritual level, but this one...  This is… https://t.co/wCBwRq5WKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the point of the quarter where I feel no joy in my life anymore, so I eat a Home Depot hot dog]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Temple City: light rain, 61°F 48% humidity, wind 4mph, pressure 1013mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[most pure and sweetest soul over ever loved, thank you for being so patient and kind. thank you for showing me what… https://t.co/d7ze2mRBHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrekMovie Lt. Uhura inspired me, back in the day.  Against the odds, her being a woman, and a black, she was total… https://t.co/RUyhlbqX9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[First workshop day of Love, Fear, and Flourishing with letterartsne at the Des Moines Social Club. WHAT. A. DAY! Se… https://t.co/DpHy6ObpUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, Mrs. Palomo-KG and Ms. Dobson’s class for accepting my challenge. This is the best day 4 acceptance chal… https://t.co/PM3r8Z6EcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_WeStandUnited Yep and he was teaching, inspiring, training young people, many went into the science because of hi… https://t.co/ga7kIDIbFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTalkCBS That’s where he belongs. Too bad is not for violating young girls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have openings Available Haircuts , color and styling  For booking https://t.co/cZjLd0W9QD 24/7 Or call 510.243.7… https://t.co/4Ea9qWAtQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all tell me why my whole store is going to Disney... We are gonna be rollin deep af in that bitch!! 😎🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[03-03-19💟 en Arteaga, Coahuila De Zaragoza, Mexico https://t.co/hYo8CHDZCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I screamed so loud when #TheMonster started to turn around. I knew exactly who it was and my guess was right!!! WOO… https://t.co/i6ZUNgMNtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm most excited to workout this morning so I can come home and eat once it's over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, the worst part about grad school is having to cite information and not being caught up on my tv shows😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WomenProsper Cooperation is the sweet spot where  competition, cooperation and collaboration intersect in a busine… https://t.co/ckYs732QPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GBachi71 @DonaldJTrumpJr Apparently the laws that apply to us won’t apply to illegals according to this Senator.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a female don’t show ha self respect, what make u think any man gone show her respect]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwgpndsurf @bakermayfield Dude!!! That's awesome! Definitely want to go back but it'll probably be a few years!! D… https://t.co/5PzKqsWpv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleeBakerAuthor Thank you! I'll check this book out..I love it! The "hunter" becomes the "hunted"...#PerfectKARMA 👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why doesn’t God hear me when I cry I don’t understand what I did so wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halsey For real!!!! I own almost every @StudioGhibli movie at this point!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Canada for so many reasons. But the weather is just not one of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My least favorite part of motherhood is by far cutting my children’s nails. 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz I’m embarrassed for Florida. Men like you should NOT be in Congress!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#myfavoritethings London was sitting on the floor coloring and I was able to secretly capture one of her many singi… https://t.co/acYxQ3wHlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlaneal24 @Airixmyth @DrPhil Did y’all see the Fyre Festival documentary?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran my fourth lifetime half marathon today! We had a great time! And a special shout- out to my prince, who carri… https://t.co/PKY0iWQ7PH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas man sentenced in 3D-printed gun case, had "hit list" of US lawmakers. https://t.co/TBJfumpBnT https://t.co/nzakxUaM1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[“there are so many cheerleaders in this airport right now it’s unbelievable. not even funny” -random guy sitting next to me in the airport]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us for our chat on Training Camp. How do you Zoom focus on priorities everyday? #trainingcampcp @CFISDClubRewind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VWherland @Ask_Spectrum Hey! Thanks for the follow! How are you? What’s the newest thing with you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_emilayyx0 But if you to Kylie’s following and type in jordyn it comes up... this shit SUSSSS AF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The power went out at Market District AND Trader Joe’s tonight... so working Whole Foods tonight was only a tad stressful 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anoten, colectivos y guerrilleros ayudando al dictador Nicolás Maduro amigo íntimo del HP de Gustavo Petro. https://t.co/FfzwqHLH5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jake_naylor Yes!!! Good luck. Beers on you @BowmansBarGrill when you win. ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonCaughy 40% of America has credit card debt too. So many go talk to them about it too? https://t.co/zecUTZTD8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peggy Lee - Fever https://t.co/S9xFhuNBli via @YouTube oo  3 -Steps up ... this is classic,  work on your finger sn… https://t.co/IpKtt0z3Yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Defenders @PacificStand Best article I’ve read in a long time!  Wish I could view Nie’s research paper, but the ag… https://t.co/M88L5e1lUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't mind me. I'm just focused on my goals and staying out of drama. It keeps me happy and healthy.… https://t.co/Tk0bR7nrh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 9 yr old: “Mom, @mrsparrish3rd is reading The Wild Robot by @itspeterbrown as our read aloud. I highly recommend… https://t.co/iVCam2qTTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much do I love Mardi Gras? Words can't explain.  New Orleans is my second home. #HappyLundiGras #MardiGras… https://t.co/xsIN6oU33H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iSlim2Real Facts but idc. I went to an HBCU and niggas call us stupid and say our degrees worthless so ima talk my shit bacc]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of you, Mrs. Haden and Honor’s Band! #imms_lions #CasteberryIsd https://t.co/TBn7S1slBe]]></document></documents></author>