<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#fueledbydecaf at Brooklyn 9-9... Day 4 on episode 6018! @ Riverfront Stages Inc. https://t.co/Ui6nnHZolw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw Glad to be a part of that cult! Glad I haven’t swallowed the leftist Kool-Aid. That Kool-Aid leads to pov… https://t.co/Zs5jnnpHUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta What about fast and furious and the two major race riots we had in Ferguson and Baltimore?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update on my life: It’s Tuesday night and I discovered that parks and rec is even better when you spontaneously dri… https://t.co/8pYfEOr7As]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all remember watching @brielarson in Hoot with @LoganLerman on Disney channel now she’s @captainmarvel 😭 https://t.co/9NNKmOlEEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoursTrulyAnum4 @lexi_apgar @ajhiteshew Haha maybe one day. I made the mistake of starting handmaids tale and chee… https://t.co/XrAfdPbzNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multitasking while running this morning. This is a good one. Empowering Educators for the Global Goals! | Mareike H… https://t.co/LsYw2CTbhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[eu só queria dizer que há sempre um pouco de loucura no amor mas há sempre um pouco de razão na loucura]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sam_adrianson It’s so funny tho. They convinced me to download the app it’s like a modern day vine. I get lost in it for hours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_JKern Sounds like you got a full day schedule hon. Have a blessed day. 🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite @imaginemason things: https://t.co/AoDvXmFKu0 and https://t.co/4w3bYLaJY0 key foods in the Foster house. ❤️ @madechamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most my life was defined by not good enough. Overtime, what tried to kill me became a tool to free me from my own n… https://t.co/IqOQqDyNkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Imperdible @thelittlejesus en @kexp desde @panoramstudios 🇲🇽🎶 https://t.co/YtIDWvUAlR https://t.co/iKD0jBsbTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[the gym is BUMPIN Jonas Brothers and all of a sudden this workout doesn’t suck so bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hulu_support the new episode of The Orville isn’t up, and it usually shows up past midnight. What time will it show up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have this young adult in my life (younger than my firstborn) whose communication style is manipulation. Everyone… https://t.co/MkVGkjqVuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lent has begun. "The fact is, sin has left a crimson stain and we need to stare at it for a few weeks. We can't be… https://t.co/Z2Blgom23F]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can be having a great day, and you’re just doing you. and then out of nowhere... *BAM!* anxiety hits you, and s… https://t.co/wtmQH75j7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering what the equivalence is for doing this with my devs - this goes beyond ‘watching user videos’ into true e… https://t.co/t7V58sYufI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oranicuhh Everything you said plus the fact sm really got broke down busted ppl thinking they can go around giving… https://t.co/wSXdmkzzqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really wanting the James Charles pallet but my bank account is telling me no]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pant_leg trust urself. degrees will give u more knowledge. but if u have something to say,,,, say it. ur audience will find u.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many things in my head all scrambled up with it could just sort them out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LinoDeShields Actually the only cure for ambition is Jesus. But I know you know that. #humility]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimKilbane @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends Yes you are, just don’t hold your breath]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twist✨ Pin✨Repeat  . . . #sunday #messybun #letsdothis @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/xERrhlHyJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually remember this. It didn't count for me though because I had my fingers crossed the whole time 🤘🤘🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KurtRamon Sometimes I feel the same way but I’m also the black sheep of my family so I’m used to it and it just feels normal to me 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[forever ordering the house Chianti 🍷   #miami #wine #chianti #italian @ Mazzi Cucina https://t.co/CYmqaXsh56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cabbageguy @RevAdamHamilton Stunned? I suggest you fasten your seat belt you’re going to be in for a bumpy ride al… https://t.co/qemU5LDOwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherOverRead @MrsD_MLIS @NMSJags I’ll send you mine too. One I got was all elementary books and I changed all o… https://t.co/nxEYJpDApN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOVTWINE Oh don't tell me Bernie is holding his tax returns back too. So sick of candidates not playing nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You know what’s behind your curtain Felix? Nothing funny....” -@BMS_Billy @BMS_Derek agreed!! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Criminal don't call the shots in an investigation.  No investigator works at the direction of the perso… https://t.co/BRadkeQu1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aurbinato They've brought him back countless times. They give him no story. He gets disgusted and leaves. Until the next time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao I’m sorry I’m judging anyone who stays with someone who cheats on them. Have some self-respect 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @RailrodeMike RECOGNISED IT IMMEIDATELY BUT THANKS SO MUCH FOR THE ORIGINAL RECORDING. LOVED IT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thewfranco @brit_covey2 @Zach_Hymas @Utah_Football @franvamo @Univision32 @UtahCoachWhitt @LDSchurch That’s a guy… https://t.co/DuIJ5AWpia]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Future of Healthcare is Female! https://t.co/iJz6PvU4kb #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewFleer Maybe you should move to Kansas City, more people! More options]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸Idol🎤 here we come.@AmericanIdol 🎂👨🏼‍🔧🦌 @NWHL @Riveters #HBD #cakecakecake #onkey #hittingthosenotes https://t.co/AvT3MPdxnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing friends getting engaged and married aaand here I am having to make my hardest decision.. which pizza topping… https://t.co/BgrsRmOUCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nonchalantnacho I tried having something like that delivered and I hope whichever neighbors house it was delivered to is enjoying it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Susan_Hennessey Abuse of power for personal Gain.  Overrule. It should not be so]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @CardsBBFan Yeah, trump tower Moscow and trump tower North Korea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump: A Good Presbyterian???  https://t.co/leRxZlHCoX via @amazon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapaSmurfUTE Somebody get him some big boy pants https://t.co/RWKG1JJ5B6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dad INSISTED on how he saw me @ Vallarta during the weekend buying carne.... uhm HELLO I rarely go grocery shopping 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarisaEThompson @GoSunDevils @HolestineRick I’d be glad to connect you with some teachers using it. We are working… https://t.co/iXLjzJBHP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[10. “Comfort Food”: Emma shows up and supports Regina at a difficult time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonamdahl11 @tedlieu Wow, seems that someone has never seen the shit trump puts out on the regular. You ask him… https://t.co/LrETLD06ou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeitnerLaw @Twitter @Susan_Hennessey @tcwittes @LorenRaeDeJ @charlie_simpson @becingber @carriecordero @SammSacks… https://t.co/LnkjVs5pMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaHoops @TheRunninRebels Go Pack! I will miss being there tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamHendrick @ISMRaceway @Hooters @AxaltaRacing @allyracing @nationwide88 GO TEAM HENDRICK MOTORSPORTS TEAM S 💪😎🤗🏁👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando no te sientes bien y lo pones por acá...Te hace mas real o menos influencer? ( experimento)]]></document><document><![CDATA[My night has been made #Oscars2019 @BetteMidler preforming... ❤️❤️❤️ one of my favorite actresses...]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Wednesday pick for the day love. #ontrend #palmtrees🌴 #gauze #comfy #blogger #fashion#jeans #want #now #dope… https://t.co/hmMg4lrmPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMcGrathKY @tammyduckworth @NewPoliticsAcad I would have to say YOU and all your female colleagues who, I’m sure… https://t.co/sAykfqO6SP]]></document><document><![CDATA[There comes a time when you give up and just start believing what they are saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day! 🌹♥️🌹♥️🌹♥️🌹♥️🌹😘♥️ Everyday is a special day, today is just one of those days. Enjoy!! https://t.co/TFuC7CBD9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it winning of your A1C is too low to participate in a clinical trial?  Bummed that I can't participate in this o… https://t.co/JkE2CYe59m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to speak to supporters of the Charleston Acceleration Academy today. This program, in partnership with Trid… https://t.co/0bOrBcUNs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly @Scaramucci Yeah God I hate it when people like Alyssa get out there and tell the truth and point out… https://t.co/i30RoAho1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCTheVoice @DomenicHaynes @leonbridges Way to represent!!!! Sooooooo good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RA97hCFHqc @ Catalina Hotel and Beach Club https://t.co/EigLSQYbuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nat wants to go to parade, i had told yes but i aint about it anymore lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job is now open at Aramark in #Saline, MI. Follow us and turn on mobile alerts to hear about jobs like these a… https://t.co/NBeQFjlhRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I blame twilight for giving me such high/false expectations of a first Romance/love lmaoo :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTalkCBS  What I’m trying to understand about @justinbieber, is why did he marry the young lady with all that ha… https://t.co/QQmST3H4RN]]></document><document><![CDATA[All bundled up for sledding ⛄️ #boys #brothers #graysonscott #axelgene @ Elkhorn, Nebraska https://t.co/PGYqvXsm8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could cry this is so beautiful. @DwyaneWade coming back was the best thing that ever happened to Miami.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would totally recommend going to a male strip club. That was the most fun I’ve had in a minute ! https://t.co/4dOjrPXd76]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5: I’ve accepted a  #bookchallenge from @butterfly13175 to post 7 covers of books I love: No explanations - or… https://t.co/Xyw5LppCKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I will join in on this Bea Arthur Party. It’s not everyday that a Golden Girl is trending! I love The Golden G… https://t.co/bORymD5AD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mamma once said “if you have nothing nice to say, don’t say it all” 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[BLACKout . #BHM #BlackHistoryMonth #BlackHistoryMonth2019 #ReginaKing #227 #HelenMartin #MarlaGibbs #HalWilliams… https://t.co/heyzUMBwO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've made mistakes and yes I've learned from them a lot we all make mistakes unfortunately that's apart of life but… https://t.co/K6vaTwNqZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomloverro @andypollin1 @1067theFan @thomloverro are you at the Key Lime inn?    Such a cool place. And that pie ...  yummy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelcburgess Not to mention that about 90% of 16 yr olds are not even close to paying taxes!  When people are t… https://t.co/ABPPeEo2Ye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlejandroSanz @jorgeramosnews @UniNoticias Lo de @jorgeramosnews fue un show muy bien orquestado ya descubierto! D… https://t.co/tZauc3ASbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG this canvas pic of my Foxy Roxy is the ULTIMATE gift...It literally made me cry!!!  Thank you so much upstrucke… https://t.co/48oucYdbQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[i cant believe it’s 2019 and people are really still out here drinking only bottled water]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @jennifermcfarl4 Thank you for making me almost choke on my coffee!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I could catch a reasonable flight I would! My kids love your “ Smart Cookie” book.... have fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luke26Weller @Jahron91 @JennellaBella @JenniferMascia @lovebscott Well I come from a loving place . That’s all on… https://t.co/KkfKOszbPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RCoalition2019 #OPSEU #UESPO Getting the second day of the Racialized Workers Conference started! Seeking solidari… https://t.co/o8i9mfEwTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Figuring Out Pelvic Pain Isn’t Easy Most Times We treat female and male pelvic pain successfully therefore I’m pres… https://t.co/5eVnv2XKIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[appointed a “special prosecutor.”  The difference isn’t semantics.  An amicus is someone who is not a party to the… https://t.co/rpcxdeSzwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got floor seats to see @MarinaDiamandis  in nashville and atlanta i’m freaking out 💚💚💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[New phone.... who dis?? 😘🤓💜#blerd #nerd #geek #blerdsrock #blerdgirl #blerd420girl #nerdsrock #nerd420girl… https://t.co/YZwNavktYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtf is Taylor Swift up too??? Also if she’s reading this tweet can she please invite me to a secret session?]]></document><document><![CDATA[State #14 - Virginia - Looking forward to visiting Richmond Va!!  https://t.co/N6Cj99cxF7 @byoungwidow… https://t.co/hiaycK04RW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t let the waiting period forfeit your faith. @bishoprosie #ladiesnightout @ New Light Christian Center Church https://t.co/FYtWOpxWSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love that pop corn is a healthy snack bc I can eat a whole baggy of it and not feel like a fat sack (-:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me he rallado, creo que este viaje está siendo una constante cámara oculta]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I lived near a decent theme park, my free time and my bank account would be SPENT on the weekends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bren_O1967 @DrJimmyStar @greg_dabbs @RoverDov123 @KFearri @petergraigs @sheri_lynn95252 Good Night Sweet One!⭐🌙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit like this is exactly why my parents will never go into a nursing home..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/LzEWYx5vTH… https://t.co/smClXPiGcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I almost threw my phone because I missed spelled something on one of my tweets and I was frustrated that twitter needs a edit button]]></document></documents></author>