<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Not enough parents think of others’ kids as their own. I hear it all the time. “I don’t know how you do it” (teach,… https://t.co/eSrtVB89zA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AceHudsonJr Bro you obviously know nothing about basketball. Have a good night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanberge I was invited to participate in an item development workshop (IDW) for one of NetApp’s hybrid cloud exams… https://t.co/DWwBHzqAcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karla4Houston @MarthacastexT Council Committee on Economic Development's subcommittee on Education brings… https://t.co/HIpWApy7PH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:16.6°F WchillLow:8.9°F Wind:0 mph Dir:--- Baro:Rising Rain2day:0.00in Hum:79% UV:0.0 @ 06:00 02/28/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I got the privilege of being the analyst for the Western Michigan vs Eastern Michigan women’s basketball game… https://t.co/bRQm8EEXr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wakeup and be sensitive to what is being done right in front of you! know what is the intent! what is the goal! wh… https://t.co/McerMruBm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smooth with a nice coffee aroma and taste. Love it. - Drinking a Black House by @ModernTimesBeer @ Belle Lago, Este… https://t.co/lq3eimIeD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[During this time last year, I was going through the WORST time of my entire life its crazy how time flies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMarieBoothe So true Lisa. Love Fox News, that’s all I watch. I used to watch certain anchors in CNN like Brook… https://t.co/DOv4LSqss2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @BernieSanders is the @DNC nominee this is more than likely the result.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can anybody express such a monstrosity, this is a Democracy.  The only ones,notvaccepting the tesults if a Demo… https://t.co/U1m2PjwPku]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Breakfast #MondayMotivation (@ Higher Grounds Roastery and Café - @hgroastery in Gilbert, AZ)… https://t.co/y0Ca6pS3Ki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanpapz @amazonecho And I thought I was creative with an echo named living room and a light called living room light😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[this week on the adamant #podcast @bigfrog619 pops off abt #microwavepopcorn, whilst i chop it up w/ comedian… https://t.co/486v1OG9Jt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobBiertempfel Bad gloves and light hitting bats. That’s Neal’s wheel house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPeitsch @mehdirhasan I set the rules of the debate not Neo-Stalinists like yourself. @JonSutz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of Blackhawks fans are wearing their St. Patty’s jerseys. I guess the green is better? #GoStars #CHIvsDAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gleannignacio Hey Glee! Did you happen to try the fried cheesecake? I believe they sell it at the same stand?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[#2020OregonProspect @Divenson_willis (North Bend HS) runs hard. 1200 yards Jr Season with 10+ TDs. 3.7GPA Student.… https://t.co/kKzaxPmROZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LFC: must win #MerseysideDerby v. the blues to win the title. #Everton : What's a title? #EVELIV #PL #YNWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agtradertalk @ComClassic https://t.co/fk80cWrS2y these are manufactured in my home county here in Ohio]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing that is stopping my from killing Myself is my little brother that would be left behind 😅🙃 https://t.co/gehDBTnhyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sacco_DNRSports @EastRockGirlsBB @madisonpride https://t.co/DZN9rheyT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fastbreakdallas @BleacherReport Yeah because it’s not like Steph Curry isn’t the only unanimous MVP in NBA history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EuroZag01 @SethDavisHoops The disrespect is palpable. Outrage, anger, how could he? Did i do this right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spann Breckenridge and the snow keeps combig down 7” last looking at another 8” tomorrow https://t.co/7WW82VXHOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LBCI_NEWS على مخابرات الجيش ان تسال وهاب عن الأربعين قطعة سلاح اشتري من سوسر]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aafiron Any chance the Iron will put together a ‘party bus’ for a road trip to Atlanta?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we see depends mainly in what we look for. - John Lubbock  #usa🇺🇸 #chicago #illinois #traveldiaries… https://t.co/CfgEUAF9se]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I’m at work and it’s sunny and warm and I’m not ripping trails.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoopshype Love @SHAQ  Shut up @SHAQ  U played on 6 teams so stop telling other people not to make choices.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elias told me “you are missing one stereotype, you work two jobs, go to school, you are just missing your child to support” 😂😂 I’m good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBG_Past_Prime @Local12 Wrong, John. Like others have said, the votes of small states wouldn't count then. Elector… https://t.co/ET62Msy8ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Randy02849810 @kathygriffin BOSTON MEDIA STARTED AMERICA.  NOW YOU CANT LEAVE.   I WILL TAKE YOUR CHILDREN.  RIGHT… https://t.co/B2bOg7sJEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEITH_R_GOOCH @The1stBAT @UpToTASK @BrianLeeOkert @The_GWW @CBNostalgia @GeekVibesNation @mrjafri @GeekToMeRadio… https://t.co/x212cUZPLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whittertron @bsbd2511 @DanielH66631700 Dude, why do you keep trying to paint me as a sexist or something with thes… https://t.co/idxpHh6LUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @princeton_hoops 🐅 vs @cubigredhoops 🐻 #ivyleague 🏀 @ Jadwin Gymnasium https://t.co/uXzAK8phUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stuttsy @WWERetroStars For real. I had given up. I walk into five below and there they are 10 of them for $5 each.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz How was the week for the billionaires? You guys having a good one?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nook and Cranny by Alex Kuno. Now on exhibit and currently available as part of the Unloved Creatures exhibit at Ro… https://t.co/NqSDobblo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyHicksGOP The professional victim rants again, please keep it up, she’s half the reason Trump was elected, Trump 2020 beotch’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[What makes me angry is the next time someone is attacked, raped or assaulted ... there’s going to be a tinge if dou… https://t.co/sMsjBQDWac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets Quick...somebody change the locks to the doors!!  LOLOL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Beatles - Eleanor Rigby (From "Yellow Submarine") https://t.co/dPnpEiZ5AP via @YouTube #Musicmakesourwolrdbetter 🎧🎼🎤🎹]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here’s the beginning of the biggest week of our year. Fully focused, and ready to make a run! #TournamentTime… https://t.co/IrHj2hUWmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay guys tell me why the Dallas Airport actually took the time to comment on my post💀😭 #lol https://t.co/VqYijGIzOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StPaulResident You went through hell that I can't imagine. Sorry this happened. Glad you have been able to move on… https://t.co/Uh2UlaAR55]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien Dear @peterbakernyt remember Obama's Brett Baier interview on Fox? For all you journalist out there… https://t.co/QOIsSfkIv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[when I die done read these tweets to learn about me.. the story is in the music https://t.co/K5PdXQPv4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Give them the FREEDOM OF CHOICE: 1.) They either transition into democratic co-ops instead of capitalist c… https://t.co/k7zi5LFpjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wherermypants @arawnsley @puckthepilot @Mother_of_Tanks @LostLT1 @sgtjanedoe @PatDonahoeArmy @LadyLovesTaft Rat Pa… https://t.co/ZrzVNyXxzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBNSports @ByMHarrington He’s -33, and we are supposed to be impressed by the fact that he makes mean faces at peo… https://t.co/rWyPs93nZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryanair @IvanSideroff Should I try a different browser to see if you have responded to my dm?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m a singer,” she answered. “And what kind of music do you sing?” “Mostly country music, I would say.” I nodded.… https://t.co/nNAP7GX5Dk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speedweeks 2019 is the year of the single file racing 🤦🏻‍♂️😪!! #NASCAR #Speedweeks #NASCARRacingExp300… https://t.co/OO9lwq7TlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just spent 30 min watching people throw cheese on their child’s face at 3 am. What’s wrong with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very cool article about what they're doing at Nuno's Bar and Bistro in Upland! https://t.co/CjsEMROBDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[New release is out today on Beatport via Easy Summer! An original blend of lush guitar, salted beats, trip-hop, and… https://t.co/D6FrkcguVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched a video on how YouTube is facilitating pedophilia and they are doing the bare minimum at fixing the… https://t.co/GLTYiHefSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Stone Harbor NJ @ Stone Harbor Beach https://t.co/lQEhYxzWMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don't even have to buy me dinner first! #greekcuisine #foodporn #tarponspringsspongedocks #hellasrestaurant… https://t.co/HjRfQbqmr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go Matt! @LamphereSchools community is behind your quest! #WeAreLamphere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drawandstrike @Vetteil Nancy, using this despicable CaCa clapping pose encapsulate the Disrespectful attitude of D… https://t.co/q0qjKwysag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Riggs_83 @wbz SHUT THE FUCK UP.  ENEMY PRESS.  LOOZAH. https://t.co/l84uhgNnSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnousBirding @LongPointBirdOb You may still need to be concerned. The ice on Erie is mobile and will start to move… https://t.co/j0IBgBW5dL]]></document><document><![CDATA[figgity figgity figgity figgity figgity figgity figgity figgity figgity figgity figgity figgity figgity figgity fig… https://t.co/XhMStDLQmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BibChr Trajectory always determines destination. Go back and read Crazy Love. You can spot the trajectory in that book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackDodsons @LangleySpeedway @811 @PerformancePOil @SafetyKleen Back in mid-80s Joey's wife at the time worked as… https://t.co/ng7G6R5PUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you David! Appreciate the way you write and how you continue to inspire! A great friend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[☀️Another Perfect Day #1240manzanita #stephansfolly #deepwellestates #carsofpalmsprings #palmsprings #midcentury… https://t.co/oelknd38nU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felt like we played with a red card but a draw at Old Trafford will do.   Would have loved a win but 3 substitutes… https://t.co/SyAWMIeOwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sf28430 @AmySolsma How does Mrs Shark Farmer have time to help you be so witty?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDonalDrumpf It would be presidential of you, Sir,  to keep your distance from the kind of people with whom you… https://t.co/ldLcvVOjXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMaherNews12 @News12 @eyesonislesFS @Offside_Tavern @Section_329 @IslesGirl3 @islesfanrico @gothambatman14 How man… https://t.co/95pJwjbOuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Royalty Lounge &amp; Bistro https://t.co/bWVtAbtj6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuiehls million dollar march wu tang Batista auiiehlll uiehl right original]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: No. 3 Notre Dame 100, No. 1 West Liberty 96. Once again top seed cannot pull a double and win a tournament. #MECTourney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fams2gether Our immigration laws unfairly punish and separate the spouses and families of U.S. citizens. The myth… https://t.co/HnGVQG488K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was bummed because nobody told me about Nicole Malone celebrTion yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's the test of anyone who claims to be from Miami: do they know Parrot Jungle, and have a photo taken with two… https://t.co/vLUdkUS39u]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 Mardi Gras de L’anse was a success. Here’s to keeping culture and tradition alive! #ilssontpartis… https://t.co/0yTada0v5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the first season of Friends, does Ross never button his sleeves????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amidst 50% growth in 2018 revenue plus regional expansion strategy, Jamaican analysts VM Wealth positive on gaming firm SVL.#stockstowatch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bobbyboy01 @ByMHarrington could be....I just want it to be finalized now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadly, the left shift key on this VT320 keyboard has given up the ghost. I can try to clean it out, but I also will… https://t.co/kNBi40iD6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harleydavidson #dustymullinax #dustymayhem #zenttattoosga #harleydavidson #snakeoilaftercare #jobstopper @ Zen Tat… https://t.co/TrwLwn1CLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never to this day be able to defend 2011 NBA Finals LeBron. I was literally nauseous watching that series after Game 3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AyD_ParaTi buenos días, les reporto una fuga en un medidor sobre Av. Casa Blanca, Col. San Cristóbal, no. 1348, Sa… https://t.co/Olt0ZKB7Cq]]></document><document><![CDATA[sample sale gonna be lit 🔥 starts Monday at danielpatrick_melrose only in LA! @ Daniel Patrick https://t.co/9Au6uGpnJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mako @TristanGHill I think it’s one of pushas best verses but cyhi definitely had the best verse on that song]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week of art related travel made me feel like Phineas Fogg of Around the World in 80 Days or Mad Max the Road W… https://t.co/63kEgY8Djt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasie ..Trump asked him whether the United States should use force in Venezuela. Graham said that he preached caut… https://t.co/cezNzmfrmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DomShow1210   This makes it imperative that republicans compete in Blue states]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so thankful for Mrs Terrones! Thank you for all you do! @jkmetcalf1 @hightower_333]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheerElk14 Thank you! Heading back to the warm and cheerful city we all love 💛✈️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irlaelena Buenos días Elena, que tengas un excelente viernes inicio de mes. Abrazos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/nhfrcSXKFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing in Action   Since January, Trustee Werden has not attended a single budget meeting.  With the fight for edu… https://t.co/crbstrveFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't fight the insurance company alone. If you have a #Florida based home claim contact me today  #tampa #clearwaterbeach #StPetersburg]]></document></documents></author>