<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Sa mga marurumi isip na kesyo    Honeymoon daw...its a group tour w/ her brother n  PA mike / a gift to  watch the… https://t.co/mJgKai58Y3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lapd2014 @LAPDHollywood @Connellybooks @LAPDLurie @911LAPD @LAPDETingirides @GoodNewsCops @joinlapd @RobertNBCLA… https://t.co/QiiSmRKp4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I Stood In Front Of The Judge Today, I realized That All You Really Have In Hard Times .. Is Yourself. ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjacksonj13 @EmilyLiebtag @Carlos_Moreno06 @kwaku1 @rewolfeJFF @kmjlbrown @mjcraw @O_MerC I can’t believe you woul… https://t.co/jEshJmkJ51]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lkirdani1 @TinMan97087572 @SandiaWisdom That’s what I’m thinking 🤔 it is an amazing sign to me that things are getting better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hornekerjustin Cool.  I definitely can use some new tricks as none of the usual stuff is working. Something to get through to spring .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuiceWorlddd Is that what @highimallyy said when she caught you pooping with the door open ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasSowell @DavidHuffman319 It’s too bad we have allowed our Educational system to become so socialistic.  Why c… https://t.co/kwZmf47Wuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW: In episode 2 of @ABC News' “The Investigation” podcast, Michael Cohen’s lawyer says his client will offer insi… https://t.co/qgcvLA10O9]]></document><document><![CDATA[When commuters and Times Square tourists collide! (Commuter does face plant, tourist runs away!) @ Hospital for Spe… https://t.co/bxCKmlkUZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[💫 Practice What You Preach Supplementing skiing with performance training.   🔹 Floor row w/ push up. 🔹Tall Burpee w… https://t.co/xzepyTEB43]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is arbitrary. Thanks for coming to my TED talk, Daylight Saving Time, at 4, no 5, o'clock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finishing up this oil painting of Mt. Chocorua, in Tamworth, NH. Two-thirds of it was painted en plein air this fal… https://t.co/jesAwynH5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great hike with my baby. @ Great Falls Park https://t.co/PSBNevL7Us]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drsarahdoom introducing the idea of Unique Molecular Yield (UMY). Important concept to understand with @PacBio CCS… https://t.co/f9DPPhMhF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indigocean55 @mmilky400 *be real not me real lord twitter edit please!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanedawson It was discovered that it there are videos on YouTube for kids telling them to kill themselves or that momo will kill them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CunningSq16 @tpcowgurl @MisleaderC @strom_annette @thesaucyliberal @ChrisToTheW @esadah @TeaSippingBarb… https://t.co/PLlOFHQH0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank u, next is such a good album no one can tell me that it isnt cause I’ll beat them up]]></document><document><![CDATA[What better way to top of your Fried Chicken Wednesday 🍗than with a cupcake!🧁 Join the ladies of NCNW👒 in King Fraz… https://t.co/qOZ3kKFdzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I really am tired of this shit yo I only have 2 pairs of pants and their both thin joggers that I look TERRIB… https://t.co/aUEbY3uRgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Janellioo @torikelly Aww I’m sure she would have said hi!! (Like I know her or something 😬😂)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ummm stfuuuuuuuuuuu i dated a taurus anddddddd  he was jealous af https://t.co/4aPZM6WAB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@felipenopollous @smalltownandrew @NolanBadylak @Sifill_LDF Hollywood is a cesspool of filth and degenerates https://t.co/MlF7MLqVEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenniferjsmall @ClandestineRos1 Maybe they tried that too! 🧐 https://t.co/MeyQ9T0mP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so glad to see more SEC teams doing really well. Tennessee was irrelevant for a while there - hopefully the co… https://t.co/E8eYxxvj5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theydidwut When I pretended Beau wanted a picture for his 21st birthday. @joejonas &amp; when someone cropped me lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertkaplinsky @TracyZager @stenhousepub @openmiddle Congrats my friend! I wish you the very best! Proud of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tinker v Des Moines Independent School District Supreme Court case took place 50 years (and one day) ago on Februar… https://t.co/aCO8Q8m1uk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is snapchat still a thing or is it just a place for women to use filters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Breaneka A majority of the homeless here are not even from Cali..but they all kno they come here and get taken car… https://t.co/wxAAR9iUNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IKEAUSA question. Why is my profile no longer accessible? I was able to log in last night and see some status upda… https://t.co/WABChEPhrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[LHS Varsity Softball all 14 around our dining room table. Bill actually made lasagna and salad, I'm having the wine… https://t.co/cjyO2wmYkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HitmanHeitzie @TommyDoyle47 Yeah, there's nothing about her character that gave off the "strong but losing the battle mentally" vibe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading non-profit development guides only for the extremely excellent graphics https://t.co/6bQITWIktZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Democrats forget  they work for America citizens..  Stop fighting for Illegal Aliens Undocumented… https://t.co/pAaVNfTMnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a firm believer of God and a firm believer of prayer and the law of attraction]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chefrocky413 I wouldn't ever spoke to you if I knew were a patriots fan, just kidding kinda 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CreativeWomen4 @CM_Intl1 @NatGeo @urbangorillas @ladygorillas @NaturePhotoNet @nature @LakeGenevaGov… https://t.co/j5ZdXODl8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had fun catching up w/ a good friend today....&amp; no broken bones! @ Millennium Park https://t.co/Qs23IaOBre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_crownxroyal Wearing something I already got that still looks fresh n new FOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ask to hangout and i say no or make excuses it’s probably because i have social anxiety and that sounds like… https://t.co/IzdBQMmLCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[admit ur wrong and stop making excuses just cause you don’t want to put your pride aside]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyToobin @nprfreshair @jerome_corsi @NewYorker Love listening to you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southerncalijen @MrJohnnyLasagna Oh Jen! You can go!! Espwa event in Nashville!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Countdown is on for TDSB secondary Technological Skills competition. I was so happy to see this poster at Northern… https://t.co/IQmG7Oigsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GHGGuru @ConversationUS There are some real doozies in this piece - I am not sure what constitutes a “factory farm… https://t.co/Mwr1Jjt16W]]></document><document><![CDATA[The joy that comes from science experiments is my favorite @MysterySci #stem https://t.co/ovdKaIu1Nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Corey_Feldman @jojoclap_1 Yes, a grown man, knows what a grown man feels sexually...He claims, he was raped every… https://t.co/5Hg9KOIegi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burning question: watching a three year old episode of Planet Earth: is a Fox a dog or a cat?]]></document><document><![CDATA[when ur friend does smth that accidentally triggers u but ur not trynna ruin the good vibe so u gotta swallow the d… https://t.co/T7tGe6mYVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“i have a lot of youngins hitting me up, i’m gonna need to start asking for their ID’s before they come over”😂😂😂💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lkoneal @ByronYork Obama used the same laws to pay Iran, as Trump, is doing, sorry but it is not illegal. Congress… https://t.co/9fohMSmEBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved seeing the dedication of the @Newton_High students and teachers who were preparing for EOCs and AP exams this… https://t.co/wY4y5HYEyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[All we do any more in America is go around farting , throwing up are getting so fat we can't walk !! Is because the… https://t.co/33B1fSlBl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[am I really gonna watch the great Gatsby two nights in a row?? the answer is definitely yes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day 2019! Explore powerful words by women &amp; illustrated by women from around the 🌎!… https://t.co/5tH3mTLnbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StanfordBSB game 3 in Tempe...let’s go Cardinal! https://t.co/n7fCNV9oVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This conversation is open to all.  This is an opportunity to hear from Black Women at the highest level politics pr… https://t.co/UeaOVuUfhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he's mailing suspicious pkgs to anyone, even himself, now he's committed a federal crime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[so much of my life has changed like my gym routine and my self care routines and how i handle recovering from anxie… https://t.co/z7Azjo1vk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoga 5 days in a row I feel so good 💓 also so excited to black the f out tonight. #balance]]></document><document><![CDATA[for the love of god, stfu with y’all dumb ass options about shit y’all know nothing about . SIMPLE AS THAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donavon Mitchell is going to be so good when he becomes an efficient scorer instead of a volume scorer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just received a release from Mississippi State stating that Nick Weatherspoon has been suspended indefinitely from… https://t.co/fKzaZgPMnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AstiGirl and #LittleOrphanAnnie keep switching bones; it’s easily more wonderful than the peanut butter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealRonJeremy And sometimes you come in a spider suit... https://t.co/vE5UAFklsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all my dreams the past couple of nights have been TOO ROWDY for me I’m shook]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePerezHilton Not so much. Things start “changing “ closer to 13, meaning you’ll have to start dealing with it about then”sh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swiftlycabeIlo THANK YOU SO MUCH MARY!!!!!!! HOPE TO SEE YA AGAIN REAL SOON!!!!!!!! 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunterHeglund That’s really sad I’m sorry. My mom sent me 2 cards in the mail. Donna is better than Tami]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c_nonya @chisoxjoe44 @AngelaF08695845 @RepAdamSchiff @realDonaldTrump back to a country they know nothing about by… https://t.co/mICLS0fnn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kris Jenner is somewhere weighing her options. Like is she ready to go against Jada “I’m from Baltimore” Pinkett Smith.. We shall see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video Now Available on @ManyVids 💕 https://t.co/McLQTu5992 https://t.co/Kc62RIKzib]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @FreedomForumIns Freedom to practice boycott, divestment &amp; sanctions needs to be protected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember this is the only moment in time you have to live. Look at your feet that is where you are. Now take a few… https://t.co/iyzQbBWNDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need you to focus on me or else I’m gone homie.  It takes effort on both sides]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get into the Winter Spirit...fun in the sun &amp; snow with ur Bestie ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoJoBelovee I love them! I also like Joan, I love her unapologetic attitude 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mesquiteisdtx I’m wondering why there was a student arrested for bringing a gun to Poteet High School today and no… https://t.co/QYcmKbbHy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TUSK81 A thought! All these agents, prison guards, etc.... Assuming they speak Spanish, what countries do they com… https://t.co/3DoTdvXTQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julnilsmith I’m here WAY early! Does this selfie count? 🤞🏼@WebsterSOC @websteru #mediaacademy https://t.co/NByjgSVP1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luchafan84 @chrischoughton @shanehoughton @RedHerington @childishgamzeno @wendimclendonco @KassandraHeller… https://t.co/f8Lm3pU9ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated Maybe he’s more afraid of what the Russians would do to him and his family - that would certainly get my attention!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my mom hotboxed the basement last weekend with her friend while they were drunk and i can’t stop laughing at this https://t.co/tAFi2vlcMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's my hope for this generation that we can destigmatize mental illness to the point where those of us who struggl… https://t.co/HaUbWZ9vO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvarto_ Lmao literally it was the only viable chasers in the house and i was skeptical BUT it was fuckin amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKubota @DivaVinophile @Cbp8Cindy @wineworldnews @MacCocktail @thisis_mac @Oberreimer @muladhara… https://t.co/cypdlarfYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bonnyjk @CatsOfTurf @Fray8 @KillerJake1 HIS NOSE FRECKLE. Just stop. 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanEast Congrats, Nate. This is amazing. Hope to see you at @CelebFightNight this year, my friend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love seeing all the positive reviews @AugustAlsina is getting about his EP. He deserves it 😩❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best to ever lace them up demonstrating that some things are bigger than basketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy one year anniversary to our baby doggy Tsuki! We picked her up a year ago today and our lives have been for t… https://t.co/eHbePtxyB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A helicopter in Kenya has crashed killing four Americans and a local pilot  https://t.co/KipAGsPfNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecl326 I’m not sure about that Ernie because I don’t have all the ins and outs of it all. But I hope one day to bu… https://t.co/xisgDRUsfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to our lone senior, Justin Folkers (@LilTippy23) for his 4 years of dedication and hard work to this prog… https://t.co/FAGJRed7fO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided to take a nap after work because I only got four hours of sleep last night andddd.....I woke up 4 hours later]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is happiness found if not in the heart? But why the heart?  Right from the outset, it is important to underst… https://t.co/KjghOlWvCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti The ONLY dignified response to being made fun of on SNL is to laugh about it. Otherwise you look l… https://t.co/fcBaF1IlkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to move out so I can’t afford to leave my apartment all I do is buy food and wildly expensive bottled water every day]]></document></documents></author>