<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[3rd graders love practicing spelling words when they get instant feedback! #DLDay @TechieHippo https://t.co/6v8cNauHYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evan_bentley Ha! Thanks. Not happy with my discussion, but ran out of time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonlovett Will Pundit or you be happier to see the other when you get home?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Blessed Sunday Everyone!! @ Edgy Girl Fitness Studio https://t.co/sdL7APEjTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csharkey40 @StinebaughCarol Sounds like what happens here! And trust me the cbj fans are just as loud!  But tell m… https://t.co/mlIu0f2Z3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this man with all my heart and soul. 💞 You give me lifeeeeee baby! kda_fitness. Everyday is magical with you… https://t.co/saK4Ua3O5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s  #NationalMargaritaDay you know what that means I’m gonna be drunk somewhere  😂 🍹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $25 Roblox Gift Card Offer     Win $25 Roblox Gift Card Offer By A Complete Simple Sign Up,      Sign Here… https://t.co/uaigotVMcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCTheVoice @TheBundysMusic @Indigo_Girls Don’t worry Blake. Remember the Swoon Brothers?   So Kelly mentioned Eva… https://t.co/c2vOEKZRXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely gorgeous day at Picacho Peak State Park. The poppies are amazing this year. @AZStateParks rock! https://t.co/2PyhaAn9lD]]></document><document><![CDATA[eu ano passado: palhaçada essa Conmebol, LA perdeu totalmente a graça pra mim, dá nem vontade de acompanhar mais… https://t.co/l3OnoUnFUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asked Jordan how he would describe me if someone asked, and he said “I’d say you’re like a pig.. you burp a lot” an… https://t.co/21ABksyJfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of having my ears pierced: I’ve lost the stuff to clean them with]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely! Bring back a theme park in Houston. These kids need to be able to have that experience like we did when… https://t.co/3CuVpoBZwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying a new mask.... it's silver!!  "Transforming liquid foil" by labotica. #ipsy #actorlife #cameraready… https://t.co/rBBO1Hhy9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[The party that brought fake native American attack by 16 yr old consertive.. a fake Hollywood race hate attack.. wa… https://t.co/WeFcc6BNC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using ELD resources to prepare our kids to be successful during the listening portion of the ELPAC @RascalPride… https://t.co/WzYROaTwfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows look at the tape, that boy was reading his answers! Proof is in the puddin'!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave_Stein That’s why I try to judge based on multiple criteria, not just isolated remarks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeymanHustle  would love to see YOU &amp; the phone go into Hall of Fame @WWE  it is well deserved]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tristesouvent MLA for World Lit and APA for Secondary Ed...are you telling me you’ve never had to use APA for a pa… https://t.co/FqTuN3psdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight @DukeMBB vs @GoHeels. Love this time of year with #MarchMadness2019 right around the corner. ♥️🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbymartinn11 I think I found your boyfriend’s empty wallet 😓 please DM me. Trying to reach @Marcellogel]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I pick up my refund check tomorrow which means I can finally move to Norfolk and everything will be perfect 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier this week, my colleague @HennepinD2 and I had the chance to tour the @Hennepin Medical Examiner’s Office th… https://t.co/xeRXcXCTqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes, we find only half the record, in this case an indenture. (Found by @geofhuth at work today.) https://t.co/vcNX11AvAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has @amyklobuchar been reading @nationaljournal 👀 re: @SenatorShaheen https://t.co/Px8GjE8Lzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maccoinnich @CMcCurdyPDX did you click the link? Because, oops, I didn't. It was newsroom chatter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetipy @DailyArtApp Je ne le connais malheureusement pas😌. Mais! Ouf! Quelle énergie!🌊 #EdoDuNorth]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel the jobs I’ve had are so eccentric everyone else my age has normal jobs at the mall lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@forkeepsbooks I got the book signed!  Thank you for this gem. Also, congrats on the @newyorktimes article. https://t.co/smcslD71ot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marykk196051 @MontanezBeatriz @RoxanneCWhiting @julieknowles3g @AngelaAP1965 @MaryKayH188 @k_pastorkova… https://t.co/h8o4hieUhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@areynarivarola Is this a contunuation of #undocubougie (which made me lol)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Fox keeps on playing with the dog toy last night while we were sleeping. https://t.co/gvqfsA8D11 @ChuckBell4 Our wilder canine friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgetCReed Or in the subway, or on the street, or in Target...drives me nuts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edu_sanders70 Happy to finally meet @Stv_Gilliland  main dude! It was my pleasure!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaceyBrazel I knew you’d say something. I prefer fresh air! And if we move from Indiana spring won’t be as cold!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill Torn. Kids idolize athletes. They’re like Gods to them. But, they aren’t entitled to touch anyone without permission either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeChams @brendonurie @PanicAtTheDisco Thank you, Jake, for letting us see it all through your eyes &amp; lenses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thesupercole The last picture is her literally saying “ yeah I know I’m cute! Keep taking pictures” @SavannahSoutas @Thesupercole]]></document><document><![CDATA[The highlight of my valentines was giving my 4-5yr old babies their teddy bears and chocolates💕 happy Valentine’s D… https://t.co/RbDQZB0gNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[i'm not sure what to make of this: someone bungeed their #crutches to a tree?? because s/he no longer needed them?… https://t.co/TMLJfp1mxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to grind and make the perfect application for this internship that is the most perfect of matches for wha… https://t.co/KvfT5hYG6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, right now I’d rather read tweets about towels than ones about Trump and politics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highlight of my day was when a hot Australian NYFD man showed up at my door because our whole apartment building flooded. It’s not even 5am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling quite festive this year!! We are all decorated for Mardi Gras! Even had Mardi Gras and Jazz playing in the… https://t.co/qQRryBnwj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iTunes Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% Free in the Link Below   Cli… https://t.co/AG6wmLa5rq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllisterDen I say that word quite often when I'm frustrated. Still a good person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinkrakow @AvaGCooper @WCTH_TV @hallmarkchannel Happy belated Birthday @AvaGCooper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinFilipski @bw77_cd23 @ByMHarrington Maybe he wants weather reports in the stories. Perhaps Don Paul could come… https://t.co/bB0L0m2k5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCSDSuper @13WHAM @nholland13wham @1AlexisArnold @ArlenesCostumes You are amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[14 Straight A+ school Awards!  Thank you Mrs. Gates and Ms. Thetford for visiting us at the Northwest Florida Balle… https://t.co/EVnrRXlkob]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we've been up to! @FairbankPS #7and8gifted math and science class. S.T.E.M. sled challenge, pentominoes challe… https://t.co/tSygrG5EF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stemfastdiet Will I ever live down the shame I feel from that? Stay tuned]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyplace. SEC weekends are almost here! @ Auburn Softball Complex https://t.co/1JFl2UA7tW]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need natural solutions to climate change and biodiversity loss.  In addition to reforestation, we need protectio… https://t.co/L1dnXq07RG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgePapa19 I heard you. You make them sound like the idiots they are. Just be careful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking news: @USFWS U.S. #Fish and #Wildlife Service proposes STRIPPING federal PROTECTIONS for #wolves ‼️👎🏻😱👎🏻‼️… https://t.co/Xy1cZTWFR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can this be allowed. I realize freedom of speech is one of our most important rights, but this is inciting viol… https://t.co/BAM2UukA7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WhyILoveTesla We no longer have to buy gas or have oil drips in the garage. We love our clean non-smelly garage :) #TwoTeslaFamily @Tesla]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣. @AlfredoJalifeR_  @marvinicio  @norma22flores  @Saucedina @PerezrobJ Dave had his 'offensive' last name embl… https://t.co/kZYpcaOFo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAMOUR_XO I ain’t bring none of that gas from back home lol but i know somebody up there wit pressure i got you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, #teachers! I’m watching @EdgeOf17 for an upcoming #podcast ep and want to know your thoughts!! GO!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog @maddow Most def, this was not equal justice under the law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmr___18 Lol, I can't believe there are gifs for this! Typed in eating a banana just to see if anything came up ha… https://t.co/rkxTFAfUeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red So is a baboon’s bum Did you know male spider monkeys Don’t have a baculum?!  #AcademicValentines… https://t.co/LLXamQ2JhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horror, entendimiento hasta donde puede llegar el egoísmo humano, apreciación de la fragilidad de las sociedades, a… https://t.co/p0QlP6T8O4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_UnSilent_ @Dovewoman1 No...and he changes his hair color weekly...or has he switched to wigs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@editorialunilit Este día celebramos el gran amor que Dios tiene por sus hijos. Aprendamos amar como DIOS nos enseñ… https://t.co/FRLMJOkLnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve spilled my coffee at the library 3 times now.. i think this is a sign to lay off the coffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingsPapa1015 @4lisaguerrero Very Sad...hope you are wrong on this...ugh!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I’m thinking about is that Marty grocery store robot I saw on my timeline and idk who posted it😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@my3monkees @ThePsycholitics @BreitbartNews IF vaccines work why is everybody so worried...the unwashed may get the… https://t.co/Zuq16Mtglf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its 4:30 am. I need to go to sleep but i'm here watching #UmbrellaAcademy like i don't have work in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t believe playlist is finally here!! so excited to see my bby’s this weekend 💘💖💕💗💓💞 https://t.co/WCNS4acHeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Some helpful advice here about grant applications, esp. importance of nailing down the “blurb”. #MSUepet]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Diversity is inviting people into the room... equality is asking them what they think.” Talking diversity vs. true… https://t.co/g5YF6SQp9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to #tesol2019 — #colorvowelchart #colorvowelroseboat road trip! @ Fairfax County, Virginia https://t.co/k74stNHbBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Christina  I was born in the water  My age is so weird  I like to go back to sleep   Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than two weeks ago you tweeted celebratory comments about full term abortion. Maybe sit this one out, Dragon Q… https://t.co/mRV2Rr6Pgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremyjojola Lil’ Bone Broth. (I kinda like it. And I’m not a millennial.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t just write, put it on the big screen as a sizzle reel, says Yasmin Neal megayazzy.  Check out our website… https://t.co/X0rRT41HfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Postmates_Help I just received a completely incorrect order and he app will not let me submit my complaint]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertbenzie Okay folks you can force him to end his attack on autistic kids too! FIGHT! #AutismProtest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjredwine was tired of stories using beauty as currency for women. YASSSS!!! #SEYA2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready to get this show on the road! #interiordesigner #homeandgardenshow2018 #centralohio #614 #speaker @ Ohio… https://t.co/dVdHfm5GXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epigmenioibarra No tienen vergüenza decir que morena es la esperanza de México  pobres ilusos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horsemandon @TeamGeeMoney Don’t like. This jockey is excellent rider as well as a great person. He should not be depicted like this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawnVanstone Heck, you’ll be done in time to come do a few shifts over here. That’s delightful news since I could… https://t.co/OCoWlYuNbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m_pereira07 @LiraHeitor Esse frio aqui é um milagre, faz um calor do agreste todos os dias pior q SP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaClinton @WalkerMishelle In an ideal world we could be hopeful. But that girl will be fine. Just as you are,… https://t.co/H1zbKzgwEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@douevnlift @BreakingNLive You forgot “needed” change to a dictator govt. we’re trying to help with humanitarian ai… https://t.co/ND0usvYO0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chinatown - @sfchinatown in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/1K4ahDXEZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sabuli_2007 @GobiernoMX y sus funcionarios sacatones igual de irrespetuosos, chango ve chango hace...]]></document><document><![CDATA[how many of y’all are only watching the oscars for lady gaga and (hopefully) bradley cooper?? lol I AMMMMMMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why would a traitor, a crony of dictators, a wannabe king,  celebrate Independence Day...asking fo… https://t.co/eGqnv0Osm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRMotorsports @DaleJr @Hellmanns @NASCAR_Xfinity @TooToughToTame FANTASTIC!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a car again feels so good y’all 😭 feels even better that it’s MINE. In MY name. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who just put her two weeks in🤷🏻‍♀️ moving forward with better opportunities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My parents are currently in Cabo . I haven’t talked to them since Sunday. Well my mom just called me today and I st… https://t.co/U9ooxFrBBV]]></document></documents></author>