<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheHashtag0nist @GenePark That was fun. But the “filing cabinet” question was funny too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash Pos hack who has to get his talking points elsewhere cause he’s too stupid to have his own thoughts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have time you wanna fill, The Ted Bundy tapes of 5 episodes is a great time killer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like peace and quiet inside the office during a lunch break, just trying to get through my last day of the week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp Sticks and stones  may break my bones but words via keyboard strokes from mommies basement shall never hurt me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Worst headline ever. Gotta please your leftist audience? Too bad you didn’t tell the right story: b… https://t.co/sRKfej2x5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solquesana Sis, same here but shoot I don’t wanna be in food service anymore. Not saying a degree will get me out… https://t.co/XYY0yX30QH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cubgranny @realDonaldTrump You can’t possibly be this stupid. Nobody is this stupid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJSnM Not quite as dapper here, but appropriate none the less. https://t.co/XfVR4gSXnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattoxgolf @osubeaverturf @KernsJim @badgercropdoc @uwpaul You are the man Clint! Sweden had some very progressive… https://t.co/n1L1OUEMSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird seeing Lebron break MJ’s record in Lakers jersey and not Cavs jersey. Cavs fans deserve better ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to Oxfam, the 26 richest people on Earth, just over the seating capacity of the Bombardier 7500, have the… https://t.co/RlWSZ8Z4Vt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya me pasaron todos los stickers de la famila p luche, ¿Alguien tiene los de una familia de diez? 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now, after calling Jussie Smollet's story an example of a lynch mob, he says he does not like to comment until all… https://t.co/jjV2Y2wc71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@creoleasf Even better now that explains your focus and drive again congratulations good job]]></document><document><![CDATA[“THE CAVE YOU FEAR TO ENTER HOLDS THE TREASURE YOU SEEK.” — #FromLiesToRiches #comingsoon #peteroestévez… https://t.co/OSKk7huBib]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so glad #SNL made fun of this interview and this sick fool...save the theatrics and waterworks..… https://t.co/95TN8aMXjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelnykEugene Worst owner in all of pro sports !! Congrats, must make your liver feel good !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half time entertainment at Sac Republic. @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/ma7jHD95xN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldnSweetCheek That’s wild ain’t nothing wrong with your name https://t.co/vnMzdGgDSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrkillswitchX @HoweRhowe1980 @IMPACTWRESTLING @FiteTV @LuchaElRey @Tess_Blanchard @TheEliDrake @MrGMSI_BCage… https://t.co/JAHRomhttr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcoreyg @scottmpetri @InsideNatGeo @PBLWorks @shahselbe @JambeckResearch @Cutlers_Catch @KatlinBowman… https://t.co/BNfc2VjlqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tokens per airdrop: 50  Tokens per referral: 10  Platform: ETHEREUM https://t.co/MeM3aZl4WD #airdrop #bounties https://t.co/UGYS5uX8f8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Football players can play basketball, but basketball players can’t play football.   Defensive backs can play WR, bu… https://t.co/NFgJ1Bl0gd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KorstJ @DISupdates Great to hang out together @DISupdates. Next meeting 🥃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brookehazexoxo @Blacked_com @BlackedRaw @GregLansky @VIXEN How can they not love you?! You're the kindest, prettie… https://t.co/TfSH7m0prl]]></document><document><![CDATA[i thank god, @mrj_ray , and Mrs. Tucker every day that I am a good writer because it allows me to write a 5 page pa… https://t.co/Mor2nqqE3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MazenGhalayini @rwdavis2011 @Forbes I attribute a lot of my career success to this skill, differentiating what’s i… https://t.co/zlcNPKy1VT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathygriffin So you want the US to be like Russia. You truly are an idiot. Once, you used to be funny. Sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snooze is a dumb invention. How much restful sleep can you get in a five-minute window. #WakeUpAmerica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsmeEddieC @sak_shoes @rdickey249 Cofin-yo and you don’t use MANCHEGO? Ave Maria purisima!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good bye Venus  Helllooooo Mrs. Robinson  @sherman_players https://t.co/wBY7RmgCJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥Daily Kickoff March 1st🔥🔥 We’re going to prepare hard this month, no matter what we’re doing in our lives, wherev… https://t.co/CHIlGo4dkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[love to time going into a revolving door with someone entering or exiting a building]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrMelliBitch @MelliBitch @AnaKasparian Sickest wins! Your reward; DEATH! God cripples are dark people.😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@francescagracie That day was in the best interest for everyone. Why risk it?... I'm glad the board made that decision.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody tell Virgil I need some off white bowling shoes. I’m going pro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Permanent Funeral by @3floyds @ Winning — https://t.co/QiuBxJoBMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakeair737 @HerreraBeutler Ok.  On the agenda for our next democratic POTUS is assault weapon and climate change N… https://t.co/xACgFIqObv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely mind blowing that there was a time in my life where I could function for an entire day without a cup of coffee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johndensford I need to compile a list of my preseason winner picks bc S37 is the first I can remember in a while w… https://t.co/BojtFYmWXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to attend this performance! I am proud of our students, Dr. Thomas and our special relationship with the Ep… https://t.co/TlYGvwW2qK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaverickIsLoose @denzelcurry @denzelcurry as a true fan of rage against the machine I gotta say that the cover you… https://t.co/c64sBED3Yw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zenzurzb24 @RooferXX @tripletsfan19 @CarlRamallo @tommyspannerman @GiselleMarks1 @figstreetstudio @Naveedraeesani… https://t.co/v4ymXTDtpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC You left out that a wall will not solve the problem. Extract your head from Trumps anus!]]></document><document><![CDATA[people think i care about them leaving my life, idgaf because the most important people in your life even walk out… https://t.co/pBUrC9nSPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaggieMadsen3 @AriMelber @ParryPierce I’ve been crying about it all along... as loud as I can... I personally feel… https://t.co/a2K1FDWN8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TATravelCenters I’m a Platinum member who in the month of January bought 2,105.221 gallons of diesel fuel from you… https://t.co/uRi1iI6okm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarkBornLight @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/NNjoThGKNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is #DuqDayofGiving! I donated to support the work of the McAnulty Liberal Arts College. Join me in donating: https://t.co/YxOdCDPiVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[17 year old Jake got his angel wings at 2:12 pm today. Please pray for his soul, his family, and for everyone else… https://t.co/w3BOGAX5fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @OversightDems @HouseIntel Witch hunt.  Overseen by a real witch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When i ventured outside my comfort zone, my life changed.  Slow and steady wins my race. @ Enfield, Connecticut https://t.co/e1qe2dIvy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bryce Harper  What an awful deal for Philadelphia! I am not talking about the money at all. It's all about the leng… https://t.co/IsVOUKauUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leonline2000 @GNBoficial Está es por mucho la estupideces más grande que le e visto a los chavestias jajajajaja. E… https://t.co/M5w8l0GZk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what your schedule may call for always try to find some time in the day for YOU.  10-15 minutes of YOU ti… https://t.co/f2CgsvtvnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phillies are going all in. Exciting time for their fans, for now. Let's see how this plays out. 13 years for $330M… https://t.co/d0IIzZuDJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez and Chakrabarti had legal control over the Justice Democrats PAC while it was supporting Ocasio-Corte… https://t.co/uWe2iuPxce]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con el caso del crimen del activista Samir Flores, se va a ver, si el Fiscal General de la Nación es independiente… https://t.co/7TZiuTTUtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKnicksWall @MSGNetworks Its not like he has a bad stroke either.  If he can learn to have a consistent mid range jumper my goodness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarzhePdL saludos guapa prueba el has probado el Kale?? te lo recomiendo]]></document><document><![CDATA[2016 @presquilewine #pinotnoir from Santa Maria Valley. Happy to drink and looking forward to hosting here in… https://t.co/bu3JZ8tGyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[[Broadcast Info] All of the ways to tune in to today’s #FirestoneGP - @IndyCaronNBC coverage begins at 12:30p ET! https://t.co/PoyBmujHyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonalTDeLay To me this is what CG is all about. A return to the cool of comics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PTT4579 Sometimes they just good old prostitutes and not someone who has been coerced by sex traffickers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBOKSR_MAGA @rosedixontx I thought she was the only one who wanted to do the job there?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sj_stock @OnHypeTrain @SageMeleney At this point I’m still most concerned that he believes that the only reason a… https://t.co/TIfM3M5QF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaitlinP_Oakley @skfroude @MaryStrothers @Bryan_21_Belle @DaveThd11 @JackieGiusti @HomerFund @nyyroro How Do With… https://t.co/ztF5skgZ7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustMyStyle579 @MSNBC Maybe we’ll get Single Payer Healthcare Insurance For All!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@artfulartsyamy legacy lives on.... she wasn’t in the room.... but her lesson sequence is this easy to follow!!! My… https://t.co/QghbiCZMCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLegere We don’t your suck ass stay at the Traitor’s illegal Grifter hotel!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quality food, quality actions, and a quality life - make quality choices.   🔴🔴🔴 Rice, spinach, kale, baby tomatoes,… https://t.co/iEwFJVU5s5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsDayTB 1st question for mail bag Wednesday. If the Bucs hadn’t reached a deal with Smith, he Would have been… https://t.co/GNCLfqxE9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pastor Jordan Toolsee praising God. #maryland #baltimore #music #essex #usa #christianity #jesuschrist #holyspirit… https://t.co/PzgaXIK8o0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dad2summit @DoveMenCare It’s over already!?! We were just getting warmed up! Have a great time at #dad2summit]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Buenos días! Hoy es martes 5 de marzo 2019. Comienzo el día con una sonrisa 😁 y con mucho optimismo y paciencia en… https://t.co/CL8RZPfbrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[❄️ ❄️ ❄️ ❄️ ❄️ ❄️ ❄️ “Some say the world will end in fire, Some say in ice. From what I’ve tasted of desire I hold… https://t.co/HudHBBzp9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[The historic Mayo Hotel downtown Tulsa.....oops that last picture shows one of the missed punchlist items… https://t.co/ZcYfSoHv2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s baseball game vs. South has been postponed.  Make-up date will be announced ASAP. https://t.co/yHhmkKY3f4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warming temps mean NOW is prime time to prune many of our shrubs 🌿 and trees 🌳. Branch out as we dig into the do's… https://t.co/z0rNqswlDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[What really unites Canadians - jealousy, dislike(even contempt) of Tarawnna.]]></document><document><![CDATA[with Russia during the election, and we're still getting entertained by the ongoing attempts at obstructing justice… https://t.co/loupRPuMI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must support the people of the Fran🇫🇷 UK🇬🇧 Ger🇩🇪 who’s are protesting against the policies that the Globalist, S… https://t.co/q3mK4s7Mpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Father thy rice thy 3 boys if death may not move n d Saud leave us that in ya mud if shit this g if river if 2 twin… https://t.co/Zn5ZAJNVN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sonnystrait Oh wow! I’m flattered. Thank you! I’ll keep working hard! 💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 7:00 AM CST, 12 NW Coldwater [Kiowa Co, KS] COCORAHS reports SNOW of 3.00 INCH https://t.co/pPq2chyiUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@electricvoilet @EricCarr_TheFox @KISSopolis @genesimmons @PaulStanleyLive @tommy_thayer @ace_frehley… https://t.co/mCjZ3JvVUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeccaMarshall12 @neithskye @WalterGeorge6 @skullmonkey7735 @kenserlore96 @Lily_Bell82 @2ManyOfUs @AdvanceHumanism… https://t.co/efZz9fBeRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #IT jobs like "Principal Architect" at AT&amp;T in #Dallas, TX.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gators1205 @TalentEvaluator Nothing would make him happier than for Hornibrook to start over JB1.   He is a Michig… https://t.co/bwuhYcIdn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Arkansas student section makes one last plea as Gafford leaves the court https://t.co/EWa8Erf1wd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SHSFLAGSHIP 💪 one of our weekly traditions...Sweet Bite Fri. Take a donut &amp; talk about your wk or concerns… https://t.co/PXAk8inzok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nick_Newman Let’s meet up if you’re ever back in the city. These are so great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The controversial Instagram, posted on Roger Stone’s account on Monday, depicted a photo of Judge Amy Berman Jackso… https://t.co/l2IJ0cc5yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonMontag @ephoustonbill @JohanBBT @zappafaye @cellmavin @beerguypdx @lhtetrick @wolv54b1 @wrayzors… https://t.co/KL51faJ4ZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[What give them 2 years to kill you ,,I know how it works https://t.co/XIOQxUvZHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[End 3: St Thomas scores 2 runs. Callahan, Baker, Harmeyer due up next.  Score: Pios 1 St Thomas 5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate telling people to keep the music down especially when they got the baddies on deck 😂😂 I ain’t like this!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachLetoa @Tristles Quiero sexo contigo amor bello a love ❤ me gustas y te lo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnIcarus @TheGoodGodAbove @itsJeffTiedrich Cats are good but you can't get them to pull sleds through the Arctic]]></document></documents></author>