<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Welcome to our Theme Parks based on our Literature Circles. @ Chestnut Grove Middle School - King, NC https://t.co/MCxetFGbxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was nominated by @CoachCarrasco12 to post covers of #7books that I love: no explanations, no reviews, just covers… https://t.co/VssPoSV8P8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever just want to tell someone how you feel but you’re too afraid to bc you might lose them bc same]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattnathanson @_favaloras Gahhh Church Clothes! There is a surefire way to get me to stop requesting this song, IJ… https://t.co/HSOEa3qmQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum @washingtonpost Well. You know how it is.  They work cheap. I cannot believe this is just accepted by al… https://t.co/aTovqhnGyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to change 3 lives. Are you lost in your current fitness routine? Tired of looking like a potato? Want to be… https://t.co/c9tw3z6WjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the best talks I've seen were given in @AACR plenary sessions at the annual meetings.  This year, I'm honor… https://t.co/jQoMuO0IPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Much needed reminder for ME as well as others! #presistenceisthekey @ Parsippany, New Jersey https://t.co/1NefYrteUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TxLChat!  8CST Tonight we will be talking about #MarchBookMadness with our guests @escott818 and @Tony Keefer]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sincerely apologize for my tweets. It’s for a grade. Pay no mind to me for the next hour.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrusso880 There’s such a thing as a movie club?!!🎬😳 I must find one in my area!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second conference of the day! Started early today!! Thank you #GAatSXSW #sxsw2019 @ Palmer Events Center https://t.co/nbG4qsG7AD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got an email today from @GESquire2k17 letting me know that they are going to be serving up some #PancakesForRoger… https://t.co/LknU2Y4hI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GunnerVike @GOPGazette @MomsDemand Most people who attempt suicide do not die—unless they use a gun. Across all su… https://t.co/mtUlC7Hel1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My storage room is getting crowded. Art 2 is ready to display their Segal-esque sculptures! @olatheschools… https://t.co/4ha3GOrNJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nummymuffin @JohnCornyn You mean this horrid thing?? 😂🤣😂 https://t.co/HQHXAI2Kvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[nicoles lips are bigger than maddie’s whole existence 😳 can we all just agree that chad should forever be single… https://t.co/0EcDtD4dhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddyMakwa Thank you! I’m working like a maniac on it lol https://t.co/RbUHR2Ju6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this is me. No photoshop, no makeup and really sick. I have pneumonia and it’s not a great way to spend Spring B… https://t.co/SVnmDK50Pk]]></document><document><![CDATA[WWRD is a playlist for my ppl that had to deal with anyone that treated them like shit while they were tryna give them the world😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Georgia70190490 @HillReporter He needs a proctologist because we know he is an AH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msldyauv @LisaVanderpump Omg you met Ken and Jiggy? Wow! Lovely photos 💝💝💝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge @Liberty_Soccer2 game tonight.   BE THERE @Go_Carondelet      7PM @CIFNCS semi-finals   ⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[High key upset we didn’t have a delay could’ve used that extra sleep ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[💯disappointed in Teresa but not surprised..Danielle is brainwashing her and we witnessed it on the show. It’s sad t… https://t.co/pIZHXRNoZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbyemmertstamp @IowaWBB @GustafsonMeg10 Show them who u are in the game today  😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday baby! so happy you liked your present.🥳♥️ https://t.co/9Ou3PXrK2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[if I hear anyone complaining about how hot it is this summer imma feed them to my goat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PainterRetired @BandB_CBS @THEEdarinbrooks @WayneBrady @KatrinaKBowden @JenniferGareis @aaronDspears… https://t.co/2d4jg3RZQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter is a place where everything is taken literally but nobody knows what your really talking about cause they d… https://t.co/c9CH9RxVKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HicksonMaike I wish i had the translation so I knew what you were talking about]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TessaDare I have many times stopped reading to admire a bit of phrasing or a skillful metaphor. I have never in my… https://t.co/EgnYPag9qO]]></document><document><![CDATA[bad hair day? no, awesome hair day! #humor #lol #grin #cute https://t.co/jF58zskERT]]></document><document><![CDATA[i fuck myself up with all these naps. will my sleeping schedule ever be normal??]]></document><document><![CDATA[The end of this segment...God bless @LastWeekTonight . ♥️ Robocalls: Last Week Tonight with John Oliver (HBO)… https://t.co/N7Tvy2aayi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chylmusic 💋 Thank you So much for putting the 'LikeY-Like' on the 🎶 music of K Michael Joseph @kmichaeljoseph  ~ w… https://t.co/2vHvo01uLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Authorities say this fire may have been set intentionally. https://t.co/6OMlsOsP2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelleHGRides @bikenewyork @TransAlt We don’t need PBLs in places without cars!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Well good -hopefully the new Demoness and Demoncrats will all be together in one spot when judgemen… https://t.co/8QURuePEh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Of course he's leaving like everyone else. No employee retention policy in the Whitehouse since Donald Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mozandy @ItsMeCathi @realDonaldTrump You don’t have to be a genius to figure it out. You’re an old white man perhaps you should.😂🤣🤣😢😢😢😢👍👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you feel good about yourself.  It shines!  👼 @ Whispering Wind Readings https://t.co/BWrJ45PAqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want everyone to know i’m over the moon about @jonas back together and I can’t wait for another concert]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random acts of toddler kindness (between bouts of being miserable) ‘Thank you mama, [for] cleaning!’]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_reyes @ACEatND @padreFJ @timothytwill done some impressive post-production work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fitch loves pizza just as much as I do 🍕#pizzacat #slowmotion #mrplayful https://t.co/0JSmq5nbBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndiFouberg @SDState I do that too! It worked out well at the airport in Portland 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnbc so sorry to see #stupidjoe back on #squakbox. I was really enjoying some intelligent discussion while he was… https://t.co/tsD0cWg9zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @KatiePavlich You’re a fool Donald trump u Ann Coulter are a danger to our country and society]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HigherFurtherFasterBaby Captain Marvel tops the box office on its opening weekend  https://t.co/SYu3GyJF5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re happy af over some chocolates? Be happy when he gives you loyalty &amp; respect boo but aye that’s none of my business. 🐸☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesMcCool @lonelyplanet @VikingCruises @RickGriffin @DanaHFreeman @AdventurPro @TheHusbandInTow @FunInFairfax… https://t.co/Kl5JetID6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is not “fashion”. It looks awful.   Girl in the background is me when someone tells me to smile at work 🤣🥴 https://t.co/qvra3rGr0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I get in my car, It seems like It’s always on full! My daddy never lets me worry about things about that… https://t.co/1qS6ml1sKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can’t believe my social media followers came to my birthday party” @yogibbygibby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @journalsentinel @patrickdmarley Isaiah 6:23 “Woe to those who acquit the guilty for a bribe but d… https://t.co/E1yXpqK9e9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti The most wonderful thing about this is I have no fucking clue who R Kelly is, the better thing abo… https://t.co/iIwmHZD6MB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheChrisDuarte @MeganPTweets @salesforce @trailhead @gilliankbruce @LeahBMH I don’t blame you. But sometimes analy… https://t.co/CwRHUmc8mG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was reading an article on FB about kids YouTube vids being hacked with inappropriate content. I opened it to read… https://t.co/kjnLVBDGzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristineDBaker It's cold out that's enough reason to want to stay home and be a sloth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madbev14 @yashar Math:  2 people x 2 each per day x 5 days = 20. Not too many.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good eats and entertainment tonight at the Bethpage Chamber mixer. 🍤 #CoC #chamberofcommerce @ Campagne House https://t.co/F4LaN0o31s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ambernamaste @GRHSPTSA Why Thank you! See you there! 💚💙😊 https://t.co/On3I6HkDEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[😭so many emotions. So proud @adamlambert @QueenWillRock Love Love Love such a powerful performance @DrBrianMay @OfficialRMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[After raising a cockatiel for the last four weeks I am blown away that they exist in the wild. Aegon is the most clumsy bird ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drew_Freeman_MS  Always advocating for our babies ❤️ https://t.co/LPTzWwzjnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flushednsticky I’m so sorry. 😢 🐱 ❤️ Kendra is beautiful and I am so glad you had each other. You know she’ll never leave your heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He hath laid my vine waste, and barked my fig tree: he hath made it clean bare, and cast it away; the branches ther… https://t.co/kNWZjLvYU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[R. Kelly Charged With 10 Counts Of Aggravated Sexual Abuse In Illinois https://t.co/GuSeOXncQ9  Justice for Aaliyah… https://t.co/7LBJdg5oxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz @CNN @poppyharlow Blah blah blah https://t.co/CSJPMyeWt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursdays are meant for thirsty drinkers! Really enjoyed the “Toxic  Masculinity” (Brut IPA) by @TurtleMountain1 to… https://t.co/2ucXqto5rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have an aMEIzing Monday, everyone! @houseofcubs @tiantianpanda97 @pinkypanda0823 @Tiashan_tian @FONZNationalZoo… https://t.co/4dvjZFo7fX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit @LeahR77 Another Judge making political statements from the bench. She has Barack Obama crony writte… https://t.co/4XaDSfKeAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before......after @ Salon Zeal! @ Lutz, Florida https://t.co/s9SnSAW0Zg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me buy seat is electronic and cost a fortune, upwalker, dental bills The cost goes on.🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh no!  I truly hope he is okay. He brings lots of joy on Twitter with that wonderful laugh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sausage potato soup ✅      Bierocks ✅  Ready to stay inside! #staywarm #cozysunday #marchsnow @ Frontenac, Kansas https://t.co/E6TgnAHrmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tweeting this for my mom and her students since she does not do social media. I have never said that I didn’t c… https://t.co/rmOSiBLQ9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stir The Classroom @Dover_Academy #barrierdiscussions #equityvsequality https://t.co/EXolEjCToU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just left the gallery where my art show is being held tonight and holy hell, even with only half of us loaded in so… https://t.co/fZ8WH1zVRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonasbrothers  when y’all out sold everyone and it was the year 2019 !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Japanese propaganda posters during WWII #kelleypd https://t.co/czNAK4b1Fe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie @BulwarkOnline Pffft - one day, some day, maybe even in my lifetime, we’ll realize that old white men… https://t.co/xIHq46B5DA]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶⚡🎶 #Rollerboogie #DiscoHermes #OldSchool @ Moonlight Rollerway https://t.co/Rb8fNWQxQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two weeks till I’m with my baby and a little over three weeks till I get my next two little tattoos 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonSexsmith Are you going to the Bowie Celebration at the Danforth on Friday @RonSexsmith? (not a tribute band - a… https://t.co/bZSmFU7dPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sgayles186 @CNN @MSNBC AMEN. It’s past the point of being too much. I think it’s going to take some time for us to… https://t.co/V5kAQWbJPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I have backpack yoga mat and umbrella on this bus and i may not make it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning everybody! #riseandshine #friday #remember #be #you #enjoytheday ☕️💋 #getitdone @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/JOFCVHc9Nm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I clean my house I wanna throw a dinner party who wants to be invited]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my mom and my aunt both live in Casper, WY. It turns out they both had active shooters in or where they worked t… https://t.co/Vhq8zZGuz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am pretty sure Ressler will think twice before taking Liz's problems back to his apartment again. #TheBlacklist]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a bulldog on one of my neighbors balconies so almost anything else could happen today and I’d be like “well a… https://t.co/PjS21OEqxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me acuerdo cuando mi comida favorita a las 9 años eran los totis picosos cm salsa Valentina.]]></document><document><![CDATA[✌🏼Peace out rooty brass, hello blendy ash!💎 Transformation by Rachel • rachelwisemanhair @ Belle Sirène Salon https://t.co/Q2HMnedZ3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilygasoi is polling the audience of teachers and best practices of teachers at the #SharedVisionConference at… https://t.co/HD9Us5s4uV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KlasfeldReports Trump keeps proving to Americans he is not on our side. He continues to defend ruthless dictators.… https://t.co/unzy5skyXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I supported my local animal shelter just by walking my dog 0.80 miles using #WalkforADog app. Get the app at https://t.co/Fw8mS2N1mA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MoTCLE is this week! Come join us to talk about test automation with dev ops!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maisy had a bit of a rough start in life, but that doesn’t seem to be holding her back. The shelter gave me some to… https://t.co/zQ02zWqb5L]]></document></documents></author>