<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Stormy night in the M.I.A ☔️⚡️  Photo by @travelswithtrac   • • • #miami #stormy #night #photooftheday #wednesday @… https://t.co/6Rsk5CPS3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@t_arnpriester @joncoopertweets People who live in glass houses should not throw rocks! Some will eventually come f… https://t.co/Hyi7YHHDla]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quando tu descobre q uma pessoa te mentiu e tu n fala pra ela q descobriu, e ela continua mentindo e tu sabendo de… https://t.co/wAzcHO9MS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaneCook Haha yes I love cinnamon gum too, but next thing I know the flavors gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite resident had a stroke and god, it fucking hurts because he’s not the same guy and he’s so so so nice and sweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Adam - the game ft lil Wayne, my life - the game ft lil Wayne. 2 songs Wayne shoulda had a verse on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imatriarch I’ve been trying for over 20 years and here’s proof https://t.co/D2OSSsXR3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SilverSurfer1 #JohnBuscema  #JoeSinnott @ Museum of Pop Culture https://t.co/99l8O3KsfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asking for a friend...Does a 1970’s Ford F100 count as “farm equipment”? #farmgoals]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had my church clothes picked out early for once and we not even going 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[After twelve hours of sleep, the fever and headache broke. So, I picked up the pieces and did yesterday's workout.… https://t.co/Aq5n4W0SFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRuhle Hmmm, are as you so “shaken” up today as you were during your interviews following Smollet’s false allegati… https://t.co/2VNsVFJQ5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[all of my memories on Snapchat just randomly deleted.... there was THOUSANDS of pictures and videos in there wtf @Snapchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can’t think of anything I would get taxidermied.... Maybe my old beta fish”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4 of 7. @JMLuethge challenged me to post covers of seven books I love-- no explanations, no reviews, just the c… https://t.co/eyWXuPUmlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaPustorino @NancySimonds1 @odyssey158 @AthanasiaTrian1 @eminethe1st @TamiMa87574821 @tracybarnes2604… https://t.co/2mJIKRoqg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s tea:            )         )        )     )     (         )       )    _(___(____)____(___(__ _ \    Speed l… https://t.co/UfTQqiiw8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I’m going to brew my own coffee every morning to take to work. Co-Workers: Want to go buy coffee with us at the… https://t.co/wW6ITyuWpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex_marand -wa -wb does not give other info of the reads from the bam file, only the read name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malburford Huge honor!  The whole school voted!  Some stiff competition, too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HBCUfessions We getting rid of Tallahassee  Sincerely, Every Floridian that doesn’t live/from Tally https://t.co/GuIVUMs65b]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goracers / Get to know Kentucky’s best college basketball player. https://t.co/a4nze3BxW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBudden is on our flight to MIA! Is this a sign of a good vacation? Lol should I invite him to my baby shower?!… https://t.co/0Py4qYxp8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Looks like a bill with landmines. No one is going to be able to read 1000+ pages.… https://t.co/byR8gWbTKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[It should not be as difficult as it is to find a nice plain black coat???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello #chicago ✈️❄️ @AmericanAir #livingmybestlife #travel #seetheworld https://t.co/yoX3oiVesX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up early &amp; faithfully just to go to Chic fli a..........&amp; forgot its Sunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keeping count of tips for the month of March. Let’s see how the cage tips 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silly stoner question:  if you clean your bong, it gets you higher right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beck_katelyn Girl we saw him in Chicago and it took him a hot min to come out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liquid gold🙌🏻 it’s a must! Looove the light feel and coverage 🖤 https://t.co/4AXo8CPypB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KariLakeFox10 Girl... watch out because I may come a callin’ 😂 #JokingNotJoking]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maden_marjorie Good night Marjorie. Had a good day, thank you. Hope your day has been good too. I'm sure you'll fi… https://t.co/I4YShBcw76]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhhayyKendra @_Samantha_Lea they shouldn’t be allowed to have children in my opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to one of my favourite friends and souls on the planet!! She makes me laugh, sometimes in the most i… https://t.co/HYTt2iHN1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our team’s St. Ansgar 2019 Engineer and Design machine! Come out and see our team help a super hero save the planet… https://t.co/JN3AKm70px]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost in this place. ♥️❤️♥️ @ Lost Weekend Miami https://t.co/roh7h9R8Q1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatWalkerWX Like a bunch of drunken sailors 😁 I've cussed more at church services 😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam just called me his little gringa.. something ain’t right here 😂💀💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USArmyReserve @316thESC #USArmyReserve God bless and keep you! Thank you for your service!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to learning and sharing at NYSCATE Digital Pathways Conference today! @NYSCATE #steameducation]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see the Chicago Skyline almost every day and I still take pictures of it like I’m a tourist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Almaurias7 Jajajajaka como en la boda de la grisel pero con los llaneros viejoss jajajaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m waiting in line for the Jimmy Fallon ride at @UniversalORL and they are showing old clips of the show while we… https://t.co/70Eu0FYhoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaylaRasi LOL go us! Meanwhile the single clock in my apartment is still behind lolololol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_ast777 The more I wake today, the better I am feeling. TY David &amp; all for the prayers. ❤️❤️❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uma participação na festa da @_MarianaSartori , estava tudo ótimo ❤️ https://t.co/fUk8uiol8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans need to get totally on board with this President for this border wall funding and stay with him until i… https://t.co/tYrGDOSqmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the thing with the dome is that it's terrible but you end up working with people you would never hang out with.… https://t.co/fVliY4SP9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok i’m never getting in a car again since apparently i’m just destined for car wrecks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great choice! Congratulations, @SueFliess! Thanks for the good news, @KidLitTV_NYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve worked 14 hour shifts two days in a row with barely any sleep. Living my best life right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE LIVE LAUGH.  ONE LIFETIME TO LIVE FOR HIM!!! https://t.co/L4kZ492z7R @ Fort Worth, Texas https://t.co/Kdb9sgIcVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gothamgato @newmarkjschool @GregDavidonNY @clauirizarry @ReynaldoLeanos Thank you! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oklahoma Sky ❤️ #oklahomasky #oklahoma #pryoroklahoma #photographer #photography @ Pryor, Oklahoma https://t.co/Ehm0oso0Uq]]></document><document><![CDATA[A small date night interruption, well worth it. Amazing job, @Hidlaymania !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Majority of guys are real life pieces  of shit doesn’t matter how long you’ve known or been there for them they’ll… https://t.co/xLm3p228f1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Grateful for “Luka-Bella”... #BeautifulLight 🌫❤️💓💖💝#365DaysOfGratitude @ Colorado https://t.co/vZ7VSK1eOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mediaite The GOP will defend him right off the cliff he is falling off of. Their claim god, country, family is alm… https://t.co/6Zwu5uIEHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plenty of high fives and hugs for @T_Graham14 this morning. Thank you so much for visiting and reading to us! ”Shar… https://t.co/TuKskGNNIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mine is gold, but same difference,  lol @ MAE Be ranch quarter horses https://t.co/ESPIAG7BMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t know that my smile could get more dazzling but somehow they managed. #smile #nocavities Also I have amazin… https://t.co/AHZSET1DfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a sad day for the fashion world. As we have lost an icon today. @karllagerfeld has passed away, thank you f… https://t.co/JZnq5Szr5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I didn’t understand intoxorated but now I do and it was funny #intoxerated #intoxorated #intoxerated… https://t.co/wpvGtCwChL]]></document><document><![CDATA[And today, these 7 seniors showed out on the field! Its going to be a fun season!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tbalacerda Sim, ao menos por enquanto está pq ficou pronto faz pouco tempo. Depois esse crocante vai diminuindo, o… https://t.co/nNPlp5ATzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[How you know you’re a true @jonasbrothers fan: You were already following your favorite Jonas on Twitter before the… https://t.co/MTgaP17asF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nails by Sarah P. #salonlegacynails #salonlegacy #artisticnaildesign @artistic_nail #pointynails  Color Used Here:… https://t.co/4TncXx4256]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning so proud of my daughter going through something right now is give it all to God I’m proud of it and yo… https://t.co/cFUH2Srq9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @DonaldJTrumpJr @EpochTimes I don’t watch ether bull shit Chanel they do they the true to the people..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudyJ31830202 @ToddTPrice24 @laura24fan @chevychevelle48 @JLee418 @kross700 @Chrisracefan1 @jonesbrent570… https://t.co/NY0m3ToUqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever souls are made of, his and mine are the same. ❤️ 📷: @abundanceofaryy  #valentinesday #happiness #love… https://t.co/x4ANAcLv4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, if anyone can update me on Plonk and the Sausage Tree babies, I’ll try to check as I am able to. Thanks every… https://t.co/XDECB2wjvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[this email is just one of those things I will never forget. I want to print it out on a big blanket and wrap myself… https://t.co/NyDyMrnDFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get it weather app...there's shit happening out there. I didn't need to be notified 72 times todayyyyyyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Myself,Lana,Priceless Commodity,Ivy Love On Tap https://t.co/KH6exmqoXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ueahhh, cause only a former trump campaign speech writer who writes fiction, maintains the Pro-Tru… https://t.co/MzRQ8qJqy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamilSmith @RashidaTlaib @MarkMeadows @jsmooth995 Members of Congress aren't allowed to insult each other. That's… https://t.co/hioE2XT9JV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Time the new Hollywood “stars” check their koolaid before they buy into it. Seems Jesse ‘s was spiked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias, @BoseOfficial. Los venezolanos te amamos 💙💙💙💙 #VenezuelaAidLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[but unfortunately not always the first to take action.   In the case of last summer’s riots Saudi Arabia, to their… https://t.co/s6TDB4OJAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traceys294 It does, but is also gives you a really nice natural glow!!! Love it and it’s a stick so u just rub it… https://t.co/iV5NNrWrhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NobleEduInit A8. The teacher doesn't totally disappear from the equation. They become facilitators as students lea… https://t.co/BUtS4vrHJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings The Justice Department will never let you impeach the President. This whole  hearing is a circus again… https://t.co/ODFRhjxtfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[No podia decirle enfrente de todos que ya no somos más que compañeros 😂😂😂😂😂🧐🧐🧐🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surprised the  #CalabreseClan with their very own the Word Collector by @peterhreynolds #thirdgradeworldchangers… https://t.co/R0MlyRnWzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing our beautiful history to work today in my @NicRoseBoutique black power fist 👊🏾 t-shirt. Get one before they… https://t.co/yPaAzi1VoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let go of the past. It’s a statement you hear so frequently. But how do you unlove someone who you have loved your… https://t.co/hr3N7THhhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[greetings from Chicago!  I'm officially freezing but my dreams are coming true 💕 https://t.co/4dTA8EyEXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaSartorelli @esadah @Barb81146 @CunningSq16 @MisleaderC @strom_annette @tpcowgurl @thesaucyliberal… https://t.co/gjLxkvmrI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pixelprotectors You need to learn how to properly use quotation marks, sweetie.😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[Italian Serie A is more rigged then Colombian Soccer when Plabo Escobar was in charge🧐 #NapoliJuve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want To Throw Your Ultimate Dream Party From Party City? https://t.co/qC2TmaIxtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Velozes e Furiosos 🚘😎 em Fast &amp; Furious: Supercharged https://t.co/9Tvw2tWEIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we want a government where anyone can serve, that can address the complex issues we face, and that can more effe… https://t.co/aWYB4uj45i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ridewithvia hey, is there a limit to how many people are permitted in a standard sedan-sized vehicle? ride this mo… https://t.co/SnJsaV36Yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobIsrael71 Subscription done. Will read this afternoon. Follow back. Happy Sunday to you and your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I may hate Greta Van Fleet more than I hate Imagine Dragons. And before you come for me I don’t like Led Ze… https://t.co/h99TfydNLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dropped the cap to my eyeliner and it sounded exactly like the opening of In The Heights so that’s what I’m doing for the rest of the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have become the mom of the apartment. Supplying my girls with makeup brushes and techniques, deodorant, socks, al… https://t.co/2EXRIZxueJ]]></document></documents></author>