<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#CHARACTER is like a tree and reputation like a shadow. The shadow is what we think of it; the tree is the real thi… https://t.co/8CwBofFj2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Southside, Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/cMlzPQwFcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidhogg111 Generally supportive of your message, but this “both sides” stance is deeply misguided.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson As far as I’m concerned they McCade is a hero.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching Killing Eve and sorry to be such a prude but the murder scenes are a little too brutal for my liking!!… https://t.co/riTNcmtPPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[KISS backstage with Elton John in Los Angeles, February 23rd, 1976 https://t.co/sqhh7ixG24]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm a huge @SamsungMobileUS advocate. Recommend frequently over Apple and other Android competitors and have gotten… https://t.co/GXbmi6NCG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoBlue #BeatState (@ Toon's Bar &amp; Grill - @toonschicago in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/qTLrc2Y19v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who doesn't love a nice spokeshave. Still working on the tools page for the new website.  #maker #woodworking… https://t.co/HPCrew14oI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @Bucks are currently beating #TeamLebron 25-22. Wow.   #NBAAllStarGame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamespk For how long it seemed like that guy played for Purdue I’m surprised it wasn’t him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travis_A_Walker STREAKS STAND UP ⚡️⚡️⚡️🔨🔨@HammerHouseMMA #HAMMERHOUSE #SJCC https://t.co/S8RPHYSFsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que triste es ir en el camión oyendo una conversación ajena y tener que bajarte sin poder saber el final del chisme.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don’t need a #Handout we need politicians that are willing to #Invest in our #Futures you could end so much depr… https://t.co/2wYVgoBB2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Half_Ref None of these are going in the park...just doing some “research” and sharing some sweet food pics. This i… https://t.co/55fupKnfWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynAthletics If I can actually sit, I will be there. It might be awkward to lay down and watch a game when I am no… https://t.co/Wtmrk8bbwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adaredia &lt;$50k, for a guy who will actually play in the NHL. Most agreed that Spooner would have to be a buy-out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[just ran into cheese at cheddars good thing i’m not lactose intolerant https://t.co/8pR8Lwfzfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charly_reynolds This is such a beautiful song, and I like your music video for it as well. #ShelbysSong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nick_berman33 How many times has @AOC pulled the “I’m a woman” or “I’m a Latina” card whenever her policy has crit… https://t.co/OorzzaqJT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jon_trexler @robsmithonline @RashidaTlaib I'm right here. What did I say about Gay people?]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMAO WAKING UP TO @che1searoberts SNAPCHATTING ME WHILE SINGING EVERY WORD OF THAT NEW JONAS BROTHERS SONG THAT CAM… https://t.co/DweO2zQYtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I can think hearing her sobbing is 'Don't climb into a compound with a FUCKING JAGUAR' but idk how I even have… https://t.co/EVuPuB7JsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THESUGARDAD1 How would you like a give away to a non profit that’s tax deductible ?? Hmmm???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure they do but to fully leverage Houston and Ford right now in a trade you want to wait until your edge rushe… https://t.co/WiJjGfyAkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JannaWilkinso69 If the gun fails, she knocks u out with those bowling balls...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @PressSec GOD willing a lot of you will do years in a federal prison]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 So am I. I have to admit, it's revolutionized the way I waste time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrienneTKnight @VirginiaAOsborn @wef @MikeQuindazzi @antgrasso @Fisher85M I have no food system right now... When… https://t.co/4YDFrPvBtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSladeNow ... I have no words for you brotha. #bleu @quisxmar https://t.co/aAlFkuZ3rG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonRBond Can we keep "Shitshow"?  Wait that one's not official.   Sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Memphis on 2/28.... Reflecting.... We STILL have a LOOOONG way to go!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I honestly don’t think James is worried about his acting career. His patriotism seems to come first… https://t.co/OmlQ9s1dm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kntonchino verdad que el teclado Samsung gasta muchos recursos en Android?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, I am pro gay rights, but waddle dee is a bad guy and worse, an incompetent. What am I missing here?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HIMSS2019 2* Dia HIMMS19  Participar de um evento mundial é uma oportunidade única para qualquer profissional.   N… https://t.co/ve8KoljCgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time we had to flip it! What an epic week of sending with @juliancarr, hitting some classics and getting this… https://t.co/kjEZ74fT6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GotNoSperm @HalNiederman My lifetime, Phillies &gt; Mets and it's not close!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pine__Tar @TheRunningDawg @F3GoldenStrip @F3SwampRabbit Cheesesteak picked up the Q at PF ... severely irritated f… https://t.co/lBPC3qEKc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top IoT Trends to Rule in 2019 | IoT For All https://t.co/kUKU1MelAI via @iotforall https://t.co/LGK89KYl3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not everywhere you go or anything you do is mandatory social media content.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scosche Hi, my Rhythm (less than two years old) has stopped charging. Any recommendations?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Therealmyamoore We do not have any bonds. W do not know each other. ot relative. No past. So no you can not count on me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo fuck battlefield 4. I mean I’m gonna still play it but you know.. fuck it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[While traveling is great, there are a couple good reasons to be home: such as the #furbabies like this one 😸 https://t.co/8R9AsFAHF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another fantastic listing from Kristi Atterberry at REMAX Professional Realty.  Get with her today for your private… https://t.co/SzUR1phYA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also Giannis Antetokounmpo will be the greatest basketball player of all time]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an incredible run by the @purpleraiders @MountUnion_MBB.. Shout out to @CoachFuline and a great group of guys… https://t.co/r5dyfU1ytr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOE_JON_FINLEY https://t.co/24MmacJnHL  remember it was all the SEC's fault for the negative press at FSU. aggy y'… https://t.co/I9YXJr19dw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m actually so fucking hurt they sold out Ik ASAP mob gonna be there and CARTI OR UZI MIGHT BE THERE IM GONNA CRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re a pretty fast swinger of the club, and struggling with hitting the ball too high with your irons, try out… https://t.co/oGEzCuDzBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo, I get Khloe sounds dumb saying Jordyn broke up her family but this energy y’all are giving her is fucked up. Pl… https://t.co/LiE99J92Wo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosManuelE Por ese libro que escribió el empleado de Danilo Aristy Escuder fue sometido en miami y pidio cacao… https://t.co/hqiLAmUkh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmclymer @AOC How about no? The US is curtailing CO2 better than EU. This declaration that the world will end in 1… https://t.co/tUQXQIpWVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @MistyStrohl @BreitbartNews @JxhnBinder No illegals crossing, asylum seekers , the real reason for… https://t.co/30KvRuECqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel was really good. Like definitely one of my favorites. Plus all those 90s throwbacks. Just good fun all around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sources say @haquesman and @Notlbk are fucking shut up tmr at the meet tmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[From post beer fest on Saturday. - Drinking an Avoiding Purgatory #4 by @tiredhandsbeer at @tiredhandsbeer  — https://t.co/0kuskIGqy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dsouzaashayne @TheOfficialSBI @TRAI dear friends if you want to loan you right place here:https://t.co/I9aSXTx9GE #canada]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TooWokeButBroke Those are the most kills I’ve gotten on this game bro !]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happens to the hundreds of thousands of jobs in the aviation industry?  What happens to all of the current and… https://t.co/SGcyC1wlYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[And plus I shot a person inside the court building before everybody know me 🦁❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GusFantastico @jci0010 @tbhogs @BearlyDoug @TheGreatHogsby Man I hope you had some bread on that long shot the other day! 60/2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travisporter402 @ultimate_j2d2 @Andys_Brain @KM_621 @andrewrsorkin @andyroddick Ironically proving @AndrewSorkin c… https://t.co/skXaKYS34o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salute to Sir Charles for his common sense approach to this situation...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sour pumpkin, weird - Drinking a Ghoulschip (2018) by @allagashbrewing at @maxstaphouse  — https://t.co/CoOWV0dSj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[i found it, a karaoke book with tonetta (?!)in it https://t.co/HOE2cFwu41]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe Sorkin isn’t terrible, maybe he’s writing for teens who think that’s what adults act/talk like. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my new headshots shot by my man @KennethDolin.   #actor #headshot #actorslife #headshots #actorheadshots… https://t.co/FiYcrSc6fY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oesparza6 Prohibido perder contra la gayina, ánimo negro vamos pongan huevo que ganamos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKatieHill @HouseDemocrats Dear Rep. Hill, please make sure no more cheating by @ABC @DavidMuir @RobertIger… https://t.co/PnNIaAbxfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pink  your show tonight in Charlotte was amazing that I almost cried the whole time. You are an inspiration!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tacos are my fuvking lyfe doe 🌮🌮🌮 @ #ElBurroBoracho https://t.co/iSx97dECa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mel_the_geek @deelane @Elinor27652146 @synredae @JBanks1980 @SLCross3 @Observer2541 @tina41014747 @YeshuaLover1970… https://t.co/5eo3nlmCfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I take back what I said about Good Will Hunting being ya favorite movie. It’s definitely Beverly Hills Ninja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BikeManStream Auxiliary fuel tank without the hose and nozzle they install in the back of pickups farmers use them to refuel their tractors]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xrayer2 @TheWilliamsDuo @ReganSmith @KyleBusch I think not mentioning Petty at all, would be more of an insult.  B… https://t.co/EU2ti65mcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_MichelleLee @RealSaavedra I see what they are doing to folks in Canada and in the UK. Pretty concerning that the… https://t.co/mMCqRTvdOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevoSaintsPage @Douglas_Aldrich Happy Birthday to one of the best axe men out there. Have a great day Doug🎂🏒🎈👍🏼✌🏼🎸🎸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WY7AA @WD9EWK @k2mts He closes in 😀 It’s fun to rove and explore a new area. Adventure for young at heart adults.… https://t.co/Qbpr3yf16a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump So why are soooooo many Trumpwiches going to jail again??? Keep up the good work bot 212… https://t.co/DjEJ5eo8FF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@northernbassist @alanhe @maggieNYT Murkowski has done ZERO to improve immigration. Now she’s set to defy OUR presi… https://t.co/Ajks1D0Ife]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mario Balotelli started this game and swapped shirts with Pepe at halftime down three goals. Legendary times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaKester @LannyDavis @MichaelCohen212 Wow. Nothing is beyond possible!! There sure is a lot of shit going down these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaceyEverett @DWhitINger @MerrittForMayor Just my 2 cents: in March 2015 Sen Merritt -eyes wide open- sold out Ind… https://t.co/JLOf7ZaP95]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is important. @joerogan @Timcast @jack @vijaya #JoeRoganExperience #Twitter   https://t.co/IIJ2EcMPsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I wanted to do was catch up with a colleague at first. My mind keeps telling me "This is one of those times you… https://t.co/K5Mx9OedKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacticalIntern @907FrostieBalls @pog6ah @__nocti__ @Twitch @dizzfila @carnmode @diegosaurs_ I'm not too far behind… https://t.co/hUI7ljPryL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleasant start to this #ValentinesDay2019   Details on the forecast all morning on @KVUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brackbuster1 By the way, has there ever been a better last Saturday doubleheader than Duke-UNC, and Michigan-MSU?… https://t.co/JefOs7stmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Most definitely trump is encouraging white racist terrorists to kill Americans!! Quite apparent...… https://t.co/lVQIKfHZtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMartyFox @Tia6sc Typical democrat walks out from committing infanticide to lecture people on their morals]]></document><document><![CDATA[got funniness. #comedy #tee-hee #grin #humorous https://t.co/rThO6lPpKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Professors who give their first test AFTER the last drop day are the worst kind of people. https://t.co/iXK3KTI1is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mason_kehrer97 Lmao that’s why you gotta grind out these shows man, twitter be having spoilers 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the view from my hotel in New York... my bad at all! https://t.co/K8J2piOlu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need this car or anything similar.. 😂😂😂 need it for a skit. Pay cash money. @ Baton Rouge, Louisiana https://t.co/vGy5xFFaQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craigcampbelltv He’s just mad because his parents named him Damian. That’s short for Damian the Douche Canoe. https://t.co/wOwNIHROkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to people who are not super congested right now. If you are congested right now no shout out for you, get your shit together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puedes creer que la tienda de Apple en la 5ta avenida en Nueva York está abierta las 24 horas del día los 365 días… https://t.co/45lj0zU6tt]]></document></documents></author>