<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@StephGrisham45 @fliflisky @FLOTUS @POTUS @TheView These woman are off their rockers. Who watches them anyway. Nobody with half a brain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My babies. Celebrating our #grandson Mikey’s Birthday. Sky Zone. He is just over the moon. #celebrate#family#fun#lo… https://t.co/tBxdKGa1yx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of our @hseschools kiddos who’ve dedicated their hearts and souls to ideating what the #NickelPlateTrail coul… https://t.co/yV2a3CB5nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am with healthcare and meals on wheels!!!   I AM VEHEMENTLY AGAINST A STUPID DAMN BORDER WALL!!! Waste of taxpaye… https://t.co/PPAOq02poD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is CRITICAL now. I was working for a large "big box" store when my accident happened and I ripped myself a HUG… https://t.co/KPSAeEbqJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the kinds of stories I'm here for. @HollyHays https://t.co/X4iFdKORaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhh my gosh I’ve never used the word bae! .... soo this is what it feels like... not bad.. I like it.. hahahahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @DavidJUrban @SymoneDSanders @ahrferrier @PaulBegala @TheLeadCNN And Trump continues to incite with his… https://t.co/NIQblYzkIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our entire organization is founded on “creating simple solutions to complex problems”. -@ChrisSuarezPDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d I’ve seen the psychosis of Trump since the 80’s.  Doesn’t anyone remember SPY Magazine eviscerating Tru… https://t.co/xueZ58DkX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinZadai @kevinzadai0128 I’ve started watching these learning modules.  They are very helpful.  Thank you for creating them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If that cat moves in, I’m moving out 😤” Okay dad. https://t.co/mKpbVdVYbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Von is a German title equivalent to From..Hans is also German.  Last part of last name Ends in Sky is Russian.  Rus… https://t.co/T0RYQmjy21]]></document><document><![CDATA[We (who support teachers) HAVE to hold ourselves accountable for creating safe environments, where risk is okay, wh… https://t.co/cfQyJrEGDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[a cutie was making eyes w me on South St, he was tryna snag a last minute boo.. turns out he was canvassing for an… https://t.co/JYFM7PeglO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewmcmahon just kills it every time. I have to say, this tour concept - the set, the lights, the intro, etc. -… https://t.co/MrnphbLDBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My project for a color printer is almost down to $100.00. So exciting👏👏👏 #retweet #donate #DonorsChoose #donorsrock… https://t.co/QHizSPPx6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did not realize that Ben Franklin also pioneered the #fundraising brochure. https://t.co/InqZUAKker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrayMediaProd I do 🤷 My boyfriend and I don't celebrate it at all ahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Potrero neighborhood in San Fransisco is a touch better then the Las Vegas strip.  You can find me on top of the hi… https://t.co/8QwiomWeQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[5SOS on Family Feud: Steve: How do you cook eggs? Luke: in a microwave  Steve: https://t.co/pcBJiE3Qdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItzDyvon @meechie69rocks @yeshua_porvida @CockDestroyerz You know them by the fruit they bare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAMFASHlON Pretty cool. #Style #Fashion #TommyXZendaya Probably where @iamcardib got her inspiration to own being… https://t.co/9YGrJoiOOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[الوزير #جميل_جبق يجول على المستشفيات الحكومية في عكار  الحمد  الله اذا وزير عايش وجع الناس كل يوم و بيعرف حاجات الن… https://t.co/L2XygXCWk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlamoOnTheRise Exactly. And what about California? Miserable person, more than pathetic = trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌌Dear Dreamer,⁣ .⁣ One of the greatest gifts we come into this life with is vision--the ability to tap into the uni… https://t.co/2zhoGGuysr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy the @cased4 Conference #CASED4 Education does matter and everyone deserves an opportunity to gain an educatio… https://t.co/RTpqFjU3TM]]></document><document><![CDATA[so much happened tonight that i have no idea what tf actually happened lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Valentines Day and my first piece of candy was at 9:30pm! I feel pretty good about that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swicklepus @1Beau1969 @BwaHh @Revitalized_Dem @ricklundl @cspanwj @nytimes @katierogers Business is a competition… https://t.co/9mLBW2BSZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I think about how I used to wanna married and have my first kid by the time I was 24/25. Shit baffles me now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debg7089 @MaryJo44966098 @AuntSara4 @RyanPaevey @muttoo_sharon @lorriefencil @KathyM1214 @YouTube @TheRealStafford… https://t.co/05ZGUp0kmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VernonLamb @kdenisec @annestivers @NightBurn0381 @B52Malmet @realDonaldTrump @GOP The question is why? Why are so… https://t.co/RfqidfnisE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DaylightSavingTime stinks. I am the side of keeping my sleep. This morning was harder than ever to get up, so expr… https://t.co/8kRxAmTlym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitRECordJoe @PaulMiller1313 One of my absolute faves. Also  My Cousin Vinny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylanreed1877 Ptolemy 8th had a son with his sister, then got into a Civil War over who got to rule, so chopped up… https://t.co/MZKfE9X73R]]></document><document><![CDATA[She looks so cool in photos, but is goofy as fuck in real life. What a cat. #catsofinstagram @ Portland, Oregon https://t.co/KKioRUeUwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[She better not after how she bashed and disrespected Ateneo in her tweets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does @Jim_Jordan have such a hard time forgiving #MichaelCohen for lying?   He was perfectly fine with multiple… https://t.co/xeTNdCWo4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradheath Yep he may have done as much damage or committed as much as .005 percent as HRC! Let’s put his ass away!… https://t.co/Vu8LXQojJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blue_saphire5 So true, you are the most precious gift you can give to someone.  Choose wisely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeanieFraser @cmonbuddyreally @jbisc1701 @IlhanMN #FGM Its real and it would make me a very angry woman!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrated fine FILMmaking at the kodak Film Awards last night, honoring Adam McKay and many others for their outst… https://t.co/9l6OcaVN1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[argued that the hallmark of capitalism is the establishment of generalized markets for what he called the "fictitio… https://t.co/xBUGKTGq87]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join me at a Brokers Open House at my newest listing in Tradition.         Tues. 3/12. 11am-1pm.… https://t.co/jPd7FY9CoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love all my ladies😘  #miraclegrow  #womenwhorock  #badassery  #foodandwinewomen  #strongwomenlifteachotherup @ Asbu… https://t.co/QZswJRGk4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[May our hearts thirst for Christ, — the fountain of living water. Remember us, Lord, for we are your children.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all the soldiers in the struggle, take care of yourself. @ City Of Tarzana https://t.co/1tEiZyyoTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a parent, hockey mom and school board member I couldn’t be prouder of our school district and our student athlet… https://t.co/nzVK0lgDVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amjoyshow @MichaelSteele This is beyond party, policy, and Faustian bargains. We have a president who is destroyin… https://t.co/jpbGLBTGqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the most beautiful, passionate article I’ve read from Her Campus. I am proud of @_madisennn_ for sharing he… https://t.co/BwbmTfxhCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilesCulpepper @calstate BUT I think that coming from CSU AND working w TT faculty helps you understand the system… https://t.co/UqaowMIXyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great win by the Ducks to advance!  Praying that Sabally is ok. She looked to be in pretty bad pain. This… https://t.co/m107mr7Y2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[yeah the person i did everything with just a few months ago &amp; now we hardly even talk :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the recipient of one of these @Flipgrid shoutouts I can’t describe how awesome it made me feel! ❤️❤️🥊🥊❤️❤️… https://t.co/UT9h6edwEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re found guilty of breaking the sunshine laws costing tax payers thousands of dollars and this is your response… https://t.co/zLVZhkhSbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner @theguydf @Eden_Eats So glad you have succeeded. You bring joy  to this crazy world. I enjoy your tweets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@mitchellreports just took everyone to school on how to conduct an interview!  She and .@NicolleDWallace have elic… https://t.co/gynerOB5nX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's burst out laughing a bit. Mothers of Teens sign raising kids and animals by kpdreams on Etsy, $7.99 #mirth… https://t.co/P5G12jNCiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joann’s has a dish towel that says “Say aloe to my little friend”! 😂😂 https://t.co/2WsVDPQsvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[burst out laughing and move on. 27 Pictures That Will Change The Way You Eat Food https://t.co/H2TybsF7Th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveEarthOrDie There will be more. And we will also record videos of the class and make remote access tickets available.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fiveski I mean your birth date is one thing...but WISCONSIN?!?! Get real!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am the queen of pretending somebody never existed n was never present in my life, it don’t matter how close we were... idk you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a DDH IPA Series 7 by @tuppsbrewery @ Little Jimmy's Tiki Lounge — https://t.co/yTlZ6xt0SM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Collider I love Ray Liotta! I hope he does this. He is great at everything he does but mobsters seem to be his spe… https://t.co/cteCnkfRIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The white trash Quincy smoke 3 packs a day crackhead “Boston accent” without a doubt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow 1/2 Really? How does one decide eligibility? The Brits cleaned up their streets by sending Irish t… https://t.co/XEfXgYrpaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilianeMilne @JudgeJeanine @jsolomonReports People are out of their minds! No common sense! Our world has flipped upside down!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are a lunatic &amp; liar. There’s VIDEO, dumb ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I adore the work I do with my ELA colleagues! @oaalexandert @Mr_Evans1109 @heyjude7_judith]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quite possibly the first public school wildlife habitat and it’s in South LA at Augustus F.Hawkins High Schools for… https://t.co/ajuIuujKTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone is going to Chicago in June and wants to share a room let me know?  I am staying Friday to Sunday probably.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski They're ok, with a cup of tea. If there aren't any other cookies available. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Coaching MORE for $$$ n Lesser Time for HIM !! That's What a LIAR Does !! What COMES around Goes Around !! WATCH out !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heiamore @abogadotellez @Abogada_Alfa @SoyAbogad0 @LicIrmaSandoval @AbgDeiGratia @flatwhitedoble https://t.co/9sUIvk4ahp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DillonFrancis But what if there were two ppl at the bar next door who REALLY wanted to see ya perform tonight... true story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rowaenthe Kinda wish the zoo would sue her for endangering the animals.  Stupid is as stupid does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUPER EXCITED. I get to go to Disneyland with @Vance444 AND all the amazing musical kids. I WANT TO RIDE ALL THE RI… https://t.co/RtIkVV6t35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjrmurphy1 @1reddragon696 How is this different than every war we've fought since WWII?  We really are not the bes… https://t.co/c6JTgHkAGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwhite7097 lol.  Holy cow, I know this was a while back,  but if I had to give up coffee and vaping on the same da… https://t.co/BXbaALUDyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in a class with students who have PhDs or are at the end of successful careers and are looking to do a  second… https://t.co/RfoElMzO27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rising_serpent She can’t fake a southern accent for anything but “I”.  Southerners don’t say be-ack for back.  She… https://t.co/OsXNTb2sTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does the seating format of @SouthwestAir stress anyone else out?? I’d much rather have my assigned seat ready to go… https://t.co/EhyyHmkXUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mind blown 🤯! Pelvic floor health!! Thanks to physioworksmuskoka for enlightening us! I think we all need more info… https://t.co/W45pJYao1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevRichardColes reminds me of something Homer Simpson once said, "if Jesus had a gun, he'd be alive today."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suttonporter @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr Thank You Sutton for making it so clear]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tushytuesday Repost from andreaabeli You ripping this  or nah ? 😜 #andreaabeli #subscribe #onlyfans @ New York, Ne… https://t.co/io4om27EJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[spring break is 1 week away and i’m still broke https://t.co/mdCOWc552U]]></document><document><![CDATA[my gal is on spring break livin it up &amp; i love every second of it 🐐🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scampadversary apparently the author is a Nanking denier, what a great guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[With @BTS_twt , I feel in an odd way like I’m watching my own kids out there, living their dreams. I say a little p… https://t.co/LaU496AwpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[OU old perv Pat Robertson! I cannot stand you evangelist especially if you're Evangelical then you're even more evi… https://t.co/mUowr7gTXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyc311 #brooklyn - #LindenSt/#CentralAve - there is some kind of enormous unsecured metal structure that is outrag… https://t.co/SpoUp3EthQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We watch certain channels” probably like fox with their delusional asses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Consider it all joy, my brethren, when you encounter various trials, knowing that the testing of your faith produc… https://t.co/KpqsWTsSON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BpdPaulina Don't say that. My daughter says the same thing at times. You are here for a reason! Don't forget that!… https://t.co/WiMmJ678m3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our place looks and feels nicer with roses. 🌹  Sprinkle in nice memories. @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/oO4aenStMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QBCares RE: Quickbooks Self-Employed when will the personal spending categories avail via Labs online be available… https://t.co/2gHDbmM5Wg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mraspinall 1983 Ford EXP - 2 seater that I somehow fit 5 people with band instruments in after marching practice LOL. Manual transmission]]></document></documents></author>