<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RushJohnNabors How can the guy not keep his feet? I mean every other possession he’s falling over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllBri_ #GD giving her good dic with a 🌹Rose And I aint talking bout @DaRealAmberRose  sorry no pics..lol… https://t.co/lORqZQR5Ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now now Ben stop confusing the girl with facts she's as confused as a transgender Muslim radical , as it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solar Warden the original space force. Created by Ronald Reagan.  https://t.co/buAHdGK5wU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susans32 @BrooklynSpoke No. Not at all. They’d rather not call school off. I just think they saw a storm predicted… https://t.co/1bpEnD5nfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Absolutely agree with you POTUS WINS FOR AMERICA NOT FOR POLITICAL REASONS!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Downtown Vegas, the Mob Museum, and a little hangover recovery #lasvegas #whathappenshere #yesillhaveanother @ Down… https://t.co/L1QEeJ3hsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikesamonek And I leave many words out and make typos, yet still continue to write. That also tells you how dedicated I am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neal_cowboy @alzhurst @realDonaldTrump @alzhurst You are an idiot and a Trump sniffer]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m planning to run for Uas Congress in 2020 for the great state of TEXAS. West Texas needs an oil and gas person r… https://t.co/mKD8IR7iKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaxOfDonuts You’re too chill for me to attack anyways. 🤙🏻 https://t.co/QGOPeSrXuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Millionaire Thai fruit farmer offers six-figure payout to 'diligent man' who will marry his 26-year-old daughter |  https://t.co/o2CKOZbUUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz I can tell u one thing I hope they like u up! #Witnessintimidation]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d like to know exactly how the right wing weaponized the “attack” against Smollett.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first appearance of The Joker in #Batman No. 1, Spring 1940. It launched the career of one of the most iconic c… https://t.co/U4lCW1l5DO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Linden Hall vs. Sayre is Saturday, 6 p.m. at Conestoga Valley. #LLsports #PaGirlsHoops @GoLHLions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oliviasolon If bridge is a sport, then sitting in my hotel room thumbing through Twitter is cardio.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starofthesea007 @drahus11 @confessions_cup @TheAngelOrsini @suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy @JackConnie @hmgivingsoul… https://t.co/v4En8lnrVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarri has lost it all! Kepa refuses to come back, he’s having to be held back from his team! This is mental, holy c… https://t.co/uqCquQXum5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jelynchjr A ton of people are picking Pivetta as a breakout candidate this year 👀👀👀 https://t.co/Y1Od47Fji0]]></document><document><![CDATA[With two of the most amazing artist in the WORLD ❤️💜💙💚💛🧡🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶🤠@brittopopart @ceelogreen #blessings… https://t.co/bl1VwzXlgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Get busy living or get busy dyin.”(Red) Lets live everyday! Thanks Dierks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@otrainfans613 How about an external review of LRT1 or even better yet an external review of @OC_Transpo operations]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capsunion @JClarkNBCS @rkuestnernbc10 I’m making a lasagna... for one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por cierto, nada más twitteen... lo que les de su pinche gana!   Pa eso es el twitter pa decir y maldecir!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Ginny and Ezri... yeah um, they’re starting 😀  #gvcfoutlaws #gvcf #crossfitopen #throwdownthursday #community @… https://t.co/810Muoyfgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Photo Art Studio | Midwest in Vincennes, IN https://t.co/WSQFx3EJ9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bedevilme666 @mickelodoole @stlpcs @jhard21271185 @blessedbutch @Aug1405 @peppertrumper @MeltingInMarana… https://t.co/BVauGaUyjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter @TuckerCarlson My son is a soldier.  Thanks, @TuckerCarlson Unless their kids are doing this?… https://t.co/cMglTQUE6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kate_canadian He will stop at nothing to get re elected #cdnpoli #pnpcbc #SNCLavalin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nullthread It fascinates me that it’s now been 100 years since it was renamed University Way, and yet it’s *still* called The Ave.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely agree with him here but this is a long time conservative complaint going back to 1950s, problem is Senat… https://t.co/5UBfxney3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman Who cares what they say. 😂only the ignorant spread hate]]></document><document><![CDATA[PHOTO GALLERY Ash Wednesday at Cathedral of Saint Patrick in Norwich https://t.co/TzkuPp4I9t @NorwichBulletin… https://t.co/EH0Y3kD1q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to hear how much kulture loves “don’t lose me.” It’s gonna be so sweet 😩😩😩❤️❤️🥰🥰 #FatherOf4 @iamcardib]]></document><document><![CDATA[For my #PhysicalAnthrology friends this is interesting... thoughts?   https://t.co/s38IuvCv6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are shooting the music video for “Texas Queen” tonight and tomorrow at Rodeo Houston w/ @itsbrandibitcch &amp;… https://t.co/4jkQyzgn3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigmelsix The only person I’m worried about is that Kobe card... everything else getting locked up]]></document><document><![CDATA[305  •••• RICE and BEATS Friday March 1 1800lucky  •••••••••••••••••••••••••••••••• • E A T • D R I N K • D A N C E… https://t.co/S8DSKge0Ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Highlight Reel- Wooden Shoes boys 8th Grade State Champs- Parade/Ceremony! @unit50sports  https://t.co/XfrSkfxyjb via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487 @EMluvsPibbles… https://t.co/HLkzBBGMz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new thing at my apartment is sporadic power loss without apparent cause]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I want to particularly honor these eight women, my mother, my two grandmothers, three of my four great grandmot… https://t.co/HSmXCset7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gradam1 It won for make up. They’re STILL giving the speech #TheOscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamjondraper  I took your advice and  asked your brother  and don Tony about really  cheap lodging  in  queens but… https://t.co/cvwYVd0Uwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you still haven't watched it, Take Off. #Documentary  #filmmaking #HumanRights #bolivia @jk_rowling 🖤 https://t.co/9nJlZkpAlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga, Elton John, David Furnish, Tessa Thompson, Alfonso Cuarón, Olivia Colman, Kiki Layne and Regina King att… https://t.co/HYIat5SXpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiernamayo is one stupid ass broad...to call @POTUS racist when he has done more for blacks than this so called bl… https://t.co/qR9Sj62DaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom is slowly but surely making her way into that list of lightskin women... https://t.co/W2mPZi5Swf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally watching this. I like it. It's like Lord of the Rings Alien Nation.   Check In: Bright (2017) https://t.co/xYB9sooAfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sknthla RE: collectivist values, is it bad to respect elders, exhibit self-discipline, be polite? Or when occurrin… https://t.co/5Qu6Bsgrn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Hokies coach Buzz Williams on needing tonight's win over Georgia Tech:  "Ginormous. I thought today was as big a g… https://t.co/EpPn8hE2KT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Well you certainly didn't to shit other than to usher in massive spending, nothing on immigration, failed… https://t.co/bIH2CkHPug]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much back-and-forth and brouhaha over who’s running for president in 2020.    Please, everyone, remember: there… https://t.co/6Tdx2pJHuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh @rickmercer could you imagine a satire show with this much political power!! “ President Trump deems SNL 'unfair… https://t.co/dDOcjX3EZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never get tired of Britney’s “Toxic,” one of the great new-millennium pop records. So catchy, and the production… https://t.co/beo1knu1Tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord: thank you for blessing me with another day, thank you for my amazing wife, three beautiful kids and a fantast… https://t.co/A648Pqkubz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't get in the water, but I was arrested for the first time that day. [unlawful assembly] @catahoulasam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember...he was the king of the world...before he hit that iceberg #titanic #shipoffools]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrEarpLA @Donadeedooda I too am grateful for Obama. https://t.co/AamnlDk97L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamcbest @realDonaldTrump Just wait until the shoe's on the other foot then you guys will start crying like little bitches again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone!  While there is still some fear in writing this, I am so, so happy to report that within the… https://t.co/Mp6tJjp23M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve Jackson Games is re-releasing a bunch of boardgames from its early years. They cost a bit more than they did… https://t.co/Emjth31bgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiradactyI @_D1vy I actually agree with Ridleys placement. I think it’s a relatively light -1 for him tho and CAN be argued for even.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the single women, go follow my cousin in snap, nigga said he tryna spoil one y’all @ cru5con]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @Alyssa_Milano oh thats right she's an actress and can play all of thoes roles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuschBeer @StewartHaasRcng Cale Yarborough Ontario 1979 first Busch sponsored car to win Busch pole]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to know why @Netflix hasn't added a skip chapter option yet. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itzGodz_tv @Mondo_Montage @MagicKupoo @Twitch Bruh what?! I have to live with the past every fucking day! This cou… https://t.co/Fy0qPskERW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Offseason QB Grind Session w 2020 pryce_whitten12 of Pelion High is focused this offseason making major improvement… https://t.co/LukLO7sF8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gates_mcfadden I’ve hesitated to check it out, but I will.  I will not know how to react to what I see to be honest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My final card.   I have Castano 115-113 but could go either way. Fight was close I can see a draw.  #LaraCastano… https://t.co/YsCGl9ZTJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[People probably gonna look at me real strange for wearing shorts today but I’ve slept 6 hours in th last 2 days GOMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Torrential rain, wind and tornado warning in the morning transitions into a nice midday walk on the Arkansas River… https://t.co/IdLXAQK3t2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raising a glass 🥂to mrs_emilou . This beautiful, wonderful, intelligent, and amazing woman. Somehow I've convinced… https://t.co/O2kDivyPz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discover how amazing you are!https://t.co/BobksolfMs #awakening #spiritual #inspired]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it how people swear they think becuase they paid to get on a bus they are entitled to have 2 seats to them t… https://t.co/ctYc221oR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Siga_a_Direita inglês então sofrível. Veja minha dica pra ela: “This case can “comprometed” him. Que porra é essa?… https://t.co/vtDjnl78tX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Curry Family! @stepencurry30 @ayeshacurry your generosity will provide a special place for the Charlotte com… https://t.co/RqstEmX2Cd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like watching your beautiful baby girl all grown up and going to MORP!  AND another corsage masterpiece by… https://t.co/sOeEUp7wut]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIDEO: Three teenagers shot earlier tonight.  Conditions unknown at this time.   Buffalo police Capt. Jeffrey Rinal… https://t.co/Lkx2lttefB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel gets 4 outta 5 True Lies standees at your local Blockbuster. #CaptainMarvel https://t.co/OhWCyDFvLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living the dream, YES SIR. #DreamBig #WorkForIt #HardworkPaysOff . @ccc10k @chris_granger @ Crescent City Classic https://t.co/Vtc166ObjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsjennifield @theICcrowd Runs the full gambit. There’s an entire industry of CMS systems (you’re welcome @DSExpo)… https://t.co/ZhRiiaW1Dd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a metal guy and all... going to a hardcore show is an experience! https://t.co/SHA0s3d8OJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do dentists insist on having a conversation with you when their hands are in your mouth? Is that something they… https://t.co/pOuIFGLIYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m27731630 @BeccaMaljak @RepSwalwell Just like the hate you harbored for Obama]]></document><document><![CDATA[SEC Regular Season Champs.  From 2-16 in 2017 to 16-2 this year. 9-0 on the road in conference. Beat Kentucky. Beat… https://t.co/ar98KlodjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nprscottsimon I am not affected anymore by what he does.  @POTUS and his entire family are “stains” on this great… https://t.co/jN6Egj9zQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very interesting, I was wondering why the state of  Florida is changing so much lately]]></document><document><![CDATA[All invited to @TheGreyhoundLA #COYS #LASpurs #MyPLMorning https://t.co/z9wsjGzTzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s snowing everwhere but the east side, we only have gunshots and the Nellis and Charleston smell 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[see ya! (@ Bill and Hillary Clinton National Airport - @litairport in Little Rock, AR) https://t.co/maWTBWfZ8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think my super power is the ability to somehow open approximately 3246748383 tabs every time I open a browser.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasThighs The Perfect #texasbuns I would love to #hump one day... #bucketlist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorChrisTeis @MichaelClark_8 exactly what you expect in a girls car LOLOLOL jk kinda]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thisisimportant - Thanks @dnimish for yet another great session on advanced NSX-T design! #WWKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBC Bravo Sam Zell hot mic of the decade when Congressman Meeks comes on talking about wanting a deal with Amazon under his terms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention those of you who keep slipping and falling off the edge of the Earth: be forewarned. Ignorance of the law… https://t.co/1MFDO1BJgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a very good take. I instantly see it.   I'm just glad to have the big guy back in the story. Hori is 2 for… https://t.co/J3se9cWFVG]]></document></documents></author>