<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SadeABC @tylerperry I thought Tyler Perry was a mastermind. He talked all that junk While doing plays. And all I s… https://t.co/gnlbr5X2uM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Go to @powerlineUS .Scott Johnson a Minneapolis Atty. has been covering this for several years.  MN… https://t.co/82O94Vh0sG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @AroundTheNFL @MarcSesslerNFL @ChrisWesseling @greggrosenthal for the best breaking news drop in the hist… https://t.co/WLM7Z4bMbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish I can convince my bro to keep goin to tryouts. Bro got the talent and work ethic but afraid of failure in the tryout 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s interesting that there are those out there who think Zion shouldn’t be getting paid for what he does...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Saturday the best party in the Universe is at trackscafeny Ladies FREE before Midnight 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥 @ NY Tracks Ca… https://t.co/zGnPZKH46z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAZE_EUGENE @Tyler_Tesoriero @ze210203 @KASHMONEYJ1 @CaldyGaming No but 2016 does]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President. Please consider Medicare for all. Many are struggling.  If you want to be a hero...do this shit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nwobball That's more of a hopeful prediction than an actual number.. prolly more like 7-8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuChainz__ Second one was on a conversation about the most marginal rappers ever lol. I’m with you all the way, he… https://t.co/m63yzSCcVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwestr I’ll eat with them for free if they pick up the tab. I haven’t been to Boulevard or Yang Sing in a while.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shameless buffoon! He'd use the flag as his napkin if no one was looking!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting #45… https://t.co/SLixaV7tFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[god i love when kaleb wesson gets angry at his defender and absolutely puts him in a dumpster with a spin move]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job by Symphonic Band tonight! Awesome sound and song selection! https://t.co/C1Y6LKXKYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snoshi @IanMacAlpine @KingstonFronts @Ottawa67sHockey Hope you are correct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahh award season is complete. I can now move on from hating Bradley Cooper. Thank you all for attending my TED talk… https://t.co/gnEP0jmDCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The single greatest thing ever to come out of the Catholic blogosphere https://t.co/FxrlufQmbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Wait!,,, Do you have some kind of inside information or something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I been working this grave shift and I ain’t made ish.  I wish I could buy me a spaceship and fly.” -Kanye West]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FMLNoficial  perdió más de 700,000 votos en la reciente elección presidencial....   En 2021, perderán más de un millón.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So THAT'S how you spell that. Thank you Hans, I was wondering that for 20 years. Please take your tour to… https://t.co/hK3KcqAqmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO Yepper, smelled like horse crap from day 1 of reporting then @GMA drinking that lying sack of craps o… https://t.co/6878ZI1X7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReemBoi25 better not go nowhere we love watching K Jack TV. Come on @HoustonTexans https://t.co/ZVXXRwJbgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwdoyle @gemmapeacocke @aksocolofsky @SteveReich @AlyssaWeinberg I don’t have a piece for percussion ensemble yet.… https://t.co/TJiljsCsck]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that @Staples won’t let me print 38 PDFs as a batch order and instead I have to print them one-by-one is E… https://t.co/v51rNG96J8]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODAY! Adat Chaverim Show Sunday March 10 10A-4P. Adat is located at 6300 Independence Pkwy Plano TX 75023. $1 Sugg… https://t.co/J8q2j4SzXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[True to form #MarchComesInLikeALion lets hope it goes out like a lamb or .... #March @nbcsnl https://t.co/CDnY4Ggb2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[That 7 rings is actually dope it sounds like they let her be the thot she is]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if the Native American has taken on a team of elite lawyers to defend his reputation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are a total disgrace as President.  America is ashamed of you.  Please go back to Russia to be with your lover]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillCorbett @HitlerPuncher How can we expect people to pay to see Mockingbird on Broadway if their local community… https://t.co/hIyL5gOLjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[RF oscillator talk by Prof Pietro Andreani from Lund University. #IEEE "big chapter" San Diego https://t.co/zu83PJHesZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My plane hasn’t moved in 2 hours because one of the catering service people threw a fit and trashed all the supplie… https://t.co/anzvGInT84]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannynmoore Private prisons get paid per inmate per day, simple math.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @MalcolmNance @realDonaldTrump Just another Trump lie that “I will not cut Medicare” as he stated during campaign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[KU lost in Manhattan because they got outplayed. K-State lost in Lawrence because they got outplayed. Both losing t… https://t.co/gP0C5KdEHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jipjap74 Anytime someone uses the term “cretin”... we all know that’s not the word you wanted to use.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetalMamaLady Lmfao we were talking about the infamous toe yesterday, people should really do a mirror check befor… https://t.co/pqJyUe6KX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte https://t.co/r8h6gjjOK8 @penguins @DuqMBB @PennStateMBB @WVUhoops @OhioStateHoops @RMUMBasketball… https://t.co/TB3uEtelUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenFoater If U professional yea if u on bs no college level u got to be removed from school for a certain amoun… https://t.co/PqBp5UQ6HZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allegantair @FlyFrontier I know @allegantair is a world class screw up but in this case  @FlyFrontier took this ba… https://t.co/ry7V2waGv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is life without a flower? What is it without appreciation for this soft and fragrant beauty? Embrace the fragi… https://t.co/rpLPDCffJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Lemon Raspberry Sourbet by Froth Brewing @ Froth Brewing Co. — https://t.co/ae1Bi2vAIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repost with missmichelleluu   . . . . . #lifestyle #color #model #beautiful #beauty #styleblogger… https://t.co/kogFC4cCRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidElEstupido @Faitelson_ESPN @burrovan Faitelson ya forma parte de la nomina de @CEMEXMx y @FEMSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrBrault @shakeitoffgirl5 @taylorswift13 @taylornation13 I’ve got my fingers crossed 🤞🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[EARLY STREAM TODAY! PLAYING JUMP FORCE!!!  Starting at 3pm PST TODAY  https://t.co/DbGlIUrG6I https://t.co/E27veCLLRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[hmm. cause you’re subtweeting me, maybe it’s time to expose you. i have every right to hate you and to put addition… https://t.co/xmwnLkEHaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[All @realDonaldTrump talks about is no collusion....but nothing about conspiracy, obstruction of justice, money lau… https://t.co/0ciZQtxA35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump Weird that I don't remember him ringing up Senators McCain &amp; Reid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soro$, Super White Supremacist, &amp; Obama licked the soles of Soros boots!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kerrydpierce @NRA @AWRHawkins I really wish that we could resurrect Joe McCarthy, and show some of these Hollyrood… https://t.co/3yEOA1OXKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWS_MountHolly @GarySzatkowski Ok I will flip over the table on the deck before the winds do it for me..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Suicide_gawd @lovejfrancis Y’all telling me that if this young man and this dominant lady go the distance and make… https://t.co/PGVeLUHEcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[These UNR basketball fans are reaching to be outraged, it’s a really good twitter read. UNR fans have said way wors… https://t.co/5rZSCJwa24]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great analysis.  Seems pretty cut and dried—this was intentional and avoidable head contact.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WednesdayWisdom #TuesdayThoughts #MondayMotivation #FridayThoughts https://t.co/vU5di9mhkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can ditch dude in a heartbeat...  #HereTheyCome https://t.co/cWoVPEgFG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girlfriend is almost done with work. I’m leaving to meet her for Valentine’s Day drinks. Devils aren’t on the ra… https://t.co/UpLFlB4dwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AShakow Her comments allow me better to understand an article I would like to write a critical response to; one th… https://t.co/YPE03hMA3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gave all you comics a 12-year head start but now that I moisturize daily it’s all over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @GamsuOW and all of @ShanghaiDragons on their first win of a bright future #BreakThrough #OWL2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SethRay @stotie2hotty Now I know you’re really lying or delusional. That’s Tyler with his 4 for 4. Haven’t had We… https://t.co/yyJoF1UuZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean if @iamcardib wants a revenge f*ck I think Bruno might just be able to work that out. #pleaseme #daaammmnn #Okurrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinLarson03 Thank you for your comment Austin - and yes, I love that the church also has people that help me se… https://t.co/mbnELa4XOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My question to @mspairport ... I’ve never waited in longer security lines, this is ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aafiron nailed an Orlando fan!! Let rivalry week commence!!!! #ForgeOn 🔨 https://t.co/kPcLpdPXnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[At @ENCLAVEORD, we humanize #RiskAssessment for #entrepreneurs. Unconsciously, business #leaders will default to mo… https://t.co/0l9syd8YeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad I'm Fukn Leaving Work Early Today...Being in Management Sometime Sucks!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lowcountry1Girl @gaye_gallops @TheLastRefuge2   How can u start something that a LIER says what the hell is wrong with these people]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Read about our latest job opening here: Personal Support Worker (PSW) (RFT 1.0) -… https://t.co/fmdEyJwuQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is one whose rash words are like sword thrusts, but the tongue of the wise brings healing. (Proverbs 12:18) https://t.co/i56YEKmXHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I've said it once? I've said it a million times: Don't fuck with elephant seals. This is a simple Mirounga speci… https://t.co/oQabGQqJWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with my friend Boscoe France 👣🎶 at NAMM behind The Paul Reed Smith booth before his interview with anderton… https://t.co/PJZGnxa9G2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Training with CUZ Jonathan Freeland 🥊new gloves who dat! https://t.co/SgDMrhR5qi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encourage one person today! “And let us consider how we may spur one another on toward love and good deeds, not giv… https://t.co/oq3vnELpdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost mr.newhampshire_trucker •  •  •  •  • Oh my😍 #kwhopper  #Kenworth #W990  #kenworthtrucksof2019… https://t.co/Nm7pTEVv0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yotami_salami @aparnapkin @MsReeezy @JordyPloy @becca_oneal @halliekhaas @walterkellytv @ChaseMontavon @lrfranks… https://t.co/oUZFQ0KOZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So,  I just had a dream about me trying to escape from some big hospital or clinic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting our donuts fix on 🤤🤤🤤 #DoRiteDonuts #ChicagoEats #foodporn #donuts #food #foodie #instafood @ Do-Rite Donut… https://t.co/CDqhwhJ5dD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really do love you Lisa.. why can't I ever be someone who goes and does anything with you??... https://t.co/NXnKah2iSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Liquid Blanket IPA by @LazyDogHQ @ Lazy Dog — https://t.co/olIRvmxRMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siracusa @hotdogsladies midwestern flats. Looks like they’ve only been using the term for 100 ish years :-)… https://t.co/h3sWbZM0DK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnSpncrAdams @fsurach As a @Brewers fan, have it be known that Tyler would be the only @Cubs that I’d root for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes it just feels right going to where they love you, where they know you n where they treat you like a brother n w the utmost respect]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girl got a haircut and now she thinking she grown and I’m bout to cry in a corner. Brb https://t.co/fkrGWSiZVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[New deal, we hold on to the terrorists and Moscow takes you back Comrade @realDonaldTrump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrokerAceKid @SpencerBoyd @GruntStyleMotor @NASCAR #DropAndGiveMe20SB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer You say this almost daily. Maybe your base believes you. You think repetition will somehow seep int… https://t.co/2v4ci1f5Cb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is an updated look at projected rain across Alabama for the next seven days. Not much change in the overall th… https://t.co/tYZreg9UHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my walk on Strava. https://t.co/5FQO5zAgNP https://t.co/OQhhvhcJ1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshRatcliffe92 @Predator805 @morterenatus There’s nothing wrong with them ash please]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BloodRedReviews great meeting u on Twitter Tara and DJ, loved ur review of Slumber 2, enjoy my latest horror film… https://t.co/rOkwB9FKsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[6:30 wya? Bc I need to get back in my bed. I’m fucking exhausted and need to sleep for 48 hours straight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mind. Blown. 😮  #heathers #beautyandthebeast #theatrememes #breacurtis https://t.co/iSDEOiubm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greenspaceguy @cj_spinks @11thHour @BarbMcQuade @FrankFigliuzzi1 @kenvogel @RepKatieHill @rebeccadobrien… https://t.co/urS3WHrdPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Amway Center for Orlando Solar Bears vs. Greenville Swamp Rabbits in Orlando, FL https://t.co/aCg5zIZevn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mva_go Capturing a project where they are building a Raptor for an upcoming showcase. Flycam making it easy.  . .… https://t.co/ggyUQdR8zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lobster so fresh it still smell like the dock... 🛳🛫 And the flutes is in line like they playin some Bach... 🍾🥂 👨🏽‍🍳… https://t.co/M6xhn7mm5t]]></document></documents></author>