<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Celebrating literary diversity @Rosetheatre with author @angiecthomas https://t.co/Icp9y5n3W4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@influensterjen1 I am @gmasudie61 /Suzanne Deleon and my sister is @vahalia241_/ Valerie Clark]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko @Gr82BUs This is outrageous. Security clearance questions that the WH refuses to answer!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie this better not be no damn Hoax : you know how difficult it is for victims to come forth in these day and ag… https://t.co/c8JFQJZ982]]></document><document><![CDATA[you gotta watch this at least 10 times and focus on a diff girl each time. 😩😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like this post to sign the petition to get the UNC v DUKE game declared a university holiday @ University of North… https://t.co/XSfXArACWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s taken me an hour to get to work. Yay Dallas... como siempre, ganando!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I am digging this Congress beIN like that girl who opens her locker and mad shit falls out and then she decides… https://t.co/Wbu9ADGHc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last morning in Daytona, had to stop in the Shores and come for breakfast!!😋🥓🥂🌞 (@ The Cracked Egg Diner in Daytona… https://t.co/Aymr7ZDKNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officerdaddo Shes also quite brave, because the other one is known for his silent-but-deadly farts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew @lilyalta and @justinJprice had something up their sleeves, but had no idea it was this. Arizona's at-risk s… https://t.co/0XxMC3JE0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eebart1 @SonyBaker2 @JudicialWatch @TomFitton Keep drinking that koolaid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my goodness! @tyhenrymedium is going to read my buddy Ben Haggerty! (Macklemore) I cant wait! He was so good to… https://t.co/03OqDddydD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saoili @daniel_houck @joshua_ulrich @Hillelogram I remember reading that this was a profoundly American philosophy… https://t.co/wTVTyPyFSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richard26908235 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews @maddow then you simply did not understand… https://t.co/9KKPgjqU4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[calvinklein #MyCalvins. Campaign coming this week. Credit to @shawnmendes @ Richland Center, Wisconsin https://t.co/hQZ66Csa4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stashtea @PeelBackLabel There are only 10 GMO crops available today.  It's time for all companies to educate their… https://t.co/kxwjYzNHcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Everyone, Are we Celebrating tonight? Let’s prepare and Feel “GREAT” tomorrow so we can continue o… https://t.co/nwwLhr9wzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your answer to the question “would this have happened if he was white” is anything but “absolutely freaking not”… https://t.co/2e4hGTVRal]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of more wisdom-speaking home decor, here are some words by yours truly: coffee table books. 🙏🏼… https://t.co/PN8wfx2Ryf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewgurza @MrEugeneGrant Can I ask what the tattoo is a reference to?  I like the color shading on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and shine for #BrainStormWI2019! Well, in a couple of hours. One of the MANY reasons I love this conference -… https://t.co/bgK8hhRPHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is NOTHING more annoying than my bf playing video games like someone shut this bitch up I'm trying to live in peace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch The audacity of the Dems is getting so much more ridiculous as time goes on. Their conspiracy theori… https://t.co/tIzSp2WVFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lolitapop9 @MTA @NYCTSubway @Gothamist They did. He did. And yeah, it was.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A6: Listening to our students. Take time to take a step back and let students share what is on their minds. Communi… https://t.co/pWTDxJ9AgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ibis, alligator, anhinga, black crowned night heron, cormorant @ Palm Island Park https://t.co/xBtS5y6uDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes I am saddened for all the victims and for all the people that used to take comfort in the church. It was a… https://t.co/HCjtRYLY2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart is full and my brain is tired. I feel like that’s how it should be at the end of a @testdouble retreat. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naturallight Lite technically is a word, it’s common in the glass industry. #themoreyouknow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtobynj @aimes_sweethrt It took me until The Departed to take him seriously for the same reason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont know why im getting an IYH International Incident Vibe from this match. (Vader pinning HBK) with Corbin possib… https://t.co/w0xeotMs6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BellaAugust4 @AndStrats @HowardMortman @IlhanMN An accent like Elmer Fudd? Sounds a little like bigotry to me comi… https://t.co/Cgu9DRJNnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REobservatorio Ayer me decía (el evaluador) en una reunión informativa de trabajo en la que coincidimos, “maestra,… https://t.co/QsQwQCXbrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anton47492193 @sheri_lynn95252 @Bozesgirl66 @CheekyAussieGuy @sweet___ash @melissamorris50 @Sugarshack60… https://t.co/uXcW2M1Qcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This seems like it just might be important. Who the hell is Trump working for, not America that's for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had a dream i was at sephora and they had a whole bunch of mini samples, y'all but i'm talking mini mini, i wante… https://t.co/cfVNWcV1iJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BreakingBad  seriously?! This is it?I invested quite a bit of my time.  I am so not happy! #notsatisfied]]></document><document><![CDATA[People allowed to go back in the get personal belongings but they'll have to find another place to stay for now. Ca… https://t.co/JbfHeIIoWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LGRed @AltitudeTV You’re going to do amazing things!!! Cannot wait to watch this next step. Thanks for being such… https://t.co/LSXkVI5KWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you wait for someone to save you, you’ll be waiting for a long time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actual picture of Vincent before the army and him currently https://t.co/3wRCvKkDyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahah! Boy, no! We dont need them either! We had our own battalion shouting at the top of their lungs at Pakistan… https://t.co/rPlJknj4d3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShellyCarrPayne Always. And I’ve gotten much better at distinguishing the accents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who said Gel Manicures could never look natural!??! 👀  * Book yours today! We have a 9:30 available! *… https://t.co/Jox5YOnVmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep myself accountable by having a tribe that supports, encourages and gives me a swift kick in the butt when I need it!!  #cncting4kids]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotMyPrecedent @sherrilee7 @BryanDawsonUSA @mcspocky It is amazing to me that this is even getting talked about bu… https://t.co/LuJHot9mYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Clinton’s have been dirty since they have worked ONLY for the public.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninaturner @Rosie Ageism is discrimination. I've been a victim. Needs to stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning your phone’s camera and audio are always recording have a nice day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoibearddeUna @sunrisemvmt LOL! You have no answer! A desset is dessert! You can’t change that! The largest desser… https://t.co/IQo5mXwAqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaLuizito @rosecooleredboy @MariaEd07812623 @GuilhermeBoulos O quê é comporta-se como um petista?Ser contra bolson… https://t.co/vQrEjjSnId]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheBalladOfSteveBrody ends with the concept of #CuntKills coming full circle.  #StraightOutta1984 https://t.co/5FvOxRaGGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracymoore1013 We are appalled. People who have been here for years are rounded up people from their work in retal… https://t.co/xc0PHzmNXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slim Jims?? Gross.  Pi Kappa Phi??? Worst frat.  Closed-toed shoes?? My favorite! Dolphin noises?? Dumb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisPlanteShow @WMALDC @seanhannity @RedEyeRadioNet     Here’s something for the dysfunctional millennial in your… https://t.co/OWz3cM0lRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[DO YOU LIVE ON  DIFFERENT PLANET ?? THAT IS NOT WHAT I HAVE EXPERIENCED 🤷🏼‍♀️ FROM TRUMP'S PRESIDENCY 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATLHailState Rpi. But can’t justify putting them ahead of State now with two more losses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[he was supposed to take the key to my mom but didn’t want to so I threw it in the back of his truck and he took off… https://t.co/3amfardzWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magsbluestreaks Fathers Club Fish Fry Friday 3/08 5pm-730pm Adult $13, Sr $10, Student $8 Meal Perch/Shrimp or Com… https://t.co/lYKwx5bDEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Millionaire To Millennials: Don’t Get Stuck Renting A Home… Buy One! https://t.co/OHzvYVX1vJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko Guess trump is going out tomorrow to buy a few automatic rifles?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity I Think You Nancy, Are Out Of Your Mind!  You Are A Coward!  You Lost Control Of Your Party and Are No… https://t.co/Dezyd8vyEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acabou de publicar uma foto em Clear Water Beach https://t.co/CspgP3Ap5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I want to shop  My money conscious side: look at all the clothes you have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAlextrifier Hopefully one day I’m going to learn &amp; help as much as I can!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my energy and my wife’s energy intertwine it feels incomparable, unstoppable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ss did an amazing job with their 1st QFT. @Birney_CJUSD #birneyproud https://t.co/q6Y419tcrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[These aren't #snow flakes, they're snow pancakes. #Q13FOX #wawx https://t.co/HJE9Mh70YU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rainnwilson @sunglasshut I have never in my life felt so much pure rage as I do right now! Someone needs to pay!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker @kylieatwood @Kevinliptakcnn This man acts contrary to American interests.  He's a traitor,no doubt.… https://t.co/b04kbvcRn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fence jump AND a new GOT trailer?! It’s been a good 24 hours #TheBachelor #GameOfThones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tie game. Apollos win if D makes a stop. Curl routes open all day - Gilbert just needs a chance for a final drive #TakeAim #ORLvsSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is happening all at once and I cannot handle it. I literally haven’t been this happy in almost 6 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopeyesChicken bring back the doubloons for the free 2 piece and a biscuit!!!   Popeyes Louisiana Kitchen celebrat… https://t.co/aGZOcm0myu]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗣NEW INVENTORY available in-store &amp; Online ‼️ Sale still going on until NEXT Thursday ‼️ #LegacyBoutique… https://t.co/E6aoa5nYpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reign and Frary fans know what I’m talking about https://t.co/nqKMR5t0Nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[all of the rich people i know always say that if you dont flex your wealth, people won’t bug you. but even people w… https://t.co/JGKSygCKOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting, Klobuchar floats the idea of taxing large companies when they share user data #sxsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sometimes you want to go where everybody knows your name!”🎶 I guess it won’t be to Netflix any longer!!! 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer @yardbarker If you’re going to reinvent yourself, this is a great way of doing it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sethpalmer3 @USATODAY Have you read the book, The Circle? There was a terrible movie adaption that doesn't do it j… https://t.co/eFQTDsnXKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron_C5 @JillKassidyy @BenLewisAus @YorkshireSmash @Matthew669691 @CarsonGarrard_ @SamTanginoa @vannabardot… https://t.co/Ja52SXGznx]]></document><document><![CDATA[wise words from my husband- “if you were a republican you’d be more attractive”  me *gets mad* him- “It’s not like… https://t.co/B9bPkDoz7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[3. And most importantly, If all 5 blind dates don’t happen in the same night, do they just wash and wear the same e… https://t.co/zoglzHHddO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mes belles amies j'ai hâte de vous revoir 🌼🌼🌼🌼 #raccooncrew @scotthelman à L'Astral https://t.co/blqSqQtZtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftwardSwing @cinemaven @peterdaou Please understand. I WILL vote for Bernie if he's nominated but he positively… https://t.co/9tV9JttNUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can see you! They aren’t charging me for this are they” -my dad, who just got his first iPhone yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where me one of those lol except if eatin at 3 Am it better be eggs n rice with boss ass Asian pepper n siracha cus… https://t.co/7zITiKNf1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 4 AM AND I just realized my hater got a wig &amp; is now cloning the old me , I’m CRINGING!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@addy_pez @LivePDNation @RCSD @OfficialLivePD @Sean_C_Larkin @danabrams @TomMorrisJr1 @WomenPatrol How exciting for… https://t.co/z8dBBX4VmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ItsKenneth_ Imma put out an ad on Craigslist so I can take pics like this lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[#watch my opener for this week’s episode and #pressplay at https://t.co/U1ocKc6JnI https://t.co/PAh2Ndxo3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bike Week, Celtic Fest, gorgeous weather.... Amazing start to the weekend all around.  #Daytona #StAugustine  #Springtime]]></document><document><![CDATA[AI will just make us all dumber. SUVs for the oblivious. So you don’t forget your child in the car. 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher Your so dumb Cher ..... you keep your enemies close! You don’t fight them.. he’s playing a game that started… https://t.co/hDUuxJVtQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooh, that bounce back tho!!! Do you SEE that CURL?? That's what you get when you allow our salon to treat your hair… https://t.co/pUIpgarhLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought you guys should know I slid backwards down a hill on my commute home. #mnwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the major funders of “conservative” outlet, The Bulwark.   Also don’t forget Kristol and his wife do… https://t.co/7zSVPpFdGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I’m in my own world and my bestfriend is the only one that’s in it]]></document></documents></author>