<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics He just saying words - where is his policies, what does he stand for not against]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tmcknight12 @BarrieSharks Congrats ladies! Fantastic! Good luck at Provincials!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[MM needs to go with Steve King, JJ, DJT all of them!! Parading the young black woman was as Racist as as you can be… https://t.co/wuoaKQzPzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to add to my sad story. It’s funny that he’ll be here today and I first saw him almost exactly a year ago… https://t.co/wEIPhpeCs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakerobison1 I'm always driving around looking for movies, so if you're ever trying to find something, let me know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 What matters is that every single Dem support the nominee. And that they can draw in Independents and intelligent Republicans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolf744 @Cabrosa18 @baladonEve @fabiannirv @luisrolando12 @roxyrm2014 @HuronPais @jgamorin @bugabea @oscarsito1956… https://t.co/VWE3D0YyDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OntAutism @MacLeodLisa @AmyFeePC @janemckennapc @Effie_ONB @ParmGill @ToddSmithPC @DavidPiccini @RudyCuzzetto… https://t.co/E22n3lwL4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle No it simply strengthened my support for him. And i will never ever again vote democrat after how they have acted. Never]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericawerner Will this disapproval include one hand on a hip, a slight head tilt, and a good ole wagging of the finger?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter world, meet Tucker! Our newest family member rescued from @AWLAArlington! We love him so much already 🥰 https://t.co/qsdq9jE7ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiMaui @SecPompeo I think I you;re right I got a secret It's late so I'll tell you My daughters husband is a Iraqi… https://t.co/t9ggOzf39N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Movie Review: @BrieLarson Soars As #CaptainMarvel https://t.co/sje5MDXgMe @Disney @Marvel @MarvelStudios… https://t.co/OvqjYaJXpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big fan of the work @BenjaminDewey and @futurebird are doing out here in the trenches, RTing @hourlyFox and… https://t.co/tBilsTVR43]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m literally so excited to have a few weeks off of clinical it’s unreal 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[4,556 immigrant kids have reported being sexually assulted in government facilities.... I can’t..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when young journalists gang up on legacy media on Twitter. VIVA LA REVOLUTION]]></document><document><![CDATA[@knott_michele @Kpteach5 @jamiller158 @kelleremix @jasontes5th @mrsmelanieroy @m_simpson5 @Jarrett_Lerner @sfillner… https://t.co/gORSOMFXpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmugglersCoffee I’m watching DC Universe on it and it’s awesome. Also I just realized I had a typo in my original tweet 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[8th Grade LadyKATS compete today at Memorial Gym! https://t.co/GmrIGnDBMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love hearing people's audition songs and (even though I just laid eyes on them for the first time 5 minutes prior… https://t.co/OQpSRpmWX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the #Space community and their passion!! My feed is blowing up with #CrewDragon #SpaceX #Falcon9 #Demo1 laun… https://t.co/QslAmXqC89]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Maintenan… https://t.co/746ImNSxdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauferlaw @ChrisCuomo @CNN been doing that lately.  I stopped watching them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to win tickets to the JONAS BROTHERS Secret Show from @1027KIISFM. https://t.co/aOoTNphtMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CarnavalSinAbusoEs la mejor manera de disfrutar, porque quien lo vive es quien lo goza @WRadioColombia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter Cute ad! Better than some of the heterosexual ads that I've had to sit through. Good for you, Walmart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DC Superhero Girls Super Shorts: “#FaultyPowers”! https://t.co/zFsySPh5OT https://t.co/5Fgvt7RSCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Two Muslim Congresswomen Will Both Be Fundraising for Terror-Linked Organization https://t.co/15ZDRhNKUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t watch the Oscars because they are so artificial and on the wrong side of history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#5thgrade field trip to #DallasCowboys Stadium to view their amazing Art collection. A special thanks to Brill Garr… https://t.co/LLw7OFknbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending the morning observing Ms. Dunklin's Anatomy class. The Nervous System is so fascinating! #WhyILoveYWCPA… https://t.co/YGMRyAQJJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ZuluBall2019 @ New Orleans Ernest N. Morial Convention Center https://t.co/83mcOqja0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s important to question our true nature and what we are underneath it all. How have our past lives shape… https://t.co/AbSTIot8mJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to one of my favvv dance partners at the games!!😍 hope you’re day is as amazing as you❤️❤️… https://t.co/6KSAojLUeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start your day off right with out new breakfast menu. Enjoy #TierraClassics plus new additions Mon-sun, from 7 am t… https://t.co/F4UZEimQW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vanya is the worst character in this show, I felt sorry for her at first but now I can't stand her. #UmbrellaAcademy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glamour and femininity are not the same thing! Sometimes they’re presented that way...I’m a woman who wants to look… https://t.co/z4qZELY6Tp]]></document><document><![CDATA[tempted to post your deleted camera roll to show that even the good guys ain’t good]]></document><document><![CDATA[queria mt saber se vai ter women's march aqui em toronto mas ate agora nao achei nada :(   queria ir em todas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey New Yorkers! I’ll be doing stand-up at New York Comedy Club on Saturday, 3/23 at 5pm. Come for the political sn… https://t.co/B9GiB8kNoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t count on her to do the right thing! She’ll just end up following her pac!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrizzTalkOU Who cares. Mike Davis is doing what Mike Davis does. He’s acted like this all over the @HorizonLeague… https://t.co/Ei0yPJt4yB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniNeutral RIGHTT mckskkssk but why can i lowkey see all of these kinda being true??? i hate this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics I think he should run with a younger running mate. Or a strong female.  Either way of your left ki… https://t.co/Lm7gSYT793]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤷🏻‍♀️ #SorryNotSorry Good morning Twitter and Jeep fam 😊☕️ Happy Friday Eve.. it’s almost the weekend! I hope every… https://t.co/XXO03KMwMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely adored her acceptance speech. Cannot wait to see her play Queen Elizabeth]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Firecracker Baby loves sparklers year-round! 💥 @ Henderson, Nevada https://t.co/dlIPEWgMju]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPEACH TRUMP!@BlogChurchWork @ProudResister @Wally_Callahan @CandyisDandy100 @Wally_Callahan @old_osc… https://t.co/YYCFbjDJXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeaBlackMiami Lots of foxes in coral gables. We had a family living under the deck. They eventually moved on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatelliotmetz @KCTVDani @BradKCTV5 @EllenKCTV5 @GARYAMBLEKCTV5 Okay but only if there are snacks when I get there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_Bunnie I do it and it ages me to like 1 million 475 thousand years old. And I got some pretty silver platinum lo… https://t.co/c17vvsdEZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[We wont have a choice IF he gets the nomination. I'm concerned he's trump-lite]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to our SENIORS.  Thank you for your commitment to and competitiveness in the program. #LHSWrestling https://t.co/AT1YkZuTPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders The Madura gov. Can’t be trusted you’ll be giving him the money ! He needs to take care of his people, or get out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurieAnneMore1 Yes &amp; Amen. Every day is a Do-Over with our Good Father God, the Greatest Lover of the Universe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great ideas for generation 2 patient portals, but missing tools that help consumers proactively understand their he… https://t.co/GRR4xvLkJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei SNL is too kind about his tie. Donald does not tie well (#alwayscrooked )]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lindo gesto de hermandad lo que se vive hoy en Cúcuta #HoySomosVenezuela #VenezuelaLiveAid https://t.co/UgRADcxR41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElleEmBoogie I’m glad you made it home but yes, please never do that again! I had a lot of nights like that when I… https://t.co/KSqKJsAYVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles is all i think about when I hear this song https://t.co/7v1ixSdEQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It should be clear to people who don’t know you, too. I hear the klan is making a comeback. Maybe grab your White K… https://t.co/gmpumksJ3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CliffShep It would have been more plausible if they had told us who suffered from Donald Trump syndrome]]></document><document><![CDATA[I apologize for anything negative I ever said about Apple Music or AirPods.  Both are 100% worth the hype.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lani’s path continues. We are so proud of her commitment to her  spiritual growth. #godfirst #catholic #shehasheart… https://t.co/oI6iDk7G6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonShupe69 @RealStreamNews Is that a huge bottle of lube in his hands for prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottyWK @DallasLoveField Driving to Dallas from Fort Worth was a nightmare this morning! My car slid too. But saw… https://t.co/D2NsvdbyRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class B: Elkhorn South leads Sidney 38-27 with 5:18 left in the game. #nebpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m having so much fun organizing the screening of “The Public” in SF! It’s going to be March 10th at @GLIDEsf! I’m… https://t.co/KYDgCS6LZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlMirRey @norma22flores @AlfredoJalifeR_ @marvinicio @PerezrobJ @spinerau 🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doctor Pummels Fox Hosts Into Submission On Medicare For All https://t.co/9USNkwO8OU via @KyleKulinski | How to Deb… https://t.co/cDZzUxw8cV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tejasbornmex @Chillichilli98 @MusikMan01 @FlourishGoddess @fierymistress @thehill They never should've tried to op… https://t.co/3R8Brr5wtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muvacode Sometimes it don’t get that far, maybe just a double tap (❤️) on a compliment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody have any really good books that they can recommend to me? I’m re-reading The Giver at the moment and it’s s… https://t.co/6LJJDIx9Gs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#marksaplang since I am sick today, we will not do MC tomorrow as Tuesday doesn't fit with the acronym, "MCM" (Mult… https://t.co/izeQwQJ1PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "EVS Floor… https://t.co/qeZmpskOl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PucciaPatrizia @ElbaklySami @enriqueiglesias @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @zetakaty @janaplauen @TereOrt51687394… https://t.co/n8RFGuOoga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one that appreciates that these two tough guys still listen to their momma? ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it a coincidence that both #galentinesday2019 and #NationalCheddarDay are both being celebrated today? I think n… https://t.co/9AX5XOitWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChefTrez__ You think so? I had Pat 2-1 didn't like that crack head angle he kept taking]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida da muchas vueltas...espero que la mía pase por Asia, Europa, América, África y Oceanía 🌍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraMalorzo @ewannaC @witchofgric @A_Badassunicorn @neighlouder @moinanderson @medpepper @Miss_Lulu1… https://t.co/qeZhZjqs18]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samsBellabob Look at the lil guy Charlie. looks like he is really moving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Melissa71349052 @PrezHillary17 @Bravewriting Not ALL Jewish people support Netanyahu, or violence on Palestinians.… https://t.co/y3pqERMvMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain @BenSasse @WSJopinion What a shameful ignorant propaganda piece.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s taking me what feels like forever to get here but I’m happy , life is good 🙌🏻🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or is Hannah G’s mom Mrs Doubtfire? #TheBachelor https://t.co/HgUssnS6qU]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they should all plead the fifth. It's just another witchhunt brought to you by the dems to remove the POTUS. If… https://t.co/kj0Sh0TAOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team @MargaretJosephs !! Danielle annoys me. #RHONJ #Loveher https://t.co/5KiQ4GOgXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the way @beEverywhere supports authors. I need some @DrDarria #momhacks to survive!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally have motivation again, I’m feeling happy, I’m getting back in the college groove I’m working my butt off… https://t.co/yBuGFh7gJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[captainmarvelofficial 90's Fan Night @elcapitanthtre was MARVELous!!!!  Go see my girl Carol Danvers. I love my Cap… https://t.co/cTXoJwuION]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrafficAlert Crash on @MaineTurnpike in Ogunquit between Wells and York exits. Left lane southbound blocked… https://t.co/X2Eihf4twB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Agronomyjay @farmgirlfran Too early to say yet, but will defs let you know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post Malone on July 25th and then Kane Brown on July 26th - July is gonna be a good good month 🤙🎶 https://t.co/aKhOeRgDH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My computer applications teacher came in to class today and said, “The internets is out.” ..... The INTERNETS 💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kitteyandkat I have never had an Illenium moment and I want to do it for the first time in this hat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackSocialists Is it bad to allow humanitarian Aid into Venezuela? letting food and medicine in for people who is… https://t.co/DV8cDluaHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When u and ur boyfriend get invited to join the same honors frat and now you’re frat bros&lt;33 #goals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HRHLou Watching https://t.co/VzW3tw4NC6 Olive Kitteridge. Love @francesmcdorma7]]></document></documents></author>