<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Listo para un buen domingo Gracias a Dios por la Vida.  #Sundayfunday #unitedforthemusic #goldencimamusic… https://t.co/cpba8GLIAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well Bernie is running again so this election is already going to be a fucking disaster.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game of Thrones | Season 8 | Official Trailer (HBO) https://t.co/9YFMHGilgM via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reunited and it feels so hood... @thelifteddjs @ San Diego, California https://t.co/ponCITNH5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Idealist_Lesego Ok. Keep me in the loop of it and let me know if you have an alternative email I can send it to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnmaddening @Whatgoodcosplay @KillEFFY @ThisIsMelSantos @SoFuckinSuave @EmilyReadEVE I sure did. (And with your… https://t.co/wzF7awDf13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get this fool to keep his hat on. @ Wakandan Embassy https://t.co/rpb23r9E9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, we can pack it in early, y'all, since Lt. Col. Gordon is in command  #BMovieManiacs]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Bro imagine if we can rip dabs.... through vape pens!”- some high guy 3 years ago that is probably sitting on mill… https://t.co/TLjASDaf5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeuceGotti__ You think the lakers would have had a better season if they didnt have bron?]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Music / New Music 🎶🎶  COMING REALLY REALLY SOON 📀🤟🏾 https://t.co/73iZOmHy5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dr1LfD12vp  Of course, AOC is absolutely correct about Reagan.   One anecdotal example to demonize peo… https://t.co/LH4I9C5Gbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Trump has touted himself a dealmaker, but this week was a reminder that he has a better record of blowing up deals… https://t.co/A4MQzh5mhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arisacox Wrong. Wheres the red velvet donut and the maple bacon donut?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great company @ProdigyGame is! Everyone received cookies and all kinds of chocolate in the lunchroom https://t.co/sgzl00oxJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElvisSinosic Ben is a dominant fighter that does what he wants to do in that cage. He’s just not gonna let Robbie… https://t.co/bkZV1ettQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smallkewlhuman @moms2398 @DalaiLama I have severe forms of egoic conditioning.... A combination of narcissism and… https://t.co/CPvG3uz5m2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will not stay quiet anymore. I am tired of suffering alone. I know that there are other man out there that long f… https://t.co/5i3aDUHlXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnemyofGLaDOS That happened to me once.  Truth is, you got to  freeplay until you encounter one.  Thought it would… https://t.co/IHQWcIUw02]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CLonegeek @SammySeabreeze @MillerFF @JimCarrey I'm gonna get Showtime again so I can watch the second season of "K… https://t.co/if24u3uiZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juan Williams Goes Off The Rails https://t.co/I6EU79P29u via @  ~~~~~ Juan Williams Treatment At FOX Is Great In Co… https://t.co/VUiyaaiwyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity How was this data collected? The story says the Trump campaign provided it, which is prima facile evidence that it isn’t true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FarFarrAway You have to wonder, can it be a object that shows life, wonderful and different. Like if it was a plea… https://t.co/jeKFtAkn9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekly Photo Showcase - Mar. 4th: Devil May Cry 5 Cosplays - - - Cosplayers: @ArtemisMoonCos j2panda  - - - Photogr… https://t.co/28ndSPpN8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[#socialfam I'm super excited to share the next episode of the NLKIII Rant!!!  . Link to watch the episode is on my… https://t.co/HljVqKTRtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalesLoft @robformanATL @ATLTechVillage The penthouse! It’s beautiful!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Championship Saturday... whi wants it? #UILState https://t.co/cPLEc8ylWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow crazy #NFL day....barron, weddle, Houston, collins.....um theyd all be interesting for many teams....]]></document><document><![CDATA[...in honor of our new CARDS coach...🤔...how ‘bout Mack 4 boy...Sam (Fuehring) if a girl?🤷🏼‍♂️  Yes Fred, I know..I… https://t.co/t6cnZAq7jq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ksbw Don't post the headline like the wild animal randomly attacked her put that her dumbass hopped over the barrier like a fuckin moron]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more thought on the Apollo 11 film after having seen it: as an engineering student, it makes me incredibly prou… https://t.co/i6cdhr8UUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjwest22 @AlexFast8 @PitcherList Its normal for pitchers to be slightly below there average velos with 2 more weeks of spring training]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up until tonight my eyes were on the playoffs, after THAT, my eyes are on June....JUNE #stlblues]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA @JussieSmollett His "truth" is complete BS his story doesn't add up. Too many holes and Chicago has more camer… https://t.co/0FFJumZ0H7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to represent HPD at the @IWCEexpo and participate in a panel discussion on mobility acceleration and collab… https://t.co/7VjSllXi8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti @TuckerCarlson Desperately trying to remain relevant after your 15 minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lower Columbia answers with 3 runs in bottom 4th. Fifita and Gray RBI doubles, then Hunter a sac fly. 6-5 Douglas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Capitalism vs. Socialism https://t.co/49jYvnnbga 5 minutes, very simple... #SOSVenezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Southland basketball roundup: Pepperdine to face No. 1 Gonzaga in WCC semis: Colby Ross scored 26… https://t.co/sIUkR0rSed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayemesssam This was actually a controversy before the invention of the moving picture. It was posited that ONE fo… https://t.co/RwdyxtbArF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gt2k99 @CanuckCognizant @artobsessed4 @TitusNation Wtf, not to buy a gun. U don’t have to do anything but have mon… https://t.co/PNWkcTV43c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Breaking: @DASteveCornwell says @nyspolice trooper justified in using deadly force in shootout on Route 17.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@all_right_Miami is it just me or is Castro looking a LOT skinnier this year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Light work for these 3 young men with bright futures. All by using a bike to carve the way for other youth to follo… https://t.co/N1jgcob4Xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unbelievable evening at the Sandusky Chamber of Commerce award banquet; Sandusky Key Club, Mrs. Erin Carlson, and M… https://t.co/wYDERJYmSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ConEd has a nice little loading animation. Pleasant https://t.co/bXA5ePTOVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crownme_cute Lmaooo okay after that incredible rundown I might be able to watch it now, and you’re absolutely right about Sam L. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenondraft I knew fox was the real deal when he was single-handedly dribbling through Yates vaunted press https://t.co/KXedt9URpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Article does not answer my question. Calculation is based on pickup location to curbside delivery not door to door… https://t.co/KTcfnYpIiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% of what I post is for me God does over an abundantly more then I could ever ask for so...I know sharing is car… https://t.co/szx31GPqUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Senator Rand ..I really can’t believe your logic! #Shallow #Duplicitous As a constitutionalist U know ..a… https://t.co/ykmzo7n3Fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MPxMcConnell @ArthurAtkinson0 @Susann_G @Ghettoman15 @trishkatree @Pepperfire @suepeac @MaggieRicker @gtlem… https://t.co/MChSpzrNtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SobrevivíEl14DeFebrero Con Un Gran Cariño De Mi Bella Ídola @anettemicheltv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller @uhbroncofan   Peyton is a very common name here in Indy, for both boys and girls. Shout out to the Lege… https://t.co/sAtMtdhAQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maxine what is your net worth Americans would love to see your tax return? You also have been awful silent about th… https://t.co/vIdWETZJab]]></document><document><![CDATA[True leadership is best demonstrated in humility and service to others. That’s why it was no surprise to run into f… https://t.co/TZyNhv1U9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at New Covenat Living Church in Jackson, MI https://t.co/Qb3Cd6wZfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna start a petition to get @hector_oaks to play in LA in 2019. Stay tuned https://t.co/XisaYYXHYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[And this is why I continue to say these guys are the hardest working crew anywhere. Why aren’t you already followin… https://t.co/xdItd8unhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took me longer to write this workout than it did to complete it. 🤣 168 reps. #crossfitopen2019 #19point2 #crossfit https://t.co/YBBrR7gqUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI, I went on a little thread storm last night about the type business.   (tl;dr: there's little opportunity in… https://t.co/IChEi9RcyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mnwild @ticasino Donato. That young man from New England has been lights-out since we got him from the Bruins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The question is no longer whether there is life beyond earth. The question is: How do we find it?… https://t.co/9iRDReaXTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you kidding me @tatecathcart23 !?!?!?   So happy for you buddy, straight stones!!!!!  Bulldogs to state!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literal ayer estuve chupando desde el medio día hasta las 7pm non stop, si Jason no llegaba nunca almorzaba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halabek55 @nytimes @malicemagic Yeah? Do they have the right to own money? Can they buy a car without a husband or… https://t.co/6KOpz6a0oA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes the “tough guy” attitude of trying to rip someone apart is a VERY poor look on your character.   “These t… https://t.co/lZBYzLEoha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItzMeRushhh @Notoriousjay90 @SupStreamers All set https://t.co/PygISfF4WU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_Nice3232 @WilliamsonNFL Not sure that will happen either, but for the sake of the mock, he was available so I’ll take it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PKoppenburg @UlrikEgede @LHCbPhysics This is funny to me as sometimes I will think “oh, maybe I should write some… https://t.co/8q28c96jj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelRi72674690 Yo VOTO NO! YO VOTO NO! Y seguiré VOTANDO NO 👎! Ese sistema FASCISTA NO ES BUENO PARA NADIE! Al me… https://t.co/DTQQxJZp3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stoolpresidente Go to the Don Caesar at St. Pete Beach- Clearwater is tourist trap trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EsportsNation I’m with alot of other people here the map is far to small for vehicles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did trump visit California after the state’s most deadly fire? Honest q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@intoxicatedrev @FlyingMonkeys @DrunkPolkaroo @Paul__G__ @SudburyHomebrew @david_buist @ottawahockey… https://t.co/jwZvMkZSne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethMcKenna53 @lesbianweisz @missbriehaven I think it would be equivalent to "have my guard up" up here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne @foxnewsalert If Chapo’s assets are “blood money,” why didn’t he get death penalty. @SenTedCruz great idea… https://t.co/FpKRX1Snyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malcolm82124184 @KaseyCatal @npwlwrestling @Taeler_Hendrix Leave her alone bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early #ECACHockey QF picks ( probs will change): QU in 3, Clarkson in 2, Cornell in 3. Harvard/Dart 3 and flip a coin, probs Harv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travconaway Thanks man. You’re far too kind. I wish I was all class. Appreciate it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubbishmael @SergioJordann lmao, for real punk left five years ago.  there are diehards who know nothing about pun… https://t.co/vbWffPqSgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wandabryant @UConnNeag Like this as I can c how it helps map evidence 2 ideas that can b referenced 4 evidence-bas… https://t.co/seqW7hwuC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s fine cuz there are times i get disappointed when the clock cuts the round too, but i gotta realize my feelin… https://t.co/bpHRAthZU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meesismijnbroer Sem, One day you may see me in that town. haha! Come over and say, "Hi!" 😎👍 https://t.co/UGGdxdhXIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can’t depend on the morals, values, standards, and principles of the world, but we can depend on God’s word!… https://t.co/ao81MOr3LJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethDavisHoops No 1 defending him .You don’t defend something by going to the other extreme. Like most things the… https://t.co/KxqP0OJHn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandiceMalcolm @TrueNorthCentre #Trudeau needs to go ! https://t.co/fw26iaJU2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cpriceNFL @BostonSportsBSJ A toast to the 59th birthday of the Boston "Patriots" @ProFootballTalk @NFL_Journal… https://t.co/MZ5IhSTEUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJayapal @AOC Im sorry but who on God’s green earth is in charge of your social media. iPhone compatible wireles… https://t.co/6Ot6wvah3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eg3_praise @ahsbucsfootball @CoachGatorTKO @RecruitGeorgia You know how it gooooooes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always try new sports 🎾 @ Arrowhead Country Club https://t.co/A0Di0PAbTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dannysanders80 @stevekylerNBA I can guarantee the Spurs would trade up to get him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackspellacy @LE_Warhawks @ofallsbaseball @HurstBaseball @cfaix15 Congrats my guy 🤩🤩🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[do u ever get annoyed when u try to open the control center but then notifications have a different plan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTP_Daily with #ChuckTodd. It's not that AMERICAN PEOPLE believes the liarer Michael Cohen over a Sitting Presiden… https://t.co/lZrK2KYLsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone posts sad shit on their Snapchat story for attention can we clinically diagnose them w depression?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andyjayhawk @CitiBikeNYC @AskLyft Also I'm very much not into this price increase]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saludos perejitas de juarez cuando gusten yo recibo en casita y disponible para lo que gusten solo manden md]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pchdotcom 😎😎😎😎ATT!! I Did Not otrder I Just Entered did not Check on Any Thing Reply!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight was such a treat. I was welcomed back to the @bovinemetro with open arms and hearts! I had a blast being a… https://t.co/CxGazEUWzw]]></document></documents></author>