<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@arrowp Vou lhe contratar como meu consultor de compras hahaha. Acho que saleiro nunca comprei na Amazon, mas agora… https://t.co/Hd6QfoHLuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@salakill @susanasilvi58 @3gcry @Darivan3Victor @martuchi63 @EllaCantaloupeH @L_Boop @AlasB73 @fabiola17970087… https://t.co/i5KxZyFqIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Cohen brought the receipts!!! I hope you are brought down just like Cohen warned.  You are either… https://t.co/Ahep1sVgQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I could find a matching pair of socks in the morning it would be a miracle. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[mood when fisher men’s basbell are still undefeated in opening spring season 🏐❄️ 13-0 #falcons https://t.co/MOc9GBcdNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaysonReyes08 Do buses just naturally self-combust? But it's not terroristic?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i cant stand properly my whole ass knee gave up on me tonight. we’ll see how this bad boy works tomorrow 😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 1, 1974.. Nixon secretly becomes unindicted co-conspirator... #Watergate]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not gonna flex I got in my car and found the truck that ran 😭 where you going 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has there ever been such hype around an announcement? Like really...just TELL us and get on with it!! Smh..I'm goin… https://t.co/lBmATHmUZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[A week ago, I stopped eating meat. I’ve observed the following changes in my life:  - Lost 5 lbs 👌🏻 - My hair becam… https://t.co/h1Yo7GM3B8]]></document><document><![CDATA[😎 @AlexCapecelatro I heard you made @joshdotai magic happen @Thermador !!! So sorry I missed it!!! #designconnection #AVtweeps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I work the opening shift, I usually don’t wear makeup, so I can sleep in. But the other day before I left,… https://t.co/dRsaK5GDMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PPCLangley_ALDG @quickshotmedia @DanielTyrie @MaximeBernier Do those 'objecting' actually understand the benefits… https://t.co/6IUxAvdxVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have people next to me talking and people in front of me talking and I’m trying to do my homework]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trumpty Dumpty wanted a wall.               Trumpty Dumpty snorts Adderall.   But All the Kings Morons and all the… https://t.co/3qbPJXqAfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really proud of how much work @FranklinPBTV has put into this campaign in such a short amount of time! He has T… https://t.co/PcC08pCtRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Funny the biggest thug is in the White House, hopefully you and your family will all be in orange suits very soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 Well-Played Hands Of Cards Against Humanity @Livia Patta Patta Johnson @Rebeccah Lovely Lovely Derks @Diana...… https://t.co/OaDj4TosNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well since I don’t have kids.... So let’s just say my nephews and my family I will do almost anything to protect th… https://t.co/ETZlLnBobb]]></document><document><![CDATA[*bursts into room and begins shoveling supplies and food into a backpack*  roommate: whats wrong  me, out of breath… https://t.co/rUfBIYgs1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCohen @AlexWitt @HouseJudiciary I hope you can post the video clip, that was an interesting interview!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MandaBeavers @kaitlynpawlak The ads don’t truly represent all of what tik tok is, its much better when you just di… https://t.co/5Lv9r3c5wn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no idea that President McDaniel is the first female to serve as a community college president in Oklahoma.… https://t.co/uXZZzaw9YZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[He will repay them for their sins and destroy them for their wickedness; the LORD our God will destroy them. https://t.co/XUM1sGdgLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bummed I’m not hanging out with @RichardDreyfuss as planned at the @IUAuditorium tonight but I bet he wouldn’t have… https://t.co/4S3aWgV64f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zelaya_francis @underwood89 @LisantiSara @TrishaSamuels @virgil_maddox @kahlams @CyFairREAD180 Way to go, Knights!… https://t.co/CZNgttx4bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my forever love  Getting ready to go out We are still in love after 17 years of being together.  #truelove… https://t.co/ifRWcMGHp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Llama on the Lamb Day!  It's the four-year anniversary of llamas on the loose  https://t.co/AtIkUlHx3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹💙❤l love you forever My love Tom Cruise FOREVER FOREVER❤ https://t.co/pp3mYAlDC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerfumeFlogger @cravenknowledge I tried to unfollow her it said account not found]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s Make Sure the South African Government Steps Up For Menstrual Health https://t.co/URH1CR0fSk #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s becoming more and more apparent to me everyday that I would have been burned at the stake for witchcraft in ne… https://t.co/ifl5mW4CQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feels so good outside, not to mention the good ol AM blunt to make it even that much better 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tanning 👌💦💦  • #goodvibes #hello #tanning #bronzage #instagood #love #lifeisbeautiful #california #2019… https://t.co/pve8ODwNd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hollywood / Vine Metro Station - @metrolosangeles in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/5Xlzyq5gc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they respond to the ENTIRE paragraph and not just bits and pieces 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarceleLofton @BellfortECCHISD @SouthArea_HISD @HISDECH Felicidades chica! 🤗👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow the end of #TheOscars this year was almost as awkward as the time they announced the wrong film for Best Picture...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Name 3 economical policies that you have implemented for CA residents GO......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go, @kmmcgraw1, for being selected to participate in the @UcaCareer student choice elevator pitch competitio… https://t.co/MaWkx3DxtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarryHo63 @FamiliesLa I get paid leave and sick time. I do save it up for vacation etc.  Cannot parents save up fo… https://t.co/o597O9oVyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coripoderosa I was close to catching one once 😫 to me it was just a cool keepsake from my fave. People legit fough… https://t.co/z9dyZfWTlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefOfBcrk @kirasroth Here is where you missed the point the first time https://t.co/HpYAH4uJuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[As if my day couldn’t get any worse, my neighbor backed in to my car and then DROVE AWAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #ValentinesDay from Bella! Taken at the heart wall outside Freewheeling Craft in Ottawa's Little Italy.… https://t.co/DgEnQTqTlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This from a sheriff sworn to uphold Maryland law. OMG. #MDGA19 #ScaryMonsters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris This is the source of the those in hate crimes https://t.co/KVuiG5vcYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s an old school song titled “Where’s The Love” and TBH where is the love in America? A country that is suppos… https://t.co/mXqFjDfh3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealStafford @SelmaBlair Praying for you Selma🙏🏻.  I sympathize with you, I got a Parkinson’s diagnosis about a… https://t.co/QvayZBycmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a Capricorn and that’s why I am so sorry I forgot to tell you that I was going to be home last night   Im confu… https://t.co/qz77iV3zZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[he’s playing so poor. this isn’t my goat. MJ or Kobe had the mentality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabrielaortizl Disculpa así son las familias pero sigues siendo mi prima política fav]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hijadeNernst Verdad que se siente uno súper accomplished? Por eso me levanto a las 4:15 am. Sino luego la vida no me deja tiempo.🏋🏽‍♀️ 🏃‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not on the LeBron train but this D Wade, Wade-Mother F’in-Miami-Dade County assist is poetry in motion 🔥… https://t.co/mjNRkakfBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am TORTELLINI🍝 in love 💕 with these two gals ... and this filter. #happygalentinesday #itsaboutthepasta… https://t.co/tK2qR6p4Cw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ That's absurd,no previous convictions,no violence,wrong for stealing,5 years is a bit much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsiaTater @Littlleome @letters4trump45 @salis333 @TomExposesLibs @mymynags @Cdeeman123 @LibMAGA @SiddonsDan… https://t.co/s80qqGHLAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/d50h1fhmM9   ROTTEN TOMATOES PURGES 50,000 USER RATINGS AFTER CAPTAIN MARVEL REVIEW BOMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost paws_give_me_purpose with get_repost ・・・ HAPPY VALENTINES DAY ♥️ This beautiful girl breaks our hearts. Mim… https://t.co/slBcicCTeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I... read this too quick and I believe alcohol is really killing my brain cells bc I was so off 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day love. I hope to spend many more days with you @MendzAdrian 💕💕💕 https://t.co/wXETNd0ty3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out these 10 AR apps for your classroom—coding not required https://t.co/Ze0FwnAVVw via @eschoolnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPoversight @RepMarkMeadows BUT YOU UNETHICAL RACIST REPUBLICAN PARTY HAVE NO PROBLEM WITH YOUR PRESIDENT WITH NO… https://t.co/hak30u8xXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The annoying thing about moving is you gotta get a new plug. Lmao dm me if you live in Norfolk or va beach I need help😂🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[abe takes so long in the shower like what are u even doing?? u don’t shave and your hair is 3 inches long bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[This made me bawl my eyes out. I really miss my dad. The I still try to call his phone hoping he will answer me. Bu… https://t.co/2cgJuASdgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLiiZiKEdak1ng @Team_Travis Yes he did Warcraft and ‘Finding Steve Macqueen’ is coming out soon. He will also be in a new series.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: stop taking so many pictures and videos of your dogs, because someday you may lose them and Snapchat likes to… https://t.co/sD8f2REkuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Yes it is.  If it’s in the residence, it’s personal and he needs to pay for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAhealthforkids @schoolnurses @TxSchlNurses @NJSSNA1 @fasnchatter @INschoolnurse @NEschoolnurses @CoSchoolNurses… https://t.co/DpxBUKliH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @KevinMKruse Not to mention the guy who mailed bombs to politicians and the media. As a matter of fac… https://t.co/0toTjzDfrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirBryanForrest @JarlRuby @ItsDaniCarr @erikaishii @ChaiKovsky @BrianWFoster @Marisha_Ray @CriticalRole… https://t.co/tYwwahMmpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRHS2019 I have seen many winter carnival skits, but none like yours. The best one I’ve seen in 20 years. Congratulations]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know what monster keeps stocking the breakroom with “half-caff” coffee, but I want them to know I just brew… https://t.co/tlM39tOP8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesnorsk201 @GovEvers @WisconsinDOT If that's the case then why did penndot register over 8,000 illegally  https://t.co/NMkP9K7mDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanda_acks what is it? i use better than sex by too faced &amp; it does nothing 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherleigh73 @Lori1080 @BuckeyeCuti @DonnieWahlberg I would LOVE to find out ........Hey Dr. Wahlberg 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#povinho naniquinho viralatinha tupiniquin. Ja passou da hora de se levantar. Vai morrer formiguinhas verde amarela E VERMELHAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaunAlex87 What the hell did I just watch? Did that man urinate on the guys hair????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeToddScott @MCAdventureBlog @MonkeysVentures @kathrynanywhere @sheribdoyle @feetdotravel @Adventuringgal… https://t.co/xA16MBR9Fm]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever think about how amazing it'll be to be with a person who is exactly what you need? Like they'll fulfill yo… https://t.co/jiiopox95Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pdprints @InboxDollars @lrhannaman @InboxDollars is by FAR the best and most #innovative user friendly app/site th… https://t.co/8SQ9mNKnG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yeah they just got $19 million of cocaine.....at the port of entry....in a shipment of pineapples.]]></document><document><![CDATA[6. My sense is the ring-shaped implant specifically is linked to Satanists, or Satanic elements in Freemasonry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[of Iranian military advisers and Lebanese resistance movement Hezbollah’s fighters in Syria as a scare tactic to co… https://t.co/d9Q3gZkqMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right. He should just become Feinsteins driver and get clearance that way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaKalynda @cowboykilla666 @jonfitztv @dietotaku @Preaus @RealSaavedra @AOC I may have misunderstood your post. Th… https://t.co/uYcO7NzFxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[let me learn how to do this y’all wouldn’t be able to tell me NOTHING 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish my employees were as nice as @ChickfilA employees and had the motivation/work ethic as @KrisJenner]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up this morning ready to set this stunning purple labradorite! Plus I have the morning all to myself, my tod… https://t.co/Ki0sIlTBNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[En otra historia de #LaRosadeGuadalupe: una dompañera dice que Jesucristo se apareció en un chupon 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep here we go again😪😪 time to go through my second store closure in less than a year😫😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wore sandals cause it was hot when i left the house &amp; now it’s winter again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ Yrs ago,was Charge Nurse in NYC for seriously disabled youngsters. If I caught my employees maltreating… https://t.co/zrOTwa7nH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AggieBaseball @DoxakisJohn Once again #DoxaKKKKKKKKKKKKis for the win!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealityTvGuru99 Exactly. I'm sick of these fucking phonies. I can't stan someone who's empty and vapid. I don't st… https://t.co/d0hEV2cZ3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaejr Couldn't agree more. Keep your boobs in your shirt and comments clean if you are a professional in your daily life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drnkinmyveins it shouldn’t be sksk idk how much longer i can keep surviving that shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csmoov1 I was lit. About to tweet that 2 hour nap mid day has me looking dumb right now lol best of luck]]></document></documents></author>