<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN And you are doing what any reasonable person would do Congresswoman. You are a breath of fresh air....and… https://t.co/QYMGL5XCW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually it was Hillary Clinton who started that rumor that he wasn't born in America. Trump did what politicians d… https://t.co/eNQFOhWHhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so damn tired of all this attack attack attack on the President. You dems should start taking care of U.S. citi… https://t.co/rYoNjCOT27]]></document><document><![CDATA[4th Grade Music with Brian Patterson and the @cafurrelem falcons! SOAR! Posture exercises, diction training, and Or… https://t.co/NUgZV0T89n]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Justin.    Or you can just say another big moment for Williams. @NHLCanes]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is even happening here? #CapsProm @CAPSPROM https://t.co/79J9ewcgcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vcixnv @vBrianGraf @MyVMUG @importcarguy @al_rasheed @vGonzilla @garyvee @VMUG_CEO I agree and my other user group… https://t.co/e4AfdLBV54]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManeatGrass @KPRC2Britta @lagaviota521 @obrienmaggie17 @helen19242686 @JenniferMlott @BestEverYou @exterminadorsa5… https://t.co/JlUkbxKDNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should be very obvious for the front office. It costs an extra million dollars to essentially guarantee you do… https://t.co/MB2au4nRft]]></document><document><![CDATA[At some point you have to push past your old you to get to your new you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE They can mock u 4 not being genetically superior, 4 not training to fight from birth, 4 past jobs, 4… https://t.co/1Jg3OK8ou5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IfYouEverMeetMe I apologize for forgetting your name within the first minute. https://t.co/dgUT8XcqaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nick_cochrane6 @kyndellnickole1 I’m blessed buddy you don’t find them like this every day but when you do it’ll be… https://t.co/7JOxSx03pZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife loves me this much. Onion and leek transplants on her island. @ Iowa https://t.co/7gIAz37Rew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Xanax and herion about killed me frfr glad I'm on Klonopins and box now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do the crowd sound they’re watching the 100m butterfly? So plastic #swans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DNCLemmings @willownorkiki Reminds me of Obama and his speak before you know the facts. "Boston PD, acted stupidly… https://t.co/S9bvzHTZBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GhostOfTick @joanne48640679 @FREETOMMY8 @Lo_Gannicus @conservativeLe5 @Diaper777 @r0xie_f0x @CoachforPOTUS… https://t.co/a5aJvZW7hv]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to spot reduce body fat by @Chrisfittt - I'll keep this short and simple you CAN’T spot reduce body fat. If you… https://t.co/2CtAb2fJI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’ve injured a stone ive hospitalized a brick I’m so bad I make medicine sick “]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alumna de la UAM pierde oportunidad de estudiar en la NASA por huelga https://t.co/vXUsYGwXiP vía @El_Universal_Mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @RondaRousey @BeckyLynchWWE still runs this show https://t.co/09VHq6G5yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[And of course the obligatory foodie pic! #croquemadame #flcafe #southbeach @ FL Café https://t.co/yg6nGVobsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart hurts today... I had to let go and move on... Its a hard thing for me to do but I had to...   I will forever miss you  Postmates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clap if you believe! #magickingdom #waltdisneyworld #festivaloffantasyparade #peterpan #tinkerbell @ Walt Disney's… https://t.co/68IkBYeAWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smfehir Hoskins another loser from Wynnes GVT. Like Butts just a troublemaker looking to enrich themselves at our expense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobSchneider Big pharma? What about big government? When did you turn into a lib?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffjacobs79 @JMLudes @RadioFreeTom At least Trump did.. did Richard Bloomenthal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Time favorite player each sport  COPY...PASTE...EDIT...GO!!  NBA: Michael Jordan  NFL: Deuce McAllister NCAAF:… https://t.co/O2PIGG9RFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican state House candidate shared Clinton conspiracy theory on Facebook https://t.co/2A8x9rCuNh via @penncapitalstar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats, @DerekLindblom! Onward to the runoff! #43Ward https://t.co/i3iwIdErv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has such an awesome time seeing lp!!!!! 💚🎙💜 @ The Observatory North Park https://t.co/97dcerZgTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The co-worker that sits behind me is out today. I'm in charge of caring for her betta fish "RGB." #bettawatch #bettafish #proudfishuncle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle The 🌎 world , @IngrahamAngle , has gone bonkers . I just can’t understand it . I really don’t see ho… https://t.co/NgZ7FtJEtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: @GoMocsMBB end the regular season with a 71-50 loss to Furman. Really nothing went the Mocs way today. Now t… https://t.co/0fMiGP27op]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thinkTANKphoto He needs some thinkTANK bags for those beautiful cameras.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything that sucks is because of the damn #TimeChange https://t.co/Uphn1VoW0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone listen to this. Go get solar. California - the new energy state. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar… https://t.co/4TCTYV56uo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tre looks like a matador tonight. Giving guys a lane to the basket ... the slide is non existent too]]></document><document><![CDATA[If and when I have a viral tweet, I'll just promote this. 👇🏽  But, don't wait for that time. Listen now?  Listen to… https://t.co/imUGgeeFPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Augustine_Wetta I'm not sure - I want to read more of the "Classics" , but I dont want to dishonor God. I would ap… https://t.co/s1jSdXMSBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Apparently Chelsea can’t “handle” the sun, she looks pale and sick. Her grandchildren should take he… https://t.co/VRQQc91J7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellyinvegas will you guys be doing daily NCABB videos during first wk of tourney?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piratenation02 @F3ENC @F3ChickenWang @Chumleef3enc Chicken wang did his Thang as #TheRock stirred the sauces . Nic… https://t.co/OmLzF2LqyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Angel2Rogue You need to come to NYC and get fucked by a true ALPHA MALE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Another words they were laying all their hopes on this low life scum bag and the purpose of this he… https://t.co/ahA6C9pq9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey if you’re on grindr and you see someone in person and you want to text them “Hey I saw you at x hall” DO NOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @memphismajic (get_repost) ・・・ Only this weekend until Sunday at midnight Memphis Majic is on sale for $6.9… https://t.co/QgWUGe9BFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is in-car video from SRF3 qualifying at the COTA Super Tour last weekend. This was my quickest lap of the week… https://t.co/ZGmsIP5igM]]></document><document><![CDATA[wish there wasn’t all this justice system shit for R. Kelly. Just put the man in fucking prison he’s a disgusting person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Analysis of a Multimodal, Algorithmic Approach for the Treatment of Liver Abscess presented by resident Ryan Picken… https://t.co/X95XVs8r8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marlon and I do this thing when we yawn in front of eachother 😂😂😂😂 I wanna punch him on his throat]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 years later, an admission about that optimistic $500k Hamilton Amazon bid https://t.co/S1yzU42lGG #CityofHamilton #Hamilton #Amazon]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: The #PrinciplesFirst gatherings across the country last week were inspiring. Full recap below.  To those as… https://t.co/JD30A8T4yA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lcolvin #awesomeday at #cabrillobeach #california #gasails #starboardwindsurfing @ Cabrillo Beach https://t.co/kFxmt581c6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to receive my Official scholarship offer from Air Force ✈️⚡️ https://t.co/WBlnrt0orr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taco Bell is the fast food of the adult. Because it’s the cheapest one, least embarrssing to say you ate and it’s t… https://t.co/67ajL1jlnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliehinds children of snow : - did they look at blue Pontiac Tempest’s and see if any police had one during that… https://t.co/VoUHnc9zTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Affordable, Stat-Based Retail Strategy For Your Agency’s Clients https://t.co/n8lyKJSwac https://t.co/VEj661AEvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jocelyn's Song  Link in bio  #americana #altcountry  #music #itunes #amazonmusic #country #reverbnationartist… https://t.co/TI9A9SlGd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piZZaFOlifE666 Maybe not back in time but I think we'll be able to travel to the future at some point]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grilled cheese goodness all March Break! @ Antoine Mountain https://t.co/mTjnrLbOeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinicioSenador @nuriapiera @DaniloMedina Ese es un chismesito de patio. Que ya no tiene ningun efecto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es el primer día que sube la temperatura y no mames ya estoy harto del calor!, regrésenme mi frío 🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanBenton83 Would be great to get him but he ll be gone top 20. If...longshot here,but "if" he.lasts to 2nd round… https://t.co/wCSmMcGJ6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting this day off right!! (@ The Rustic San Antonio in San Antonio, TX w/ @funsizenancy) https://t.co/TDJP5WKV3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minnesota IIlan Omar Congresswoman says no to law outlawing child female mutilation.  Says the law is not needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbeezy2599 Those who defend the Tulo and DJL signings are the biggest kool aid drinkers of all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who's back? @HSBC seeks permission to open a branch in Depew, nearly seven years after selling off its upstat… https://t.co/dfdQEWz766]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecto1outatime @MalcolmDavidSt2 @SauterRory @real_defender @realDonaldTrump Is like telling a democrat socialist no more free stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro, I said this on a popular sneaker page and mad bozos called me a “lame” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp I guess you want to join your wife -I hear @WhiteHouse is hiring]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett He should have to spend time in jail to show others this will not be tolerated in America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bexchangewords can you put what each syndicate member gives on their card so we dont need to google a spreadsheet like last league? 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am very excited. this is the first time someone takes a picture of me with a hello kitty camera. ✌🏼 #SXSW… https://t.co/RJUmsddZxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TowbinCatherine @RNVenusiii @MahgdalenRose It's all about fake news. Its in ya schools, not on the news. Day1USA H… https://t.co/4nwhaMe5Mw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear my lips stay chapped no matter how much chapstick I put on... it’s a problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're off to GREAT PLACES! and we're at one now! #ChesterJordan Elementary is decked out as a veritable Seusstop… https://t.co/f5TQjtAW0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuahind i also thought this was bizarre. i dont think i have been a canadian "pundit" since 2014]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmykimmel Jimmy! What's best mailing address to send you my fitness book "Ageless Athletic Assasin"?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The only way to do it is to do it”. Amelia Earhart  The rehab from a back injury and subsequent respiratory infect… https://t.co/kX2yCHWSVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t think you did that 🤣🤣 she off a couple years hell #NWA #Dopeman didn’t drop till 88 🤔#GangstaRap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me tonight @SoundbarOrl with @im_johnq and @_allmyhomies for the best in soul, lo-fi and hip hop.  LADIES DRIN… https://t.co/Hu8rJVS2f7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi,  how can @IlhanMN, an anti-Semitic, anti-USA person sit on the Foreign Affairs Committee, receiving… https://t.co/CynEDWwTgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kinsellawarren No way he will call a spring election. He's got to stop the bleeding first. On the other hand he ha… https://t.co/2idbCnIeB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 defenseman goals tonight! My hockey team is better than yours I promise]]></document><document><![CDATA[BROWN PEOPLE WE DIDN`T BRING THIS DEMOCRACY INTO AMERICA\YES THE WHITE FOUNDERS\BUT WITH ALL THE HATE OVER AMERICA… https://t.co/zG6sLHQyKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DNeckel19 @MattNorlander Disagree. Gonzaga is having a historically great season. One of the best of all time. SOS is not everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ola k ace? 🤣😛👀 ¿Cómo va tu lunes? #saludando @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/CnNJenZwKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitoNolan Been on and off awful for me. Always during or before a raid too. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PokerPotato73 @Alsboringtweets @_SgtSlaughter I’m an idiot!! Yes the Cobra Clutch!! So sorry @_SgtSlaughter.  I’m… https://t.co/a6y8KfoVxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 💯#moment of the day. @bnswhat davidparkergallery #stopworthy #alwaysfrida @ New York, New York https://t.co/8BVVanswAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the result that United wanted today. The damage and the deficit that Mourinho left the club in was always going… https://t.co/Dn6HXohnTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lawyer: Jussie, the prison is full of very large, sex-starved men who have nothing to do all day but lift weights.… https://t.co/GXeEbngeQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Speqtor You sir had my respect before,  but now it has skyrocketed based on your humble opinion on whataburger.  I love that place!]]></document><document><![CDATA[☆☆Ever Average Athletic's☆☆                 Alien Athletes 🛸  Off season training week 2  #vierrahighschool… https://t.co/OSEIbHejFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC Raving isn't improved by the fact that it doesn't require notes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#embraceLove #EraseHate  #makemondayzgr8again #givethyselfahellyeah #andthatsgonnabethebottomlineoftheday… https://t.co/TRGF1VvaUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canadianborn75 @AnneWheaton If you have followed @AnneWheaton and @wilw you would know the dogs sleep in the bed s… https://t.co/kT45ExgeTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Associate AR Accountant - https://t.co/MF0D0OmJt6 #Finance #Coppell, TX]]></document></documents></author>