<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[See Your Matthew And Stephen And Raise It A Tina And Shan-Lyn https://t.co/JLFg9Uqgq3 #retail #retailtechnology #femalefounders #shoptalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco is beautiful ✈️ #SanFrancisco #twitch #travel #streamer https://t.co/jrQb5LSFsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hola buen Martes! @RadioDisneyMX #RDMty Me Pueden complacer con "Deberías Estar Aquí " de @RioRomamx Poorfavor!!🙏😍 MUCHAS GRACIAS #OaMty 🙌❤😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessesingal Omission of fire damage from nuclear weapon calculations. See Whole World on Fire: Organizations, Know… https://t.co/v4KEnX0aCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drjaclynharris The “low” nephrotoxicity of silver in the urinary tract has been confirmed in experimental studies… https://t.co/grxD8zF1Tp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time at @ParkviewFB. Saw a very talented group of prospects in the 20, 21 and 22 classes. Even got to drive G… https://t.co/h205chejS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djboothEIC This song is available on @audiomack right now   https://t.co/8Xj1NETP9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaMimik Quite. It's rainy and chilly (also still Winter) where Iive, so no pretty nature walks for me today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guatemayabyesi All but 3 Senate Democrats voted to kill the Born-Alive Abortion  Survivors Protection Act - which… https://t.co/uA5vJfyt8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a beautiful week to be at MacDill AFB now it’s time to enjoy #SaturdayMorning and head to the beach for s… https://t.co/UAHUwLVw6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5 we are currently working on finishing a picture e-book of landscape photos we took of the school. Once we have c… https://t.co/gp7BEJtxvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's hilarity. Yes!!! That always makes me laugh....but sometimes I do it too....escpecailly when my coach is… https://t.co/SdanoEC0aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrantFlanders @barrybrown05 @deanwade3232 @KellisRobinett @Matthew_D_Hall @Matthew_D_Hall why you so swole!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lee Snodgrass is running for Second Vice Chair of the Democratic Party of Wisconsin. She's amazing. Ran a killer ra… https://t.co/pra8LbNnqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP King King Buddy. One of the all time funniest heels ever! @DocDonnieH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say this as someone who has received feedback that I spoke too much or too often in a meeting. I try very hard to… https://t.co/ro00CEzk6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pgonz12 Good luck this season my brother and have a great spring practice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lawprofblawg AND IT GLOSSED OVER THE ADMINISTRATIVE STATE AND EXECUTIVE POWER IN WAYS THAT STILL MAKE ME RAGE!!! https://t.co/YxyZkSlSXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Etch_a_Fletch I have an overnight softball tourney starting at midnight and I’m ready for bed right now😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommykrattiger Jets, raiders, lions. No where AB prefers. Steelers have done it to mike wallace and santonio Holme… https://t.co/Eg38G3FvSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beauty of @bigten basketball is every road game means walking into a challenging home court advantage even last pla… https://t.co/lgaYOfLtkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Sieze cnn shaw media open jfk files it saves you 2 million illegal jfk families employees]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson Exactly what I've been saying for years now. To separate blacks specifically is basically saying that… https://t.co/T0izZ2K93I]]></document><document><![CDATA[We nearly won the league again , we nearly won the league again and now your gonna believe us and now your gonna believe us  🤭😂 MUFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bermudaman442 @SenSchumer @SpeakerPelosi You must be blind deaf or stupid or all 3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how many people look at posts and are like , "God, I hate that guy.."]]></document><document><![CDATA[GBK: Hiland starters checking out with the game all but over here late #LoganRegional #TDR https://t.co/0pkUpGxcxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP The liberal elite are mocking black people. How can it be anymore obvious?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new anonymous @Twitch Bit donations are adorable. Can someone please make them into Gifs so I can use them for on-screen notifications!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brie Larson probably grew up dreaming that one day she would be cool enough to sing karaoke in a car with Samuel L.… https://t.co/9zo0f6t6il]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like when people sub tweet because it just shows how much of a child they really are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered for a chance to have @Go963MN pay for my rent, groceries, gas and concerts for the rest of the year!… https://t.co/4nOd3SU5W3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Alejandro_Suar Lol that’s what’s supposed to happen when a code 9 is called... welcome to baptist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday Soccer Club moving indoors because of the rain was the highlight of my week. Never doubt the power of positi… https://t.co/jxYEaExAjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michiokaku why can a quarterback throw to a running receiver with accuracy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichDevitaIII @tradestreetpost @BaconDwayne1000 @Devonte4Graham @hornets Eh, there’s been plenty of guys that do t… https://t.co/SvS0ZqhTJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MileHighCape @jordangeli @AltitudeSR ...Tuning📻 in once I get my 2for1 deal!⚽ https://t.co/ZSV71ShGTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SagaLudziLodu Moja mi kiedyś taki numer wycięła po deszczu w lesie. Gdy byliśmy jakieś 20 km od domu :-) ujmę to t… https://t.co/LP5cExuWNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller @Eddieonfox @uhbroncofan @raider_rob24 _You’d like Patrick’s Guys!? Maybe your guys would like Patrick!… https://t.co/3PaovbE2aH]]></document><document><![CDATA[As always follow for #Syracuse game pics/videos HERE https://t.co/GzZbwJ1tPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @trumps_feed @Jim_Jordan @FoxNews Gym Jordan. LOL what a hack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katriana74 Then again, they just might popularize Paganism. https://t.co/swb9SyyyaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tributes paid to John Candy on the 25th anniversary of his death  https://t.co/69fy39rZLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amazon why can’t you ship me Philips Hue Lights? Tried multiple different addresses/ cities in California. All shown as Prime eligible. 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[And to think, they actually went out of their way to move there, and create a cluster. :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear, if you steal my idea to restart Buzzkill with @DaveSheridan and don't loop me in in plain sight...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KerryWa39459959 Almost left the Navy when we stopped over 20years ago. Abraham Lincoln went through Sidney on our… https://t.co/XQSZVxnsh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@minor946 @NickBoles @EUflagmafia The EU has taken away our rights and abilities of being an independent country, i… https://t.co/sHQqIp5DeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stowspike making the trip to Akron to lead the cheering section for @SMFSports at Ellet. Good to see him (or her). #RCNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's gonna be a bright (bright), bright (bright) Sun-Shiny day @BristolMountain https://t.co/0OVFCrstAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buccigross Can we get another hot take on the passion of #isles fans @LeafsMaz20]]></document><document><![CDATA[KW to Page and Backlink to Page analysis is very limited. You need to do BETTER competitive auditing! @TopHatArsen #Pubcon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little newborn sesh from a couple weeks ago. This little guy was only a few days old with already a dashing smile 🖤… https://t.co/Wqei96GLgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now, this is a story all about how My life got flipped-turned upside down And I'd like to take a minute Just sit ri… https://t.co/5hOK1PJpgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @smokemrainey You know our leadership is really bad when the Taliban, the Syrians and Kim Jong Un all w… https://t.co/o4669Q8uPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarbjeetjohal @APGuha @McKinsey @dhinchcliffe @rwang0 @nigewillson @schmarzo @mvollmer1 @waynesadin… https://t.co/DHBiwcsoVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today on #InternationalWomenDay I’d like to recognize the amazing women in this profession. Specifically… https://t.co/JJweogxxy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisisqlaw @Biisi96 @tipe2009 @Alex_Houseof308 @OlaTheOG @DaddyTheBoy @_tenthtop @chemicalbrodar @iamvictor__… https://t.co/l5Wsf6BbXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing better than baseball on a RARE sunny day here in Georgia. https://t.co/jrXwk2hc6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 52 years, Lordstown must face life after GM - CNN Video ⁦@WarrenBuffett⁩ Pops, isn’t there something The Orac… https://t.co/mfn65bYRoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump as well as your hero Obama and every other president. The lgbt community with the help of the media will cond… https://t.co/yWce6s2PmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alexpad @RobertJohnDavi @jjauthor Guess what color Crispus Attucks was. 1st to die in a revolution. Not on the new… https://t.co/yALcQd6Uh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a wild guess who I had in the studio for the first time? Such a fun group. Had me laughing the whole time! . .… https://t.co/5iU8UXOVYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, @netflix, more seasons/series with eight 25-minute episodes, please! The hour-long shows make me sweepy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VGK_702 You don't want to see them in any round, as they found out last season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zoevaldes She is pouring it into a glass as you can the glass in the lower right corner...and even if she is drink… https://t.co/7b0NZYklR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trboxing @MrRickyEllis27 @amirkingkhan @Tyson_Fury Your chin. https://t.co/knqDBPcica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkbjournalist DST is an antiquated idea that is no longer need, it does NOT give you more sunshine. It just moves… https://t.co/rAtmopLzKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwistedOne96 @rogueranger23 @Randal68052371 @donjone38970700 @RickLRobbins @unctarheels5633 @James44306277… https://t.co/Z6QTZw9jzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tony Two Times.  “We called him that because he said everything twice.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awlasky @AuthorMBTosi @AuthorEllie @PletchaPJWebb @MJLaBeff @deann_native @DianeShute @birdwriter7 @Ajmarkstahler… https://t.co/t4QRfxDYcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren Christopher Lacy, a software engineer who lives in a rural trailer and  apparently sympathizes with the… https://t.co/p6hyW2RSnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeTomlinFan @PaulZeise Nothing that child says will change my opinion of him.....which isn’t very high. #punk]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8cAWEfTJHY ATT customer service is cheap and easily available 1-833-554-5444 #attcustomerservice… https://t.co/xBDu09tpzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking back at photos and realizing that these last 3 years have gone by so fast it’s insanity. I miss so many thi… https://t.co/7imOQswLUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec If they can in their minds rationalize the party’s new leanings. Anything can be explained away if you really want to believe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WEMSText @jemsconnect @EMSTODAY @lippincott Ping @WildMedSociety @NAEMSP @NAEMSEpgh @NAEMT_ @ACEPNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding Liability for Falling Trees: Recently, I addressed a question posed by a reader who asked who is responsibl… https://t.co/iYMkKz64Bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d34f @jimmyeatworld @zlind76 @jimadkinsmusic Straight up, that record pops off. I bought the “High” 7-inch last ye… https://t.co/sxCdQfK5s4]]></document><document><![CDATA[yassssss time to kick some more heads off with the aid of modern endocrine science!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brandon Beavers throws down a big slam after grabbing a steal and Harvest Prep leads 51-27 with 4:34 to go in the third   Elite athlete]]></document><document><![CDATA[Polarization and Civil Disagreement: Confronting Americas Civic Crisis https://t.co/6HwNZCZbYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evans wrestlers Jackson and Drew Eller are a combined 105-0 this year!!! They gun for state titles later this week.… https://t.co/VPs6vmQnmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Graze and stargaze with @aveytare on @dublab mañana! https://t.co/n0CshGW3rh]]></document><document><![CDATA[José Abreu says he’s been working with his private hitting coach Marcos Hernandez all offseason and even here in spring training some]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1clevercupcake I have packaging, Fedex slips and $$ i will assume all damage done with shipping and still eat it!!… https://t.co/TPQpjC96TP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suzannegeorge02 @LukeSMahoney @MandelaPS @ateachertweet @mccutcheonpeel @njames4nj @DrWestonClass Very cool!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NHL #20122013 #FlamesSharks #CSNBayArea #SportsFan 🏒 @ SAP Center https://t.co/PKL97juzUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best 4 years of my life🛬 One Team One Family❤️ #18out @ Connery Ice Arena https://t.co/LLuAFB5kA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the best race another single file race I hope to God the 500 ain't like that tomorrow #XfinitySeries #NASCARRacingExp300 #Daytona500]]></document><document><![CDATA[discussion about race. The NFL-Players Coalition deal can be directly traced to his kneeling. He has taken $1  mill… https://t.co/voALeJ63Ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsDaysPast @Pacers Pacers should have never stopped wearing those awesome uniforms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[COLUMBUS/ST UNIV,OH (OSU) ASOS reports gust of 50 knots (57.5 mph) from WSW @ 1827Z -- KOSU 241853Z 25028G43KT 9SM… https://t.co/gzJWb1K7kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say hello to Bert, who just got his shots at 11 weeks old and is progressing nicely into becoming a handsome young… https://t.co/LYbzPvBeVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheleykva @itstatyannag love 2 learn from You, the expert on being agreeable]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got sons that ain’t tall enough to touch the backboard, but every week they touchin the glass at visitation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love that we’ve created a way for all fans to get involved in our game experience, in addition to showcasing some i… https://t.co/ildeyPbBlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonfarone Lol Maybe they mean the same dick not every dick you see because that's diseases right there]]></document><document><![CDATA[With 4:45 to play in regulation, Talihina leads Hartshorne, 49-40. Nobody has scored since the 6:28 mark. #OKpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Por que será que los más asiduos seguidores de cuentas basura como las que acosan bloggers o Whitexicans son puro… https://t.co/fAtq92Mr6x]]></document></documents></author>