<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[overrules career experts to to our nation’s most sensitive secrets.'  They cited an 'intentional, concerted effort'… https://t.co/aSkoOghbft]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have SUCH a bad problem where no matter how much i like a house i legit wanna move every six months..... like i’m… https://t.co/I27EWQiqDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/SkqEt8Fp69 #CBD #missteddisllc #missteddistncture #missteddisawardwinningtopical]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichAllan501 You could do one eye. Ask. I used TLC in LR. Free consultation. You never know friend😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My winery girls 🖤🍷🖤🍷 @ Catoctin Breeze Vineyard https://t.co/mqPYYwzing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMVivancoHRW Q desafortunada afirmación ... lo tenía en estima pero se nota q ud no vive el conflicto armado de ba… https://t.co/BCfrEMMI2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously....Is there anything this guy CAN’T do!?!? We are so blessed to have ryanvaughanweather to jump in anywhe… https://t.co/VqziLFGc4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobLoeb @ElizabethCano23 Factual issues (“I am wonderful”) arguably predominate so probably clear error.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesonAPLang @LTMusical No big deal. We are on break next week, but drowned in fatigue this week. Plus, we have an ice storm happening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Travesty to nominate such an incompetent person just to reward donors 😡  @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brujaizm Did this by chance connect with the dream we discussed about the text sent to the wrong individual? Just… https://t.co/T5liCmRwT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you blu _ ya @chayap16 for liking the early show this morning! I was  so glad to be on it!💜🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Credit Specialist" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about these types of opportu… https://t.co/qeQQiGMVXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! My 1st time using artist quality #watercolors, #brushes in my new fieldartist #artjournal! 🎨🐎😍 Staying with… https://t.co/CUqQy1vKxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have a problem with the fact that my delayed first flight made me miss my flight back to Minnesota, the lay… https://t.co/9TIYvrrxoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeBrownRadio Can’t believe you don’t watch that show https://t.co/ZbMZOeYoyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaihenH 😥No puedo #alegrarme!!! @EsamiraDeTerror!!!😟😟 Qué Dios se apiade de el..!!🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women in all their diversity stopped by the state captiol for Women’s International Day. Every woman should have th… https://t.co/hsVoRSlkDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The X-Files was added to Amazon so I guess it’s safe to say I will need the whole week off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheItalGal Good plan, I will get ready.   When the ice storm hit #Toronto a few years ago at Christmas I was witho… https://t.co/iWyAAan7xX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Ridiculous! Stop their paychecks! We are Done throwing our money down the drain. Read the Bible]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the sweat of your face you shall eat bread, till you return to the ground, for out of it you were taken; for you… https://t.co/19vGbPciQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren I only donate to official websites. Sorry. This could be a scam for all I know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having dinner with My Grandson, Andres. #ilovemygrandsons💕 #saintclairshores @ Gilbert's Lodge https://t.co/bkyC5Gxki6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTMSBulldogs PRIDE day celebration being led by “the leader of the pack”. #proud2BaBULLDOG https://t.co/DzC5YRGw7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have FMLA at work because of women’s issues and every time I take an FMLA day, my coworkers always expect me to t… https://t.co/s6z0SZPiqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[fan photo for free people "Bldg 25 Blog" #laughter #tee-hee #grin #clever https://t.co/qmAwgFZSFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @seanhannity @FoxNews Are you going to tell him what the Russians have on you?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially considering the reports brought against Gerard Antinoro were investigated internally and it was found th… https://t.co/N2Bpmz4JF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @SebGorka That is it in a nutshell!  Look at those on top now?  They will never be held accountable… https://t.co/dGe5A1KoHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiraSorvino Always enough prayers to go around. Prayer are never spared they are freely given]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being able to contribute to my industry's legislative advocacy efforts at the State Capitol yesterday was absolutel… https://t.co/hM5CIuoc6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetZameer @SarahBCalif @ProudResister Thank you for your support. There are thousands of us in America protestin… https://t.co/dXAtfYUJue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a Beautiful Saturday! @willylevy29 @WlwBolivia @WLW_Arizona @WLW_Cuba @WLW_EGYPT @WLW_ElSalvador @WLW_GRECIA… https://t.co/EW2PeS5TzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[i low key love drag makeup but i’m too scared to make that jump with makeup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 2 spots remain for our 5th annual Weekend of Wellness retreat @MuskokaSoul with myself and trainer @JS3PT on b… https://t.co/xTDTmO1RTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Texas sized send off for @ariel_plasencia as she leaves CLT for @wfaa! Dallas, you’re getting a good one! We will… https://t.co/s0Z5jG8sLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all tonight I had the honor and privilege of meeting @marcusluttrell , the Lone Survivor. Honestly it was so surr… https://t.co/6aMSmfHCX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tsbe is here and coloring. He went to color a bunny blue and my mom piped up “bunnies aren’t blue.”   STAND DOWN S… https://t.co/0BeLTCZ8qa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im not bout to watch this racist ass white man point his racist finger at another racist ass white man. I’ll clock… https://t.co/e9rPw9fMti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_baliad @MicahKTLA @mcdade_mb @ToddKTLA @KTLA @ChipYost @kareennews @courtneyfriel @veraktla @JohnFenoglio… https://t.co/tzCmzDlFSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy day today had to hit the gym early #fitness https://t.co/d82nEdQMGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SAndrewVaughan @A2schools @A2SchoolsSuper Oooh!!  Can’t wait to chat!   Got your message!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danibby0611 I was speaking on behalf of all parents. Don’t worry it’s not just you judging parents for what they s… https://t.co/LzmeUk5fSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/72Dscgdh4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_Freeds It’s all over the map... late twenties, mid thirties, 50-yr old men love to belittle me, too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@millyscot1 So true Milly! I miss them every single day! #ForeverVane and the #BcndOfBrigands that we all loved!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas Trip #amazing #cesarpalace #venetian #bellagio #hardrock #partynight #love2travel🛩 #loveit❤️ en Las Vegas, Ne… https://t.co/Clg77UMTNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peggybolton80 @cassie was in it for all the wrong reasons! So mad that she strung him along for her own fame! Ugh!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so sad about #lukeperrry. But these stories of his kindness and humble attitude fill my heart. #RIPLukePerry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CASinotte @impactmontreal T’as fait deux excellents choix !! 1)🔵⚪️⚫️ 2)La 125 #☝️ 🙌👏🙌❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoopi Goldberg Says She 'Came Very, Very Close' to Dying (Video) https://t.co/hwQSAQ9UZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clouds_supreme @NitroNotify @FOMO_supply @SoleTerminator @expressproxies @ProxySesame @won_0925]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurnie234 Its funny because my daughter is 5'2" and my sons are giants, but she was the biggest at birth lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched you recall your YnR life story today! That took my back to when I first started watching YnR! We were… https://t.co/R5HZZSd65U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GustavoArellano 😱 Avemariapurisima! O sea que así se sienten mis compas argentinos cada que vamos por pan dulce y pido una concha?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump JUST BECAUSE YOU PUT IN ALL CAPS DOESN'T MAKE IT TRUE! #TrumpLies https://t.co/AGsxOnSfco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackWagnerhpk @LoriLoughlin @hallmarkchannel @WCTH_TV Phone for Bill! Hello!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing.@POTUS will sign the spending bill then declare a #NATIONALEMERGENCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[listening to your best friend cry knowing you can’t do anything about the situation sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke briefly from a dream last night and wondered if I was "sourcing" the dream correctly and including the right quotes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EJ__Lee Wasn’t scared to get dunked on either.  Just a good energy player.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheria63 Well, apparently the young Mr. Trump is offended by the truth, because his dear old Dad declared bankrupt… https://t.co/kjrAomh00d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always thought my grandmother was going to be alive forever, that she was never going to never age and everything… https://t.co/ynb9Ws0Ugp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost jenineinf with get_repost ・・・ Look at SWEET ZOEY....she has been WAITING WAY TOO LONG😔...please keep SHARIN… https://t.co/ScoqcqR6MQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SofjaWay Страдать, что же ещё. И себя любить в промежутках между страданиями. Или когда страдаешь - упиваться стра… https://t.co/gnolfDVQBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Do you think our child will know the crib is from pottery barn? Will they tell their friends it’s from the colonia… https://t.co/V0AU6WRTbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puppies and pints night!! - Drinking a Bootjack IPA by @iciclebrewing at @tappedtaphouse  — https://t.co/q8xR3zn73R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manriquehector Nuestro DRAMA No Es Un SHOW Son Muertes de Infantes, Hambre y Crímenes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get bomb seats for mean girls on broadway 🤙🏼 #youcantsitwithus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took our graduate communications lecture to @innoworksldn - I love this building. #MMJCTakeFour https://t.co/Jhtav3eSnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Break the script and make constraints to the math class.  @MikeFlynn55 #wsmi https://t.co/KyK8YHjWML]]></document><document><![CDATA[As much as i cant stand my parents constantly asking me when im gonna get a gf they leave in a few days and it make… https://t.co/Wd0Uztqluv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think Robert and I have ever celebrated Valentine’s Day now that I think about it LOL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care for anime but i won’t say that I’ll just watch and act like I’m interested]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qbtimetraveller @nytimes it is not Walgreens! It is the shitty clerks working in Walgreens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasJsmison @mmpadellan #ImpeachTheBiggestDangerToAmericaTrump #ImpeachDictatorTrump #ImpeachTreasonousCorruptTrumpTraitorPenceNOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are my women. Couldn’t be a better way to celebrate #internationalwomensday than to spend it with them. Each… https://t.co/CTiufZN1SA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I invited Anna and Katy to the Mavs game tonight (floor seats) and both bitches said “sure!”  ...now re-evaluating our friendship 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just opened my #Tillamook Creamery box. We’re getting ready for our #NationalCheddarDay party tomorrow here in… https://t.co/sRuMPpndGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RakeMeOver @realshakau @GustavoXBIZ Smoke weed. (FYI I'm one to talk cause when I was young I tried practically ev… https://t.co/R3X68N7yXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabriellaR613 Pelosi is afraid of them you can see it in her face aside from the fact that she is getting far to old now...]]></document><document><![CDATA[More adopted tufts from Sunday... #gally1 #tardistuft https://t.co/2M2vgXkOeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you hit a home run, you get ice cream. Even if that “home run” is just a hard hit ball that never stopped roll… https://t.co/Qa2C0WqzQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you Lead with Love you honor those real superheroes! Thank you Wake and Orange County First Responders! And, t… https://t.co/YowiWUJmKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally at the boss of the first palace.  Crazy it’s taken like, 15 hours to get here.  Guess that’s Persona for yo… https://t.co/E0c1J5NI7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@i_iove_nature Nunca había visto un pavorreal chiquito!!!  Gracias por compartir la foto  🤩😍😮❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet dreams, y'all!  You know you'll have them 😇 https://t.co/vzJhraB1MT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A true STORM WARNING impacting both weekends of @lakeeriebase so far this season!  Thankful @Coach_Skold worked so… https://t.co/GGR0WscWgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump You work for America citizens..   Stop fighting for Illegal Aliens Undocumented imm… https://t.co/RmjGjTsFFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vicky4Trump @KAG4All @MichaelCohen212 @POTUS I think he sould it already...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanda_granata @justinsplanet42 @296_cool @loveujustinjb5 @BhanuRajput33 @kulsgrace @Monika_Kapoor19 @curly_bug… https://t.co/ecOmPQ6tvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FatherGarris ohhh, i want to play. i have woosts class on mysticism and liturgy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fordnation @KingaSurmaMPP You are NOT STEALING OUR TTC! unless you are going to take on the Transit of EVERY City,… https://t.co/CXNgiWdyjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Commonwealth Fund assessed the performance of healthcare systems in 11 countries based on 5 groups of indicators.… https://t.co/9j8AANrhLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aug1405 @RUUnmasked @MoreCowbell_USA @harjo111 @CensoredC1 @Scott09555420 @marcicpr62 @LoriMillerTX1… https://t.co/0OXtnHL9hS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE Y’all are doing a awesome job keep knocking that glass in and this is what the wwe universe needs right now more attitude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @FEC @saikatc @AOC How are these people getting away with breaking our laws?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this is taking place at my school @TaylorsElem right now!! #TLIM #TaylorsLeads]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Instead,hunger only becomes relevant when people confront negative stimuli or situations. But why would hunger onl… https://t.co/awaAq0Wiz6]]></document></documents></author>