<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tjconnorstweets Kraft singles isn't cheese.  You might as well eat that spray cheese.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badhopper @Dante7237 @JohanBBT @ElkValleyBrew @ManvsAle @JonMontag @mtravis63 @TheStraightHops @CasaskullMark… https://t.co/ANZrvv0JSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! Fun show ahead on today’s Sunday Sports Shootout. Have any thoughts you want to share? Give us a call… https://t.co/ktYan5NF67]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Antebellum▪︎AT&amp;T Center▪︎2.20.19 📸 for @iheart / @kj97sanantonio  #ladyantebellum #sarodeo #attcenter… https://t.co/h57BQfBnef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1… https://t.co/CC9mhL13Wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@churhoe @ErikaBreigh @xMiyara That was our secret you bitch wtf is your problem 🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay down for the come up🙏 #GlobalDistortion @ASAPMOB @ygAddie https://t.co/nWaiwgah3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vigil service at St. Nicholas Russian Orthodox Cathedral - Seattle, WA  #Orthodox #Christian #Православный… https://t.co/Jri6C6uSwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Relaxing day today! 🙌🏽  #happiness #torobrands #toroenterprise #Toro #maryland #virginia #dc #dmv #love #instagood… https://t.co/rzcYPkr8sJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found out I’m adopted. After all these years I can’t believe Willie carter held this from me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hey I Just Met You And This Is Hazy by @sasquatchbrew @ Sasquatch Brewing Company &amp; New West Cider — https://t.co/e5V66JTCZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly wonder what makes people think they can run twice and stand any chance. Is it that Nixon did and was ult… https://t.co/OnYcXPHEbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep telling yourself that "democratic" socialism is different from authoritarian socialism.  Here you can see the… https://t.co/WynbMS6bVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DollarTree Store #2051 is a serious concern. No shopping carts, no dividers for the registers, product constantly… https://t.co/mKZEY2CyGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abcWNN C'mon @ABC way too many baldys on TV give us a break.  We just got rid of one and you put another one on.… https://t.co/bbLLSJELMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Bush and Obama used emergency declarations to reprogram appropriations 18 times between 2001 and 2013,… https://t.co/MW7VKGLSwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hailiedeegan #wallawallabob @ Las Vegas Motor Speedway https://t.co/JsdyFA4GiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I imagine when news anchors party they make fun of their fake ass tv voices https://t.co/6ulw6qp7S0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slade @joereid Slade I was there for this and it was my THIRD DAY living in NYC and I fucking lost my mind. I was… https://t.co/WM318WLVqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was the most important book for me back in 1998.   Sunday morning feels.   #seriously #allthefeels @ Black Mou… https://t.co/ZwXUuN2R1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wore it for his win to move him into 1st place for US goalies all time! #WhatABeauty]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t get to re-write the National Anthem. That was terrible!! #ALLSTARNBA2K19 #USA #NBAAllStarGame]]></document><document><![CDATA[They need to turn the bayley buddies into boss n hug thugs..give them some gold chains and sunglasses @itsBayleyWWE @SashaBanksWWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robert_QSentMe @rothschildmd He didn't say one fucking factual thing in that speech]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelseysorrell Yeah pm can’t even hold a candle to Mac. That’s just wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The good folks at @TwitVI have Mississippi State as an 11 point favorite for tonight's game against Missouri.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BR_NFL If he woulda went to LA he'd be saying LA was the greatest city.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnTheMetra there goes the onTime performance for February.  At least forty minutes late for BNSF#1267 tonight. #METRASUCKYsucksuckysuck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re at a black persons house &amp; they ask you   “What’re you about to get into”   They’re asking you to leave 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikefromWCH Are you ready to defend your fantasy baseball title? Draft is next Mon nite at 8 pm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Godspeed Mr President. Thank you for your strong leadership. I pray everyday for Gods support for… https://t.co/bK9pZADGBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@techcoachmama @justintarte Wouldn’t it be powerful for a student to turn in incomplete work with an explanation of… https://t.co/skdGLuM48Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WestVirginia_02 @WestVirginiaAFL @Lisa_Asillie @WVStateParks @WVtourism They are so busy playing grade school. If… https://t.co/SeEUfvf01B]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FBF #NYC 17 years ago with the #UVA #college homies.  Cameraman looks like he was about to get flexed on,  cuz bac… https://t.co/GTWegSn56f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse no it is not according to his tweets its hate those different from him can the wh employees stop lying… https://t.co/GGwgfo6AeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to friends, tacos, margaritas, and music from around the globe on Friday March 15 at Guero’s! @ Gue… https://t.co/DTCNsOanDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fania All-Stars - El Raton (The Raton Pack Edit). It’s out there somewhere. Good luck! 🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 Cut my friend and push him into the bear, someone has to live to tell the story. Aw just kiddin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying AGAIN. This time w/ the book cover. Duh. Day 7-I have accepted the challenge from @KempHiram to post covers… https://t.co/nFMFrFta5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrErnestOwens I think he was truthful during his interview. Story has been consisted. I don’t find it hard to beli… https://t.co/8t7tche1lm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethreinhard @alice_crites It may have been an innocent attempt at a peck on the cheek gone wrong but anyone who h… https://t.co/tgelKCpxM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enorman75 @NHL Also, I chatted with his Dad, Walter, for what seemed like a half hour. Without question, one of th… https://t.co/Py2mmPURL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Jeremy_Roenick, Charlie Coyle was not one of the @mnwild most valuable assets! He is a 3rd line player who can… https://t.co/HfBDSjDMx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@osnapsteph thanks for letting me be a part of that discord chat it was fun chatting a little with you,… https://t.co/yTm05bJDQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyeball @Chribonn58 @TamRuther @cathmckenna @liberal_party @JustinTrudeau https://t.co/HxDUVfbRqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if it only lasts a short time, it's still very pretty!! Just wish I could enjoy a #snowday instead of sleeping… https://t.co/XnYufuIwRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a few minutes to sit in a dark quiet sanctuary and meditate on the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE: RT @itsLioRush: @fightbobby ... Hey man, if you get this, give me a call back.  https://t.co/fW3abi0ax9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@niceoneWern No. Because that AWOL marine probably checks every day to see if Jordan finally made a PSN account using that name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When is the media going to start treating @AOC like they treated Sarah Palin?  Same level of stupid, different poli… https://t.co/9ABVH3sOnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Channel surfing and came across The Sandlot.  So funny.  “You’re killing me Smalls”!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latest @UCF_Banneret podcast includes my exclusive interview with @UCF_WSoccer Alum &amp; @CBF_Futebol 's goalie… https://t.co/snZcMcygeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericahilll @OliviaBBCan6 @derekjacobkess @MoveWithAli @JohnnyBBCAN @thejesselarson @kaegrant @BBCANHGRozina… https://t.co/t9YvnRr24V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenLemieux Not even a remote possibility.  CHI is in the playoffs right now. There would be a mutiny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He will skate .A lie or felony is not a lie or Felony if committed in front of 50,000 witnesses by a liberal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The truth hurts: Applebee’s boneless wings are way better than Buffalo Wild Wings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tennessee @Vol_Baseball trails for the first time this season, after allowing 2 early homers. Down 2-0 heading to t… https://t.co/OY3mKiyYnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DevinNunes @FoxNews Your going down !! LoL you will be impeached!! https://t.co/F4YjS7LyOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MO_Outlaw41 @NASCARONFOX I hear in so me areas Boudreaux’s Butt Paste is selling like hotcake amongst the butthurt… https://t.co/HMy8PsI61P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next week I’m leaving the cards at home and making some magic with a special celeb on @WorldsBestCBS. GET READY… https://t.co/0V9S28VAnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember the good old days when people as dumb as Lyndon LaRouche would run for President and lose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: AOC's Brilliant Take Down Of Ronald Reagan https://t.co/Xi2oWBS6f9 @TYT @bern_identity @BernieSanders… https://t.co/h52HjiymhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nkraus13 @Team_Poppe Said it before and I'll say it again.  Love watching poppe.  Coaches with passion.  Y'all hav… https://t.co/e466CACx5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine's Day is stupid. I don't need anybody. I just need my cat, this couch, my laptop, these 10000 vinyl recor… https://t.co/vXLI5phr21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TETempleton @AOC @amazon Imagine someone wants to give you $30,000 in business but wants $3,000 in free upgrades.… https://t.co/P3AVLzAAQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollyhood4ever @HHlibertarian @realchuckbearry @stranahan @ali @GarlandNixon Are you a descendent from Africa?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listened to Tupac’s Keep Ya Head up  this morning and realized that it’s basically a bunch of @AOC Tweets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since we don’t see each other anymore I can understand you’re lack of direction . Answer 1. Put dirty dishes in the… https://t.co/45CrbWlfUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaronEgerton are we kidding with your singing voice? Omfg why is the movie not out until end of MAY! 🔥🔥🔥😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning and evening prayer from the Book of Common Prayer, curated and simplified for Lent:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMOinndisHo I like my shi straight up, no ice. Got you feeling like you’re flying 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/2 What businesses don't understand is that just because hemp was legalized doesn't mean we can start putting #CBD… https://t.co/GrBo4liNIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The place is jumping!  @HyattSacramento is teeming w @calymca #YouthAndGovernment leaders in town for #71MLC.  Thes… https://t.co/C0rlduQsMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JU2419922 We will have another system on Wednesday but I wouldn't call it a storm. At this point snow looks to be… https://t.co/KPQT8fqrtk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TashaTrips777 😂😂😂 that's what bathrobes are for 🤷🏽‍♂️.... that or wrap the covers around you when you get out of bed... 🤣💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach Cal told me to let the face heal, and you have four years of eligibility left😴 Thanks for a great time brotha… https://t.co/dWWxur36BZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A full cast of life passes through my neighborhood. Tonight, at a low-cost large-portions homegrown fast food place… https://t.co/88J2U521LM]]></document><document><![CDATA[FUCK YES, can’t stand Gall. Diego smoked that little turd. Stop calling your shots take what they give you. #UFC234 https://t.co/THTWfUKUyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[😤/ qdot02_  🎥 overtimetj  #coldblooded @ Fort Myers, Florida https://t.co/edxzEafM1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson Tucker Carlson: This talk about high-school girls having sex and it's okay to rape a girl if you're… https://t.co/MCwLs520Jx]]></document><document><![CDATA[DMC5 is very good. A good 3/4 of the game is set in the same place so environments got kind of old. I've only playe… https://t.co/YbhZlXJg31]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom Perplexed When Son Darts Out of House, Heart Melts When She Sees Him with Elderly Neighbor https://t.co/4kFHkzTlVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danlevene Should’ve forked the money and persuaded Gary Cahill to go there till end of the season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beisbologo @jguaido Hermano en México estamos pasando algo similar, todos pidiendo que amlo fracase solo para deci… https://t.co/A0hcuguVsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[That kinda day. #Snowday. #mama sleeping..#catsofinstagram @ Bristol, Connecticut https://t.co/qIPkwY2V1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[When “Sentry Mode” switches to an Alarm State and blasts the stereo at full volume it should default to playing, Br… https://t.co/7EEgNUllml]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @buffalobills are adding the missing link, @AB84. Buffalo is going back to the big show!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the one and only, The Nature Boy , Ric Flair 🙌🙌🎉🎊🎉🎊 #Raw @RicFlairNatrBoy 70 is the new young 🥂 https://t.co/uxk3mOszvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been gone almost ten years, but there’s always a huge part of me in Texas. #TexasIndependenceDay https://t.co/Rp9WDHIAKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know she’s ready! @breezyhalll has been relentless and has gotten better in every facet of the game! Go get it yo… https://t.co/SNzYJcD3Ts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders And fwiw I can have whatever I want as long as I earn it. That's what a free market allows. ANYONE a… https://t.co/q3BUakeHn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_kmoney @Amanda_Buehler @BaseballUGA @LIU_Baseball @necbaseball never said that. Georgia isn’t even the best team… https://t.co/W3zqFllruq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a good one so far, 3-pointer by CC’s Byron Joshua gives Crescent City a 21-18 lead going into 2Q vs. McMain #nolaprep]]></document><document><![CDATA[No fewer than four crosschecks from Hagg to Malkin with official looking on. No call until retaliation and it’s bee… https://t.co/DdZOJAFayy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always remember, you may not be able to reach what's in front of you, until you let go of what's behind you. #Quote]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/LvHVGxNaZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iCAM_YT I subscribed, #265. Keep it up! Good luck! Check out my channel if you have a chance. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_anything @colin_dunlap @RamonFoster Without a great O-line, playmakers can't make plays. Football 101 dude. This isn't a video game]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Ector boys bi-district #txhshoops set https://t.co/0heCnaOm04 @hoopinsider @Texas1AFan @DCTBasketball @Tabchoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @realDonaldTrump why don’t you send some of those soldiers sitting around doing nothing about the emergency at… https://t.co/x2VjHRFfEI]]></document></documents></author>