<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu Dr. Gu, I follow you because you say the honest truth. But, pointing out first that Jussie is a black gay… https://t.co/zSeMorShfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuyingAir Yeah, B/C.you know it’s all about Carly and Sam? Sam is running off W/Shiloh, and has no clue that Jason… https://t.co/RuRlpYmJhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a mom of 2 honor Ss, we’ve worked hard over the yrs to find how they can each self reg. Wasn’t the same for each.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean do we even still need day light savings time?? I feel like it’s obsolete at this point in time 💁🏽‍♀️💁🏽‍♀️… https://t.co/aJI1Guz7TA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered for a chance to go to the Rock &amp; Roll Hall of Fame 2019 Induction Ceremony! https://t.co/oXrSdt9e1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking in early here in Daytona beach, Florida. For the #9PMRoutine.  @PascoSheriff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahMcConnell @Becksiecakes Yes and maybe an updated makeup board too thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[not gonna lie that new avril lavigne song slaps. christian jesus banger]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump might be a huge POS but comparing him to a man of evil incarnate whom killed thousands upon thousands is too… https://t.co/oBeqYTHy0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m obsessed with natural oils! I can’t wait to try this one by loccitane #perfectleeimperfect  ・・・ 100% natural oi… https://t.co/0C1A2nr1wh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jack just "gets" crypto. 🤖🤷 (via @Investopedia) https://t.co/ZlOGPcNZTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James36Leonard That’s a beautiful story. Maggie was a puppy thrown on the side of a farm road left to die. Rescue… https://t.co/67dmhZ7qG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the 2019-2020 7th and 8th grade cheerleaders! 📣❤️ https://t.co/QmujE2BDUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lori_criss @OhioMHAS Will you please get a selfie with Director Hall?? I believe she’s right next to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialBrianaB killin it!!!! #SPNNash #nashcon https://t.co/DFTgloTJG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time today learning about media broadcast techniques from @JeremyBrisiel! 💯💥🎥🎙 Learned SO MUCH! Thanks… https://t.co/0DM0C94nGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HorsesAreBetter I'm not exaggerating when I say these CHANGED MY LIFE. It is literally like you're not even on your period]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a nervous lil bean that hates confrontation but a conversation MUST BE HAD. I CAN DO IT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This says it all...thanks to CNN blogger...  "Anyone who uses the phrase, 'deep state' without irony, is too fuckin… https://t.co/LoxehexD77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork A lot of Democrats on Twitter which make it such a hateful place]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muyevil Demasiado. A mi echarán, pero el no juagaba ni un segundo más...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stratosathens @realDonaldTrump He wants to be able to drop his lies on Twitter “very fast”! https://t.co/4VF7TNsn71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WonderyMedia How do you let this joke of a man/podcast exist alongside podcast greats like @replyall. It’s a godda… https://t.co/wIKHJ1Zo8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted the challege from @engteach98 to post 7 covers of nonfiction books I love: no explanations, no revi… https://t.co/Ar78O4Cjkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interest Rates Hit New 12 Month Low! https://t.co/kVntHcqCow such great news!!!  Call me today- lets buy something!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t ask me for relationship advice bc my default thought is “leave him sis”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate girls that say all men are trash or that we don't need men and stupid shit like that. Just cause you dated t… https://t.co/zXL07mArVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NEW: This is the latest from the @CityPGH officials! 71 vehicles at the ready with ANOTHER 36 on standby. Also the… https://t.co/cBjzOEeyMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[ᴇɴ ᴇʟ ʙᴏxᴇᴏ ɴᴏ sᴇ ᴇᴍᴘᴀᴛᴀ. sᴇ ɢᴀɴᴀ ᴏ sᴇ ᴘɪᴇʀᴅᴇ, ʏ ᴠᴏs ɴᴏ ᴘᴇʀᴅɪsᴛᴇ. ᴛᴇ sᴏʙʀᴀ sᴀɴɢʀᴇ, ʜᴜᴇᴠᴏs ʏ ᴄᴏʀᴀᴢᴏɴ. ᴏʀɢᴜʟʟᴏ ʏ ʜᴏɴᴏ… https://t.co/uZOKvJP1Zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LawProfButler I believe you are correct. Enough cumulative evidence is there! @hardball]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for PJ Washington for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/CPYnOobAwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day I've beat @avthree_ in the exercise and move rings!!! ...I've got a 30 min head start on him though so my… https://t.co/jWJe6K7NGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[5:30pm. 💪 #jamfitnesswithcarlee #fitgoals #fitlife #fitfam #fitspo #fitspiration #fitnessinspiration… https://t.co/s7SqNFJoQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así como a cada estrella, tu me sostienes. Mi alma en ti descansa, en tu amor Jesús.  #karijobe #asicomocadaestrella #palabrasdeamor #]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know you think it’s funny that your ex is not a running back but that nigga came runnin back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jfeliciano55 @AndrewPollackFL @realDonaldTrump How?  What are you doing about school shootings?  What is Trump doing??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama Those kids taught us all what determination looks like. Lends new meaning to the phrase “out of the mo… https://t.co/iLygljGrV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeartOTXHeartMD This is a 12 hospital system with many outpatient,urgent care sites. She is a hospitalist and has… https://t.co/Mve2m0CAIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que feo tener la ilusión de querer contarle algo a alguien y no poder :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 I love this picture of our President Trump hugging our Flag I wish I had a painting of it✝️🇺🇸✝️🇺🇸✝️]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that dance marathon is over can i start venmo reuesting people just to venmo request them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @maydaymindy9 Me too but with my 100 pound dog. Lol he hops around loves it. Best therapy also. 😂😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[a girl who can’t cook, has no sense of directions, and takes 5 hour long naps &gt;&gt;&gt; I love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfTerryHughes @EdJoyce @OregonSeaGrant @MSI_OregonState @HatfieldMSC @ODFWMarine @tomcalvanese @NOAAFish_NWFSC… https://t.co/SrgXBYq9Gf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shelia are you out of your mind?You and  the Village idiot AOC Socialist  like Sanders would destroy our Country!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson #VoiceBlinds Kelly BIG mistake that no one turned for TJ!!!  I don’t know how it works,but I’m hopi… https://t.co/ZtdUDnanSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictorResendez Gracias *toma una caja de pañuelos desechables y la guarda en la bolsa*]]></document><document><![CDATA[And Who Will Be Next?  Who Else Is Expendable?  The Elderly, Disabled, People With Chronic Illness...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#godsword #life #joyispower HopeJoy Love can change your life @ Guntersville Recreation Dept https://t.co/6loHwQJBdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if you feel like I’m shaming you for that, then yes. I’m shaming you. If we mobilized as the black gay communit… https://t.co/iKPKS997mw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @AOC How can you predict the weather 12 years from now, when the daily forecast are rarely accurate? You… https://t.co/9O0iHHtzLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[where can i buy this, asking for my brother 🤷🏻‍♀️😂😂😂 https://t.co/ELC6PwAqhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re right @PrincipalTrots running does good for your soul....thanks for checking on me @LarissaSherrod ❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/F3uoTcJ7Zo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @MorSeaS He is not orange enough or fat enough to be the real trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crackbandicoot @BT_BlackThunder @SonySantaMonica @corybarlog @PlaystationBrah @Nerraograyghost @Farore5… https://t.co/BediYCdmkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I’m trying again in 5 years for a boy after seeing how cute he looks 😭❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ralph Northam to Jussie Smollett: How Black History Month 2019 Has Been a Total Disaster https://t.co/5u8V1Sokil via @thedailybeast]]></document><document><![CDATA[#castlife preview event for #starwarsgalaxysedge super excited about the costume choices! Plus we got to ride… https://t.co/JjKweUIOi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner @MalcolmNance The GOP is going to try to run a Kangaroo court! Hopefully the democrats will not let them get by with it! #MSNBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MccownWendy @mattnathanson @MattsMoustache @themattwork @MattsManBun @matts_hips I just followed you, would love t… https://t.co/kpdrtIFw2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[También existen esos días... en los que asta escuchar música duele. Y mucho sin Ti, ya nada es igual! 😔😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I basically have unintentionally fasted today. It's 5:10 and I'm like oh food, I haven't had any.  I should be skinnier dammit!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @fran_tray @realDonaldTrump He knew people would get confused about that favorite president part, so he added “me”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty much sums it up... #resellercommunity #reseller #instafam #insta #instagram #peopleofinstagram #friends… https://t.co/ICtesCMn7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glitter is good in the rain, too! #Muses #getreadytoroll @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/SzDhKuXWZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mailomarcos @JoaquinBondoni @MiMaridoFamOf al ver las promociones de el gran final no pude evitar que se me salier… https://t.co/A726uNzk5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Claire trying to channel Shaun is getting me all verklemmt. He's such a force on that team.  #TheGoodDoctor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pascal: All of humanity’s problems stem from man’s inability to sit quietly in a room alone - https://t.co/EkznrRZrTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[thE one and only place to be next Thursday‼️ Don’t miss out on this beautiful event 💛 https://t.co/cAlZvlngfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[i haven’t thought about this place for a while until I was scrolling through some older pictures today. I love seei… https://t.co/113aoLFVJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@munch9419 Stay warm and cozy my friend...🙋🙋🙋👍👍👍 https://t.co/qV4fBgwjnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wearewyland Malahide Castle in June and Columbia, Maryland (with Smashing Pumpkins) in August]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spearson2904 @joemcelderry91 I'm watching the American Voice right now. Love these coaches. So funny. Kelly Clarks… https://t.co/d6VqZUW40c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t know lil peep died and now I’m really sad about it and idk why]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st round of the SWAC Tournament kicks off today. We’ve earned a 1st round bye, but are looking forward to getting… https://t.co/VR2WdxuZfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo unico que quiero es estar rodeada de gente que sea honesta y sincera.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teka lang. Sumbatan? Mag compute ba? Ano @thereisanocean labasan ng resibo? Pucha nman oh since 2015 p gastos namin… https://t.co/C6JKFG1DLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only want happiness, and this guy has so many problems of his own, I don’t want them I’m sorry... I don’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barely missed The Daily Show newsroom performance so I stayed in line to make sure I caught @JoinTheDynasty to see… https://t.co/Ubmy0IgnsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien I love you, Soledad! Why do so many others in the media shy away from calling things as they are whe… https://t.co/1CVCsxkGHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang merry. #funniness #chuckle #smile #ludicrous https://t.co/iL07PmCYRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoisLowryWriter That was the original poster’s question - how would the story be different if Gabe were more of a… https://t.co/Rl6N42vCg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Pooler, GA? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/KPYg7sf3AI #Cosmetology]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made my donation. Please join me and help get @marwilliamson to the debate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ascendantofrain I like you and your wife and twin pics! I’ll never unfriend you. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fondly reminiscing about the double OTK I did with a pair of identical male twins in jeans back in 2015 in Oklahoma… https://t.co/MbnmEVSKkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My lyft is playing @Jessiereyez I’m crying on the way home from the club 🔥❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, because many of them don’t have their fathers, or other male figures in their lives... sad 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to wrap up tonight's @taylorswift13 binge listening and last minute @ghc session submission writing. After som… https://t.co/MyFkWvbIMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite receiving Mayor Bill Peduto's support, Bobby Wilson came in behind city councilwoman Darlene Harris in the… https://t.co/Ps7XoqB2MK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astudyinsnoggy @poshboy221b MJ I hope you still love me 💖 but when it comes to my love of Mycroft https://t.co/b5C8b12SXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[YALL READY FOR ROUND 2⁉️👀  YTS ENT PRESENTS‼️  WE RUN THE CITY:  BULL CITY TAKEOVER  🐂  🕗|| 10 pm - 2 am  MUSIC BY:… https://t.co/aad5oJpVHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Septembers_Song @charbhardy Heard it will cool down next week &amp; I cannot wait]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a nice time hanging out at the #beach . It is so wonderful that even thru #LakePlacid and sand, we can conne… https://t.co/G5Am1xRhHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[What time is it??? It's Kids Workshop time at 6533! https://t.co/cVm0PfJAuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[: I REFUSE TO BELIEVE @AidanRGallagher IS LESS THAN 48 YEARS OLD IN REAL LIFE, IDC IDC #UmbrellaAcademy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl  Sons of Liberty that's what you, Laura &amp; your gang are...get your own tree (great American history) 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @LifeStructures for the invitation to join your breakfast table this morning.   #IBJHealthHeroes https://t.co/kCyQjVoRiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheFive.                                      God bless the Police Chief, he is laying into Jussie !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve dissected and jordyn and Tristan (been) had to go. But Khloe saying the reason they broke up is bc of her is laughable]]></document></documents></author>