<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Pulse- Why Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez’s Green New Deal is Disastrous https://t.co/kqIaV8lLAb; #PragerU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winds are 3 to 4 kts from the E. https://t.co/LnVdm6vuAq #OnSiteReport #WindAlert]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RAClifford2 In observing middle eastern culture I think we can surmise that their singing (“do it with all thy mig… https://t.co/mm68In9tfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Imagine what it must have been like during your outbreak of “bone spurs”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another election cycle and another white angry man hiding his tax returns when every other candidate releases them… https://t.co/IuaFXdCixe]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Wednesday #humpday and time to #takefive Working on #legato and #hybridpicking ideas.   #Jazzguitar… https://t.co/5I1bathe9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Promoting and caring it out is totally different. This sounds like more liberal bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@libby_poche @radison33 @elaine_burk @Renevelation @Franklin_Graham Your telling me WHAT you believe. I want to kno… https://t.co/rOXEe1hNon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lil_kmonster @HelicopterLegs @cherity1313 @thegymterdotnet They’re the opposite of Sam 💁‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magmendonca GOOOL PORRA TÔ ACOMPANHANDO O JOGO É OS SEUS TWEETS CARALHO OOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[6am in the morning is way to early for me . Omg I forgot to feed my son breakfast for he left. 🍳😕🙁🤔🤔🍳 bad dad. @ St… https://t.co/5xoPUuMtmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[MMU Alpine travels to Burke for day 1 (GS) of the State Championships ... #CougarNation🐾 https://t.co/TBpl05HII9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok hold tf up. People do this ? On a public website ? And expose themselves ? What kind of negative ass IQ shit is… https://t.co/qx0M2cplu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are four features of emerging pandemic threats: new pathogen or new strain; initiated by effective contact wi… https://t.co/UzCrtT4cnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomstakes She did make a homemade video that made her famous, that doesn’t count?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first few days of spring training are when you really have to double check if you're reading a beat reporter's… https://t.co/7t1Wa3YDuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Good Morning! The #American people see how hard your fighting for our country. Thank You! Prayers… https://t.co/4aoLqHDqCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[You do not need to be perfect...just be you. @GHS_Falcons  Trying to be "Perfect" is Killing Our Teens and We're to… https://t.co/8YaJCYs3iF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bensnider94 Based on interviews with Wade, I disagree. Him and Buzz in particular seem zeroed in on that "every po… https://t.co/N3YHYH9uuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Did not know Byron Cook was governor of Wisconsin. No wonder he didn’t run for re-election! #txlege]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bshelly Thanks for tweeting the whole thing!  I will have to go back and read your tweets to refresh my memory!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey everyone this is a new cool playlist I have 3 songs in. Mine are last in it so enjoy! Lots of cool music.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carter2189 damn autocorrect, I meant who DOESN’T wanna play for Oakland!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bless Devil May Cry 5 for not having QTEs during the coolest visual moments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in Monroe MI - with Vaud and the Villains!  Playing tonight at the La Z Boy Theater at Monroe Community College… https://t.co/tS6k3Q3sEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minky Chocolate Radiane Hair Colormelt™️ @Chadakenyon using @Olaplex redken @Framarint HairCut raphael_silerio… https://t.co/pANl7XPa8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[See energy _nigerianjawn #dancer  #dance  #dancing @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/cXvRS578uL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalAlbaneseNYC I'm still scratching my head. Not to denigrate the talented winners but this did seem like the most… https://t.co/POKyVh9NzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbehr1128 @__CNP__ You’re takin me to Bojangles when we come there next month. Gotta knock it off the list. Among… https://t.co/9MTyllQyXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UUA Yes! 150th anniversary of the Oakland congregation! https://t.co/E3xHpz4uDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three conservative MP resign , seems like intend to follow a variation of the Independent route of the 7 former Lab… https://t.co/DTXbqDccxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaclandJ Glad you like it.  Thandie for checking it out https://t.co/eCh2iVhLl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir @reply Seattle makes @sus_uri and I smile. Right? #iFlyAlaska #AlaskaHappyHour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrantBrisbee Three channels on the TV, 12 movies released per year, one book of the month. Let’s get back to sense people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The President's Day event is still going on at Alton Blakely Honda! These 18 Accords are at unheard of bargain pric… https://t.co/D14fXLuwgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[501-410-7018 Call or Text NOW •  2016 Toyota Camry for sale 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥 • 45k Miles 🚘 • Warranty included 🔑 • 💲299/… https://t.co/esQsuEonQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 19 of #alphabeticalfebruary was challenging, especially trying to make rice using just procedural textures, internal to @maxon3d #3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaichartRanch @prranch Now that's a bit Spicy for a Midwest Funeral salad....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see the @MBTA finally take responsibility for clearing this sidewalk. Pedestrians no longer being forced t… https://t.co/jTgT3Z4yqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewarkNights  #mailmanlife #photographerslife #pbdajr @ Newark, New Jersey https://t.co/YN7AQLIVdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Until the ppl who were plotting to remove a duly elected president are arrested and prosecuted! There is no justice… https://t.co/wOpETVXraS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sari- what is the point? C- we have social problems that are big and money will not solve.  If you want to really l… https://t.co/Ocj94x03H9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roodysmom @garthbrooks I am so sorry, we are doing a push to speed up processing time. My sincerest Apologies. Ord… https://t.co/Y0hCQ7iBJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[High Blood Pressure Linked to This Surprising Nutrient Deficiency #care2 https://t.co/QxLwQN4xKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArsalanAKhan @jayferro Products &amp; services are made up of people-process-technology.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felicidades a @TequilerosF por su primera victoria en la liga @Soy_FAM ayer en Guadalajara, México @plandejuegoNFL https://t.co/iq7g1ytt1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelpingHearts1 @CBSSacramento @tomhoganlaw @sacbee_news @SacramentoKings @thegrupeco @SacPolice @SPDOutreach… https://t.co/yvFJXfPViH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptainJackSzn Kane obvs made sense cuz he wasn’t coming back but the amount of people who were excited about it w… https://t.co/1uMVydiqFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_political_p Not an option for @AlliancePTY?  Now legally registered in 23 states including @IndyMN? Here’s a radi… https://t.co/IdwLTgc1oS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kofi Kingston is the highlight reel of the WWE when he do something incredible that'll make that crowd jaws wide op… https://t.co/JPxgqngcqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pa #pennsylvania #igersoftheday #iger #igers #igeroftheday #picoftheday #photooftheday #pictureoftheday… https://t.co/34pTTDWd2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASJBaloch #Iran before the @IlhanMN types took over ! https://t.co/VxTSy4dtSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@datachick The makers of dBase were in a suite with JPL (developers of dBase) about right to use. It wasn't about SQL though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@IAWild in a playoff position, 2 huge games this weekend vs Grand Rapids and Chicago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forget the Jar Jar Binks line. This piece suggests that “moderate Republicans” might cross over, if only out of dis… https://t.co/2lSUcTJC6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at West Nyack @LevityLive Comedy Club in West Nyack, NY https://t.co/Klz8YQAGzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber Hey, its jail 4 U if U can't pay 4 a top drawer legal eagle &amp; the MUCHO $$ bill! jml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind Unfortunately prosecutors only asked for the gag order so judge was constrained.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4% of about 3,000 votes is 120. I didn’t realize Gary Barta had such a big family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, interesting that he was right next door. Our thoughts go out to the  family]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody notice how spineless @SpeakerRyan has conveniently ghosted the public eye?  #Failure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mjhall412 @AylaForTrump @Christy102863 Me too. :-) That is all we need.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OC_Transpo Just an excuse to cover up why the buses no show on a regular basis.   Three times in a week my “regula… https://t.co/lbVAxw3kFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attitude, not Aptitude, determines Altitude. - Zig Ziglar, https://t.co/HJdBvpLrHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[ur shorty will do more for u than 99% of these nigga’s u keep around you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minnie and Pluto #waltdisneyworld #prajznersinvadedisney #epcot #werehome #Chase #disneycreditcardholderexperience… https://t.co/p5IIav2NvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow it was a year ago today that I got accepted to @GeorgiaTech, so much has changed - all for the better]]></document><document><![CDATA[-a political declaration from Trump and Kim that essentially states that enough progress was made in Hanoi to conti… https://t.co/rG2nYelFuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlscharff @Fall_of_Civ_Pod @PaulMMCooper For a “first timer”, I’m almost shocked at the quality of writing and editing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JorgeVelazquez @bolivarvalera Muy bien hecho por la joven. Ahora no se puede opinar libremente por las redes ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've never seen that before. A review decision overturned by blowing the horn and calling in? Has that ever happene… https://t.co/H0SeEGgwjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicciGeri Nazi Pelosi has tall walls arose her homes in San Francisco &amp; Napa Californiasylum 🍷🤡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@base_primera @YkGueva @AsambleaSV This is really really make me mad 😡 me indigna ver cómo abusan de la humanidad d… https://t.co/oq3mISvXuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deirdredejean @ottawacity There was no Megatron! Who knows what happened? Maybe he has finally been vanquished onc… https://t.co/kqHs0ykV4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Minuteman223 @akkingon @kooolhanluke @bushcamp2 @44_rem_mag @WassmannBill @teamregulators @HOYTARCHERYInc… https://t.co/itDmD6PCbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited about our upcoming Midwest Real Estate Networking Summit. This event originated from conversations with my… https://t.co/3HmseoZ83g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LutonNews_LTFC thanks for your coverage. Much appreciated by those of us that can't watch live]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald! Putin is "coming" get on your knees and sing praise to your idol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muffin_factory2 @ava @GayleKing Actually narcissistic behavior is quite the opposite.  Sociopaths for example woul… https://t.co/nLZwtgqtEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jajajajajaja ja cómo si él no formó parte del equipo de destrucción. Oportunista de altura!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a frustratingly unproductive weekend, but I did create a nice temporary app icon for my #ios side project  It’s… https://t.co/d8RDfNg3SP]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is evidence that Fox News faked the debate by providing Trump with the questions. Fox has become trumps state… https://t.co/mSrACKYKmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all got me fucked up if you think I’m picking any of these... https://t.co/p2gkEl1spH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@studioonesb @PeteButtigieg @HRC The man prays to God and isn’t a baby murderer. Remember the Ten Commandments? Can you name them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuicyGameReview I used to love playing as Colossus jus to hear that powerup yell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gennefer You don’t always make my day, but when you do, it is almost always because of burgers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not taking a side on this aspect of it but there’s generally a fatherly dynamic after so long with good coaches is… https://t.co/OfRpVQ6vGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Im_JustAl A.i went to the ship with noooooooooooooooo body lmao 💯, and lost to a legend 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sierranevada #nationalpark #yosemitenationalpark #yosemite #usa #elcapitan #yosemite #america #california @ Yosemi… https://t.co/bSek4dU2jM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickVau91631106 @Cleophas00 I must say Ltinv2 Mayor Turner, You look GOOD BEHIND BARS, especially if it's for Life😀😀😀😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sir we’re watching you closely! Don’t cave into the leftist especially when it comes to watering d… https://t.co/eGh8pMCljO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WTA @CaroGarcia Swing volley was right at her. She timed the passing shot well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kthorjensen Oh. I just thought you were getting your own Netflix show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catchleh watch “true nightmares” on Amazon it’s horrible and spooky and awesome and sad and hilarious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irvgotsoul @_2OLEGEND_ @BigBlueUnited Haha it's all good. It's good to have open discussions. We all have our opin… https://t.co/9ByLYgQlC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDailyShow JUST A BUNCH OF LILY WHITE BIGOTS.@GOPoversight AND OF COURSE THEY ARE REPUBLICANS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Brunch #date with this #beauty on our #dayoff! We were both admiring the #clouds and #snow on the #mountains and w… https://t.co/oAzSK9527f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know when #RedRockCanyon will look like this again, so I had to do some exploring today. #westbysouthwest… https://t.co/AAox4O31wO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LawyerLambert That’s awesome! Glad you enjoyed it. Next time you are in town, come a little further north (2 block… https://t.co/mP9Xanlc7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman @IlhanMN Friedman was vilified for these remarks and eventually admitted he had a poor choice of w… https://t.co/uwsA80hkbo]]></document></documents></author>