<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan I listened to your audio of your interview and you DID say those things about Obama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee She didn’t mean SHE has to be inconvenienced just everyone else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBWolfeVox No IPAs can be good if the brewmaster doesn't get carried away.  American piss water are things like Bud and MGD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On top of that, the team extended tender offers to TE Darrell Daniels, TE Ricky Seals-Jones and OL Jeremy Vujnovich]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondRioBand @philvassar my favorite guys all sharing the stage at the @Opry tonight! Can’t wait to listen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Indyrdls yEE YEE and I’m most likely seeing you and the rest of the beans Friday my mufuckin heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@citizenbolesp Have an affair tonight! Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight. https://t.co/D30OFvedLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristaonAir @wfmjtoday @21WFMJNews If you had a loaf of bread, you could have made toasted cheese sandwiches.  Hope no one was injured.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🧬EARTHA🧬 Profound: Very great or intense; having or showing great knowledge or insight. ✨  I AM WOMAN: Experiences… https://t.co/qaDV96tH5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever need help but don’t want to ask for help because you feel like you’re annoying? Because same]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love using @Square to run my business! Process $1,000 without fees when you activate with my link https://t.co/4GX2SW4vjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@real_jamielshaw Thank you. Where in the US can we find African Americans/Black Americans that could survive anythi… https://t.co/ujsA0eN438]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FadedSpadeCards @ThePokerBoss @ARIAPoker 🙋🏾‍♀️I’m a proud low roller who would be down for some 1/3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor Texas representative, WILL find his WIFE WATCHING THE HEARING with the remote in hand on vibration! BWAAHAAHAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaywasley Uncut? Oh so this might not suck as bad? Cause NOTHING about Demon House scared me. I was more terrified… https://t.co/8yzr2FgElm]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way back to PR🇵🇷. I won’t say goodbye because goodbye means going away an that means forgetting...and I’m def… https://t.co/5NeXFbYxjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where Are The Dead? A Biblical Look At What Happens When We Die. https://t.co/wYve1sCMpj via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary @RealDLHughley! Continued blessings and favor to you and LaDonna.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeBillieLee @khloekardashian We love you Khloe, you are beautiful and True is a gorgeous baby.We have always ro… https://t.co/uyqucr41F2]]></document><document><![CDATA[TGIF 💑👧🏽🍻#Hilton #pittsburgh #weekend @ DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Pittsburgh - Cranberry https://t.co/YAQ1aqL45F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsemscott @KelvinROfficial Across the globe, a parent is having a conversation much like this. You captured it well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@writeforapples @SpringRunSTEAM They loved chatting with you and thought it was so neat to have a real life author… https://t.co/POBPIR81G8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know why my friends are trying to make me join their work out boot camps. Look at me. Listen to my knee cli… https://t.co/vGVvIBtZoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting off the month with a new Monster flavor 🙌🏼 and a nail crisis #DrRatchet @ University of Mississippi Medica… https://t.co/raz4kJnwed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bristol-Myers responded today to activists who are opposing its deal for Celgene, saying it's the best path forward… https://t.co/ksA3krPju0]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I said I’m done dying my hair for a while and will let it grow out but I just saw a pic of someone with that pas… https://t.co/aTDDUbtIRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders. Watcha gonna do when they come for YOU, bad bad boy🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @TomColeOK04 You are a complete and utter embarrassment to fellow Oklahomans. And to the human race, you need to leave.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylvainMetz56 @Morning_Joe @samstein And Sam was cut off. God forbid we actually speak about human rights in regards to Israel 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s good mood is brought to you by coffee #starbucks #vanillaicedcoffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnEdwardBake1 Yeah, I’m not keen on using the national emergency option to push through things that should be legitimately legislated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got this Lemieux jersey as a gift from my mom for my sweet 16, I genuinely was the happiest 16 year old ever... better than a car to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A salad almost too pretty to eat annapolislighthouse Please support this restaurant when in Annapolis. They train h… https://t.co/sqD4R8RqQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wellsfargo forclousure manual was entered in BK Court Judge Drain .  Procedure wasn't illegal but could be used il… https://t.co/uk9miwg7L1]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no such thing as a Hate Speech, This is America, we have Freedom Of Speech]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willisbro We know what they want from the babies body and it only makes them worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is he really that naive to believe we're so dumb? This is the result of a sheltered life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLoyalO @RepUnderwood Unfortunately it's not un-American in the America @realDonaldTrump has created.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump You're getting paid for these stupud comments??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss you Billy Hoop,like you we were here today https://t.co/QZ4gDvOAOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentMccallie @markbaker0312 @SanAngeloISD @OfficialTHSADA Way to go Mark!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 @HillaryClinton The ONLY thing about the current occupant of the WH is all the revelations that may not h… https://t.co/BN65Wb8DDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JrwX2Rh7aZ   Trying to get some more wargroove vibes in my chat, check me out, tell me how to play! :D]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️ these two goofs with my little shadow perched on a pillow to the right. 😻🧔🏻🐶🐶👑🥜🖤 #myfamily #birthdayweekend… https://t.co/04l5DUF53t]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you enter a market you enter to dominate and if you’re not planning to dominate you probably shouldn't enter.… https://t.co/o4N8p4eXtk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Últimamente algunas personas me han dicho que soy su ejemplo a seguir; es algo que hace mucho tiempo no escuchaba.… https://t.co/hcOlVITlcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Festejo de Cumpleaños 8 de Eugenio Vanegas Garza, miércoles 27 de Febrero del 2019. https://t.co/3phrKCn4YS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I managed to get purple liquid bandage spray on my lip. I’m going to have a purple lip for days now]]></document><document><![CDATA[So allegedly someone's account was hacked. That still doesn't magically negate my point; harassing VAs is a problem… https://t.co/RFvipxkBFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soheilaghodsieh @JamesKosur @realDonaldTrump Cause they broke they law to sneak in??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is the latest on tanker fire from Rocky hill Pd. Evacuations underway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cannibalststegd I mean. JuSt give me Hennessy next time.   Specifically the thug passion daiquiri. 2 larges. Working on number 3 now. 😶😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[我朋友花園有好多橙，於是佢比左一堆比我，心諗就整橙皮醬啦。因為用左椰子糖，所以顏色會深色。  白酒玉桂橙皮醬登場！  My friend gave me lots of orange! So I think I have to m… https://t.co/FzVPmK4Y4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else think Bohemian Rhapsody wasn’t that good and that Wayne’s World was way better?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bytchfest @muttslikeme @Ltd_To_Two @_____YO_____YO @80MusicGroup @saferprint @twizmwhytepiece @Julz_Crown… https://t.co/rfoDlJYrvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Illinois wins at OSU, ties Gophs for 8th in the conference. Best 10-win team in the nation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends Mike Dense and his tone deaf performance in Europe. You are the Laughing stock of t… https://t.co/CW6eOwwtGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadnotkyle @BasedChasen damn right there are no hoes in buffalo only beautiful, classy goddesses from the city of good neighbors 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[#familyvisioncare #visionserviceplan #vsp @ Family Vision Care and Wink Gallery https://t.co/NV4zgEcSmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I am the mother of a dragon...an overweight, middle aged bearded dragon but Frank is a dragon, nonetheless.… https://t.co/LCLsf8MRzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SolidAAr @CNNTonight @donlemon You shouldn't thank Lemon for causing the divide to widen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to more direction in your life like motivation/financial freedom/being the best version of yourself, li… https://t.co/nuC6EOT8or]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylynrayy Good night!  Very proud of you ladies tonight! Looking forward to State with you eight😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CestLaVie97 Okay! So you already know it’s slim pickings around here 🤣😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peeperpea29 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Jimmysimmonds1 @FRISEEMYRIAM @MyEngland2016 @Iluvinspireu @MelindaYoe @Jilliemary… https://t.co/ZejKXgVlXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most satisfying thing is using a whole tube of chapstick before losing it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richroll @nukeSchuhmacher This was a great talk! I believe in  second chances. Many simply need to find and feel t… https://t.co/UN6K4shf5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosieLong1995 @MarissaMFOX5 You’re missing a story about a disturbing pedophile and a star-struck, enabling mother… https://t.co/3NBc4JZCZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[tee-hee time. Funny Pictures Of The Day – 125 Pics #laughter #giggle #smile #hilarious https://t.co/KHFcXHQ5GY]]></document><document><![CDATA[They should be doing something, say, on Smollett. Now that would be funny stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn man I’m dead asf . I’ve didn’t realize how much work a pharmacy can be. This early morning shit is whooping my… https://t.co/58lsO720w9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si estás sanando y rompiendote al mismo tiempo, no temas, esto es crecimiento]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGould_SA @andrerucker51 @Itridpm @DudekLinda @keanothedog @JayValenz67 @hey_butter @terry313401 @delgeo1… https://t.co/VhPRyQRznH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being in a happy, healthy, committed, equally-yoked relationship ADDS value to your life. The media told you that y… https://t.co/LeY2FtOQHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@X_Mr202 @RealDannyBailey @JamesComey2020 @Scott_Baylis @thecjpearson @realDonaldTrump @AOC @IlhanMN @RashidaTlaib… https://t.co/lmk94ag2w9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifeofaladybear @goss_ie Well done, Michaela #irishwomen #InternationalWomensDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a girl, standing in front of a coffee maker, asking it to brew faster]]></document><document><![CDATA[And my last team is in the air!  Good luck fsufalconswlax and stay safe! #mamafalcon @ Phillipston, Massachusetts https://t.co/WgfPIhcEKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great turnout for our Kaiser Medical Panel today which included nurses, physical therapists, surgeons and physician… https://t.co/3hCnG6nTJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't really put into words what this photo represents to me. All i can say is thank you for saving me. https://t.co/FJfgIXah8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is a PSA to always drink water. i’ve been sick the past few days, and i woke up with the chills, stomach pain,… https://t.co/co4asT6KIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish you could leave a voicemail when someone doesn’t answer your FaceTime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumanistReport “Allow Me to Explain Why Beto Sucks” by Kathy Copeland Padden https://t.co/ITBTqTXd08]]></document><document><![CDATA[still not over that the jonas brothers are back. i’m crying. i’m so happy. they were such an important part of my c… https://t.co/BJa6SCA8sq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsRamiMalek IT’S WHAT YOU DESERVED. Congratulations, you’re a star!!! 💫 #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coco doing it her way at the vet!!  ————————————— #adventuresofcocochanel #fiestyfern #cocossidekick… https://t.co/XMvKkDOK2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you realize you’re single af and have no one to laugh at gifs with https://t.co/6hd8eGRaIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi @JRubinBlogger @JohnCornyn @GOP I'm sure Jennifer is as outraged as you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Después de 4 meses vuelve andres y sus malditos cólicos, no podía quedarme así?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Marvel if you need money to #SaveThePunisher and #SaveDaredevil and keep the story and actors intact, ask your… https://t.co/GKX6E04s2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avery Strong Elite 32 Sacramento 7v7 CHAMPIONS!!!! 🏈🏆🙌🏼 #AveryStrong #N0Z0N3_TPGURU @ Inderkum High School https://t.co/JTLcZJHZzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[A preview of our @Scholastic book fair featuring @ellyswartz @StudioJJK @kwamealexander @writerkmc @angiecthomas ! https://t.co/hupzFZdsu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetsFanInPhilly AND he directed a Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban.  I only mention it because SOOOOO many… https://t.co/x1Po7TudWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's Wall Threatens 93 Endangered Species https://t.co/ftkznjGlM6. NO WALL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful for my momma on this beautiful Monday! 🥰 https://t.co/Mg7zUEcONm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rough Sunday nights lead to angsty Monday’s but I’m not against it, I like this angst, it motivates me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie Keep dreaming! Still waiting for your apology! Be a woman and apologize for blaming our President for what h… https://t.co/UygOOQNcqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IAmBecoming me. Thank you, @MichelleObama for being real, authentic, genuine &amp; yourself. 💙 You were amazing as… https://t.co/YejE5nEEg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliaJoyH Pockets should be a priority in every type of clothing for women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who thought this was a good idea for Rkelly to do this interview? #RKelly]]></document></documents></author>