<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RepCarolMiller it pains me😝🤣. Jim Jordan protects pedophiles and she crying about child separation 🤬🤬.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got to watch Ralph Breaks the Internet. It was fun, had a little something in my eye at the end. #imnotcryingyourecrying]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a tax payer as we all are. If IRS determines Trump avoided paying his taxes properties, then the Government shou… https://t.co/vt4TMklxku]]></document><document><![CDATA[#decisions #decisionsdecisions #oops #valentinesday #pregnant #joedamico #thehostoflasvegas @ Spanish Trail Country… https://t.co/uSjkI06StU]]></document><document><![CDATA[went to the Cheesecake Factory tonight despite all of my obligations, not impressed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jstrachm @merfe05 If I’m Jordan, I make him stay there until he hits one, even if that means leaving him til next year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of the morning shadows to the sunny Storm Peak summit. #sun #ski #skiing #snow #steamboatsprings… https://t.co/s5BEZAV9ZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowmageddon has past and the Nielsen RE Group is excited to announce its newest #milliondollarlisting in Newcastle… https://t.co/DpDVPuLOzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day4: I have accepted a challenge from @Coach_EWood to post #7BooksILove no explanation, no reviews-just cover(s).… https://t.co/U0m4G7UNs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing to see here, just waiting for @genitorturers @RealLordsOfAcid in chicago https://t.co/PHBC6GYwSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FSUeyedoc “Built out of love, made for the water Ran her for years, till the transom got rotten A piece of my chil… https://t.co/AlhX762WN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[For as long as I've been riding the Muni 5 Fulton bus it's jogged a dogleg from Fulton to McAllister on one block o… https://t.co/vXqb3tqfx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This city about to get crazy for @NBAAllStar #NBAAllStar⁠ ⁠. Everyone be safe, allow yourself more time when going… https://t.co/PoBDQNN1DL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuicoToro @IlhanMN I live in her district in Minneapolis. I’ll try to make sure she gets the message that she’s no… https://t.co/iahpsGltzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahNRO Oh please.  Are you saying that both Bushes, the Clintons in Obama giving N Korea food, oil, and more whi… https://t.co/vfkGDv83tX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brannon McManus gets us a 10-minute timeout, inadvertently, last night. @GopherHockey @TheRinkLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4uConservatives @PoisonIffy Nearly exactly correct. It should read "... tens of millions..."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Myself and @DerekDuke25 interviewed King and Morris yesterday at #TheOpening for @Heartland_CS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lakers if I wanted to watch an unmitigated disaster I’d tune into the trump administration]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Well that’s just great, you’re now going to be trolled for poor dietary choices “Carbs are evil!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[A classic movie scene, Akroyd, John Belushi and James Brown, have you seen the light? https://t.co/BQ9fZOyaqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Neoavatara I can’t ever hate on The Worm. Had an interesting meeting with him in 2004 or so when he used to own a bar in Huntington Beach]]></document><document><![CDATA[The meaning of life is whatever that is preventing you from killing yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s look #ootd #dailypic#picoftheday#guystyle#gentelmanstyle #instafashion #instastyle#estilo#mystyle #instagay… https://t.co/W3RF8kkHB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to experience a truly magical restaurant, they should get a reservation at #elevenmadisonpark. Trul… https://t.co/zSViy4qk6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost feel bad for the ass whipping Vandy is going to get tomorrow..almost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbwilljr Smell that? That's the shit baked in the system. We will see how much of that he serves but this is a punch to the gut.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPol @natgeowild I saw a Tony Packo’s mug on one of your counters. You should sign one of their buns - Klinger would approve. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just look at the list of those the clown tagged and you will understand how deep the rot among our youths is,the id… https://t.co/DuxmygznLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@king_mk2012 @MrDaltonDomino That’s a sexual harassment allegation just waiting to happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachLashSr From an educator in the district, I’ve been told that the plan is to matriculate freshmen to the high… https://t.co/dSewOnBKNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[When brittany murata   gave me my fan pack  smile I love it . I love this collage too it  so nice @brittanymurata… https://t.co/EPXOnILJBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarah__Reynolds @DailyCaller Yeah and protect this buphon https://t.co/UE0efn9GZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we know how this guy ran Casinos into the ground... morons should not be given the helm of Companies.  Morons s… https://t.co/bDredZjRau]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of y’all need to stop hypin me up because then i feel like i’m decent looking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panthers I know not many will be able to be there in person, but if you see our guys today around school let them k… https://t.co/otg01laI6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demeieus Williams with the steal and TO for @_WildcatHoops.  They have possession down 1.  55-54 w/ 1:02 left.… https://t.co/LcyvLcjzeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missmayn Are we allowed to say that some Blue Lives matter less than others?]]></document><document><![CDATA[After giving up a two goal lead, Nic Dowd gives the Caps the lead again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vladimirala1_gv #TorrealbaALa1 espero ver a Jorge Rodríguez con su circo y sus 20 mil cajas clap en Cucuta ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GunOwner2 @shenanigans052 @TomHolliday7 @_RainyDayWoman @davidhogg111 @marcorubio @noNRAmoney Apparently it’s a “M… https://t.co/1w6ZPmQpdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Super Sap by @TreeHouseBrewCo @ The Pour House — https://t.co/z18pJuQsBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry Judge. I disagree..                                                          Fox News's Napolitano: Trump can… https://t.co/7SiFsEf6AT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm generally a let the scientists science guy, but in this case...maybe we shouldn't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drphilDONTEhue This reason No. Uno, then on Saturday these fools congregate and make believe they in the Tour de F… https://t.co/xBK2iduB0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Americanush Some times u need to give up and it’s so painful u don’t know y but at the end the real happy u will c… https://t.co/k1j2aaQI3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some interesting 👀’s: The 25 most viewed sports media brands in social video. (via 2018 VideoAce Winners Guide) (HT… https://t.co/18u6M21BR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A 9-0 Jones County run opens a 24-10 lead over Corsica/Stickney in the 2nd wuarter https://t.co/o4G8D78BxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thinkingpoker @NittyJayTD @LivePokerRoom And on a positive note, now you can bankroll my Main Event take down for a 50/50 take!😎😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Robert Half Technology team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/nh46vADjh9 #IT #Dallas, TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green lighting the shit out of this move. Mikey Mo is a gem and a world treasure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRochaSays @RottenTomatoes Did you actually read the “negative” comments that were left about this movie?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes we gotta clap back at niggas..😂 https://t.co/OgKxkkWswZ #YBCENT https://t.co/nrezUaLgdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bergerkg @nheckenberger Great picture! Congrats on making it to that level!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Word of mouth is everything in sales.... @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/6q2oHQn4xX]]></document><document><![CDATA[walking around new york beat me tf up. i guess that’s why they call it battery park https://t.co/jYFAa2vBqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hasanthehun “Letting him get away with everything?” Joe Rogan is not a journalist. It’s an entertainment podcast, not a NY Times exclusive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@creepybranson @PromoteHorror @FreddysMuse @1carolinagirl @bringbackfear @HorrorMovies @TommyDoyle47… https://t.co/yRZNirz1yM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronBelton14 @espn975 He thinks manu was the best spur ever after Timmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m noticing a lack of Sting Rays in Googles Steve Irwin tribute #TooSoon?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fridayfunny #notreallyfunny @ Holt Physical Therapy &amp; Performance Training https://t.co/q9BaGOSyex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Searching for the real answers. #platano #iosdeveloper @ C4Q https://t.co/JNto2NiIHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what?! I’ll give credit where it’s due:   That’s a beautiful kick from Asuka!  #WWEFastlane   https://t.co/7awWeX4pEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_Kay3 Damn straight, I’m not getting into it anymore lol but Dirk got the best revenge imaginable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngeldebritoOk @ulisesjaitt @rialjorge @NatachaJaitt Dicho sea de paso ... @rialjorge hablando del cuidado de la f… https://t.co/JPIWTwST7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what it’s hella true “ some “ people are ungrateful for the “things” they get from others....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryRadnich I’m so sorry. Sending prayers of comfort to you and family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One batter, one K for Taylor McQuillin. Solid start for the Arizona pitcher.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pastor Vetrano beginning #ALSS 2019 with worship this morning with confession and absolution. https://t.co/fiIYe8s49c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndrew_lawrence Why hasn't everyone realized by now that Republicans never say or do anything wrong?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CameronMaybin Push thru it heads up take your medicine and move on your a good guy Cam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN If one uses that excuse for Omar, then to be fair, it should be applied to everyone.  However, her words were… https://t.co/d4b1ODr4Et]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/7XFpo4viv2 Verizon Customer Service Phone Number 1 (855) 431-9111 is free… https://t.co/sfGYEaMkjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brownrobin64 I don’t disagree w/you there, but that seems to have already been decided for us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jenn19Trump454545  once again this little girl talks crap Bernie and a ACO loves what's going on in Venezuela this is socialism at its best]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's WOR time stamps makes it look like Dave discusses his Donahue appearance for an entire hour and my body is ready.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well the day matches the mood.  I was let go of what was the best job I’ve ever had yesterday.  They need to cut ex… https://t.co/e7Y2mf9pLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[So cute @SashaBanksWWE #LegitBoss #imtheboss #BossNHugConnection https://t.co/GfjT8kzJ5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arriba que se viene @FirmaEspn  junto a @EJerezESPN @vikingomartell por @ESPNDRadio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarijuanaPolicy @cannabis_times Shouldn’t our Congress be leading our country instead of following our states .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought several items from the @The_SecretStash eBay store. They ship super fast, everything arrived well packed i… https://t.co/8yUdRg5JG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Club América y Club Monarcas Morelia han llegado al estadio José María Morelos y Pavón.   #S13mpreElMásGrande🏆 #PorElBiCAmpeonato💛💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRiffRepeater Thanks! It’s annoying &amp; I haven’t found a way to keep one or two videos on my account 😟]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd be more than happy to just take a class in how to earn a living wage in academia tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  Its still early as a whistle but not for Robert Kraft.. under the @NFL rules.. his possible .. charges and pe… https://t.co/uVp3gWRi7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GenZ is truly the "digital generation. 91 % of #GenZ use a digital platform which has heightened its importance to… https://t.co/FFEt7O7wx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacmupJim @Haudenschild_17 @MarshallRacing_ Amen Bro, they are our future. Good man Mr. 🇨🇦]]></document><document><![CDATA[being successful at 21 is something I never thought I would be, im so happy 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AiG It’s no more wicked than any other generation, actually it is less wicked. Holy rollers cant stand for people… https://t.co/wVjwZiA1vg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rattlesnake. Copperhead.   Phoenix ✅ 🌵 @ ISM Raceway https://t.co/V6gYyLfLrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vhslreference Good win for the safety school. Just make sure the records of my state title stay online, and you ca… https://t.co/UPOMzWfwto]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re right there in @ManeatGrass territory, that would be bucket list esque 🎶🎶🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just looked at my pay check from LMH and I'm still shocked what 3 days off work looks like there. 🤑💸💸]]></document><document><![CDATA[4-0 Usman over Woodley going into the 5th  #UFC235   https://t.co/9yzNyHlHwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only reason i know that man had a balenciaga hat is i was at this Grammy afterparty and going oh wow interesting ch… https://t.co/Bi04eKGiJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[How far from the trail does one need to step so as to avoid mudding up their shoes? Then how many steps does one ne… https://t.co/LUCmKyagVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kind Of Odd To See TV Ad For Cadbury Eggs, While It’s Below Freezing Outside! https://t.co/r0JX0Bs2Fp]]></document><document><![CDATA[They both look like freaks of nature. They had too much plastic surgery. Halloween is over ladies]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHO’S WORSE PEOPLE WHO CLAP AT THE END OF A MOVIE OR AT THE END OF A FLIGHT?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re still sleeping, you’re already behind your competition. GET UP AND GO GET IT! #BeGreat #ODAAT 🎯🏈]]></document></documents></author>