<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@awalkermusic @krassenstein @Outback @ZeroWaterFilter @Progressive @CapitalOne @mitsucars @GreatCallInc @onepeloton… https://t.co/ql8Qahytz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[URGENT UPDATE: @jamescharles is nominated for the #ShortyAwards! We can help him win by voting now - Let’s do it!! https://t.co/dLzSz8v8Vm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You just can’t let go that Hillary really beat you can you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @go_watkins this song is stuck in my head! One more day before a much needed break! #HoldOnForOneMoreDay… https://t.co/A1iqGge8Le]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a rumor that Hannah B is the next bachelorette and I. am. here. for. it. @BachelorABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing white Anne Klein Dress, beige JJill duster #wearitnow #fashionable #weardresses #stylish #fashionblogger… https://t.co/HmkSbSCCey]]></document><document><![CDATA[No filter needed, that cold and windy!!  #snow @ Silver Mountian Ski Resort https://t.co/S7Goc4SsKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did I not show up in the security monitor?  I was standing right there in the middle.   Something is seriously… https://t.co/Hc53gzQtEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carodlm @icircpremiere L'entrevue était très bonne! Un parcours différent et donne espoir à ceux qui se pose la qu… https://t.co/GsCf84R97Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[She should be president. Thanks, Pennsylvania, Michigan and my home state of Wisconsin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reallikeastorm y’all killed it with just three of you! kentlikastorm was definitely missed! May he and the rest of… https://t.co/dZncM6E59Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tend to spiral into anxiety and get really worked up over my future, but then I remember I’m still in my 20s with… https://t.co/wEFlOQy2Iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realizing you were wrong is the worst. Especially when it’s way too late]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian You are common and it takes no effort to look like you. Nobody wants to spend that much money 💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarrieAnne1177 @AndrewPollackFL @realDonaldTrump You mean stop resisting and become little koolaid drinking puppet… https://t.co/n05DqhFhlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love a beautiful floral kimono and for spring pair it with some denim shorts or double it for a cute coverup for… https://t.co/OJiF4Nj6iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you #EXOLs! I wrote a blog for @Patreon #patrons with my candid thoughts leading up to @weareoneEXO #Baekhyun… https://t.co/0ocZCTqOYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zambranitis @OdalhyaFernandz Jajaja es q no hayan q hacer ni decir esos ridiculous 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexwhittemore @tindie Yes indeedy. It is toner transfer. It took me several tries and some experiments to get it… https://t.co/TgmBnVaa21]]></document><document><![CDATA[my new glasses come in on monday and it’s sad how excited i am about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[#eyespiration @hyattregencysf #earlymorning #quiet #onlyinsf #sfwc19 @ Hyatt Regency San Francisco https://t.co/2PF3MVo2gW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign this petition &amp; urge Zimbabwe to halt their shipment of 35 stolen baby elephants to China!  #care2 https://t.co/aknzED438X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APDiploWriter You would have experienced genocide and likely retaliation from the war Dunford was trying to start… https://t.co/L8Wmr3KoSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCPhiladelphia @Telemundo62 proud to be passing forward the mentoring  we’ve received in this thrilling business… https://t.co/GWsAPc7NbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorrectWinger What is a Primary list??? This AOC Person is a pushy ignorant little immature girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Different Oysters, Same Feeling! charliebrown87 @estelanyc thedutchnyc #TBT @ Estela https://t.co/NbxHqdtYHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nouratowel They can be big mad. Just they get big mad waiting for a soda in the ED.]]></document><document><![CDATA[rando at the bar: did you finish that whole pitcher by yourself   me: yes  rando: that’s badass... especially becau… https://t.co/b9bqQUGnCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still haven’t watched the Masked Singer and probably won’t but T-Pain’s Tiny Desk Concert remains the epitome of… https://t.co/cYa5S9wKfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone has the right to a proper trial. No one has the right to a perfect trial.  -- Justice McLachlin  Canadia… https://t.co/ALaq8PPZES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, have yourself a beautiful day!  #GoodMorningAmerica #goodmorning #TuesdayThoughts #TuesdayMotivation… https://t.co/e6LbhCWP7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[El Salvador has an information access law, but there’s no real culture of transparency, which makes investigations… https://t.co/jQhzPwwwsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting my baby to sleep but I think she putting me to sleep instead 😴😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonOfGodAndMan @erinscafe If that had been the case, he would’ve been a National Merit Scholar…and we know that didn’t happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #CustomerService job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Team Member (… https://t.co/GcTBJi32sg]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and if all else fails, hang on to the wall while you call 911! #femurfracture]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPENING NOW: Audrain County emergency crews working on a natural gas pipeline explosion 1 mile north of Mexico.… https://t.co/y6Y7iwfWBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esto en Cócorit. La fiesta de los libros. 29, 30, 31 de Marzo 2019. Asiste aprende y diviértete. https://t.co/Ka8Revt984]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE WON!  The Amalgamated got best world music album at the San Diego music awards!!!! #sandiego #sandiegomusic… https://t.co/lAJRR7Igha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our blessings are presenting its self slowly but surly 😍❣️ thank u God for u never disappoint #GodIsGood… https://t.co/eKKw9WodIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADAMDEVINE Loved it! So great to see you both together again on screen...don't let this be the last time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjakeberg @itsGalenMiller What is this cat's problem? 1) he got caught and now he is scared about going to the h… https://t.co/wO2CLn5xSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[12 days left until baby:   It’s hard to breath. I have no energy. My back hurts terribly. I can’t walk normal I jus… https://t.co/fvx9R0biPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk man I’m pretty sure my mom put my on birt my control bc my periods were really bad..... also how the fuck does… https://t.co/1rLcrAymTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonaKAbdi  How did u get on world news tonight???? Are u still on ch5?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKinkhabwala No one said that they need to be friends. I work next to a lot of people that I don’t necessarily lik… https://t.co/mxhhyYO95c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen Are you aware that the Atlantic Council is planning to colour code the media?]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was your last chance so I hope you never decide you want another one. Case closed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coinbase: “Neutrino’s technology is the best we’ve encountered in this space."  Chainalysis and Elliptic: https://t.co/tHDq1ziE1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbiefaulk247 And for what purpose. You teach your children to be..........]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyhenrymedium @hollyrpeete Does location really have major impact for how easy (or not) it is for you? Like the mo… https://t.co/U624lszYfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAMSUMMERWALKER I’m trying my hardest to win these tickets because all the shows was sold out but I probably won’t… https://t.co/uWHJq30ZJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want my first child to also be my man first child so we can go through the experience together 😩❤️🤞🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you kindly for joining us! It is always a pleasure to see my friend, Kandi! 🏳️‍🌈]]></document><document><![CDATA[💯 this! I also include administration and auxiliary staff. Kids remember. Their parents remember too!… https://t.co/xV76sZ804j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Gambit Sorry, but the jury got it wrong.  There was a VAST conspiracy going on regarding the Kennedy assassina… https://t.co/GKoEAx5VeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaheenfatemi @Barbi__P How is that a Shame? Trump is the BIGGEST HYPOCRITE KNOWN ON THE PLANET TODAY! 🐷🐽🐷🐽🐷🐽🐷🐽🐷🐽🐷… https://t.co/uSMqdSgYH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigRSawyer If not in this life they'll pay for it in the next. Straight up evil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[stop. acting. like. CDs. have. two. sides. they. aren’t. cassettes!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fue una gran presentación, pero que 🐕🐻 con los presentadores, se entiende que quizá no hablen inglés fluido pero mí… https://t.co/WH49hiWdWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to hear @NatVanH talk about bilingual journalism as a tool for social justice #UHGlobalCom19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mathinthemitten Today’s conversation: C: Stop mathing me! Me: I will never stop mathing you.   M: It’s true she won’t ever stop.  #i❤️math]]></document><document><![CDATA[@L61Bx I’m not a fan of her either. I’ve tried to give her a chance but she’s made it hard. But she’s not running f… https://t.co/Oste24texB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My valentine’s day plans consist of studying for test and then failing the next day :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk The Constitution creates and establishes the process of impeachment. The law you dragged off of Goo… https://t.co/XZr7QxaJUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brooklyn 99 es mi serie favorita de comedia de todos los tiempos, tiene el mejor humor del mundo @AndySamberg es un… https://t.co/JKnTxfe8YM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @RobertJohnDavi @JussieSmollett @realDonaldTrump Smart boy]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you show zero effort while texting me... just don’t text me. i don’t fw lame ass, couple word responses. that shit is wasting my time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriasSecret my account keeps getting hacked with you guys buying electronic gift cards. I’ve contacted your cu… https://t.co/A8W3WIjxqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Design! Check out this Society6 post by Betzel Creative (@betzelcreative) called "Cute Baby Dino"… https://t.co/GBwHtAbyLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy V-Day aka the 21st anniversary of my conception (I was due November 14 but my mom was late 5 days) so celebrate accordingly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelinaLozano9 Mama is here. It is, what it is. It'll be hard but, you'll get through it... you're tough💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[i get so butthurt when people ignore me yet i continue to ignore people constantly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw @mmckinnon It does and I’m more than disappointed that GOP Senators hate Trump more than they love this country!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oprah @Sothebys @missporters Monique was right about you-I thanked God that I never went to your "church"! You're… https://t.co/EQphKeTTH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sinead_ryan @GabbyMonaghan Disagree. There's no way that all facts/details have been published]]></document><document><![CDATA[• N E W to the c r e w • we are heading home today!! #AidenBennett #littleman #newtothecrew #perfection #2daysold… https://t.co/Hvh1cCxsjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that's my kind of box of chocolates!! Happy Valentines Day! ♥️🧸💐 @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/Z6j0mogGe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjs1951 @chrislhayes Autonomous sensory meridian response (really, I googled it!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched the product demo for Samsung fold unveil   The folding.  The price.   The multiple app use and split… https://t.co/RNmx34Igsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a broken off bit of a shoelace at the top of an escalator...that's the nightmare! 😬😬😬😬😬 https://t.co/jyIlpJlw2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Counting a state as “visited” doesn’t count unless you’ve peed there. I’ve visited 45. (Finn’s visited about 30 I t… https://t.co/DLqZ1hnjFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unlvlibraries Great to have Kwame Alexander at our Literature Conference.  And better yet to see so many children… https://t.co/0olzDtEMad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardF44411321 @FCDFtweets @pnjaban The President’s name is Donald Trump We respect our President in addressing him as President Trump .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chayab77 ... well, something v kind about how no matter what, if I’m in this for the long haul, no one work will m… https://t.co/zVQ99rV2ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish you were here with me 😍😘 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/s8pjED7pwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch Ferris Bueller’s Day Off with your significant other.... if it doesn’t work, try one more time (personal experience)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jury duty tomorrow.... the only thing that will get me through the day will be knowing I get to see @colton later t… https://t.co/XQnUaeHQqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JScelza Many things like this are unavoidable as a a lady sci unfortunately]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maurice_Grier @langstonwertzjr @dub_lions @AKbasketball @NCHSAA Finally a truthful message]]></document><document><![CDATA[{Most Important Episode of the Entire Season} 🎧 SOUND ON  In honor of International Women’s Day #IWD2019, we releas… https://t.co/iJTp8j3fVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hcyang0115 @29rain I'm allway right  dont think  and still be discussing  by her remember  this is pretentious]]></document><document><![CDATA[Politicians like Feinstein created this ignorant monster...now it’s trying to eat her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krqe_headlines That’s pure consideration of others. I really admire admire this man.  I would like to think others are like him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wholesale Seamless Workout Leggings and Tights https://t.co/vZEEgG7qPh #seamlessleggingswholesale #leggings… https://t.co/dy7hJwUREb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLeftWingCafe @ileana2018 @David_Leavitt Norway 4th wealthiest nation world per capita with 1/2 pop NYC; U.S. ra… https://t.co/l9IQHYYKuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luluHru @TammyMa47798225 @JohnSandersSr @SteveMcCall10 @Chrisca15442861 @stl900 @garway95 @ROHLL5 @TigerLetsRoll… https://t.co/CGoxZOXGQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antimike43 I agree. She stated a fact, not hate. You know that fool in office is stupid. I saw the documentary. Fo… https://t.co/RSHUJh4UOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the GREENBERGS and the the wrestlers #GHS #roadtrippin s#chocolateibarra #foodie  #love #paintedladies… https://t.co/tI7hCJuBCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mom just said “the only way to handle a bully is to bully them back” 😂😂😂]]></document></documents></author>