<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@yellingstopAL But allowing anyone to mark it still seems odd, but I know people put births and marriages in it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna go to my momma house and cry on her like I used to do when I was lil 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will all you weathermen start talking about spring in three weeks. Boston Red Sox debut their 9 game road trip on M… https://t.co/TIxTRFnTn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chocolate Raspberry Layer Cake https://t.co/3JXO0RYCxR via @MomLovesBaking]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hardest part of working 3-11s is honestly trying to fall asleep afterwards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VixenVegas @goodenough_fu @balbuen5 @DeannGoss @HPL_JDeLaughter @GreatCthulhu420 @owner_swm @LadyBlackTear… https://t.co/ODsGCWbMYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to these amazing 3 for letting me join them on stage at #sxsw today for a conversation about creating “sound… https://t.co/UDy5QFBzvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielHeithorn @ThreddyTheTrex @TashasEv According to @BerndVerst this ^ is the closest 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can find me in the saddle at @thecycleloftgso tomorrow morning... I think I may need to take a load off my feet… https://t.co/A9SrEU12RU]]></document><document><![CDATA[At @traderjoes: 6 yo: “Can I have a sample?” TJ’s sample lady: “What’s the magic word?” 6 yo: 🤔  6 yo: “✨Abracadabra?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AviraMenachem Are you a fake liberal? You literally make no sense. Or your a trump bot posing as a lib]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will’s already messed up by picking a bright pink color instead of black]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen I wish someone would have told my parents this back in the day :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ♥️ is forever so grateful!! 🙌🏻 #littlestoriesofmylife 💕 @ Springfield, Missouri https://t.co/uTpFI5k6Cf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieDaniels My kids walk around school with a picture identification.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulStamets researching treatment options for family member with glioblastoma, any insight greatly appreciated]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancy_hamm1 @DaveSchreiber3 @Solmemes1 @Intelligencia76 @ChrisBragdon @_IamAnita_D @heyitsCarolyn @Rbigzs… https://t.co/erKgaX4TP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelmcgee @KristyT @grlalx @WesOHaire At this point I’m just counting on one of you to be the plug and bring me… https://t.co/joo400FIjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The secret to success..."Draw a circle around yourself first... and make sure you are really happy with yourself."… https://t.co/y7E53jmQzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Pix3M_ @BleedingFool I'm saying if hairy legs are a surprise, naked cyclists would freak you out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_houstonian @realDonaldTrump Trump rubbed salt in a wound that had almost scabbed over for absolutely no reason.… https://t.co/EkPCrJdOwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[”Don't stop. Prove them wrong.” - wise words from a family member. Family doesn't always have to be blood-related but LOVE. Remember that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Urban_Wolf I'm horrified! This sick fucker dressed his dog up in costumes, raped her over and over using sex toys… https://t.co/i145e9ldY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@galelinn I’m sure if you look up momo video or something it’ll come up!! Apparently they were disguising like cart… https://t.co/5x0cltAClg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 12:36 AM &amp; instead of sleeping all I can do is lay awake thinking about how excited I am to eat my lunch tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CeDemocratico le tiene ya lista una embajada o consulado así sea en la puta mierda ! Pero no creo que pague cárcel… https://t.co/edGRNIn14X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw Joe B for the first time w my girl! Wow!! What a genius! He sounded like Stevie Ray Vaughn,  Buddy Guy, Eddie V… https://t.co/j4iF3IXAy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hobiesmalls Sometimes is good to cry. Whatever is your problem you will find a solution]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my practicing what I would say in arguments when I’m in the shower]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally talk to no one so when my baby mad at me and not texting my phone my shit be dead fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donniedanko5 Thanks for reminding me, gotta go do my insta clean out now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kayla Reign (@KaylaReignXXX) is now advertising in Atlanta! https://t.co/y2KGiCw7kA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was really struggling to get out of bed for the gym then I saw that my baby cousins were at my grandmas.... boy I… https://t.co/RnsuplV9VZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr I'm old enough to remember when Americans would have a huge problem with a president who lies cheat… https://t.co/ltY4hQKm23]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good news is I extended my stay til Sunday cuz ain’t no way I’m leaving tomorrow hell. Tonight was supposed to be l… https://t.co/0UgCcsJaAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msinsulindpndnt 2/2 If that doesn't work, try https://t.co/mcMT9FkP6p. You sign up for free, it gets you discounts… https://t.co/DnM0uaEEId]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you up, possibly getting ready for your Church? Join me for some Praise and Worship! @ImpactChurchJax https://t.co/qvyYj7XydT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcgillu Dean of Students is here at #JackSummit to y’all #Mentalhealth SOLUTIONS.   Thank you @CMBuddle for joinin… https://t.co/QevpExBtxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bank5clo5ed Woo! Well I’ll be there girl! My mom has literally wanted to take me for like 25 yrs 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheProfitCNBC @RealityAwardsTV Hope we win! #TheProfit https://t.co/modNW2wX1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister did an #ancestrydotcom #dnatesting and these were the results. I am actually surprised about the Great Br… https://t.co/Xfwdt4sWcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASK_Esq29 @Mikel_Jollett @pxcaballero Yesh, right. One of the things that can not be left up to the states is if t… https://t.co/YS1HBwB8rG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4 challenge  from @CPurposeSlater she challenged me to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no revie… https://t.co/OhxqkI4IOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Srpska zastava na plaži u LA @ Santa Monica Pier https://t.co/KZOciZJpcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PBOTinfo’s @pkoonce delivers on the #seabikes / #pdxbikds rivalry: “Seattle just timed signals for 25mph downtown—… https://t.co/caz3IZAAi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Why are we even talking about this garbage. Push the real story the clintons, Obama and co this is the… https://t.co/izu5HpVWcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a hot minute since I did a Taco Tuesday post. But I would be remised if I didn’t mention these delectable… https://t.co/YncjJapue3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dormí 3 horas nadamas, estoy dopada, no he comido y tengo una fiesta a la cual no quiero faltar mood https://t.co/VwCweoswXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for all details but agree - sex trafficking young women is the story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Después de que @Spotify saliera de compras, @pandora mueve ficha con los podcasts con Pandora Stories]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love playing these and watching my cat prowl looking  for the intruding kitty!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also from @mubi: CLÉO FROM 5 TO 7 through Agnès Varda's Paris. https://t.co/VIHy6Jqh5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tall praising models who show their arm hair? I do that every day. Carry on 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking Cuba, Venezuela, Syria...   vientos de cambio... y North Korea?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llegué temprano a mi training para coger un power nap en el estacionamiento.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nighttime walking earbud volume level is somewhere between getting lost in the music and thwarting potential muggings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She looks so sad leaving him and the egg. He looks so lonely all by himself 😢 #Dynasties]]></document><document><![CDATA[@voss651 @Everytown @kharyp @MomsDemand Prob. Yet,  Sen CS, as minor lead, can call 4 a vote, so we can see where e… https://t.co/sbD5UW76hY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of fun on Presidents Day!!! No Days off for those who are committed! @MaynardKeiffer #keepurdreamsbig #earnit https://t.co/2EDWbBzBm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[💖 Happy #MakeupMonday! This natural look is perfect for a date night or girls night out. Makeup application by Elli… https://t.co/zZEKYuQwfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steczar Ok got ya. Blueger and Trotman would have to be the first sent down because they were emergency. Can be re… https://t.co/e8wIC8cP36]]></document><document><![CDATA[I modge podge and glitter my new sign!😂😂 ghetto as hell but I got to do what I got to do! At least I got a little a… https://t.co/GFDOG5EvEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friend: I’m driving to Nebraska over spring break Me: oh cool are you going to Las Vegas?? Friend: https://t.co/1tfw1bWBkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RHOBH. Of course Dorit.  It’s all about you and you. God Forbid you ask about your friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mickelodoole @tnt_dad @Rand765624692 @siresandblue @Razorsmack1 @Briteeye777 @TrumpmyPre @luluHru @Danie1607… https://t.co/KpBi0sznnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaveJersey @GovMurphy U R dumb simply creatures https://t.co/0ABQcpQild]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soigne_Metaphor I think people are just easily infatuated by things that are out of the stereotypical norm. What t… https://t.co/jE3jJndrWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[All because I do know the truth and understand I was setup to destroy myself because they knew I was going to die f… https://t.co/lR8sWQABTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukePerryIII. There aren't words.  Theres just not but you are an amazing person and I hope that your family gets… https://t.co/tV64Gws5oj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill..my deepest sympathy. You can have peace knowing that one day u will see ur mother again. She is an angel in t… https://t.co/RBswZBGwiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/yM9CxahqMt… https://t.co/LJTVm29DNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carapie @krassenstein Some people I guess know it, I know it. Some people, some very fine people know it, but I qu… https://t.co/htEQzmHJXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please meet these lovely Swifties @taylornation13 @taylorswift13  @AshHettenhausen @repudrama @repqueen_13… https://t.co/wdj0yYXZqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff WHEN were you elected GOD? YOU HAVE THE ABILITY to determine exactly what is in a persons heart and… https://t.co/Fk5OGSwF6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaceForTheWH @K_JeanPierre Jr is a follower and not too bright-I vote Javanka]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/7Vm5gpQF2R What 2020 is about is whether we have health care or we don't. The rest of the rhetoric, th… https://t.co/YEHbHhJcdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both honored and horrified by the number of people who have messaged this to me to make sure I didn’t miss it. It’s… https://t.co/p9Owe5mM36]]></document><document><![CDATA[Officially going home for @BeccaMcc18’s bachelorette in April 🎉 https://t.co/0ga4sP5y3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Christopher Palme as my NC School Hero. You can vote daily. don't forget to share! https://t.co/4qCpIARuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates Here’s Mika: she just turned 10, so this was her challenge photo #LoveYourPetDay https://t.co/b5nFIW09cB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why yall stress over Valentine’s Day so much, you’re literally single the other 364 days too. Chill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uhitscaitlin I remember the password and everything but my account was deleted cause it’s been so long]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keith5179  Larry Bird - The Fall-away (fadeaway) https://t.co/RHxP5Rglpb via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sha_fiyah @xMegatronBarb @Deitycomplex_ @GodlessOne1 @Da_geee_man @saiahhhhhh @CGsaidso @Chisom_baskkard… https://t.co/OsXv03mgEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought a new dress. Now to decide whether “Manic Pixie Bodycon Spinster” is a good look for one day of 221b Con...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te Perdiste De Un 14 De Febrero Que Comienza El Mes De Enero Y Se Renueva El Año Nuevo Te Perdiste De Lo Que No Encontrarás... 😙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimash_usa I saw next weeks #WorldsBest . I was shocked by what appeared as something bad. I woke up this morning… https://t.co/sfFFJzNgt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a date for the first time in two months and I just keep thinking how much I miss my baby girl 😩😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @CrenshawCards for allowing us to attend house meetings! https://t.co/qbhoxkG4un]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogueSNRadvisor I will vote against Trump no matter who runs.  I do think we can do better than Bernie]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gop sitting back and doing nothing to stop trump so they can get re-elected are complicit. Did they run on “let… https://t.co/ADX8aZMwsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Photos for making you Laugh Such as Kids. #funniness #tee-hee #grin #farcical https://t.co/yDZ1RnB7eq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#awesome @RobertW48787695 @wecanmag @PrezesPan @DanielBrasilia @DavidLogan2020 @XandraXandraBX @GiselleMarks1… https://t.co/SGp1KsyVM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[god damn it’s 5 in the morning and the girls on the MEPS bus are so freaking annoying]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been known to do that a time or two...😉 #ReadersAreLeader last #ChildrenOfBloodAndBone #TeacherLibrarian… https://t.co/yHPnNLVQcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Uber, it’d be great if you could factor both weather and footwear in your #ExpressPOOL ‘s algorithm. Sincerely, #freezinginheels 🥶 👠]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/uWj8fkmMRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe people still think self care is literally just face masks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrcowan @SenSanders That still does not mean they should not pay taxes and create the most richest man in the worl… https://t.co/wl16WiSpG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Butterfly Center sues government to prevent border wall construction https://t.co/b5X9eZjEsr]]></document></documents></author>