<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@froquedm I was hoping in JLA, they'd play up the joke more when recruiting Aquaman.   Batman: Your dad is named Th… https://t.co/STiDOi2mWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand And yet you support open borders allowing drug and human trafficking across our national borders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Do not go where the path may lead, go instead where there is no path and leave a trail.” Ralph Waldo Emerson . .… https://t.co/g2jI9RoVx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stacieskelley @PaulSzoldra the cat was just sitting there, looking pleased with herself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning New York City! Where #supreme customers receive a stamp on their hand, wait in long lines and some gua… https://t.co/mJUCewJRSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[if u read this im free on thursday n would like to hang out. please respond to this n then hang out with me on thur… https://t.co/qHtwbKIMgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Lindsey Graham Went From Trump Skeptic to Trump Sidekick https://t.co/ECxlV4fjeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/WXtDg8Zz9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joehick58 Schlapp has repeatedly (often) demonstrated (shown) that he is not a smart person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[50 Cent says Trump Team offered him $500,000 JUST TO COME to the inauguration — which he refused.  "All money is no… https://t.co/m9b5PJn3FU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Modern Art  @lacma  #2019 #Travel #Mexico #Photography #Hobbies #Guadalajara #LA #China #Thailand #CarCulture #Art… https://t.co/E3CCWYXozI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night last Friday evening at the @milwaukeeart, sponsoring the 3rd Annual Veterans Light Up the Arts.  Glad o… https://t.co/XJpfHEe42P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuesaVerdades @donainesdsuarez @AccionNacional @katedelcastillo @Edd_Campe @NachoRgz Esta se vende con cualquiera]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been challenged by @JeffRodin to post pics of my 7 favorite books, no reviews needed. Each day, I'll challenge… https://t.co/RMM1tjKqOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASUNTO DE TIEMPO, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/KuCqZz78Cg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go to https://t.co/MUgtp9NTLy  they have a PayPal link on the home page.  I hope the fucktard that abused this kitt… https://t.co/MB5kR8lxex]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s .005%.  I’m counting @AaronRodgers12, @itsCrab, and ....  #WhoAreTheOthers??  https://t.co/ThVf9thgfT https://t.co/PLOy7jGfOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The two versions of this photo of our cats that @ZILLAMOROLL and I posted really say a lot about us. https://t.co/g27kc8tQCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little @bluejays Spring Training with Vlad Jr at the plate. Jays win 5-2 over the Pirates. Nicely done! @ Dunedin… https://t.co/VVb5I8ozsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meetings with folks that do what I don’t do make the milis beset believe I’m scheming]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kermit Davis said UK's "two young wings are fabulous (Herro and Keldon)" and the Rebels just couldn't stop PJ Washington in the second half.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, phenomenal play by @SwitchbacksFC. But all celebration goes to @ShaneMalcolm23. Well done my man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanSchemmel @ToeiAnimation @FUNimation You’re totally down for 20 more, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[These things happen when the entire team buys in, that W better open some eyes across baseball nation. Much success… https://t.co/0iNYRKz2Bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[im still over here trying to prove my own doubts wrong so i don’t need to hear yours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petermckinnon Being a fan of others is something natural such as I am a fan of you! Who are you a fan of? Such as… https://t.co/H1oFi7NP5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisarrant @Kris_Simon @Doncates @mikescigliano @blackem_art @ChrisEliopoulos @FrankTieri @AmandaRantsAlot… https://t.co/3fEGJ93OC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[2004: In a landmark federal court decision, the 9th U.S. Circuit Court sides with the Hemp Industries Association a… https://t.co/YuC8uVhOhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Maldito .@chavezcandanga. Malditos .@NicolasMaduro, el #chavismo, #FidelCastro, el gobierno cubano, el #comunismo,… https://t.co/hNXVdGP1ce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aplustexas This is inaccurate. Chaos isn’t invoked by school start dates. Earlier school start dates lead to earli… https://t.co/E1DMyRDh4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @KayleenTruex to post 7 books....I am taking a bit different angle.   I am posting seven books… https://t.co/KZPgSxC6nW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chatham High Students Attend Women &amp; Girls Business/STEM Career Workshop https://t.co/SWhNjU3xrX. #brainsandbrawn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arielhelwani No man that good-looking should also be a great fighter. There is karmic justice is in his inability to stay healthy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of 1Q. 2-Lewiston-Porter leads 7-Health Sciences 16-14. LP opened game on 10-0 run but HS as usual doesn't pani… https://t.co/qrMt6Mkd0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenWalke one thing that no one has really brought up is when Obi-Wan Kenobi is next to Kylo Ren in Battlefront 2 h… https://t.co/gdh2edJgan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FDRLST What is wrong with you? I thought that this might me a distasteful The Onion parador, but no, sadly it is n… https://t.co/0KeTqYDY1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FtBraggNC I laugh at demons now because they are metsll7c creations typically of titanium but once you crush the m… https://t.co/u2SxDQ4Z8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rishaleondra In my experience, artists usually 1) don’t have the time for it 2) assume their manager / PR / Etc wi… https://t.co/q04VnV0pS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rupertvaughan Not saying don’t investigate hate crimes. I’m saying the gigantic pile-on from press and celebrities… https://t.co/9W7fgP4aL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Long Island City, NY in Long Island City, NY https://t.co/ByicJ4AzSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning 🌈☀️🏞🖼❣️#goodmorning #good #morning @ Beaverton, Oregon https://t.co/TJjfeUQIE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamLover69 @BetoORourke Line the border with dodge rams, Beto president of Mexico 2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RalphPena1 @JimFree65 @ggreenwald @AOC I don't have the money, I'm just that sure they'll all win. You're clearly… https://t.co/57G78vWjFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN was it a "white wedding"?  #Incestuous #Illiterate #Incompetent Resign now... https://t.co/yO9MlpOAfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warmups, officials stretch and encouragement to watch the broadcast. ✔️✔️✔️  Red-hot @StonyBrookMBB in Durham today… https://t.co/MjBy3rpwM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO I'll tell you. Isnt it great to have all these keyboard warriors come after you. Saying things on… https://t.co/7bSIGwaY37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GSUniverse Here's what's new on Toonami this March: https://t.co/N3KfqrOoRU https://t.co/2zywgvMhC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReBourneAgain OMG their using sanity to face rico chet &amp; their using asuka on tv but not on ppv &amp; in an interview no less]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeCarrollAZ @whatznextfolks @TheDemocrats @realDonaldTrump The US Senate has declared it is legal to end this life AFTER it is born!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunset in #cheseborocanyon #hikingtrail in #agourahills. #Beautiful #hike with my #friends and my #sister. #hiking… https://t.co/lEMqjSnrd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[America's nuclear legacy in the Marshall Islands @President_Heine @kathykijiner  #BeingMicronesian https://t.co/ZkjaY9JXlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pulled up on my god father today #BigQueens #QGTM #LindenBlvd @ Christ the King Regional High School https://t.co/dlxKJgvU6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stupid dogs wake me at 3:45 am to go out. They come in and get right back to sleep.  Me? Not so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cgully27 @Mr_Wright_8 @wavydavey25 Ik y’all heard Dave say it was the practice round]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheResident  @ResidentFOX Very powerful episode tonight. Compliments to the writers, crew and outstanding cast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite bar at the airport is the one that has direct eyesight with my gate. I can order beers 🍻 until the very… https://t.co/FMApLrTzRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fat Tuesday fun - Drinking a Phat Ash Paczki by @Baffinbrewingco @ Baffin Brewing Company  — https://t.co/v70wFtPAr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiskeyAndSoba Hell no I love fries except skinny fries they are not my favorite and waffle fries those are like t… https://t.co/CTuMFWikbo]]></document><document><![CDATA[SÓLO GANAMOS CON PAPÁ, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/tiAq5Xkpgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey! Help me get money back from my last purchase on Wish. https://t.co/FbXp6lMvQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiLBPromos @OMAStormChasers @UniWatch @PhilHecken @Cut4 @darrenrovell @espn @MLByahoosports @MLBONFOX @MLBNetwork… https://t.co/bOw6rbX99C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had the worst dining experience @metro29diner in #ArlingtonVA. Been a customer here since they opened. Service… https://t.co/eR6x35HnLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of doctor-prescribed medication A, my child will be using medications B and C, based upon the expert assess… https://t.co/vmxgJyDosm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soria_moria Smitherenes is great stuff. I blind bought Anger, haven’t seen yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the nicest things I like when soldiers come home got bless and thank you for your service]]></document><document><![CDATA[BIG BEAR SE PREPARA !!  Marcell Ozuna 🇩🇴 realiza ejercicios de calentamiento en el complejo de entrenamientos de lo… https://t.co/urPS6GuSXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xavi_Bros Is that last statement MinTruth-approved? https://t.co/wNid79D44a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle Ok let's support the military, roads, better infrastructure they  make the country run smoother, mor… https://t.co/JzWaXYisfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattyMurray @SenatorCantwell Suck it up big girl. You don’t have a copyright on parliamentary maneuvers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The point of the “talking” stage is to get to know the person while keeping your options open.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does trying to prevent an already born child from dying impede a woman's health?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read his « Message to Garcia » and you’ll understand where our stubbornness comes from.  Thirteen Hubbards were on… https://t.co/FuyvraRBGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Designed to live for 90 days, Opportunity has been roving around Mars for my entire adult life, 15 years.  Sad to s… https://t.co/Fy5dxynzni]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phantasm director and filmmaking legend Don Coscarelli @ Aero Theatre https://t.co/h7ZisKT08H]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you carry your bros after they been talkin their shit on APEX https://t.co/ldXBF1aAXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CONDESCENDANT @patwhitenl @kerriclaireneil now. maybe it was in the story, but now i'm wondering why we're on the… https://t.co/DTnRcm2xAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewjudon @bigmike7772 @CalBear_G @AdamSchefter No, he's correct. Mack is far more valuable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliauci16 @universidad_uci @silvanouci @dcolome2010 @dellylien1 @Roexcy1 @Ismaray151 Valores ? Vivir ? Los unic… https://t.co/HVD2fzAYcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man has done so much for the world by inspiring thousands if not millions. Its time for us to be there for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st H stats: Ahmadu Sarnor leads all scorers with 100 points for Ranney. Scottie Lewis has 8 points for the Panther… https://t.co/HZsNK83Prl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crafting with friends and drinking cocktails!. I made a leather wristlet clutch to store documents under my motorcy… https://t.co/zAor22s8hR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gut wrenching stat I read today: 88% of students who say no adults from their church invested in their lives while… https://t.co/iluHUm4Xfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffRichie3 @baserunner0723 @NikonUSA @Astro_Zach @NASA_Nerd Plenty! https://t.co/wZ84ajPQoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever not feel yourself? Like it’s been weeks come on jay where you at]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchWeasel hi friend Mitch,  this picture isn’t sad; it’s zesty.  hope you’re enjoying the Stones climb back into… https://t.co/lS2vrEgL2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Keyofcminor @realDonaldTrump Obama was the worst President in American history a sell out to the world and Iran bribe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrote a special #ValentinesDay poem for all of you with a special guy in your life. 😍  Roses are red, Kylie Jenner’… https://t.co/7FM4wHFF16]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accidentally hit my dad with the “kk” and this happened 😂😂 https://t.co/Yu3WYH4UQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kodaklens Discernment bro ... many are called but few are chosen BUT GOD will show you whose on your team #grownwiththeclique]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TRUEKidsPRO @maureensheridan @realDonaldTrump 2-3% are violent criminals, but that’s 2-3% too many.And what about… https://t.co/x0cRM8lcUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a slew of batteries in stock. Shelves full. But not for long. Call tomorrow.  #toppost #sidepost #dualpost… https://t.co/DrzSAXCXaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SparkyKat_Lives @adamcbest Please tell me you didn't watch the whole thing. They took 10 seconds from me and I cal… https://t.co/KDHNxMInXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BostonStrong_34 @mattbarnesRHP will be disappointed. https://t.co/wJ9KDEU2UF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nategeraci it was nice catching up with you at #insideetfs.  It put me in mind to get caught up on your podcasts a… https://t.co/lny0qEJY5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LzLwsn @eeberquist A bath sheet is the only way to go forever and always.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sonically this Mark Trombino's magnum opus and a genre defining piece. The 'hits' are more Hughes-soundtrack than R… https://t.co/GJz2ZApb00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 @TuckerCarlson @maddow @NicolleDWallace @SRuhle @Lawrence @chrislhayes @HardballChris I will happily lose… https://t.co/2hlswDuGsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadly, Butler has been knocked out of the #FMA quiz bowl bracket, but #MSUM has advanced to the semifinals!… https://t.co/ffmceyqIP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/bt0Jtnfb6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelleyj89 @NikkiWadey @ericdier Poor Ben sitting there wishing he had a song]]></document></documents></author>