<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Regional Engineer Quigley and his staff are discussing IDOT's incendent management strategy at the District 1 ComCe… https://t.co/X64GKoYLRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DollyDeighton The 3 B’s of #SXSW  Burgers &amp; Brisket &amp; Beers   Hope all is well?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol John Crotty just said “absorb that contract” instead of “absorb that contact” while talking about Dion Waiters LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pulled up to my homie crib after work to pick sumn up. I left my car running, I got bike in the car and drove hom… https://t.co/RzPLyWyK9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice chance to win the Presidency you have here. Be a shame if something happened to it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The District will operate on a two-hour delay today, Friday, March 1, 2019.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s really sad that the @metpoliceuk arrested him. Isn’t there freedom of speech and freedom of religion in UK?]]></document><document><![CDATA[There were a few other people in my boat so the agent called customs down the hall and they told her they would sta… https://t.co/8gIJyNFKXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmcconnell54 @wbir Thank you Janice! Had a blast speaking with you both times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had The Flu With An Ear Infection All Week Since Saturday Night. Missed All Week At Work It Was Soo Bad. Finally St… https://t.co/IKA4r1QQIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ensayando explicación a mis nietos: Una vez en Col hubo una banda narcocriminal(Farc)q firmó un Acuerdo con un Pte… https://t.co/GlL7Wp8hAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird All this DISHONEST LIAR CORRUPTS COMPROMISED COMPLICIT ENABLERS SO CALLED WOMENS THAT ARE HELPING… https://t.co/K1DqkMh3VB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDeanP @allan_cheapshot It’s not. Sometimes it’s fun to make stuff up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Squad Feelin’ / #newlove #oldsoul #vibes w the #realest #realone emanbfendi #representationmatters #beauty +… https://t.co/udN2V31zQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a Great place to stroll and people watch and maybe take ina free show!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repymkalish Amazing to know both of you...by coincidence.  @dafna_m #SmallWorld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting fancy tonight.. (@ Flannigans in Coralville, IA) https://t.co/3KbEHNGO4y https://t.co/yBAHc57SKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Wrong again douchebag. Are you ever truthful about anything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swervin66 @ronwilliamswv @brithume Yeah great down payment without NAFTA. 5 years would pay for itself with the re… https://t.co/5z4xiTu8Qu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyFrankSmith @sarahwoodwriter @TomiLahren @realDonaldTrump Yeah I did so what.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys of summer are coming back... shot by @M_Andrew_Photog https://t.co/yxiCd00w2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reparations shouldn’t be apart of preaching the Gospel. It’s just flat out wrong! https://t.co/FtcHwRwBO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh by the way had a dream last night that Peach was back and it came with a new feature called “coin” and idk what… https://t.co/hJB8z1IqGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Fox News...the ugly step sister compared to othe princess networks. Should be disbanded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrainMashup Meth is bad but @AOC will give PETA Power if she has her way]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught a @Peticolas truck in the wild for the first time! Is it Saturday yet?#DTID https://t.co/vr9SuOksEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been stuck in this heavy traffic for like 30mins this is not that sweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week’s edition of #BrainsToGains. For more great content and information, follow themusclephd and join the Mus… https://t.co/9DW4JEJyKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My oldest of 3 daughters just started at @DCelite yesterday and I am not only happy about that, but happy about how… https://t.co/62VeUP5ja4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stalman At this point, I think you need a “Tim Apple” reference in order to get clicks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrismessina @rrhoover @travelyInvestor A Sprinter camper van would solve some of these housing issues 😉 Our house… https://t.co/koMrllEpPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guardian What kind of youth did the editor of this piece have that NOTHING stuck out to him about this headline?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACLU @ACLU counseling murder in broad daylight.  #InfanticideIsMurder  My how you have changed....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARONFOX I’m on the team of the guy that still has his helmet on in a fight. Any fight, no matter who it is Impicking the helmet!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't think I'm going to leave the house today. Got plenty "supplies" and @Vol_Hoops  play at noon. #geauxVols]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent around 15 hours on Nfinity and I have 8 bruises and my body is so sore from 1 full out on stage... #thisis30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wild Saturday nights on a college campus in student activities may consist of arranging a 72 pack of colored pencil… https://t.co/UjzURUxwar]]></document><document><![CDATA[News International:      A Surge in Women’s Mosques;     U.S. Peace Talks With Taliban Trip Over a Big Question: Wh… https://t.co/8HTjxXxpkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[why are we on the hook for a cleanup in marystown that should be on kiewit? #nlpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly Tell me again about how HRC was a national security threat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early Valentine #antivalentines #spectaclepic #standupcomedy #losangeles #marvista #valentines #love #hate #cupid… https://t.co/0K9nyXw6BZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it possible the patriarchy extends into a field as rational and objective as science? Or, maybey not so rational… https://t.co/UWFUfTELH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING - new episode @ABC “The Investigation” podcast - As Dems arm for more investigations, Trump insider Dave B… https://t.co/6RwAK0aJFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 white, 1 whole egg omelet with 2 oz mozzarella, spinach, jalapenos,  sweet onions,  Cherry Tomatoes, Avocado  wit… https://t.co/5807WHw0gy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Putty Hill Ave/Harford Road in Parkville, MD https://t.co/OJBW3gp2iQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hughhewitt You not talking about it would help. You have zero "non-political" credibility.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We see and hear you “ROYAAALS!!” Can’t stop, Won’t stop.💪🏾🏐🔥🦁🙏🏾    💙🖤@EMU_Athletics @emu_volleyball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Torts answering a phone call in the middle of his press conference just now is full on Torts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[felt obligated to do this, mood in sd this weekend for sure lmao #rihannabirthdaychallenge https://t.co/mJXBfvPO8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rvaisred @ChrisHSport @awaiters86 @IronPonyChef @USLChampionship Montreal slipped my mind, and I completely forgot about Minnesota.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmbrown09 @AGPennyPacker @ryanwhitney6 Yeah that's the coldest take I've heard in awhile]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohhmik @brentfreshwater @Pens_Lynn @JodN20 @jhartlov @BuffBills53 @WestVirgyinzer @steelrzfan2015 @EHUNTER55… https://t.co/jZt0Jj2BDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you wear something that looks like a practice jersey when you have these options? https://t.co/YAAP1noNEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLBNetwork Ran into Carlos Pena at Sky Harbor Airport. He was very nice and I told him to ask Byrnes what’s up wit… https://t.co/oLxm60l60s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live PD kills me.. they stopped this dude and searched his bag. He had heroin in it. He said he just bought it from… https://t.co/ViTNKyqeT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patriot_17 @HillaryClinton For Donald Trump.For Donald Trump Jr.For Ivanka Trump.The pain of prison and eventual p… https://t.co/h6EXMtCeGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhschenker @Applebees we've generally had really good experiences at the @redrobinburgers in at 7 corners, even w/ my custom orders]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF, and that’s a big if, they manage to pull it off, I don’t see how they don’t go down as the greatest team. You’d… https://t.co/QOWgpu2RBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pofavo no juegue con los sentimientos de tantos fieles a San Onán!  Hacerles concientes de su propio pecado les pro… https://t.co/dqU8KJRovJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Even during the National Emergency?   Where did you get the money dickhead?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PatriotsUnite #PatriotsAwakened #WWG1WGA #GreatAwakening #MAGA #Q #QANON #WEARETHENEWS #FAKENationalEmergency… https://t.co/brg13Q49yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sammy_Markle I'd rather be a rich narcissist than a poor, broke leech. #getalife]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two nights of Tritonal was the best way to spend my weekend https://t.co/vkxMuxWZrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Your one of those people who likes to cook people's aborted babies and put hot sauce on them .]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cookingupsomethinggood #shakespeare #othello #theater #techtheater #ideas #latheatre #thebard #sound #analogsound… https://t.co/8TDoFV4EXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel like I’m wasting my time at school like I could be doin other shit during the day to make money now😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the weekend yes #wine #gruet #gruetwinery #redwine #weekend #albuquerque #newmexico @ Albuquerque, New Mexico https://t.co/KTSSn92vF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great news. It is about time we tackled this issue as 22 vets a day commit suicide!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tsmcgee1 @calebhenderson6 @brandondarby Only 10% of Texans want the wall. According to @Breitbart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love when kids I used to coach go on and do great things. Way to go buddy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kioscomayor @LillyTellez @sylvia_duarte @SoledadDurazo @LinaBuenoLopez @roviedoc @Mony_Alarcon @teresalizarraga… https://t.co/4bYNG0UquU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only thing better looking than the view was the gal! @ RIVUE Restaurant &amp; Lounge https://t.co/YOKLcnWywA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since finding @BarstoolSam on Twitter I have done nothing but to try and earn his approval as one of my honorary in… https://t.co/EBlvsW9rTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[These comments are so not needed, especially from the lead sportscaster of the lead statewide station. Come on Sull… https://t.co/UKNSibmubj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maduro_en Bolivar jamás fue socialista. Todo lo contrario. Fue un aristócrata, un mantuano, hombre culto educado en Europa con la realeza]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BWOODKNOWS  1 ON N🥶NE  @nyknicks newyorkrobbery size #medium  #BULLETS 🏀 #KNICKS  #ASHEVILLE #HOOPDREAMS #EWING ✂️… https://t.co/66T7B5dMLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirginiaYankee1 Voit had the best numbers of any player in MLB over the last 33 games of the season. He hit 14 HR'… https://t.co/p1b93fs3Ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliciawrotethis @clemtownkernel @TellEmSteveDave @BQQuinn @Tesdtown That's a blanket. A beautiful blanket. Damn I want one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜🦋 Fighting for the #lupus cure starts with learning more about the #disease Raise your awareness 🙌💜📚💜 #educate you… https://t.co/QWiZ06vepz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liberty beats Jacksonville, advances to ASun tourney semis @LibertyMBB @ASUNSports @WFXRsports @SWaddellTV… https://t.co/hKBWAbAhr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to take away what he’s doing because it’s remarkable and truly amazing, but maybe because the US has its own is… https://t.co/2q77qE61t4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOakLeafs *calls artichoke hotline*  "Hey yes these artichokes are horrible" "Let me forward you to my superviso… https://t.co/jKwuk45ZAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppleSupport $1000 MacBook Pro. 3rd time it’s failed, Apple want me to now pay $475 for a repair. Agent just hung… https://t.co/uZ0KqYgtF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new “Triple Threat” #tripleCrown winners is a Super Bowl trophy winning; Catcher catching; Tony award winning W… https://t.co/l1Xo1FGSTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw this yesterday. I’ve never seen water pass through both Big Bear Creek and Little Bear Creek Dams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you really want it #Ucangetit #MMFYY #BAHA #Crosland  S/o 🤧shmateo_ ogleloo @madeintyo @dwn2earth_ 🔥🔥🔥 @ Germant… https://t.co/TqFMH5YCoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know LA is statistically hella liberal or whatever, but I’ll be damned if I haven’t met the most Trumpers in my l… https://t.co/y4e3fZWQJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got asked to be featured on a bodybuilding page, so I had to do it to ‘em 💪🏻 @ Gold's Gym https://t.co/9WYBiM9eF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanBleiweiss @Carolyn_Lyden 💯 Related Questions are now part of a question graph sourced from things like query s… https://t.co/HT0E49Ibqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOATunes @BrotherJammer might have to drive down and have some fun with the locals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rrosenbl @TeslaParaTodos @DMC_Ryan @BenSullins @HyperChangeTV @TheTeslaShow @Model3Owners @FredericLambert… https://t.co/XK562Jcn80]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueBros_Craig I’m not proud of the amount of gameplay I have on both the PS3 and PS4.. I just started Game of Thr… https://t.co/fMx2lkbHav]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concrete Rose (3-1, @JulienLeparoux) holds off a pack of challengers in winning the G3 Florida Oaks (R10) on the… https://t.co/rxPvfEiWSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradley is about to get the ball leading by one with 2.3 seconds left. Stress city in St Louis. #ArchMadness ⁦… https://t.co/DEGbeUWOHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Johnson from Trinity is a beast. UofL getting a good player for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[Royalty...  Tattoo by Jen @artbyjenpoteet  Model: @amandamariexxoo  Black Sheep Studios… https://t.co/DJ0orD9srN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizabethraine @devinforparks @KevinLovesDonut I don't doubt the good intenr, but intent doesn't provide the child… https://t.co/aPPkJjcCXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Observations reveal new 'shape' for coronal mass ejections https://t.co/bXj9AUMSFc #science via @CosmosMagazine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved the movie, but I’m more interested in Hanna than I am excited about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenasis818 sigurado i-re-report na naman ng @gmanetwork ung pic ni maine and AA ..  un ang manok nila pero si alde… https://t.co/qEEomoFgE6]]></document></documents></author>