<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[In Asia: "There was no collusion with Russians, no phone calls." ~ Clown in Orange Makeup appears to have slipped.… https://t.co/XUEZ0XvYmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhaletweets Disaster capitalism is... a disaster. Time for this shit to end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The puck has been dropped at @wesleyan_u.   @ncpuck and @Xavier_Hockey have started first period action at the Free… https://t.co/Gs4HHm7nvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Arbor will be set up - come see us, it will be a fun night downtown!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReginaldBoulos see why force is needed ti neg se baton ki fe yo travay. until you understand that nothing will word ask till you turn blue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitter “Just searching for answers to life’s big and small questions, what can I help you with” -Google]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear my teams: never activate playoff mode. Just play hard always. Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard NJ went hrc in 2016 AND blue in 2018. Why waste Trump time in a US citizen predator state?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2forme2foryou Warriors are gonna have to deal with Houston, Okc, and Denver, most likely 2/3. Can’t wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#picture #dibujo #dark #ghotic  #paraelyana #art #paraelyana🙅 #arte #photoshop #ilustreitor #adobe #freelance… https://t.co/gbBzSuMB5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxfireBroker @LauraRudy4 Much more useful data-backed information here, sadly.  The number of hate groups operati… https://t.co/H0j2gAFnf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[O no sabíamos que existían..... Muchas enfermedades y curas radican en nuestra mente.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I went to a bike swap meet of sorts @HandleBarSTL tonight. Did I sell anything? Yes. Did I make money? Yes.... S… https://t.co/onC8sSZWpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[By Leica M10, Vario-Elmar 28-70mm em Nassau Bahamas https://t.co/gpKV70aWGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MizzHoney23 for voting and tweeting to support Oh, Wiley Dear! #Wiley_RYS19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cyclethepacwest @sean_spicier how stupid is someone that doesn’t recognize a parody account? Never mind you’re a democrat right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NEBeer30 I actually gave that beer a try once. The @ThreeBeersLater guys (actually @MarksVoice) regretted the exch… https://t.co/ZufH4vD6dM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Popped up on my @Snapchat memories from two years ago today. This isn’t fair. https://t.co/pVlnkXmg45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYTTYTTYY @agreatbigcity @TimeOutNewYork @ABC7NY @nycgov @nycfeelings @NYCDailyPics @nycgo @Artofvisuals @nypost @lottenypalace Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sports performance class in action!  The fellas know it as “Morphin” time!  Also the “Brody show!”  Great work this… https://t.co/e7KK7wxHBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OJBorg @BBCRadio2 Happy Friday OJ you really confuse me with saying it’s officially the weekend. It’s still Thursd… https://t.co/rm2NIUmtim]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never catch who it was but if I give her space to forget I think everything will be ok.. I love you Hannah...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This, right now!!  Looks like a 4am wakeup! @BVPrep families and staff prep for regular day, one hour delay, two ho… https://t.co/JvP2C0RTsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@postlpeter It can be a bit of a pain... we dropped some of our bars lower so they don’t hit when folding... still not ideal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Incognitoameer My reaction when I misread this as walking around with Coke https://t.co/GcT2pQqDUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚽ BOYS: Titans allow a quick goal 2 minutes into the second half.  Madison County 2 North Oconee 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shirtless Samoan 2019. #USA7s #Vegas #rugby7s Parade of nations @ Fremont Street https://t.co/6lxqmnleEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@princeduncan22 @SkkyDnt4gtTheV I knw the months are just flying by too]]></document><document><![CDATA[person, the little things that people would do that irritated you before them, don’t bother you anymore. The things… https://t.co/LMxBTpOLzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrazMaster @RyanRamey3 Almost happened to me too... around midnight.. right lane was all snow was trying to get over to the left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here he goes tweeting authoritarian BS again, because SNL made fun of him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Climate change to expose half of world's population to disease-spreading mosquitoes by 2050, study finds (via… https://t.co/Rm0s3BTocU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SatbirSingh_ @OUAsport @WLU_Mbball @BrockMensBall @LakeheadTWolves @Mustangs_Bball @MacMensBball @UofGMbball Wish… https://t.co/2s7hR8T7Iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[vinyl covered foam sports seat cushion Overbrook High School New Jersey Rams htf https://t.co/fRL5Cu78PQ via @eBay]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALL OF YOU IMPORTANT PEOPLE OUT HERE!!!!! NOW I KNOW HOW IT FEELS WHEN YOU MAKE FACEBOOK FART!!!!!!✊🤪🚔❤️🖤👩‍🚒💕🚓🚁🚑🚒… https://t.co/ZuDMCpoJBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to call this guy a friend! Best #highered enrollment management coach in the biz! @CoachTiers #Emchat #IACAC… https://t.co/D8epuMJyEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivien2112 @RushFamTourneys Good morning Vivien! Take yourself a snow day! If you have to go out, be careful. Just… https://t.co/7lkXgNrRPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[What you say to yourself matters. The Bible reveals “for as he thinks in his heart, so is he” (Proverbs 23:7, Amplified)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptDavidRyan Precisely. That’s the part that infuriates me. He was “decorated”. So was Custer, Benedict Arnold, t… https://t.co/WGf7RvFwRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because I just watched the Roger Corman doc, I now want to watch a Corman flick I’ve never seen and  pretty much ev… https://t.co/dPMf9GSpMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sylviadefender Boom great take and I didnt even have to watch the show to get the info!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hobbination @woodyjwd @maziehirono @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/npD0AEhUA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuntiesBlocc Ah, I see, I kinda took it as mostly jokes. I doubt any dude would actually get at her in real life lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amazon For heavens sake, don't change your mind about NYC. They will get you back then screw you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MPaulkovich Seriously, if you read of Jesus praying in the garden of Gethsemane the night before crucifixion it su… https://t.co/8ZCjjqwasY]]></document><document><![CDATA[He that is faithful in that which is least is faithful also in much: and he that is unjust in the l…… https://t.co/cauS3l9veA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought it was an electronics store at first.. then holy fuck it’s a gun shop 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't think too much about things that really aren't going to matter down the road! Cast your cares and leave them to God!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shot it like he fully expected it to go in. Gene Hansbrough was the man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great afternoon with you Jay. Thanks for all you do. Keep fighting. @Lombardi_Fdn #preventcarecure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames sorry bro, this isn’t going to be any good. Can’t replace the original, don’t even try. Just to name a f… https://t.co/WucZs04Md2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sprint can you guys not call me and harass me into adding a line to get an iPad for 4 dollars a month if I wanted… https://t.co/xINKglpNcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn Nina Turner gave her heart out at Bernie's first campaign rally. That was inspiring!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Just a master negotiator unprecedented in our time.  We r truly in the presence of greatness! Now… https://t.co/LUIVpPSV2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Distancing the crimes in time won’t make these go away. I’ll bet these Peds  have tapes. A lot of nervous people ou… https://t.co/WMDHA9C5fT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey y'all need to watch forensic files . They came in and said don't move , police , . Lol . They was in the next r… https://t.co/h7fuqx0WNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tiptuesday Pick The Right Moment For A Haircut - To get the undivided attention of a barber or stylist, timing is… https://t.co/QWvlxV2FJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newton Conover HS 6'3" 2020 F China Cornwall @Working_Gal_ has been in beast mode all season posting 32 pts 28 rebs… https://t.co/caGWDEGD5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help to end trophy hunting. Pledge to stand with us as we put an end to the senseless killing of wildlife ar… https://t.co/uFc3E5HtgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislongview @LisaTalmadge @reesetheone1 @Kamalaallday @KAMALAMODE @Needle_of_Arya Klobuchar and Brown I would co… https://t.co/Kq9E3NAd5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi Where the HELL is Congress? Digital Book Burning Must Stop! (GOOGLE, FACEBOOK, TWITTER. YOUTUBE CENS… https://t.co/DwWZagJAgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t work out if I’m a fan of the whole OTT American style danceathon, make some noise, titontron shit they do in… https://t.co/eNzoto6Rya]]></document><document><![CDATA[I figured why you must turn off your phone when reporting for bond. So you can not record when they threten you! Ou… https://t.co/8wVTWMPEA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dfacastro @axuan25 @jdegoes The fact that you know the complexity bounds is an example of how TCS solve the proble… https://t.co/9Mm16gxvkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between school / my company and my personal life ... I’m not sure what is what. I know easy isn’t an option, I just… https://t.co/PIc2p0LZqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell Beverage Distributor That the Iditarod Is an Arctic Nightmare for Dogs https://t.co/3PFLN61db7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who has ever told me that “blood is blood” can go fuck the fuck off. Sometimes you have to realize that bein… https://t.co/n4DoEGGmxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bending 1\2 inch bar. 40 Ton @ Fishtown, Philadelphia https://t.co/dFN6EWkOlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eating at Marbach @JimsRestaurant. Every part of my meal is exceptionally fresh and delicious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump will call this #FakeNews. He will say his name got a standing ovation. The longest and loudest standing ovati… https://t.co/AD8as7iiZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hegazy_12 اسمها اوبئة مش وبائات والانسستورز مكنش عندهم حروب ياصاحبي هما كانوا شوية نموت علي اسود وخيوانات بتطاردهم… https://t.co/zdrKFaFBkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Btr2sDay Doubled over on the bike with a serious case of swollen nuts after the shakedown and police beat down, I… https://t.co/PPPXhcwdEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chill Weezer fans that love the new stuff as much as the old stuff watching other Weezer fans threaten bloodshed to… https://t.co/bEQzDQulUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who thought our Cats were gonna win when they were down 15 in second half. I really wasn’t feeling it, thankfully T… https://t.co/B6tn3Xpsp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fuego88649356 @SenSanders Yes. You're right. This disabled woman needs to work harder so she can afford not to be disabled anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They know. He was in that back room. And remember my ID was missing, so I was using my passport. It does not mean that I am not American.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Blood of Hades by Mount Olympus Brewing  at @fortgeorgebeer — https://t.co/pwwDQFdqqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScotPollard31 The Roo was clearly just trying to steal the ball. Offender is soft and "LeBron" crying for a foul!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahayz33 @Raiders @NFLinVegas @sportslogosnet @theScore @RJ_Sports You’re right on that one 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubiesCostumeCo Slytherin like my wife says the house I would belong to, lol https://t.co/ntz7J2V1Et]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bryce Harper's dad looks like he could go hit 15HRs and drive in 70RBIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing compares to the feeling of having bills that auto withdraw when you get paid 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petermanna128 @JackPosobiec Where did the heathens live in the New testament, I forget.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the billions and billions of galaxies that exist, humans have to be the dumbest fucking species]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptG2 @MalcolmNance So what? Pay way too much for a coffee and scone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LegacyPreneur  As I build my businesses and focus on bringing the highest value I can to everyone I come in contac… https://t.co/kSB8SdUVUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMCCA Presents Lifetime Achievement Awards at Collaboration Week Dinner https://t.co/x9xbChtf0V @KjesbuSnorre @MrShowGuy @THEIMCCA @UcWeek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ung_isaac @Profeco @KiaMotorsMexico En cuanto a servicio al cliente la neta me quito el sombrero por… https://t.co/ycDjHEorbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneak peak at the latest “Rowlcast” episode, presented by @Doritos #CoolRanchVibes https://t.co/ifV3gp60nD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tstokes8040 They said they were short... so I’m helping out one handful at a time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dontreplyifyourcis Its going to be 15 yrs at this point before I get top surgery  Lord knows surgeons don't accept… https://t.co/RbeWMbxROF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samsonofsam @9975Ts Britain we love you becareful!😢🙏🏾🇺🇸😢 https://t.co/7fibeop15M]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫One Night In Soho by Najee, from #SoundHound https://t.co/3e5AbmflXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant believe some of yall never heard the free weezy album before. https://t.co/PaUTIfFx6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fleming getting work done with 18 points .  Maiewen 11 points. #2 EL 19 #1 Bangor 31]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late night talks with @Infiniterisf will always be the funniest things ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Devinrios23 ,,,DEVIN this is the second time I have had to @ you with this in less than 12 hours I- https://t.co/a1AduOcgHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of these same Democrats that called US Troops,Baby killers during the Vietnam war and are against capital puni… https://t.co/wShcGBFQBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[After watching the mauling in the first 30 seconds I’m not surprised Dana wants to see that again lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 / this will be a bigger disgrace than the failing ELD mandate which was also pushed by ATA ! Anybody see a patter… https://t.co/rWj6Lg3U4E]]></document></documents></author>