<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I guess he got tired of all those Coast Guard / Officer jokes. Red neck POS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KavinderGrewal @chrislhayes The $3 Billion (from my understanding) breaks wouldn’t be given until AMZN met its obl… https://t.co/bHhBWTZ2IW]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI For all the Geeky Patent Nerds of Nike and Things, Google has a Patent Search Engine and it shows the offical filings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[making this farcical. Define Christmas Card Set of 6 - Share a funny bit of perspective on Christmas with...… https://t.co/dbD7YVDqGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't heal what hurted you, you'll end up bleeding on people who didn't cut you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericmetaxas This guy literally turned into a statue holding a My Pillow, it was so comfortable. https://t.co/ln4BMJTbnK  @EricMetaxasShow]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t smile for the camera                          Only smile for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GGTurfCommander @TitaniaMcGrath @BarackObama It’s the best place to see pics of Michelle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar I hate how right you probably are about Taj being second best. If he’s not, he’s close and not ok, like yo… https://t.co/T8pkU7miem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kahokfan1 @QHSBASKETBALL Forecast has backed off slightly. Hope they will get it in. 🤞🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThaSoapBox When i got to the part about her not working and fumbling the bag MULTIPLE times i yelled. I never knew she remarried lmaoooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Perfection_PLL @blakelively 😍 i mean, do you really need a reason why? https://t.co/OUljDAvyRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @MayorAdler, @Loweeb, Tate @MayeuxBroussard and @projectatx6 for reminding me what makes Austin such a sp… https://t.co/KJCk6mTNZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Is Random, But Why It Seem Like Errbody Only Gat Something “Negative” Ta Say About @chrisbrown ⁉️Like If Ya’ll… https://t.co/Mx3ub0tDG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesPPierce I thought it might have been because he made fun of Kim’s glasses. https://t.co/0QvSsao8Lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I baked cookies last night for the sole reason of getting to secretly eat raw cookie dough. 🍪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews You mean like Josh Holly is bringing to the Senate, asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1 in the Universe!!!!!! Really he's just that Great!!!!! https://t.co/XrRY45XRoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@go_jos_go on parlait de gens qui aimait ça se donner de la misère et j'ai dis rendu là aussi bien porter une cilic… https://t.co/duFKhZXTMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClydeSteel @ChoiceVaccine @VaccineChoiceCA Both accounts should be taken with equal seriousness. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blac Youngsta Lil Brother Yung Money Feeds the Homeless in Atlanta, Ga #Topbuzz RealNiggaShhTho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaxPackGods @MHMorissetteJr Remember when you had a Ripken Fleer rookie card?]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM SO TIRED ALL THE TIME MAN. I JUST WANT EVERYTHING TO STOP SO I CAN REST FOR A SEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday George Harrison! #george #georgehartison #love #music #peace #compassion @ Venice Cafe St. Louis https://t.co/dixF9LKpd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally just walk away whenever I'm having a debate with someone and they act like Steve Harvey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Severe Tire Damage by Fat Orange Cat Brew Co. @ Big Betty’s Dump Station — https://t.co/eSc0vS5ljE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Corruption at the highest level within the FBI. Cleansed it now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask me if I give a fuck about BCBS going out of business if we pass #MedicareForAll. #NoFucksGiven]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @gkatr, constitutional law professor &amp; former fellow @nyulaw on his recent new position as… https://t.co/k88MVSBUqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the spot, I made up the word Eeyoresque in conversation and everybody understood what it meant.   I couldn’t ima… https://t.co/ykWxwnkfrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be a mother who’ll say:   “Yeah @AamirLiaquat ko TV per mat lagao, ghar main farishtay nahi aengay”   And go b… https://t.co/gc1kcR1QoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@44ina4door Of course, you are welcome to keep guessing and looking even more stupid. Your choice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emiliafart Finally, you’re an awesome person, and I’m happy you got to hang out with her; so she can see why you’r… https://t.co/zQ3zTpjoIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dickchallenges @dickchallenges #WeeklyDickChallenge #RED https://t.co/sULfNILEC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blaming everythinng and one but yourself for your situation is immature as hell #Narcissist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose @realDonaldTrump Great job using a serious medical condition that affects more than 65 million peo… https://t.co/YecD5mScQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misfitmedia31 @LAKings @Dodgers That's not the point...it's Dodgers night]]></document><document><![CDATA[First national emergency then martial law. There is probably another first step ahead of that, but I’ve forgotten b… https://t.co/WuhkiQ5f2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[enjoying a late night coffee &amp; beignets at the world famous #CafeDuMonde with @Jubilationlee11 #BoysGetaway… https://t.co/CcdWlyItHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BringTheBeatIn I had some good times at Cobalt https://t.co/egGRHUe0uu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think the official state drink of Arizona should be lemonade? 🍋 #Fox10phoenix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump IN THE WORDS OF THE ALWAYS-BETTER-THAN-YOU PREZ, "...TEAR DOWN THAT WALL!" -- EVEN REAGAN BELIEVED… https://t.co/DOi66FixqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traditional school day and calendar out of sync with the times https://t.co/4eSNdFsDXs via @EducationNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bufshuf @annalecta @real_farmacist @thedailybeast @samstein @willsommer Is that directed at me?  You make exceed y… https://t.co/ZjCe1iMO1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanStNick @JoeNBC @realDonaldTrump @GOP Really so you think the @GOP is the first to use them?? If that is yo… https://t.co/0DrprwcjeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[look who reopens Saturday at @NatickMall @AppleSupport @metrowestdaily  https://t.co/sH5DMwK3Lf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryangirafffe @steezy_cbreezy If you ignore Andy Samberg in the beginning he does get better. If you ignore him all… https://t.co/DMoUZzQhxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[It used to be Professor Hawking, now it’s either Curry or King (the writer) or King (the congressman).]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many years of phone calls do you think it’ll take for @Chase to stop fucking sending WEEKLY credit card offers… https://t.co/XjcQzPv8dp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ME Undergraduate Seminar series will continue on February 25 at 3:30 pm. in 1144 Hand. The guest speaker will b… https://t.co/C7CXLrn4Am]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are calling for a foot of snow Friday... A FOOT?? WHY ARE YOU LIKE THIS ARIZONA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump When are you going to pay back the money you and your brother stole? https://t.co/yNlnBTRuhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3rdreviewer for some reason, I get more than 2000. https://t.co/IeerLL5rhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[You see? That’s what I’m talking about. That’s why I fuck with @kanyewest  That’s my bipolar shit, nigga what. That… https://t.co/Sp6h3cyZHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just fought someone for my best friend and no regrets I live by honor...I feel bad for homie..he going to have a bad day waking up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jjpatt92 @JohnAnzo Well, we agree there. Honestly though, I was very surprised by @aoc’s choice. The House Committ… https://t.co/GkFab5Taxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most important thing I'm bringing on this youth retreat #snocamp19 https://t.co/7prfMcBCTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[This 👇👇👇is why I #follow @waltshaub because he understands #ethics like nobody else!]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YUW3bPuvxl CPC: 38%, LPC: 31%, NDP: 14%. As the CPC capitalizes on #SNCLavalin, the NDP unfortunately… https://t.co/7ZcaJGDuKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaMoralesM Esta señora sigue resentida con todos nosotros los Uribistas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisMcP Oh damn!! 😂🔥I hope some of the tech people see this and drop some fire honestly it really enhanced my creativity]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am more baffled every day as to what is happening with the “reparations” discourse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting some interview prep in on this morning’s run. @charismahousebooks @christianaudio https://t.co/H9lnqvlXOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wendys I hope you guys treat your employees better than @sonicdrivein https://t.co/fTpjb0nAji]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 17- to 19-point lead has been a danger zone for UK this year. They just relax around those numbers a lot. All t… https://t.co/bi0DAHbrGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wild4CA Lol, I’m asking for your educated guess silly!  And watch your twitter tones too!  Do you think it’s a wal… https://t.co/WU3lSFxg16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunalshatti @CatUnfiltered Very impressive. But have to tell you I expected more out of Bruce Leroy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plvgm_ @fastbreak_ent @_tee_32 @corderius5 so the dunk wasn't basic https://t.co/vGfBtQFoDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MohamedMOSalih @kwetoday What my mind envisions. https://t.co/FCQNqevhWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A learning leader in the classroom finds ways to keep the students involved in the lesson... [because they need] e… https://t.co/nwLdNGj8Jl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradfatherSpeak Were spoiled after 19 years of Mangold and Mawae, but the last two years have been awful at that p… https://t.co/4iwh7N3SPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stefanvonimhof Grocery is devilishly hard and the upstarts are all making losses. As an aside, I’d love it if regu… https://t.co/wQaeho3JOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another 16 hour work day. 8 hours here and 8 hours later at the airport. My day starts at 4am and ending at 11pm to… https://t.co/tRlSaf2ckP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eddie Bravo and Alex Jones in the same room, holy fuck I can’t wait to listen to this today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr4thAndLong Good question. Seems like an easy path to injury without the payoff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol He continues to lie about things he doesn’t need to lie about! It’s absolutely astonishing! And no one… https://t.co/5IfSCX2AWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been in New York for roughly 3 hours and I already had the best slice of pizza in my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #pieceofyourlovechallenge is just blatantly disrespectful...y’all gotta chilllllllll]]></document><document><![CDATA[People like @isaiahthomas keep me going. Good to see him getting back to that MVP status he once had. He will come… https://t.co/43d8Q01fp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grift warning:  Instead, how about helping people better understand themselves and how they relate to others, under… https://t.co/3zWkfjdpXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 1853. A border between Mexico and the States of America iswhich aren’t yet United is established. In 166 years… https://t.co/lJk36j9rNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tim_Price_1971 @stldreamer @PPact Obama is not president Hillary is not president trump is president time to live in the now]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/s0CKEsDz4Y.   My YouTube channel @YouTubeTrends @YouTubeInsider @YouTube @nytimesbusiness @MSNBC… https://t.co/JbYTuT7N6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Actually__Amy_ Yes hello can we duo somethin cheezy like this please and asap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Levi’s IPO plan puts its ‘good governance’ reputation in jeopardy - San Francisco Chronicle: Levi’s IPO plan puts i… https://t.co/KW8bqK7Zgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the inspiration is usual prestige and/or to be elevate your socioeconomic status.]]></document><document><![CDATA[one of my fav holidays a year but can’t really relate. i was born white and wealthy but ima fight for a change in t… https://t.co/BUO7oCTInO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jleigh40466485 @JonasAfrend @alllibertynews @OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1… https://t.co/DBf4wObuCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #FortWorth, TX job and click to apply: Merchandising ASM - https://t.co/aYFbOh2iRL #BusinessMgmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thinking of deleting Peri because ppl add me in groups and many fucking male are wanking lol , so far I blocked over 200 account s]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's summer everyday  Never gets old @ Downtown Celebration https://t.co/OMFOKyENk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James_Steiner_V @nonsense_PW @luther_bj @NPR Did Lincoln "invade" the Confederate States during the Civil War, and… https://t.co/XaEY5oSjQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA:   stop putting individuals down or insulting them for seeking mental health treatment. whether it’s once or th… https://t.co/p0bTnTSGBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustnRZimmerman @prairiegirl0028 @downthebyline @jcmack03 I wondered about the cold as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@exjon Bane speaks through the mouth of Hizzoner Bill DiBlasio: "There is plenty of money in the world. It's just i… https://t.co/CXEyVGkPfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBrockCast Idk we will see who all comes to play tonight. Go Hard or Go Home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kingphotosaz @ru4kc2AZ @Nick__Tucker @RosenberryEthan @RyanKing958 @FHSGOPHERS @fhsgophertrack @FhsGophersbball I… https://t.co/tJDZmFTq5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[End 3rd: #Sooners 2, Dallas Bap 0  Both teams go 1-2-3 quickly in the 3rd]]></document><document><![CDATA[When y'all suck a dick..quit playin and suck 'n lick that shit from tip-hole to balls and nack again!! Da fucc he d… https://t.co/5Q2jUfeq9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's how you do it! My goodness, I had so much fun last night! Thank you to everyone that came out, heard my stor… https://t.co/1GuIU5Ctkw]]></document></documents></author>