<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Floral embossed silver necklace with red beads  ♥️ 3 available. $5 each ♥️  #karissparkleroom  #karis5sparkle… https://t.co/9IP6wxvRj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨Faltan 2 días!!!✨ Para el lanzamiento de “Mi Padre” espéralo muy pronto! Gracias y gloria a Dios!  Si te gustaría… https://t.co/AHrCMNzUFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, my baby just laughed at my loud ass fart.   Children are truly a treasure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruce Donaldson started the Princess Fairy Tale Challenge! https://t.co/KWpw3StFSM #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mumford and Sons... and Daughters @ Quicken Loans Arena https://t.co/DP964fjtts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their food was fantastic 🥞 @ Wildberry Pancakes &amp; Cafe https://t.co/Rq1TJEzBXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart @AOC @NRA REEEELY? I DIDN'T HEAR ONE PEEP FROM THE NRA THEN OR NOW ABOUT SEPTEMBER 11TH!  WHY? BECAUSE… https://t.co/rNVFa0K3yM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the nominees for Best Picture leading up to Sunday and would like to vote for all the cats in Bohemian Rhapsody. They killed it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@All_Geek_To_Me @AnalisaAtFSU I believe I have another video of your dance abilities... let me check my records]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaGaGayPK Omg awful! They need to give you a heads up!/If it’s more than a day you should definitely get a discoun… https://t.co/x6p3dIIFtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great night for a mixer! Spark spark everywhere! 💥 thanks urban.timber for allowing us to host at your beaut… https://t.co/AqdtN8qQYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HippieVol @volrob33 I got up, grabbed my blanket, and was going to sit on him in the chair so he changed his mind lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jameswstroud @frpatrickop I can tell you with my entire heart, every hour I spent with Sr. Electa, to me (not payi… https://t.co/6T1Lj4vvaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[What color do you flag for “I have weird shits and I’m not into poop play?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was sharing my dissertation research project and almost teared up doing so. After 4 years of this I’m glad I stil… https://t.co/OsCHuMc6XF]]></document><document><![CDATA[mosaic murals introduce a bucolic atmosphere to new york's subway https://t.co/KaJj2kiPfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does the thought of a custom walk in closet make you happy? Check out this new listing at 7 Mineral Ave in Bozeman… https://t.co/iuu1FlJjha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Target: Use sustainable palm oil - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/2YyQdpGmH8 via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time for the birthday Bih, Two times for the birthday Bih... @ Paparazzi Lounge Mob https://t.co/JfH2T2Blnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeding and cleaning up after my babies 🐶😺🐶 (@ Home Laundry Room And Backyard in Los Angeles, CA)… https://t.co/IK7vOq0OC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Born 1802 Victor Hugo France, author (Hunchback of Notre Dame, Les Miserables)  1846 William F "Buffalo Bill" Cody… https://t.co/Ux6Rmbgvh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being in the car with my boyfriend and dad is aweful bc theyre both drummers and its drum part time three always 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else’s parents say they would kill you and stuff you with drugs to smuggle out of the country? Or are my pa… https://t.co/jVpffYR9zq]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3: Work ethic, time management, effective communication, creativity, interpersonal skills ... the things employers… https://t.co/tDzAJY72eT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiriRod Chilling with Frida the fried chicken dog. 🍗 🐕 https://t.co/tsw2kf4s3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tr3yDay @Rylee_Hladky I mean if you had to pick a sister, she is a pretty good one to have!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Netflix’s one season shows hit ... but when they all pop up with new episodes ima be like https://t.co/Xi3ZWL8NAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[just stoppin by to say i am living my best life &amp; i am the happiest ive ever been ok thank u for comin to my ted talk have a good night]]></document><document><![CDATA[This honestly was my dream girl. Sports Card Girl! Anyone kno the story as to what happened? Imagine how popular sh… https://t.co/tbeUAxJZn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HedgesRemington @2TLMShine @KleinErin @jasonmkern @coolcatteacher Thank you for the shout out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 8/1.63 Miles: Fitting a quick run into a very long day adds for a nice break in between all the grind and hustl… https://t.co/6Dspqbfibf]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don't microwave relationships? I'm dying, I love this man. Does he want a new daughter since his is a snitch? 😂😂🤣🤣 #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inkiwell Another Fun day. Love the cats!! OMG, thank you so much for picking my Oliver!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FloorJansen_ @DLMayo Happy Birthday @FloorJansen_ https://t.co/UM1rAkZyDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[totally wishing i was apart of the franklin st. celebration in chapel hill right now... #GOHEELS 🐏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit, I’m bout to be single single. Lol oh, wait! I already was!! 🤣🤷🏽‍♀️🥂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg the jobros used their girls in the music video 😭 I love it I love the song I love life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drunk eating scallops and lamb chopsT 1:30 because why not. Evaluate how does 24 really work?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been awkwardly going between Jazmin Sullivan and Alice in Chains  like what the hell kinda vibe is this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every part of your dream is all ready to be fitted into place. You just have to imagine each aspect being possible.… https://t.co/tbmwOCevxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[when tf will I ever not leave my hw for last minute, I’m getting real sick of myself 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those who want to chenille with panels it takes 4. In these photos posted I have 4 or more. I will post in comm… https://t.co/G4rIZEZ0jF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost All bcuz of @JennyMcCarthy spouting this crap on TV. We put so many people in danger when we don't… https://t.co/oRQ3uSXHU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @realDonaldTrump 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 so trump was blind-sided? He really is a moron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizlottable @BettyWho She is an amazing soul!! Full of light and love!! Next time you have the chance..def. meet h… https://t.co/oRkJCXjPp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker Keep the pressure on. If you give an inch, he'll take a mile.  But you know that all too well! You'r… https://t.co/up7ki4e9Zc]]></document><document><![CDATA[No words or emotions can express how proud and how much love I have for my brother!  Love you @Bakes_Jamie13 ❤️🙏🏻… https://t.co/eW40FIQg5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[He never disappoints! Vacation reading commences now...  alexandermccallsmith #loveallofhisbooks @ Delta Terminal -… https://t.co/CKZ4FfOROR]]></document><document><![CDATA[me and zack: *get high and turn on a movie so we can laugh* us, 30 seconds later: *scrolling through twitter not pa… https://t.co/p9t2BFEzdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[We Demand The Govt.Stop Wasting out Taxpayer Dollars on Investigations. FUND THE BOARDER...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buncombe County/City of Asheville launch survey on renewable energy priorities. Info via @CityofAsheville #avl… https://t.co/6l3dste9of]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got hit by a couple of high bills this mo th so I’m really hoping I hear some good news soon 😅😅😅😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[#blessed #hope #positivequotes #strong #faith #health #believe #fit #inspirationalquotes #lifequote #nevergiveup… https://t.co/uwZTIkhNan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinstrasser So sorry for your loss. I have the same issues with my father. I try to make it right but he will no… https://t.co/qq1JoFXGWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you (in loving memomry)dariush @miti_dariush for liking my post! Happy day!💙💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you ever feel like the pastor is preaching directly towards you during a sermon bc same]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day to the many women around the world. You all inspire me, and I can only hope to do t… https://t.co/l8JDt4MbFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Dr. Suess! Guest reader in 5th Grade today, Pat Chisholm! #readacrossamerica https://t.co/sIXa1gtu4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @IndyCaronNBC @IndyCar @Sportsnet when is the Canadian racing deal going to be announced? @Hinchtown… https://t.co/JIHIGkBqWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmmeurer Can you help my elementary public school students with a 3D printer on DonorsChoose? Thank you! https://t.co/z9OoHe6J04]]></document><document><![CDATA[so funny. scrolling through channels I spotted a familiar face on @newsmax  @BillOReilly! yea! The guy who sat atop… https://t.co/kXaFtc8HEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[A "fun" Saturday morning workout. Thank you rvrickey #fitness #tireflips #prowler @ Prevail Family Fitness, LLC https://t.co/phUW4shPR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are the mountains. The light that reflects beauty in ourselves, in others.  The strength that lifts the ragged,… https://t.co/pLCgXXNRhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fear of Death; a photo assignment by me📸  Model: margotthecowardlydog [IG] Asst. moulto_photo_op [IG] [Side note; c… https://t.co/phknSDb8jS]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you punch a dude in the cage over and over and over and then get choked out and lose  #thatwasbadass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico The bison produces the same bullshit that comes out of trump’s mouth. No wonder he wanted to visit his Crapper-In-Chief relative]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Bring in groups like @EduColorMVMT/@educollabor8ors, the #DiversityandInclusion reps from @ETFOeducators/… https://t.co/Jy4S8TbDUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rwdavis_edu @smgaillard @DavidGeurin @tamaraletter @TaraMartinEDU @woodard_julie @Wes_Kieschnick @hansappel094… https://t.co/RKSlY7JLxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback!🌊 . . . #throwback #takemeback #miami #florida #trip #sun #happy #beach #waves #beautiful à South Beach,… https://t.co/ZWBTHugEwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyLawyerDiary Read “Plain English for Lawyers” by Richard Wydick. Mandatory reading before my first year in law school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will always care about people more than they do for me and THATS the tea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i cried so hard &amp; then hit a mailbox the first day i got my license 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caparosa52 @grannyanon1969 @4x_Clubchamp @ehgreenie @TexasDeplorabl4 @galacticaactual @Carolyncorneli8… https://t.co/PH4AdRpid9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried stitching seed beads for the first time ever this morning. The beginning is pretty wobbly but I got the hang… https://t.co/csI1DVsDYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAKilkuskie @Jim_Jordan Best at lying, covering up and resisting.  Worst at taking care of America's business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @GameOfThrones Bleed #ForTheThrone drive is beyond amazing! @hbo has outdone themselves here st @sxsw… https://t.co/RpEbhND84I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought a pair of Old Navy jeans while they were 50% off and I have never been so excited to wear a pair of jeans. S… https://t.co/PBBYzloE6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeromiahValeska @ChainsMack @hellermyers @OddNMacabre @BlankPetra @Horror_Disciple @JMikeMorbid @MsChaunceyKR… https://t.co/0qAzmBdMzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes PLEASE!   National Margarita Day...orale!!!!   #excuseme. #salud. #friday. #thirsty https://t.co/UkrPj6Pg1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question: Would you prefer an accurate forecast or a consistent message with few changes the closer to the event you get? #wxtwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unsolvedmoments you should definitely investigate the abandoned asylum pilgrim state! It’s located on Long Island… https://t.co/sNcqBOwdrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StuartWeitzman return policy BLOWS. 14 days is your window for returns! Rude sales associate gave me a blank stare… https://t.co/nA0RJnq8qz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sick knowing that in a few days, it’ll be 4 YEARS since my cousins were murdered. Like wtf man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drakenic Great article @drakenic. @GIPHY has certainly helped make communication more expressive and entertaining.… https://t.co/BpRzM8MejG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HornerTom @rosenbergtom @Paul_Sheridan I love that @Jeffcheley looks like he’s checking his manicure.😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discussion of personal experience with Japanese Americans incarcerated in 10 camps from CA to AR during WWII, paral… https://t.co/KXqY56aZp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeLibby2 I remember when people would put their garage door opener on their waistband- as their "pager".  Pretty sad.   Pass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou Because she knows McConnell will NEVER address it in the Senate no matter whatthe House does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love seeing pictures of @LukeBryanOnline fishing 🎣 #LukeBryan https://t.co/qsLbjwDpUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday with @thejuliaforster shopping for #addidas found the leggings at the first store in the mall still had t… https://t.co/T2ip149VX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisajaneKY @oohgoodness @JohnnyAuGratin @louisvillekygov @LouSafetyZone Dealing with the same in Charlotte. 😠😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emrazz One of the things I've learned over the years is, when someone interrupts you, keep talking. Raise the volu… https://t.co/WdyLs5DmJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have ideas of moving to the west coast but I know I'll miss my fam.  Living in my thirteenth city.  Hopefully one o… https://t.co/oPsrGscWlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I figured  and hoped it’d be a good game since both teams lost last night. Unfortunately my side team won.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey I hope I can get tix for your concert  in #Oakland #California😎  Maybe you can add on #MtView since your tour i… https://t.co/PUlUfzCj2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Art Creation Party: where the walls are canvases and everyone also wears white to also *become* canvases. Art s… https://t.co/XqspH7ophG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a big thick huge hung 9 or 10 inch cock to come over tonight at my place. To fuck me. I need it bad .  My bo… https://t.co/faRbAjKNjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooo, you got a haircut!  Lookin’ good in the neighborhood!  Have a fantastic weekend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shane dropping beautiful wisdom as always . I adore him with all my heart 😭✊♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[We just sang kareoke ... drunk.. to Big girls don’t cry and Baby... ty Dukes 😭😂👋🏻]]></document></documents></author>