<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Lucy Loo is disapproving of of #earlymorning pictures. #lucyloothelovecorgi #corgisofinstagram https://t.co/ufErUl4bj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelindaMisjuns @LCSEDU @Bitmoji We need you to share these at #techstravaganza19 !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your focus is on your persecutors, you give them more power. When your mind and thoughts are on Jesus, you rel… https://t.co/MNwK7VZQ50]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY MONDAY KID!  RISE AND GRIND AND GET AFTER THOSE GAINS!! Awesome rest day yesterday...I did NOTHING!!  Relaxed… https://t.co/AX7maxtTuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every parent in Etobicoke be like #etobicoke #torontoparkandrec #registration https://t.co/iP4Kmq4NbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@watspn1013 @LorettaSteddum But please New Yorkers do not bring your voting habits with you. Florida wants to keep… https://t.co/yvzn1evc33]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh cmon. It’s cold as shit this AM!!!!! What happened to the 80s 😓😓😓😓😓😓😓😓😓😓😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok @chrisbharrison you were right this time. It is the most dramatic season of the @BachelorABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great preview from my shoot with @KeithPics for @keithpics  • • • #photographernyc #redhairwoman… https://t.co/YZB5Z2sDG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only one of many @GovernorPataki policies paying off for all of us! Very cool!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@light4c @NormEisen @CREWcrew @WhiteHouse @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Trump has little to do w/ it, same as he has litt… https://t.co/6vOCoJWLrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[God bless his Soul but my daddy caught me 🚬 a cigarette when my cousin fave it to me and like to have sh..on… https://t.co/8GKVhYZuWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancyr77 @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Disgraceful - she always avoids talking to the Angel Moms.  She's an evil woman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LAST CHANCE FOR #GIRLSCOUT COOKIES! 🍪 https://t.co/kCeV5FNd6b  Buy 🍪 for yourself or send to a pal- the shipping fe… https://t.co/hyaLcLYYFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look what we can do 💪🏽 #internationalwomensday #ididthat jlajphoto @ Columbus, Ohio https://t.co/0T9CNffNT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MGBookMarch #MiddleGrade The Among the Hidden series is one of the first series I really enjoyed. Followed closey… https://t.co/HTWIJry04A]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I see on my timeline is everyone having to say goodbye to there pets because they are sadly leaving the earth.… https://t.co/ZsdZICl8RG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bonjour @Souriswingette  Today is #CherryPieDay🍒🍒 https://t.co/4uQAYpAnGC  Cherry Pie by Sade]]></document><document><![CDATA[This how whoever @FloydMayweather lose to gone have to win and they still might lose 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Principal’s Honor Roll Pancakes Breakfast 🥞 @miamischools @mdcpsnorthregion https://t.co/MmWcppuiBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to be excited for every new thing you try and then get sick of it within six months. (Except writing - somehow… https://t.co/KcDP5uvFg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just found a show called #tacotrip ... how I am NOT the producer???? @AngelaDTaylor it has me rethinking my life choices]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenATurner @zofloyd1 Thank you! We have a lot to work on for the off season. But we ain’t done yet! See you Tuesday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh Valentine’s Day? Yah.. I tried to go out but ended up just going home and eating a bag of shredded cheese :))]]></document><document><![CDATA[To what causes can we donate? @D45Schools @D45Westmore #d45learn4life https://t.co/AP9X26NoS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me walking through Turlington in Greek paraphernalia knowing both impact and inspire kids alike will leave me alone https://t.co/YMyeNwNUEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[And usually when I friend zone he loves to retaliate. I like that....it gives me an excuse...To kick your ass seven… https://t.co/Ng7XeNjWos]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @high_university plays at home on Saturday.. while @KCS__Athletics and @huski]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big, beautiful Bulldog collard greens, purple Mizuna mustard greens, a few new broccoli transplants and “the creepi… https://t.co/5EpqEIvPVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WinterSwearJar I hate this f******g winter weather!, hot one day, cold the next!  Tweeting with my pottymouth to… https://t.co/MoOhzDeW11]]></document><document><![CDATA[How happy you are motivated certain behaviors. That knowledge can be used to build a knowledge base to impact change. #APLHealth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@truthandfiction @marcorubio I have been praying for your healing and comfort. Journalism is alive and well, doing… https://t.co/RVzSpX5SXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[SPRING, TX see you March 22nd to celebrate it being March 22nd with the musical sounding of my friend… https://t.co/Ude3lqQlUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UKFootball @JoshAllen41_ @BednarikAward @MaxwellFootball Congratulations!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @MarkWarner @Jim_Jordan I don't know if I can stand one minute of Jim Jordan...an embarrassment to Ohio and Congress...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdieujuste25 @JustChillLou This faithful black King does nothing but protect his marriage and family while she tries to tear him down 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess my work figures if I’m off early most days then why have a day off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Local students in the spotlight for their entrepreneurial skills! #JA_NLA  https://t.co/49xDUXU1xB]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dad just walked up the stairs and said “goodnight all!” and my mom said “where’s my goodnight kiss bitch!?” and… https://t.co/cUwDrsGeL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m becoming a better person again because I actually took my makeup off before bed tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith @KingJames LeBron needs to take responsibility for being a bad teammate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This duck who has just discovered his feet for the first time. #hilarity #snicker #grin #playful https://t.co/Ccto5UMjhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got tons of snow yesterday.. Gentry liked looking at it, but wasn’t quite sure what to think of walking in it! 😂… https://t.co/b2mbG2ETL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win a family four pack of tickets to see Stomp on Broadway courtesy of your local Chevrolet Dealer https://t.co/XJwrJSOUaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SleekStealthy85 @BradleyMartyn @Snoowwflakeee @MitchelChauvie @lee_1122 @phyxious562 Woohoo!!! 💪🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @LitVentures to post covers of 7 (children’s) books I LOVE: no explanations,no rev… https://t.co/i1FsUPy1qQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[YESSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! #wwechamber #toosweet @FinnBalor deserves that!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommy_tommybaur Helll yeah it is Khloe refuses to find out who her real dad is tho so we will never really know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HempBombs I’d like to try your product to see if your CBD product can help me relax and deal with a very stressful… https://t.co/S1iMyCDU6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT SCHOOL BOARD MEETING TO ATTEND ON MARCH 5th at 11:15AM at 600 SE 3rd Ave, Ft Laud  School Board members w… https://t.co/g41LbDlzhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Euqinomist @kathleendames @DrJenGunter Not sure. But she was under age so she could file a rape case.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HBD MITCH!!!🎉🎊 Hope another year  of life helps improve your dancing😂😂 lmao jk, hope you have a great one!😊… https://t.co/7njxEn7J1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teachnMedlin @ncties I am SO sad to not be there #flu. I know you will do a great job. Please tell me all about Jeff and Dean. 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyO cheetolini called him to reduce the sentence i have that feeling wake up kelly if that idiot was black he would get a life sentence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timccsread @Yogiwankenoby @shawn73yuk I have read the research and I’ve seen videos. I want no part of it. Stop th… https://t.co/jbmwSYtiOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kamilah Sameeeeeee I think you missed my fb rant on it https://t.co/ezb1s274EW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at New Orleans Marriott Metairie at Lakeway in Metairie, LA https://t.co/VzJCJ8R8QX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiSoxFanMike Also, check out this video shot in @fromthe108 . It has our feelings too! . Was featured on… https://t.co/OoQhp40WCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 YES THERE ARE REAL CHAINS ON THE SHIRTS AND THE SKIRT! LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEUniverse @TheDeanAmbrose @WWERollins @WWERomanReigns So awesome to watch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/DOc6WsOW0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Indians My God, that Tito takes his hat off for the smacker is precisely why I ❤️ the Tribe #MyTownMyTeam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacob: I can't be an alcoholic cause I have a 1.9  Hannah: oh you have a low alcohol tolerance  Jacob: no Hannah, t… https://t.co/jl9UfoxvY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GotEvidence "Context changes perception and can change behavior." @RobertPearlMD Use research and data! @CCM_Cert #CCMCNewWorld2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY DOES IT FIT😂😭😂😭😂😭😂😂😭 #PLEASEME @iamcardib @BrunoMars #notwhattheymeant https://t.co/ag1vmV8W7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶 And all I really wanted was someone to give a little fuck... But I waited there forever and nobody even looked up… https://t.co/NHX280QJMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up to the sound of rain is always such a 😌 feeling..... until I remember that I’m the opening scheduler and… https://t.co/INegirgCBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz Please Lord not another millionaire-out of touch-clueless white businessman ‘splaining politics to us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the privilege of photographing Ms Lee in her “movie star” home in Beverly Hills for my book Jazz Photographs… https://t.co/FIhSFEEgZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garyrgruber @heARTISTatWORK @tracyscottkelly @tmajorjames @MagicPantsJones @MaireCervenak @RitaWirtz @Richmondruss… https://t.co/FrJ5fBsvOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[after waiting about seven years, i finally got to see @youmeatsix live. there’s literally NOTHING better than live… https://t.co/nHFsO0gmhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[took me the whole time, but I messed it up, and I put it back together, @BenRisinger!!!! @MFBrehab https://t.co/qitm2vsGSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland either you intend to impeach the president, for alleged crimes that have yet to be discovered, or you intend to embarrass him.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Josef Mengele actions in Auschwitz concentration camps Rnow coming 2American politics true Democrati… https://t.co/cfVRjMkNSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I officially ended his "break" tonight... for my own sake. Apparently he wasn't expecting it at all but he took it… https://t.co/2YKREFCbim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeLibby2 @MicheleDiane8 The one where is pops blood vessels on his red face and his super size mouth opens and… https://t.co/3dcdzt8rS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods The only one in full crises is you Hillary and the Dems in Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i like my braids but i need to feel like a badass, so ima need to switch it up. asap]]></document><document><![CDATA[« Bad B*tch, small waist, pretty face... »  . Here another cool sexy  vibes video from Ashville. During my Sexy Acr… https://t.co/o8qoD3SM9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@COACH_Y0UNG @FHCMaxwell Couldn’t have said it better myself!! Happy day friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The majestic Multnomah Falls, OR @ Multnomah Falls https://t.co/XsBLRH33PX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClemsonFan1123 @LindseyGrahamSC @marthamaccallum @FoxNews Girl, we have to get him out! Could there be a blue 🌊 in SC? 😊🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like Bitch not everything revolves around you and stop being so sad all the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahR77 @POTUS the left is unhinged they have been since President Trump won but what is more evident is this Luke… https://t.co/DkPaesyhZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stradagangelica @akomama_tm @DerekPa56710094 @BrownieJohnston @AintitMarvelous @PatGrant7777 @SUPERGOCHOo… https://t.co/lK815gi6zC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sites of Suffragette Protest and Sabotage Officially Recognised in Nation's Heritage List | Historic England… https://t.co/93wJVWkogn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is a CON MAN.  He has been known as such for decades by every business man and bank in and around NYC… https://t.co/ZdgXRwh0MZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to school today for the first time NOT wearing glasses.. it amazed me how many people noticed that I was not w… https://t.co/zjhTLKuW5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @timpcapps on your  Diamond 💎 Award! We appreciate all you do for our store! https://t.co/kpUQ2oGXyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here to meet josh_j11 #GoSuns dosequis #DosEquisXXSuns @suns @ Fry's Food And Drug https://t.co/zMarOLIMpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 100th Day of School! Lots of 100 year old friends shuffling about today! 👴🏼👵🏼💯 @WWP_Dalers #100thDay https://t.co/7JAJ83Rnvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cast of West Side Story in repose. #theatrelife #somethingscoming #march8to10 https://t.co/cgIuPN5J0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitches who don’t like me really be in my views that’s really weird cus i don’t be watching y’all shit tf u looking for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALF: Missouri 46 Arkansas 34. Missouri with most points in first half this season. @23SportsMUTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging Out tortillafactoryboise doing some behind the scenes work and enjoying some of the delicious food, mmm chi… https://t.co/AewFXSFKkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChetSokolowski @MegaChurchMouse @spotlitetruth @lindsaymccaul @MancowMuller How did you end up blocked? Crazy pants!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGSniper @csantoyo145 I’m going to forever tag you on all kitty things forever and ever 🤣😝😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwg1wga1111 @riwired @DJCraigTwitty @IsraelUSAforevr @JacobAWohl The sad part is you're one of the morons who actu… https://t.co/xSujn1WIrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yehey! I’m forever grateful to God for this blessing!! 😭 I’m done with Walt Disney World, Florida with 4 parks - (f… https://t.co/GmfSR5k87m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawnheinrichs @LVADone True. ❤️ my passion for the ocean leaves footprints in my artwork.]]></document></documents></author>