<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I know this is a very unhip thing to say but I can really imagine myself enjoying slice work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenCarmanShow college football and basketball players start in the spotlight and transition the the pros without l… https://t.co/beMwMu20VW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilSpoiledlife Can’t do nun but respect that even if it’s something you may or may not want to hear. It’s better t… https://t.co/5ErqMznSLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smith_Hays kkkkkkk Protegeu protegeu para depois Foo com os que votaram sim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KasieDC OK KC - did Trump get to Manafort's judge? Is it possible Trump made a deal - low sentence = no need to pardon??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I saw a sedan civic with a sti wing…what type of fucked up world do we live in]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notevenvegan gotta hope there’s no afterlife. i wouldn’t wanna have to explain that situation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePoniExpress This got to break Poni_the_idiot's heart that his hero wont respond to him. Then again why would Ma… https://t.co/GIIYYpgMzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thekidgib45 I don’t think so bro! He is tough as a rusty nail but his style has passed many moons ago🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your school closes, but you can’t enjoy it because you fell asleep early and have been up since 3am!  Ugh. https://t.co/yzHo999lVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DSWorld614 @No1Hudson @MichaelBensonn @NiallerDoran Like who? He beats everyone who’s in ranks at 130 and 135 right now. EVERYONE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harmeet Dhillon Slams Microsoft Blacklist Partner Newsguard in Daily Caller Op-ed | Breitbart https://t.co/uuXjZBU0Ws via @BreitbartNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuoteTheMiller Yeah, it’s a complete reverse of Toronto and the Islanders the other night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormOrnstein Trump knows more Russians than my aunts and uncles...who were Russian.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlevenson I hear you didn’t reach out to the scout council to give them a chance to respond before you made your report. Any comment?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevemagness @darrenrovell My group has  a long-term vision that will be shared with the track and field world very soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aramaithea Actually no you Hate Jews because you are a Islamic ideologue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved speaking to our Team Leads last night. Love the quality of people God has brought into our world. Love what G… https://t.co/smJ0rJxbdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 3am and I just finished our film project for one of our education classes 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t seen a Great Lake in a long time and this one is frozen https://t.co/0rkEL5P9Sy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imispgh @AlexRoy144 1/ Michael and Alex:  I posted this elsewhere, but let's not forget that every single time a n… https://t.co/ycNthxZ8sW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think masturbation at school is a great topic of conversation. Why? Because it’s so polarizing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAO SO TRUMP IS A RACIST LYING BITCH AND WAS CONDUCTING BUISNESS WITH RUSSIA  AND THIS COMING FROM HIS PERSONAL L… https://t.co/vGEJ2Zbl3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bridal shower ~ Advice Box i think i would want something like this for my bridal... #hilarity #chuckle #grin… https://t.co/yNwQzzmo1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandhyaABC7 Drought was nearly pushed out of #California, with only a lingering sliver of moderate drought along t… https://t.co/SseTBLHTX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[BASEBALL SZN ⚾️❤️ #1 @ Mountain House, California https://t.co/HvHFu2U0h6]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEALING. #texas #art #writing #acting #health #family #law #usa @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/J9dxrlVFZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans are acting like a wanna     be  Scooby Gang. They keep unmasking a villian who the audience knew was gu… https://t.co/c9J4erRyxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harlan What happened was the predatory student loan program.  I would consider socialism too, if I owed $50,000 fo… https://t.co/ww44DAlI4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a guy who I barely know finds out I’m a kindergarten teacher... “you’re perfect for it” “that’s so cute” “I be… https://t.co/rLxrp0BIfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que estusiastas han estado los que tienen la palabra Fidelista: Mayameros, a flor de boca: como insulto, descalific… https://t.co/EvDGXF9xnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHerd @ColinCowherd @JonGoulet @gregtoohey @JoyTaylorTalks @jasonrmcintyre  https://t.co/U8cXvT8Lip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaneSuh5 @Bose It's accessible now? The set up process wasn't when I checked them out last May.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weather has me wanting to be in the marsh grass with some 12 gauge 4 shot loaded up 🌾🦆]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me that you love me, if it's true, I don't want no one babyyy if I can't have youuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ian_mendes @6thSens He's over coaching at this point of the season. If you bring the kids up, let them play and have fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bppfeiffer @WSJopinion Please explain what is meant by “abolishing fossil fuels “, I am not sure it means what I think it means]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alfonso Rodriguez sería bien presidente, pero si ganara le dirán el mismito golpe de estado que a Juan Bosch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cynroseM @DonaldJTrumpJr Hello Brian child , of course they won’t, hello. Then the whole 2 year effort is for noth… https://t.co/Z9qvQkI7Vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have fallen into this rabbit hole and the possibilities are endless. https://t.co/7coZV4HcRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was such an amazing day. I forget how many amazing friends I have sometimes. 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkieTutorials You will be missed @KarlLagerfeld #RIPKarlLagerfeld https://t.co/nt43yRcrtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePdMass @SlidellPD @OfficialLivePD @Bran_Blackburn @dancesareo @BigFishUSA @LivePdFans @Bifflawson Got to go wi… https://t.co/dkBLM5t04q]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a simple #Numbers game. If you think #Positive you will #Multiply your opportunities, resources and energy! Th… https://t.co/mIvRnuwX5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody is talking about the married news anchor who died after he met a man on Grindr and put meth in his butt and… https://t.co/t0q2008qNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealLonestarTX @nemesis283 @ChuckCallesto The federal government's criminal jurisdiction is at 18 USC 7. It is ter… https://t.co/pjhd6AAVq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cranberriecosmo :constantly killing it with the original content https://t.co/JZifOrXuXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yael_heart @DCEagle1 @dallasjenkins @reachjulieroys @GarrettHigbee I’m cool with a maybe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RanaAwdish @BariatricPFA @GTCrandya @BerylInstitute @RexHealthcare @sickgirlspeaks @asmbs @ObesityAction… https://t.co/jeqJAEb8FG]]></document><document><![CDATA[emilysears x Fashionnova | #johnsonsportsent @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/R46FrcyZ0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tmcarr I didn’t want to fall asleep on the floor of the data center that afternoon from a food coma ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every week I always tell myself I won’t drink til Friday. Well it’s Wednesday and you could guess what I’m doing now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Tonawanda, New York https://t.co/jCGr8OxRuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP8809dfs My core over here on fanduel also lmao 😂 https://t.co/UjkJB7kxcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nconti23 @YoungMacintosh_ Except don't listen to Jake because he is jerk off idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[. Tonight - storymiami djkhaled! * VIP Guest Lists * Table Reservations Text : +1.786.877.0060 @ STORY Miami https://t.co/jfRHsVCRqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Windy cloudy days, sunny days, snow, rain, hail and I only been back home for a week tf goin on]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Mother Nature and negative vibes from the universe collide that is a force to be reckoned with. Powerful shit. I survived 💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another happy referral partner about to enjoy "The Playbook for Success" by a great friend amybsells !  Enjoy the b… https://t.co/o8V42FGux3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking to do a live stream debate or uncut filmed debate tonight...  do you have a liberal friend who would b… https://t.co/NvptDCoWJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyberToolsBooks Invaluable book in today's world of global cyber-espionage. A counterespionage nightmare for U.S.… https://t.co/sd4iAUcqtY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTimefurlulz The fact that you dont KNOW what those degrees are?? There is no reason for me to continue talking to… https://t.co/giBrqGNecy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vairochana in Tibetan Royal Robes • Tibet; 10th century @ Rubin Museum of Art https://t.co/JeTNt19BHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffMerkley You don’t think that she’s a liar 🤥 as well as a Nazi, do you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been thru it all, felt all the pain, lost my family, lost just about everything. I don’t feel a damn thing. My heart cold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clarencehilljr @MrChrisArnold @MrChrisArnold’s brother from another mother @GuyWVTM13 is next 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister is commenting on things on Facebook while on vacation I think she may be drunk lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin you think you can hide this girl from me by blocking her on Instagram. Fanny Linnea Ellinor. I will find… https://t.co/9jUWugplwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WNYTKateCorey @GregPollak His good dog 🐕 is cute so i bet it was worth messing up the shoot. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be honest. Anyone can get a link from me. Help girls gain skills. Help them meet goals. Help them experience… https://t.co/D78qTQzExZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS @WhiteHouse I bet you really love the Russian visits, to get to know fascism and understand your unfaithful “Spanky “]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ShayneGWoods gives some great advice to advocates—after you leave DC, pick up the phone and follow up on your asks! #RareDC2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsundaymovies @wikipediabrown  hey if you like the drug addict brother in @UmbrellaAcad check him out in a BBC sh… https://t.co/ALIWn1goen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@24_archito Did you know you can turn left on a red if it’s a one way 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @Lisa24681012 AOC: The right constantly making idiotic. disingenuous, bad faith, bull shit arguments. The fact… https://t.co/mzGGGEP9JB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Baywatch heute mal ohne David #Hasselhoff . #beach #Kalifornien #gelb #yellow #Strand #Rettungsschwimmer… https://t.co/GaP0wbSiY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 I'm still having issues with the fact that she approved Ben Carson for H.U.D. Secretary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the #VillegasLawFirm, we help our clients through the entire #probateprocess. We work with our clients on a one-… https://t.co/IRge1LqseZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[happiest of birthdays to @izgigliotti! i hope you have the most wonderful day my beautiful girl, can’t wait to cele… https://t.co/p5YYmZbnxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir here are decibal readings from flight 1022 today that had a broken safety seal on the door! Average ov… https://t.co/cp3rV44QKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usatodaysports Parents are loathsome?!?! Your child ain’t perfect!! Do you remember being a kid? Acting a fool “at… https://t.co/2shtSHCga4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @CraigSBPA She's referring to @FoxNews saying the nation is broke from Dems giving free stuff to laz… https://t.co/KvfbTfMJW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fire alarm just started blaring and Tom came out of his room talking about how it sounds like Donna Jean on a ‘77 Playin’ in the Band]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Springfield, MA job and click to apply: RN, Registered Nurse H&amp;V CARE Unit - https://t.co/41nOnlzFpU #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fragile #collage #mixedmedia #ink #paint #antique #contemporaryart #text #baltimore @ Charles Village, Baltimore https://t.co/tQUO3S2M4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimBob87966760 @smfehir Not his money anyways when he's not working he's supposed to use his money n'est pas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandonshrider @Courier_Sports @sentineltribune Good luck, brother. Take care and do good things!]]></document><document><![CDATA[BUDGET BILL CREATES MORE TRAFFICING AND LIMITS THE WALL AND OTHER THINGS!! @realDonaldTrump  DO NOT SIGN THAT BILL. VETO IT!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tierneyzzz @Diaz__Julian literally a kid puked today and did the same thing, I swear it’s tradition now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JStein_WaPo @WAProgressive @joekennedy @RepJayapal I hope this “Medicare- for-All” bill truly is Single Payer Healthcare Insurance For All.]]></document><document><![CDATA[a more accepting society with equal opportunity for disadvantaged communities so there can finally be a sense of eq… https://t.co/Qw4gmwO9ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealFakeShanti Hurry up before I report that video of you and bamous terrorizing that mouse]]></document><document><![CDATA[You want an idea of what the far right media does to people, read this and the comments that follow. None of this r… https://t.co/CBklH2xa7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Suns are the only team keeping us from getting Ja Morant. Lottery night we’re gonna need an Al Capone “we’ll gi… https://t.co/FAiDcYWQAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McGruf @leosantacruz2 You cant teach power bruh. You either heavy handed or not. But he’s already late in his care… https://t.co/q8Md68Cch3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hair is so long now. It literally looks like a weave. By my birthday its should almost be at my butt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanesssaaa2 @SYFY The series is so good, and the books to me are amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright @LadyBrainsCast, I need some #CPAC2019 meetup details. Getting way too excited over here. Mama’s on her own… https://t.co/y7V2RNlMKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time in over a month I’ve gotten in weekend climbing! (@ Vertical Endeavors Glendale Heights in Glendale Heig… https://t.co/DRS633iBdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me gustaría ver una entrevista del periodista @jorgeramosnews al diputado @fernandeznoroma. Creo que ya sabría que pasaría.]]></document></documents></author>