<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So @jocephusNWA  would you buy a set of random VHS tapes for $40? Mystery bag? 😂 #80s #90s  https://t.co/wtizW0chAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@packysmith @byMorganWright I’m the same - mostly cause my handwriting is bloody awful though]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, word on the street is I get to spend my birthday with my favorite people from Convoy, OH! @CK_CoachK… https://t.co/6CIRYJ5XnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agoddessreigns I’m relating so hard to this 😂Impulsive buys are the worst (especially while hungry) I was at Targe… https://t.co/nxYxY1TdgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where do I get the motivation to pack my room? I’m moving across the country in a week and I’ve only packed my perfumes...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of my 7 day Book Cover Challenge! Post 7 covers of books you love - no explanations, just the covers.  One co… https://t.co/bJrEnNV20D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU???  TELL US, WE WILL HELP YOU IF YOU ARE BEING THREATENED.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebonepatrol @haldornimrod @HumanistReport @jvgraz @ewarren Afraid of Mexican folks too?  Wow!  What a sorry existence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joanne79633723 @EarthandClouds @EarthandClouds2 @ViaAStockADay @WizardWeather @NewSouthWales 😍😍😍👌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NAIADIIMBB Let’s go WVU Tech !! You guys got this ❤️🏀❤️ we all are watching you on the big screen tonight @in Florida !! ❤️#42]]></document><document><![CDATA[Schiff will use subpoena powers if Trump quashes final Mueller report  https://t.co/IK26uaM6fZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was listening to @ArianaGrande break up with your boyfriend and I thought the song changed to her doing a cover o… https://t.co/NHOJmgnImg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am speechless to realize that GoJo’s in Westport is still open and operating. I thought that place closed years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevonSheaCook @chelseanachman I guess you know your sparkles. Interesting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj Most Black folks don't even know what racism is -- they don't know the proper definition, thanks to the media misleading them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we talk about how Franklin Jonas is the essence of all the 20 something year old girls listening to… https://t.co/OPlMSCXaRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE ON AUBURN OFFICER SHOT FRIDAY NIGHT: This statement is from East Alabama Medical Center.  The Auburn police… https://t.co/wHEaUMcSBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m. Fucking. Crying. What did I EVER do to deserve a man who loves and supports me so GENUINELY?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cryptic_hag I taught Year’s End in my fiction workshop last week. It’s def in my top 3 favorite stories of all time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyIdol who made your jacket? Incredible evening. Personal performance. Thank you to your Mom! #unplugged… https://t.co/EGRhWbhZZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We know we are getting decent snow when the county actually plows our street and cul-de-sac. Usually we rely on the… https://t.co/Ntpgp47tcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg @Wahlburgers @markwahlberg  Here is one very Satisfied customer and fan🍔 https://t.co/CEPEvo9RaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new single “Timeline” is OUT NOW! Stream here: https://t.co/JdHvZUSKmd   https://t.co/gGUunMYxGd https://t.co/sRkxUiGgRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanillaice As much as I’d love to see you in 2 weeks, I’m posting my tickets for sale.. Have a great time in Minne… https://t.co/IUbsEpVntj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsBreak @samwatts4BREXIT @SkyData What they think has more to do with what propaganda the newspapers tell peo… https://t.co/om7afT6M4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Chik-Fil-A for the first time betraying my morals. Hope it’s delicious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tombo_fc Does it make sense to kill no handcuffs? No pepper spray just shoot people? 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Few things, I complemented the events DJ on his set, introduced him to Rainbow Kitten Surprise- and turns out he’s type 1 diabetic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a fierce girl squad! jmags213 had some beauties by her side! So honored to have dolled up all these be… https://t.co/wGXAyfrk2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Texas Independence Day has $2.00 beers and $3.00 wells up and down ATX. Ya girl over here doesn’t LOVE doesn’t… https://t.co/9oCjtbWxLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cumberbatchlive Me too. I do believe at some point in my life, I’ll be able to. And with that desire being present… https://t.co/cT8xHiHn9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, should getting security clearance involve submitting your tax returns, etc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NetstrucLLC @nyjets Hey Sharon I was the NY Jets 1st Female Coach in their Franchise History (2017).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mr_rwinter @IrvingHigh speed walking too! leaving me in the dust in my heels! and I couldn’t have been happier about it 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SummerBreezy__ Well I'm glad for them both and also glad for them that both of them dropped out of Rihannas life]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at CSz Indianapolis-Home of ComedySportz - @cszindy in Indianapolis, IN https://t.co/wXn2lEVSr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pink will make u blink twice! @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/FkYwL6tnqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I painted behind the fridge. Lamest answer to, 'What did you do last night'? #truestory #HomeImprovement #painting #DIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter Leave it in God's hands!!  He takes care of all things in his on timimg trust him!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimGoodwin17 @YuH8TM3 @joergschimmelp1 @realDonaldTrump This has been a 'known' fact 4 years.  I have written the… https://t.co/1i54RYjb92]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one time I wish I didn’t have my contacts or glasses to unsee what I saw🙈🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hsunberg should feel special as she’s getting grace with my pre-makeup and pre-hair fix on Snapchat 😂😂 those kinds of photos are a rarity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennybake0320 @funder Nothings being said so I guess it didn’t happen last night. It would be on all social media I would think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See how to take care of your sealed concrete floors... https://t.co/UHTK0x649b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bj95432geemale @NevAriJason @herringtowater @MerriwetherW @essenviews Oh glory]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that March is here, we are busy tying up details for our first couple of weddings for the year and we can't wai… https://t.co/H7XulqhDne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theladykatie @Sparki777 @kenziebeck23 @WildChild69 @LandorMelanie @cheomitII @huskerfalcon44 @HERterus… https://t.co/HTjYHoneu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had my first Webinar nightmare last night. I had no slides or agenda ready AND my video feed started while I was… https://t.co/O7zFGg3MiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petttyy_quotes @itsyaagirlyamii Please say it again for these dumb bitches. The objective of your life doesn’t hav… https://t.co/xlbMkI5lyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesleyraekelly Yuck... spent a few weeks in the south: Savannah GA and Florida... Nice weather. Come back to cold… https://t.co/led8dPyEc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a busy day in conference you need to get outside #NOLA #fridaynight #precarnival @ Bourbon Street, French Dis… https://t.co/jb7KsG7a5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirGoldenrod @The_Trump_Train I suggest U do some homework on otraitor, killary and gang. Are u fools truly that blind??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunSentinel i know this nigga gonna get #DonkeyOfTheDay from @cthagod smh https://t.co/ybNFnqQM09]]></document><document><![CDATA[Il gesto che ha indignato l’Italia? Macche ‘ noi ti amiamo Simeone e’ tutto Fake News🧐  Grande Atletico. #Simeone… https://t.co/jPyBS2rHmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all my bitches is too lit in New Orleans 😂😂 @Raaamiah @Akaysiaa @imightdee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time we go through the Everest queue line we always have to take a pic with our fav explorer @joshuagates and… https://t.co/QLj24iCz2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alicia262girl @usatf @runinrabbit @BB_Performance @shakeology @Beachbody @jumpkck @oakley @fitbit @JDLFastTrack… https://t.co/zBduxq6dsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen, no one knows anyone’s individual situation.#SteveHarvey feels like he’s paving the way for his legacy but… https://t.co/ALIiHbtUE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacticalDogLive @LivePDNation @OfficialLivePD I like Kansa and what it stands for]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe if the windchill would be not in the negatives I might be more positive about leaving my house for class!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom: “what’s this thing we’re going to tomorrow? A breakfast?                             Me: “yeah”.… https://t.co/TyoYGaaQaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey guys i just pointed to arizona on a map and said “Las Vegas” so that’s how my life’s going]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarissaSherrod @ReedleyDowntown @aweblossom88 @LisaLisalew @achavez_8 @kristanichols09 @chrisharr27 @vickiej10 I’m… https://t.co/OsjjNxGbnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDurant1963 @realDonaldTrump @DevinNunes @FoxNews You are right individual one does not]]></document><document><![CDATA[saddest moment today was when a preschool student and I were playing with a toy pineapple I said “Spongebob lives i… https://t.co/U5lPUWYkMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My babydaddy soooo handsome gon have a gorgeous light baby with good hair 😭❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine going to school the full 5 days all hours every week . Imagine ur attendance not being so bad the school wants to kill u 🧘🏻‍♀️😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrLTMiles So excited to hear about this! I look forward to reading/seeing it. Thanks for sharing my work too. #Rural #Rurality #HigherEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had boots on all day, but switched to sneakers when I left for the meeting. (idiot)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerLbrtyorDth You earned my Follow for wading into MAGAt territory &amp; telling The Truth. You go guy! 🏆 https://t.co/paAVTXte07]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I can't get over: Gaga's Grammys look, her A Star is Born look, the fact that she and Madonna are no longer… https://t.co/uqLVwvDF5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are from Tuesday and there’s dog hair all over my jacket but that’s okay https://t.co/ofW9fu4Alq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @DaughterStPaul motherhouse has a truly astounding number of books per capita. Seems fitting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@se4realhinton Whatever happened to #MattDylan? I feel like we will be seeing him on #Oprahs #Wherearetheynow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrispy0515 @MichaelWaddell_ Just seeing this now - would have come by and said hello! What a great game ... Memph… https://t.co/ddN5edHe6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unumdesign Hey guys, my captions keep getting eaten when I try to post to Insta. Then I go back to UNUM and the ph… https://t.co/gFTnpeBCwc]]></document><document><![CDATA[tonight while shopping a lady had a dog with her, and caleb wanted to pet it.  she asked if he was used to dogs, an… https://t.co/Gd5zkTC69L]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY WOMEN'S DAY TO ALL THE BEAUTIFUL LADIES. HAVE A GREAT DAY. https://t.co/Fw4OEgAeU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has this ever happened?  No. Why?  Because we’ve never had a cheating, lying, corrupt, mentally unfit president lik… https://t.co/BrgDizONaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[A decade ago - I hardly recognise this skinny lil goth twerp 😘 #throwback #2009 #goth #gothgirl #altgirls… https://t.co/TWH9U2NThI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapehartJ @SchMieke It makes me feel that we will lose the election again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was appalled at Trump’s defense of Kim! Is Trump serious? @realDonaldTrump has the nerve to defend this cruelty a… https://t.co/ix3k9rVMze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senderling @RobertJSchoen3 @AngBach7 @jerseelaundry @Himself3909 @Chrisg19722015 @ProblemPanacea @LynnRog72… https://t.co/JMX6T8pO3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Rosio724 #gonuvo #nuvodanceconvention #nuvo #dancersofig #dancersoninsta dancers.on.insta @dancersofinstagram… https://t.co/IL0Jo1eYbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGlamazonn We have been constantly hiring for the past 3 years but have also been growing constantly at the same… https://t.co/WAucrfIAK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course my very very best friend would meet me for International Women’s Day!!! @ Fig &amp; Olive https://t.co/xLMMhvd1jF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some times them years don't mean shit in a relationship if he/she has made a fool 🤡 outta you 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff locked up and ready for an exciting night of Live PD in Tulsa! #9PMRoutine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ruralowl Detective Pikachu will be life changing and I personally will not associate with anyone who doesn’t want to watch it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had as much money as Bryce Harper, I would make this my breakfast every morning @TheGameMKE : https://t.co/h9jGjkM4H9]]></document><document><![CDATA[But if they do not listen, they perish by the sword and die without knowledge. https://t.co/magvDp559I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun and mentally-demanding night @QueensMuseum for the 12th Annual #PanoramaChallenge hosted by @LevysUniqueNY in s… https://t.co/ix86Ip94Fa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te das cuenta q somos un país ignorante cuando solo se dedican a criticar lo q llevó puesto Maria Juliana Ruíz ayer… https://t.co/CgOIuIWz0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m alone and in pain and scared. I can’t sleep for anything. I just miss you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now, see THIS is an appropriate time to say "I don't see color," and then follow it up with "or ladies, and neither… https://t.co/7iR7vOiXRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 @montrose46 I think morons in this country are afraid of the word socialism and that’s what Bernie br… https://t.co/Pe1VjiuLH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shigasumi да. на сцене казни меня подбивало громко поорать с безнадеги :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fooling with Nijee my hair got drenched in the shower, a whole blowout gone to waste]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BluRadioCo @VillaPrensa Ese tonito burlón no le queda muy bién Alcalde...]]></document><document><![CDATA[It actually makes the whole process longer by preventing everyone from seeing the bags that ARE coming out.]]></document></documents></author>