<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WorstBeerBlog We need more high-quality lagers from independent brewers, more variety of lager styles (there's mor… https://t.co/63GxqAYZ7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is where Trump defends himself by saying “Why would I kiss her?... She’s (insert something incredibly offensiv… https://t.co/DT3zXZ42lh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#love #dave #happyvalentinesday #bemine #philly https://t.co/IPMrZBnFLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[And Lent begins... 40 days of prayer and renewal, Mustangs. Let’s embrace our journey, @MullenMustang!… https://t.co/zOXvMTkY2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lighthouse is the only team in the entire state that is still unbeaten. But Mackay is leading the Sawtooth Conf. ch… https://t.co/EHAU92NYxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bit of “smoke” covering the mountains this morning. 🏔 #smokymountainsnationalpark #cottageatmountainmeadow… https://t.co/iP8j5HfcRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[FUCK BRUH.... FUCK THIS SHIT....TIRED OF THIS FUCKIN BS!   FUCK LUPUS❗️❗️❗️  FUCK CANCER ❗️❗️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HPluckrose 1/ I see at least two definitions of "diet." One is what people eat. The other is a sustained nutrition… https://t.co/a5kefrDMU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crbates1 @think_again_7 Excellent site, and an even more excellent listing of texts!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@O_omynsx @Keff_C Hopefully a good team win &amp; atmosphere can help convince a couple kids to look at attending later in their life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOrville Actually there ARE program errors with the @FOXNOW app for iOS which are not letting me @TheOrville ton… https://t.co/JhE2QJqbWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well it looks like a two time winner got his booty yesterday (I needed something to make me happy yesterday, great… https://t.co/glv22m71el]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt Throwback Thursday . . 💈: @SteveTheBarbers 📸: stayinthecut .  Book button in bio☝🏾 for salon appointment 📅 . T… https://t.co/t0jN0AbHOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraIsABerner @WillClifford38 @dpolicare11 @RoseAnnDeMoro If you can’t find a good qualified person in the curren… https://t.co/ZNnGa9lyFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevengeOfMyLs Lebron James has a drinking problem and smashed Rihanna AND Beyonce?? Nothing but respect for MY goat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iisupahot_ @SSaibot1 @Scoundrell_ Jose Aldo is my favorite. Conor starched my guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[a whole lot of people are addicted they just don’t see the signs because “weed’s not addictive”]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the Los Angeles area and want drum lessons? I have some slots available as soon as this Sunday! Tony@tonythaxton… https://t.co/UuE4ohMCyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InsteadOfSheepICount wine bottles (after I drink them)! https://t.co/qFm1ZkF73C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilElsonPxP RBI is an acronym making it a noun thus RBIs is most appropriate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog @JackPosobiec You have that right about a three day old Puck sandwich in Charlottes airport.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love doing a curl set! Prep with #biolageraw small #curlingiron. #dress #tanyataylor #cutbydanielroldan #hair… https://t.co/J1pKNWLY57]]></document><document><![CDATA[Des nouvelles de Shadius Grey pis de sa « blonde » ? #bonnesaintvalentin !]]></document><document><![CDATA[#owl #birdofprey #lunchtime #roadsidewildlife @ Sheffield, Massachusetts https://t.co/363Q9z0UXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson i am on the side of the fungus and the tree's.  No joke they were here first and I love going to the… https://t.co/DiFzHHv3nQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t everyone dress for the airport like they did back in the 60’s?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jack Arnold 2 FTs. @auroraathletics 89, @GALancerAD 84 - 4.6 left. #RCNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boeing Boeing, I am a German soldier by German law. I have a German family and by now my German citizens have loop… https://t.co/3UoZssru4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cashwellcubs @CumberlandCoSch #CCSDLDay #DLDay #OfficialDLDay  @kimrobertsonnc https://t.co/ybxrA9lDVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen and Thank God It's Monday! Let's Have a Great Week Everybody! #Blessed #TGIM @ Moncks Corner, South Carolina https://t.co/SZEYFg04N9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff he’s next to go down. I was told he’s abused young men for years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briankhan_23 @MaioccoNBCS The 3rd string running back has to play special teams]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great little immersive museum-ing with the better half kristenfaye617 at @artechouse . Nothing like a relaxing lay… https://t.co/KRePkMDRL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ozecrivaine @thejtlewis @realDonaldTrump Selling more can't you read...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ruthless_RL is all class. I don't think anyone else would've been this cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[150901 Balloons, Umbrellas and Snow (Me) Considering Veganism and returning to Maine. #balloonsumbrellasandsnow… https://t.co/RTImIJawwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I reflect on #InternationWomensDay, I’ve learned, it’s not enough to be an ally.   As a cisgender, privileged ma… https://t.co/mL4jwlQ14q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katie_honan No. Based on the letter Moses sent me in 1979 (when I was editor of @ColumbiaSpec) that sits on my des… https://t.co/p0wysN9Xtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidBegnaud @washingtonpost @julito77 This “piece” is tin foil propaganda. full of crazy speculation and with a… https://t.co/zWeHvfPA28]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ 1st United Methodist of Callahan https://t.co/e3IcmMdmpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s bigger than basketball in the city I’m from. That’s what all you bitter Cavs fans not from Akron don’t underst… https://t.co/hnSVTXF0hk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newsroom union files unfair labor complaint against Post-Gazette after publisher went 'berserk' https://t.co/xRaYn4ys7N via @theinclinepgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniel_brinkley @Christian_Racin @RodneyChilders4 People like you need to get the hell out of NASCAR.. you guys ju… https://t.co/ogsr5OFb7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tigger &amp; Piglet, LA New Times, 3/17/2002, art direction by Eric Almendral @ Park Slope https://t.co/RpNjdGhJtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Varsity Boys warming up for the Wolverines!!! #Mpire19 #MbraceTheDream #F1NISH #BeatWest https://t.co/RcIo6Pu5Yi]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the Lakers fans barely cheering when Bron broke that record last night was pathetic. They should be ashamed of… https://t.co/Rgvjs3Z1BK]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUESS WHAT. To celebrate the launch of BREAKING CHAOS on the 14th of March, you can get book one in the series, Cha… https://t.co/eLNE9mqw8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are an American citizen, please do not do anything illegal, because you will be arrested and sent to jail. W… https://t.co/fINvFmQgS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is the reason the Hawks won last night.  She is the Real MVP...The Timberwolves started missing shots every tim… https://t.co/bgiIY9mAZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1Z62PkAkV5 Shop your favourite styles at Facebook Marketplace 1-855-479-3999 #facebookmarketplace… https://t.co/82BiJodJ3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how hard you work, there is always somebody inside of you that will work HARDER!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dandakich Agree with most of your takes in reference to IU hoops.. but you’re delusional if you think Juwan Morgan wouldn’t punk Bohannon]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a really interesting and detailed take on the increasingly progressive policies of Democrats.  What I like… https://t.co/Eo3FwC9ihJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@00b922be14374d2 @eduardoinda @Piar47881710 Ya te digo....ladrones compulsivos😝😝😝😝😝.....cortemos el grifo y se acab… https://t.co/Fr2I91623c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom But it is,  Joe. It comes under the "life" part of "life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness. "]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunrisemvmt @SenFeinstein 16-year old girl "we're the people who voted for you"   @SenFeinstein asks her how old a… https://t.co/q4RBmTZKHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Tykers practice of the season tonight. This will be my 14th season coaching with @wax_lax Big thanks to Mark… https://t.co/tDhEAgEgiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[miss you so much Recruit Miles, 9 more weeks until I get to see you 😍 so very proud of you, keep pushing baby https://t.co/TCMvWmoirp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewYangVFA That’s what I’ve been trying to tell them @LifeofLynnsey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isaacmarqueso @Lc_Specialist When I saw this link, in my head I thought “please be gasolina”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @jonz970 @RodHillis1 @vida_sirois @OLDFLACO @DebHedani @MAGAgirly @Branko_MA @arabellaa12 @willowmycat… https://t.co/hdEeoGHIBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dotdash1961 @surfcityphoto @girlsreallyrule @rushlimbaugh’s favorite sex-tourist spot was Dominican Republic.  Upo… https://t.co/1nPNWqZ7cU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Veronic55917416 When did the topic become hurtful? You really ask that?  Ask yourself what topics to you have become hurtful?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterTV #JonSnow #ForTheThrone with #TyrionLannister as Hand. I unfortunately don’t see things ending well for Targaryens 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my beautiful nieces !! @hannah_greg9 @HaileyGregory20 https://t.co/ZuogeUiMI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very important invite for me. It's not all football; the mind needs more. Thank you Mr. Potter for the invitation.… https://t.co/CIIw8PcFT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ll be at the @UTSOA Career Fair tomorrow and are hiring for several positions! Come see us and find out what mak… https://t.co/mmAYDoJpII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terrymarvin63 @JimCarrey No shit. It’s called a joke, try it sometime. Damn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the black in the james charles pallet is the best black eyeshadow. try to fight me on this but you can’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisKreutzer2 You mean this new trailer that always has a wheel bearing out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interview: @Gianluca_Vacchi talks dancing, 'Mi Gente' video &amp; making music 😎 https://t.co/S9gPQFfSuE via @axs https://t.co/Hn3EBCvi8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[There seems to be a subtle motive that’s concerned me with DoH, which is that DNS itself is being targeted for depr… https://t.co/QOZOtiw17l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hay que estar atento al Twitter de @coronelclaudio 😜https://t.co/8k5919eAxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is unbelievable!  We just lost ACC Regular Season and #1 seed in Tournament in one night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#REDBIRDhoops  Away vs. Southern Illinois 20.0% / +6.5 / 134.5 https://t.co/ji3f460pPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You’re Too Late For I Was There In ‘66-‘67!!! But You Wouldn’t Served Your Country Because Of Your… https://t.co/6lna1Rjo2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delgadoj8 @Feisty_FL Seems like you are one of them white women beaters,,with that kind of hate talk,,no doubt you… https://t.co/5mJQLqBpYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally getting a chance to pay my respects here. Wrestlemania 2 is my earliest @WWE memory, and the Bundy/… https://t.co/mZ7phhbZO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katebevan I am unable to find an appropriate .gif for #smug to send you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turning the 1-9 to the 2-0. Thanks to everyone who wished me a happy b day! @ Seasons 52 https://t.co/IdFOl3wkmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex_Kozora What are your thoughts on Myles Boykin at one of the third round picks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[New school NBA meets old school NBA. Cya in 4 months lad airball_jamaal enjoy those Asian women #amiright #wade… https://t.co/IjJTOwkOrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[another junk call. all my phone is good for. never get the important calls no]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna hate to see you go, but happy for you going big time! Don’t forget about us little people here in Arkansas.… https://t.co/pms1U47TxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[PS I already know the answers. I'm just annoyed that the A line was so slow and late and far from the W line that w… https://t.co/523mm3O7Vp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richo3000 Not yet, might have one by the time you arrive. It’ll at least have the same address, 14 Old Fulton Stre… https://t.co/PRCTzCFN6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack @KarenLL11 I am a well educated individual with 21 years in the Military, a non-profit executive for 15 b… https://t.co/Bgoiz8sRp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you play @PlayOverwatch and you’re the only one defending the point vs the whole enemy team https://t.co/dfaDhMUuVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[4x800 (3A boys): @hcpss_mhhs finishes right behind winner Chopticon, which set the 3A state record with a time of 8… https://t.co/nYpIusGA9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[So either I've strained my oblique from walking or an organ has exploded. Neither less likely than the other]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I’m old enough to remember when we called that the Fourth of July.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I really have to take a step back and marvel at the size of @janewayxyz's GIANT ASS https://t.co/mmVHvbzMSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtkinsonCraig @ScottLaudati @Boozie_Smoocher @zineninja Thanks man!! 🙏 nice to see Dave’s epic Mercy in that stack 👌🏻 🐎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to say that the @Allegiant Airlines Network powered by @ismconnect is now live at @GreenvilleDrive ⚾️ @MiLB… https://t.co/9d0Yer9iG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[God when are you going to bless me, i literally have the worst luck/life 🙃😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeopardy Alex MUST regrow that incredible mustache that I remember from my youth!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeGoodberry @AndyCarlsonShow 6 to 7.......it explains so much about me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJeffMerkley Serious Problem w/your stats: you can’t do a per Capita comparison of a population of illegals when… https://t.co/7ziSztzzpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyPhlyr @mitchellvii @JussieSmollett @EmpireFOX It sounds “tinfoil hat” but I wouldn’t discount your theory. I… https://t.co/EQtxBxqvTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msinsulindpndnt Why the hell donhave to pay so much for something the LIVE, and it’s like 20 bucks for a prescript… https://t.co/4FFpeWwrSo]]></document></documents></author>