<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@B0RedS1 @LevyMoriya @Turki_AlOwerde @Gottrocks @aalhaily @Herald_Reports @LJT_is_me @Lebanon1Tarek @305local… https://t.co/1n83VTdyrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laxlife summer lacrosse camp dates will be coming soon. #July #3rdAnny @Suits20 @CheddaBob21 #Northmen #Family]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJCflipdascript This is Stanley. He’s been my buddy since he was 2, he was so skinny and bony. You could see his r… https://t.co/BKua0fqujq]]></document><document><![CDATA[What makes watching a future Ladies player work towards a state title? Getting the call from another one deciding t… https://t.co/R0KAoDkga0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely Sunday! Meals prepped, lunches and dinners are ready! #MealPrep @ Frederick, Maryland https://t.co/IH60l7yX2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is sad that United States have the same abortion standards as... China, Vietnam #sadcompany/standards]]></document><document><![CDATA[LINK IN MY BIO: MyhellofalifeTV does a Reaction to one of our favorite artist on the channel @JadeDelValle new audi… https://t.co/kWrumjFJtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birfday to my work wife ❣️ You’re getting old but it will be ok. @ Ernst &amp; Young https://t.co/DQYSNrBwPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kaepernick’s critics contend that it doesn’t matter how much he received because the payout is a drop in the bucket… https://t.co/J0zrIaiPiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[If she gets good dick AND good personality then she’ll inevitable catch feelings, and we can’t have that in the atm… https://t.co/svDdGVhEgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karivsco A veces siento el presentimiento de que la gente sabe mucho de mi... jeje 🤦🏻‍♂️ https://t.co/0kJwvrxx4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Marco, God knows your heart, but, in my books you're a hypocrite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: We’re officially in that extremely rare time of the year when it’s around 65 degrees and the sun is shining, it’s GORGEOUS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Trump-Kim romance seems to have a bit of dominant-submissive kink to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahShachtman @marschaebee When they share a Facebook account or a bed after 30 years of marriage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/TO7yUAmjOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sports are so interesting because grown men are paid millions of dollars to play children’s games... what a concept.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now abide faith, hope, love, these three; but the greatest of these is love. I Corinthians … https://t.co/vCOTehQZem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kystatepolice Westbound lanes I275 COMPLETELY blocked for one hour - nice...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@no_pullbacks @alphamakerchris That is very true.  Bad for ppl like me who don’t do it for a living so have to hold… https://t.co/qzGxvDWIvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katie_honan @JoeCrowleyNY This epiphany dovetailed with the loss of his other job and his start of his new job?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hamudlaw @ADodek Great. So if existing human rights law and principles of non-discrimination cover the field, no n… https://t.co/pgYf73SlXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our boys are currently getting the opportunity to listen to a panel discussion from some great retired Law Enforcem… https://t.co/KUElRF0pGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollingsBridger I mean hey. I only deal in facts. I was really pullin for em too]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to see what a nuclear bomb going off looks like up close, watch someone say the word “no” to a white mi… https://t.co/Lsr9R6qlEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜🦋 Fighting for the #lupus cure starts with learning more about the #disease Raise your awareness 🙌💜📚💜 #educate you… https://t.co/DkdID9etsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You mean the guy who is trying to make it harder for people to vote?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaHilyer @StormIsUponUs As bad as the government wants to control speech in America, they know they can’t so the… https://t.co/hKjtxXVck0]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG, It looks like a " Bronsolean ",piece!! $24.95, HMU only 1 left! https://t.co/nWKw0upApl]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that; it’s gone. However we will build it back bigger, better, and stronger stay tuned! #VANGARD @ Va… https://t.co/3wPZexmB5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tfickenscher @SalfordGroup @BakerSalf @NateLegler @isufarmer To my bar. Replacing ST-10 for the new ST-12. 2 ton e… https://t.co/sMWG1gGDVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mourinho cree que la opinión pública habría sido más dura con él si hubiera sido él quien hiciera el gesto que hiz… https://t.co/OtuZhMnsur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bigboss76513626 @DDDGURU @SteinmetzNBA you a real tough guy on twitter... probably still live at your moms house,… https://t.co/d7Vipb8Ph2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClayTravis It will not surprise me in the least when he wins the Espy for courage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwd40 @Nicky_DAgs I wouldn’t make a change, even if it was 100% tactical error on rider’s part...poor rides happen… https://t.co/0fCoZilhBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zalman888 Praying King’s elbow issue is just a blip.  So much has to go right for Florial in improving his contact. But talent is there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theologymatt @ecampbellreed I was so interested I spent 8 years part-time getting an MDiv.  I'm not interested in… https://t.co/LfHWlMCcOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra You know the problem with @AOC is she did something that no one expected and got elected. Then she ma… https://t.co/jtx8MXQ2Tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody:   Deezul truck owner: Yeah bro it's got all the deletes, 35's, rolls coal, sucks my caulk and can haul a single pallet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Whole Lotta Ruckus by @revisionbrewing @ Launch-Ness Monster — https://t.co/dE8n0NUSyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Please Prosecute all of them and put them behind bars and send a message]]></document><document><![CDATA[Won doubles today at @LAN_Hero with  @ShiNe_Smash. Ngl winning today gave me a bunch of confidence going into… https://t.co/z5jyFXfzyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is aware that the Bulls beating a good team is a good thing, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ngl i popped off just now. I hope you know you’re a fuckin joke LOL flexing when you obviously aint shit. I laughed… https://t.co/Q54OJPOXU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAGalaxyFanTalk Or maybe u had a world class coach that had a game plan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you still Addicted in 2019?  One of my favorite tune on my playlist for surgery. We are addicted to our thought… https://t.co/9cJFtLZZSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck on your new journey @DilfersDimes.  We serve an incredibly big God and it sounds like he’s not done with… https://t.co/IaXkBBsAPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a #ATATWalker #StarWarsTattoo at #musink2019 LOVE IT! https://t.co/AFz5TTCbCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fun #friends #upstate #newyork #travel #winter #redhookny #snow @ Red Hook, New York https://t.co/nZ16aIV008]]></document><document><![CDATA[hating on me with an empty stomach and a broken screen, ain’t you dizzy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__chaachii_ people think it’s so weird &amp; im jus like 🤦🏽‍♂️ that shit is amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great times radiosocial tonight doing a @flxtable pop up and @elementwinery dinner! Really cool to see so many frie… https://t.co/EYiCuPS1V6]]></document><document><![CDATA[El doble discurso de la 4T, columna  "A 40 Grados", por Sebastián Moreno @Sebastmd / @ramonriveraval1 @Elparaclito… https://t.co/Jc9ZlAONaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@80sWrestlingCom Is there any chance I could mail you something in to get signed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Performed at the Industry Mixer last Wednesday at The Enclave Studios! I had a great time meeting new artist and se… https://t.co/7QqPJIFkQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oligarchs in the Morning! @7BOOMERESIASON is all-in defending Jeff Bezos and Fred Wilpon on the radio this AM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has someone passed a law in the U.K. that Lily James has to be in absolutely every single British film?  Don’t get… https://t.co/K4oEGgLHGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deja Prendo La Cafetera Para Mi Cafecito Mientras Da Inicio Hoy #HoyconMhoni #MartesdeMhoni Nuevas #Predicciones 🔮… https://t.co/0KzFYOGQu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @allmanbrothers trio of Jessica, In Memory of Elizabeth Reed, &amp; Little Martha. ✌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoingRight1 @_achilles65_ The question is incomplete. The real issue is more about man’s contribution or lack ther… https://t.co/pRyn1GKnhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 State Wrestling Champions!  #collinsvillecardinals @ Oklahoma State Fair Arena https://t.co/DOPuJSS2We]]></document><document><![CDATA[@G_L_A_D_Y_S_ @cyndilauper Cyndi has such an amazing memory. I ❤️ your picture. It’s a joyful picture of you w her.… https://t.co/cUZOvLK9eQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One 💙! ! Impeach Trump &amp; prosecute, now! https://t.co/iddNpFyIxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll get back to this later but quite frankly it’s time for me to be a 28 YEAR OLD FUN HAVER for a couple minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go and Tell evangelism seminar is an easy way to equip you to share the gospel. Go and Tell is free online at… https://t.co/6XfaogwRLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a sneak peek into the next addition to the @mitchellpooltables collection! #badasspooltable #coolpooltables… https://t.co/dG8DdsRHvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not going to be fat anymore. I’m tired of all the mustard on my clothes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody in ATL need some Bas tickets? Willing to sell then jawns at face value. Idk if I'm tryna go anymore lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parscale @KatrinaPierson @Nike @realDonaldTrump Emergency!! Call China and have them use more gum!! This is more s… https://t.co/QRUv6cTo48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmineZozzora LBJ said, you don't need no daddy's,. Uncle Sam  gonna be yo daddy.  Another racist democrat settin… https://t.co/Bzlvh2W3qA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mboyle1959 Very impressive! Looks like she’s got a bright future ahead of her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, we can leapfrog if we harness mobile technology to build a robust human capital that is knowledgeable and globa… https://t.co/zStbpHTCP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister I’ve never seen a MAGA hat here in Chicago. I do see a lot of signs saying “no to hate” in my north… https://t.co/Q0Ezv0I94B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I think the free throw counts for each team tell that story pretty well, but missing open shots and an inabili… https://t.co/V4oOUYv666]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urbanexus What the author doesn’t know is that ride sharing companies are in a war for market share in anticipatio… https://t.co/b9RM7qMBlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black novelist James Baldwin vividly described the phenomenon of racist brutality in his 1962 novel, “Nobody Knows… https://t.co/jjeTqd8WdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard the new @bartelldrugs ad on the @NPR radio this morning - they are promoting that they have measles vaccine “… https://t.co/36kmQCSg8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔴 William Barr Flusters Hirono After Telling Her He Won't Recuse Himself... https://t.co/ySOQ71xQw6 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laughing my bachelor ass off, ding dong the wicked bitch is gone. Good job Colton #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kooder67 Could you imagine? I’d love to see his DMs with Simmons... 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the brilliant writing team at WWE can write a face @RealMelina character they can write a face character for @SonyaDevilleWWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton All your words are BS you are as corrupt as they come we must move with out you]]></document><document><![CDATA[People watching at the BMW dealership is definitely a unique experience]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walt Disney World Trip 2018 - Beautiful topiaries at The Crystal Palace in Magic Kingdom! We booked in for a Charac… https://t.co/aeQ33RyGb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elrenecito2 @gueronieves @dalcz @GildardoReal @JavierDagnino @juanarmentam @alejandralopesn @MiguelSesmaQ… https://t.co/KjCGjjDjAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squaasha but the people want to know about your PIZZA OPINIONS  plus the rest is cancer, ravenclaw, and tbh I have… https://t.co/Se5XcwkLIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last time we had a snowday and there was like no snow. Today there’s a lot of snow and we just have a delay 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivibarreral @Santifer57 Es mucho más hermosa en portugues, y si me la recitas en portugués te amaré toda la vid😉.… https://t.co/DDvadiujvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[main squeeze. 🍋 #besties @ Sonora Diamondback Grill https://t.co/mfpwY8mP7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a honor to be with Pastor @AnthonyNeedham I love being around Kingdom minded people. Beautiful church buildi… https://t.co/BfrPn0QSAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch me on @wusa9 with @brucejohnson9 at 7pm tonight . Tune In #Slugg #DayofEmpathy #DayofEmpathyDC #DCorNothing @… https://t.co/WIxCDwrAX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealTimBlack Speak loudly Tim.  Thanks for your voice on this.  I disagree with this too.  They are pandering.  I… https://t.co/n7PQS3DfPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good but whisky aged doesn't compare to bourbon barrels. - Drinking a Barrel Aged Black by @centerpointbrew at… https://t.co/Voc3JPzvd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Nice job idiot !!!!  How many potential jobs just left your district today?  Do you have any clue just how stu… https://t.co/lgSxfM17FD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dsgersten @BrooksBrothers @DynCon365 Maybe we’ll need to retake a team picture at the next conference now that you… https://t.co/SZPQ5BDwI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tania_con_i Exacto.  O los cabrones de aquí que nada más se la pasan con indirectas...digo no tienen huevos ni din… https://t.co/iHED9Q01ay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year I saw the ocean for the first time in a long time. I had forgotten how beautiful it was. Sometimes you ne… https://t.co/ZcIdawC0yy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReBourneAgain sasha bayley eliminated so oh god who knows whats gonna happen now who'd they piss off in the back lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBBonFOX @IowaHoops You could do a full game length livestream of the control room.  I’d watch that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart @WhiteHouse Does she send out the tweets in Russian? Make America Great Again- bring back Measles.. -… https://t.co/eIT4F8pN1F]]></document></documents></author>