<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[GREAT NEWS: My #BlackAmericana #song "The Whiskey Wouldn't Let Me Pray" made it to the finals in the ISC.… https://t.co/VpW1BvVL75]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE when Dropbox starts syncing all of my photos from my phone onto our SHARED WORK ACCOUNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indigo_Nai But I’ve heard that some vaccinations are “laced” with other things to kill off certain communities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdPowdrhnd67 I think Sam looks like an older version of Chris, they lool like they could be related.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There needs to be a new Punisher movie made with Jon Bernthal.... that would be amazing! 😮😍😍😍😍💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t agree with Trump on most things, but if you leave the country to join ISIS, you don’t deserve to return.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @thejuniperspoon for serving our lamb at the 2019 Small Farms Conference! #silvervalleyfarm… https://t.co/Dp1sk6wGn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianCcanada1 @6thSens @redscarfunion Oh don’t worry I’m a part of the #melnykout bots lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilieeelove Especially here they just give you them automatically in your drink ! But you’re doing great!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[so I’m at this lil mexican joint and I ask the waiter where the restroom is and he giggles and says “it’s thru that… https://t.co/sYPyDDJiF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusaTariq @caro @Airbnb So @tsmith I think I know what we're doing next weekend 🐴 https://t.co/52ByC99EZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurarichards99 @GayleKing @CBSThisMorning Gail King is so awesome! Great composure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calm Birth and Hypnobirthing is a great way to focus on your body and your baby throughout childbirth, acknowledgin… https://t.co/bItU5uPDvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the kids from NY don’t have school this whole week but here in jersey they do.... da fuQ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rocking socks this morning helped me rock the climbs during #computrainer class this morning. That and a new… https://t.co/u7GWedUlir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oscars2019Live_ Qué belleza anunciando el premio a mejor película extranjera en Español. ¡Bravo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheyianne_ Lmao throwback to when we were in Costa Rica and how we bonded bc we were both so over it and ready to get back on the bus]]></document><document><![CDATA[YAAAASSSS 🙌🏽🙌🏽🙌🏽🙌🏽🙌🏽#GodISGoodALLtheTime!!!! @ReginaKing @BealeStreet congratulations! #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff What else was he suppose to say you ass, he is trying to stop a war from happening, that we may not… https://t.co/x6g4Fz5DxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to all my #Tweethearts! I’m so blessed to have the love and support from each and every one of you! 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's such a privilege to be sitting around the table with so many rockstars in the suicide prevention field. Inspir… https://t.co/C7XlIl82WX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayasax Sitting next to Ursula Le Guin who was also attending a panel at a science fiction convention we were both… https://t.co/xAURk39tM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I like most about men is their egos ☺️ it’s very hot and sexy when a guy says “I’m the best”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Keep on keeping on! I am completely thrilled to read your opinions and agree every time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I genuinely hate when somebody messages you and asks you if you were somewhere earlier, instead of coming up to you… https://t.co/flrma6ByHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[should i change my username on insta &amp; make my youtube acc http.caroline]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silas would love ❤️ it if you wrote a nice review on ITunes, Amazon, Rotten Tomatoes and IMDb of @HitlerBigfoot… https://t.co/fNBcuydGvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DareenFatimah @slurrysoslurry @CP24 The point of the alerts is to alert everyone in the nation to be on the lookou… https://t.co/L3DEhknhm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday... also known as “Will Colton jump the fence/wall Day” @BachelorABC https://t.co/DKxPnjer1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awaiting baby Flores, but until then we showered the Momma and Daddy with love and gifts. @ Grand Terrace, Californ… https://t.co/DkTnJ7LE3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheonlyAkorede No bad...is this what his father brought him here to be doing 💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jchick11 @Hanover_GBball @phspythons @crusaderswbball @CHSLadyHoops @EHS_girlshoop @WindhamAthletic @slbdgbb… https://t.co/WAv8z0Icla]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating all of the women in my life!  My mother, sisters, aunts, family, coworkers, friends, colleagues, client… https://t.co/nndT5R7SJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netanyahu @TimesofIsrael @Israel @IsraeliPM @IsraelinUSA @JewishVoice @JTAnews @JewishChron @Bloomberg #jews… https://t.co/LhGoh6zxL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmSteveHarvey What happened to your radio broadcast in Houston  TX Miss you in the mornings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Starlight (feat. Myles Kennedy) by @Slash on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/sxjML7uqKx https://t.co/O8bQ9Lwt3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithUrban OMG just heard your coming to Louisville, You Bet Your Britches Ill Be There!!!!♡♡♡♡]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You don’t microwave relationships!” Tayshia’s dad - so good! #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[A todos nos han roto el corazón alguna vez. Todos hemos tenido que irnos cuando no queríamos irnos. Alguna vez nos… https://t.co/PUkElFdfSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to joining this amazing lineup at #SXSW2019 for a conversation on #micromobility and how #cities ca… https://t.co/5B8kDUQGLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The focus look on my sayang face when she working at home is very charming and cute 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mother_Faulkner She wakes up every morning at 6 am to paddle board but also loves ironing shirts. She’s tall and b… https://t.co/DB6Dpm09O4]]></document><document><![CDATA[all i gotta say is thanks for lying to me when you said you never would.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How could I forget?! Goldilocks was sentenced to 100 hours of community service (jury couldn't find concrete eviden… https://t.co/ECNyZmfL93]]></document><document><![CDATA[a few powerful images from today. stay tuned for more via @theCSPN https://t.co/T0IS6ktl5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[R. Kelly's younger brother says he's afraid that the singer may harm himself to avoid potential prison time tied to… https://t.co/V9xSOacjp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Satellites reveal North Korean rocket facility activity  https://t.co/f73uq9OO8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standing room only for Dr. Mirza’s @kmirza hemepath unknowns! Beautiful glass slides, and great tips for the boards… https://t.co/WhpfrKShWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other day I did such a good wet Willie that I said it deserved to be called a met William and I’m still laughing about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julian_moffit I know it's so pathetic! And the Sister was used as a prop as I tweeted earlier! That was a STUPID t… https://t.co/HlG9FxukOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeMorris186 @SlidellPD @OfficialLivePD @danabrams @Sean_C_Larkin I know you’re happy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoyGeorge Akkkk I’m posting things before I scroll down and then the next post down of yours has similarities to m… https://t.co/l8SyHQUwjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigDTwo @bindelj @Heritage So I’ll take that as a yes. Good luck with your extreme homophobia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NCFFA Students prepared and served breakfast to the WCHS Staff in honor of FFA Week and CTE Month.  #NCFFA… https://t.co/AbGftEEc1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[😭😭😭 Just watched the season finale of #AMillionLittleThings... @AMillionABC when does Season 2 start?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoirAmnesiac Domestic terrorism is still mostly Islamic. Remember Omar Mateen killing 50 men in a gay bar? ISIS cl… https://t.co/r3Y63ZShv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiThisIsJen @DizzyDi72 @Bebhearli @wwwbigbaldhead @SuzieSaysPlease @Moonkat1234 @smoking_reedus @joanne111100… https://t.co/oTgT0Qn1Al]]></document><document><![CDATA[@replouiegohmert @UNCF No idea why @UNCF would give you anything, let alone let you give a speech😂🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a wonderful weekend at such a beautiful campus. It might’ve been 29° and snowing but we made the best of it to… https://t.co/TvQ6siMqMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LunarSkulls Like why not wait until you’re outside to beat their ass. Come on 😫😫😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Investor_Smith Always loved Nipsey and I love how he’s never strayed away from his values, beliefs and wants for his community and beyond!]]></document><document><![CDATA[im so close to being done with the vampire diaries then I’m starting the originals finally 🥰🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I camera roll is full of pictures of Jensen I’m so happy since Friday what a good way to start spring break ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@real_defender @realDonaldTrump Not me. I prefer someone w/a higher IQ than you seem to possess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Table manners 101. #trainhard #focus #happydog @ Sheboygan Falls, Wisconsin https://t.co/w3J9atuBqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️☃️… https://t.co/wFYSiZ8lCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strongforecheck THIS IS VERY TRUE AND I DID THINK ABOUT IT WHILE WRITING THIS. YOURE THE ONLY PERSON ON EARTH WHO… https://t.co/idcna3ZupO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@admiralelite15 I hope one day you’ll sit down and read all these comments! Just so you’ll know how much we love you 😍 thank you. Admiral!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnorHapper @937TheTicket I am so tired of people coddling these kids. Kids need to learn how to lose. In life, s… https://t.co/KfjeQNxKr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewScheer Andrew if elected would you get your Public Safety, Justice Ministries together to enact swift and tr… https://t.co/V5hnxagh05]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer Gold-plated and worthless just like Trump. https://t.co/ah5uxp7LzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustriaJ_ i would’ve evacuated school it’s never a good sign when they run mad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else noticed ants inside this season? Just saw some going after my  sugar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gl3nnc4rt3r @GaolbirdSal @NadimNaaman Such a tragedy! People should be honored for their talent not their beliefs.… https://t.co/27dkAFZI0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #StreamSetup.  GIVE ME ALL TNE #LEDLIGHTS! @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/zmXzgwGdXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopping home before a concert in Hammond Indiana. (@ Home Sweet Home in Wheaton, IL) https://t.co/MR97ZhL9kP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@margret_hammy @Mwfis @retired_ada @PAAttorneyGen @POTUS So are you a British multiple karate champion, as my Googl… https://t.co/FiEDYRLpCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nation_myers Noooo. Just I would only wash what we needed to get by cuz I was always busy. Now during this time of… https://t.co/gUbSUopQLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me! Me! I saw this cover and knew my @HMSpageturners would eat it up! #kidsneedbooks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Preston Lakes, Frisco, Texas https://t.co/MqNQQ05ON7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpockResists @StormResist @porpentina2017 @IronManResists @meg_Y12 @TrisResists @LunaLuvgood2020 @chappie_cat… https://t.co/oOrSVG3SQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s investigate her. Heard her and her husband did some corrupt things with a bank.👺👺👺👺👺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wuttangie @AstorAaron @ToriTeal1 @GetBenThompson @maggieNYT As, I clearly stated, she is representative of the wom… https://t.co/JYyhmaUGje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn’t matter what @alissa_ashleyy does everyone just wants to be mad lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelindaHoward4 You’re on fire today! I literllay lol’d at this and a few others today. Thank you. 😊👊🏻❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @Sara_Givens ‼️‼️ Thank you for being some positive and awesome every time I see ya. Hope today is great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdawsey1 DEAR DON THE CON: It’s impossible to ‘misinterpret’ your statement about Kim and Otto Warmbier. You said… https://t.co/UNNiKs1U31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Heidirathjen I agree with you that our gun laws are far too weak. Toronto is getting as bad as some of the bigger… https://t.co/HuBwNsvmH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bien dicho @MiamiSup it is who we are and who are parents are or were. With my corazon lleno de pride por ser quien… https://t.co/tNvmlrjvQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hahasierra @chrisdelia @brendonurie literally two of my favorite things, so here for the crossover]]></document><document><![CDATA[Far reaching response for Team Buzzy :(. Power down in our neighborhood during FJ. Impressive superior effort!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DahliaBlue3 @sarahkendzior Narcissists and sociopaths ALWAYS accuse others of their own actions or fantasies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rodneyroe @Yousaf83 @uhhmommy @S98Billy @IlhanMN They play for New England represent no one... being from NY I’m f… https://t.co/QeYRhuEhqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliamichaels Thank you for motivating me with your words of encouragement. i love you more than words can even be… https://t.co/SgzBa1s74W]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is constantly hostility because of a certain manager micromanaging everyone (including me, despite being her… https://t.co/WERXxHPguJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyy_dee_ I’m just glad I passed I walked out that test so depressed LOL 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Media? @CNN  @MSNBC  @CBSNews  @NBCNews  @ABC  @Acosta  @costareports  @HeidiNBC  @shelbyholliday  @AriMelber… https://t.co/W6vHYhQjLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmac_1025 @PorthGame @1025TheGame you know I love the Colton love! #Preds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamHeughan Congratulations SAM!! Well deserved!! 😊♥️🤗♥️😉♥️😘🏴󠁧󠁢󠁳󠁣󠁴󠁿⚔️🇺🇸🤴👑👸🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m obsessed with this water bubble. #Pokemon #PokemonSwordandShield #starterpokemon #sobble #SobbleSquad https://t.co/nnGTikeRws]]></document></documents></author>