<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I babysat for my friend’s 4 year old tonight. While I was there I pretended call and enroll him in monkey school. I… https://t.co/e8pSRjJoui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LionelMedia personally I don't want Muslims here at all in America they do not assimilate they come to take over i… https://t.co/MLiv3NCn6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatbyNature @mariashriver @TheBethPhoenix you and @NatbyNature are always beautiful❤️😻😻😻😻😻 https://t.co/HFSTm8ZvFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_axelrod @realDonaldTrump He was soooo bad you employed him for 10+ years? Seriously stop trying to change the… https://t.co/x2HfzM4lZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Claribel_Ortega I’m so sorry for your loss, Claribel. My younger brother died two years ago. Sending love and hugs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A powerful story that gives a glance into the lives of poor and working-class people living in “flyover County.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Port Dalhousie, Canada. Hace unos días.  Camino donde los ángeles  descienden del ocaso. https://t.co/EJgw8SPljF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only Valentine’s Day card that really matters https://t.co/UTYTxTpVDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just read the latest poetry drama on Twitter and @jasminnemendez and I started singing out intro song : 🎶White Pe… https://t.co/Beywx1BkEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Claire no way called her mom belle to help Haley #days today.She facked calling her! She wants her way from Tripp!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing off our scare skills!!! @ Walt Disney World https://t.co/BGEzo9YCoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen's bombshells just keep dropping. Holy shit!! #CohenTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bopinion @bethechange76 GO GREEN, NO POP PILLS... MENTAL ILLNESS  WEALTHY,WEALTHY BEINGS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God's promises are yes and amen 🌸 . . . #DeclareAndDecree #HighlyFavored #AMustardSeedFaith #Anointing #Grace … https://t.co/Ey0olBKF2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RloretdeM1 @YouTube Mayoría, usted tiene buenas intenciones y mucho conocimiento, pero por ejemplo usted se desesp… https://t.co/jolTapb1j4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Farewell for now, #SanDiego   What a wonderful week of learning new things, making new friends, and creating powerf… https://t.co/ol3COiJtLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyJKoch @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump We have a list as well AOC...🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SurrealBrain @skyboundgames @Skullgirls @LabZeroGames I have it on my vita but a hard copy will be great]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know why it's so God-damned hard to get the bastards at Twitter to do something about those who doxx and th… https://t.co/AAK1BLi6ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[this reminds me of that episode of it’s always sunny with the egg frank wanted to merchandise]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the people here in the US had a choice they would work the 40 hours a week. Most people cannot feed themselves a… https://t.co/WJAwlVpG9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never have I seen a lake as gorgeous as Lake Tahoe. Beautiful and stunning. I felt like I could sit there and liste… https://t.co/4oUVHn7NBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[D O N ‘ T   M I S S   O U T ! ! ! A great opportunity for a first home, second home, or investment. #northpark… https://t.co/NvUNvNiCS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me on world's First classic Tonk Multiplayer https://t.co/vFvazMN2pF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meatloaf... I love meatloaf I never make it the same way.. and I prefer it cold the next day. https://t.co/S2h0svCv5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course this happens 1 week AFTER I leave my New York office...which is THAT building 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Haha.  Trump is an overweight slobbering old man compared to Obama.  We want our Obama back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmarshwx It seemed like it had arrived on my way in to work around 330pm. The dusty brown haze over everything was… https://t.co/bwqlAaYytM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naijagym this post is from 2 years ago and the answer will still always be yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[a night on the town with some beautiful women 🍷🥀 @ Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania https://t.co/a32ZA992Hi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Where the hell do you get these numbers, @FoxNews? Talk about fake news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolaPerez0109 El privilegio que el Creador puso al pie de mi puerta y la bendición  de quienes podemos reconocerlo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s all fun &amp; games until someone walks in n scares u to the point that u accidentally break shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now imagine these floating apts in polluted water or no water. Maybe Trump will understand climate change if we sho… https://t.co/nqKOPNIp4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Código de policía que refleja la mentalidad represiva que impera en la sociedad colombiana. Vergüenza...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HojokoBoston is the proud new owner of @Edelman11 beard trimmings! This super cool restaurant located near Fenway… https://t.co/JEFvclciMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Trackstar1 Lol I already know 🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️ it’s an evil world we live in]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not enough time in the day to explain everything @LanceStorm did for me. He taught me everything I know. I wouldn’t… https://t.co/erZ7xbywty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 I have accepted a challenge from @Moonekev to post #7BooksILove-no explanation, no reviews-just cover(s). 1 c… https://t.co/Fd1lh5zgiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PNCBank_Help I don’t recognize a $40.00 transaction on my account how can I find what it is without putting a stop… https://t.co/0rXqPTXw5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lasttextreceived “Hi it’s Brian T.! Your past #VEGAS promoter! Wanted to REACH OUT IN CASE you lost my info!” Oh b… https://t.co/aY1uQCZlkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[God Speed Please! The DemonRats at the @DNC are over reaching! Fed UP American LEGAL CITIZEN is FED THE FD UP! PERI… https://t.co/4nt566QqXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching The Good Doctor on @hulu and see ad for @QuestNutrition and I know: These are my people. I ❤️… https://t.co/Lyej9vfvps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseDemocrats @HouseGOP @TheFive @LouDobbs @SenateDems @SenateGOP @POTUS 'You didn't build that by yourself'--Inf… https://t.co/SC3UEaSHjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[First week of March is in the books. #planneraddict #eclp #teamhorizontal #plannerlove @ The Enclave https://t.co/pv33OOT0o2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davelackie @reviews_yay_nay @voirhaircare Ooohhh awesome! Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holidayobsessi1 “If you face disappoint planning a holiday always helps” 😅 Such true advice. https://t.co/l2A8sarAoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy as heck to see Kamala Harris call for paper ballots in elections saying in part, "Russia can't hack a piece o… https://t.co/bMRjsa5yGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando enseñas con amor y disciplina, @gapmeta23 siempre consigues un resultado asombroso. Flamencas ampliando sus… https://t.co/sM7pxmiQ1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 15" alpine With box for sale $250 @ Tallahassee, Florida https://t.co/9MloTPJrCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergyHeddy @drenight1 I have to stay away for my own safety you know I’m autistic believe it or not !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TananariveDue Or why no one in the Rose Garden is standing up, turning off their cameras, and walking out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlessandraAslzr @Jhoananallely Jajajajajjaj un poco tarde me vengo a enterar 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chronotope Don’t tell the people who are still putting up those boilerplate posts saying “blah blah blah you don’t… https://t.co/iwcGbf4DMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to be in a new studio in my favorite part of Miami. #littlehaiti  #laundromatartspace #dvcai… https://t.co/zZOEbXGMpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Organizing should be making you humble. If it's not making you humble, it might be a sign that what you're doing isn't organizing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michie8 @behindblueyes72 @kez2009 @EternityBroken4 @MelliDuevel @melli Agree on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy happy birthday Jeannie! The years and memories get harder for me to remember but you my friend remember every… https://t.co/xo4Qd6kiF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Syfyfangrrls Saw it last night, and will be seeing it again tomorrow afternoon! #CaptainMarvel https://t.co/G7exOtNYuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elysethompsonn   WE WERE INFANTS IN THIS PIC 😫 https://t.co/3lnNo5J1Dr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surround yourself only with people that will take you higher!  -Oprah- #internationalwomensday 💃🏾💃🏾#blessedwithlove… https://t.co/UjR3ZMLYu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JilldarWu @ElenneMigo @yellowbelle @DestiniLozano @Lanasanette @marykk196051 @AngelsCumber @JazzmaCumberful… https://t.co/23RbumpPaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidMcKayTV @WFSBnews Congratulations and best wishes to you and Ali.  Always a pleasure seeing you out on stories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TinyBoxTink @BeMoreChill I see what you did there! https://t.co/9V65f8jwi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lwaterfield13 @StoupasTeresa @KimSandel2 I second wanting to go back to fourth grade- just to be in her class!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[East &amp; Lafollette tied at 36 in a Regional final at Lafollette. Under 11 mins to go in half. #wisgb  @EHSGBBALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh, yes, kill me birthday boy!! It’s Tobirama’s birthday!! https://t.co/bMX5btYNuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great coach and great player. So excited for @BryceButler_5  to be part of this team!.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is #Galentines Day! Will you celebrate with your gals?! Let’s see those friend pics so we can share on… https://t.co/xUoEdMcq5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is Not right for Russian Federation 🇷🇺 to intimidate little guys like Ukraine 🇺🇦 Moldova 🇲🇩 Azerbaijan 🇦🇿 and Ge… https://t.co/bsBJOQjXkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe I bobbled a bit when trying to get a bike share bike underway from a standstill on my way to a work… https://t.co/VPzgHhdf6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a #badasspenguinfeet kind of day @ Kearney, Nebraska https://t.co/UURsIirU2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could always be as happy as the first sip of coffee makes me feel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom said “did you pack today?” Lol no I’m on season 10 of Big Bang Theory]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BestonOriginals Follow me, I follow back all #MAGA #KAG #MAGAVETS #DEPLORABLES  #TRUMPVILE #TRUMPSUPPORTERS… https://t.co/tNjkmLnnSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[personally thanking @BIGVEGETABLEASS for ONLY playing Mancala w me for the last few days bless u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randy_jr1 @cmoody14107 Can he like share some of his hair with Sadie becauuuuuse.... Girl is thinning 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m kinda drunk hahahahahahahhahaha😂 It’s probably best to get off my phone 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA['it could be anything' acrylic &amp; graphite wash on canvas, 22x28", 2019 #abstraction #abstractpainting… https://t.co/mlmjqHIpEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mabel_carrera @SUPERGOCHOo @angieflower59 @ElderAcost @Merquis8 @halconavicencio @Violet_Isak @como_angela… https://t.co/2ScmBjH2WS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvdpeters @TexasDiocese Well, as they say, you can take the girl out of Texas, but you can't take Texas out of the girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhhhh, but it’s Ok to starve them to death after they’re born, denying them Medicaid by not extending it; which wo… https://t.co/6cGxTxfUPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RSCGOP Climate change is not any kind of a threat to humanity. It’s a 💯 % hoax!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would say something on here but y’all wouldn’t be able to handle it !! Ima just say y’all need to repent !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy people in ay someone to tweet against the President like CNN gets paid for Constant Crying Negativity!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perlmutations The man on the right looks embarrassed. He has that “oh no” look.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever notice when #hollywood liberals fuck up you never hear a peep out of them or their Hollywood friends?? 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although I know that there's always that the cyst I had removed might grow back so I'm hoping that it doesn't and t… https://t.co/NoQlvWjZfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tishrich @TaraMartinEDU @dbc_inc @burgess_shelley @burgessdave @wenders88 @iluveducating @hmarrs24 @jbengfort… https://t.co/cbCtRm5el1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @harleyb11 I am incredibly ashamed that @realDonaldTrump is the President. I can only hope this nightmare will end soon!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why we kneel. #TakeAKnee @TheEllenShow had the yodeling kid on, how about this young man?  Also, charge thi… https://t.co/n55izEkX6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[that freaking smile 🤩💕💚😍♥️💛🧡😚💓😸💗😘💚😄💙😺💟💛😚💌❣☺💜😻💘 what a rockstar @ShawnMendes https://t.co/YWjC7fijmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join myself @DrRob_MD and @Richzeoli for the @the_USO Radio-thon this afternoon @ChickiesnPetes in South Philly!… https://t.co/zOVywoy3x8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look how close the votes were for #marchbookmadness round two! And round three has Catcher in the Rye against The G… https://t.co/bwTkCRMarZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody love how real &amp; sweet I am until I say some shit they don’t like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertW48787695 @wecanmag @PrezesPan @DanielBrasilia @DavidLogan2020 @XandraXandraBX @GiselleMarks1 @gaylinnenola… https://t.co/KQvEoDFfJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 @swimmerkw Omg!! This is fucking Awesome!! You have come up with a Genius name for this Generic Wonder D… https://t.co/j2XwXjT6pW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spend more time worrying about you than I worry about myself these days]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘On the Midnight Train’ to Memphis @MsGladysKnight is headed to the #SouthernHeritageClassic concert along with… https://t.co/mq9Wszh6Da]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJusticeDept MISSINGPERSON BILLYGENEHAMMONDS..  Why is this not being addressed ..or even contacted me??? https://t.co/hfvebZvzX1]]></document></documents></author>