<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@lno09281978 @MsAFromBK @Jordandelmont2 @SandiMarie79 @DragonMom98 @Crazy4OReilly90 @JustPlainT @SabreKevin1639… https://t.co/vbzLe33rMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video grabado con el Samsung Galaxy S10+. Fue capturado en 4K a 30fps con HDR10, aunque acá no se aprecia el HDR. https://t.co/D0RNZhADQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when I'm in a good mood jamming and catch myself singing some @iamcardib lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[in emergency break glass 💔 #bwoodknows #madeinnyc #swish electric 🌈 @ Lower East Side https://t.co/zxuAceRuYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CirkusMaximus @ADemocratica @hramosallup @psicoanaya A mi no me cobra, y es un placer conversar con ella.]]></document><document><![CDATA[More than medically recommended Jutsu. - Drinking a Double Jutsu by @bellwoodsbeer @ Newmarket, Ontario  — https://t.co/76OJx4kCus]]></document><document><![CDATA[She ready! @JaniceHuff4ny is on Watch What Happens Live with @Andy on @BravoTV! https://t.co/aHS8eJADBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still rockin’ that pronounced Kim Kardashian backside 🍑 #foodieproblems • • • • • • #kittens #cuteness #funnycats… https://t.co/VjJHFDTiDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is actually pretty cool, though. I immediately started trying to build a story about how this could happen. LO… https://t.co/lifjO09FeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport @A_WHITE_5 if you do this make sure you make the shots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@s_oo_cc Hmm interesting - not sure they achieved their aim of revolutionising video! 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillmkelly12 Jim Kelly is Buffalo. My idol growing up in the late 80s to 90s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACFbaseball20 @acflorahigh @JackEasterby @Patriots Clean @JackEasterby]]></document><document><![CDATA[As for work, the database project at Catholic Community Services is finishing up this Friday. It's been a good experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I chose to not get tattooed when I was young due to fact that I was on the wrong side of the road for a while and t… https://t.co/uMzCBTh8bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We still have a few tickets left for our First State Democratic Dinner with Keynote Speaker VP Biden.… https://t.co/3LAqb1S4HR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @boeing737 just keeps getting better over the years. @united alone is flying over 250 of the nextgen! Grateful… https://t.co/mRfFx1kb19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I’ve been watching this video for 83 minutes now. https://t.co/1IX1gtJ1Rx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump STAY UNITED  This STAY is LegA-L United for All E-WALLS public And privAte  NOTE TENDER DEBTS STAY… https://t.co/NxkSI8W6yN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking of planes, I feel like I’m in for some trouble at SFO tomorrow https://t.co/SYhIot6UuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KJBanach @SalSports You’re in dreamland if you believe Hughes is worth a first]]></document><document><![CDATA[created this remix . Q: “Can Black folks stop blaming whites for everything?” . Speaker: James Baldwin Baldwin was… https://t.co/W9bfrh8jVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burger for the road #RVA #VIRGINIA #change #solid https://t.co/JPCMjL7xdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UnderConstruction | Why Is A Global Grassroots Supply Chain Community Starting in NYC, and Charleston, SC? https://t.co/vve78S12ni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bob_Lazzari @PittsburghSport @SteelDad @Steeler_Girl77 @pittsburghst_dp @SteelersBros @steelers Addition by subtra… https://t.co/gKT6BN0vop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger Jennifer, I think if a landslide comes, it will be a lot further left than you prefer. The conservat… https://t.co/3i3f62iYeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard Its the elusive "glass ceiling". Democrats dont create solutions Only problems to exploit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegan friends, what supplements do you take to get Omega-3 and other essential nutrients?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben Simmons had his wake against the Celtics and Funeral against the Knicks 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mickeyhart @GratefulDead @FriezeArtFair This is a wall I can get behind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJDEMARAY @Shaolin_Prophet @charliekirk11 No wonder we didn't make much progress as a society. Explains a lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliner @megtuite @BendingGenres I’m super excited to join in on this fun at the last minute! Thanks to Robert, as… https://t.co/tCoJJMwRzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion alert: even if you don't support pharmacare (I do though) you should still support paying for pri… https://t.co/9iKqehEVw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TTS112019 @PillNation True, cause every time I’m driving 70mph in my car, Hurricane-force winds are pelting my face, amirite?? DO ANNOYING]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular Opinion:  Breaking Bad wasn’t that good of a show.  Bryan Cranston was a great actor in the show though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOP 3 MOST HATED TEAMS —————————————— 1a) Michigan  1b) UNC  2a) All of PIT 2b) ND  3) VT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertWHughes @PlantBasedNews One of the co-authors is a long-time childhood through to adulthood friend of my sister. Small world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A guide (through pictures) to seeing the Big Island of Hawai'i. See all I saw in 72 hours in my latest blog post.… https://t.co/YPTQ0wt8Em]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still remember to this day the moment I put glasses on and could see clearly for the first time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cinemaxwell Honestly wish it had won best picture over what we got, but that’s just me like, personally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamMarquar8 @BrienneTarth6 Thank you, remembered an album cover like that. Was having major brain lock on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesVanFleet Freezing my A$$ off here in Iowa!!!  Anthem in 11 days Cannot get here fast enough!!!! https://t.co/v9cTaf20YH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muffnbear @USATODAY Ah, unintended consequences.   Also, HOLY SHOELACES!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HKA_Tanalski @CodyMandell29 @yannidaboot39 Once again he is at the end of his swing. And how many balls has he kicked in his life again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawnthegourmand Would your husband like to play @FortniteGame with me? I’m streaming it in about 18 minutes! Pleas… https://t.co/kQceXUkDya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 @KathiMost Falwell is to Jesus what Trump is to Mueller.  Toast!! https://t.co/O040cQGeGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karinabarbosa La constitución interpretada por quien? Estoy seguro que para el TSJ @jguaido es un terrorista que v… https://t.co/4I6jcRNDdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnneWheaton @BobRossOfficial That is some wonderful variation there. Yours is lighter, your mountains less craggy… https://t.co/yuSNJUDIfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without “A” scandal, yes it was many scandels. He was the worse President ever. Remember a Democrat looks at what e… https://t.co/OuYMhzTjAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can I go for about 20 hours straight and be on the verge of sleeping while standing up at work but when I final… https://t.co/nbXvBCmSsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChivasseraCampe @alanpulido Soy chiva, pero esto me recordó a esto 😂 https://t.co/iJhcOlvaaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, same reason u flew Air Force one to Vietnam Nam , for nothing . Same reason you shut the govt down at a cost… https://t.co/lTuDuIFYta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayejaxs Smh she don’t even look black but always saying sum bout black people 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Test run, yup, new printer works!  I'm excited to be offering smaller low cost prints (free to subscribing patrons)… https://t.co/JQTJevP71H]]></document><document><![CDATA[it was 31 degrees outside this morning &amp; the number of people i saw wearing flip flops was concerning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was a tough night being a judge on @WorldsBestCBS Vote for your favourite on #WorldsBest by using their hashtag ☺️… https://t.co/8PINrJISMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Medicine is a profession founded on the principles of service, dignity, and compassion.  Yet research shows that ph… https://t.co/5idN882w7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mostly use my browser tabs as a way to keep track of the films I want to watch https://t.co/YrXMlQygsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay away from my tarpon. Love the way the jamesprosek silhouettes showed up in the reflection. @angelesalmuna . .… https://t.co/vK4bLvWLBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarshunKendrick @bluestein @GAWINList @NARALGA @PPSE_Advocates @wabenews I was with you until you got to the toys.   Just kidding]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ianbremmer Are you watching?  No choir boy, for sure, but neither was Joe Valachi.  In the present circumstances,… https://t.co/ay8hHv9wk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[What reality do you live in? The Mueller report will expose you and your cronies, and nothing you say will distract… https://t.co/ee9voFAbvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#APRIL13TH  #MenvsBeast #MelTaylorvsLordSparxx  #zoobattleleague  #barcode @ Micanopy, Florida https://t.co/TbYAm7Zjsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EtaEpsilonPikes Someone made this for MySpace in like 2006. So blurry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@littleredkatTV Haha! Thanks buddy! Keep@grinding!!! I have to tune in soon to show you some luv!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennKesslerWP @washingtonpost Maybe it isn't always the case that the mainstream media is accused of not covering… https://t.co/qHgpNScrYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newenglandgrl @nycSassenach @SamfromSpain @Debra_McGill @GraziaMgb616 @BlackbyrdGyrl1 @SaraMD15 @KarramKaren… https://t.co/RSGpbozzxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestleChatNet Guys watched it and thought the same thing.  Let’s remember that Seth is the one who turn his back… https://t.co/5NmjGL2teb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitziJohnsonVT Excellent. Thank you, @MitziJohnsonVT. Looking forward to working with you now on a woman’s right t… https://t.co/RQnEQc7ucs]]></document><document><![CDATA[At my funeral I'll be performing a "Weekend At Bernie's" style interpretive dance to Ice, Ice, Baby so people can r… https://t.co/3ooY1Q32Dm]]></document><document><![CDATA[No a los mega proyectos de muerte✊🏽 ⁦@lopezobrador_⁩ #SamirFlores #SamirVive   la lucha sigue https://t.co/VI1JBev3ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you tell people you’re an actor in LA they snarl with derision. But in Tallahassee they take your picture, make… https://t.co/LGlqzpn4km]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLEdwardsIII @DarkoStateNews @TheAthleticDET The Pistons are my least favorite professional sports franchise in De… https://t.co/CcDKnnEfkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids waking up at 4 laughing and shit.... like okay fam well I'm going back to sleep, just keep that same energy at… https://t.co/aAnrmStsnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s so good. Always love it when he’s doing a game I’m watching, especially during the NCAA tournament.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul I'll believe it when you start thinking protecting our nation is the most important thing over anything else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEY I’ll be giving a @Tedx Youth talk   March 2 @ 1:35pm  Topic: How Young People Are Leading the Gun Violence Prev… https://t.co/Z5CjuG5L88]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imNickiTaylor @GenG Because anyone who loves Fallout Boy as much as @imNickiTaylor must be a winner 👍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life and Logic are in a dysfunctional committed relationship.  You can't be 'hated on' by people who don't know you… https://t.co/7KTLKq1o1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Baltimore a long #history of #segregation and #racism From Redlining to the Redline https://t.co/kT32UQhVp6 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is amazing! I am a big basketball fan, when I was performing in Australia years ago they took me to watch the… https://t.co/wBAiqXbbyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how much of a dog Isiah Briscoe is, dude doesn’t back down to no one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright, let's go ahead and fast forward to May (hopefully I'll be over whatever super cold I brought home with me.… https://t.co/uLobiLFbLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard to celebrate tonight’s win, but also impossible to stay upset for too long. Lets go @BrooklynNets! #wegohard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally was able to get some good squat work today.  Finished up with my last set 475lbs 3 times.  Shout out to g_d… https://t.co/0pMmX9sEVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is the name of the place you have been in your mind   I was born in this world   My age is so bad that I’m… https://t.co/YYHjl9R8PK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, so if/when the PIHL Postseason schedule gets released expect a Facebook Live on Pittsburgh Hockey Digest’s pa… https://t.co/cERP9YGdth]]></document><document><![CDATA[More people believe Andy McCabe over @realDonaldTrump @PressSec @VP and @KellyannePolls #TimesUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSUNMBB Only a Freshmen but plays like a seasoned veteran,  the future is very bright for CSUN Basketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_Tirado For real man, I got no food here too so I can’t wait to go eat lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simonamangiante @GeorgePapa19 You guys definitely have one of these Awards coming at the 4th of July Celebration… https://t.co/yXsGTkIDpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm in the running to win a custom fit Titleist TS2 or TS3 driver thanks to @GOLFTEC Here's how you can enter the c… https://t.co/FEzV8Oqtx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first job. Toyan’s Barbershop in E. Oakland. Drove my bike here every Saturday morning from 4th-6th grade. Swept… https://t.co/EtWsoTTnk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Penguins game being at 1 o'clock today not doing Duquesne any favors for attendance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who lost their life defending our freedom or was tortured and held captive for years like Senator McCain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noah_fear @TheReallyRandy @walterowensgrpa @AOC A nice double #Waltering here...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McSqueezey You are not just a dissapointment, but a failure. Failure makes us who we are as human beings. "It ain'… https://t.co/PC9ZiKOmlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[HS Coaches if you have a talented player who is a good kid but needs to get out of there environment .. well… https://t.co/rjWKwMZkzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#feed #eat #digest #process #think #become #do #your #choice #my #choice #today #tomorrow #everyday #every #moment… https://t.co/xLqBwyrPJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[MONSTA COMPOUND TIME TO GET IN THAT WORK TODAY!!! #groupfitness #hwpo #training #houstonfitness #killerworkout… https://t.co/hfBGE7kShn]]></document></documents></author>