<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[No words needed...  @CertAngusBeef @Pattonsmeats https://t.co/bYl2D4Q378]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s probably the best “fast food” place to work at tho so I guess the money gets put to good use]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had this at age 5. Was playing with it and fire engines. I found a screw and for some reason swallowed it. My poo… https://t.co/x4BKllPsV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[El noble y valiente pueblo de Venezuela nuevamente en la calle! Que orgullo! La cuenta regresiva está en marcha! Tic Tac! Tic Tac!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tims_Burner @AP_Sports 7th?? Holy cow. Seems like just months ago he was 69th.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we building a wall to keep Michigan water in? We don’t want them getting MI @zumiez revenge...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martyduren @Twitter @SBCExecComm @EC_SBC Study has started and an official report will be made in 2021.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp Are you kidding?  He made up a story claiming 2 Trumpsters attacked him and the mainstream press and celebs… https://t.co/le5JcSRRUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren A minimum wage job could NEVER support a family of 3. Why are you lying??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when all the liberal Democrats had to have those screaming protest. I was thinking it's going to be great… https://t.co/9ihEAFiUWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbrunton76 @rex_rexchapman The “hold my beer” moment, most all learn to regret 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuánto cinismo, pero entiendo que solo escribes una línea por qué así te pagan los de arriba, y ellos felices disfr… https://t.co/Y6O0BRayF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1underpar @aaronjmate Guaido is a socialist and Maduro is a trumpish crook, nevertheless, I agree everyone needs t… https://t.co/RcutJsCjad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bodgei @tgshepherdvan @LetsTalkTigra @LetsTalkMock @angelt18 Bobbi Morse Pole Dancing based off a conversation wit… https://t.co/bGsaPcOkr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yeah and Ambrose chased after Brock after he tried to ruin his match lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandomNewsFeedT @HappyManor @PamelaParesky The replication crisis is limited to social psychology. Not what I do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s fun electrical projects include installing the 220 volt car charger in the garage and a new light switch in… https://t.co/oXzPYGkrNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m NOT even sorry for how I’m about to start acting😭... I been nice too long]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aspiration  Bill Gates says that 30 percent comes from cows farting and belching]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton No, the real national atrocity is you have not been held accountable for Benghazi!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doncates @cosmicbooknews @CBCebulski @DerekLandy @TomBrevoort @cracksh0t This guy sounds like a blast at parties]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet Robert Smalls; #Republican  If Hollywood is looking to make a movie about a real #HERO here he is. Take a look… https://t.co/4ZCxg5IJSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yassin09503578 @SuperSpacedad What are taking about you misogynist! best movie in marvel cinematic history. lol 🤪 #trigger_warning #joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real growth in grace is the result of sanctified trials. God often takes away our comforts and our privileges in or… https://t.co/oyht9Gw4d4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just booked #wedding 6 for 2019! 14 away from reaching my 2019 #weddingplanning goal! #ontarioweddings… https://t.co/q0X4IC0YpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump beat 17 Republicans including Rubio, Cruz, Graham, Walker and Bush in the GOP primary, i’m excited to have qu… https://t.co/ZYC4pl10p9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #EndTheAnthem on @tyltsports. The national anthem has nothing to do with sports https://t.co/LRi8PVBAJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend I learned I'm about a 3rd line grinder on the ice, and I can live with that. My possibly broken hand?… https://t.co/Nw4vH9ssIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngiePalaciosL Así estaba yo con mi viaje a las Vegas y colorado JAJAJAJA 🤦🏻‍♀️🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PC_Angry @KTherev @WYP_IanWilliams @Peter_Kirkham RIPA hardly has a stellar reputation in the eyes of the public.… https://t.co/JLVgAwEMff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@82ndmackin They put our country at risk because of her being moderate and still ended up with an extremist lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was Epic! Mercy! Muse Simulation Theory World Tour! @muse #muse @mattbellamy #MattBellamy @Dominic_Howard… https://t.co/9mYziNQivC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JagTVNews @BSSHSTheater @BSSDnews @bssjaguars Kim and I went to this last night and it was awesome.  Incredible pe… https://t.co/E5F3ykMFPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VexingVixxen I don't have cable ot satellite.  I can download the shows I like.    Now, my morning started at 1:30… https://t.co/c0wdvc8jbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevin_McCashion Hey Sandy,  can I get an Amazon Sunset on the rocks please?   Maybe she can do that right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flybull1 @RNcat50 You want to talk about a racist look at Van Jones I don't know how many times this jackass is ma… https://t.co/bGHYSB7D1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Derbinator I didnt see 1 match I liked tonight I didnt mind the roman speech or wont mind ric's party but the… https://t.co/35jyDaQjYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello beautiful people!  Be sure to tune in to my upcoming podcasts - inspiring stories, interviews, health topics… https://t.co/sTIhaURY5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevorWrites Always thought Zion Williamson would look great in black and silver]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimAnglum If you’re above the age of 13 and you’re asking a player for an autograph, you’re a loser]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmhansler @craving_filled Like money Trump has borrowed from you. Good luck getting it back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had some fun last week at Tin Roof🥁🤷‍♂️. Soling has never been one of my favorite, or anticipated things to do a… https://t.co/suA8t2Q3Ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recovered footage of quite possibly the biggest heartbreak of the century. Man I miss Athens lol https://t.co/EBLCsp5pNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[“@JeffBezos has gotten distracted lately, but he’ll be back” @karaswisher at #CodeCommerce]]></document><document><![CDATA[ST😳NE M💩N-B👀Bzz Flap in The Wind  Until the tip of one Nip Gets C🙈UGHT In Mueller Ringer 😨😰😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Play revolved around a Vietnamese family of three in 2020. The dad is an undocumented immigrant with criminal recor… https://t.co/nuN3WkFAxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my sister on her marriage! Fantastic wedding! 🎉 https://t.co/krhAdy2OIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young and old fall fall victim to domestic violence. So fortunate that we have organizations in the USA that suppor… https://t.co/YWCW9usGap]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY COUSIN DRIVING FOR HER LIFE BACK HOME BEFORE HER MOM WHOOPS HER ASS😂😂😂 https://t.co/8AijDCgVzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Costco congratulations on being ranked #1 over all!! As a member and a stock holder, great job and keep up the gre… https://t.co/f7k7GoPRmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: aye hamz you want a 40 from 7/11 too?   @HamzAllawi: can you just give me a smirnoff ice?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collab the homie Friday glass and I made at the last live demo on first Friday ❤ the onie is sold but the sherlock… https://t.co/VCgjD6MOfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[These 6’s selling out, don’t think they gonna sit, u can still flip...black cement 3’s all over again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarissaLingen @alexandraerin Yeah, I wasn't trying to say it was bad or good, I just find that their cherry pickin… https://t.co/EwyQUzbqVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsElincia If you're going to commit to the grind go straight for the growth egg. It's a game-changer and some late… https://t.co/pU1GEccP2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rory is a xenophobic piece of trash. He’s a joke and I wis @TrueGeordieTG would just put a muzzle on him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@21kiara3 @HHStigerhoops @Bartlett_bball @LancerWBB Outstanding!  Welcome to The Mount!  I’ll see you in class next… https://t.co/3NY7NxeEOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daaanielgeee mom stops me in the middle of the street to have a good 20 min talk LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been jamming to the @killrockstars #201 Comp lately, so  "I don't know why, I got a joke too silly to say. Don't to… https://t.co/ZLFLtKNZ6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilovejohnkimble Some ppk just cant handle Arnie and Tacos.  Fuckers. https://t.co/1YDd2FZIzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rest of the state recognizes the progress Jackson-Madison County is making. If only some of our local folks rec… https://t.co/z9R6SW621P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel Just can't fix stupid.  Trump is going down as the worst president ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama had a cold relationship with  him. It's funny how @realDonaldTrump snuggles up with those criminals  like him… https://t.co/GgVRxbrNrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a #Blockchain meetup in fabulous #LasVegas? @LeeOfAxel of @AXELUnlimited and @Steemcafe talk about… https://t.co/w9JCrcEWvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to see my cats take down Florida again, this time on the hardwood.  Now let's go win some championships  Go Big… https://t.co/VSvgXfEmrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemocrats Killing babies is a national crisis and an act for war. The Saints of God will not be held back on th… https://t.co/BWY1VQnHHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my talented wife’s new website! Schedule of classes for some lucky kids coming soon.… https://t.co/7BYLJxjNBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Crenshaw is exactly right. Government should be a protector of the people not the provider for the people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you made a living off your prize earnings from tourneys and wagers yet? No Do you have a flawless win loss rec… https://t.co/903i30R4CI]]></document><document><![CDATA[View from the stage in this beautiful, old theater. So honored to lead worship here this morning. Thank you connect… https://t.co/DvArxReDGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ford County Youth Entrepreneurship Challenge winners! @networkkansas @ecomm_ks #kseship https://t.co/Ex9X5zoxXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miranndacas 45 has given them all the courage they needed to come out of the closet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drewseph17 how they gonna live on land with no limbs to be able to move around? they’re a fish for a reason 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joined today by the Environmental Defense Fund, @RiceUniversity, @HoustonHealth, and area health departments around  https://t.co/qEw3LQcJZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell As a @DetroitPistons fan Michael Jordan is never the right answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I’m watching @undercover_cbs . One of my favorite shows. @diamondresorts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zalosnv @viicurry @wiosnabiedronia @PawelRabiej To przestancie byc dewiatami seksualnymi. Proste. Rodzina decuduja… https://t.co/Uec6BoHm7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Dragon's Milk Reserve: Orange Chocolate by @NewHollandBrew at @PBTSlice — https://t.co/Gc4ekSYE8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is bull shit. Half of these guys were ousted cuz of weed... something that will be legalized nationwide in les… https://t.co/xuSDxCicnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @Elaine_Greek @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren… https://t.co/tcP21GHaDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatholicSat @EdwardPentin Term, misbehavior is like saying I misspoke while lying. To place @CardinalBCupich in co… https://t.co/zClnvdADS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #XboxOne had been making noises for a while about becoming THE place for #indiegames, and somehow the… https://t.co/yRKd9fnIKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkBuchkowski @GeorgeBrauchler @KyleClark There is a law against the former]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFHS_West @FirebirdHoops I'm not crying...I'm cutting...ah...onions...yeah!  That's it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next 24 hours are going to fucken suck...... After spending Valentines Day with the same person for the last tw… https://t.co/dGMcGcK6rE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great #teambuilding and looks like fun - we need to arrange a staff #rockclimbing event too!  @western_ccfpem… https://t.co/hWFspGtoXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWSwagger Excellent.  We are going to get 8” of snow tomorrow and you’ve got a KC Pepper crop about to arrive .... it’s so cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theodramatist Oh...and one thing I’m kinda happy about. I’ve “trimmed” the “baptized membership” number so that it… https://t.co/ZcKLNVes5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[11th grade video project thought process: haha it's funny because it's loud https://t.co/tMvgj7dD8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jen_for_the_win @TheOfficerTatum Brandon is a bright well spoken blackman.  He says things to get a white base sha… https://t.co/OMFkXXhyZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColliderVideo Will Disney rethink making more Live Mainstream Remakes of Disney Animated classics should "Aladdin"… https://t.co/ZgxKvNlx0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeonHWolf The worst thing is @AmericanAir will see this, not reply, reach out to you, or address the issue.  Terri… https://t.co/NxEs0HsEQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be sure to check out @aowconsequence -- a weekly podcast hosted by the terrific @dchendrix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really thought @AnaKasparian was about to say "shut up and take IT" (tries not to giggle) #tytlive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of all the females I’ve dated only one of my exes were able to keep up with my insane sex drive 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidLe60561687 @nynjpaweather Rope machines are great cardio as it does not involve me knees lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am having dinner with my Mother and wife at @WelshfieldInn tonight. https://t.co/kafzrl8UFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonSpake @JoeGibbsRacing #NASCAR got the finish they wanted. I'm over the unfair TRD advantage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottWalker Answer questions about Foxconn Scott. You stole taxpayer money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deport The Illegal Marriage Fraud Brother 🐀👿Bastards 9/11 ✈️🏢🔥⚰️🇺🇸 X2✈️🏢🔥⚰️🇺🇸 Anti🇮🇱Death 💀 To 🇮🇱✡️… https://t.co/F4D6rjUrtP]]></document></documents></author>