<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hilton Head is so beautiful I just can’t get over it. I was gonna go back to Savannah today but I might just stay here]]></document><document><![CDATA[zac brown band was honestly the best concert ive been to at the rodeo and ive been to a lot]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m da raw thang these other niggas round here stepped on https://t.co/XelpaVpLd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCIPspecs Naah, it won’t. It’s a tempest in a teapot as are almost all #architecture scandals. The real work of do… https://t.co/OEDsZlClqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasminHumphrey My blog is at https://t.co/OhlZnD8hQc ♥️♥️ Check it out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Vital Strength and Fitness https://t.co/Itg2Q5Eepv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thumpy McLoud Bass is at it again on the other side of the wall. 🙄 He was not missed while I was away lol. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevKeithBritt @misspunk63 @Serremmy @Sequencer16 @my3monkees @jonz970 @CaliRN619 @Briteeye777 @ctanner3… https://t.co/vhzdg4wGGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom was talking today about getting @GoldenKnights playoff tickets and her girlfriend was asking me about season… https://t.co/RbTZIMvdj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amysierrabrown @QuillenJoyce @realDonaldTrump @marklevinshow Coming from someone like you who voted for Obama, I c… https://t.co/v8eEbctOxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMartyFox @BorgmanKelly I think another major question is why is everybody so sick?!?!!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobhavlik Since back in the day... You've always had the tea jam down!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accidentally discovered that you can double tap videos on twitter to fast forward or rewind them &amp; now I can’t stop doing it hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not going to tell anyone what their work is worth ... but I'm gonna be quick to tell you what I ain't paying ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mom called me saying she’s drunk already, it’s burly 11am lmao.  That’s my mom🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to hate everything natural about myself until I met Trevor....it’s crazy how one person can give you so much… https://t.co/OiFS26HOnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheryl_monk @GayEqualGlobal I will post pictures of my babies as I did of our pups. Speaking of furry babies, did… https://t.co/zKYI1jhfo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TubeTimeUS I like how older houses have labels on some of the electrical boxes that say, "do not open. no fuses inside"]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly probably have something that is killing me &amp; at this rate I don’t even care .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alaska5000 &amp; @ChadMichaels1 w/ homegirl Avril-I mean @trixiemattel in the back of SuperQueen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angle3246 @jasminee_iris @NorthernPriss Tristan cheated on Khloe. Travis didn’t cheat on Kylie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[chief.cim started her talk on culture with a game 'if you really knew me' = FUN!! #ThrivePHX #Phxstartupweek… https://t.co/wOcUUEPQ7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sound of my 3 year old and my 15 year old in an epic nerf battle makes me so happy. I want to remember it always.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom’s feet dangling sitting with her daughter as I walk by #feet #barefeet #barefoot #bare #milf  #footfetish… https://t.co/DSfXxd5vJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[No offense but @pen15show is brilliant. I need everyone to know. @mayaerskine &amp; @annakonk new ideal @TheBroadCastIRL guests.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leedee584600001 @Ironhorse76 @CytkoJ ONLY HAVE SOME OF THE SONGS UP! I WORKED ON THE NEW VIDEO LAST NIGHT! NOW I N… https://t.co/6K8NmiBLlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flu breakthrough: Universal vaccine may be in sight @MDLinx  https://t.co/JJIbpTsQ34. Great news! @catielyd interesting...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easy coming easy going talk to much making me really wanna come through]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was going to say “i don’t want to go home” but chicgao is home now and i really just wanna stay home 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winston53660 @tedcruz Lol his paycheck couldn’t pay for that vacation in aspen. His wife is the earner in that fam!! And good for her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woman Assaults Man Wearing 'MAGA' Trump Hat in Mexican Restaurant #Topbuzz https://t.co/NyODLSTgUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Orderville by @ModernTimesBeer @ Park Tavern — https://t.co/W92DZ8lktS]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happens to all those election signs we’ve been starting at for months? @mina_bloom_ and I found out:  https://t.co/EPtqzLS82Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEPTA_SOCIAL on some of the city trolleys (and a couple buses), I've seen a yellow rotating light on top of the fr… https://t.co/umO2z1zQF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband just turned over in bed and said “I know I’m not always the best at expressing myself, but I love you so… https://t.co/Oad0TgZ6Fe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @newsobserver , does anyone at your esteemed organization know the answer to these questions? @dankanenando ?… https://t.co/spvTEK77gV]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am thriving in every class except biology so if you’re any good at it pls help me 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods One scary big mouthed uneducated bigot. Terrible combo-arrogant and uninformed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great, candid shot of Marilyn | Photographer: TBD #humor #chuckle #smirk #comic https://t.co/iZJfinPJZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fenderputty @robbystarbuck @benshapiro @LynnePatton @RashidaTlaib Thats a lie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelbie_jordann IKR like why even adopt him if you know you can’t give him quality time ... me and my dad are alwa… https://t.co/71tFjAJei5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum CNN is a lot like @realDonaldTrump. Their both frivolous, anti-American fools who’s one sided perspectiv… https://t.co/7BsEImoosO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at AMC Deptford 8 - @amctheatres in Woodbury, NJ https://t.co/lkkPQrkahq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliverMcGee @Jim_Jordan @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @MichaelCohen212 @WhiteHouse Yup.  He loves JIM JORDAN'S  opening… https://t.co/nMuztE6Z2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[2️⃣0️⃣0️⃣ days until my wedding! That means 201 days until Disney World! 🎉👰🏼🤵🏻💗💒🏰🎠🎢 #ihearwebbingbells @WDWToday @WaltDisneyWorld]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always love you as a great friend. For the other side I don't want to waste my words. Askim all the years that we… https://t.co/kEdeCWEc0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please always do these kinds of skits when you host SNL, @mulaney !! Good follow up to Diner Lobster https://t.co/8bUpkHO9nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom  YOU OWN THIS! PERIOD! YOU EVIL! PERIOD! How about you go live in a Tent? https://t.co/pwkrIWz1E4]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Friday night walk to your overnight, passing all those happy “we’re free, it’s the weekend” faces and you’re l… https://t.co/rQrMPvRYqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @MSNBC @ABC @CBSNews @NBCNews @SenFeinstein @jahimes @DickDurbin @maziehirono @RepCohen @CoryBooker @AOC… https://t.co/YV91VH9PwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[the release of these new pokemon... it's making me feel young and happy again...]]></document><document><![CDATA[JAJAJAJAJAJ LA CÁMARA 369 de la care cuica jdkfkfkfkfk wea chistosa 🤣🤣🤣🤣 #PartyChilensisFtGala]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy 17th to my best friend!!! i love you so much &amp; i hope you have a great day🥰 @skyler_alsip https://t.co/zcGivv9RC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstroKatie Just signed up Katie!  Are you offering autographed copies - I'm willing to pay extra! :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler You’re on the wrong side of history, Gym. Again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚧Con Sue Photography and Design🚧  🚧Like our photos...Follow our IG 🚧  🚧This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/JIUWUfR7U4]]></document><document><![CDATA[como diría una amiga que tengo por ahí: “quiero ponerme anaaaaaal, anaaaaaal” 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so utterly obsessed with Shane Dawson and Jeffrey Star I could die. 💞🦋]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Man you playing” why the fuck is that so accurate 😂 Like no buddy I’m not finna fuck in your car who tf you think… https://t.co/LzOCqmOJZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirkhawkins @99Only @courtneyfriel @KTLA Hahaha  When I'm there, I don't either!! Great seeing you wearing your Ug… https://t.co/hG8hInMnZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope parallel universe caroline is doing better than earth caroline right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[after doing 4 years of high school choir, listening to “Seasons of Love” and not doing my alto part is impossible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eh_Double 'SAY WHAAAAT?  whach you talkin' bout Willis?  when we were in our 30s we started the movement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcimorelli HAPPY BIRTHDAY! I HOPE YOU HAVE A GREAT DAY! https://t.co/axWkllBZtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[MOOD if you weren’t on day 5 of 2-a-day lacrosse tryouts , at your 3rd 6am tryout of the week and it wasn’t only da… https://t.co/9NcNJHprl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pankeywg Will you are intelligent in so many ways! Cut yourself some slack. You're great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being forced to look at this creepy photo repeatedly is the true crime in this hoax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #MardiGras! Uncle @EddieMaupin is so cool! https://t.co/XNPsnMVx2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewDay If you are stupid enough to not vaccinate, then you get what you deserve. I would it give you vaccines now,… https://t.co/TMjSYlXfx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garrisstroud Can’t wait to read the next piece your roll out!!  Would love to collaborate with you on a topic!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can’t just “get over it” Trauma lives in the body and can take years, even a lifetime to heal.  It requires, tim… https://t.co/LZeosfuir8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dierks is one of VERY few charting men in country actually putting his money where his mouth is. Taking women on to… https://t.co/8icgOcuqmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna make a heartthrob out of me, just a bit of minor surgery. 🖤💜 https://t.co/KezNwqsls2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soo ppl always letting me down nowadays.. that’s why I stay to my down self]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard of the Reproductive Health Act, or at least know four Dems proposed a bill revamping IL’s abo… https://t.co/jv9E15fup0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday - every damn day ❤️ @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/aYp8NZGfVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RueNahcMohr @MLE_Online It occurred to me that you might be able to get more insight by disassembling the code tha… https://t.co/I71KuUSylq]]></document><document><![CDATA[let me find out one of you sick mfs on campus done gave me your cooties.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby These people make no sense.  I am not a vegetarian, although I am a democrat, and I have no interes… https://t.co/vlPw5kx9Ls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Tuesday work day started out right. #coffeeprosejxn #needcaffeine #goingtobealongday☕️ #buylocal @ Gulf Aut… https://t.co/VQ1MPfI3sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buttonpoetry Just got my new read! You are amazing @phil_kaye !!! 👌👏❤ #buttonpoetry #philkaye #poetry… https://t.co/22pk4NetV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilybest @PennyRed @CHSommers Hugs and love and offers to baby sit anytime.❤️😘 My two kids are adults now, and I… https://t.co/SRzyM24u9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Martin Robinson is sentenced to 55 years in prison for shooting Amherst police officer in May of 2018 and for numer… https://t.co/EdCGTsxCmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leonardactivist @rcrcoll6 So sad. There needs to be harsh penalties for animal abusers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanda_granata @canal28794274 @JJAdoresJustin @MichelleCaissi1 @justinsplanet42 @Bizzlex8 @296_cool… https://t.co/tnpGidleuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlongsideWild @DrShepherd2013 @NPR Groundhog says he is a rodent not a meteorologist. He later admitted that he li… https://t.co/gSipID3btd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LincolnCSheriff @9PMRoutine1 YOU are a sick fuck....just sayin!! #Trolls #FAKE #ASSWIPE #GetAFuckinLife #PissOff 👿 https://t.co/aVB46dWalv]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, basically he supports minority rule as long as the minority is white people...]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/WHnGawlnYB Prayers That Bring Healing by John Eckhardt w/ Music]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWisemanSaid2 @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass… https://t.co/QnAqDakIgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HATE WHEN UBER DRIVERS FORCE CONVERSATIONS like I know the silence is awkward but please just put on some music]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wait til I get to see my @citizencope !! Come on March! Get here!! #citizencope #wilma #missoula]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read something powerful and eye opening today about abuse. When I think about it, I really only think physical ab… https://t.co/3jcJTZlvMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been a workaholic lately and life is humbling me and telling me to calm down by giving me neck problems wtf lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @CNNOpinion She did a great job but he was a fool to do that interview. He did harm to his own case. That temp… https://t.co/5P3STozodg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I went hard on tinder this weekend and I’m already over it... someone tell these boys to stop messaging me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me Encarta despertar entre tus brazos, y sentir el dulce aroma de tu suave piel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[we needed Randle physicality this season @LakersTalkESPN @Lakers #lakeshow #lakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off to Uganda- after 5 trips here, I’m planning on visiting some big animals on my arrival,  then I meet up with… https://t.co/vKL42fwC6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotherJones It was fantastic!!!!  You're so tolerant. Do you have a new speech protocol you use now? https://t.co/RYJIid86SB]]></document></documents></author>