<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Hasselbeck You tell me when kickoff is and I’m there like: https://t.co/oI8NoKZoSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Jackie Joyner/Serena/Billie Jean/Mia/Michelle/Diana  #InternationalWomensDay https://t.co/5vggLv773q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaugie01 @GopherHole He does. I can understand the aggravation with Fleck constantly harping on culture and the ze… https://t.co/8i9Wy7UhsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaytonTramel @AnnCoulter @realDonaldTrump had 730 days to make the wall happen. Oh Wait- Take out 60% for “Exec (… https://t.co/0H0H28tOjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyJeremiah @inboxbygmail We’re working on making @FrontApp an amazing individual experience. Recently we added… https://t.co/hFhOBO0oI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at The Office.  Another Work Weekend. @DukeMBB vs. Miami https://t.co/B6lICH8S1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Bar 14 Ranch House Restaurant in Ellensburg, WA https://t.co/TON2MyTcld]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE! Got 83%! It wasn’t easy either, so I’m proud of it! It took me 2hrs to finish!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill She put the bodies on her rewards card https://t.co/GPH4wf8UA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neill_o @candikahne @RyanAFournier @ewarren @SenWarren And European cities should take a look at their border situ… https://t.co/rMMk84XlfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of #BlackHistoryMonth we “brow down” to the queens of past and present that have inspired us and shaped cu… https://t.co/fzFdYuS8F9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The very thing that defines our nation the rule of law failed. https://t.co/hYkB5XXdon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC Imagine that ! ! !  Nobody, knows more about trade, or anything else, than Donald Trump !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I can’t watch Adam Shifty with volume off or on. He’s just flat out annoying either way]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight ladies and gentlemen. The R is for Robert. 💋 https://t.co/1pRJMZt7pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsJroChicago @BenBradleyTV A single conviction from 24 years ago does not constitute "a criminal history." And an… https://t.co/k3CvVN33vb]]></document><document><![CDATA[my nhl picks were good last night 5 right 3 wrong. and nice cake arlene very different.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4-3 DE 1st priority is contain. Not pass rush but contain the perimeter to force everything back to the linebackers… https://t.co/Qu89lzeCpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleAMadson @HeuristicLineup @SactownKings916 @BofA_Help https://t.co/bPip0KetWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A”, Point Pleasant, West Virginia, October 2018 @ Point Pleasant, West Virginia https://t.co/tRASV5HjUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Havent looked at Twitter today have I missed any big news #BillsMafia??]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can’t deem your friends as family, then they’re simply just associates... stop letting associates get more a… https://t.co/RQyi9xaRKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNewRDurle4 @choppsly_ @LSUBasketball Yea LSU is 100% fucked rob, I know this. I hope I’m wrong tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_BlakeEddins How ‘bout this stinger from the US Open? Fairly certain the iron shaft is touching his neck on the ma… https://t.co/9ysJRfE912]]></document><document><![CDATA[Narcissus’ beauty really did last forever...except his face...”which was damaged”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaHeatley @CoachDrafts @coachjasong @TenaciousD83 Congratulations Josh! Continue to ball out!!! Keep God first young man! #FalconNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulamrz97 Imagínense trabajar en el lugar donde imprimió esto y leer esos mensajes xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilePosts When I went to Tokyo, i just slept normal time but had no caffeine on travel day.  That’s what works for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Why would they? Despite what you say evidence shows a wall is not needed. Better border… https://t.co/UWamTGkCRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strangest and most dysfunctional problem solving process Ihave ever seen. Can’t wait to see tomorrow. Jeffrey Warre… https://t.co/s8U23kKv9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TheRuler I never remember her name so I just call her Michelle because I know it sounds like Michelle and she was… https://t.co/MzO8wxl2wQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump wake up shithead   The shit hit the fan today. By the way I heard you fucked up andtold Kim it’s o… https://t.co/IXUJ9zmB5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain Your father Was a good man, and a hero, but in the end, he was complicit in a coup to overthrow a dul… https://t.co/1lNF1mqFZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got It right (@ Suntrust Bank in Nashville, TN) https://t.co/vRGNlbzQsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad my life insurance is in order. You win.  Just take care of the puperino’s. APD, it’s all yours. 😷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllenPage he just put a Big Dent in your cause.  Oh and you need to apologize to @VP or your word means nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Don4Fire Don, please do not do that, people lost their home and some literally lost their lives.  If you do mock w… https://t.co/hPCtWhrlFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 Beto must be under the thumb of the Cartel. Where does he get his money?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPeurasaari @starwars I am... no one, apparently. 🤣  In actuality, I read a lot about the original movies when the… https://t.co/UK7LzyoNI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 seasons ago this franchise had a 15 win season. Today is March 2nd and the Bucks already have 48 wins.… https://t.co/QU453gOhRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @SchultzColton and @UAB_Baseball for a wonderful weekend swinging the bat. Colton not only knows ho… https://t.co/cC1424R9e4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jim_newell This led to deadlock for several years, until William, as a last ditch effort to avoid giving in, appoi… https://t.co/i4MLhy0aZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dcsanchors #risteam day is tomorrow in collaboration with @ptech_westerly and the PTO!!! @WesterlySuper… https://t.co/4YcUB2pcf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyKempski Did you ever update the 2018 press box food ratings? I can’t find one after Dec 20.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So - again, your tone changes when you’re faced down by another leader. You issue this statement a… https://t.co/fEXipc8k3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Such a glaring double standard.  Why can’t R’s turn this around on these lying Dems and still keep our principles?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇦🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss ANGIE! _angeladunn_ The White RACE Australian BLONDES👑🇦🇺 Women Are The MO… https://t.co/7trcRepViK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFordFANatic Autoshow on Saturday ! Updating the resume for a a job tomorrow.....   And lunch with friends :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventurous Adventure in Adventureland for adventurelandday 2019 awaits those willing to travel to parts unknown.… https://t.co/J9D2c8kEil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Wasn’t  he Trumps lawyer?  Did the Democrats tell Trump to hire this guy? Who gave Cohen a job as Trum… https://t.co/AOGZI0nfxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a German Pils by Smith &amp; Lentz @ No Quarter — https://t.co/6JyfNFbYnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Views like this make me smile with my 💚! Let’s make today the best day ever! #FeelGoodFriday #FamilyFirst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading the headline, hearing about an article on tv or in a podcast is not the same a reading the article. Thank y… https://t.co/OH1t5AMcyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great friend of mine wrote an article about the game of baseball and how impactful it is on life and those that w… https://t.co/NA46DIwUHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t help what cards you’re dealt but it’s up to you how you choose to play the hand]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You can find Speech assignment #2 in the Google Classroom. Anyways, here’s Wonderwall.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Presidents Award of Excellence for Science #waltermunk #barackobama #scrippsinstitutionofoceanography… https://t.co/fQDDUoJHIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimplyAJ10 Baseball needs Adam Jones.  Especially  the Mets.  Hope they come calling with an offer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Judith Godwin: An Act of Freedom” is open through March 16 at Berry Campbell. We are located at 530 W 24th Street,… https://t.co/osRKbxyuhE]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are going to run out of people as well as $$ https://t.co/itjJrRsnPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know how it looks from where  you sit @HelloooJack and @Matt__Devlin but from out here @PMcCaw0 looks like… https://t.co/YgaGkaUZdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How's your book "The Art Of The Lie" coming out. https://t.co/YBc8Ryvhd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenJRivers I could care less about the history part but it's a fight I wanted to see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 9th Birthday to my little man. @krispykreme #birthdaytraditions #beingadad @ Krispy Kreme https://t.co/DOpd2PgrVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveBen52466738 @ProfessorFormer @DCTFTW No we won't forget or let anyone forget all the way to Oct.2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracylorenzo I kno my momma got em for me. I’m just now showing the world what a lie they are ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganteCalipari Cry babies offended by everything who needed a safe place, counseling, and everything handed to th… https://t.co/gW10VTBj8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know that I really love my baby. She can give me. Everything I need.  There is no one to take her place. She’s… https://t.co/fxCfcc2S1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tangerine Wheat by @lostcoastbrewer @ Fishweir Brewing Company — https://t.co/ucV1KaIPAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I aspire to be like Tim Tebow. A great man with a great head on his shoulders who always believes that they can ach… https://t.co/8XVRxnxsHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/nbBEvzi940]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #Trinity, AL! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Jack Daniel Cooperage Team L… https://t.co/PRTEW57glY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from coasttocoastbicycle  -  Gary, the bearded gent with the chalk, helps keep us headed in the right dire… https://t.co/pboRgIeUb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Biddco The were living like rock stars. Has performance at the Ralph then slept on a bus meant to get them to thei… https://t.co/kuVtiOWeU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hackers also changed the name on the account to "Bob Cuckhorn" and replaced his image.  By @carlmarksTimes https://t.co/HNaPNo39QY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RefllexDesign @Excision That’s cool. I didn’t know if there was something that made it go off automatically or if… https://t.co/t4Y3ZfPsc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AncaGene 1. Dark matter is a bad metaphor taken from astrophysics, an example of physics envy.. 2. I suppose that… https://t.co/wYUC1uIBYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Santination Racist don’t assault women of other races? https://t.co/ZHTkYaVlPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilverAdie @KarenShuter1 @robreiner Trump may not be a full-blown psychopath but 88% is still pretty bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was gonna say this is my favorite local rock song of the 2000s, but it came out in 1999. What is life.… https://t.co/ga3uKwtjkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NightShift @susannng Check out Take You With Me by Susan Gibson on Amazon Music https://t.co/6Q3OHActdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hounds Of Love tonight then. ❤️ #np #KateBush #Vinyl https://t.co/6SZ6R4Fqa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are still on the fence about about coming to the game tomorrow, it's 100% worth it. I highly encourage every… https://t.co/pHP52hzJMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[HIPÓLITO MEJÍA EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en… https://t.co/MsNe03DW7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B75701721 @CNN @StCollinson @realDonaldTrump The trampling of our Constitution on a daily basis. We have a crimina… https://t.co/x9mFlooZ5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was gonna go to GameNest, but made the right decision to go to an 8-Bit Club officer’s birthday smashfest / fightin… https://t.co/hVjIOrHQcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UnitedKingdom #London #Europe #England #Brittain #Cheltenham #Pontypridd #Germany #Spain  #Portugal #NewMexico… https://t.co/JedOlVblCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendanKutyNJ I think they’re trying to tell you something BK lounge :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[El que diseño esa aplicación de @LifeMiles de @Avianca no tiene ni la mas mínima idea de hacer una aplicación amiga… https://t.co/RLaTXoU7Yr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandaseixas @Leoni_a_jato @LixoMidia @zehdeabreu vou ligar pq sou do bem.. não espalho fake..só falo de futebol n… https://t.co/fdjy6eazqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#stormyweather #manhattanbeach @ Manhattan Beach, California https://t.co/rmI0DJIbF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UpToTASK This sucks. That show was a big part of my teenage years. Rip]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It is here, inside the Manhattan office building that houses Beyoncé’s Parkwood Entertainment—visitors sign strict… https://t.co/qJkPdmut6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Pueblo Yaqui, Sonora, Mexico https://t.co/YgpKsctyiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[NFL combine: These defensive linemen are ones to watch and likely stars of NFL draft: Stifling defense. Underwhelmi… https://t.co/UBcIqCJYQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE NEED to translate dense science and complex topics into understandable everyhuman language.   Non-truthiness rea… https://t.co/xUzOHBF9os]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanTrende Coalitions in US politics are fluid, and we may be entering a time in which they are realigned. I can’t… https://t.co/1lWUqdHmcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow She should’ve severely reprimanded and taken off all committees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost bsdrivers •  •  •  •  • Preach Preacher, PREACH! 👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽 #barackobama #michelleobama #blacklove #blackboyjoy… https://t.co/K3KvMLm0Vp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Martes y Miércoles de  #Champions y #ConcaChampions en #Tabernabeu https://t.co/kRaKbUaIJV]]></document></documents></author>