<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Huge, shredded, but he’s not 1.6% body fat. Basically impossible. People don’t realize how lean sub 10% is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AltcoinSara Well, maybe not the blue hairs or the white hairs.   But yea, as the tech gets easier, safer, and more… https://t.co/7dVgsvLYYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @TyHyCHI #bernie made Socialism work...for Bernie.  First Voted age 40...for Himself. On Govt Payroll plus grifting ever since]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me:  My ex: *sends a before and after photo, thinking he looks any better* I may have not lost 60 pounds and gone v… https://t.co/nGdjmCQl1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! Can’t wait for this keynote at the National Teacher Leadership Conference! #TeachersLeading]]></document><document><![CDATA[KFTC is against hatred/prejudice in any form. Incredibly disappointed by @KYHouseGOP for this rubbish. Kentucky and… https://t.co/TXwTgP3079]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josb0731 @FlatgroundBats @sahsclassic @CTJbaseball @jjnation @Blast_Bsbl Nice work coach! Do the little things and… https://t.co/rgsNVxi71A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Lupulin Shutdown by Red Dragon Brewery at @RedDragonBrew — https://t.co/paIHOQXmcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think about this, while you gloat how wonderful and "diverse" Oregon is.  Oregon was - and in many ways still is -… https://t.co/0NG7uw8R8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CosmicMacabre #CFBallou #fiction #nonfiction #writersofinstagram #poetsofinstagram #teachersofinstagram… https://t.co/ZQ8uGR3lOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@velocb @rusto88 @GoFahr It says the injuries likely happened _after_ it was dead, and that his actions were justif… https://t.co/8qGvLC9ADD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJordanRachel Liberals can’t remember their lies.  Can’t tell the true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudraEqualityMc This can’t be Audra. Glad I learned of it on your post because you’ll make sure action is taken]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Que Pasa Mexican Catina - @quepasastp in Saint Petersburg, FL https://t.co/qrtZ3fgp9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to Sherri Parker Lee Stadium in Knoxville, TN! @KUSoftball is set to take on the #7 Lady Vols at 1:50pm CT.… https://t.co/x65AXDqrcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DgenerateDemon @outmagazine @mathewrodriguez I'm not really going to get into a discussion on his merits as a huma… https://t.co/PIqkfK4ACt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Eric Andre let me in meme is probably the only meme I can see in pretty much any context and always like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thea_Elizabeth Aw shucks! You're my favourite fat squirrel enthusiast and that's no secret 🙏🐿️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like I’ll be driving the xterra this week. https://t.co/uYp1R8mIPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[For such a stupid reason my car did not pass inspection and now I can’t race this weekend. My week couldn’t get any… https://t.co/iVAMvp2ON1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If a man meets a virgin who is unmarried and rapes her and they are discovered, he shall pay her father fifty shek… https://t.co/OhDV7QVkoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DjDarkness810 @GSignature843 I guess that’s what happens when Thanos snaps your ass out of existence lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se você erra a entrada de um viaduto em Miami o próximo retorno fica na Guiana Francesa, acredite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best way to support our CSGO team at the major! Love this futuristic design and take on our brand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSneerReview Sober hell no but when I used to do drugs it was different]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAthletic Very cool to see @TheAthletic offering 3 months fully paid parental leave #paternityleave #parenting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJWW will you please consider selling me your glasses with the side shields ? Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we need is an education-based BALTIMORE protest, in conjunction with the state protest. I'm tiring of Baltimor… https://t.co/9kuxp8fJXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had no motivation to do my homework I’ll literally do one problem then get on my phone for about 10 minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to play Shadow Creek today for a shot at 100k. We finished 3rd ugh 🤦🏼‍♂️🤷🏻‍♂️🍺🍺 https://t.co/mxb5QHVdyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turns out the rainbows are pretty awesome too :-) @ Chateau Margene Winery https://t.co/oZHSNGP9rJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NellyJo2000 i just love ur profile statement. I thought I’d give u a follow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump An entire news organization helped get you elected, sat on stories, and caters specifically to you… https://t.co/mGZRONIili]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men's Health: The 10 Best Pairs of Basketball Shoes for Men - Best Hoops Shoes. https://t.co/JlvqD88Ngu  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunrisemvmt brainwashing an army of children to the delegitimization of an important cause like climate change.  S… https://t.co/gOWcm2qJhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@voxdotcom Hey shes jefferson beaurgard sessions explainer! So is there a lie she hasn't heard,told,or sworn to not… https://t.co/MPAZLEKqiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like @bencranegolf but the funny guy becomes much less so when he becomes the human jam car.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it looks like a duck, walks like a duck...... https://t.co/mrW0Yk47p7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vadervanodin @dguspodcast Yeah, he's SUPER rough on later NG cycles. I would've uploaded the whole fight but it took nearly 7 minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being 13 weeks pregnant and someone asked you what you did today and said “just made a circulatory system nbd”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Millennials #babyboomers - KNOW THE FACTS - POTUS Lying Big Time on The Wall https://t.co/KCzFXZtsFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @jjauthor Man, the drones of the new education system is showing the fruits of their labor...Swear… https://t.co/Z0YRROA8So]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlexxPins But when they go they love it. And they coming to see you shouldn’t matter where you live]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the past 2 years i had braids on Valentine’s Day. I’m slippin on my pimpin]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BnUGnv4NGN Verizon Wireless Customer Service 1-855-431-6111 is non-stop running… https://t.co/p9y1mPGbUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel this in my spirit for someone! @ The Refuge Church https://t.co/y8mqmSyFuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone needs to make cupholders for crutches. I tried putting my drink in my waistband but ended up with Shamrock… https://t.co/Jq3OzHq5Yf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I hope my story inspires other woman across the world” https://t.co/N4y6Xn5fRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_hiphopforlunch @hydrothemc @KC__Kev @CrookedIntriago @OfficiallyIce Gimmick rap is super duper whack]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got back from Houston. I feel refreshed. Heres a peak at what my vlog will be like from my visit. 🙂 https://t.co/1Dw9Tw5XwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimisaknight @IvankaTrump In a world where a man worked hard for his money just to find unskilled workers seeking… https://t.co/99NHKln9PR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My oldest is now a local celebrity. He enjoyed seeing himself on the big screen. https://t.co/dJuopVSOyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycSassenach @PamBermond @GraziaMgb616 @SaraMD15 @KarramKaren @CharliesWhiskey @newenglandgrl I’m taking a nap now… https://t.co/6Sc6xcBbz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dinopicvsso @kswaggiee_ I have family in fort mead and in Aberdeen they definitely don’t call a blunt a J FOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[ڤيديو كليب ناسيني ليه - تامر حسني   Current Obsession  Naseny Leh - Tamer Hosny... https://t.co/owPp226amM via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rochester Lancers Wins over the Muskegon Risers @CityRochesterNY @Rocjazzfest @News_8_WX @StormHour @13WHAM… https://t.co/rRRAdpudx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I listened to ‘Sledgehammer’ by Fifth Harmony 8 times in a row today so if you think you can get under my skin toda… https://t.co/10aWf2cxhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bowseratediddy @LelenaPeacock Friends for life. 👊🏼 Who raised these young Gentlemen? 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[that is ridiculous; the second missed high stick tonight. NHL 🤡 officiating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder @WallDesu I have no respect for EITHER Party.  Or for the apathetic assholes who didn't bother to VOTE most of them OUT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what you're saying is LSU who's been mediocre at best in basketball since Shaq and Dale Brown left 25+ yrs ago i… https://t.co/rr4TdgvGn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Jimbo's Pit Bar B-Q - @jimbosbarbq in Tampa, FL https://t.co/O0qbuAWpDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SammiScarlette @raulmalo01 @johnpaulwhite @JoakimKarud Legit song contest. For 50th anniversary of Moon landing.… https://t.co/cHYHRD3GoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very interesting point came out with Cohen hearing today, when the Republicans were over the Committee with Nunes… https://t.co/ShQ8xCLVQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @orangetheory class ends 1-second too soon. 😫😫😫. 1 calorie away from 1K 🔥. #OTF #OTFRoseville #SplatPoints… https://t.co/M8WoaETNPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#scotter heaven by Lime-S best way to travel in downtown #Atlanta @ Omni Atlanta Hotel at CNN Center https://t.co/YOvj3A5ORd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PChrisBrantley Agreed. It was moving, but at no point did I think that it would be nominated or win an Academy Award.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyBrunoShow @jemelehill 3. Trickle down does not work so howsabout we try trickle up? To my way of thinking, a b… https://t.co/b3UkKU2Sfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthernMissMBB And Yes Reed-Green needs to be Packed This Afternoon! Esp the Student Section!! These 5 Guys deser… https://t.co/Om0yQOTit4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing. She dominates women’s basketball all year and ESPNW can’t even get her name right. Disrespect is unbelieva… https://t.co/lD5f5Wi0GT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillRei31970767 @pateng2bourque @GNSensay @EricMCornelius There have been 9 cycles over 35 years that have each pe… https://t.co/v3Q6Wn52a2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bernstein_lynn @LWVofWake @WakeElections I think the counties that might move to ballot summary cards are those 25… https://t.co/VrBLUICyyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UKAthletics might want to organize student ticket lines a little more. Complete shit show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Citizen Campanola Cosmosign, Minute Repeater Watch - Top-grade limited edition Citizen watches https://t.co/3inDslZSmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgiaTech A bad look that GT unlawfully suspends their female coach and replaces her with a male when they are a… https://t.co/ZjBjHPMpFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 lineups in the @NHL tonight led by Rask/Josi/Reilly as MAIN with a HEDGE stack on the @Senators TOP stack is… https://t.co/xpGcFs8Pil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToriLetzler Hahah I thought I saw your name in there when I watched it last night. Grats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#therapeutic #pain #healthy #recovery #rehab #zen #treatyourself #stretch #philadelphia #philly #philadelphia… https://t.co/WKwGZS3xmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuisThirdWorld Idk whom it is but this person keeps trying to go to my brothers and say stuff that is irrelevant!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancywgonzalez a.hahahahaha !    You're too much ! Big hug https://t.co/94CPefkIkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yNotkC I used to go to Junkers for karaoke alot... Havent been in a while but it's a cool hole in the wall spot with good people]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mass panic at the Hamilton show in San Francisco isn't funny, but then in a small way is. I'm just not sure I c… https://t.co/AGb3XHpDGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy international womans day to my mum cus shes that bitch 💍💅🏼 #InternationalWomansDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKAUZSport @LocalTVSPXPrbs Oh crap I still have to do this, including with Gridiron Player of the Week pictures from football season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericturnr @aantonop Great list! Would this make another good bulletproof resource? https://t.co/cIsPUL7Ony]]></document><document><![CDATA[This might be the worst technical I’ve ever seen given out. If this is worth a tech, then I can already think of 10… https://t.co/l2f3L4ssuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw the prodigy a good few times, Warehouse project’13 and Shane’09 deffo standouts! Flint was an absolute focal po… https://t.co/2o7D8XwtgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw it in the @nypost, and now the Daily Mail.  News of Laurel’s transformation to @SMOKIN_MRS_HOT is making head… https://t.co/t06p5NX9QI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went from an iPhone 7 with no case to an iPhone XS with the battery case. It is chunky.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielTurnerPTF @JackPosobiec What will my gardener to do with out his 900 horsepower leaf blower?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr We also learned that even your daddy thinks you have poor judgment, buddy...]]></document><document><![CDATA[You really like music don't you?  Meh, I guess so.  **Goes to four shows in one night @ Spokane, Washington https://t.co/0Fq6oOjfij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real happiness is found in the struggles we undergo to realize our goals, in our efforts to move foward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@migemunderscore I’m trying to decide if I should do the online thing.  I don’t know that I play mine enough to do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CVBB83 @kennedykelly98 Not willing to make the walk and they don't deliver 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maritta_oh He does that every day when we get alone with Him, the great lover of our soul who draws this close eve… https://t.co/UBjSgS95pB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really love you so much Lisa.. find me somehow Lisa I'll fuck you so good I want to make you feel so good all the… https://t.co/Jw6TbIc2dA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TKyBuMGohPT7pdc @atayyh ياخي خلي محمد علي. يرتح  ، عندك مكاوي مع الدنبوع وعندك  كم واحد مع الحوثي. ،  بن علي اشرف… https://t.co/zPZ2fdxpy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brett receiving his 1st Homer Award 🥇 for being the “February Ops Associate of the Month “ . Congratulations and aw… https://t.co/mW5S2hcAKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the @NBA season is conducted fairly and unbiased, then @OfficialNBARefs need to be paid more so the position hol… https://t.co/YVFWoE2Vcl]]></document></documents></author>