<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@maddow @mamahotone2010 I wonder how long now that the BFF’s aren’t in love anymore, it will take before Kim starts… https://t.co/uDLKXLcuEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The House  just passed HR8- the universal background checks bill, a bipartisan piece of legislation aimed at streng… https://t.co/p5hEVYvNnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busted today with 25 pounds of weed, in checked luggage at Orlando International Airport. A lone man.  Not a carava… https://t.co/RbJhm1MUbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colombia, can’t wait to see you! Estoy en camino! 🇨🇴 #bogota #weekend #travel #ready @ Newark Liberty International… https://t.co/JG5T1zkQ3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlanetDann You are seriously making me question if that is real or not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my friend really tried to say you don’t do your own stunts but that’s a lie @maryjblige #UmbrellaAcademy]]></document><document><![CDATA[PULL UP HANG TIME....DAMN BLISTERS...got out 4 assisted pull ups with my green band...1 UNASSISTED negative pull up… https://t.co/amjdAsVxDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani @DonaldJTrumpJr Then she shouldn't have run for anything if she "doesn't understand"! #bullcrap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because I don't run like a white person. I run like an Indian.  #borntorun]]></document><document><![CDATA[K-Town!! If you haven’t been to @tactilecoffee you’re doing it wrong! #coffeeshop #shopsmall… https://t.co/bFKAmvdPWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like the United States, Brazil needs progressivism. Like many of us, many Brazilians were conned by a right-wing de… https://t.co/A0PudKc4a2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s tea: we should all be protesting the Staten Island St Patrick’s Day parade until they let LGBTQ people open… https://t.co/utcBqGyTH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me too table stain, me too. #relatablecontent @ Beercade https://t.co/PLDdNKvKHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao my dad really just said my mom was his ex 😂💀 Im weakkk , he always be saying something dumb and I love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out our second grade students participating in the El Monte Swims program! So wonderful to collaborate with o… https://t.co/YBgYHHvFy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find out if I got into my program tomorrow and Ive NEVER been so nervous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TLeeOnTV I never listened to that show but anyone dieing at 33 is just tragic!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zengonzo @sarahcpr We will...Presidential races always bring out large numbers and the largest group being progressives...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saddened to hear about Luke Perry. Gone too soon. Love, spend time with and hug the ones you love. Life is shorter… https://t.co/pevf8HUkD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disgusting , when someone is doing you wrong they will make it seem like it was you 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanBezilla @FedEx Maybe that's for the New Orleans folks. Must be hard to get around during Fat Tuesday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhoni3369 @kyfreak01 @seanhannity @trumps_feed Obviously not you could careless of Angel mom's and women and child… https://t.co/Vs5pEXXmvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@LarryObhof isn't sold on the need for a gas tax hike. https://t.co/RyiTW9gNZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sun is starting to peak its head earlier and the temps have been in the 60s and 70s Spring is surly arriving 🌷… https://t.co/vNTxM9VcYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[De las 20 ciudades que hubo marchas x los100 dias de Desgobierno hay info ??? O  bloquearon las cuentas!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that.... I’m going to @sitw!  Logged in RIGHT at 12pm and 150.00 tickets were gone though... hmmmmmmm… https://t.co/3F3bbJuRuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CentriaAutism @crainsdetroit Really?  In two years, we had probably 6 to 7 behavior technicians.  A couple were tr… https://t.co/YcudwmF4HB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being Annoying For 19 Minutes Straight https://t.co/0Fiai4Wrht via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the Au-Rene theater as the background &lt;3 . . . . . #minervaphotography #southfloridaweddingphotographer… https://t.co/Iz40qVOpxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GougeonMarc @SnoopDogg @Lakers @GougeonMarc @SnoopDogg Soooo trying Marc..Told him bout my Fanism and my Lakers to… https://t.co/EfXyk8G6LB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @jennygustavson : Post covers of 10 albums that make up a soundtrack of my life: no… https://t.co/30lLVxAUuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[no matter how much someone may hurt me i’ll never be the resentful angry person i used to be. i may make mistakes,… https://t.co/5wyQDm6zEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proper weather to take the scooter to the pool.🛵🏊🏼‍♀️ . #kask_cycling #tucson #scooter #helmet #shareyourkask… https://t.co/u4GBwv0Kiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Long Beach Airport (LGB) in Long Beach, CA https://t.co/0zjpFikttc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCognificent1 Okay this is weird my tweets &amp; post on YT are posting twice? Some like this and others the complete comment. ODD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enamoradas de Trista:  Femineidad , romanticismo y elegancia hecha en MÉXICO. En houseofzatt ,    Arboleda.    Flor… https://t.co/VLIKp4zmjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If you have not committed any crimes then what do you have to fear @realDonaldTrump ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enamara @AFRINIC Such a great meeting @digigrassroots this is where so many meet on policy and tech And you see me… https://t.co/oLXTrmo8jk]]></document><document><![CDATA[this guy added my friend on snapchat, tried paying her $400 for sex but she said no and this was his response wtf https://t.co/v18vMZQU57]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaYaYaCandanga @isnardobravo @lalogitud Si... Mereces la mierda que estás comiendo.  Que la disfrutes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too bad, the Washington Post can’t soothe your ego with alternative facts; like Fox Noise!]]></document><document><![CDATA[all my layers have grown out &amp; now my hair has this really ugly pyramid effect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff Doors all locked in Sutton Ontario tea made snuggled under my blanket on the couch watching #LivePD https://t.co/kavM9b7rV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DontEverAskMeTo keep a secret from my mom. I can’t do it. All the woman has to do is LOOK at me &amp; I’m spilling my guts. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a little girl selling boxes of Girl Scout cookies on FSU campus #PowerMoves #CantSayNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[if maddi says “it’s my birth month” one more time i might have to just ignore her birthday all together]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy hell. If Bradley cooper and Gaga don't marry and have beautiful babies I'm going to be very sad. That performance was sex.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 @GeigerNews @phildevine1 @1saneman @PhillisjSmith3 @thedaywedecide @down2dallas @MichaelRocklin… https://t.co/nYM5qTPRi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraK93322487 AMEN!❤️🎊🎉🎊🥳💃🏻🐾😁  It's really such a shame that when these #dogs or #cats are in danger of death..t… https://t.co/oKkdRrrzQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[my 1 year old tells me when he wants belly massages and when i stop he gets my hand and puts it back on his belly lol🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y can’t there b a society for people who don’t want to be in actual society]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Ms. Valencia Rose Chambers!  #Moreythan28days https://t.co/bkFMADTaBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will be both my husband and my own first con and cosplays.  Im almost done with my leafeon, then it's on to Darth Vader ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fbf to last Saturday with my favorite crew! Lucky to have such great friends ♥️  #friends #goodgroup #squadgoals… https://t.co/lDugVs82q0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WatchChad It’s an sickness they should get Rx for that and start thinking RIGHT‼️🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[2. Muddled masculinity. What it means to be a man is a "?" @rohitbhargava Powered by women, fierce women, 2018 ungendered]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continuous line contour drawing selfie.#Rememberartschool? @ Wagner College https://t.co/Le1MWEQsa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not built for this kind of weather! Literally. https://t.co/qjqBShEcua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope, @porterairlines. Not going to pay an additional $150 per person just to take an earlier flight. Thanks anyway… https://t.co/vmT7Dayd4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is already working on his lies and name calling against his opponents. He is also working against the constit… https://t.co/IlX4YuFxcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw and LOVED #CaptainMarvel. I adore how the Earth is saved by women...one woman of color, both… https://t.co/Il9PGpiBfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUPCASE is giving away a brand new Galaxy S10+ 😱 Entry is free: https://t.co/6xn0GNseZh https://t.co/RAns05jAnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg he really said “I’m an honest person” 😩😂 some boys really are trash 🚮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baddielish oh damn that sucks. I don’t really know many places that sale shrimp grits frfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MUJERES LIBERADAS DE HOY El papel de la mujer a través de la historia de la humanidad ha tenido grandes cambios qu… https://t.co/jZvThNtCTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backyard blizzard y’all @ Silver City, New Mexico https://t.co/FEjVmtX7hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj If you had good parents, you knew nothing about politics before you learned it in school...At 16 all I wan… https://t.co/5dqoo28wQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maggarooo Thank you for the lovely floofs you shared with us! No one has the skills for finding these beautiful floofs like you Maggie ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be busy for the next couple days... #cutepuppies #cutepuppiesofinstagram #puppiesofinstagram @ Buckroe Beach,… https://t.co/9EMyrJCa5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd times a charm. .... (@ UPMC Pinnacle Harrisburg in Harrisburg, PA) https://t.co/yL6rmBf4Wi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another 💯 in the books!! Go Christian!!! @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/Mnc7lzDjfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @TheDailyShow and that "Jessie" skit was hilarious @Trevornoah is awesome!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday ding dong!!  So excited for the first of ogdc3vb to turn 21 this year, and can’t wait to celebrate y… https://t.co/2seAqABaAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Litzy quiere que me cambie al tecmi e irme con ella todos los días jajaja pero con eso q está embrujada es probable… https://t.co/kIg2MTscWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blindseyeview @wonkyalison See cool that you fund a place for yourself.😋😛🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump What about charged with treason? This should not be allowed to happen and they get… https://t.co/QJhTLaJxzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eye Candy to Feed your Soul https://t.co/5E1UwAvb1G via @YouTube @pangaeaoutpost #pacificbeach #encinitas #coronado… https://t.co/09Pd652S3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imaginarymargo @EdonaGKrasniqi @_starpostgroup_ @trUeLOVEdatsME You deserve sis https://t.co/qy3pBM0xCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horsegrl17 VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥 LIKE… https://t.co/Y9g1CVbd4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[a friendship where you can share your favorite worship songs&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imashleymi N agrees! “That’s so satisfying” she says, after she drains a glass. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alleyson22 @rennellredhawks @Fuller4th Absolutely!! Couldn’t agree more!! Very proud of these kids!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhlythgoe @AP @BretBaier GET REAL! OUT OF HIS OWN PIE HOLE , HE HAS PUT DOWN BLACKS , MEXICANS, PUERTO RICANS. HE… https://t.co/iDfPvTOcGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philosophrob @RockyMntnMike I would like this done on all federally elected &amp; senior level appointed officials.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad people can’t fess up hang ups wil always be hangs ups he has issues and can you do to]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Saturday night....  :-) . #irishnobleman #chicago #chicagobars #booze #drinks #riverwest #saturday #upshow… https://t.co/baoYzXjPya]]></document><document><![CDATA[時々アートビジネスやりたい企業から相談受けたりするけど、バスキア言ってないで市場調査とか自社でやったらいかがですか？と毎回思う。個人でやってる人もいるわけだし。そもそもアーティストを搾取するような仕組み作ったらもっと疲弊するだけじゃん]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBrothaDrew bruhhhhh you just made me fall the fuck out you readddd Ryan https://t.co/AGkwzaprWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for being such a loyal patriot.  We really appreciate what you are doing 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews So we can listen to more diarrhea SPEWING from ur mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Gene C Reid Park - @tucsonparksrec in Tucson, AZ https://t.co/E1K1VzBR90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bringouttheweed It’s actually quite disgusting how they are trying to gaslight ppl into accepting a low wage. Who… https://t.co/9yYzSKDreg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubyMohans @subbo7 @KelvinROfficial @Just_Brian_01 Aww, thank you, dear Ruby! And I'm giving you a gold medal for… https://t.co/4lkUixt8CF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eliecerdrum - mi amor te compré este Ferrari!!! - no me gustan los asiento de cuero.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to do spiritual warfare for him. I could see that the enemy was taking advantage of his weakness and could ha… https://t.co/PrrnYgCa2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilverAdie #She is why #He jumped up after #Breakfast and packed to come home from #VietNam! He is scared!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you not know? Have you not heard? The Lord is the everlasting God, the Creator of the ends of …… https://t.co/hjcADWoxW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patriot7231 @TheRocketRobot1 @jjjlaughter @bmxmom156 @lisastoi @DineshDSouza Not a lie because you say so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsaacDovere @mattgaetz "I was happy to do it for you.  You just keep killing it," Gaetz was heard telling trump. “… https://t.co/auqxz1s7lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KincadeCaela @TrACkisMIne17 @_jaistopher @OmgItsObii @Theyloveejaz_ @_LoyalTee__ @SlideeT_Ware @___simbaaa___ Than… https://t.co/CTbbTdx5hU]]></document></documents></author>