<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Steeler89733412 @KiXSTArTV @team_empire @G2esports Unfair would mean they are cheating or exploiting. This is truly fair, domination.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hernameisBANKS You are enthralling to watch live! Hope to see you again in Nashville 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand the hate the oscars are getting for awarding movies that “most people haven’t seen”. The oscars… https://t.co/JP6tbmDzlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnyminardi @HotWaterMusic Ha, I'm a forever and counting kind of guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@YahooForde Hey Pat -I’m Jack; we met in the ND pressbox prior to the UM game watching App St/PSU. I have a battle… https://t.co/NW8h6wZzI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OntAg @Shannon_Farms Yes I can contact but it would save everyone time if more details were listed. It is importan… https://t.co/YLSQNJXZqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, our national championship (for a team that has 7 actual ones) is winning the ACC regular season. Brilliant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GusFantastico @KATVBarry @KATVMelinda @KATVToddYak @Ned_Perme Be safe brother!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmaooooooo. Dog. This might crack top-5 tweets all time on twitter dot com for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notill4me @rodgrisier1958 @SiekerSales @reinke_farms Need 12 for a white 8222]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can buy Sennheiser's own HD 6XX for $199.99. The reasons I haven't bought a replacement cable yet is that I can… https://t.co/NJZLlPyQEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@modishaurya23 Oh I don't think he'd do it, but if things didn't go well he could switch it up...you know Sarri won't switch anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonofaMitchToo @JohnOSullivan36 @forrest_crellin @TheMominatrixx @BernieSanders @HillaryClinton @DNC Not really an… https://t.co/Mii1J37UDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished watching #BBL08Final I’ve never been big T20 fan but watched much this season and format is growing o… https://t.co/WqIlpRnYD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephen90045069 @PAlterBoy1 @henry5rex @AltUS_ARC @puntanenyahoo @DieterFrikadell @SonOScrutinizer @MedBennett… https://t.co/p5BuwBDbVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews You have given me a glimpse of a hopeful future! With you as the seeds of a new humanity, I truly beli… https://t.co/n2ZX3ebF10]]></document><document><![CDATA[brogdon is actually having a great night but man i always get nervous when he drives]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laker_squad Why the hell rondo sitting all the way down there ,who's the leader.smfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold on, weather through the storm, and then look back and see how much you grew because of the rain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaypickrel @GOPLeader Well after three years of republican investigations they came up empty handed. What part of… https://t.co/mmrNg6fbfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBHWJoe  I love you so damn much!! The comment "I'm a Dildo" made me almost crash in the rain in CA. You sir are a… https://t.co/p8LbtUYrsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews No if you would have been elected we would have been in serious trouble! Go away already, Trump retired you permanently!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good friends... better rivals! At the garden with mikeoffwhite for rangers vs devils. #njdevils #letsgodevils… https://t.co/p354urLb4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murallaverde @clubleonfc Le falta también que escudo este bordado. Es como el de la Jersey, un pegote. Pero esta b… https://t.co/bAWgBhAXgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrBradJohnson After several "resets" on scoring as well. Noted the drastic decline of reading scores.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swerveconfident It’s like rough racist wise? Like I’m going to be angry as hell?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will come to your place of business and destress your entire office. Schedule Now: https://t.co/VaPQgz8CgV (213)… https://t.co/43Ao1XhXHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The grind been good to me.  Never switchin it up.  #Legacyspring https://t.co/zCScLMHIVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am very sad to hear of the passing of King Kong Bundy. Another wrestling great has left us. Seems to be happening… https://t.co/5OBOZK7VMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsteve014 @BobCooney76 @MarcFarzetta The half court offense is terrible. the Set plays are so transparent . This y… https://t.co/PgxGPPGQro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now and later? Fire and ice? Half hot and half cold? Either way it makes for a pretty cool snapshot.  . . . .… https://t.co/LzyQtN0UE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 @realDonaldTrump Like Obama paid a terrorist state $150B dollars in the middle of the night, in pallets o… https://t.co/nl7l6DdKcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drakkarklose hey Drakkar, when are you returning to the Octagon next???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't seen game of thrones but gen:lock (one on the left) is absolute 🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Bullshit Lots of bullshit Tons of bullshit Bullying with bullshit He does bullshit on auto-pilot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t worry about others being humbled. Humble yourself and put the work in. #Life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GopherHole We should tag @ Jerry on this! Or wait. Does Mr. Kill tweet?  Good thing he’s not a coach anymore I gue… https://t.co/qO9iFRRHHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the biggest differences I see between Lebron and MJ especially at age 34 is the perimeter defense and the ab… https://t.co/BAAHg5T6W0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ivy_Gracexx because you are beautiful and amazing and you deserve it!!😁😗😗]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found out one of my family members I was close to passed away halfway through Crush. I started crying and didn’t… https://t.co/FbwIjMZM9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andrewnorris141 @kyleevans_10 10:30 when they’re at home. 11:30 on the road]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jonnythedamned @Sphynxian I got interested in what he would say in his defense, also all this brought his art to m… https://t.co/zIybsltrNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ummm.. that’s definitely NOT Melania. Watch this and then go watch actual footage of the First Lady. Who is that???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz Say her name if you are going to attack her! Such a cowardly tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Minecraft #NintendoSwitch Edition #ShoppersDrugMart ... #LIT #2019 #Gamer #Vibes #TakenWithXperia #Sony #BLESSED… https://t.co/kPA6ANQGTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[so I didn’t fight a Hydra but I did see a really tall woman @ TriStar Centennial Parthenon Pavillion https://t.co/fWZlF0s9K0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SegevBenNoonAdv @LiorYarmiyahu על הספסל: עומרי גלזר,סנטיאגו קני סארס,לירן שטראובר וניימר.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always a good day for a clean truck @MisterCarWash https://t.co/8yFFAASi1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Philadelphia imam’s Jew-hating sermons: “the Jews are the vilest people” https://t.co/tDJjQ4OSeX via @pamelageller]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickPaulas The Departed is "dumb" and Idiocracy is a bad movie Hitler would love.  This is why you're not a movie… https://t.co/29OR0ukoST]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been known to make dark jokes regarding my fathers passing, but humor seems to be the best way to mask the pai… https://t.co/LtxCvOMl9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theinkgame @MaurkicePouncey @RamonFoster I’m the cool one, he just does what I say 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSNSteve Dylan Demelo was the reason we lost!! Smith did all the work for the 7th goal !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbarnes30 I remember him. he was pretty good back in the day. Then he went and played in Oakland]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting our community by setting up a fence at the Strawberry Festival. Come join our Kids Workshop Monday March… https://t.co/snB67txkQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonhickman Thinking about it now, I can't really remember why I was underwhelmed. It was certainly fine. I was r… https://t.co/TMYHJydt9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rob_Bradley Maybe we should chance it to Committee “reefer-ence” 😉 going forward. Great read Malcom Gladwell read too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[VERBOSITY. Killin me smalls @ Greenville, South Carolina https://t.co/rDW9GjaQNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont care what anyone says. This song slaps and it’s got such a classy sound. https://t.co/U0kapdXYvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMig29 @boyroshima @ButtBoob @quill_monger @BloopinDoober Mutilating. Lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sairasameerarao I can’t stand Nancy Pelosi. That being said, you are insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Hair braided  2. Fresh fade  3. Mani  4. Two new tatts   Best slow Friday yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner And yet the question remains...why is a blowhole like rob reiner relevant when he hasn’t made a decent f… https://t.co/eNWYoWfIN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickyDavila Wow! I would change my political stance if that dude supported me. The mental illness is strong with this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbillinson @AOC This explains it all. I compare it to sewing. U continue to attempt to sew with a needle that mace… https://t.co/m00vfFeLhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevecofield Appreciate the reply. Love the show. Listen every afternoon on the commute home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Los Angeles International Airport https://t.co/7BdYDSUtVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcflem @outkast_168 @leebosky @CoachCVF @j_garrels @NJCAABasketball @NJCAA Let them know 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Understand this, my dear brothers and sisters: You must all be quick to listen, slow to speak, and slow to get angr… https://t.co/t3nDpnWSdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living rent free in that empty brain of yours. 😆 Actually, Baldwin is coming off as a smarter version of yourself e… https://t.co/vvb9j9zHJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @ThomasPKennedy3 @godrockin @KayHair1 @jjauthor @jjauthor @godrockin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanMPhipps @ericarhodes heck yeah! Your coming to the right spot. My family and I live just over the Veterans Bri… https://t.co/xCNoQmPXHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Maiullo, “That Physics Show” @bolden_science @MsMoyer_Science @ChungFLHornet this could be a great daytrip. L… https://t.co/UNj0hjdpPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joaquinlife @chrismessina But why wouldn’t I just use my iPhone or iPad for that then?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @by_the_ppl @CREDOMobile All your statements about our President are false. You are an obsessed Presi… https://t.co/9YVApXsJe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elijah_Reaves @just_kayy If you were to pack up my tv and take my vacuum id let you take it cause I would be laugh… https://t.co/Op5DVhTLzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @NASCARONFOX I’m so glad we didn’t buy tickets for this snooze fest!  #GanderRVDuel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dudeitsemily I went after going to the Opera solo to see Carmen! Dooooo it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lawson Lynn with the gameface stare down! Her prediction .......PAINNN!! @coachmeg15 😂 https://t.co/Hu5CjWOmkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moment of Silence for the Arby’s by my apartment that has closed. 😩 you will be missed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouMerloni I really hope this wasn't a ruse.  Maybe Smollett isn't well.  Google "lynching" and you'll see what an… https://t.co/nc8j8zRM0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwedishStunner @RickSantorum @NikkiHaley @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @CNN Correct not trump’s fault for him dying. But… https://t.co/4sQtpNujsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm foreal annoyed af it's fucken 3:30am and nobody in this house is being considerate of my feelings y'all fr annoying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCofFootball @GoldenKnights He may not have been exceptionally fast, but he always seemed to be in the right place… https://t.co/vm95yxszu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 18 of "21 Days of Tinsley Twofers" - looking forward to @TinsleyEllis playing 2 nights at @The_ZOO_Bar  3/11-12 https://t.co/FIaLtbFeqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s actually brain dead. Has nothing but trying to capitalize on something that isn’t there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jcole held the state down with his Allstar Game performance. https://t.co/I2ZUijO4XM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Supervisor Sales" at Harbor Freight Tools? Apply even if you're not a 100% match.… https://t.co/bkORefaT8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m unclear once again why @BernieSanders is talking most of his time running against @TheDemocrats and sowing fear… https://t.co/53yzeRRmaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wicker_robert I can’t remember a college hoops game with so many bodies on the floor. Kentucky was the better club last night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMikeBagley @PPistone @Sammy_Agee @DDefruscio @ProducerPAT @rbalick @DGodfatherMoody @mattdracing @LFR95… https://t.co/Fnuuc7vysx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aszneth @SmilinJack2099 @willowlaurel @ChrisAFilippone @chrishambyfilms @ProfessorFrenzy @DerMudeTude… https://t.co/vatu6UBQJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsCQuinn @alkinahan1 @Google @msaudraabro @MsCathrynWake @TheSPearson @OCSB_LT @LeadOCSB Awesome!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neontaster @planogirl1 I would ask when did Russia get to Mueller and when has Wikileaks ever posted fake news? Re… https://t.co/CxkIUix7Oe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar @kimguilfoyle   People the Democrats that  want this and I think it's a disgrace to American to allow this type of murder happened]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbiedollmary_ I will fill your holes tie you down have my way with you for hours and then I'm gonna get you to b… https://t.co/tIsTr5NUBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcbrisbin If it that was Doc it would have just been a coke fueled hallucination.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for joining Ken the 3rd graders are attacking you at once i don’t know if a plan but  No disrespect to third… https://t.co/LVJ0AQ6hfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Grant Park in Chicago, IL https://t.co/FUDYo5gsjJ https://t.co/UA6H5qGaai]]></document><document><![CDATA[The pressure is now on Wilson-Raybould in the SNC-Lavalin scandal https://t.co/yy6Q7gx2IZ via @torontostar]]></document></documents></author>