<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@IndyFuel @Wichita_Thunder @Jason_Schawe I know and I’m apologize for it. C’mon Malsy and Schawe, tighten it up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow wow wow!  Former colleagues breaking huge news on #JussieSmollett late tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaredfromLI I think so, but I've only seen white so far. They're off now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[August Alsina - dealing with death, relationships, religion and music  2... https://t.co/p86YoyoCGS via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:10.9°F WchillLow:-1.8°F Wind:1 mph Dir:WSW Baro:Steady Rain2day:0.00in Hum:81% UV:0.0 @ 02:00 03/06/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@becca079 @geogilley970435 @CoreysDigs The page you linked has the following:  Broken links: 8 Off topic: 3 Opinion… https://t.co/t48524UGGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SBondyNYDN Replace the word “effort” with “season” and you will have it correct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the mountains above Santa Cruz visiting friends. They have a wine dungeon that’s accessed by a secret door in th… https://t.co/MQPu1UtpbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AP You should really resign AOC PS all your 15 pages are from the movie Idiocracy, cows can’t fart, drink rec… https://t.co/KzlIpyincK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself That’s the second time @HamillHimself went undercover as a stormtrooper to save the galaxy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pontifex I hope for success but one must be honest with yourself. The issue at its heart over 80% of the abuse is… https://t.co/Ur8Ar0LWRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! (at @PaneraBread in West Homestead, PA) https://t.co/HVRBvWXgwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sxsw w/Rasu Shrestha Atrium Health’s brand spankin’ new Chief Strategy Officer @ Cooper's Old Time Pit BBQ Austin https://t.co/8Lk71Ddpky]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBA Announces Basketball Africa League to Start in 2020; Barack Obama Involved https://t.co/6nxaoUosO6.  🏀🏀🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly @OutIn2020 young Americans just have to look at Venezuela some other countries that are going to shit… https://t.co/fOCk72W26o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael @Evan_Rosenfeld @ManMet80 @jaketapper Ikr. Tapper fuck off with ur divisive reporting to stay in biz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penguins @PPG @johnosartstudio Wanna ship one to me since I won't be attending the game today? :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevDon You remind me of the guy who goes to see a doctor, punching his own leg - he tells the doctor, Help me! He… https://t.co/JvU4fHWOvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best conversations start with remember when ..... all the fighting ,cursing falling outs ,making ups made a hel… https://t.co/tsqwlhFZGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodriguezNegrac Puedes mostrar el tweete donde Bukele dijo eso, es facil decir Las cosas demostrarlo es lo dificil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to land a job like "Payroll And Benefits Service Delivery Manager" at Kelly Services? Applicant tracking syste… https://t.co/oAtmAg6oD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#instadaily #iphonephotography #travelphotography #travel #city #slc @ Salt Lake City, Utah https://t.co/LOm8pb0Xpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to rush over to aberrant_ales to try their latest collab with @cultivateypsi - #KaijuKing. This #DRIPA with sak… https://t.co/pZ9aPmIy9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed. The world is watching his neurotic behavior. Take him to court. Shut him down and start Art 25 procedurs fo… https://t.co/b2XnTewLio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is this a thing, what does it mean, and why am I only questioning it now? https://t.co/LdtWC1YoEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr__Pepe__ @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @CNN @FoxNews @wapo So you can't find those supposed claims. My guess is that y… https://t.co/jKonuRHF2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arrington172 “hooking up with girls and BOYS behind my back”😂😂 that’s just fucked😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh man, kids these days. My almost 6 year old’s assignment was to draw a jazz band. He says, “That’s ok. I’ll just draw a DJ Booth.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[haze -&gt; snow temperature down 42°F -&gt; 35°F humidity down 61% -&gt; 57% wind 13mph -&gt; 7mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richchetwynd @elonmusk @WorldAndScience Not to mention, replied to with tons of random memes anything Elon, for re… https://t.co/tfvcKzOHJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sullympls And I forgot hosting a groundbreaking for an aquarium to impress a girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JYarcho_BUCS I thought it was surprising that when Vinny got cut, he kinda new it wasn’t working out. Or, maybe he… https://t.co/jc83RQQlrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since my beloved Pearl Izumi cycling shoes but the dust three months ago, I’ve struggled to find a suitable replace… https://t.co/GPKp3VarGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BirdsWatcherFS I feel like maybe Sisco could be the fourth reason, no?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zeppajacky @Le_Figaro @EmmanuelMacron Une belle idée idiote. Ils sont français, le but est de les ramener a leurs… https://t.co/MukqCKbeLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna miss having one of my favorite players ever on the #Cavs, but retiring in Cleveland is so fitting #Champ… https://t.co/n9OgF3gH75]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flashback Friday: Prairie View’s 2002-03 regular season men’s basketball championship recap https://t.co/UhSbZyAd2y… https://t.co/1pGuMF0a8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister said since I didn’t go to class today that I could blend in with the college students here 💀😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never forget that God is always working on our behalf. Sometimes, it is easier to see/feel than others, but His pro… https://t.co/9pn7VFkfUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasHall17 In that case it was probably an invitation, but she nevertheless ignored them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auraambitions I mean, hell, no white person is going to get shot, beat, or murdered from this commercial. Meanwhil… https://t.co/eW62z9aoMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only EMU treated racism like they treat parking on campus without a permit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come out to our HISTORY OF MUSIC trivia night THIS THURSDAY! 🎸🎶  7-9pm @ West End Pub. All are welcome! 🎤🥁 https://t.co/hXoiTXjUAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillSimmons not to mention she was a 57 year old successful business owner when she married a 72 year old man.  No… https://t.co/Pvjz1HSuHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[2A Grapeland defeats Woden 53-44 in Regional Semifinals. Play Marlin in the Final at 1 pm Saturday. @theroyreport… https://t.co/CPRWaTugsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[So stop living life because of that 🤔 he loaded lol he not gonna mope around for something like this .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nahmias @NomikiKonst My wife assumed that the beginning had cut off, but also opined that it would be a good idea… https://t.co/u9jpvMQJcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Toronto Public Library (Runnymede) - @torontolibrary in Toronto, ON https://t.co/lT83C67nAQ https://t.co/P3y1fW8Y3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here it comes!! My generation’s #BohemianRhapsody: @MotleyCrue’s #TheDirt trailer - https://t.co/RGTefGVI5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Imamofpeace @PaulConservativ #Jesus is the way. https://t.co/ig8Pde7R8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Good Morning! Good luck and have fun on @foxandfriends Thanks for your hard work supporting the… https://t.co/ibpC0lhQB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheeSouthside i see stuff like that everyday on the news here, and baltimore is even worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ava @USATODAY Not only did he fake the maga attack, I believe Smolett made that threatening letter and sent it to… https://t.co/nSuG0o5rPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidThe_3rd @DMilner13 I won’t wait in a 5-min line at Disney, but I’ll wait 3 days for good bbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fisty @MaurMaur82 @vixticator @1an0maly @billyrunaway @IanFHood @QuandaryMan Thank you. I'll raise you a Morrissey… https://t.co/xg00aeEvVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now you wanna go to what I thought was my besties wedding and don’t even really like him... nor him you! The gopper… https://t.co/oCQPcojhPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thesnakeeyes @CNN That wasn’t required before and it isn’t required now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bell I'm money hungry and it shows. Which Team is Stupid Enough to "Show Me The Money!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems appropriate somehow. I have guns and know a lot of people with guns. I carry mine in a secure holster when I’… https://t.co/oY7x73N7l7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know what challenges and adversity you've been through growing up. But I do know that whatever happened to… https://t.co/OLv80UyVg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Considering how you treat trump. I’ll bet you haven’t listened to Rush Limbaugh or any program on Fox News]]></document><document><![CDATA[80% of the music that’s been released in 2019 that I’ve heard has been absolute garbage]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really had to pull out my San Marcos cobija for tonight cuz fuck the cold]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW VIDEO'S  BY LUNCH IS THE THEME  FOR FRIDAY MARCH 1 VIDEOS  BRING A NEW MONTH IN RIGHT🤗.@musiccity2018 .… https://t.co/BE6cr0s2XX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing is ever mine anymore. I came home with a smoothie and now its Ethans 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[My whole left arm gave outwalking out the club tonight and that might be my Kobe-achilles moment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow in Hawaii? If this isn't climate change then I don't know what is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After talking to basically every TSA agent it looks like they have no idea where it went and this is going to be a very short retreat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAliceLittle Alice, given some more time, I can probably think 🤔 of 6 or more fantasies ☝🏻 One really excites ⚡️… https://t.co/EbkZJlpbD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days these quotes are exactly what you need to hear...#keeplookingforward #positivity #dontquit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DWilliamsTV @AnnCoulter MSM sure buried this story in a hurry, three weeks ago they wanted a moment of silence at the Super Bowl for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TristanThompson walking in the crib since he ain’t wreck his home 🤣 https://t.co/wuwjM6nJmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[ABV: 7.8% N/A IBU Color: Reddish brown Aroma: Sour brown ale Taste: The Sour taste is permissive and place that ove… https://t.co/wFySE0Pz0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@physedreview They should have your picture under innovator in the dictionary]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all funny 😂 keep arguing it’s entertaining. oh &amp; jonesy you funny bruh💀💀 @CalebJonesy0497]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCAR @JimmieJohnson @TeamHendrick Only if he wrecks 2/3rds of the field again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HEMIvik What kind do you usually drink. I have become more of a taster in the last yr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might get a job cleaning mirrors. It’s a job I can see myself doing. @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/wWpK14gcYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SC2019SC And if we win. Where is the money from the ticket sales and fundraiser going?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valval41 @facingwestmusic The teen sisters are a class act, very sweet young ladies! 😇😇🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahbea89 @WalshFreedom I'll be dead and gone but when your old like me you'll be thinking that old man was right… https://t.co/TAaEJnb1hj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwilton52 @CoachStengel66 @briancushing56 @markdero7 @BergenCathFBall Happy Birthday Coach!  Hope you have a great… https://t.co/FfOcL5rugH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gargano Vs Ciampa The Final Chapter at NXTTakeOver before WM 35 Yassss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its always fun to be back here! :)  #mvsb #stna @ Mount Vernon High School (Fortville, Indiana) https://t.co/nDiuWYKtNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adriana7C Jajajaja... no no tranquila! De hecho es muy común que si se tiene gym en casa cuesta más sacar la fuerz… https://t.co/GgtYxOU5SS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President don’t forget to stop somewhere and get yourself a souvenir because in 20 years from… https://t.co/vzwlRYamye]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s competition day. STEM Day at @montgomerybell means we’re prepping downtown before the first round begins. @ Na… https://t.co/kaAmbSxO9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulmares72 @JJ66616 @rmorrow2018 @ItchyBacca @expandeduniv @ClassicGlu You know what trips me out. That Froghorn… https://t.co/EXalD8UNcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve stood behind Miley Cyrus during every insane phase of hers beginning with her original sheet-draped VF cover b… https://t.co/nJXPYSsjij]]></document><document><![CDATA[📖1 SAMUEL 16:7 L😏😏K N😐T🔛 HIS C😊UNTENANCE 😔R THE HEIGHT 💀F HIS STAURE 🅱️CUZ ℹ️HAVE REFUSED HIM. 4️⃣THE L😇RD SEETH N😐… https://t.co/BNAxYittWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man is so done with the Lakers sitting with the fans😂😂😂 https://t.co/57jz4NL8Gs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mouthful of Freedom IPA by @3keysbrewing at @squawvalleyldge — https://t.co/zYlEI4otcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the matches we need to judge the squad and Ole on.   How are both doing so far?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexHaynesLaw @tidalport @ChanceSmitty @JOEL_Slyman Oh yea I’ve heard him say that many times]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could think of something to do with wheat...because it sure doesn’t cost much]]></document><document><![CDATA[1878-1854 Crenshaw Blvd 1878-1854 Crenshaw Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90019 https://t.co/afLEL434b5]]></document><document><![CDATA[French Tech 4 Good panel starting now at #EUatSXSW ⁦@Konexio_eu⁩ ⁦@linagora⁩ ⁦@unknownsfrance⁩ ⁦@BF_TechServices⁩ ⁦… https://t.co/7UJjk5tYqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotLAkid we were just watching Val Venis entrance video 😂😂😂 Valentine's Day makes us look at Val Venis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatCunnane Fair enough I respect your thinking as well you know how unfair Hillary was treated]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GasBuddyDan Correction: "unless a court strikes it down" or Justin Trudeau is kicked out of office in October😁😁]]></document></documents></author>