<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Can really taste the wood notes. - Drinking an A Tale of Two Villages by @werkforcebrew/@OswegoBrewing at… https://t.co/RkIwirBLaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful concert with the Harmonies De Charlesbourg et De La Croix Valmer! #PoPride https://t.co/9KQctB1EaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raugatuck and Sale for you and your mom nnn you Sale the Sale; A Waterfront Fantasy Cottage starts on 3/8/2019… https://t.co/reue5Dzt09]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddisonKirkland @dog_rates You know, we can care about all of those things and still care about this dog as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRF23_ I'm not even political enough to say anything. It's just a tweet. Relax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since their complaints about Trump are based on their conservative beliefs, I've paid more attention to those belie… https://t.co/sPHkSe7Syp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open Letter to Congress: Remove Rep. Omar from the House Foreign Affairs Committee https://t.co/9U5Bc1gZzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyEAwesome Take measurements not weight.  Your body is going through a metamorphosis right now.  And are you w… https://t.co/uO9CYsMrVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Them: "Hey Tasha, we want you to take over this doomed project which will involve a new capital project with struct… https://t.co/t9R2gFx0I4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a few minutes to watch an amazing thank you video to Gary Senise, aka "Lieutenant Dan"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boogie2988 I'm the one to talk about this subject with. I went thru the same thing last year. I can tell you about dentures.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TereRodriguezTV Una periodista que admiró desde la Universidad! 💜 https://t.co/7FBeYsTzob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her income was too great to make this communism happen, said redhead angrily with me, who substituted for Admiral… https://t.co/2jgc28NtKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARONFOX TRUEX NO SIT HE ISNT ALL HE THINKS HE IS WAY TO GO BRAD👌💪👊🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Who cares if PPL are outraged.  Those poor individuals had just been throu… https://t.co/OhlqCXUwV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@linhmhoang I used to be there all the time when Ryan was in school bc it is so great that I think people thought I… https://t.co/eUFaV0k767]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nude year, nude you. Barely there set from @touchdolls. Use code GINGERDOLL for 10% off in store or online.… https://t.co/gLqRlswn57]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it that every time I’m in a situation, everyone on my tl is having the same thing happen to them. Y’all just make me more sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleased to be in invited to attend ...  The PIPSC HC-NCR Branch Executives, in collaboration with Ottawa Public Hea… https://t.co/8017DcmLbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Janet Montgomery’s American accent deserves an award.. #NewAmsterdam #NBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let my silence speak louder  than what my words have.  Maybe then, will everyone see what  I’ve been trying to say.… https://t.co/mPuAByAbAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our whole approach to Depression is to yell "SELF CARE" at people until they slice open their wrists and I wish we'd stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was featured on the @nprinterns tumblr and my cat’s instagram received a shout out without me asking which is exa… https://t.co/jm2CbGORyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your iPhone may be secretly sharing private health data with Facebook | Advisory Board Daily Briefing: https://t.co/DJsA9wk8FT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Well you're a little premature! Rick Gates singing like a canary along with Cohen. #Havana]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 AAPL shareholders meeting: New iPad Pro features, philanthropy controversy, Apple health push - 9to5Mac https://t.co/nln3WqH9PM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m cleaning off a shelf and trying to figure out where everything goes.  There were a few things on here to keep -… https://t.co/3oB76gE9eu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“i will not allow myself to not feel chosen every single day” PREACH hannah b #TheBachelor https://t.co/bXTcC8Ht3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[The presence of Donald and Goofy in KH unchained has some DEEPLY unsettling implications for either the KH timeline… https://t.co/TKFqLFnuOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goes out for one night: Random white man with receding hair line: grasps upper theigh on both legs for 5 seconds wh… https://t.co/N0eLriyMI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TariffMYtaxCUT @cspanwj @joannepikedrph I refuse the extra $20 for a package to include Fox... only have msnbc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @hunter_catka Hunter Catka on his region championship! Incredible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher You carried this dress off in your inimitable classy style. Besides Mackie, let’s not forget the efforts of y… https://t.co/7IRWhU0ndF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karlyn DeSteno last night. We’re playing a show at Bazaar Cafe March 8! #karlyndesteno @ The Lost Church - San Fran… https://t.co/3QUEWd0Q2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies, your shoulders are not meant to carry someone's dusty son... Support him... but never let a man weigh you down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IrregularDave @showupforthis @IrregularDave we have the same birthday!  Were you born on a Friday?  I was...explains a lot, I’m told.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salt Flats at Badwater Basin in Death Valley National Park are unlike anything I’ve ever seen... See more pics in m… https://t.co/lpi7XNpuZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fabulous #staging by #coasttocoastinteriors team members mkletendre and @homestagermimi at this #studio #condo… https://t.co/da8hTVTlR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson when Jej Vinson picked her for his coach on @NBCTheVoice 🤣🤣 https://t.co/xvl7oke6AD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CelesteMorgan99 dont miss that place at all but i do miss all the dumb shit we did when we were supposed to be wor… https://t.co/O7w2FlOdLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[AI QUE RAIVA HIJE EU NÃO IA CUIDAR DE CRIANÇA PQ A MILHER FALOU Q NÃO PRECISAVA AGORA ELA ME LIGA NOVE N O V E HORA… https://t.co/kqyFbySQHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[A play with some very strong women on #internationalwomensday ❤️💪🏼 Great show about family, how crazy life can be,… https://t.co/jTbcpzLhdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yungjunge @VisitUofSC @UofSC @Penn Your navy blue Penn/Ivy League Nike long sleeve light jacket that I can’t curre… https://t.co/yyEfGkLhCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @maddow They will end up voting the party line. They are all cowards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Trump: why are you letting #FakeMelania troll you? When are you going to stand up for yourself? She trolled you la… https://t.co/etAJ4WluE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[One Minute #BREAKDOWN: @DUANEBANGCOM Creates the Perfect Moment for the Counter #BINK!! . This analysis of this swe… https://t.co/w81pfY3KZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peyton: I don’t want to go to sleep  Me: well you have to Peyton: I’m mad at you. Now I’m going to sing.  😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morgxn @UberFacts It’s so real. I don’t have any female friends that really feel much of anything about being chea… https://t.co/TGYJkKAD0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiepatrick Also, I'm not sure that anyone would be able to read the fine print from so far away, but since I can… https://t.co/eJc9cjyUwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you come home after a long ass day at work and your man surprises you with @JeffreeStar brushes 💕👌🏻😭 https://t.co/9FxruDuHjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m forcing myself to go on acutane again so I can get rid of my acne for good. If I get severe depression again ho… https://t.co/r1D0swKs3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National #LoveYourPetDay now that is what I call some #WednesdayMotivation 🥰🐶❤️ #RHOD #wednesdaythoughts https://t.co/5w9he5l3iN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RbKerry @LouDobbs Hey Kerry, you do know Cohen is going to prison for all his lies, yes???  Under oath.  Now, poin… https://t.co/uSKpIiL5vY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Trump is a lost soul. when it's all said it done, he will wish he had done things diffe… https://t.co/Xyrqlo5iIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AyannaPressley @IlhanMN I disagree... the person closest to the pain should have a voice, but not the POWER!… https://t.co/gtrtuisqNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordan_overby happy birthday!!! 💗 I hope you have an amazing day! Love and miss you sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[MLMS students can choose from a variety of activities during PE, including but not limited to Flag Football 🏈, Fris… https://t.co/5I9mTHS46k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was watching legally blonde last night and it low key stereotypes and is racist af😩 I still like the movie thoughh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Houston_1_Fan Ha! Not weird at all, I’m good :) Now, how do I figure out who you are?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Best explanation I've seen so far! #BuildTheWall https://t.co/cSnpM0Sii4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giles_whitaker @barb71 @Mopor777 @joyce92009250 @KathyDutton16 @thelastmilehome @ElkeHansen7 @MiAbeck13… https://t.co/npiHqY82Pl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning to everyone especially @MikieSherrill who won my heart by turning my hometown district blue AND also j… https://t.co/48Wn9VUASu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKalenAllen It’s crazy how fast your life changed, for the better. You have a blue check mark, fashion shows....… https://t.co/xYFUeBQI3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took them 2 freaking years to figure that out!? Morons I knew just by listening to him come down escalator]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually had a professor two semesters ago for pre law writing who wouldn’t share her LSAT experience with the cl… https://t.co/cpFMSdJCea]]></document><document><![CDATA[i honestly don’t care if i get a follow as long as my mutuals who deserve it gets one 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerryGlavin @nationalpost Indeed it was. Although someone tweeted they couldn't wait until NP went bankrupt. The o… https://t.co/kNOVpSmEBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianYelich, my son just got home from his catching lesson with your brother and has good reading material for… https://t.co/Z5X74LGS4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see a Horror movie in the making by Japanese film makers. Momo vs. Slenderman. Y’all know it’s coming 🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @Mix965Houston plays a meaningful song about your identity in Christ 😍😍 &gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday Kiss  Up to good in Whittier passing out a free event March 9th Learn why you need a living trust wh… https://t.co/f17SI5b7ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life isn’t about finding yourself, it’s about creating yourself 📸🎥✨ Big things in the works for #leahfreemanmedia a… https://t.co/Q2FBEYRDPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lopezobrador_ si todo el mundo lo ve, Tú -alimaña- por qué no? Qué contubernio tienes con Maduro? https://t.co/L8AtAauSud]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream I was @KimKardashian’s nanny but all we did was sit around and listen to Kanye’s music and gossip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PenPure1 Really interested to see the adult William who is suppose to look so much like Jamie. How will they pull… https://t.co/ugiViK4YCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[These commercials tonight are FABULOUS!  For an intelligent audience - thank you, buyers and creators.  More in oth… https://t.co/FvEdXvKU2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to kick off the 2019 Job Shadow Day with @ITAbuzz, Women Influence Chicago and Tech Forward on this year’s… https://t.co/gKdQ58hXeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats To my cousin Olga!!! What a great educator to name a school after!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RidersNY @NYCMayor Where's the money from the past 4 years that was supposed to be dedicated to the subway? The ta… https://t.co/VUHHxWrs3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CopsandBarbers1 Not sure yet. It depends on what the topic is and then I have to find out when guest speakers are available to join me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FREETOMMY8 @Vincenz42493578 @aleeyun_nvaazun @Merry_Hippie @Lastplace_champ @BertJ4411 @oldscool18… https://t.co/k9d9Nl1CcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi...STOP INVALIDATING PEOPLES FEELINGS... thank you for attending my ted talk☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing shows dedication than getting to work 1 hr 15 minutes early when you are on salary...ornis it stupidity??🤷‍♀️🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh the only news I needed today 😋🥒🥳   #30thbirthday 👇🏼👇🏼 https://t.co/zMR12gz9qT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity After all the fires, floods, and landslides California has had i would find a closet and go pray it’s… https://t.co/HVfWGeFwqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like to watch horror movies. Alone. At night. After finishing listening to @NicolZanzarella read to me about murd… https://t.co/giS1469KWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlobalMarshal @RealCandaceO Truth... or get ratings for a dying Hollywood!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kassanmccan @HonestLeYo @_lightbrigght_ @DearSpecialK No that guy was blocked from my side you may not have seen i… https://t.co/E05Jx5B34d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best practice in #blockchain : include collaboration and governance. #Think2019  ⁦@TechwaveC⁩ https://t.co/EOV33Pmpjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this #IWD19 take time to recognize the all the amazing women in your life that shape and inspire you daily. Take… https://t.co/65dmyfWecH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo era esa residente que compartía memes y no artículos... Al menos si iba a joder lo hacía con sentido del humor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun adventures @feetloose #thefootes #thefeet #adventurebuddies #mrandmrs #gusgus #wondermutt #biggie #haggis… https://t.co/0DiIRzgLbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senegalese people cannot folle directions.Why are these people taking pictures of their envelopes and leaving with… https://t.co/hN3uYXpih2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discovered I have a hole in the butt of my leggings...I’ve been wearing these dang things all day. Sorry to anyone… https://t.co/zcjxXfCeuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching and listening to the #MichaelCohen hearings and listening to Jordan be so upset over lying is the ultimate… https://t.co/JCqebAz4H5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oprah @GayleKing @CBSThisMorning Yes she was Oprah! Learned from the best you think? Lol Meaning watching her best bud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the mid term blues. I’m trying my best, but I just don’t feel like I’m that student. I have to try harder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I measure 61.1 dB(A) using #NoiseCapture https://t.co/RNXLChcaqG via @Noise_Planet]]></document><document><![CDATA[alright i’m out here spending my vday doing tests and papers and so far we passed this test now let’s see about this paper]]></document><document><![CDATA[GAME DAY @HYPETEAM_MLCHS! LADY TITANS VS SIMON KENTON! #LetsGo #GETHYPED #MakingHistory]]></document></documents></author>