<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Who goes into a bathroom stall to blast lil Wayne? Let me wash my hands in peace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoonbootMurphy It's Terrace Creek in Montlake Terrace, WA. Pretty good, but difficult course]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I just hear "Smack my bitch up" by @the_prodigy as bed music on @WABEfm? RIP Keith.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Autumn Ortega and Lindsey Crawford fall in a pair of heartbreaking matches. Chanel Siva, Anna Schander and Will Inghram up next]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who says there isn’t a sealed indictments already YOU R SPREADING non factual garbage]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same energy you put out in this world is the same energy you will receive. All love and positivity around me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caliicoder3 @jepp03578406 It’s a game they play. Still waiting for real racism from Cons. So far it’s only coming… https://t.co/UXMlAk1wip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDSussman Eh...I’d say they are rebuilding rather than trying to lose as many games S possible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Draylen_Ellis5, “If you aren’t going all the way, why go at all?” #Lionheart #Beastmode #GetYour🍿  #4️⃣🌎ISHERE… https://t.co/wZ026HSwZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiguelSanchezPR It was given to us at the Senior Leadership Mtg in January.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇦🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss kirsty_lee__ The White RACE Australian BLONDES👑🇦🇺 Women Are The MOST Beau… https://t.co/uAXBqVHilo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryWmMyers Thank you for following me! I am very excited to connect with you on topics such as writing, blogging… https://t.co/8apEKq6iao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaggiegreenwood @EsotericExposal Examine our religion as opposed to what?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morrrrrrrninnnnnnng! Have a kickass day everyone! Smile in the mirror and say “FUCK YOU NEGATIVE THOUGHTS. POSITIVE ALL DAY BITCH.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/stbmhkob3A Amazing Trump owns a hotel in Punta del Esta Uruguay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJCavan A few, but I don't know how many were scheduled. At least a few weren't because they came on the PA to tell us why we were waiting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarahchowtrail This seems so complicated when you look at the list and try to decide what to send. Is there an opt… https://t.co/YtduRcum8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely so excited for @white_alea !  Way to go!  So proud of you and your journey!  Keep being you and shining… https://t.co/hLXgtFFxYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freezebrand44 AOC here's a great idea I'm surprised you haven't thought of it, pay the WNBA the same salary scale… https://t.co/GBT1KU65br]]></document><document><![CDATA[He knows I’m trying my best to take care of my momma and make sure she never has to worry about money and bills🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter Legal Warns Michelle Malkin Her 'Mohammed Cartoon Tweet' Violates "Pakistan's Blasphemy Laws" - Which Are P… https://t.co/GUyBH5YkhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeGero I'm referring to his shit performance 95% of the time when it mattered with the Yankees. And he didn't wif… https://t.co/ptA99Sahsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@commutertutor1 @holdthelineWR @Cycle_WR @s_weldon It looks so nice out there... Why can't it feel like that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH: "The only real adopters of TSX were, as it turns out, exploit writers."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going down right now!! @ Crosstown Brewing Company https://t.co/ZJmaLmpVNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taber @irapolis What if cities had Housing Approval Departments HAD with the  approval process in one department that prioritized housing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juan: “is Mary ‘Pretty Bitch’ on Twitter cause I honestly can’t tell she’s always changing her name”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankfully the jaguar won't be put down for HER stupidity. Maybe they should put the woman down so she won't breed… https://t.co/6tIkDNAkOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st time cruiser would love to have Make It Rough included sometime #OTMFB @NickHexum @pnut https://t.co/keSyTfnXJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spvmty @Mty_Leones dos perritos sobre la joroba Gonzalitos y leones están muy asustados alguien que los recoja por qué los van a atropellar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fico_ciello hit the rt button for this; just thought I would re-up it b/c it’s v much Drew 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WitchyWife1964 @ManicMinxy @Tarantical Beets...never been a fan of them as a veggie, though their other applications are good for everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett And the Department of Justice lawsuit against you and your father Fredreich for re… https://t.co/MVSIOb00RM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Black Currant  by @FinnriverCider at @fortgeorgebeer — https://t.co/BIJ74OxFPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jajajajajajja #amor #badabun #lol #crazy #amargo #haha #oops #diablo #malo @ Burbank, California https://t.co/vqIlymYSob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jetlife_Ryan_ They pops was cheating they ass off saying they had to go “get that over time”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hopitoulas by @nolabrewing @ Parade Route- St. Charles Ave Between Constantinople and General Taylor — https://t.co/o5IPw81XoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summoning circle!! Hope this works                             🕯               🕯              🕯         🕯         U… https://t.co/GYDdmQ1OkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHebert89 I wish I had the confidence to speak on national television about something I knew nothing about. Truly impressive]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guitar was signed by each member of The Beatles, and it's for sale at The Mirage. The same hotel that hosts Th… https://t.co/An1qLpSrJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patrickviolence Yo I’m down for my Filipino cousins. But fuck that thing. I would adobo the shit out of every single one of them binches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejester999 @RealGlenMacnow My wife watched it and barely made it to the end. That says it all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidwoellmer hello! I made a typo and wrote “a well” instead of “awhile.”  You liked the tweet that portrayed Jud… https://t.co/VReulNdTtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skalawag37 @RyStar7_ Sarcasm lovingly accepted.  Only strive to hit balls over defenders' heads, tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only in @NJGov do I sit at a bar and listen to a man "coach" the @NHLFlyers while the bartender struggles to get th… https://t.co/ZIUnclIMvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Molly_G24 Things I never thought about before I was already working: how valuable WFH is in the state of Minnesota]]></document><document><![CDATA[BLACK People want EQUALITY just like everyone else!! THE AWAKENING!!👀 IM SO HAPPY SOME BLACK ARE WOKE!! BLCK PPL, W… https://t.co/99OHvF0Nfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrosBros1 Oscar’s reaction was priceless.  Then his brother drove off in the damn hole]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ssj5goku28 @jamin000 It brings back the battlefield with friends feel for me https://t.co/pRd5va2HPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[GET READY TO PAY MORE Sales Tax #OrangeCounty I voted no but lost to #GardenGrove 😐  The tax increases, 1.5 percent… https://t.co/adMtMmZOIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hamptonbrando You lost everything because of your toxic behavior and you don’t even have the slightest clue about… https://t.co/wqmaoDdBrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW SAUSAGE. NEW FRIES. TELL YOUR GRANDMA YOU LOVE HER. // veal/guanciale hot dog, dijon, sage, new england roll https://t.co/iOGb2rGtsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know, this used to be me but honestly if he doing all that you can just go right ahead and have him just let me… https://t.co/s9pPhTH8T7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohmygod Kickstart from a fountain what did I do to deserve this glorious bounty??? https://t.co/WTwrJwSv8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mugshot of 25-year-old David Fuentes, charged with Intoxication Manslaughter for the death of 1-year-old Corinna To… https://t.co/XVAydDguVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wherefore, my beloved brethren, let every man be swift to hear, slow to speak, slow to wrath: James… https://t.co/YvnhnwySjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, someone leaked a memo from @SpeakerPelosi about tomorrow’s resolution. https://t.co/NXaAd59WKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am CRYING laughing so hard at this. This, without hyperbole, is the greatest thing I have ever seen.  We are in A… https://t.co/tzuaKF28V8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful process with the most beautiful woman ❤️ https://t.co/dK5OOL4MrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selling my old 21 UX Cintiq. It’s got a lot of mileage on it but was still getting the job down before I upgraded c… https://t.co/ThHPVZtRv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who needs an American made Buttula #bbqbuttula if you're good on the grill it's a must have just ask @GuyFieri #kc… https://t.co/M1WeRNdEm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharlesPreston Butterfly tagger Farm worker Janitor Computer repair tech QA engineer DNS administrator (why I lef… https://t.co/uLsSm43Oey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Heather! That is awesome!! All The Best to both of you!! 💑💍]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @buffalobills can kill this year's draft! Deep talent at their position of needs and 10 picks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely disgraceful. It will be an unfortunate moment for our nation in defining a hard limit on executive emerg… https://t.co/ONyWGx7YaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows @MarkMeadows you dropped the ball on the lady you said you brought to the committee.a decent Africa… https://t.co/p5q7WiSpmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @DonaldJTrumpJr @LaraLeaTrump @EricTrump Happy birthday to Kimberly! Now help DRAIN THE SWAMP! Celebr… https://t.co/iveBiZaXGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greetings and salutations. BESS Art Exposure Gallery 5386 Broadway Merrillville Indiana needs your assistance.   To… https://t.co/FSfq24PX25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillF1 @F1 @SkySportsF1 @MercedesAMGF1 @LewisHamilton Nah, 2009 was always going to be tougher.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenMatthews these avowed so called open minded "socialist " you speak of would all enact hardcore Marxism/communis… https://t.co/Yk1md92jnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morbid Angel - 03/10/2019 - Baltimore Soundstage @official_morbid @ Baltimore Soundstage https://t.co/csBCq3qp9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to rock! #fergslivetampa #tampa #lightning #tblightning #florida #bethethunder #musicianlife #giglife… https://t.co/Ti80LL74Pj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN If Abe did this he falls into the obsequious, sycophant Trump toady category along with other Trump losers. No… https://t.co/ufTs7EFFGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The minor charges against RK, optics. Condition the public for highprofile arrest of worse crimes.We're only gettin… https://t.co/OZCRPaaTcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Denney_ You probably moved on from me but you’ll always be a real one to me bubby 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SantiBajaPanti @HisNameIsAdrian It’s my guys other Ad-lib... OOOOOOOAAAAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben Simmons is regarded as one of the best young players in the NBA and has the same issues. He doesn’t look lost o… https://t.co/bJrBvOwr9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tednaiman please could you advise me? I am Keto I have been for a while, but staying at the same weight it’s so fr… https://t.co/pdTQrKmN5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[...stories. She didn’t have much but she gave me a gold giraffe pendant and your her high school tassel. People may… https://t.co/JxOpL3HUVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS request for $8.6 Billion for the Wall/border security should be easily approved by @SpeakerPelosi… https://t.co/RcmloUS1rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodgers_randi I remember Kimbrel struggling to close games in the playoffs. I don’t want him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Airport Cancellations so far today - At O'Hare 12 - Midway 12 @TotalTrafficCHI  @Bryesha_Adams  @WBEZmorning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimoraland_ @Don_Thomas_ Lol 😂 they retired for me. Put them in early retirement! 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoemiNalgona @ASRBOOTY @ASRBABES @swaglive_app @GuiaCalienteMTY @scortsexmty @amigasdiscretas @ESCORTSPREMIUMX… https://t.co/TAxGu9l3nL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clownlesbian omg can i try this too n tag you?? i don’t even do makeup but this is so cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RIDiverGirl @SaarduLady @RepMarkMeadows And @realDonaldTrump is incapable of telling the truth. Wonder how Trump d… https://t.co/nyi1mlgNYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two campaign workers have been shot this election season, one didn't make after being hit 12 times. I personally ha… https://t.co/VcHXezqmbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Rip Cord Double IPA® by @DaredevilBeer at @Boombozz_Indy — https://t.co/1zlqEtBgU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m up ready for extra dialysis. I feel amazing. If this can continue for the rest of the day I’m looking at a wond… https://t.co/hBxD8O7xSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @OEBMcNerney to post seven covers of books I love-no explanation-no review-just th… https://t.co/6BrQs6ThmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#askali "SHOULD I BLOG, VLOG, PODCAST OR LIVESTREAM?"   🤷‍♀️Overwhelmed with all of the options?   I don’t believe… https://t.co/8Ekos8RZut]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @MeganInky @NestyXXX @VeroLealX @ZazieSKY @DeeWilliamsXXX @siennasinclaire @BlairSummersXXX @1daisymarie… https://t.co/YghjqcqN2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know preseason doesn’t matter, but it always feels good to beat those damn Yankees. 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[This last week of apartment hunting has given me a headache every single day. I’m tied.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josh_Haider Dude I was like crying, most of it is just them like breathing heavy haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics Gentleman Joe knows what a sleazebag pence really is and needs to call him out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our hardworking kids. Using their skills to make a difference in the lives of other kids. #omgrobots… https://t.co/muBqXXLAry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tad_Walch @DeseretNews @UtahAG @CivilRights @LDSPrinciples are violated_  The blood of unborn cry against you all.… https://t.co/ByER8wOYn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#COAC2019S2 Desde Austin (Texas) viendo la comparsa de Don Antonio ! https://t.co/3ZysOarzz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs. Palmer...you blessed us this morning with how you honored our daughter by all that you said. You are a blessin… https://t.co/5iJlvLwl0v]]></document></documents></author>