<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Have you pressed play? Its @EmmaBunton #NewMusicAlert #NewMusicFriday #newmusic #BabyPleaseDontStop #RadioShow https://t.co/l000XJmpHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsmebeccam @JacksonCDavis @KamalaHarris not coded language, just me being snarky towards a profile that seems extremely neo-liberal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flanagan72John @6549lmartin @terrietime No politico economic system in history had proved its value so eloquently… https://t.co/sgSuYma6rJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fugue state between “look at all the things I’ve accomplished” and “you hubristic fake, you haven’t accomplish anything”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 6th birthday to the furry homie  Waffle #OGChungus https://t.co/F2tFwWADG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rangers coach livid for good reason. “F*%^*ng joke” he said if my lip reading was accurate. Staal probably got away… https://t.co/EgkCUxeU9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelseymaccombs @TBenFischer You mean, happy hour at our house because we have so many marg fixins? Still a shame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @LaraLeaTrump @realDonaldTrump Get'er done Trump MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@levarburton Not all heroes wear capes...but some get parks named after them. https://t.co/4acbzBsgEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catturd2 Not an ounce of guilt earned everything I have through hard work]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que hermosura de ejemplar no creen? #luisfernandomusic #despecho #popular #caballos #caballodepaso #caballo en El G… https://t.co/J8rFUAxdak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sigh why everyone i talk to for a while end up getting a boo. This shit trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unless non TRS party gets strong mandate from people, KCR will not let the opposition survive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry So conversations and free speech is criminal? No actions occurred and no laws were broken, In Russia you… https://t.co/6IZdacnnLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 hours, 8 minutes, until I'm 41. Heading downhill with my foot on the brake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I am #grateful that my #friends @JamesCurryIII and @kennicollins17 are in San Diego! I am grateful that the… https://t.co/Fo5AeuV78I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@velvetmelvis Cinematography not critical?  You mean the Men and Women how actually work the camera that creates th… https://t.co/4yX3NjtkPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogerwaters Hey Roger, why don’t you live in Venezuela? You can give a chance to Venezuela’s dictatorship to have… https://t.co/K9T4nLRbXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Harvest Time by Dianne Reeves, from #SoundHound https://t.co/PVSEgZRNzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hunt_roger @spkstl @redfacts Not sure the origin of this thread but it’s enjoyable! #blessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skulleigh @FlyingTrilobite Ah, memories. I'm pretty sure that's the first action figure I ever bought with my own… https://t.co/psQF3WVbuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@La_Bella_Amor #JussieSmollettHoax is unacceptable and anyone defending his actions are unable of accepting the tru… https://t.co/O16hgnQPqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I think we forget how lucky we are as @RedSox fans to have such good reporters coving our team.  This guy… https://t.co/z8qTLE0gJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicagobars Serious question: what is backpack etiquette while on the el?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys! I'm streaming some real money poker. $300 gtd. Come cheer me on or just say hi! https://t.co/ICfYQhZS04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Calebcongrove I think it’s fairly easy to imagine most things taste better not expired IMO 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbcpnews @gilgueva Kayo dyan sa pilipinas mga pari kayo , tinago nyo ang inyong mga at pinagtakpan nyo huwag Na il… https://t.co/iIAB0HsNBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Womens Day and I ain't got no womens. It's like Valentine's Day 2.0 or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jweirREP I predict it will come to an end and that the majority of Cavs fans will act like the world is coming to a catastrophic end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝🔥🍭😍😘 https://t.co/UIdxw4UyF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at intersection of Little Creek Rd and Chesapeake Blvd in Norfolk, VA https://t.co/yB8qJfgqnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[25% of presidents (up from 20% last year) say campus race relations   nationally are good/excellent - and 8 of 10 s… https://t.co/69H8bvBFLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at American Airlines Catering Facility in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/YAs7JoYCHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asuu13741726 @samiia95 @dtb1016 @yaboysherwood Have we made friends worldwide?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The WPIAL has its first wrestler into the PIAA semifinals, as South Park’s Joey Fischer advances at 106 pounds with… https://t.co/1oy5Pjw860]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RitaPanahi I don’t understand how these two pendejas think that it is their responsibility to worry about others.… https://t.co/8me0QfEPYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of these players getting released or not having options exercised is crazy to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irishvixen21 @JeffreyStites I’ve been challenged by @irishvixen21 to post a cover of a favorite book each day for… https://t.co/Cgelxq7fkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree Candace, so long as we are looking to the author and finisher of our faith. Our source of strength is in hi… https://t.co/S8sETygsHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both @NotreDame and @NorthwesternU made the morning show today.   Great institutions.  Tricia and I attempted to be… https://t.co/PIusR3cIe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoaRShoukR Btw when I say this. It’s a little extreme. I met some really cool people, made friends with amazing pl… https://t.co/KLATmuJJth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dalek_fan @Andre_Dragosch @RobinBrooksIIF "But the reason to dislike excessive inflation is that it ultimately mak… https://t.co/BomIje2zzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madison doesn’t know it yet but. We are catching an Eagles vs Cowboys game in Dallas this December!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be presenting the @osstf Cultivating Resilience workshop with my colleague Sarah @TheOldMillInn https://t.co/vxMmJ6BRSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Project Complete ✔️ #nuviewlibrary @ Fullerton, California https://t.co/N4kiglpcvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanBloechl @DanaBecker @MurphyKeith Install a private-school shot clock? 🤔😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rlaurich Nailed it.  Thespian? (Not that there's anything wrong with that...)]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can you criticize the #Habs 4th line when they have only played one game together and against the best team in… https://t.co/d0diNCVZgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shocked SHOCKED that Richard Burr has been a bad faith partner this whole time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markyce617 @Patricia_Traina Have you been to a game the last couple of years? No one was at the last 3 home games.… https://t.co/AKR6sqiyVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradTakei @GeorgeTakei The bathroom on the landing is at least a conversation piece]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I just watch @AndrewYangVFA just convince @TuckerCarlson that socialism is the future of America?? I think I di… https://t.co/SrVaxsgLuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will be the scene whenever the Harper signing finally goes down. https://t.co/7IC1LWy0Nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chubbywaifuu &amp; I are stuck in the @TheTwilightZone 😱 https://t.co/YY1A1oGGFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fabrimaccioni @CiscoLive @FwdNetworks Nice!  I need to swing by and checkout your stuff sometime that week.  Haven… https://t.co/4PcJxjKwJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilsarg @JoshDavisthinks We’re a team, Sarge. Both from the ragged edge of the middle class while Davs rigged the… https://t.co/4o6gpqMBud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miren, a todas mis queridas  caraquista, dejen los celos que a todas las quiero a pesar de ese notable defecto. 😂😈 #vengandeauna]]></document><document><![CDATA[When one producer who drags me into hours of reality TV every week calls out the other producer who drags me into h… https://t.co/8jGSJVVlLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us tonight in the 47th Ward for a Meet and Greet (no cost) with Aldermanic candidate @jeffjenkins312 and the C… https://t.co/bOM6LEyd2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceWaTheTruth @jackie_macleoj @cspan @GOPLeader I imagine you've done nothing to improve the environment, especi… https://t.co/NOpzLqMWHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edhenry @FOXTV If New York's FOX station (WNYW/@Fox5NY) does not break in to their local newscast airing (as of th… https://t.co/NajPOljnPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t get lost in procedural details. The procedures can be facilitated. It’s power politics played by people who m… https://t.co/Lv7BnsMFwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @ClareDunnMusic for the halftime show @dallasmavs tonight. #livemusic #Mavericks #NBATwitterLive https://t.co/SufNFV6T98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RossTuckerNFL Eli by far.  2 time super bowl mvp and future hall of famer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ne fais jamais cette erreur d’oublier de mettre une bonne bouteille de vin rouge..., okay ? 😂😂😂😂😍 ps: c’est pas des… https://t.co/YJFydrWigV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RossRamsAD Also on @WMOHGameNight  on @TuneIn. #NowPlaying https://t.co/1rwykoslwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulwaldman1 Nothing she even said is a criticism of Israel, so that straw man has nothing to do with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisGOP @gogrl_tx @shanest94828972 @seanhannity @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @POTUS @FoxNews @KXAN_News Not… https://t.co/sn1c6ScWra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long drive ahead of me and I smell like a burger shack, which is both good and bad.  Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elie936Elie @kinsellawarren For someone who claims to be independent,  you're spending a lot of time defending the… https://t.co/2beIeTS91n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve longed thought pro sports is an untapped opening to build US interest in intl affairs, but seen more often lac… https://t.co/qlFIj7KTrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[it makes NO sense how I never take picture with some of my closest friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fitness19sac I am trying to keep this program from scams. I do want to cancel my membership but they have many BS.… https://t.co/A7J6fpNS3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoadMastery @GHSAHQ Everyone has a role to play in safety but it will take much more than reminding pedestrians to look both ways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeattleHoo @RTD_MikeBarber Agree 100 percent. Perhaps you get very little out of it if you’re going to the nba aft… https://t.co/i53aKJoSKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_MrBuentello_ Yes I wouldn’t be telling you about it if it didn’t lolol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsTalkShea Damn didnt notice that. Dude is fucking delusional lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that ESPN shows more Spring training Baseball highlights than regular season NHL highlights reeeeeeeeeeeeeeeally annoys me]]></document><document><![CDATA[André Burakovsky should be scoring for the #Sabres, not against the Sabres]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s always that one kid at a restaurant that stares at you for no reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kurt Busch #1 @CGRnascar  kurtbusch @ Las Vegas Motor Speedway Pits https://t.co/6q17S9QHh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaddCompani @TheOriginalNai this is all the reason people need to wake up and push to have him fired then sent to the nearest prison!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally watched "The Merchants of Doubt" all the way through for the first time. And, man, Naomi Oreskes is a hero.… https://t.co/AAK5kLqazF]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ronaldacunajr24 Llegó hoy a los campos de entrenamiento de los Bravos de Atlanta en Lake Buena Vista, FL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #NBA is in an era of positionless basketball, where players are expected to do everything on the court.  How Lu… https://t.co/RCrMLP1X0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sundayrun #southflorida @ Royal Palm Beach, Florida https://t.co/KK276lrQly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great advice for educators to take on and share with students from current panel on Inventiveness @SXSWEDU. “If you… https://t.co/o78w60NVBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbeSnowman Even though it ran perfectly every single time. And I always put on a proud face, in spite of constantl… https://t.co/Hc9LoNPKsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a record. Now the law has caught up with him. https://t.co/IoHpXtBYkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bjjbox #Newaza #Absolute #SubmissionSoup #Barnana #sweetsweat @ Houma, Louisiana https://t.co/tq7DSLmX9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to be quite a show watching these guys tear each other apart for the nomination.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticusSarah She has never had to start working at  2.12  cents an hour in the 70's .]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TodayInChurch I learned that this is not only powerful... it’s leaning. https://t.co/VJ43jfA1Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPXI @ErinClarkeWPXI Allegheny Co. Controller Chelsa Wagner is pathetic.  She needs to resign from office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The day when @CHAOSSEARCH demonstrates 100+ terabytes / 100+ billion rows scoped in less than a second on Amazon S3… https://t.co/iqhooJnlbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadly, we are wasting our heritage with our insatiable greed.  We refuse to become stewards...😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilByram39 @EASTENSPREG @TheCarterHornet @CarterHS_BBall @CarterCoSports Let’s be honest it’s not like the game s… https://t.co/1cMJEC3jMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Sarasota Circus at night during set up. Taken late January 2018. • • • #igers941 #sarasotaflorida #circus… https://t.co/xs4UuG1l0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s insane. Did you hear it two nights ago? Never heard thunder so loud in my life. There was two bug ones that sh… https://t.co/TG3epd5HwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 Oscars commentary and rant on what was once the #AcademyAwards https://t.co/PtLE9y7kUT]]></document></documents></author>