<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I always find it hilarious when people assume that I don’t know anything about marijuana. Believe it or not, I get that often. 💨💨💨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JViscoNJ @garrettoran @TheBlackKidJ Take a look at this video. This kid is 13 years old to be exact https://t.co/5rqaVVHsvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Medicare for all but keep the option open for private insurance because...In 2016, there were approximately 2.6 mil… https://t.co/GE4XgB0Gia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImranKhanPTI Please free KAVAN in Islamabad hell , send him to elephant rescue , please🐘❤️🙏❤️🐘]]></document><document><![CDATA[You look like a rockstar @techspire! What do you think friends @hooksettcms ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have two classes left to graduate and I’m freaking out.. don’t know why, I still have a month left before I can register 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a Snapchat premium though. 4.99 subscribers get 5 nudes for free. Lemme know cause the first is almost here s… https://t.co/HMuGJmzG6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[the fact that people STILL hate and judge others for the color of their skin blows my mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[7th grade honor roll assembly today  @GMS. The parents attended to support their children’s success for 2nd quarter… https://t.co/B7vrMLEQ0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad you are ok and thanks for being out there for us. #SlowDownMoveOver]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrOzAtheist Watching television. I hear people talking about great shows and I'm so. I need to work on  getting th… https://t.co/ivj978uixe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger You ppl are so dellusional with your shit talk! #45  has been ripping off… https://t.co/4BseQcbMdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[They said that’s it’s her time to go, no tears in sight, I kept the feelings close]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably just tried on all the clothes in my closet to put on all black and a Jean  jacket ,so luv that]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really funny how when you treat people how they’ve been treating you, they get pissed and turn it around on you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_MoveUP The refutations have been available for a long time now, he could have got the vaccinations done since and didn't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kweansmom I gave her the benefit of the doubt but she’s at it again. Her job concerns Americans in her district, n… https://t.co/GCgUF84QU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruvverEccles No, I think you got it right. I spend too much time in the morning voting for bad cardinals and maki… https://t.co/Iv24qSbi8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Job Opening: Senior Digital Marketing Associate - Work for a global information services and solutions leader offe… https://t.co/lv38uwL5n3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to the #BEWPS conference in Vegas! This has been a bucket list, vision board, personal goal type thing for a… https://t.co/RuQywKQw2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOfficerTatum @lisamartin64 @IlhanMN Impeachment for her Sign your petition  At https://t.co/1UjnjAZB1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t sleep because I can’t stop thinking about decorating my new room @Madisoncarriee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex_Micati Can you send me the link to your new blog post again? Thanks! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonRadosh It did look as if she was reading a paper she was unfamiliar with.  Ilhan is the attractive face of a very ugly agenda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EarlyMorningWorkouts #Drills #Weights #PuttinginThatWorkToday💪🏽 #NoDaysOff @npbutler22 https://t.co/Y28BWOLiz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday its Day 24 of the #FebruaryChallenge to do my #Daily #Pullups or #Dips Just woke up! #JoinTheMovement… https://t.co/Sb4QyYaiRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh THIS is wicked good!!!! Totally hits home with me. Can’t wait to read parts 2,3. #wellness Resident Wellness is… https://t.co/HCD2xWxQ2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Your comparison is so off the wall Eugene! Time for u to get real 😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[yessssss! so proud of @jpspecial and @jadebdub!!! #sheinspiresme 👏👏👏 https://t.co/mIQDrifJAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NIBScase way to go @StMarysGSB We are so proud of you! #NIBS2019 👍👏👊 #RattlerPride]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Operational Risk Consultant 5 - WFS Spread" at Wells Fargo? Apply even if you're n… https://t.co/B1a1YkTnvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[que final de semana tedioso do caralho, vem segunda feira, vem aula, vem professor americano]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scientists Pin Down Cause of Mysterious 'Icequakes' Shaking Antarctica https://t.co/76K4xpah70 via @LiveScience]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phildrost hey Phil...still out of the country right now...flyback tomorrow night. You can reach me at abch2005@gma… https://t.co/9SgdJ1ksv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to see a system that actually increases funds allowing families especially in rural and low income situation… https://t.co/L7XTutVtOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom Tom are those Billy bookcases from Ikea? If yes, I’m thinking of buying them. Also this is my kitty,… https://t.co/jRfkMIHj5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[having drinks &amp; contemplating life with my bestie girl what can go wrong? 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodoldcatchy Why in the world did the designer run text over the subject’s face? Secondly, that’s a weird catchph… https://t.co/XjI53tRfEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week officially marks 2 years at KWWL ♥️ From behind to camera to now in front of it, I’ve gotten to tell some… https://t.co/ANBcPxQGx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Waldorf #MD  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/TyqAJ5Mw7O  [For sale]]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold On   Hold on to  your hope a  little longer.  As spring will  soon arrive  with gentle  music for your soul to… https://t.co/fGfaWikLl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RIDiverGirl @SaarduLady @RepMarkMeadows Charlie Brown teacher wan, wan, wan wan....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Capital High School hosted the 14th annual "Live to Dance" competition this past Saturday. The event included 64 pe… https://t.co/agIKziOkzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will Rogers performed both on the midway and in a Wild West show inside the fairground.... #humor #chuckle #smile… https://t.co/7Yvd10P28H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder: BMI is a terrible measure of individual health, regardless of what you think about the president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s here! Maren’s second album #GIRL is here and you can tell this album was a labor of love 💖 I am so proud of yo… https://t.co/pwrYdRBiVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Never having to turn the clocks back and forth and I have about 15 would be wonderful ..when my ch… https://t.co/44hKEtDhxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stefsstuff @PalmerReport But Kraft not involved I n trafficking   Kraft is not accused of or charged with being in… https://t.co/xVwIGqubAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes @KamalaHarris @JacobAWohl I’m wishing you a healthy life and happiness🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxBoot @renato_mariotti Exactly. Manafort is whining that he was charged with crimes other than Trump-Russia camp… https://t.co/VDAj66z00O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@8erpentineskies @Iheartnoise There’s a sicker kind of cynicism to this way of thinking also.  a wanting to believe… https://t.co/aoRB2BmbeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those of you wondering what kinda woman I am: I’m allergic to cats....let that sink in a minute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlaylistLive Thankyou Playlist for Having me❤️ https://t.co/z5lcqmVLMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngryDingo I have functioning ears, a brain capable of analysis, and have never relied on Democrats for anything i… https://t.co/MeQXXsSMQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebKates @DanComp02107462 Will pray for healing so no surgery is necessary.and for his wife. We have a mighty God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He does care for the people who have loss what they have]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi Is it really for the people? Or just for your own addenda (enter rude half ass clap)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so excited to actually feel safer now for my morning walks at 4:45 am before work! It is by far my favorite ti… https://t.co/z6NZEb70dK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wore our school’s v-neck work shirt today and during class where I was sitting on the carpet with my kiddos mixin… https://t.co/1e105d30eq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m happy in the sense of I have a home, a fridge and cabinet full of food, a job that actually values me, and a ma… https://t.co/9e8Q0phCde]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwamealexander We has to step into the hall and talk when he finished. He was pretty upset. 15 minutes later he to… https://t.co/koMN8J6czX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mary Berry's Bakewell Tart Recipe and a Mincemeat Twist from Christina's Cucina https://t.co/XCEhhICpDC via @christinacucina]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this #dynamic #duo  performing #swan 🦢on the #reformer — #stunning 💜🙌🏻🙏🏻💪💦🔥 @ Pure Pilates https://t.co/bfe8XEu5vL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Return_Of_RB @SethOnHoops @franfraschilla But Rico! He has catch phrases!]]></document><document><![CDATA[just wanna remind everyone that bryan singer still stands to make at least $40 million off of bo rhap and the more… https://t.co/HqwaS6G8bB]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the kind of patriots we need. He is braver than I am. I am too old to get beaten up or harrassed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@papialexis6 Imo when people dress up for the rodeo to match the theme people call them out and say “ y’all are fake country “ blah blah .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meta analysis of data on 350,000 adolescents shows that technology use has a nearly negligible effect on adolescent… https://t.co/gWK29aQf0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is just pouting because his State mainstream media for decades had the light of truth shine on it and show the d… https://t.co/LxvWrqwVPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[But there is *nothing* that is *light* about the Burning Man scene and we mix with them all the time. Burning Man is dark AF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always think Lyft and Uber drivers secretly sign-up just for the riders that say “can you get me there in 15 minu… https://t.co/WDn96rnEyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg when I watched Stage Plight I knew Benny’s voice sounded familiar and he’s played by Sean Giambrone, who also p… https://t.co/MeRFmD1ucr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahNRO Dos Zoe's tail puff up (like my cat's)? Or is she always so fluffy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZapposTheater @gwenstefani @PHVegas Haha thanks! Lots of time hand painting every song No Doubt did up until that tour!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn't figure out y Ss didn't ask critical qs Then I realized they do all the time they just don't let me know… https://t.co/eaYd2twLxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@splendid_SHIT “Speak it into existence” if a bitch wasn’t broke I’d spoil the fuck out of you. You know you’re my one and only 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sexynana35 @JerryDMayer @SearchQueen @RepDanCrenshaw It happens almost everywhere.  Texas has an ID law, thank goodness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vanessa1971 I’ve heard talk about Puerto Rico lately. I’m talking about in 1898 After the Spanish-American War. Yo… https://t.co/Obshfp8MNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/m7zFkUSoD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m the only person that’ll buy a cheese steak just to eat the meat out of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHEN I WAS IN 10TH GRADE HALF THE NEIGHBORHOOD GUYS ASKED ME OUT AND GOT TURNED DOWN.   IT SEEMS SEVERAL OF THESE INDIVIDUALS HAVE A GRUDGE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does the estimated travel time on iPhones for your most frequently visited places freak anyone else out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have to use oil dry from the garage..... in the kitchen 🤦🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️❌🔥 @ Las Cruces, New Mexico https://t.co/2JDNZ16iMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So tense watching Paige and Davis move her cake 😂😂😂#KidsBakingChampionship https://t.co/XCPaz9WAdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahjaswim @MyPeakChallenge @MPCFitlanders @SamHeughan @Sheugs @barbaramills1 @SamsSecretAlias @ladybay8 @10MinDQ… https://t.co/QNSNhc96Qp]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/xTw4HFTXuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few reasons why I #loveteaching ❤️ #MDLTW19 @shmseagles https://t.co/OYM6LFKGio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, curious Kansas Citians! If you could ask the people running for mayor of #KansasCity one question what would i… https://t.co/erwwnNE3ZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbouzy Somebody should check if the judge has had a bunch of debt paid off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buffkin_90 I know I was trying to make a terrible pun...but that usually means a family is around if you see just… https://t.co/j51fEadqiK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m just a girl from New York that wanted to be an actress.” RT my Gaga lovers! @ladygaga #Oscars #eTalkRedCarpet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iiiiiQra Have an affair tonight! Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight. https://t.co/D30OFvedLZ #us #uk #nz #ca #dating]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom insists on talking to me like we are friends!   Mom: I wouldn’t go back to my 20s for nothing, I don’t miss… https://t.co/eJKDDKIfLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching The classic #CadillacRecords @itsgabrielleu @Beyonce @ColumbusShort1 @adrienbrody @CedEntertainer @jfreewright on @tvonetv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump @GOP Just leaving this here https://t.co/Q2hTSE1ies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemWrite @realDonaldTrump @GOP I really not a Bernie fan, but if he is who our party nominates, I will vote for hi… https://t.co/2KZeABzuMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @paulwesley it’s my birthday today!!! A tweet, like, or retweet from you would be the greatest gift ever!!!!!!… https://t.co/1MCKjQqLgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of luck East Grand Rapids hockey team. Not done yet!! Frozen Four.]]></document><document><![CDATA[these are hands down the most repulsive food bc ur literally picking muscle off the bone w ur teeth... arteries, ca… https://t.co/PZNUb06zAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just watched my boyfriend tell the boy hes guarding while playing in a district basketball game “i’m like propane… https://t.co/LdZzujCHxQ]]></document></documents></author>