<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[2/2 I want to thank the Lord for all his blessings and I know even in defeat he is a great father and deserves all… https://t.co/RLjIp5WPPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m werkin on myself for myself @ North Canton, Ohio https://t.co/uORA9ggW9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m the One” #jeffwoodmusic #austinmusic  #sanantoniomusic #texascountrymusic @ Aloft Austin Northwest https://t.co/YeUdzgBj98]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm fucked... I have interviews lined up.... but they are all part time with no health benefits   I dont think this… https://t.co/gWY629jOjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[No work today due to roads being closed so I'm being productive....ok I'm not being productive at all! https://t.co/rvRcf5yUMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad spent 20 minutes trying to explain it and I still don’t fully understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nheller22 &amp; @lynnesilver  It's that time again guys Gonzaga will it all! Just wanted to be on record. https://t.co/LTPR2oYdbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[When "concern about trafficking" takes off its mask and is revealed to merely be policing of women's sexual behavio… https://t.co/cSqwMwJXXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanzisf Looking for #UX #Writer in San Francisco, #CA Check full Job Description:- https://t.co/CPf45YsjxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dweeebus_ Remember the robotics program that built the 3D printer. I heard that no one else took this over and the… https://t.co/qhB94m7rvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaSchuld I see. It's hard to focus on the big picture if we let the little / sometimes irrelevant things eat… https://t.co/HSYKJEdpMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RacingRT1 @NASCARONFOX Along with those critiques are the ever-present evaluations of “he should retire and hang i… https://t.co/Wp4Y576hpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@endtimeslife @Israel את חושבת שאוכל להשיג הלוואה מהסוכנות @3337771961 @316hotel @TotoTooTheatre1 @ison… https://t.co/GJw1OyTJJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyry5 To paraphrase Groucho, I’d never belong to a club that would have me as a member!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoyPutins said the twitter account with 6 followers.   "Lol"   keep trying.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreeVandy @Lrihendry Too bad they don’t have a battle over ideas to continue making America great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who act different around a certain group of people are the worst kind of people .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @230FifthRooftop Lounge in New York, NY https://t.co/ZAaxKglc4C https://t.co/d3rubmSkLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: Today has went from me wanting a beer in the morning to now a liquor drink. What a day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oracion_milagro AMEN🙏❤ GRACIAS #SANTISIMOS #DIOS #PADRE #JESUS CHRIST🙏❤🙏❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when you think you’ve got a fool-proof way to estimate the missing counterfactual 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Jim's Steaks - @jimssouthstreet in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/eikOjeAZWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HurricaneDebs @smillerdegnan @HeraldSports @GatorsBB @CanesBaseball I prefer calling them the slimly reptiles. It’… https://t.co/OivGue8IOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @dr_cbetters to post covers of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews. I'll challenge… https://t.co/oDhc8E8xwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hudsonwisler @leahdb98 I can’t wait for you to get jury duty next month after this tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Following Duck Tales was A Goofy Movie... #agoofymovie #goofymovie #gooftroop #disneyafternoon #fireworks… https://t.co/pdk2mbNfIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I downloaded Wish thinking it would be fun... I already hate the notifications.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is no one talking about@how different Viggo Mortensen’s career is these days from 20 years ago?? Whoa. Talk about c… https://t.co/ldVjCbmdNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave How can anyone listen to a word this fricking kook have to say???? That just amazes me https://t.co/SbTyHhe2aZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice finish by Minneapolis own, Jamal James with the TKO after the 6th round at the Armory.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday February 28 - Balance of Power:     "Sometimes you have to walk"    Via @bpolitics @RosMathieson       https://t.co/i5iTu4b4Zx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo John, Crooked Donald Trump lies more than you do and that’s a hell of a lot of lying.   I’m waiting f… https://t.co/hx9CoSsWit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok... I’m no vegan or vegetarian but I’m definitely back on my plant-based meals! #eatingmorehealthy #plantbased… https://t.co/JHar9v5Jrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son in his 19th year now grown a lot😀 ONE PROUD DAD https://t.co/cwtdgiN4gH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen’s opening statement is the best reason to be up after midnight in at least a decade]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of Luck to the Shamrocks of @dcchockey as they play tonight for the STATE CHAMPIONSHIP!  #winforadayoff #letsgo https://t.co/coxcF5Z49z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t help myself. As soon as i get to know someone, i have to introduce them to someone they ought to/need to kn… https://t.co/FhNv2u0jut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine sending your son to college and you decide to pull up to watch him play and the team got him on a dog leash… https://t.co/sOeFZaTST5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Israelkicksass 4/5 s of all weapons, used on Israel 🇮🇱 will boomerang. The good book says. so they will just blow them selves out. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMSOSMaggie Do you think the governor would be interested in removing Columbus Day as a holiday and replacing it w… https://t.co/1KpYqjO5YS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VAGirlsmom @Seahawksgal81 @dana_lacie @ilovebakedgoods @angcould @we_r_Psymese Words through the grapevine was that she a bitch to everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[City Government has decided to open the distribution center tomorrow morning (03/02) from 9am-12pm in order to acco… https://t.co/JWdF39iLul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Azalialexi @Sassy_Linn Plus. Don’t focus on the past ain’t shit for you back there. You want a better future focus… https://t.co/GpnQ7S24Ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnHypeTrain @SageMeleney But the real question is, how smart do those 10 followers think you are? If you’re lucky,… https://t.co/lJciP71Yot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teamtrace So the gun control laws failed... and it was in a gun free zone that had a bad guy w a gun. A well armed… https://t.co/PzOfAW7YPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ant entered the weekend No. 3️⃣ in the SEC in on-base percentage for the season.   He’s one of three Rebs with an O… https://t.co/LDVrbhy4jt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mynamejong @overallgoodude @The_Raheel Better hope @DELv2 doesn’t see this tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's as though George Wallace has returned to Alabama on Trump's back. #RepublicanBigots https://t.co/BT6IMqx784]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok! Getting back into my groove!!!  Had to stop early today because I almost hurt myself... lol. 3 weeks off and di… https://t.co/N9cEcGqhGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@litseyco85 @wlemon13 @SaraFouche This is obviously a Satan worshippers home lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was 3, I got in trouble for selling stapled together pieces of construction paper as “books” during my cousi… https://t.co/2fqd8wkGxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the NC Ed Summit to see if there is anything I can learn to help teachers and students alike.  Besides donating… https://t.co/fEHpr05K9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little more of the World War prototype setting before channel 2 of the Slapback Delay. It’s hard to tell in the v… https://t.co/gH807688cO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolinevsequin Dugin is insidious, with defective reasoning and relying on the passion of his political viewpoint.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Protestas y toda la información sobre la visita de Donald Trump a FIU en @aurelio02 #Miami #fiu #donaldtrump… https://t.co/dIChJxy8RX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Walt Disney World Dolphin Hotel - @swandolphin in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/tPaeMepWBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Federico a las 7: Nieto revela que Rajoy ofreció un referéndum callejero https://t.co/jX2oj4kTML vía @esradio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcsandiego Do you guys really have nothing else to write about?   Tomorrow's headline: Trump took a shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskTrillAC Just make sure that very same exact energy is reciprocated equally when I say, “Nah sis, I can’t chill… https://t.co/9fETo2cPpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I say callie instead of babe or baby she goes “that’s not my name” and it’s so funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @RepLucyMcBath 2,000 people a year are killed by illegals.   Maybe a background check?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics @monikapphd That was the best segment I have ever seen on FOX , of course it’s only the second one… https://t.co/brPkrn1lWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrakashAmritraj @TennisChannel @AtpThirst...tennis channel is out here setting traps! Lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Hey Onion Field, the death penalty is something we should outlaw in this country.   There is no “Oo… https://t.co/Sy6FfXaIee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonaldKlain @Lawrence @washingtonpost @PostOpinions Most young social democrats for Bernie think that what he prop… https://t.co/rE4tJw1R1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Telling your mom how you feel about your other is the best feeling in the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great analysis by @Samwilliamsnrdc on fixed electricity fees across the country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LessisMORgan The whole “government after me” feeling wasn’t funky tho. Dead ass outside of the imaginary best frie… https://t.co/hJP9lzmq2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimMill784 Vote the Ass holes out! They are not standing for America!! Illegals that's all!! That's why they're go… https://t.co/rxH6CUZzNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CREWcrew If this was a hotel owned by Obama, FoxNews would have had a heart attack. Why is it that this ConMan con… https://t.co/n7urccgCfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinBinVegas @ted_newhard Would like to see us do something even if small to shake things up a bit but really only… https://t.co/xhjFUMhhUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jorge is fine too, it's on my birth certificate but not many in public call me that. It's been 'George' since befor… https://t.co/K3R2i5UZ18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @ClemsonLacrosse  for moving up in the rankings this week after going 3-0 to start the season including… https://t.co/L3Jfj3jDBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it me or are people on Twitter more even keeled about things that some on Facebook?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BUSSta_Move Like I said it would “catch up” and the chances are small lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gryselr @liderunox @El_Buen_Miguel @jguaido ¿Me fui? No sabía. Bueno, hagan de cuenta que regresé.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Everton and #Liverpool is what Man U-Liverpool should’ve been last week. #EVELIV #MerseysideDerby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laylalove_xxx U have such a hot sexy sweet yummy pink slutty pussy so hot baby very hot😍💋👅🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pistons are playing with some heart and look like a semi competent team and the Lions have money to blow and free a… https://t.co/RtXelpubnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nooo. BQ = Band Queer. CT = Corps Terd. Hole = a fish cadets room. Don’t hide the truth of what we do! The corps is… https://t.co/TbKZ0teHX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JarrettHill The trailers were a terrible representation of the film, IMO. I had similar thoughts before seeing it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Training Chest at Time For Change Performance.. 5yrs off and only 8wks back with 30wks to go before #tampa weighing… https://t.co/5jA5WdeC7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[gotta love the hilarity #funniness #lol #grin #funny https://t.co/Mrz7BIpj5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Madame Tussauds Las Vegas https://t.co/50Qq8Z22pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aw, bummer. Just saw that Jan-Michael Vincent died... always loved Airwolf https://t.co/jdBwVBZOJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kareem Abdul-Jabbar auctioned his NBA rings for charity.  The money will go to a downtrodden group close to his hea… https://t.co/n9hdLtJfRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeGarafolo @zachkruse2 @gimmedajuice24 bless you.. here is your Kleenex... don’t be so sure...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPFrance You are absolutely correct Doc, they sang their hearts out!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenWo4LiFe High class. Kraken (or Captain Morgan Black Spice) and Mtn Dew. That's my go to mixer if/when available.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreppyProf Some of us still do! I’ve been trying to spread the word, but not everyone wants to listen. https://t.co/H0VXwryx00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetUpESPN love the show, but need some work on that green screen. One guy looked like he was glowing and I could s… https://t.co/WJ7XUEl6AR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s get this day started!!  Big things are happening ⁦@firstcleveland⁩.  Go God!! https://t.co/fklIMyHAUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always remember to practice Shaun’s 1st rule of flying. #FindCoffee @starbucks https://t.co/kHJlKex26U]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did they resign at 0:00 time? I'm confused 🤣🤣 https://t.co/9e2G2jMEA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBOKSR_MAGA @rosedixontx What is that? you pay staffers who spent $200,000 to go to law school 15 an hour- what a sport.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day at First United Methodist packing lunches for PADS yesterday! Thank you to Mrs. Patterson for organizing… https://t.co/C9jvwY6DD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously, the only real national emergency is me trying to find a bathroom after having enchiladas. #🚽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me faltaron dos de las más frecuentes.. "Donde estabas cuando" y "Es culpa de la corrupción que había"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I won't be able to think of a word for a while, like 5 mins to 5 hours, and then it will pop in my head l… https://t.co/H6JPrWemzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope everyone enjoys #DMC5. My plate is absolutely full of games. I'm going to have to wait for a sale on this one.… https://t.co/4XxBOk67O0]]></document></documents></author>