<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@iamQ123 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump You're just responding to a con who is paid to comment on every single one… https://t.co/7ivCVfg9lw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThousandBelow Just do a Fast and Furious movie cover and photoshop yourselves in it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialRezz got a lot going on - is it possible to resell my rezzrocks tickets?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stupid cat. How do I sleep without headphones? I only set them down for a second.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simpson was great. But he is offensively challenged. Great improvement this year for X. Simpson is great for Michig… https://t.co/uWjEu8Kif3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hunkereddown. Three hours of emails  with #musicsupervisors at @dennysdiner at 10:30 on a Sunday night. @ Santa An… https://t.co/E59bSMaCG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hokieprorichie @tnsportslive @BHCSports @WCYB_Heather @WCYB_CaseyGoetz @kevmays Pack has really played impressive… https://t.co/njUrkfiKsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys, come get this cash gift! The sooner you go for it, the more the money! https://t.co/VatxdIGn1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Habsterix @BWildeGlobal He got Byron because Kassian broke a foot 24 hours prior, and nobody else in the league ha… https://t.co/TVTB1YG2NE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoneyBeeLvr Everything I've read has *extremely little* to do with your native/indigenous peoples concerns and muc… https://t.co/WJUTd3A8rb]]></document><document><![CDATA[All AB had to do was go to the Steelers after the season and privately ask for a trade, would’ve got atleast one of… https://t.co/hUU6jmHmeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serious question: does a dog shoots man incident qualify as a man bites dog story? #dogs @simonasiri]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabyShaq52 Like homies like @swavvywoodstock @Justin_Cabrera2 @draper_23]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great!  John Mulaney is one of my favorites!  Bodega Bathroom - SNL https://t.co/CvOf30YHvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emotional Intelligence is an important factor in leadership success.  Join us on May 20-21 for an Emotional Intelli… https://t.co/iVvTUsns3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have never been so depressed before in my life . i am so fucking worried about myself tbh but at the same time i… https://t.co/7PE5QwclyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hxncho_ @WORLDSTAR I knew that would be the first answer before checking. Not because it’s correct, but because th… https://t.co/36oNhiH5uf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyJJ10Million @ryanwhitney6 @BizNasty2point0 Don’t throw things at people, pro athletes or otherwise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redtache @MooseNendick @nacnudeel @gene70 @realDonaldTrump Do you have evidence to back your statement up??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard to fi d a barber that actually listens and follows instructions #leaveaninchontop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TEdge73 thanks for the follow.  Really appreciate the you and the other coaches and players being so nice to Wyatt… https://t.co/B6upY4MT8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top flight times with some top flight guys #GHill @ Slippery Rock, Pennsylvania https://t.co/WWg8Qt1ffo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just cleaned my bathroom, and organized my whole desk. I think I’m pregnant. 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofiasivan I just got my calendar and I couldn’t be more excited!! Thank you as always, Sofia! https://t.co/I2nFI2vkzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Super Yooper Computer Solutions https://t.co/66w3Z6AQnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roldanj1264 @lopezobrador_ hipocresía traición y simulación, fuera prian todos contra la corrupción]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working relentlessly  on multiple projects. This one made me smile a bit because it looks way better than it should… https://t.co/dGureo0rhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @Borrego_Ricky are at the bar and the dude next to us is the “I see dead people” kid from sixth sense 👻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrkambN @lillyt72 Ahh.. yes, it's so simple that anyone and everyone can and does do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tinojaramillo No podrían haber otras explicaciones? Esto simplemente son dos curvas que divergen. Complicado asignar relacion causal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mats are down and we’re less than 2 hours away from the @IHSAA State Wrestling Finals. 12 Siouxlanders, 9 in Cl… https://t.co/VfFS8DXQJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @realDonaldTrump Your pictures don't tell the whole story.  Lol  Love it when Liberals put their ignorance on display.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A gift that could be particularly fitting at some point today... #Sens #TradeDeadline https://t.co/hpbxbZndXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LomaahhMore @adamcbest @CarlyPildis Overall it is not great, but Omar Jamal is probably best known Somali person i… https://t.co/C8MiChbwzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Can you hear me now?” William Gracely “W.G.” Brorein made the first  transatlantic #telephone call from #Tampa to… https://t.co/NE2Ve3Ir9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guy sitting next to me on the plane is making all@his calls on speakerphone. We don’t want to hear it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was driving from Ft. Benning, GA to Chattanooga when my friend put this album on in the car. I was blown away and… https://t.co/1RURl2mtj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can't get a bachelor's at a CC though, and transferring can have many complications]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol, Colby never talks shit until people are in between them, but more importantly, Ali is a proper fucking cunt. D… https://t.co/6mXvVewvrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to #7 @NevadaHoops on their 33-pt road win over Wyoming, notching their 19th double-digit win this season!… https://t.co/Gu00Gwqkyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF YOU HAVE NEVER BEEN THERE rusty_gate_succulents IS OPEN TODAY 10-4pm..  LOTS OF COOL VINTAGE GARDEN ART,… https://t.co/F4X6bBWhKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faith is fine and all but fucking see a doctor if you have HIV or Cancer or lupus, don’t be a fuckin idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ModelJusticeLee #theVenutiTHEOREM  This post  written pre President Trump. Convinced that Obama would never step d… https://t.co/tPimwrlDA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Observer2541 @Atheist_Dragon @Mel_the_geek @Elinor27652146 @ITDave2 @deelane @YeshuaLover1970 @DB_Grimwalker… https://t.co/UOXWCa3QMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Barista -… https://t.co/uuCZBtcRRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[As expected, tonight's lines and pairs vs. CBJ:  https://t.co/FfB3F3Qtpv #dkps #penguins]]></document><document><![CDATA[This wind tonight is ridiculous.  And of course everything iced over and froze the fuck back up.  This constant dre… https://t.co/0vDtdNW5QK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedZone921 congratulations on your addition to simulcast on KARN @SportsAnimal920 another Razorback sports heritag… https://t.co/KIIKW5tsJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[can you send the files at the “right size” has to be one of the most frustrating requests I’ve had from a printer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warriormama1019 Just maga doesnt watch media.  Kings can't rule unquestioned with it around. https://t.co/e4iPnfblGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthonyspiteri You should have known better given the time of year. Time to go shopping. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Michael Cohen made for great TV. But did he make a difference? - San Francisco Chronicle: Michael… https://t.co/LXGStvKiQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to all the girls who don’t need to exploit their body to feel empowered and beautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hgtv Windy City Rehab has to be one of your lowest rated shows right? The girl sounds like she’s alway whining and… https://t.co/Bm6tTdPlHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[No score after one between the @StLouisBlues and the @DallasStars. They did no harm in the first 20 minutes. We'll… https://t.co/E6lWj3EsXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t think that Representative Cummings is biased against all things conservative, do you?  I’m shocked, absol… https://t.co/oog99Y2KAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been on hold for 1.5 hours with @GustoHQ.   I just have a fairly simple question about my insurance plan. https://t.co/JU8J9KIEc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyKimmelLive just wanted you to know that I've never done black face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[6/ time when we acted rashly and emotionally only to wonder, “what was I thinking?” And the answer is: You weren’t;… https://t.co/ivsKdcy2Yx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leslieberland @tpatt220 @NolaBeth Happy Twitterversary and first day of kindergarten!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Former owner??? This has Nothing to do with trump ......The mighty CNN has fallen so far that they are no long… https://t.co/qknnOuqm7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganA_mma  hi megan anderson mma fighter and hello my love i like megan anderson mma fighting pro i like you are… https://t.co/AfiJ7iplJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking forward to Donation #108 March 30 8:00am @LifelineGuelph according to the GiveBlood app: keep track of… https://t.co/IWfMuBRc44]]></document><document><![CDATA[@backpakngram @BreitbartNews @joelpollak Stop with the modern day lynching crap. Please . This guy played you and y… https://t.co/cJYtJE70AH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByScottCullen @RichZagon1 @mcnuggetswhat @islandermania I did, none make sense , hence the reason for more questions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Texas19771 @MashCurphy @mbishop423 @SEC I think any informed fan is well aware of that. It’s hard to escape when t… https://t.co/rqM5bYQ4jc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those #bucketlist items may be closer than you think. Want to get started on them now? Do it!… https://t.co/dJ7zfFoJjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeharoldoswald @BillOReilly Sorry.  My daughter as well. That's 2.  Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today marks one year with @UberStrategist! I've learned a lot, failed a lot, and have grown immensely as a person and professional. Woo! 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyyGabriella So glad I don't need to deal with that BS anymore🙈.🖕🏻the @LIRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SBProductions7 @newcountrysbest @inexrecords @BigIndieGiant @theBobavich @RecordsElmo @2743EntInc @fscradio… https://t.co/x6IuYqJMpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couple of cool action shots of @RileyBost in the slide show.   For those who would like to keep up with Riley and t… https://t.co/dMNI7kZZ0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnada_89 @alishajane777 @AOC @KamalaHarris @MichaelAvenatti @CNN @JussieSmollett @SpeakerPelosi @shaunking… https://t.co/O9rNSRMO3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShamrockTourny Looking forward to attending for our fourth year in a row. Many more to come #fourboys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jstrauss @ericnakagawa If there were an app to provide mental support while doing home renovations I would be a paying member]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmTheWardog #LGM &amp; good luck this season, buddy!! If you haven’t got my book, I’ll get it to you  https://t.co/ZtA0Gy70MZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The USS Constellation in Baltimore Maryland. uss_constellation_   @PrideofBalt maryland.state #maryland… https://t.co/39S3mR3K1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The person who invented the word booby trap knew that he was way over his head #nostredamus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great visit to Newton HS. @CoachSkelton06 does a great job with those guys each cycle. Spent time with Nyland Green… https://t.co/olcPg7vBkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kanye has been an average artist since 2012 and hasn’t put out any good music (except last year) for a while.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to lay down just now bujy cozy I kneed my phone it flipped 20 feet in the air and busted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @SashaBanksWWE @itsBayleyWWE @ScottDawsonWWE @DashWilderWWE Wow, that’s a great video. #WWEJonesboro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao I loved this video @JeffreeStar @shanedawson https://t.co/fjvhqlV8Sv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BWOODKNOWS B #1OF1 @liljon 📈 ♻️ #vintagemashups ✂️ #sustainable couture #zope #newwave #madeinnyc with ♥️ #ATL… https://t.co/f9sWjl6iLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my president idgaf about what y’all say... I’m volunteering #DeadAss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rationalexpec @_BarbaraBB_ Resultado empírico -&gt; resultado teórico. Gostei.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bacon wrapped scallops! @ Ryan's Restaurant STEAKS-CHOPS &amp; SEAFOOD https://t.co/MV03OSSWsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonnyWilkinson Hi Jonny! Please may you retweet our event in support of @RestartRugby aiding mental health for rug… https://t.co/SSXY1SD1OD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Philly is the only city that seems confused at the town being one big garbage pile, yet they make homeowners sponso… https://t.co/cgPoDdjkYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remembering Dale Earnhardt Sr 18 years later at Daytona International Speedway https://t.co/tu3C0YIS2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Real_EllieBrown @CoreysDigs much more, but all RED HERRINGS related to DEEPSTATE corruption. God bless… https://t.co/PPNrnfevve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JedidiahBoone @peterjgowan @johnsonjakep He’s a liar. Plain and simple. That was just one incidence of his racism… https://t.co/sZ7oAATFX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetterGop @BusterTiberiusB @AlanDersh @SethAbramson You are part of the problem and not part of the solution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can only hope @Nicoxw1 😀😀👍 Impeach tRump. #IMPEACHTheMF   #IndictTheMF  👍👍👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billikenhawk There's a lot of truth in it but what Duke did surprised me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell yeah Kyle. I did free assessments for a lot of local high schools this season. Used Blast for bat data. I foun… https://t.co/R7jlYJx6lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cover is one that certainly got my attention. I can’t help but feel conflicted about it. As a Mustang who supp… https://t.co/C4ZlGj50Bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lafont is a great shot stopper, but has a lot of room for improvement in all other aspects of his games as a keeper… https://t.co/3NI18FZxFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylawyoung @steakfromwv @TribecaRocky @roya_zaree @MaryBocchino @Grandpa_Pat I feel like this could be something… https://t.co/0YCgP4HZ2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raider_rob24 @mr0pini0n Sorry Roberto, but since my team has traded for Keenum, I'm going to stay hidden. I like t… https://t.co/pUIDB36RXu]]></document></documents></author>