<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Took a couple of trips to Holy land today, God is good, anytime you feel the closeness of Christ, it’s such a bless… https://t.co/dKVjbCp0Jt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missouri_in Better than that, lay naked in a tanning bed.... remember to cover up the love machine 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[One to go when they get to the line. Christopher Bell showing as the leader #NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Sales Associate" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about these types of opportuni… https://t.co/vE5NcKESgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1b ended with me very short but tripled up to 108000 and qualified for day 2 Sunday Million Guarantee just befo… https://t.co/g6V5fKAbAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet16 2019 #basketball #hsbasketball #slamdunk #billyhicks #bteam #redheat #schs @ Georgetown, Kentucky https://t.co/iBf2sgwhre]]></document><document><![CDATA[ROUGH OUTLINE: Tour Runs 1-3 from 7:45 to 11:00 - Lunch and drive to MPG wheather pending. Work 12:00 - 3:30ish. Ba… https://t.co/A1TVcqwLy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinMeade @MorningExp @Knowlesitall @Christi_Paul @LindaWSB. I would like to know your answer to tge question Nic… https://t.co/SdjSTQmdjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bot 6th: #Sooners 9, Columbia 0  Tyler Hardman keeps it going with a single to knock in Zaragoza from 2nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @ItsRamiMalek on your Oscar! I among so many others have followed your amazing from the beginning.… https://t.co/vP8TkjEizZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing will be the same for me anymore. I’m changing who I am. It’s not gonna happen again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmadison1787 @renato_mariotti When the Trumps face prison they will rollover and he will say I don’t know them. Pl… https://t.co/achnwkrzbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[gcu_swimming doing great today! @ University of Houston https://t.co/KnwDUdVyxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is true to an extent, but only highlights the need to buy a home well within your budget, and that budget shou… https://t.co/PjrkrrKkdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soccersam717 Sorry if it was too far. I'm genuinely sorry for your loss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #TradeDeadlineDay in the #NHL No matter what happens today, this is when the fun stuff starts! #nhlplayoffs ar… https://t.co/qSlK11q89s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lately, we’ve all done something we’re not proud of. I’m sure nobody would want to be identified for their mistakes… https://t.co/fs3WqESmnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeZimmersEars @Nate13Burleson I thought so but figured I would send tweet as I walked out the door to take son to school lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If #LittleDonald can get upset so easily about @nbcsnl making fun of him then he might want to cho… https://t.co/gzAmQrcIT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Ja Morant for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/8e8lVw7rrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Potsy_70 @fnveenie @GrittyNHL @ChanceNHL @NordyWild @HowlerCoyote @Gnash00 @StingerCBJ Unlike our power play that needs a nurse]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to both graduates &amp; local Fire Chiefs that continue to support Call-Firefighters.  @MCVFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oliverdarcy @mikiebarb There's been *actual* violence perpetrated against Trump supporters as a result of insane r… https://t.co/oRyOP6Ru6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir where should I go to find help getting my bag when in SAN??? Flight has now been taken off carasouel. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Warren started the RnR Washington DC 5K! https://t.co/kFxRAxPvgk #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jake Allen seems to always give up late goals in periods!!!!!!! He think he losses focus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though im bedridden and sick, the newest discography review just went live! Let’s talk about Bloc Party https://t.co/IZbqnAhdow]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the attributes of God is His Faithfulness!  God is Faithful! Thus we find the Apostle Paul declaring in Phil… https://t.co/0kOnqU8KAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leah95kkfan Yes !I like kyle Busch! But like when mark Martin won all those  lower level races ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreacherLawson if it’s any consolation... you won a spot in the finals. Darcy was given a spot. Therefore I think… https://t.co/O2WFgA3bgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nonna6553 @nypost Agree. She is the last thing we need right now. More than ever we need people to get in the  Pelosi boat and ROW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why would we want a brutal regime to become a world power? Read about Neville Chamberlain and how… https://t.co/59PChJKtj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbdulMahmud01 It won't get to that level. We are LAYING HIM OFF finally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #BuildTheWall #MAGA #JobsNotMobs https://t.co/apZoPFANSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @POTUS You look either sleepy or worried. Too much executive time!  #PornStarPayment]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEY EVERYONE IM DOING A CASH APP GIVE AWAY !!! IM PICKING 5 LUCKY PEOPLE OF APPRECIATION THAT HIT THE LINK IN MY BI… https://t.co/i13g4BnI6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lumberist @cathmckenna Good post Chris and very current this constant guilt trip your promoting must stop For one… https://t.co/i3ycGdoTBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you look at your screen instead of your camera when taking selfies and it really shows...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If you got a dog you could use some of your “Executive Time” to nurture and care for it. Maybe Bar… https://t.co/Osre04KAeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive seen 2 flames fans at my work now in 2 months (i get them like once a year). MORE FANS IN TORONTO!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@margaretcox2299 @basedinfidel8 @fellspeaks @AlexWY18 @Chriskl70208387 @JayCory7 @SmackYeti @Americanthatguy… https://t.co/VB2xnocH2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrcBarbies @samriegel @TessFowler @bullyart07 @matthewmercer I missed it in the episode.   Does anyone have a timestamp?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most of these basketball players are as soft as ten ply TP... I still love the game. Just grow a pair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still stunned on the daily there aren’t 20 #GOP #Senators who care about the #USA. More shocked than anything T… https://t.co/Iu9haBa4ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hes baaack! #karcenowinchipsallthetimeb @ Chicago metropolitan area https://t.co/XZzphh5vKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kay got her official Stephen Oran Tee!! Special pricing ends TODAY so get your's NOW!! https://t.co/sQVMRcSCKb… https://t.co/IdPqFHm04n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegymterdotnet The wolf turn that she was having problems with in podium training]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I get an "AMEN"!👏🏿👏🏿💪🏿👌🏿💯🎯 #FoodForThought #OneToGrowOn #Inspirational #Motivational #Positive #Powerful… https://t.co/h3k0n2gf7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't let your small business fall behind in 2019❗ #ChooseSuccess 📈  https://t.co/rW1hoSVKRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tjonesonthenba Don’t understand why we keep having this conversation. We actually have a bona fide go-to guy on ou… https://t.co/20phUt2gRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me waiting for everyone who was enraged over all the female leaked nudes to have the same outrage over Matt Riddle https://t.co/nSWpMGGasN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachLRJ @Exisco @littlejenna37 Yeah. That fight was awful. Gotta make a beer run in the hopes I get drunk enough to forget it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilSzostak @KristinBaver Question. Where are the dice? On Ach-To? The ones on Crait were fake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get the call from your job to stay home https://t.co/a1gqwUr5rQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@czabe A list of Kraft food slogans that now double as entendres... "Unleash the cheese" "A little taste of Heaven"… https://t.co/BNn167DnN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The absolute best part of this video is that it gave me my new favorite meme format. https://t.co/px28mEPxHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe conception's ironic to reflection's definitive, true extent. https://t.co/JC8VyCInzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AltcoinSara I think we just sit back and let it happen. Or suggest everyone read The Creature From Jekyl Island by G. Edward Griffin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFinnFTW @Phillies There’s always this as an option: https://t.co/I5CSrXdhIt Or this https://t.co/IzzJiR4ihz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Severe threat has shifted slightly north. I'll have all the details throughout Saturday. #cILwx https://t.co/q7DRfqAmYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Unfortunate photo of Jerry Nadler, beaten, basted and humiliated victim of Tom Steyer. Out of shape, dulle… https://t.co/dHh39mQOA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@princess_stef69 @SupremeBlizzard It's about the under lying hate for white men, we are not all bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr you think by going against tRump on a manufactured crisis will save you in 2020. You stuck out your t… https://t.co/omDQPJVd99]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hooptveast @MidMORoyalsFan You claimed he was on press row and I told you he wasn’t. How he got the stat sheet is irrelevant to that point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green Smokey eye for March ! Are you feeling lucky ?! #makeupartist #makeup #lashes #ardelllashes @ardellbeauty… https://t.co/BtqatKXXPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tvann2 @BettingFinesse Hey man as much as I have to hear 24/7 it’s well deserved lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[6-foot-9 forward commits to Colorado State. Previously was committed Nevada. Also had an offer from UNLV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muddy fun today! Hiking @MontgomeryParks Little Bennett Regional Park with a stop at the Wims Meadows #NegroLeague… https://t.co/CRe6ECtb4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily breakdown is   Total Kcals 1,950   Carbs 175G  Protein 160G  Fat 60G]]></document><document><![CDATA[From my newsletter today on Warren's proposal (which in the case of FB I support).  Breaking up FB is another way t… https://t.co/6H2DBR3fWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrissDeck1 @DiamondandSilk @realDonaldTrump @POTUS 133 and still climbing, but, hey, who's counting? While we're a… https://t.co/NoKWuW2FO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caleb’s bball game (@ McMurry University in Abilene, TX) https://t.co/FC0m3ZBVYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy we got to watch @JProcyshen17 catch 4 innings of intersquad baseball today for the Dodgers. Great to see a… https://t.co/rZctwrkR6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I am not married. Of course your not. Little boys that follow dictatorship are.always looking for daddy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unFOCUSedST @Schug_Keith Your opinion no longer matters on this subject]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @TyJohnsonNews I always hated bananas too. They made me gag. Come to find out I’m allergic to them. They’re a death fruit 💀🍌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GesuMontolivo @GraficoTigres @rickcenturion @TigresOficial Aqui lo metemos en cintura @TigresOficial]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuinnyPig @pfredphotos Sometimes the minority is on the right side of history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in Unexpectedly Positive Stories Involving Kanye West: https://t.co/B7gN4xg8mt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDTNKelleyKing @WDTN This story breaks my heart. May she be with the Angels in Heaven.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the more reason to look forward to the future @BA_WMN mentoring groups!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just keeping it gangster. 2 and 3 already cooler than me. #gangsterbabies https://t.co/30p9TZLyyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itscharmingshan One time I got my period in the middle of a 6 hour car ride and my boyfriend asked me if I could j… https://t.co/YASJRThtcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lewis saves three separate set points but Loyola ultimately prevails on a flukey play that technically will go down… https://t.co/RJpezRiPSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes it's just a matter of showing up. #oldguyrunning #slipperyslope5k https://t.co/sfT1QtWJqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[*listens to sad music to stop myself from being in a panicked state of mind.*             *becomes sad.*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder @1976penguinfan That’s why they want that traitor Isis member back in the states. I have a picture for… https://t.co/YiEgfgWmHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This place can be loud is what the FSN crew is telling us on TV.  Sure, yea...remember what it was like back in the… https://t.co/gTZ29TgOBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horne_wyatt @KeenReason @scrowder Fun stuff man I'm HVAC technician, I was taught be an electronic engineer lol  w… https://t.co/2O3J1DPGFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilesFilbert @GashouseILM @BradGDickey @addicted2helmet Even though I'm an NFL guy, I've *always* loved the CFL!… https://t.co/2DvAp5YY0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSawyerH @SebGorka @RealSaavedra @AOC She's behaving like her seniors. https://t.co/z2LFgHkexC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving others means you strive to stimulate their interest in spiritual growth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stevenbarrett41 @muscleworshipuk @gavinperry60 @HotUKBoys @Eight8ofclubs @MaleBumBeauty @RTVLads @new_gaywanking… https://t.co/nOrnqXO0j3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always look beyond the horizon and focus on what you want...   #mondaymotivation @ Dania Beach, Florida https://t.co/wKwNxmsXt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Yes, I do still have the clock radio I got when I was 10. What’s your problem)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why, though...?  There isn’t enough land on Ocean Blvd to build a bloody baseball stadium.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people who don’t have jobs go to the casino? They always tell me they lost all their money 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPeregoyIII Don’t hate on Eli! Still@so bitter! Maybe someday your boy Phil will get two rings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rule #1 always takes the fun out of a “PAW”dy! #SundayFunday #followifyafeelme https://t.co/fYNZl3C1iU]]></document><document><![CDATA[ARE YOU KIDDING ME WARD PROWSE!? Unreal stuff going on at old trafford. Turn it on if you like exciting competitive football]]></document></documents></author>