<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#AloneTogether in Salt Lake City, UT!! 😱 Sold out mga showtime! https://t.co/0wEOPsuT2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnwarLodhi If this is how things are why not disband NAB altogether. It has become a joke. How can PTI carry out i… https://t.co/EY0VNbFEjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 26th birthday is approaching this week and I don’t feel like myself. I don’t even know why.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caseyjarman Yeah def a wierd trip... but homegirl got drunk girl revenge and puked all over that fool. So kinda ba… https://t.co/uk3QMEchxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drakenstein75 He's great I just wish he would help develop the younger QB's because he's gonna be gone soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Isabel of France, Roman Catholic Virgin and Nun. Sister of St. Louis and daughter of King Louis VIII of France… https://t.co/OYj2OOqKnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisonegirlamy From.a guy in my kitchen.. he is from Mexico and I am a white American Male. He looked at me after… https://t.co/E3gZAamBEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starrbryte67631 Sounds good to me. 😳😂 Good morning 💫 ☕️☕️ https://t.co/FmyLwbnhuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Digging into the archives, featuring these two kick-ass ladies, @cassiemaries and mightaswhale _________… https://t.co/qx2DZmAipE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinsonjoel124 @NRA @RepDougCollins You obviously never attended college did you. Just Klan classes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aviones militares de EEUU dejan toneladas de ayuda para Venezuela en Cúcuta   https://t.co/rdIIQjmAcy vía… https://t.co/BdDBmhe4wQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome Daylight Saving Ride! Trails were in incredible shape! So nice to get out after work and see the sun ☀️ @ H… https://t.co/hxRoBPVGDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @HawkofNewYork @prageru Voter ID can suppress some votes on the margin, people who don't have their i… https://t.co/qZTSKsZ7RW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ameliaboone check out your local Grocery Outlet for these gems! If they don’t have any you could run-swim-bike....… https://t.co/bcxW1i54PP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This creates a very valid question.  Duke pays for Zion’s $8 million insurance policy.  That is a benefit that no o… https://t.co/1TqTwZf2QQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IOnlySayFacts Just spent 10 minutes reading EaglesTwitter and I feel like I lost more brain cells than reading Ars… https://t.co/RWU0hLP4Rr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alita Battle Angel (@ AMC South Barrington 24 - @amctheatres in South Barrington, IL) https://t.co/WpGtKEiAsg https://t.co/UY5UdgLBJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being happy is very important, I agree with you. But some “American babes” are trying too hard to be American. It’s… https://t.co/H0dOEdTmO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[LC’s March madness can drive us on and donations are flowing in! Don’t forget to donate each Friday in March! @ Low… https://t.co/sZmsSGMVoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raganwald Brian Wilson used voices as instruments, and conducted the band like a symfony. So good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hayfrann @OaklandMBB Y’all are for sure making some noise next season. What a game—it literally could have gone ei… https://t.co/G0R9HmuwHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity I’d vote for Trump for the next 15 to 20 years instead of any dinner any any Democrat and that’s a fac… https://t.co/ligPglUlYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taken at 40,000 ft, 240miles off the east coast. Beautiful sun rise welcoming me back home to the States! @ John F.… https://t.co/vCjzRTjVGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’d think as healthy as I am I wouldn’t get sick as often as I do🙄 this time of year killlllls me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always liked: “Wise people have strong opinions, weakly held.”    If your goal is the best solution, it’s OK t… https://t.co/4Yid8Xd9pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hokiehack @NotRyanAdams We’re gonna need a full tv TO here @Chad_Parries]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lacoutita @OttleyJam @chrisdorsey @washingtonpost You should atleast try and read the headline.....sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what drives me? She restaurants give me more ketchup than mustard...🙄thas discrimination🙅🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the quality of our work which will please God and not the quantity. #MondayMotivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m putting an alum bout before the end of year. Hopefully it does well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este año serán 464 mdp el subsidio del @GobiernoMX a #Sonora para la tarifa eléctrica de verano, informó la Goberna… https://t.co/y0oCB3LzhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you https://t.co/q49A1ccFk4 for having us!!! @ Wisdome Immersive Art Park https://t.co/nrYaFzx5BS]]></document><document><![CDATA[20 AA wrestlers have wrestled all the way back from a first-round loss to clinch a medal. Hats off to them for winn… https://t.co/Uy3PjhsfFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone else noticed their iPhone apps being moved into different places? I’ve noticed it every morning for the past week...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Kentwood ! been kickin it since 6th grade ! Hope your day is great. @kenlee_mchugh https://t.co/hWfLWTBrMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that there was a group of computer scientists, faculty members and researchers, who asked Clinton to dispu… https://t.co/ReDmKV1v8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omarSG__ @dommyslaps @andr3s_m0 I swear I can see him wearing that same fit tmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattfunk985 @TReddy13 @Noahsyndergaard @sskbaseballusa Matthew, you can say all you want about League growth but j… https://t.co/PJurf0XlMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Leftists: To protect our sovereignty is unpatriotic it will cause fire and brimstone coming down from the… https://t.co/v12EPMIXo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1mDollarVegan You're welcome and thank you @1mDollarVegan for all the great work you're doing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomstakes And think it’s 3/30 not 3/10 which was reported first. Schefter/rappaport just posted that]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if Taylor gives out an award tonight and announces TS7?! I mine as well call in dead to work tomorrow. ☠️… https://t.co/wbQ0Xs9wRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#instagramer #influencer #funnymemes #havingfun #donttakeeverythingsoserious #lifeisgood #letsgo @ Los Angeles, Cal… https://t.co/UCtx6VRCWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh god I just found out one of my fb friends is an anti vaxxer time to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico If theyve carried out criminal acts they should be treated like any other criminals, why would you give them a pass?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only thing getting me through this week is knowing I get to see @lukecombs on Friday 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC understand that the middle class, Blue Collar employees work hard, work overtime, even second jobs. We built o… https://t.co/CWV3ql8nr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, they're the best batteries I've ever bought. https://t.co/ctkQ3w9LgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to know how I know Captain Marvel is going to be fine?  Wonder woman had similar issues before it came out.  H… https://t.co/UvG5U27hQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes , #LeavingNeverland showed the dark side of Michael Jackson.   In terms of his influence, Micheal was a si… https://t.co/5YaGsPMTYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We #booked‼️ 🤙🏾 #bossentertainment  #pressure #yrntakeoff #beachbash  #OrangeCrush2019 🍊BIGGEST BEACH DAY SAT APR 2… https://t.co/wLz4aqKP4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flyoverAmericn @ChrisRi80029765 @StormIsUponUs @JudicialWatch Kinda silly...poor photoshop skills...detachment fro… https://t.co/a8eU7auiB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when you thought things were better. @united strikes again. Sitting on tarmac in @GrandRapids_MI waiting for o… https://t.co/003bcvOF7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally saw Pikes place market, but wrong time of day. Everything's closed.  Pretty cool seeing the elevated Viaduc… https://t.co/Uo0WllBpBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day on the road, cruising along the San Andreas Fault Line. Also finishing the last clifbar. Well calculated a… https://t.co/AOhqRltYPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same recently happened to me! Got excited to do a full 5 page site for the business of somebody close to me for $24… https://t.co/CA4zaodrLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roldanj1264 @lopezobrador_ Creo que en estos cien días las pruebas de que va por buen camino son más que claras. E… https://t.co/fqmh2bcpAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO EL SOL SALDRÁ PARA TODOS, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/l6kFgZZF0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never sit with my back to the door.  I gotta stay ready if something pops off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WaPAH! So PITTED! 🥑🙃🤙🏽 . . . . . 📸 @renaelavonne #sopitted #avocadolife #plantbased #rooted #hyperactive #vibin… https://t.co/0yVN3ekPRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like how anti-lifers make pro-life people out to be people who hate babies and children after they’re born.   Whe… https://t.co/JgyMvEGRv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whydyouhave2BOO @DonCheadle So no protect white kids shirt i guess? #CovingtonBoys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Setting up my python development environment for code-based projects! Woo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are at LACOE’s GAIN office on Valley Blvd. in El Monte. Our Director Steve Yamarone sharing with staff our commi… https://t.co/c9iZcmqR66]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would rather date somebody that’s ugly that’s loyal and treats me right and make me laugh.  Then a cute, non loya… https://t.co/79daFjuShA]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELLO. HUMANS ARE MAMMALS. GUESS WHAT HAPPENS TO US IF WE DON'T STOP CLIMATE CHANGE.  https://t.co/LFTL01KcQM https://t.co/e1rctYfKCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom As much as I hate to admit it you’re right on this one Tom. I always believed Trumpism couldn’t take… https://t.co/QHWFz2U4IG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreatPlainsBC @Pastor_NPBC @JillJReeves Happy Anniversary from the Tyson’s &amp; WBC! A blessing to be with you all on this special day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking about the state of our #Oceans w/ @dvfernandez1 and @JadeFloydDC #marineconservation #Sustainability… https://t.co/e2fpxYySUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8lhUJJ9Np9  “Not Gon Cry” Official Music Video Mary J. Blige 22,656,185 Views on YouTube… https://t.co/Zrd8HjRYwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain I’m so proud of you and admire you. You are the balance at the table with a View! Thank You! I miss y… https://t.co/NjdXyL8jzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dontHARPonme 50 on money line didn’t hurt either.. King said I get a new stroller 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will be amazed how much stuff you can get done if you just turn off your electronics!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a great meeting tonight with members of the Boston Marine Industrial Park Business Association.  Informative… https://t.co/GqdJneY11J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bittersweet leaving Orlando this evening with a great Vacation coming to a close. I am ready to come back to realit… https://t.co/vogrMO0Glf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyPN @Nisleecita Las dos son dos venezolanas maravillosas y están en el mismo lado de la historia, el correcto.… https://t.co/VF8CAnjuJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 New podcast 🚨  Former @GopherMBB star @TMbakwe32 joined from Japan, where he's currently playing pro ball. A fun… https://t.co/ql7y8o40Mu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ITS_KAAAY13 I have one day off a week🙃 always have shit to do and you won’t watch Harry Potter with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfpelosi Pretty cool if you ask me. The witch is an enemy of real Americans. She is a traitor to this country of t… https://t.co/BiBMtwlAsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC The most important things we can do to address climate change are building nuclear reactors to replace coal an… https://t.co/5FtgGEgbVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben is a strong proponent of a small central government unless the government wants to ban porn or blow up Arab chi… https://t.co/Ka0YNsdUFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tatergraham @TrentWagstaff5 @tyler_bouget12 @tannerd6 @_drakef @trevor_dosch @caleb_nornor @Shannon_C05 To the ign… https://t.co/X2CxwWfKQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear men read this thread DO NOT COMMENT it is a simple yet educational thread on women and how to pay attention. T… https://t.co/tcME8F0ngh]]></document><document><![CDATA[3:30pm. Multiple miles walked. Hundreds of pics taken. Just realized I haven’t eaten or drank anything today yet.   Oh NYC 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhldeS @mjaeger6 Linn uses the same equipment we do just like they used the same design we came up with 16 years a… https://t.co/A0Vnxgf9YL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_AWalkingBucket Pretty sure he quoted me anyway, I wasn’t lying 😂😂🤘🏼🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump It is NOT a national emergency! I hope Mueller indicts you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TransformacionDeCuarta #MaromasDeCuarta 🤸‍♀️🤸‍♂️🤸‍♀️🤸‍♂️🤸‍♀️🤸‍♂️🤸‍♀️🤸‍♂️🤸‍♀️🤸‍♂️🤸‍♀️🤸‍♂️🤸‍♀️🤸‍♂️🤸‍♀️🤸‍♂️🤸‍♀️🤸‍♂️… https://t.co/muIvHNmJAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever just want coffee but then you check your bank account... Cause same]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday, March 1st.......  Read Across “the World” Day!  🔥Amplify student voice🔥 by adding to and listening to ⤵️  https://t.co/I4oa454foN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKatieHill @KatieHill4CA @MrKatieHill1 #KKK #GrandWizard #DavidDuke approves of #IlhanOmar so does #AKKatie have… https://t.co/FlHlFY5kBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eight12GaRounds @HardballChris @MalcolmNance Stating articles in google is far from evidence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradPowers7 great call on Colorado and Utah, man. Thanks again for all your great work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calebleemusic @AmericanIdol Nothing will ever come close to your storybook ending. NEVER!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iStayWinning247 “Beating a team that’s rebuilding” LMFAOOOO rebuilding from WHAT?! #youallSTINK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielBrownLaw @TrevinDavid @LTThomaslaw @ErinDurant42 @_JananiS The article reminds me of my own experience worki… https://t.co/eMVLdrzG96]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Tanner Butler—FFA state winner in Job Interview. Amazing! #WolfpackPride https://t.co/GyKvBHKfRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Etm114E @scotttaft11 The older buildings also have hire assessments to take if maintence. Taxes are higher for new… https://t.co/hHnEloRYzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WrestleMANia is back on schedule @BeckyLynchWWE #TheMan https://t.co/HmFMLpxn8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump Another Cock Swallower spitting out another Load of worthless dribble !]]></document></documents></author>