<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mskrst3n And on NJ transit they have the seat facing forward and they flip them when going the other way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahRose_0420 it’s the day before my spring break, so that means I clearly have to make bad decisions right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate: If you get another cat you should name it Tofu! It would sound cute with Sushi! Me: If I get another c… https://t.co/J9ERzWpBLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_bbbcb01 @IsaacDovere @BernieSanders Lol! Yeah, you've found out my deep dark secret. I'm a bot. See? That's t… https://t.co/hIg3DF6htW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Happy day and beautiful memories as you get married. Your friend will always be with you❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yellowrangerr_ wait till he get older he gonna be like ohhhh this is what this is used for 😂😂😂 kids be so curious]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ride by his house &amp; pop 3 of his tires. If you do 4, insurance covers it. Be smart with ya shit 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[ELIZABETH TAYLOR QUEEN OF GLAMOUR💫  Winner of ‘best jewelry’ from now until the end of time  #elizabethtaylor… https://t.co/eO9j2KPdUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when people flash their brights to warn you there is a cop ahead. You are the people we need in this world. #thanksforthesave]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come and support our students @SSTSanAntonio at their SHTEAM festival! https://t.co/WMXt7O89g4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thistallawkgirl Please call 911 I am being sexually assaulted. I never consented to this. I would like the @ACLU t… https://t.co/GFEsv0iHEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna be a really “hot” 🔥🔥🔥day for me today🌺💕🌺💏💏 https://t.co/0pQxbwCIvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[“sweatpants are a sign of defeat. you lost control of your life, so you bought some sweatpants.” - karl lagerfeld… https://t.co/iddgrI6MFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[which one of y’all know about those virtual headset things guys be using? I need help trynna find the best one bc a… https://t.co/u56QGyJDZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read this in my book tonight and reread it about 15 times to make sure it really sank in:   “...you don’t stop lo… https://t.co/q0n6IwB0qc]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELLO I AM SEEING @KALIUCHIS IN DENVER I AM CRYING WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO WITH MY TIME UNTIL THEN???? I GUESS SLEEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[morrisville still hasn’t sent my new college my transcript after i’ve asked 4 times already so now i’m missing out… https://t.co/WwU578awhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azrattlers14 @MyersRacing19 @LSchuchart1s @sharkracingWoO @TeamDrydene @LVMS Great shot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[throwback to my post Lady Bird convo w/ my mom: me: i love it because it really made me appreciate you  mom: what t… https://t.co/pQmeHG2r8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #ValentinesDay  Enjoy a marvelous day! #love #friendships https://t.co/rEycigzaS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaileyOsmer Love to my Loggie 🌻🌻💛💛hope you feel better soon!! Thks for being the bbff]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @TuckerCarlson  is worse than we even thought ( and tbh we thought he was scum)- absolutely vile #FireTucker]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got accepted to study abroad in India this summer, focusing on mental health!!!!!!😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted a challenge from @missreedyreads . Post 10 album covers that make up a soundtrack of my life: no explana… https://t.co/9AoFb8ZJcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never give up on me, try to understand me and share your ideas with me to expand my own ideas. Be honest with me, a… https://t.co/aQJjMr295o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing is more energizing than having a spider crawl out of your grapes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoBeepUK @mcfunny @Siubhan_H @Rosewind2007 @Zigmund_Fraud @EdDarrell @SarahsCunning @WendyOrent @MsTrixter… https://t.co/5iy1W70bJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aqua Squad ⚜️🐠🐟🐠💙 @ Audubon Aquarium New Orleans https://t.co/WKvrpWKZkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@FedExHelp please explain to me how my package, which was approx a four hour drive from me, won’t be here until ne… https://t.co/bzunT3NinX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clicky groups are whack af, like we out here trying to bring people together. My group of friends love bringing peo… https://t.co/Pz1FKWsFfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetterCallLara Don’t worry- the same thing will happen when your a licensed attorney and you don’t want to give them free legal advice. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al pùblico en general misa de acciôn de gracias x el eterno descanso de mi hermano Javier Herrera Borrego sera en s… https://t.co/2ZVy9DXMZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[More proof Dems are in trouble in the Midwest in 2020. Ohio not in play (a state Obama won twice), resources aimed… https://t.co/9wuBZo4u29]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait for the hometown premiere of the feature film The Dancing Dogs of Dombrova 🙌 one of three films I have… https://t.co/QzaGyYehEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristaLeAnn_ Like locked knees??😵😵 I see that all the time and it makes me so nervous😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[McCarthy Calls on Schiff to Recuse Himself from Russia Probe: #Trump2020  https://t.co/6rTOtojzE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Texas_Rose52 @tonyschwartz And her spastic smile episodes that come apropos of nothing as she speaks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#COMMITEVERYTHINGUDO2THELORDTRUSTHIM&amp;HEWILLHELPU🙏🏼♥️☦️☝🏽☮️🌟 #THANKULORD🙏🏼👏🏼  #COMMIT #BELIEVE #TRUSTHIM… https://t.co/cFZsjQ2lAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter really scared the shit out of my mom and that’s a chapter I’m still in 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every radiant color of my solitude,the reflections in water,the shimmering strands’f lights like stars on earth,the… https://t.co/uOBEeqvEnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am sure you will be selected to any school you apply too! I wish you good luck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt @chirodale1 @TheStevenThomas @realDonaldTrump Same mentality as 45 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do pets you love to steal count? #NationalLoveYourPetDay #DominoDoesThings https://t.co/yCu7nGw0lH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so glad i got to watch you play this season!! You are amazing! Can’t wait for next year when you guys win it al… https://t.co/TEmXag45vu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexiiiilu24 getting a tad impatient w/ this wait game of Miss Eli Bear! Goodness- 12 days to go! Any day now- PLEASE!! 💞👑👣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been moisturizing my dog’s paws    everyday for the last month. Honestly the most extra thing I’ve ever done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's Kenneth Tobey!👍🏾 @ Hertford, North Carolina https://t.co/tevu4zknjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo quisiera saber quien les hizo tanto daño para que no les baste tener Facebook sino también el messenger 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aritbenie Who didn't know that was going to happen they probably will sell the young teenage girls into sex slaver… https://t.co/MzPVPgL1ni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @cbs46 @bmelley Sure liberal wierdo's put butterflies before the stupid Americans that vote for yo… https://t.co/9yCu4oRjWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m cryin’ he fr touched my hand!😭 @YellaBeezy214 @YellaBeezy214  #SpringBreak2k19 https://t.co/rg4PwMUAAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@interjaketion @nycsouthpaw @HDTGM They talked about it on the show for an hour and a half and I knew it was nuts b… https://t.co/99cTD7M0AY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TamaraPiety @kms_gigi @HillaryClinton My thoughts exactly!! Well said!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone heading to #SMCoP today wanna grab coffee ahead of the meetup? @SMCoP_CPMS #GCDigital]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyleejo22 @AspenHealy Do you like her Kate Spade backpack as well? https://t.co/MMQdJvxg3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[And when you get off the phone and he 1) makes sure you were okay because you were spending Valentine’s Day alone 2… https://t.co/nRjH9Xqp8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogelio11025708 @Angelic86416803 @Veronica_sphynx @monerorape @V_TrujilloM @Milenio Pues prefieres a tus ignorante… https://t.co/9ahbGm9Uqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peopleintrees @jenstaletovich It’s like an all out attack on or disregard for black neighborhoods in Florida. Seei… https://t.co/esKfyLcvmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tailopez I asked for my $100 Tai, like the homeless guy on your thread...]]></document><document><![CDATA[talking about Jesus + eating spicy food. good times with the case’s. come back soon. 👌🏼🤟🏼 https://t.co/jFmTMFJHvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so bored I might just end up getting another piercing or a new tattoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old bridge across the creek #reflections #watercolor🖼🎨💡🖌 #danielsmith#watercolorpainting #paintingonpaper… https://t.co/nf0VTCY7HJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I had the balls to stay with a longer length when I get my nails done. They look so pretty 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity I hope are President stays strong I would not sign the bill kick it down the road we do not need to gi… https://t.co/9vqIopLDkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve not ate any beef today and noticed than I’ve been more hungry than when I eat beef. 🤔 #Keto I ate chicken and… https://t.co/BU42t9hpwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh. F u Girl Scout cookie season and your irresistibly tempting deliciousness 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CastCompliment goes out to Nour Marouani from #MoroccoPavillion @WaltDisneyWorld !! Thank you for a lovely evening… https://t.co/msQq8C7p8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ann91237283 @brennan_elliott @TheNannyExpress @VanessaMarcilM No.  It's affecting me in a very strong way.  This i… https://t.co/rEZZ4Bk5IB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am honored and humbled by the opportunity to serve as Superintendent of Schools here in my home county. There is… https://t.co/uixiu8aTdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably Miss Iyanla in her head right then.  #FixMyLife https://t.co/QvyAc4Zwc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking Its just sad the ignorance guesing Fox NEWS is only thing on in the house]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKGarcia331 @RockhillStrat There's a sad dog?? Fuck it, maybe I won't eventually watch that after all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #closingstatement: "Killeen is called the Great place and I'm running to make it a greater place. Join me @… https://t.co/72Iz61pJ9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[brianna walked into my house and i almost tackled her to the ground but i didn’t so it’s alright.]]></document><document><![CDATA[so like it happened again guys. talking to this dude for two months then find out he’s plottin on our home girl. mf… https://t.co/akjoFYwlej]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, were these refs from West Noble or did they just forget how to call a basketball game? Whaaaat happened!???… https://t.co/6jOB6Tzmwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ CrossFit FYR- Find Your Reason https://t.co/jELToSCnv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaumeeMom @GeeGeeAkili @kylegriffin1 @PressSec She would only lie anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus the fact that he’s a celebrity, which means the cops gave it about 50x the attention they give cases involving… https://t.co/0fY8dw7GvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhiattsteele @JeffreyGoldberg @MapwifeJodi That’s just stupid!  I mean, incredibly stupid! Trump is merely EXPOSIN… https://t.co/maaWflLyv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Presidents Day to our wonderful President Trump. Thank you for standing strong and we will stand strong with you . On to 20/20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dguajardo @SpeakerPelosi @RepCuellar @txamiu David:  El típico inseguro que niega sus raíces y su cultura por sent… https://t.co/S5lFCOfhFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NisslyJen @mirandalambert I love her, too!! She deserves all the happiness in this world and beyond !  Miranda, you got this !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you birthday girl for an amazing Sunday ✨💓 #tatreat @ Five Sense Collective https://t.co/tYx1NY5SMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Says another prominent Wall Streeter: “He is this mysterious, Gatsbyesque figure. He likes people to think that he… https://t.co/U9YGbU8Bob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josephmasood24 3 for 3 no money sizing because I always go for my size but I’m glad my accounts are still hitting… https://t.co/AajmY1iqdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spanish4TheGoon @GoodKhush @F73 @B_HavinPatel @GoonsBeWylin https://t.co/lVE3OXQC6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mo a real one. I can’t imagine being on the metro and seeing her hop on. Random stuff like this happens enough to m… https://t.co/PC2MXXYpuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick PLC moment with @ALPHA_Cable to go over the Depth of Complexity cards. @NISDCable @SillerRosie @MrsDAliano… https://t.co/b2wkyQ9Bwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been listening to this podcast about the Zodiac killer and it just hit me how brilliant it is that a home secu… https://t.co/ai0CHuWrTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great feeling having our team go 4-0 at the Courtney Miller Invitational!! #BirdGang]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: The anti-gay president of #Brazil Jair #Bolsonaro has shared a video of a man urinating on another man’s hea… https://t.co/BfLryoRpC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[MARYS AFTER DARK! Every FRIDAY and SATURDAY night after our fabulous Drag shows! Stay and party all night with the… https://t.co/1NvUJXiWhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@votevets I now officially see the military as enemy of the people. Their alligeince is to Trump not the Constituti… https://t.co/BQZmUWJtnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaylorTheGreat @TheRealMikeEpps @ItsDMurph @chrisrock @DaveChappelle Bout time this shit dropped lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[even though my boyfriend is miles away he still manages to surprise me w/ flowers &amp; our babygirl w/ a stuffed animal 🥰❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best friend I just want to let you know you’re going to be the God mother of my kids 💞 and we’re going to grow old together]]></document><document><![CDATA[some days people just need some reassurance. today is one of those days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dametokillfor I still feel guilty that I have a pair of the Captain Marvel Vans and @McKelvie doesn't because they… https://t.co/JbjHiwu1bz]]></document><document><![CDATA[so hug those who are important to you, tell the teachers who’ve made an impact on you how much you appreciate them,… https://t.co/1LMvLy9s3w]]></document></documents></author>