<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Comment on your conspiracy theories.  Tell me, Odious Taint Jr. WHY YOU DIDN'T CALL THE FBI WHEN AG… https://t.co/nXM3W4IDEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeerJeet Pretty sure Shapiro is an ancestral Ashkenazi Jewish name, no?  Not really in his interest to bring this up...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewNBC12 @AlexWhittler @AnthonyNBC12 Need to work on your bird dog form. 🤪🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like Stephanie McMahon forgot to apply the bronzer to her hands. Her and @realDonaldTrump love that orange look. #RAW #WWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a blatant double standard. @IlhanMN is a black, Muslim, woman, calling out the USA for supporting a  regim… https://t.co/3E2e4Kalko]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey @BitOBaca I love you let’s make a charity bet on the sixers warriors game against the spread DM me for charity details]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt❤️ Wynwood Arts District MIAMI!! #miami #florida #dalailama #wynwood #wynwoodmiami #usa2017 #travel #wanderlust… https://t.co/Yy29djuimV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really forget if I took my contacts out some nights and start looking around the room to try to read something to… https://t.co/b5I2oudQO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sights and sounds of Little Sugar Creek Greenway this afternoon from its intersection with Tyvola Road.… https://t.co/Wpiq7a74kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶Mass Dorinda, I can’t turn off what turns me on🎶 https://t.co/iGXveI0Wt0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Splish Splash Laundromat in Bloomfield, NJ https://t.co/ZjcxVQerbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WesleyWorden @SmoknSara420 @OneFallenAngelM @realmedicineMI @cannaworldsite @EmeraldZoo @johnnyrebel907 @Raymosaki… https://t.co/QLiuDwYq3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mooose_8 is staying one more year with Milwaukee as a 2nd baseman? Travis Shaw? Schoop?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genius of 1952 Act was to categorize standards for patents. Standards should be untangled from way getting treated… https://t.co/Rlla9nVO1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeBearison @cane1222 @THRMattBelloni @THR First of all, no to “sweetie”. Second, I was referring to the commen… https://t.co/CRWQefSHF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoniAhm Also, I don't think I actually knew Marion was a UNLV guy, and now I can't figure out what looks so funny… https://t.co/AICRlRhsld]]></document><document><![CDATA[So then people who like Morgan Wallen are going to be the ones to change the world?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThankYouOmu! #OgeMora  #literacymatters #imagesmatter #marchisreadingmonth https://t.co/o4JWfiIjrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetBlue why is it so difficult to get someone on the phone at LAX lost and found? And when the gentleman answers t… https://t.co/tXI6eHhGE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Moncks Corner, South Carolina https://t.co/b7dlLDjc2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar I made the exact same promise. Perhaps we should start a support group.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet Yes. Human trafficking is part of every Super Bowl. Fans can’t get enough sex with underage girls h… https://t.co/eKf8o61zbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirstTake @maxkellerman Why are we always looking to make some new, hottest player the beat ever??? He isn’t close… https://t.co/K8gZGigmMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so ready to murder these fucking crying dogs next door, I hate them. Like my dog just lays there not bothering… https://t.co/avzttgSdX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to the shelter to meet some cats I saw on Instagram but they were already adopted. Sad for me, happy for the… https://t.co/1yZVI3EDaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Altas dio un gran partido .. pero 90 minutos son demasiados para muchos equipos.. jugó bien y perdió. Así los númer… https://t.co/fuiGSg0cvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dstebs02 @missarahashley They're becoming there parents👴👵. Yep, they're settling alright and living boring lives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this how niggas who believe cardi b is actually bad baby moms be lookin 🤣 https://t.co/ju2O61Ivne]]></document><document><![CDATA[ᴊᴜsᴛ ᴀ ʜᴏᴘ, sᴋɪᴘ &amp; ᴊᴜᴍᴘ ᴀᴡᴀʏ @ Downtown Atlanta https://t.co/qZ9G04Ayid]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can never tell who my favorite Cub is, until Jon Lester starts talking shit to the media. Then I remember it’s been him all along.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trinity at night #boston #backbay #copleysquare #trinitychurchboston #night #urban #nofilter @ Copley Square https://t.co/stiEAG3Usk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacUidhir @kligup53 @Quarterback_USA @kissmyfoot24 @Lrihendry Hell, I don’t care for my government, but I love thi… https://t.co/U0oUNA7zKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr True story? You dumb shit, the ACA was passed by Congress.   Your senile daddy couldn’t get his pas… https://t.co/zPK20buEdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think the Electoral College distorts the will of the people, the rules for contingent elections are so far o… https://t.co/JdMIpJv8S3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just left work by John Wayne Airport and I see this ominous sky @soumada_weather https://t.co/lMEM6LzCAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nextjen Without reading the article, did the phrase "all is well" make it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pelean 33 Alcaldes el Fondo Minero - Vía @elnorte https://t.co/JvEYbaCu31]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your tweet suddenly becomes popular and you reply to your own tweet with: 1. Your venmo 2. A SoundCloud 3. Some… https://t.co/fAV18Pwpv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenRissotto Correct for me 29 out of the 30 active ballpark just missing Toronto and other baseball ballparks who no longer  exists]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un día cerraré los ojos, y diré... «mereció la pena haber vivido». en The Bahamas https://t.co/9b9Q6YzkhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow He's deleting evidence now, @jack. Might be a good idea to archive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinC_199 @IamLilimar @savannahlmay @Nickelodeon @dibenedettolexi @daniellaperkins @JohnDBeckTV That’s what make… https://t.co/mhPoorEhpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told you this has the potential to be an unbelievable experience. #CanPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MancusoKellyA18 @BevCederquist @AOC What do you mean by exclusive? She seems to be exercising the same freedom to… https://t.co/lOVcw42NQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejaiho the show makes me too uncomfortable to watch sorry. Anxiety by proxy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mexico will pay for the wall.  Sit down and shut up Donald. Nothing you say has any credibility]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColesStreetPoth I couldn’t even tell you what that Nissan looks like. Teslas here seem to always be the car that t… https://t.co/QC8EYcOzLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @SebGorka The idea of violating human rights. The Congresswoman wants a guarantee on human rights by… https://t.co/tuvc5VgICG]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my guy @JonTLangston is not in your rotation...get your shit together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not magnificent it’s ▪️◾️💫BLACKnificent 💫◼️▪️Join is for our Black History Month themed fashion show: Harlem R… https://t.co/xv3leDgaL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[He has the Racists &amp; Bigots, they embrace his lies because it supports their white supremecy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceLeshan @wusa9 You know in life sometimes humans change as one gets older views change humans should be carefu… https://t.co/pPFtyZjFO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMARRSHABAZZ @luluHru @Brenderm1 @JulieReichwein1 @ctanner3 @SealeyGerald @AmericanAuburn @wendyp4545… https://t.co/Mm7pOHVNxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaitBuddies @MattMuck1 @greer_xxx @GioCaruso new vid on bait buddies https://t.co/K47GnaNEfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[neadsdogs pups in TRAINing. #Choochoo #worldclassservicedogs #Brothers #EmmittForrestFenway @ The Station Diner https://t.co/muowSSwEuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@witchytwitchytv It's like I told another streamer as a friend I wanna respect and treat you right but my inner per… https://t.co/LxKb8fmG1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Campaign in Dallas to clear negative stereotypes about hijabs and Muslim women https://t.co/91wmQatfwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcmessmer58 @IngrahamAngle @AOC This nation isn't broke from Dems giving free stuff to lazy Blacks so..... https://t.co/TGssr8XDtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC What is her background how dose her resume read. Has she ever owned a business dose she have children how dose… https://t.co/SGvD90NsOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @amjoyshow Trump is treating the White House just like he does every other house,it’s literally For Sale or For Rent ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fav if you’ve ever skipped class to get stuff done for another class I can’t be the only one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is brilliant. I love it. On a humorous side note: maybe Baymax will one day be a reality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #InternationalWomensDay and #RKelly gets busted as Arsenio would say.... https://t.co/drzbaAP8zT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday Reflection and Gratitude 🙌🏼  #kolesarteam #valuejedi #mortgagebanker #friendships #clients @ The Kolesar… https://t.co/gSLrNmNHYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to fuck you so good and tell you how much I love you Lisa.. we can always finish where we left off Lisa... https://t.co/deEFbnblq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My besties ! @ Central Park Downtown Winter Haven https://t.co/DTnODKeirK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fitnessVwork Hi, If you have any plans to hire a resource from an agency to work on your project remotely, we woul… https://t.co/jNyahlYEvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@HowardStern .@sternshow OMG.  Fuck all the haters.  I love bobo.   Never has a more perfect moron existed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrindSimmons94 Hope you get drafted by the eagles Jeffrey. You would love that locker room. Be blessed brother !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in Lakewood, CO, check out this #SupplyChain job via the link in our bio: Associate Logi… https://t.co/bHkU5fCf56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchlafon Detroit Rock City all day every day. Spirit of Radio is a great song though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USATODAY Good, hope the Republicans do the same. Who wants to see or hear more of the same corrupt BS?   Take all… https://t.co/eoVv7xv7bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaeljknowles @IlhanMN you are working on being a bad person and you should think about that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImmaNupeBih @KingOfDarkSkinz @double_cupp_me @Knickolas_ 😂 I been seeing him talking bout Tarly gang, Tarly weak though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day is my 67th favorite holiday, right behind National Pet a Snake 🐍 day. https://t.co/qvh7Z3kWKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join our Mayor Kevin Hartke tonight for his first State of the City as Mayor. 🇺🇸🌐🇺🇸 Catch the Council on Facebook L… https://t.co/NyXUwtudZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drawandstrike @flybyjones_tony I don't think it is that funny Brian, Beto was way to close to Cruz in 2018?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/6Gvum3R5ej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGaLmHD I’m going to pretend I know what that last word was 😂 yes, yes you do need heated Windex.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJoeQJarvis @50linesonly @organicfanatic5 @mikenorman @sdgrumbine @TxEx I disagree about political stability whic… https://t.co/5xCv2pV0zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. I’ve struggled with tremendous guilt, anxiety, and depression taking time off to recover from mono bc my body… https://t.co/0xeRumGaTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan Why r u so angry at POTUS? I find myself caught up in the heat of topics myself. I forget God is in ch… https://t.co/Nq7iNz9oCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brian_Cashman_ I’m talking facts! He’s a HOH SS good hitter and defender! That’s a fact! Yankees fans would agree]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClareDaher @CarmineSabia @RonColeman @ggreenwald @Cernovich @IlhanMN @RashidaTlaib Yep. So many on the right are d… https://t.co/foqtBnJCjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night @UMassHockey and reconnecting with my mentor @SportsLawMaster a HUGE reason why I am where I am today.… https://t.co/sZeYwTLoWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman Make sure U review @LynnePattonHUD comments today.Why would you interject yourself with”F-ing pig”… https://t.co/DtkLN8wvzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish you could turn off stories on Instagram. Like just swipe away the entire line of IG stories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Safe to say that on this frigid March day, #SummerHouse has jumpstarted my longing for patio-season in a few months… https://t.co/Uo75JWl0Eg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canphan666 You said illegal, that's wrong and harmful to that firm's reputation]]></document><document><![CDATA[The match everyone has been waiting for tyler.badgett @RBWrestling vs aarongandara powaywrestling @cifstate… https://t.co/AWJe7FMcwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJacobsRad @nationalpost I think this is the reason Butts resigned. Him and Brison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[novarestaurantandlounge un lunes con @SoyTonyBravo djinoxlmp ferragamonyc eddycarr75 aneudypuello ferragamonyc… https://t.co/EKxGvcYGUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely preferable to “Warrrrr Eagle,” which sounds like pirate talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slightly flat but still delicious - Drinking an Aragon 1904 by @BlueBeeCider @ Blue Bee Cider  — https://t.co/gRg1o4Yq9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLBTheShow in #MLBTheShow19, are replays of reactions of hitters and the dugouts during and after home runs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sonicsman @sonicsarena Reposting the same thing over and over isn’t doing anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jalenmcmillan20 @salvelaz You can see the passion in the comments below. No one gonna show you the love like UW...… https://t.co/PcJSko252L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi @KINGDOMHEARTS if all I care about is the gameplay itself, is there any difference between the standard and delu… https://t.co/AbHylt31Dr]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yYJEB5IiEf Verizon Wireless Customer Service 1-855-431-6111 is ours #Verizonwirelesscustomerservice… https://t.co/UJzH9CPd6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, would you look at that. Morata receiving crosses from his teammates and scoring goals. Who would of thought]]></document></documents></author>