<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'm at Mira Loma Middle School in Riverside, CA https://t.co/77eSnLlyj8 https://t.co/xx5fOiew34]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now ur about to affect my valentines days plans with myself STOP WITH THE DELAYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[First team All State IBCA In Peoria @devonhouse2323 Congratulations All! https://t.co/dUkH1uGqPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[picking out an outfit for church tomorrow and was picking out a @JeffreeStar lipstick to wear and got sad again bc… https://t.co/yqhO5vGHdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hyphy_republic @DarwinBondGraha @castillodavidca @OUSDNews Most of the charters came in during the Broad board and… https://t.co/LxuCD7XUNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Side....you can order these awesome shirts too!! Positive Action is everywhere!💙#EC__Proud @MrParsonGrade1… https://t.co/4YypADyFb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntiSoylent @Anola1177 @GridironSchol91 @AOC If your on mon wage you get things like food stamp medical housing etc. Yes i can.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulHeroux So sorry for your loss Mayor! Mura was such a friendly dog every time I met her. May her memory be a blessing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All those things people cared enough about to drag along for weeks, across borders, through deserts and train rides… https://t.co/7L0sk6Dht5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Montgomery County Detectives still haven’t given up solving the homicide of Phillip Welsh.  https://t.co/8ngWtSjkZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loretta_Swit That’s awesome @Loretta_Swit ! Congratulations to you; enjoy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 Successful #businesses  That Employ  #Formerly Incarcerated People  #RecidivismReduction  #care2 https://t.co/WpsOkrOTRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosaMendozaa10 Se que todo de va a salir bien se ve q eres una persona bien creativa y detallista! 🙌🏼☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@BBCAMERICA #Dynasties #petswatchingdynasties 🐶🐅❤️ https://t.co/JjXBLNmHYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just don’t understand how people can find it in their hearts to be so fucking mean to other people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we might witness two people coming together out of authentic love.  But none of these levels is what the Bible… https://t.co/uwLIXKvf0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[That certain someone you like texts back with “k” and that means they never want to... #mirth #lol #smile #cute https://t.co/NReLPnD9RL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Relieve low back pain, pelvic and hip tension and build thoracic mobility with this foam rolling #sundaystretch ⛷ T… https://t.co/sU1B5xL3Mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m up early to write letters and thank you notes.  Read and meditate before the day starts.  It’s a perfect way to… https://t.co/RTBz4mM6aK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FPMurph @TheGaragePod @vcspreps I agree. It would have been fun to be in 3A and had a rematch in the finals with B… https://t.co/xzXUQtORN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Although I agree with your position, I find it reprehensible that you are calling for a twitter vote on… https://t.co/mNueiDIHjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@victori68207096 @BachelorABC @colton So painful. And I just want to tell her “stop playing with your hair!!”🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M1A2Punisher @RocketNina66 @jimsciutto Since trump has become president, he has destroyed the career of several lo… https://t.co/va8PrjnPOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fakemikeboudet I hope you find something real to do with ur time my dude]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only way to go is up. #table #rocket  #2019 @ Great Homes in Orlando https://t.co/dVHmDhUeba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShemekaMichelle I’ve worked super hard for what I have - not much, but also in the same boat as you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol Kristopher will do this in public and I love it especially when an ass grab is at the end 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DitzMcGeee Wow I'm so happy and proud for you! Way to go! https://t.co/nq5uYVHqzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist Italian Sausage, Roasted Garlic, Roasted Red Peppers, Mushroom, Extra cheese.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealtyWiseJacq I think I'd rather rob a bank than steal cactus. It sounds painful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter What’s wrong with you? Would you be happier if Hillary was your President?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahsimmons179 All you can do is take it one day at a time. Some don’t understand that when some people love they… https://t.co/uavRj8iOhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchmidtheShit @PlanetRichie @marylougeorge2 @pacelattin @DonaldJTrumpJr Hell NO, NO , NO !!… https://t.co/iSNLl5QnQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patricia_69 @KillyLove4ever I never said Scout would be Jason’s. I said the opposite if you read my post.]]></document><document><![CDATA[feeling pathetic.. Open url. Not even a penny. I just hope people are donating to help others because in life you n… https://t.co/wIU6gAqDUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chanitons @mundodeportivo @marcelosottile Y paraMessi! Argentina 🇦🇷 es horrible y no va a ganar nunca y le echarán… https://t.co/ocWKy5bXSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandmas 74th birthdays Wednesday &amp; it’s her first birthday in heaven 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d black if I took a shot every time Aileen says “**insert name** is such a fucking **insert zodiac sign**”]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was so nice to have the glorious sunshine today, I just had to get outside and create. It was so nice to see man… https://t.co/44a0PXe84U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NealSchonMusic THERE IS NO ONE BETTER ON GUITAR THAN YOU!! KEEP SHARING VIDEOS UNTIL I GET TO SEE YOU LIVE AGAIN .… https://t.co/7AecMIKj1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii INSANE..what has happened to our country ? This is really scary ! How can anyone be willing to change… https://t.co/jDRU63IOvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good example of unconscious agency. Clearly those two were “trying” to “escape.” They’re just not consciously aware… https://t.co/WoNaLpG7fl]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES there’s such as thing as a “stupid question”. Stupid questions lead to irrelevant content.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am Available for the next 6 Hours on https://t.co/GwVVOpLwzG @TS4Rent #TSEscorts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HerbMartin @realDonaldTrump @POTUS I love love love ❤️ this video...it shows the enemies of a free America ! God b… https://t.co/WPl3GfeRWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NuclearAnthro What late capitalism social media branded sex shaming pseudo-medicalist fresh hell even in this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I  just screamed stfu @ my TV &amp; it turned off &amp; now I'm scared.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it when the president circumvents the democratic process and creates a crisis that doesn’t exist in order to… https://t.co/bqC551ukGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KiddNation @kelly_clarkson Sad face! Y’all how many retweets can we get for Kelly to see this invite?!… https://t.co/A1gMeTY4vd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer @DNC @GOP  Awesome..even more people see a bias..and more and will keep moving… https://t.co/buyKU9YnsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start your day right with coffee and a feel-good story. #inspiration   Courtesy of @KingJames @IPROMISESchool… https://t.co/txCJKs8rgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Premium #WordPress website themes and eCommerce website development, also offering GoDaddy hosting and SSL certific… https://t.co/SCwPeqGucN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4: "Educated: A Memoir" by Tara Westover https://t.co/fp10NbsewG @DrFloate you would like this one!… https://t.co/XBXmsf0S2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[If ppl, directly or indirectly affected, didn’t speak against Wrong actions/policies, it’s “possible” until ppl too… https://t.co/vIZj7VSSWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rollbluntss if i hit a white person for saying nigga im going to jail 🌚, if i spit on them and they hit me first welll both go😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff You just lost me. I am a law abiding citizen who loves to shoot. Why are you penalizing me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did anyone else forget what genuinely-happy-yuina looks like  Like i was thinking she's looking a lot happier in bi… https://t.co/4ZpDIVY2MK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZoeYoungin1804 I do, but I’m talking shit. It jiggles lol when I’m jumping]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Psychosocial by @slipknot on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/XQv5euGDs5 https://t.co/d1DEbObo80]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to be on this stage to do something for 2 minutes in answer to the question “What did you expect?” #sxsw… https://t.co/3ZR37kGfjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TRUEDISCL0SURE May be no proof yet but my bet is she was murdered and her body added to all the others leading to Clinton’s door.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to inspire people! I want someone to look at me and say “because of you I did it and I didn’t give up!”💖🌟  I… https://t.co/HqfraCrboo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader Disagree @GOPLeader   Congress has taken advantage of their power for too long.  This bill is needed.… https://t.co/bdG0nG3X77]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is this allowed and why is nobody investigating him?? He’s so slimy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moving on now to 3-A girls @PisgahSports taking on Glencoe. We’ve got a case of a slippery basketball https://t.co/VtSgfgxNqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Trump had come into the office and been presidential, not contacting and tearing down every Tom/Dick/Harry aroun… https://t.co/HHOVkfgVi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the Fussy Hussy #BestVeganEver #SupportBlackOwned #LovedIt https://t.co/YdGwA1lDdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[What makes people listen to the likes of assholes like this roger stone dude?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cryindonnie @JpwellerJim @RepAdamSchiff I’d do a little more research. 😂😂😂😂 really. Do your pussys all sleep with… https://t.co/d4Yy2PYCFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay to the amazing, inspiring, hardworking, and uplifting women in my life! Keep killin'… https://t.co/XyoqlvQXtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I still didn’t consider you my best friend and I wish I still didn’t miss you because goddamn it sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teacher friends, do this for yourself. We expect our students to develop a growth mindset, so why not model it for… https://t.co/uKQBA5s2qJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay so now that we can all recognize that @DarrenCriss is talented af, can we PLEASE get him to host @nbcsnl PLEASE???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HereComsTrouble @FrancieML @ChronicPainDad @Charmainexxxooo @katelcasas @GaryGSP89 @kitty4hawks @ISignforYou1… https://t.co/t4o0nBvQAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima start back hooping and playing volleyball. I miss it, and I’m too good at it to not start back playing. I’m just saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Duncansville, PA, check out this job: https://t.co/amNZwpY0G6 #Clerical]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Postmates I’m waiting for a “promoted” ad on twitter not to be bogus! https://t.co/G7eOD8mHqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DalyKirsteen @KerriDHowell Thanks for coming, Kirsteen! I had a great time learning what other b-schools are doing… https://t.co/rEtj7LOR5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rfragan @ffoxxface @ProudResister @Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump I will put you in Kasha no Tejina. かしゃのてじな。As an… https://t.co/2wiw8BzTTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@euphyllianna @TheGreedSide Pas toujours de verre de disponible. Dans certains resto si tu veux un verre pour emporter ça te coûte 50 sous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the support S Atlantic! Always our star partner!! ⭐️⭐️ #takeyourshare23 @jaybisping @gloria_terri… https://t.co/aamtcKemm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wannabe_Mangaka @LadyBowtiful @mangacomiccon I will check it out! Heading to work now :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michael101991 I think I'll stay in the Reformed Episcopal Church and avoid this problem altogether.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how matt always says he’s more obsessed with me than I am with him, but let’s face it. That’s a lie 🤤😍❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Jackpot Junction Hotel and Casino https://t.co/FsuuV1bDaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricofOC @brithume You're obviously not a real American. Or you would also defend the right to free speech.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i ain’t never understand the purpose in shooting up a building that holds your friends and loved ones in bc you got beef w one individual]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so scared when I enrolled my kid in preschool, i didn’t want him to be without me. I didn’t want to let him g… https://t.co/uhXip8trxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Faculty Awards with T.Haas @GVPEClub @GVSU https://t.co/Lq69wJ16lm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacob was around for everything my first bf my first break up my first time smoking and drinking. I miss him so fre… https://t.co/U7WzEnVylo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angie_karan These Elephants are loving their dirt baths,that`s cute!!!🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph_manning07 @sxsw @AllRaise @CapitalFactory I'll be gone by then, unfortunately. Have a great talk! #allraise]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I learned people from Winnipeg are as insufferable as the sharks said they were]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodyvance Funny thing is, I worked for Eaton’s and made $12 an hour then... came back in 2010... rent was now $850… https://t.co/taNtgpM7QQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SexCounseling @lowrad57 @realDonaldTrump Not rude you are a bot that’s are electronic response on Twitter  I will… https://t.co/UgShvrVnyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[trying to sleep cause my flight to Sacramento is at 7am.... too excited for @jtimberlake show]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had been waiting for this show for a while now and now it’s it’s done I have no words to describe how much fun w… https://t.co/WARUNSWDOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird @wickedwone How'd that election go for you there meadows? 2012 didn't turn out like you expected?… https://t.co/w1hzz4hGb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of dogs and toddlers...👶🐶  As mothers we often say of toddlers, “look how sweet and innocent they look when they’re… https://t.co/zdx40ZC03Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[[E N C O U R A G E M E N T . . . |happy Saturday! Hope you're enjoying the weekend ✨ https://t.co/DxmNR4TiL1]]></document></documents></author>