<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Norah_Holder @StephPavao5 7054452550 x 8615 Hope to hear from you soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t tweet about celebrity deaths. Luke Perry saddens me. I watched every 90210, and with my daughters, every… https://t.co/eLbfpzOc89]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez Shouts 'I'M THE BOSS' During Green New Deal 'Ego Trip' [Watch] https://t.co/9T03qORbSB she is going t… https://t.co/4KdfWdi4sW]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RVvJEip1NA use promo code NOVA10 for a 10% discount on your purchases! 🔥🔥🔥 #fitness gear online!… https://t.co/bTPgbkqWNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[People complain too much about their favorite shows getting cancelled when they don’t even watch them on TV!!! If y… https://t.co/Z8lf2CCEkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AcademyLI #MTCenoughsaid @TmcgrathTom Hire - Fire - Promote #CTE offers working environments to provide profession… https://t.co/y8P2DI5Smz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 She could teach @SenatorCollins a thing or two about being a patriot 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was magical night!!!✨#Oscar2019 gown by @saisumancouture https://t.co/7AZJbnoFoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo, no one told me getting married and planning a future could be so stressful 💆🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_rendel Such an informed and well-articulated decision. Next big challenge is finding effective ways to commun… https://t.co/tXfzDisIoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes, just getting up, carrying on is a super human achievement. #gogently @ Virginia Beach, Virginia https://t.co/GMAiTFEiH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmarroquinn finna give some crackers to the (very few) homeless people there]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Charleston has 5 times the #alcohol consumption as the rest of the #usa.  #travelwriter. #TravelSouthUSA #travel… https://t.co/0unLvH00HA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a Patreon of @CrimeJunkiePod BUT I NEED MORE! I’ve listened to every podcast already and now idk what to do with myself 😩😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamHeughan @apriluvn @Pennyyo79 Wow and the Oscar goes to.... @SamHeughan and the 🐟]]></document><document><![CDATA[She literally said Sometimes, I think that you're draining me, sometimes..I want you at home, sometimes..I feel lik… https://t.co/qCEkD8xInI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfanoMundano Prometo ir, ahorita mismo le digo a mi marido que me lleve, al cabo seguro él si conoce.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jack_be_lucky @realjefogirl @realDonaldTrump The god of this world is Satan aka Lucifer. My bible says this and I… https://t.co/46uYHBF16S]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to have been selected to attend the first AP with WE Service Summit at Microsoft and learn from some amazi… https://t.co/0N3v3dvreP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeahLieurance Empathetic as a serial killer, but would never put in that kind of effort. (And yes, I realize this… https://t.co/BXtEOqDNJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Ichiban (Ichiban Shibori) (一番搾り) by @Kirin_Brewery @ Harumi Sushi — https://t.co/wPSZLPwgmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizloganhere @nicoledwallace @DeadlineWH Please 🤨. Judge Judy here I come!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kathy_LovesIndy @GMA @IndyCar I hope it's aired at all, at this point. It was supposed to be between 7a-8a. Didn't… https://t.co/t0VoYat7TU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!! Jim doing big things.. it is truly great to be a part of such a great team..#TUtvS3Finale #CronintheBarbarians https://t.co/c57kx3OiK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys when Auburn sports inevitably kills me just promise to show the kick six and Patrick Keim's three on loop to t… https://t.co/AU2SITAVGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t like giving my time to a lot of people nowadays because a lot of people don’t know how to reciprocate the sam… https://t.co/H8Z7zZg2AK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJeffDuncan thank you, it was a HORRIBLE bill and one that should be vetoed, this is no compromise,]]></document><document><![CDATA[As if the first weekend of October wasn’t going to be epic already, it just keeps getting better! So excited, I’m g… https://t.co/tzmWTxCzPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this #InternationalWomansDay2019 I am spending my evening enjoying one of my new fave ladies @jessemermell podca… https://t.co/ZLdLsQjQqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fighting climate change and reducing our carbon footprint one vehicle at a time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Wonderful Chinese #Herb Huang qi  (also known as #Astragalus) https://t.co/EtVUo95tkE #ChineseMedicine #holistichealth #Herbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basedinfidel8 @SpringAyn @TH3R34LTRUTH @Chriskl70208387 @Americanthatguy @AlexWY18 @fellspeaks @johnw299 @AJuM809… https://t.co/mWAQJlDXQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5 of my favorite books. This book was amazing. The movie barely resembled the book. Read the book... https://t.co/4Jx1OTOb2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christinetchr @SPESharks If the are @WillistonTigers , I can check for you!!!!! Let me know:) 💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me and @afsc_org and write to Congress and say: Keep our families together! Support immigrants with #TPS. https://t.co/JyA7rCGxWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a45cooper It was quite cold. It took a little while for me to get warm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch me kidnapping @chloeeelove193 so our busy asses finally hangout 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jmonst @benlamers @tiahedenland @BibRave @hoppe_feet #BibChat https://t.co/0gsSDNa54s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tina Star (@TinaStar4u) is now advertising in Fort Lauderdale! https://t.co/FOaGzCznZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cizpoetry @SunshineFiine Can’t defeat the devil without a demon. 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexGaskarth @simplecreatures @markhoppus We love you and we support you both!! So excited to see you on tour soon!😍❤✌]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many fucks do i give? @ Slaughters Portland https://t.co/pTw96ratWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BootsRiley It infuriates me that something as respected as the NYT couldn’t be bothered to check their sources bef… https://t.co/EcZDIdYUwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ShadowoftheColossus 🦄💕 https://t.co/NeqrAdspQg  #livenow #thiccchickgaming #ps4 #TeamB42 https://t.co/Dgpj2L6yQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NGDAverk @hjhollis93 @tweetNorvena @frostgirl11 @darker_dearie @Danielle21A @AlliCamAllison @SourceRobert… https://t.co/QnmLCnJEPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's adventure! @ Disney's Beach Club Resort https://t.co/26w99Ne6pI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesonAPLang I had them brainstorm topics of interest. They coincided with their major/career plans and area of i… https://t.co/vihEj5JskQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day and thank you to all the great women in my life who helped, molded, inspired, and d… https://t.co/8sMDyS4gQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Motivation for all pitchers for all teams,  Tenn SO LHP Garrett Crochet JR season FB 79-82, SR Fall FB 84-87, Summe… https://t.co/l4wNdJhraW]]></document><document><![CDATA[...if you made $0 in tips, you’d have a fatter paycheck bc restaurants are required to pay you the difference so yo… https://t.co/e1AcqTFTdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys are my hero s pictures and videos don't lie......... I still have hope in the American people..... And a hero lies in you......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!!! @_emichellec  I hope you have a great day! https://t.co/tuTxqbzXGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MontesoDebonair She was in her late teens... which  was not unheard of.  Freaknik was supposed to be for college students lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminds me of the time @Nicole_M_Clark and I had a panic in Iceland not realizing the parking brake was on 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlessBattle Imagine laughing at your dog and not checking to see if he Ohkay I’m going to hell with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy_Zimbardi @EVornheder @UniceVince @CWittwayTHD @zmanski42 Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Google Play Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below… https://t.co/c3Xp0sdu0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItalyMagazine @perillotours     Steve Perillo hides from repeat customers who bring up the thorny issue of SEXUAL… https://t.co/Ilzvko71KG]]></document><document><![CDATA[BATMAN!!!! #wizardworldcomiccon #wizardworldcleveland #kevinconroy #batman @ Huntington Convention Center of Clevel… https://t.co/PBdMgJewH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another low point? This special not airing live. And all the so-called "singers" who were there because they wanted… https://t.co/Ioo5akadq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KIRORadio @shannondrayer @TMobilePark @Mariners @mattpitman Do they do pedicures?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sha is so dammmm fake. Like all she does all day is kiss all the girls ass. #ExOnTheBeach]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE SHEETS ARENT CLEAN. I WANT TO BARf. Good thing I got “upgraded” to a suite and I have a couch I can cover with… https://t.co/7VCOuza2Nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[“you’re standing over there, and your standing over there, and I don’t know which way is up.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also I feel for her and her relationship with her mom. I grew up with a narcissistic parent. They just want to feel… https://t.co/6O1nSv2QWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miz_Rosenberg Actual conversation when I was his research assistant: Me: Professor Dickinson? MD: You know, you ca… https://t.co/eWzVylwwpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My God My God!! Heartless and my tears are rolling!! If anyone can't see the evilness of this, then they too are ev… https://t.co/fs1Q1IPeE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrgentPart2 There's not one dog on this list who wouldn't make a wonderful PTSD companion dog... Your murdering potential heroes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheeseheadlucy @PressSec How does she walk with balls that big to state that blatant lie with a straight face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamuraiSam17 Also. Stupidity generallyvdoesn't exclude one from parenthood. Obviously someone had and raised you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing Largo High students how EZ Rock Nupes ride it out 👌🏾 #Achievement #KAPsi #NupesDoItBest https://t.co/Ykc5RaIk0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uvi Poznansky: Alice caged in a strange, fish-eye world: https://t.co/B4RF6eGhAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND THEN ONE DAY SHE REALIZED SHE COULD. . She could let go of all of the beliefs that held her back. . She could n… https://t.co/dwMoUym6U1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LightfootForChi @toniforchicago OMG I’m so glad you made it to the runoffs!! Congrats!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want to have kids in a world where vaccines exist but there are people in a first world country too stupid to use them. 😑😑😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Betcha if anything where the #UsMovie is gonna be like Get Out; where they make the trailer seems like a horror fil… https://t.co/MrZqEuim89]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucson Police Department investigating mysterious 'white powder'.  🤣🤣🤣💙🚓💙  https://t.co/f6hxIfmet4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a rough start to the morning. Forgot to set my alarm but luckily I got myself up on time, my coffee wasn’t made… https://t.co/YNlBbD7NX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I can’t wait for @IamTitusShowers single to drop in March!!! You really blessed us on yesterday! #Forward… https://t.co/D7nqXGe82X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Maintenance Person I" at HMSHost? Apply even if you're not a 100% match. You might… https://t.co/rlRVgTblG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister swears I’m a heavy sleeper but I’m actually just ignoring her 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I can think about today is Boogie T tomorrow. Can’t wait to see you @boogietmusic 🖤🖤🕺🏻🕺🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ❤️ the fact that 7on7 brings the entire nation together.. so beautiful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a slap in the face to all of our heroes and their families fighting for our values under our flag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bout to drive down to Daytona to celebrate not even kidding. https://t.co/Lm9lzERa0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJGlenn @KLEINOAKFB YES!!  So who are you going to challenge?!?! Gotta keep this thing going! Know anyone else that’s #ALLIN ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its been over 9 months I just want my old messages back https://t.co/XLMc7PHSwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhammy_love You can’t be coming for Leo’s like that &amp; not expect us to come for you https://t.co/ILBLCRfgMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra But she isn't Governor just like you are not President.  But you don't understand that either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennkirschner2 @WajahatAli @UPonMSNBC @UpPastryPlate @PastryPlate @MSNBC @davidgura Found it encouraging that MSM… https://t.co/scB3DitSeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This scene is going to slay me 😭 #AfterMovie #AnnaTodd #AfterBook https://t.co/VGj8DaPvVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[As an undergrad (‘98-‘99), I wrote a thesis examining confessional poetry—and specifically the work of Plath, Lowel… https://t.co/NMWSwpnL8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blake: I was really self conscious when I was in college, I was bullied as a child  Me: bullied by who?? do I need… https://t.co/FpJ6eScb0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could listen to @katyperry as Gus Gus all day 🤣😂#talent #americanidol https://t.co/nGU6DEq1Sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RyersonSA Book Exchange happening now until 1:30pm in POD-60 🙂📚 #SAwellness https://t.co/IXLB9gQurW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could say so much but I’m just gonna keep my mouth shut   Calladita me veo más bonita ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They are the American People's intelligence agencies.  Why are grouchy old men so enamoured of Rus… https://t.co/7zXUfXQ7Yf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvEsquiress The Portland anti-fa crowd tends to behave the exact way you would expect a group of teenagers who hav… https://t.co/CgGyPP2tCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely chance to recharge and listen to another senator at Politico Playbook. #sxsw #sxnoms #sxdrinks https://t.co/atX9cnqbU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moonkat1234 @iowamamaof3 @KKellynnG @Me_Cennet @smoking_reedus @wwwbigbaldhead @linalan96 @legitDottieO… https://t.co/dEgoc56C1j]]></document></documents></author>