<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thanks @jmandal99 for speaking to “Assessing AI &amp; Computational Technologies” class in San Francisco today! 22… https://t.co/QjgrbeHd7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well today’s the day right after work I’m heading to Cali 💪🏽👌🏽🔥 so excited ❤️❤️ #California #vacation #apple #]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want everyone to know that @walmart styles the people behind the camera. If you didn’t know, now you know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quinton_clarke I took Luke cause at least he was cocky/careless when he took the L. Aldo tried his hardest and ate… https://t.co/AfZRKAN0SW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notevenvegan earl vs tyler is on there and they don’t rap the same at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[as all will Miss Heidi Klum on America's Got Talent we wish her the best we'll miss all the funny things used to do… https://t.co/t0hyR0Npyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phyllisj1003 Two come to mind, one in Central America,one in Southeast Asia . No names.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies... great gift for your KING!!  Gentlemen... 🍻 @yeticoolers thanks 🙏🏼 nalah0615 thanks for a lifetime of cold… https://t.co/yXnrrT5oQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay this one was just for a cute lil holiday shoot, me as joker and my friend as Harley (they're gonna be my five… https://t.co/l2RjIrAO0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else editing a hooorible fantasy? I’m going to finish this edit again and again, even if it kills me! My mus… https://t.co/8jYKCWYswj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marylin13_ Greeter calling for a checkout for us all mad cause we get to leave https://t.co/Ck57USTXYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaBannister11 @RyanAFournier Hillary would do anything for a dollar bill. So don't even go there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on finalizing my first beat but this dude was really persistent about getting a taste so I kinda had to jus… https://t.co/kXpLKe0UR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACPinternists Rising drug costs, increasing drug copays, lack of formulary transparency and progressively narrower… https://t.co/2LaP7prPwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Alberto de Armas (Cemex) and all the team who made the idea of the “Digital Hub MTY” become a re… https://t.co/Q1IsFWFD8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Gpa I know you looking after me up there love you promise to make you proud 🙏🏼....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama threw his clubs and walked off course when they told him he wasn't keeping score Cheat cheat never beat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoChilds It’s such an addicting show! I’ve got...  Bee - Gladys Knight  Rabbit - Joey Fatone Lion - Rumer Willis P… https://t.co/PhDB7ezKoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot take: The socialism piece in New York Mag is awe inspiring. True art. Everyone played their roles perfectly.  Wouldn’t change a thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally less than 10 minutes 😬 #WhyDontWeMV @AustinMahone  ❤️❤️  🚀🚀 https://t.co/vD6ACsXnn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgramonteVictor @Jseriousaccount @CIAspygirl @davidmweissman I’ve lived in South Florida a long time and yes, ther… https://t.co/Znx3EP3734]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe they let us into the #MagicKingdom secret vaults #PandasGoToDisney https://t.co/qsEdo9LHv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally!  Some murders in this city don’t generate as much outrage from the public or as much media attention!  Why… https://t.co/IsXg7QwKmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KATCTV3 allegedly found 54 grams of powder cocaine, 12 grams of Methamphetamine, #METH #Evil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @charliekirk11 @SergioGor @TommyHicksGOP Kim is really trying to bec… https://t.co/VXaKWGVzIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuschwitzMuseum @Roseamund Sad, and if you trumpers don’t open your eyes, you’ll lose our democracy over turning a… https://t.co/L89q37FYXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noooo! El pastel #mynephew 😂😭💀 #birthdayboy #ViralVideos #VideoOfTheDay https://t.co/cFfqFINUpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F150SuperSnake @Bucktailes @ElleRguez @mnguy152 @panekbill @pensfannc5 @swinginberrys @mbabs21 @pcdebol… https://t.co/hfYGlRO7KE]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's 1 prediction that I got wrong, but I ain't mad. #WWEFastlane @WWE @WWENetwork @KingRicochet @WWEAleister… https://t.co/qrnW5qT5tT]]></document><document><![CDATA[FroKnowsPhoto is GIVING AWAY a CAMERA, LENS and MORE, hurry, get entered now!!! https://t.co/3D0jhPRZQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[a meme i find very funny but will probably never use is the “may i get a crumb of ___” meme thank you for your time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyLyons08 @lights don’t know what you mean haha but I live in Montreal so EST timezone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMKRIDE_Jon @MMAjunkie I mean.. 🙋🏼‍♂️ @Cowboycerrone , @TheNotoriousMMA ..  Whiskey, Beers, fists, two tough SOBs.… https://t.co/KV8xbJD42z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter Something "long distance", but not while I live in California. No more big ticket buys until I emig… https://t.co/ZIi1WG4DzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanMillward @CityOfCincy @pat_laFleur @WCPO It was starting to slide when I was driving home at 1am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If i wear this fit tonight, no one take pics with me. It’s getting recycled within 7 business days]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's go @dropkickmurphys !!! @ Lancaster County Convention Center Authority https://t.co/VhyTLpq9Hr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/IrP6vOCfbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jovanmhiII i was like four and bitmy sister and she put a fork into my face right above the eye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @OneArtsPlaza in Dallas, TX https://t.co/zvxE8Ar3O6 https://t.co/tSQbQRny47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmekler Gee you would think the small government party would be able to pull themselves up by their bootstraps a… https://t.co/z0rgvexV1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's stop pretending this was a good movie. It was not https://t.co/ZW75jkoZe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow is gone.  Let's get this season started.  #GameDay #OpeningDay #GoLobos https://t.co/EUcqnHvo5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axios Looks like someone made Pelosi a coloring book on how impeachment works.]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 teams from the Crossroads league are playing in the NAIA National Basketball tournament...5 of our men’s teams an… https://t.co/uXPTe3j1fM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veremos cuánto duran sin que AB se empiece a quejar que no le tiran y que no se qué]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not too funny when you realize photo was taken in 2009...he's thrilled 'agreement' w/ Hot Teacher got him bigly cro… https://t.co/650lhyFqXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que rico ser independiente, no tener que rendir cuentas de algo o alguien]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MackDaddy1002 @Alyssa_Milano BORDER SECURITY. ENEMY PRESS  I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on E… https://t.co/EQREBbV08z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisWeekABC @GStephanopoulos If so, then why did Trump and Ivanka and Abbe Lowell all lie and say that Trump playe… https://t.co/4Hk2CZJq1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennkirschner2 @chucktodd @MSNBC @tribelaw @neal_katyal I was thinking… policy is always subject to revision… wha… https://t.co/A7D8rnsNlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVacchianoSNY Shurmur should brace to be fired as a HC again. If he believes Eli has years left, not only is he de… https://t.co/tk4U4Q0RCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's time for some 80's musical comedy romance! Did you RSVP for The Wedding Singer at @ob_playhouse 🎤💍💞🎶🎭 Well, if… https://t.co/Ur8SbAHVcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheLLbeLL_xo @MiKullBouchard Her motion reminds me of this...https://t.co/6x8OE9Orjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SantaAnaPD Arrestan a Sospechoso acusado de supuestos abusos sexuales de 5 victimas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AceHotel #Rooftop! Appreciate the 80 degree weather! @ Ace Hotel New Orleans https://t.co/dQ857cZ7df]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my latest article on @RisingAppleBlog where I dive deep into Jacob deGrom’s odd stats at opposing ball pa… https://t.co/61wBwgOxSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy bday to @PABruinFootball 4 time FB state champion @LayneHatcher ! Proud of your hard work @AlabamaFTBL ! Repr… https://t.co/wdXlmpxCks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissherm2 can i send you money for shipping?? or can i just send you something madonna in return?? both easier t… https://t.co/BhzkW2Mgfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBigCat just when you thought the dab was dead https://t.co/sMNKQekRH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching this on the big screen is always such a treat. I wanna dive into the screen for that final scene. Thanks f… https://t.co/kMF5uoFeuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolfweekRingler No, just go to a rolling checkpoint system.  If you don’t make 2 consecutive checkpoint times, you… https://t.co/a8W0ymNkKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My body feels like I went to a Brazilian steakhouse and ate all of the meat tonight... which makes sense because th… https://t.co/x5bfwCc2P8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was talking to a pretty girl once and she mentioned one time that she was violent. As in lose her temper and swin… https://t.co/VlnOEO6Olv]]></document><document><![CDATA[please feel free to contact us for more details email: bettertoy@yeah.net website: https://t.co/V8qzgsiTFt whatsapp: 0086 15538152259]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TakeThatStraw Why do you repeat yourself over and over , you have to stop hitting the bong lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the fact that he could not be silenced, and won again when the attempt was made to limit his earning potential… https://t.co/8neFbjPeEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kangaroos have THREE Vaginas... but don’t care for Paragliders...  #TradeOffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @AceMeeks @Jantxnc @jonz970 @reillyzona @sgmb7781 @clovis1931 @MQpatriot @IndeCardio @Cleanman0… https://t.co/sGkHSWzQJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re-Focused Bulldogs Head to Ole Miss for Thursday Battle https://t.co/nCWm7j8hgg via @247sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TropicalTidbits Can you remember seeing this with deep-layer shear, too? Seems like part of it might be the shear-… https://t.co/OLZE8fLgBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrayforDale @LucilleBurdge Kirk..i mean dale...u are too fucking funny https://t.co/CgYFnesdrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do NOT think it’s sexy when I see gays on twitter in scrubs or a firefighter uniform with their dicks out! Do your job!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Played Kingdom Hearts 1. Played #KingdomHearts 2.  @SquareEnix with Kingdom Hearts 3: Yeah, you definitely have… https://t.co/TlYx4sP1ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's true, it's so so true. I'm so so guilty of loving Friday pizza day too much 😍  #FriYay #PizzaDay #Flat #Square… https://t.co/BkI0wC7BF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched this last weekend. It includes a mention of a Gary Hart campaign stop in #FortWayne in 1987, apparently c… https://t.co/x0LZTnZXxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Sorry James I’m out of sick time and don’t want a write up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What part of, that this is a  "Clear and Present Danger" to this Country don't they COMPREHEND?  O… https://t.co/1bXKWvOAEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a good time at the #hlsrcookoff2019 @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/yNvJXajjSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoneStarCraig @mitchellvii @Redeemed1952 You missed the point of the question. If you support Democrats, then you… https://t.co/vPI0LAAJtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Endymion Day! Love this time of the year! @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/My61AiBiZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[When democracy’s for sale and oversight’s been outsourced to cronies, there’s no end to the type of deals people wi… https://t.co/wT4SCL8T4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pessoas chamam de semestre, eu chamo de puta que o pariu o que aconteceno?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sam_isd Lady Rebs' Brinlee jointly claims all-district #txhshoops top sixth person https://t.co/eudaNuy8kc… https://t.co/j5J41ECvmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halcyondon @tklforgiven @The_Ouroboros__ @michellmybell1 @commonsensejan @surgerysleeper @TedPerkins10 @TertiusIII… https://t.co/jgmUFeeaYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“By any definition these few companies don’t function like corporate entities. They exist as social movements.” Thi… https://t.co/7e9xSCZa89]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GayRepublicSwag And by 530pm, I am ready for dinner. Bed time at 730pm!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteAbe Just shocking and horrible news. Thoughts and love to his family...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmoser @ProjectLITComm Thank you so much for coming and for letting me put you on the spot! @mmoser]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Giuseppe's Bar &amp; Grille - @giuseppeslv in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/McGy0AbGiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@singlesoberlife Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[The man who threatened to nuke Americans, is mad about a headline that doesn’t even mean what he wants it to. What… https://t.co/jJCXVhfiSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkihiroArsene no shade but I've lost 2 "best friends" over changing fandoms like it's so mf sad how shallow people are]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mixinwithmintz 3:20 @38Godfrey 3:40 @kanemcguire 4:00 @TBob53 5:00 @SmartestMoran 5:20 @fox4sportstalk #MixinItUp #KnockinRoundTheZoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Silver_Buck @TxEx @tjfxh @DeficitOwls @StephanieKelton @CNBC Agree it will be rough. But we have to question their… https://t.co/QITM4on0aK]]></document><document><![CDATA[me in the LF bleachers when manny takes his first AB at camden with the friars https://t.co/UoPNXZsZk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N0TF0RN0THING @ScottAdamsSays .@MichaelSteele has lost all sense of intelligence. This is my take: https://t.co/SWOA8TryRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just bc she fine doesn’t mean she’s good for his mental health y’all never realize that and that’s why y’all misera… https://t.co/l50ZfPhY57]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at that point in this Minnesota winter where my shoveling is ‘that’s good enough’.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to dispatch atgmiami @ Sherman Oaks, California https://t.co/52hOEyYwsp]]></document></documents></author>