<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@klingershow , I have 4 plunger in my house! Hit me up if you need one?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Order 🍕🍟pizza fries🍟🍕 and more exclusively through Mobile Food Order delivery on the Universal Orlando App to the M… https://t.co/xcVyMMjf9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Porsche should be embarrassed. Price difference is about $10 trillion! Imagine if it was a MS with Luda!!! 🤣😂🤣😂🤣😂🤣… https://t.co/7vR0zf90BH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kdrak I’d be an NHL player if all my Easton sticks didn’t keep breaking in high school. But you don’t see me complaining]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luz_Cuba Empieza el entrenamiento para convertirlos en esclavos al servicio de la cuenta de banco de la familia Ca… https://t.co/xbJXFsGqIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CGasparino If you know the answer why don't you just tell the friend what it is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL SERÁ EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Y… https://t.co/KQ0xGcVydJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClayTravis I think he probably is paying his players. But that’s an assumption based on evidence that’s purely cir… https://t.co/HV2IU2iVNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckeejm Haha it's the most wonderful store in the city IMO. Bought some camera gear and today 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaitvukovich @taylorswift13 Old Taylor is dead and new one is coming for my SCALP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is this organization and the awesome volunteers who grew my love for the golf to the point that I'm willing to f… https://t.co/iF9gDOMCJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthSoundShane Yeah pretty much. 1st half was promising but obvs didn't turn out well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdnansMind Autism is worse than measles’s but vaccines don’t cause autism so anti-vax people are absolutely ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY ÓSCAR SUNDAY! With it being Óscar Sunday here are my top 10 movies of 2018 AND my Óscar picks for today.  It’… https://t.co/Cy8IhIDV51]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendaryEnergy I was just talking with a guy, making $9.00 per hour.  said he was hoping they make UBI a reality… https://t.co/xb6pfTwiAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temo más a la actitud de los Venezolanos que al mismo momento que estamos por vivir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer Donnie, you’ve been a bad, bad boy...and you’re going to prison in the end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five reasons #Raiders trade for Antonio Brown was a winner . . . https://t.co/JUrwbspkQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertMurdock11 @HLAurora63 When Juan the white man hater is on ....I go out n pick up dog crap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meekwire @Doctrine_Man The veterans serving in Congress haven’t made our nation’s policies in Afghanistan, Yemen,… https://t.co/h8sJyyG5ja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JShu_ I don’t think he’s a “bad” coach but when it’s his time to shine as a coach he’s always doing some dumb shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LasVegasUK @VitalVegas I don't sit at the bars to much anymore even with the light system.they are taking the enjo… https://t.co/ZupHbEOt8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take Weekend Update and cross it with the Futurama alien newscasters. That’s #AlienNewsDesk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy argue about the Hodge Trophy and who should win it without having a clue about the criteria for which the winner is determined season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boxersforlife @KAG4All This is what these socialist idiots are telling kids. They are creating a generation of laz… https://t.co/zuOMYr7rlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune in to the finals mat for the @NHIAA_LOA Meet of Champions at @nashuaathletics on the @NFHSNetwork and… https://t.co/m90UFAiBBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brian Viloria has transitioned to being a trainer,  works daily at the Churchill Gym. Has a nice stable already...… https://t.co/Vcq9XpD5rB]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔸🔸Nuts Money Call🔸🔸 🔸🔸  🌰      💵      ☎ 🔸🔸 ▫️ 5TH PART ▫️ 🔸 There we go again!  Fifth part that talks about going b… https://t.co/CRHfjU2fzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 92% Off Services at Elevation Chiropractic &amp; Wellness https://t.co/nXtcw60179]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are proud of you! They say college changes people. . . .in a good way for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#music #love #art #like #follow #instagood #hiphop #rap #dj #instagram #photooftheday #life #photography #fashion… https://t.co/lEr5FBw4Ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FABERGANZA @jkimgt En eso estamos de acuerdo. Yo hablo del sueño de poner centros de estudios avanzados para perso… https://t.co/uKcBtOq1Y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF THE LORD IS WILLING, IF I EVER GET THE WONDERFUL PRIVILEGE OF RAISING KIDS, I VOW TO MYSELF AND GOD THEY WILL BE… https://t.co/mUifSYaIoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to work early on Valentine’s Day is always a reminder of the need for some sweet snacks to make it through the night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToniTonit6 @BenSFletcher I don’t fall for Russian propaganda. I listen to the candidates, I follow policy. I for s… https://t.co/5uPCaj4Fdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Art Music Education  AEM  What if I inserted an   I  https://t.co/bOWLttznji  There   iAem the @Target   Someone el… https://t.co/KLIbGBjgOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@restorationpac @DougJones @Hfluit I can't believe it's a question.the fetus /baby has a right to life according to GOD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loleeaahh Mercy, and I thought Weimar was devoid of logic. This is so illogical it sounds like a joke 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UX no-no: 2 hamburger menus with no labels. This is no different than repeating the word "Menu" twice on each side… https://t.co/Z7XtutzPHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillBeckerman @RWJMS @VascularSVS @AmBdSurg @AmCollSurgeons @nj_acs Fantastic stuff! I also love that more women a… https://t.co/tcOEEotp7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@option_snipper @ChazAltitude @TradeWithNinja @SimpleTrader1 @BenAltitude @HiddenPivots https://t.co/AcN1NtsBnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t mind please say a prayer for me around 4:00 today. I really need a miracle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcrow_baby @PhilipRucker @goldengateblond @jdawsey1 I mean this guy has no bottom. When will you realize you’ve be… https://t.co/M7NnEDPCDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We Stan this mini skirt” -me putting away clothes after quietly ghosting on my friends’ art openings downtown]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @OversightDems Your a disgrace..it’s people like you Rashida Tlaib whom promote nasty manufactured li… https://t.co/F7r5YFUZYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diga lo que diga, en concierto es uno de los mejores, simplemente espectacular.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored and excited to welcome Retired 4-star General and former Commander of Air Force Space Command, Lance Lord t… https://t.co/JNTmUEpB8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo te llevo dentro, hasta la raíz Y por más que crezca, vas a estar aquí]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwetsBizarros @TodoEsJoda @SucioGato @reverendaperra @TotumaStereo @SoyTuPadrastro @Roxkleis Estamos invalidados p… https://t.co/lrXZgwCOiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportSciSum @JFEsculier @AJM_Rambaud @clare_ardern @BJSM_BMJ @bcphysio @amsmcsportmed @sportphysiocan Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Great Sight! #lauderdalebythesea #bikeride #peaceful @ Lauderdale-by-the-Sea, Florida https://t.co/y9SkycreJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t see how Adam only gets one year, three mill?  What am I missing? @SimplyAJ10  ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @realDonaldTrump NoKo always wanted a seat @ the table.  They don't deserve a seat @ the table]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toomuchcountry Schaefer on tap? You may have to get here early for 600! https://t.co/GmtHz2LPYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Culpable son los “periodistas” como tú, que un dia son lambe bolas de un jugador o equipo y al otro dia, tienen que… https://t.co/sFOcUQVWX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is driving around a snowstorm while listening to Sade on your day off a 30 year old thing to do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo on the real idgaf who I offend but Caribbean people and I mean Haitian, Jamaican, Trinidad yea all you motherfuc… https://t.co/WQur9m0dXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Prairiehauler @jrow9670 @Cornfrmr @silagechopper @FabionPicheco Hard to get a handy in the cab of that bad boy]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of dolfster for getting his first tattoo! Thank you salstattoo and gregkidd73 for such a great job! I know… https://t.co/lAJNuIuX6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arsenal Rose put his studs in Leno's chest and missed the ball! Shocking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Art inspired by #Health #Black #Static #God is coming #Fuck your #Armageddon https://t.co/N5Hjv7YwgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loski_3pointO @Bhelseyy Yup, whip it with a spoon not a fork. Cook it on medium low.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am loving the backlash from Hummels, Boateng, and Müller. These guys have done so much and do not deserve to be t… https://t.co/sZx7pdkoBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been sick and been in contact with my teacher and she promised to help me but here I am not being helped wasting time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's go! #Bernie2020 #BernieInIowa #BernieSanders2020 #FeelTheBern https://t.co/N8xaBFPLKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got new leggings from @PopFitClothing and they are AMAZING!!! The pockets are so deep I love it https://t.co/JoPvG1E27u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Citizenkwarren I agree but for me one of the few I prefer the whites. Winged wheel is a beauty]]></document><document><![CDATA[This coming from an Irish newspaper just proves what goes around comes around. @IrishTimes #BrexitShambles #Brexit… https://t.co/5tCNzN7Edg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @MissAngSays I remember putting a penny on the stylus to fix a skipping record.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you in favor of Maine joining the lawsuit against the Trump  Administration? I voted Yes on WCSH. What's your v… https://t.co/63lgoqNTSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is good when you have friends like I do. Thank you @icedteadamon parkmgm ontherecordlv @novacancyla @ufc for a… https://t.co/e6LtgfNn97]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElPincheJuan4 @cero3801 @yorguinho58 @GorillaMan06 @davidant264 @2booty2muscle @BootyAndMuscles @TittyFucker411… https://t.co/Wgwiuo1N8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bath room scale has me 10 pounds lighter. Guess it doesn't need those new batteries after all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Fake social media news has tried to fabricate and lie and spread rumors about the #ThickBoys and even tried to… https://t.co/AIoU9hxSqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hiitaylorlynn @AnnaTaughtYou thanks for making me feel like part of the family ☺️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really should bother more people that Trump gets along better w/ scum like KJU, Duterte, and Bolsonaro than he d… https://t.co/exvAiW7SyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boston, MA: YMCA, unwrapping Valentine gifts from Sister Virginia, Florida resident and family member. Late, of cou… https://t.co/UgswqDty2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[That time when you eat a hot onion rings and a cold slushy then burn your mouth and get a brain freeze. @ Suffolk C… https://t.co/dIWIThNypk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VulgamoreRyan He’s playing in Buckeye Storm 7th grade. Had his first practice this past Monday. Thanks for helping… https://t.co/bSKkNDTocK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so I have 3 names to choose from with my new traveling companion and @WynonnaEarp fans get to pick the name they like best for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t say enough positive things about the HRL ground crew and service agents! With an early AM flight this team ma… https://t.co/cPm6zTzCp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MannyDouglas419 @Rollicking_R8R @PhilRobinsonNFL @NewKungFuKenny I'm gonna say the pro bowl is a winning teams pop… https://t.co/sTchVxB8o8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BorisGrantham Siempre el pez grande se harta al pequeño, ya vendrá uno más grande que el perate!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bruins_stats Replies here case in point-some concerned about extensions for less-impactful players to validate eagerness to shed ZC cap hit]]></document><document><![CDATA[when a girls XL jacket is warmer than yours 🥶✌🏽 @ Wisp Resort https://t.co/bot9aRf4jD]]></document><document><![CDATA[VE-ra-JO-nes 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻!!  #B1G #Hoops #Tipoff #LetsGo https://t.co/QKbViJzsdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, to say it was a little amped up in there last night, would be an understatement. It was awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Directed my final newscast at KQ2 tonight. @alanvanzandt and @mikebracciano have been here since long before my fir… https://t.co/RNRwaDIXq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarpeDonktum @jonfitchdotnet This Jussie guy makes me sick. Now I’m laughing at him. @JussieSmollett you had it comin. You deserve it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbyk52 You're right, those Dordt games were wild 😉  But seriously, I'm not used to this kind of success for Iowa.… https://t.co/L9lq7JgBVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ernie_Webb_3 @adidas Cheating is cheating Ernie....”losers focus on winners, winners focus on winning”. You clearl… https://t.co/yiV29TXSdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[6-0 Mustangs run and NY lead down to 35-34. 3:13 left and Mustangs have ball. NY has led since second quarter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is this idea that men are some sort of minority that can be subjugated or framed for things when the interest… https://t.co/QeEr0PHsah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 @zerocutster_AK @voxdotcom Tonight Robert Kraft is in LA at Oscar parties, that's GOP power in action 😡 https://t.co/synQnAUCWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bmw0916Heart @17Thanq @Heywood98 @DDog0311 @jlbeldin @Tonyandsannonw2 @my3monkees @MAJMO50 @RStieben @45Quickdraw4… https://t.co/fogLoHluDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi What a joke you are Pelosi you and your goon gang voted for and support killing baby girls after bun… https://t.co/Xhlp6vjL95]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Star Is Born - I've been screaming, literally screaming for someone to do what @mehdirhasan is doing. He's aggres… https://t.co/8YoM1npo6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the last Wednesday of each month, mrsbborel and I are privileged to lead, along with our incredible team, our Dy… https://t.co/LRiHlkJnWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_Mahfood The world of Batman: TAS continued in Justice League and Justice League Unlimited. And technically t… https://t.co/FRJz3GwDNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your face had been crying You were ravaged by jealousy You said, look what love has done to me" We can slip out t… https://t.co/12C72By4sR]]></document></documents></author>