<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RudisColby Facts. Zion would’ve made it a closer game but UNC outdid Duke in everything. We will see March 9th whe… https://t.co/IvU5MO3EQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week’s evening office.   #mammamia @ Williamsport Area High School https://t.co/Oio6KDU7MN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle wow, what show were you watching? #Spokelee was clearly the most memorable one. but nice try at denial.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @washingtonpost @jguaido Sad clown @marcorubio upset his coup ain't working #SadClownMarco… https://t.co/t4SHF3S4vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judging time! A lot of time and prep went into this, by @Cullen4EDU and the students/teachers! https://t.co/qOprI6Ydqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FMF @ESPNCapitanes @ESPNRF por qué abrieron una carpeta de investigación para Sosa, por decir la verdad ?? Por les… https://t.co/iFr5LCUnVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And thus begins the work week: Drive from Hickory to Kettering, Ohio, Uber to Columbus, drive to Marietta, GA, Uber… https://t.co/4j1IeZiEtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BootscootinGMaw @IHboog @TracyLCotton @scoopermomma @thebirdfarmer @birdfarmerswife @dbatie @FarmChicJodi… https://t.co/nslm33FjaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[bedtime.  wishes:sweet dreams, healing, impeach the douches, kamala;cory or julian to become president, bernie to d… https://t.co/yZLVEPrBc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandontonlu @Iivid @bszphoto I know that’s the second time this week so here’s back when I used to only take pict… https://t.co/5ZqkzCnVdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexdgreenfield @JoshJHess Oh Lord, what did you do now?  I'ma watchin' it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sourkrause23 @RealMNchiefsfan That's an entirely different story altogether but no, Aldon had serious issues both… https://t.co/ZBg8tCGmcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @elonmusk @Tesla  here’s some positive vibes sent your way today to help deal with the sec! You’re doi… https://t.co/iNqxKBWAtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great benefits to Level-1 Whey Protein 1.    Best tasting meal replacement. 2.    Fuels your body to help repair an… https://t.co/48iUx9mNr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Indians @MLBNetwork Really hope you guys pull some magic to lock both them up long term]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever sent a text and then say to yourself “yeah I fucked that up” ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faxxxx I miss all the homegirls I had when I had the Benz and the studio and was booking regularly. I wonder what h… https://t.co/C7juKnCEpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign this petition to demand Congress repeal the Trump-GOP Tax Scam for the Rich. Sign here: https://t.co/0odsNLidTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nick_McGurk @AWorldOutOfMind They're terrible Obama and Reid shouldn't have allowed to McConnell to bully them lik… https://t.co/TE4r5nUDIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay a lot of you are being dumb as hell on here, I'm gonna give you the weekend to get it all out of your system a… https://t.co/DMpDbI8K14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesantiMichael @DBrunoEsq If they were wrestling women and like guys do slap on ass or Peck and they did it for a… https://t.co/QRxjlVfY8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConardCaleb @beckercarson @Brody_Lawhun33 @NathanMontgom11 @sam_elliott2241 Maybe next year you can dunk in game👀✊🏼🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Besides meeting Sunday in Chicago in the @B1GMBBall Tournament Final, @MSU_Basketball and @umichbball could both st… https://t.co/gpoGGn8jpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My review of HAUNTED HOLLYWOOD https://t.co/rZigMOnQY2 @AFizgig @stevecourtney79 @flixology101 @bonkersasscin… https://t.co/3XePY7FP48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AjLemons @FINALLEVEL Tell me something girl, r u happy in this modern world?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when you’re standing in line and the person behind you is uncomfortably close]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got my iPhone replaced at Apple! Don’t like this tweet. Don’t retweet it. Just text me your numbers ‼️🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hookemcougs That’s weird. How can one wait 3 hours to watch a game already played? 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanMatte Interesting to think that Microsoft has now shipped x86 emulators on Itanium, PPC (Xbox 360), and ARM64 T… https://t.co/arVO8ABk00]]></document><document><![CDATA[boys.. Turns out.. her pussy wasn’t air gapped... found some other users on the server :(((]]></document><document><![CDATA[PCPS will open 2 hrs late on Wednesday (2/20/19). We will check road conditions in the morning and announce any change in status by 7 am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[one small positive thought in the morning can set the tone for your whole day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t believe I’ve ever seen Michelle swear on social media! But sometimes Bullshit needs to be called!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hughes is unloading a ton of 3s which is rarely a bad thing. 3/8 but has 13 of #syracuse's 47 points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely spot on. One of those laws should be that no close family member of a sitting congressman should be work… https://t.co/X1BEj04mIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love me some @MorganCWallen music, but here in East Tennessee we do not need anymore rain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yonnatancriollo @asoprorin @OficialINH El miedo muchas veces es más fuerte que el amor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tackling corruption is not going to be easy because the entire system is now woven into it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it April yet? @SportyDivaAE #SALF #LearnLead #GreenTeam https://t.co/XMMXDpFM4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 2nd favorite place to eat (in the states)... ☝🏼🇺🇸 #OldEbbittGrill @oldebbitt https://t.co/iLeJu8Ghiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like I need to be following #TrevorConEden.  Anyone got his social media handle?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole thing came from the top, O and HC set it all in motion, they need to be in jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenidraRWoods_ Look back over your life especially at the times when you struggled but came through it. When you d… https://t.co/ei2pVaQ5aZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[As someone who actually, honestly, waited to drink until I was 21, I feel like I actually have the right to comment… https://t.co/73erWBIdYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ky_33 @GailYou72514463 The #Longhorns just need to finish the job anyway sweep LSU. I have had peace from Aggies/S… https://t.co/hZLgaWjB02]]></document><document><![CDATA[The criminal/radical lefties have wasted huge sums of taxpayer money trying to find dirt on our prez.  They have wa… https://t.co/Hzpi9UnoTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shoholanana @POTUS @DonaldJTrumpJr Another friend of Trump involved in sex crimes with girls forced into sex slave… https://t.co/8iDiXvd2Ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starr_abel @_QuitaBee @iamdelva Queen you are right. Nothing wrong with being a plumber an honest living.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeySmoke14 screaming loud as I can from California!  #GoBucks https://t.co/btMFzKfFFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayBilas said in my book, “Beyond the Streak” (shameless plug, sorry) that Kansas’ run of 14 straight Big 12 title… https://t.co/yWwCrovIhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonBialy @DEADLINE @Variety Woooo! Kudos for being able to not spill the beans on such awesome and exciting new… https://t.co/uVaklUVUST]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had an amazing time with these amazing students. #p1day Thanks for letting me join in. Love the wok of… https://t.co/IX2iWPjNOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uncle_Jimbo @andrew52220582 @JerryNadler @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr Whaaaaaah' Whaaaaah' Whaaaaaah' you are… https://t.co/6MgbLlVH40]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did it this morning lol @ U.S. Naval Station Mayport https://t.co/ILRQFbvHwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kerryb214 @RepMattGaetz @FRCdc @tperkins Trump's all too brief absence has been a godsend in that it has served to… https://t.co/fzKuMfXjKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbaAdventureNY That's the dream. I'll check out your vids and maybe we can get our crews to ski together some day. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No entiendo como le siguen dando importancia a lo que dicen VFQ y FCH....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Party 🎉 Tonight @djfive with Me 3/7 @Letzgitit at #taonightclub Nightclub Lets Git It inside #venetianlasvegas Thur… https://t.co/5LMvN4z7l6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This pic gets me every time!  Thank you to the homer fund and THD for taking care of our fellow associates]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seabolt73 @Sowokeitswoke @Amy_Siskind @JussieSmollett LMAO Yikes! LOLOL When did we land on the moon? When was the… https://t.co/9aPoTrMSPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see my Alma Mater @MDCollege assists students with food insecurities! We also established the @uofcincy Be… https://t.co/iGWq8uscPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelleyVSiN @spshoot Yeah free agency will be crucial before I go making any big boasts lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be listening only to T-Pain and Gladys Knight for the next week. Thanks @MaskedSingerFOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/CDjUdwxVBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciating the versatility of @NBCNews @PeterAlexander who yesterday asked @realDonaldTrump about his Nat'l emerg… https://t.co/SZMwTZPbUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherStormLA @TullamoreDEWUS @ManSeeksAdventr @sevengrand Looking good girl!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wolf pack in da house 🤟🏽⚾️⚾️⚾️🔥🔥🔥#👍🏼🤟🏽✌🏽🙏🏼⚾️🔥❤️ @ Indio, California https://t.co/WKxGCXuhGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tidalwave7705 My mama still got the whole set and every thanksgiving and Christmas meal since I was a kid has been… https://t.co/Eld9E322O4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mdessary59 @Yuwantokno1 @AOC I'm English, I just live in Texas. Hope that helps?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordyMyShorty @RapSheet They can talk and negotiate as of 1 minute ago but nothing can be official till Wednesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[burst out laughing and move on. This person who knows exactly what's happening. | 17 Perfect Responses For When Som… https://t.co/6mo0vm2Uwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Newark Liberty International Airport in Newark, NJ https://t.co/ws8SSYsb6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s snow coming ❄️ @ New Hope–Lambertville Bridge https://t.co/BsoVc2oSBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @realDailyWire democrats should really love her I hope they do because it really makes me sick and… https://t.co/CQ6JcRyP01]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eitanhersh I guess I don’t learn good. I voted yes. It’s a political gamble, true, but I’ll take HR1 + Green New D… https://t.co/lViY2dolJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught up with Vrabel after his double (!) plunge. Here’s what he had to say: https://t.co/8SGCvr9NXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[These beautiful, talented, amazing humans filled my heart to overflowing this weekend with the way they brought the… https://t.co/C9qMJjK15B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Allies wary of Shanahan's assurances with looming presence of Trump https://t.co/oB7CaA4nM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cr38ivCasey 😡🧞‍♀️😡they were SO sure that Hillary was going to win , they didn’t even hide their dirt and win she l… https://t.co/BBWL33QF7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[11315-11331 Santa Monica Blvd 11315-11331 Santa Monica Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90025 https://t.co/7IEaLK7fUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello @Twitter @TwitterSupport please have someone contact @RalstonReports so he can be @verified thanks its 3/8/19 already]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @WWE was smart the would do The Club vs The Shield the right way come one WWE out the boys back together… https://t.co/LHbMLZASjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Snaggletooth Bandana by @solemnoathbeer @ Dubuisson Bar and Grill — https://t.co/pRGqrjKQeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@13thconcept_ She made an ignorant statement. You are attempting to defend ignorance. Why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonloftis @kindofstrange I figured that must be it. It certainly didn’t look like an account that would block you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I prayed this morning, the word "Simplicity" reverberated in my thoughts.  It pressed on me heavily but in a goo… https://t.co/cnu54Ycpe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@domenictiso4 @Franklin_Graham It is also true that science cannot study what us occurring "inside" a lightning bol… https://t.co/Ia4tLg4snT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StraVenadita Seguro no tienen papá, ni esposos, hay Jos, hermanos, ni siquiera traidos. Daddy issues? FIJO!! Y qué… https://t.co/njLTNpz1E3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsungSupport I just bought a dryer model DV45K6500 is their an alternate part number for the WiFi adapter to use… https://t.co/HrQexfcBt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy international womans day to all the amazing , strong , independent , beautiful ladies I know out there.  #TooManyToList]]></document><document><![CDATA[Health and Strength @ Yamacraw Beach Estate, New Providence, Bahamas https://t.co/ofyPiCPCAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 14420 Beatties Ford Road #Huntersville #NC  #realestate https://t.co/bL0SXIsH3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoCalLyn1 A belt is good to have, but I only wear them for maxing out weight. I was not wearing one here. If you u… https://t.co/0id4v9RFw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECISDAP @JaimeBoswell2 @Tabchoops @THSCAcoaches @hoopinsider Thank you Mrs. Surber!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianelovesAmeri @Jenn198523 I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Way better to have.  Day1USA HISTORY 3/… https://t.co/CtiAo6PM2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love doing laundry at an obscenely late hour knowing my clothes will likely take 3, hour long cycles to dry😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t cut the cord but I look at Facebook far less often than I used to. That’s a good thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the two Curry bros, Seth of the Portland @trailblazers gets 16 and eliminates Middleton. Steph has his work… https://t.co/d10ZSU5tv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karimmature @RocketLeague its not my engine. i wasnt pressing anyhting other than the left joystick to look around… https://t.co/sg3DZtIDK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warm ups underway @NRHSGirlsBball vs. @NOlmstedEagles https://t.co/MRlaWb3bCT]]></document></documents></author>