<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Amigos gracias por acompañarme en #EdicionDigitalHouston este lunes festivo, día de los presidentes 🙋‍♀️Mientras mu… https://t.co/X3MXk9F3ZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Company Turns Kids’ Drawings Into Stuffed Plush Toys https://t.co/3EVNBUR4zq via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got the set flats painted. Next step - full day of school so they can have rehearsal!; March 22-23! #rowvastrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure to pick up some of these lovelies! Ill be selling and making them until Feb 28th (I'll be gone for a week… https://t.co/SYWo7GIZL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely love these Guys ! ❤️💯🙌🔥😉😘 @danmillerotown  @iamerikestrada #thecowan  #pop2000tour   #otwn #myFaveGuys… https://t.co/dEqr9I4jPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You'd have it made- if he woke up like Walter n demanded some mc nuggets. Don't forget his cheese burger too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They fought hard.  A joy to watch this team work together. Thank you seniors! #LHSBBall https://t.co/9xM3FIwccU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im sorry if I hit any pedestrians, I’m just so focused on avoiding being swallowed alive by a pothole]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrClearyKC well. if you ever decide to go sliver you knows who to call ;-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cborkowski @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump She has no idea what she’s talking about. Just another Trump cheerleader.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You must be in your late 50s because I remember the last time he wasn't a sexist, narcissistic, right-wing tool was… https://t.co/B8oGNB2bXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This means I either A) won't see Chris until then or B) see him for less than an hour on a few of the Fridays till then]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperDarkRose So glad someone took the time to ask him how to correctly pronounce his name. Shows interest in the… https://t.co/RFCKEvZEIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I Write the entire 🌍listen. Father God give me a extra slack To be me. No need to walk and run 🏃‍♀️at the same… https://t.co/YXzjpcJ5nb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Motherhood is sneaking into the bathroom at a fancy restaurant to use your breast pump on date night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all come back now, ya hear? #smashville#kimstours #streetart #girlstrip xx @kimbo_morris @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/biQLM7G2A5]]></document><document><![CDATA[29 Memes That Will Only Be Funny If You Remember The 80s. | Someecards Memes https://t.co/TrKVJMzYFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigDaddy_Don @WHEREISQUlNTEN They are getting $14+ per hour. Servers get $3.30 per hour because tipping is expecte… https://t.co/dm3BM1QQCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Love of My Life gave me this for Valentine's day❤💑💍 I love you💕 @RyBizzle95 https://t.co/VfNolB1zoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at N. 163rd Ave. and W. Jomax Rd. in Surprise, AZ https://t.co/YP2tV7hI4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpitC @stoked84 WRONG. You ignorants, are the MINORITY. Those are the facts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YandR_CBS Rosales family boring! Story line boring! Please please not another court trial. I can fast forward and not miss a thing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPaigeWWE @RealRoyKnight Happy birthday God bless you Roy Knight Happy Birthday to you!!!! Have a beautiful day Paige &amp; Family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parabéns meu amor.... te amamos muito...  #bdayale aleiodice my❤️ em Buttermilk Mountain https://t.co/HrxMT4jXgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aprendí a no obligar a nadie a quedarse a mi lado, quien se quede lo hará por amor no por obligación o compromiso.]]></document><document><![CDATA[im house sitting for my dad and i miss my mom i facetime her every night :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLS 2007. My first(and only) year at Houston Baptist University. The school didn’t have an American football team… https://t.co/oqVERfRRW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessJ114 Good Morning Dear Sweet Princess Happy Thursday 😁😀😆 Hope your day is filled with joy and happiness  🦄🕊💐🌹🏵⚘🌷🌼🌻🎪🎠]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really thought sis was finna fuck us up with these vocals 🤦🏾‍♀️ #sigmapageantperiod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated Would be great. Chris Matthews' style is obsolete. His constant interrupting of guests, especially… https://t.co/C1M61x6dAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will give back what u lost!   Can u even imagine the memory that Adam had in the Garden of Eden???   How he named… https://t.co/85ujsMCHVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been a Gibbs fan a long time.  We should all strive to live in a way that honors our Creator.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it is a wrap with Katelyn. She is an October bride getting married at Bishop Farm. @temptu golds and bronzers… https://t.co/dx4vFjms9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom called me 3 times, I had 3 alarms, AND my roomie came to make sure I was up for game day today💀💀 can y’all t… https://t.co/L2p7UlKuwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nolan_Nichols @BenAnderson321 they’ll have to renovate the food too, but I’ll have to give it a chance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch She forgets that it’s not all about her... she’s not royalty but a SERVANT to her constituents. Ok less se… https://t.co/FU1M8n160E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always see a guy on the train on Fridays who's a pastry student. He always has a container full of pastries and h… https://t.co/ati1elD4WN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m always torn between wanting to be the loving, always supportive, reaching out and checking on you friend... and… https://t.co/9fdvOxnM4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Kristen Strickland as my NC School Hero. You can vote daily. don't forget to share! https://t.co/yvHUadW3FX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t listen to thank u next the same after seeing the vid bacon eggs 😂😂, allllll I hear now is bacon eggs]]></document><document><![CDATA[if I gave you my kindness and you fucked it up that’s your fault shit don’t come around twice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fred_Delicious “Hollin” (pronunciation of his first name, not actual spelling) Huang]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Captn_Sassy DURING THE FIRST FUCKING AVENGERS MAYBE??? TONY COULD HAVE NOT BEEN SUCKED INTO A VORTEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE CAN BE BUTT ASS NAKED AND THAT STILL DOESNT MEAN YOU CAN TOUCH US!!! FUCK OUTTA HERE WITH THAT SHIT BRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The PlayStation Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below… https://t.co/He9BQ6kK3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz @BatmanGothamUSA @GovRonDeSantis I’m proud of you Matt go get them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You claim you're a great businessman, but won’t show your tax returns  You claim you're a genius,… https://t.co/C9TOyq8w9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police: Two brothers told investigators they paid by Jussie Smollett stage attack https://t.co/DZkEBahEWN MY MY! WH… https://t.co/y3DZJA82xP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Verdant_Quo @alexjonesshows Someday when you need a job people will scroll thru your tweets 😲]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreakingBrown @tonetalks @tariqnasheed 16 trillion dollar minimum. #ADOS #Reparations2020 #Tangibles2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harvey_acosta Ya la publiqué, según yo no se darán cuenta cuál es la dependencia en cuestión.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Field of Flowers Acrylic Painting By Kara Mayfield @ Citrus Heights, California https://t.co/ZRaQx6reJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CT9008 Dedicating 3 months! Could potentially turn into a paid internship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm gonna love you forever, no matter how long that forever is -Gary 💕  That pretty much sums up how I feel about… https://t.co/gOYHDc98Qg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scav61 @Cooey1967 @CajunChick25 California wastes billions on a train to no where]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time...thanks for letting us sit with you! #sundayfunday #pluckers #lookwhoisgettingmarried… https://t.co/NGO1TzTWa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougDavidsonYR Love you, too. That's why all the fans were clamoring to get you back. So glad someone with the pow… https://t.co/bf1gr8cg9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaSuhler @realDonaldTrump You realize when people say "nothing to see here, nothing to see"  there IS something… https://t.co/frCOIeewGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got off work at 5:45 first bottle down already. Getting ready to crack  # 2 off work tomorrow momma needs a break.… https://t.co/1ouhl4DhiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Studying with your friends is all fun and games until you're all supposed to focus and everyone has something inter… https://t.co/aKqLe0HaPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FitHPrincess I got it off the sale rack a few years ago at Belk, it’s a Calvin Klein!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRMiracleman Such a person who has the fire burning in him at the time of the Bride Grooms return, will go in with Him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to through a lot of bumps before you’re able to say the truth...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Episode 2 of A League of Our Own on @blazesports or on my website, link in bio!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Well then @eugenegu why is the administration more than willing to sign off on lies that this frui… https://t.co/T6NDYUFvuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MaduroDictador #MaduroAsesino te esperan en la paila desgraciado mal nacido... #FreeVenezuela… https://t.co/1AJoPY8DnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@checkjfooty I think all 3 TX teams will be a rivalry of SAFC. Austin, being closest, #1, plus w/ all the bad ⚽ blo… https://t.co/iHZRL4lwQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJMieres @WomenHeartOrg @WomansDay @GoRedForWomen @SharonneHayes @drstaceyrosen @LiveLaughLeigh @mizzeyheart13… https://t.co/nP36KMlOQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChantelPratPhD @olsonista @cherylrkaiser @scheryan1 @ElenaGaby_ @TarynSouthern https://t.co/3CIneWZkqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now this is why whenever people ask me what animal I want to be I always say jaguar! They’re ruthlesss!! Dominant!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekend Read: 'If I'd been white, I guarantee you they wouldn't have taken my money' - Southern Poverty Law Center https://t.co/Xg2nugPe89]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicheleWolpert @spank419 @billritter7 @ABC7NY @LizCho7 @SadeABC @LeeGoldbergABC7 @RyanFieldABC That’s ridiculous Michele.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Does anyone else find it weird that the same party that screams about freedom and the Constitution w… https://t.co/VlJTzd8qEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafetyPinDaily @PoliticalBee Thank you Mr. Biden. You gave us this SOB.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my Buyer on purchasing this beautiful Townhouse in Gran Paradiso. I’m sure he will enjoy his pie… https://t.co/fa9pJyomGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was just informed there is football in March and why  this is when we all become ride or die basketball fans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to danny who always makes me laugh so hard, I got tears in my eyes 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing Tom's talk about Fox News in a way he will not talk about the Democrats relationship with CNN, MSNBC, ABC,… https://t.co/FWIXG6z0Xl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandson he's so cute @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/tp0yJ7EyDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My seniors wanted to know if I had an alter-ego... nope. I just sit in my driveway and sing to myself. Bahaha. Enjo… https://t.co/Fe6WwgKVyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great @GameOfThrones #BleedforTheThrone t-shirt @RedCross is giving donors today! https://t.co/3oo7Y5Du3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[A naked girl can get hundreds of likes, how about our boys and blue? https://t.co/BqpNbiZO1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteButtigieg @DTSouthBend @LOGANCenter If you get the chance, listen to Pete. He has sensible ideas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will make it easy and ask for same gifts for my birthday as well. Especially The Favourite!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @damian_godden 200% agree. It pisses me it’s taken this long!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cselken @MrDane1982 Same here... smack dab in the middle of 7... and it does explain a lot.🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epidural is in. Anna is resting and we should be meeting Oliver sometime today! #itsbabytime #Olivercomingsoon… https://t.co/k0HGO9Q61n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attended #IPPE Tradeshow this week @GWCC_ATL Shout our to friend @MIMotionInd : Good to see Hal M https://t.co/2JoxrLSefx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 1420 DESTINI Lane #Southport #FL  #realestate https://t.co/3MBKhi8HMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So happy to hear this ! People MUST come to our country the proper way ! Period !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 @Ashluelaroe No. Being gay isn’t really a choice. It’s who you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldn't sit and "talk" to that fat tard ...but I guess that's why I'm not president lol 😑😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC WE are Latinos and we VOTE. If this Repinochetizing of Latin AMERICA will be ignored enough of us will stay ho… https://t.co/Jxwh4K5aId]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another day bringing sunshine to the  DC Swamp! 🙏🇺🇸🙌👍☘️ https://t.co/lZ4XbxiPQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martian434 @ChafeXcream @gotailwind @SPIBELT @XOSKINUSA @oofos @topoathletic She is.  What a funny puppy!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great awareness video! Perfectly laid out and edited @jsutfin @TonySandersU46 @sehsMoran]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker Daniel Suarez talking about our recent @Audubon_GL State of the Grasslands Report. Showing the importan… https://t.co/uMcMsNTOGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump trade chief changes terminology after president contradicts him https://t.co/2U4JlHjP0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris12902 kdhdjdd ill be real idk how to feel about how thicc the model is but the texture work is lovely,, i have hope]]></document><document><![CDATA[People that can eat without a beverage are the real heroes.  I cannot.  #RandomThoughts]]></document></documents></author>