<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This is why the media NEEDS the power to convict BEFORE due process. Turns out it wasn’t a MAGA attack, but it coul… https://t.co/lCSeXFVV8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sportstein And when it happens I shall rejoice and say that I knew him near the beginning👍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @maggieNYT @realDonaldTrump This is absurd. This is not about a wealthy president taking care of pri… https://t.co/1hRyznzvq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmileyYYC @jimrome What if it was just a happy tug? Let's give the old billionaire perv the benefit of the doubt lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might I interest you in 77 degrees at 9am? 🌞🍾🍊🌴  Why isn’t there a Bloody Mary emoji? @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/ItYNwMlsDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @senatemajldr show us spine and get these folks confirmed don’t continue to let the elitist social… https://t.co/WptgblY8VR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que feito es irle al @atlasfc ni en liga ni en copa ni en nada... Que feo es irle al @atlasfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the people who go to sleep after 10pm and be back up by 4am]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear, If I hear that dang song “Eastside” on the radio again......  I’m gonna reach up to my volume button, turn… https://t.co/lrHNVMAcYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[A nice, warm day that starts with a light rain and a little thunder sounds perfect to me right now. https://t.co/ujsR00Gu1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd @MarkWarner @Jim_Jordan @MeetThePress # the truth he is telling it ! I’m voting for Trump ! Again people… https://t.co/HquA72eak0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You REALLY want to discuss "national emergencies?"  How about every burger place at MCO serving BREAKFAST at 5am in… https://t.co/EFpVAxRH6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Furanciscus @RottenTomatoes Then you know that rotten films don't get certified, they're "Just rotten" with no fanfare.]]></document><document><![CDATA[VW Beetle #vw #volkswagen #beetle #peoplescar #red #car #carshow #automobile #rollamo vw @Hagerty @GrundyInsures @… https://t.co/3OjSDRaPFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a lot of fun in my life right now and dont know what to do with it all. My brain is so suspicious. Like bitc… https://t.co/Ll0sOfE5Yg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of the opportunity presents itself, I'll become one for it's own sake,  even if no libs are owned]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeatrizGMuller Ese tipo tiene instancias infantiles por eso anda de ardido no le haga caso a ese wei tiene más propiedades fuera de Mexico]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haaylirae Apologies. I was unclear. When I said, "Show you adhere to Christian standards," I implied, "Punctuate  their hypocricy."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaniellaMicaela Wasn't he fired before the editing and mixing were done?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love you Karen Pence, you guys keep up the great work that you do and thank you....!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know about anyone else. But I am disgusted with NJ Gov!! Trying to take our presidential votes away for 202… https://t.co/ichnJtk9o4]]></document><document><![CDATA[All it takes is Zion to bust through a shoe and the NBA officially submits to the PA to lower the draft age to 18. LMFAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrEasyStreet @KHMakerD @steeztabor @BeastFBall @brianslionsblog @the_lpc Maybe... Just maybe... The Democrats coul… https://t.co/EC6HTTnOrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for the CHL tournament in Charleston, SC. Getting sharp with @Sparxhockey first. First game at 845pm… https://t.co/X9NIpaZcTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why don’t they just make the conditioner bottle 30% bigger than the shampoo? Ain’t nobody ever run out of shampoo b… https://t.co/pM0EYB7Y8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading out to run some errands and I see the @IABankers used some more of their record profits for a horribly thou… https://t.co/w8NTJbfgoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaltDisneyWorld Will never visit any Disney Properties as long as you continue to support hate on FAUX News with advertising!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WRadioColombia #laiglesiadebe entender que el mundo avanza y muchas de sus ideas retrógradas deben ser reconsidera… https://t.co/SrFjdKIjdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2phat2fish @NBCSAuthentic @NBCSGiants That’s what MVP, CY, SS, GG, ROY are for]]></document><document><![CDATA[really hoping the domain “https://t.co/UasDL0HFnv” i bought in 2006 shoots up in value soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its Love Songs Karaoke, at bureaubar16th and @spirits_nmotion is whipping up these delicious Aviation Gin cocktails… https://t.co/f63OUTDoAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrs_Malindo Hello Mrs Malindo, you now have a new follower following you. Will you please make my day and follow me back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IchabodMBB @CoachBBallard Happy birthday, @CoachBBallard ! Have a great day today and even better night on Thursday! #BeatNWMSU #GoBods]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laser Focus on the details makes everything better!!! @ Be Positive Competition Academy https://t.co/14mvwTnDFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @hulu I cannot stand watching that future man commercial anymore!! Please please take it off 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[With me being sick I’m supposed to be on this strict diet but your boy likes to eat so the diet thing isn’t gonna happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can only hope that this is the last act and the curtain will fall on the Idiot-in-chief and his minions. 😠😠😠😠😠😠😠😠… https://t.co/7Jc8j6lwKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For real that’s where you shit! I hide my toothbrush too cuz it’s dirty. Also, when people drink in the bathroom or… https://t.co/6xknJWCbQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ll always be my one good reason to keep on moving until I’m in your arms]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel like this match is gonna he boring lmao they need to face a real tag team]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WMonnat @RoKhanna Absolutely not on estate tax.  Tax has already been paid on monies inherited.  Our tax problem e… https://t.co/7Va7jWY1B4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rieper47 @JustifiedJackTV @RE_Games Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music… https://t.co/xI5dqMGKIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DH44_ Re disgusting racism of all people,Lincoln,is his noting looks.Looks R 1of++major things feeds prejudice.Bu… https://t.co/ddcHBDfejh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scifi themed bar, hot girls and karaoke going on right now at the Scum and Villainy Cantina in Hollywood. Party goe… https://t.co/9XGYduoaiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenixsmile It’s the most frustrating food service app I’ve ever had to use.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you're going to chuckle. 33 Teachers Who Got The Last Laugh - Hilarious! I miss being a teacher for these... #humor… https://t.co/D5Q10ozwp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Soma Paloma by @4quartersbrew at @amherstbrewing — https://t.co/AMZpHhQCD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[People wonder if Stanek or Yarborough understand what they're  doing to themselves financially, but considering tha… https://t.co/k0Z0fu2tXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A heart felt ♥️ thank you to chefdeborahvantrece and the entire staff at twistedsoulcookhouse for helping my mother… https://t.co/A6Yf8lIzLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Okay she needs to go and Omar needs to be deport she is not a citizen and she was put into office by t… https://t.co/3ArhusHwfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[fucking democrats better get their act straight and compromise on 1 candidate because if we do a repeat of 2016 whe… https://t.co/73k1RL6DDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Russian investment fund chief defends Michael Calvey, US investor detained in Moscow https://t.co/hIZ7QiV7Ob     Aw… https://t.co/LB7Mpt2awo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chronotope I) There is one method superior to all others for ad ROI: the scientific method. Aka randomized control… https://t.co/4XrMgEqVFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjjohnson1216 @teachergoals @PrincipalTribe @PrincipalFrench @mafost @MaireCervenak @MrsHankinsClass… https://t.co/W3FqmrQ6GF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let this PSA be my last: GLENN CLOSE WILL WIN THE OSCAR OR HEADS. WILL. ROLL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyinNYC You’re starting a movement, Mr. Speaker! #Gotham #BAT https://t.co/DNAxh6iKJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrapped up another incredible #NACS #LeadershipForum in #Miami shared great #insights learned #bestpractices and re… https://t.co/dJ3sLonDOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lara Logan on media bias: People know that we've slipped.  About time, one of their own exposed MSM lib lies. Let… https://t.co/cuShxPFKAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me today at 10 am!💫🌟✨  Come have some fun, meet new positive energy people, clear your head, get inspired and… https://t.co/O2RsfjQQBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#life #doc #doctor #doctors #med #medical #medicine #er #wakemed @WakeMed #raleigh #nc #919 #livingthedream #why @… https://t.co/AHFj7DmLQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinDiMaio Literally where they going that’s so important ... I wanna go lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one is safe now... Everyone has realized how to score with their backs to the goal 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport @NBA_Reddit HahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaahahahahahaahowishenotyourMVPhahahahahahahahahahahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dawg at least get a better picture of it. There’s a sucking super car in front of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOW THE FUCK AM I SEEING DEJA POSTS WHEN IVE MUTED ANYTHING POSSIBLY RELATED FUCK YALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I’ve come to bed after Tash for the last 2-3 weeks she’s fallen asleep watching murder mysteries or snap… https://t.co/nkfGQLmd4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at the #Avs winning in OT now.   Who’d have thought? #GoAvsGo https://t.co/mqSVknzBXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pelicolombianas Habla de @DCoronell o @DanielSamperO ? Cual de los dos Danielitos los pobres e ingenuos ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marxist Communist talking points beating down Capitalism valuesdone before didn’t work but if you are a Commie then… https://t.co/HUV1beMl8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveH_RPh @HilaryKimMorden @Skywtchr @rlamartini @mard55859518 @Iamchronicpain @LelenaPeacock @headdock… https://t.co/qNpA24k1Ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙏Happy are those who keep His decrees and seek Him with all their heart. Psalms 119:2 HCSB https://t.co/nj73J3d7l6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gillibrandny You're currently trending at 1% among all announced Dem candidates. How much $$$ do we need to mail in to coax you to resign?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylviaRyan2018 @rick_thd @DeniseHR_THD @KaleenA_HD @jmajusiak89 we might have to steal this idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my digital paintings... @mADurgency @MrChuckD @hiphopgods @HipHopGoldenAge @RZA @blackthought… https://t.co/iJqg0WyZBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Viri_Rios “ Como pierden los partidos hegemónicos “ Viri tienes el autor ? Excelente participación. Te ves muy delgada 🙇🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber now charges a “waiting fee” .. Ok  ,    Wait ..  can I charge a separate waiting fee when 3 different divers… https://t.co/Mdw0I4tkEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachDavidSisk @VU365 @VandySportscom I doubt Vanderbilt could beat any of those teams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mathewjdp @JasonGregor @Condors @ahl This lightning team to date is fastest team to 100 points in NHL history. Wil… https://t.co/iJ3mQahT9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoxScoreInsider Don't get me wrong @lohudinsider, I love the CC but I have been to many a game at the CC during th… https://t.co/JFnpnXCH0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump U preggers??? #dotard #hamberders https://t.co/8uZn8upS1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clear skies overnight here as bitter cold weather continues with a low of 21 degrees. Take a heavy coat if you're o… https://t.co/xQ7LMlzM1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaboard2 @BowTiePolitics @theobserver Voter ID law specifically exempts any part of CD9 re-do ordered by @ncsbe FWIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thepointsguy have you ever checked into a room and found someone in it? Well it just heppened to me @HiltonHotels… https://t.co/Nlwg9ZW3mT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @PamRollins not seems, he has done them all and more!Just a nasty human being!Good lord ,i cant wait… https://t.co/xIMqLI5hu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 SWEETHEART!💝 Miss blondecollegebabes The White RACE BLONDES👑Women Are The MOST Beautiful In T… https://t.co/Yh0CpYUSlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#forsale #dontbuyfromasalesmanbutafriend #whatruwaiting4 #2019 #car #guy #vandergriffhonda #arlington #tx… https://t.co/H3LV8Y3628]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today for my  #IWD2019 highlight, i present to you Kira Wetzel one of the driving forces behind @girlsanddata - she… https://t.co/V4Z6SivuxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakepurpleInk Go enjoy life take a break and travel it’s lots of fun doit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theobyrnegroup @brithume @ByronYork How dare you support a criminal like trump. You should be ashamed of yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carliejoprints Sorry it was a shit show but you did absolutely ROCK THE RED DRESS 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: little caesars fuckin sucks  also me with two hot n readys and crazy bread: damn this shit kinda smack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolasMaduro @DrodriguezVen @jorgerpsuv  @jguaido  "Bienaventurados los que tenéis hambre ahora, porque seréis sa… https://t.co/RTwRWRrGC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not love the world or the things in the world. If anyone loves the world, the love of the F… https://t.co/vOL6ubk1A9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #WorldBookDay! Treat yourself and get lost in a book! 📚  Harry Hoffman, “Portrait of Mrs. Lois C. Robinson”,… https://t.co/wv6jwj6Ore]]></document><document><![CDATA[#americancoot #birdsofinstagram #birds #birding #birdingphotography #audubonsociety #audubon #ctbirds… https://t.co/rCwt70wdgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finebaum @JRsBBQ how about having good ol JR fill in on your next time on vacation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeGoldbergABC7 I have to be where the rain/snow line is? About 1 mile south of LIE in Deer Park? Keeps changing f… https://t.co/qAPxo9O43T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to George Strait on @995thewolfdfw and @Markphillips995! Thanks you for playing George Strait at Strait u… https://t.co/5eu6qdFlS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well let’s just say last night was interesting @ Brothers Bar &amp; Grill Bloomington https://t.co/XaAT1ZyZQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not one joke about Alex Trebek having cancer is witty or original.  It's like when Paul Walker died in a car crash.  Just leave it be.]]></document></documents></author>