<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Srry Colton but like why would you assume that she would take your name? #Feminism #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SupportMW @MauraWest You’re SO welcome! I loved seeing her this past weekend SO happy! Just look at her face!! She… https://t.co/u0O2MNSstL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amikegreen2 @RevDrBarber Actually, I wasn't! I barely had interactions with whites until then. My family and neigh… https://t.co/XufebJ9x6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yes; many of us have struggled against suicidal thoughts. Satan is busy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slept a lot last night, feeling ready to take this on! (@ Orangetheory Fitness Thornton in Thornton, CO) https://t.co/K4DXRDwVVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both @RepJasonCrow and @RepKenBuck agree on the need for campain finance and election reform but have very differen… https://t.co/AJ2Eeo1hoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support Black Owned 🗣🖤✨ https://t.co/PY6YzYhm9y @RichSocietyChi #stayblack #blackowned #youtube Staying Black w/ Da… https://t.co/IaHPGiXqRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is low key and what is high key ??? Cant twitter please explain this... thanks &lt;3 grandma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trash__fire @inthesedeserts fascism is the melding of corporations and government, so yeah, this is straight up fascist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fully endorsed by a full time University staff member! @HarrisPastides #gococks #goscotty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo we walked on a hill/street for about 30 mins and then went to studio city to eat 😅 #wetried https://t.co/Hgo7RxaCHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[que lastima que se me haiga roto la uña del pulgar que estaba perfecto y no el que esta bien arruinado ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofzz2020 they're all the same movie 🎥   watched infinity bore over break with my little bro and it was every bit… https://t.co/DSAUE8RxRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to former baller Taylor Snow! Have a great birthday weekend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#COLDINLA is amazing I'm so proud out these guys and hope they keep it up on making the limelight's happy… https://t.co/9A7FNj869G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been having an awful Morning to say the least and I’m in line for coffee at Hot Shots and this random lady dec… https://t.co/KRUfUlVaeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Drum on the US market? I checked the usual suspects and no one has it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[one realization while traveling every weekend for season - the real heroes are the charter bus drivers...how they n… https://t.co/Va0hdwRJbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheerUPDATES  @cheerworlds2019 @FierceSport @worldofcheerxo @CheerFessions1 @CommonCheeer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warriors We @warriors are the best PERIOD!!!!!!! Win or lose..... https://t.co/AuGOZTGijN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idkaila i felt the same and then i got a pair and they changed my life lol 100% worth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump I often wondered why you chime in right after POTUS Twitter. You are being paid you… https://t.co/crwtkEuVjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParkHillPS #intern Aidan Lueth exploring his #passion for music with Harriman-Jewell and the William Jewell Music… https://t.co/Q2RvmR08pj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catgclaay @x0x0LC this tweet made me find her etsy and i’m about to drop so much money 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewmerez @MNC010101 @matthewjdowd @BetoORourke He's from TX where many voters work for  Big Oil.  He's pragmat… https://t.co/NOqqC68jlH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pregunta seria: ¿La gente debe disculparse si llega tarde a otro lugar? O no?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brings tears to my eyes. The great @LynnePatton is now doing couragous work at the @NYCHA. God bless America and Go… https://t.co/TuVkvxekQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiSixx OMG... Ace is like 400 years old and weighs 800 pounds... Of course he used a lift! Come on!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spaccatelli, Sorrel Pesto, Pignoles, Black Garlic, Preserved Lemon adlibgables // Lunch Menu @ Ad Lib Coral Gables https://t.co/nsG3gwCTAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imlaurahouse @HollywoodImprov @anylaurie16 @DebraDiGiovanni @damonjr @jamielbridgers @eddiepepitone @Fieldingedlow… https://t.co/b0s18GvoCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukeseymoup @BlackKat1979  https://t.co/bVjWZHH0VK  Ayeeeeee you must check out this dude. He is everything that's… https://t.co/owGBSvS8o8]]></document><document><![CDATA[a question i never thought id have to ask in all my years of child care: “did you turn your brother into a soundcloud rapper?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump Shut up! You're the incompetent creepy daughter of an incompetent president!]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMFG this is me. Though the soul mate is the dog I acquired after moving in with the 3rd person I dated in my late… https://t.co/nNdyttOk13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Happyheart411 @CoryBooker @SenBooker Oh Spartacus, what happened to ye?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@overtime @zia_cooke Awesome talent! Can’t wait to see you in garnet and black future GAMECOCK❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ella es genial y yo la adoro!!! Reposted from @tutifurlan  -  No es fácil reconocer esto... pero es revelador descu… https://t.co/cdvKXbEDWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[i get so happy it hurts my heart, because i know one day i’ll miss these days with these people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LummiIslVal @Tim_Melon @IRONRANGER_218 @JeremyDBoreing @benshapiro Sounds like you will stay firm to yours. That i… https://t.co/XiDSt2N8Wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealsharon61 @tedlieu @jcorycma @POTUS There are more than you think under sealed indictments.  You’ll find out… https://t.co/xSEFBrXXXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter So when someone goes after you because you've suddenly changed your mind on trump and calling him an id… https://t.co/9jwh0JaPXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[No discussion @IDWPublishing @SYFY @IDWEntertain season 4 must be delivered on TV! Melanie is #WynonnaEarp, Emily d… https://t.co/DdXFTL2glA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jvergara I fully support this, because I get stuck in food ruts! Going to Andre's for a sweet treat? I would not b… https://t.co/C6z4DPTvnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad I didn't obsess over the Buckle in high school cuz everyone who did looks like this now:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConPisces3192 @tracy_mzz @jojoh888 @tina_MAGA2020 Please! So does the Right! 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rmasher2 @IvankaTrump @jaredkushner It’s baffling how they get away with multiple lies daily and multiple underhan… https://t.co/YiCSrgNDE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarinR525 @niles_francis @SolutelyAbe @AOC The list includes 50-plus names of organizations or individuals: from p… https://t.co/wCOaUUg4Qc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t been already, you need to check out Nonna‘s Pizza in Concord, North Carolina. #italianfood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elalbertomedina @EPN @lopezobrador_ @JACrespo1 Presidencias vemos, pactos no sabemos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight up Peacockin’ 🦚  Artist: El Niño Medium: Oil on Asphalt @ Hermosa Beach, California https://t.co/6EEPkkZmM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever see me with my headphones on and I just wave and don’t make conversation, don’t take it personally. I’m… https://t.co/pCir433UJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Larry’s Latest Flamingo Fruit Fight by @BellsBrewery at @hopscraftsgulch — https://t.co/PRLjEI8vLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattjlange @TamronUSA @SonyAlpha @DJIGlobal Should I upgrade my Sony rx to an alpha? Worth it? 🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my 70 year old aunt just hooked me up 🔥🔥I’m guessing she my plug for now on 😂😂😂 https://t.co/atdS8Edgch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSports @SNFonNBC @packers @Yankees @celtics @CanadiensMTL @NBCSBoston @NBCSCeltics A. It's called the Lombardi trophy FOR A REASON!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReemDepp @linneaeliasson5 @Fleur_de_Lys85 He's my husband now.We talk on our cellphone. He finally found me. https://t.co/v5xxbHCVEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GLITCHFEST_ recap video ‼️ by @turtlemov 🤮Song: 4th Down (UNRELEASED) 🤐🤫 #TurkTapesVol1 #March22 https://t.co/p2SNibMKT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheChrisDean @RuPaulsDragRace She’s definitely one of my top 3 favorite queens]]></document><document><![CDATA[mornin B’s - u at work this #sundaymorning #comingdown 😮💅👛☔️  🍀 ❤️ 🔥 🖤 🐥 #truth  #dare  #doubledare… https://t.co/Q3n7j3df9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[My motivation to get through this week is the @Cubs first spring training game this Saturday⚾️ ((I missed baseball season a whole lot))]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6Af3VTR9M6  The Amazon Phone Number works via our toll-free number 1-855-431-5111  #amazonphonenumber]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark your calendars!!! NEXT FRIDAY is First Friday 🎉 Doors open at 9. Guest List ends at 11. Text 904.422.4488 to b… https://t.co/FFR6FuywGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just read about a mattress that monitors heart rate and other vital functions. I think it would cause many people stress. What do you think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I love watching my baby grow through out the years at his award shows 😍 always looking 🔥 daddy @PrinceRoyce]]></document><document><![CDATA[That hazy, cold California daze.  #bluesky #california #huntingtonbeach #surf #sand #winter #leadwithmemories… https://t.co/KwGnyhBAEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeumaSantosgma2 @Bren_O1967 Hi Neuma!! Have a beautiful Friday!! Stay warm &amp; safe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG @GMA, when you’re feeling like a fashionista after you see what @RobinRoberts is wearing this morning! https://t.co/J7vTHaMTid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcwva @jake_zuckerman Aunt Ann showed up just to scold him for it too. https://t.co/lSHbK8WWrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[to be fair though, any pickles other than the Claussen Dill Pickles are gross🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[If one is safe in one’s own country, one  does not need to apply for asylum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm to that point, where I just want to sleep in...Just once!  #ThisWeekIsTakingForever #MommyIsTired]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Mr. Charlie's Chicken Fingers in Murray, UT https://t.co/FT5MGdroEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This makes me sick!  Precious souls. This has to end we can’t ever@give up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well @blakeshelton you did it again, an outstanding show in KCMO last night. Although the weather to say the least… https://t.co/J5WSVaACYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a coach, there are days that are easier than others. I’m reminded that it’s all about my mindset and the attitud… https://t.co/XjJ5vfC4BK]]></document><document><![CDATA[my aunt and I are wine drunk watching the finale of the bachelor, this is a greattttt night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LILBH0LE I literally gagged and now it’s all I’m gonna think about when i see her]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is clever. Celebrity Tweets You Missed Today #funniness #snicker #smirk #amusing https://t.co/AY7LhPW5AN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake up America! Capitol Hill will be governed by sharia law! Shame on you America! Let this be your wake up call!… https://t.co/vPo2wN7zpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si se humillare mi pueblo, sobre el cual mi nombre es invocado, y oraren, y buscaren mi rostro, y se convirtieren d… https://t.co/6zOsZskVo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there a war in truth? YES - @WajahatAli #SXSW2019 https://t.co/V7ASBYzLtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to be honest.  I could give less than a damn where the real Melania is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New paper out on the search for signs of advanced extraterrestrial life from 12 extragalactic sources including TRA… https://t.co/Et6oVLywJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clouds and mountains #roadtrip @ San Lucas, California https://t.co/WqMgR1pL7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennandJuicex3 Pillows make my neck hurt I need a flat service or I can’t move my neck the next day 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donhutto @DrWheresthe @insektmute @AOC @paulkrugman The Green New Deal is a blueprint for the future, a concept, m… https://t.co/Gzx0buKXbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put on makeup for the first time in over a week. This stupid cold is trying to make a come back. 🙅🙅 Can't let it. •… https://t.co/29E7OIduyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrandOleParr That ending. Wow. I was not expecting that. Grabbed me by the the throat. Spike Lee is something else..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right Side 39yrs ago  Left side Now ! We’re still Together (married) He’s my Best Husband, the Best Father, the Bes… https://t.co/LlfWmlCWfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guy implied he’d drown his son and daughter if they came to him and said they were gay. I think we can just wri… https://t.co/5uwQn6L2yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paumtzurita podrías ver por favor el dm de @zuriconchudas es importante ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottRvr91 @wazikuza Though he’s not as Phresh as he can be. Come talk to me when you have perfect gear again😘🤣😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen The man with the highest IQ in the world, Christopher Langan, supports President Trump. When you're inte… https://t.co/jaNjftZ2se]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a bit I will have a long drive I put off last night because of the snow 🤗😆🙏#tributes make everything better #findom]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Aww this commercial was about shelter puppies that became insta famous” “So they were never adopted??? And they became insta famous??”]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: what my teenage brother posts on social media is NOT representative of my values, my family’s values, or the c… https://t.co/1uDqwD2c2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feels like yesterday! Grateful for our partnership w/ @austinmarathon, the great memories keep on coming. #spibelt https://t.co/pk3L564x53]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cute doll I found at the Antique Mall today. @ Georgetown, Texas https://t.co/TVvT2xQXO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy ♥️ Day! Twins loved donuts!#krispykremedoughnuts @ San Jose, California https://t.co/qemx2FMaF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't really think what @marcorubio did yesterday can or should be minimized...]]></document></documents></author>