<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You should talk you Repummunists are Ridonkulous! President Comrad Dontov TrumPutin!­ЪцЦ­ЪцА]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka One term wonder we hope,this country can't sustain the barrage of stupidity coming from her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the best thing about AOC is that she appreciates and harnesses the power of people buying into an idea. HowРђд https://t.co/4JwfO9JuGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews No they just planted seed, business as usual. Ordinary bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CristalEnAmor @LADELAVEGA @YalitzaAparicio @MARLENE_STAHL @SofiaRiveraT @laestrenado @elbajimenez9 @TVale2012Рђд https://t.co/mwaP1xMcML]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luna is my my new partner in crime.   ­ЪљХ­Ъўѓ #DogsOfTwitter  #Boise #Idahome #TreasureValley https://t.co/pU9UTLIDhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConenMorgan January 13 or 18, NC starts vote-by mail (@ncsbe to choose one of those dates), February 12, NC starts in-person early voting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with my buddy Fran Strine at the pre-Oscars Kodak Awards. Thanks  @stevenjbellamy for the invite!Рђд https://t.co/7gKJVnooSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to bed thinking @NateGearyWGR was a dummie. I woke up only to realize that he is absolutely right. Bills wouРђд https://t.co/iJzXs1wBac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saumyadadoo @sridala @AnniZaidi Check out @anniezaidiРђЎs Tweet: https://t.co/BL7E1r8V7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kivlind He was trying to compliment the dude.  I suppose he couldРђЎve picked a better fictional character that canРђд https://t.co/rFpxv22o2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckMartin_SC Thank you coach, hope youРђЎre doing well. I appreciate you looking out for me when you were here. Meant a lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, can you imagine my face right now? #IMissMyCanineSymbiont #TearyAtSeeingADogLikeMatigan https://t.co/wfRbKyw3fz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgoyer @tommyunger while I'd be fine (happy!) fielding complaints that my insights were too honest, I understanРђд https://t.co/gASdT2uKeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO. PROUD. OF. THIS. TEAM!!!  @RacerRifle out-performed their qualifying 5th seed and finishing 4th overall at theРђд https://t.co/c5t7XfKlKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dogs, Chocolate, Cheese!! Your Turn GO! #choices #cantlivewithout #letsgo @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/vtgkcAD9dA]]></document><document><![CDATA[knew I was selfish when I was single but realized you where my happiness when you were not anywhere to be found and I was broken ­Ъњћ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tim_Beshara , in #NYC we call these Rats ­Ъљђ, ( exhale slow and deep in this good news ) they are very much NOT extiРђд https://t.co/YbTcGMyvmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dropped my phone 2 times tonight and i still havenРђЎt gotten it fixed lmao ­ЪўГ­ЪўГ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angieD53978533 PA is a huge state for haunted and abandoned I sorta envy ya for that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flying to Arizona to escape the Michigan snow may not have been the best plan. https://t.co/RAUiwxkRct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GC1CG If you like Trump - you should never disparage Comey - he won the election for Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know I came in this game independent right.. @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/a30JGEoW3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kid helped murder 2 people and assaulted an elderly man. Nothing about this is sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ РађРђд https://t.co/RsN0Q6MPkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some haters are jealous of what you have and others are jealous about what they know youРђЎre about to get. Just keepРђд https://t.co/dbxNcI8iEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoanneCangal @ShanRussell72 @JRubinBlogger @DavidCayJ Unlike every other candidate who ran with him, Bernie is notРђд https://t.co/WwGuJ8ka1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PresqueIslePete He actually did have his car towed once in Cleveland- it was when his don was at John Carroll - itРђд https://t.co/cmJCe4KNUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadeABC Beyonce doing nothing but got a bunch of gay people dancing to her songs­Ъўѓ they do it better than the womenРђд https://t.co/gBZdkPWhzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pure quality from @ManUtd. Love watching them under our new boss! Crazy how important leadership is and how much itРђд https://t.co/4K7QDeNMlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 @DonaldJTrumpJr A mental evaluation has been done, itРђЎs no secret, heРђЎs delusional! I also believe thРђд https://t.co/61DSKIYeYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to former #Alabama safety Landon Collins on signing a 6-year deal worth $84M and $45M guaranteed with theРђд https://t.co/ZoIJuc0177]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMichelleJ87 @NoahCRothman Yes, but life is always better than death. Also, who gets to choose who lives and who dРђд https://t.co/9CFjbLavlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Tom Brady really really plays baseball after #SBLXXXi, imma show his CANNON arm up at the 3B.   РђюAfter footbalРђд https://t.co/1KrIMThaI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@upulie Walking and more healthy eating regularly would definitely do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some times the hardest thing is hoping certain situations in your life that are not entirely in your control work out for the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PSPhenom @3xwrestling Ahhhh shit!!!! Alright - IРђЎll get ahold of you tomorrow afternoon! Got an event at work toniРђд https://t.co/Lwa2pyRjHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[people be embarrassing there selfs every night, but hey cheers to your foolish ass­ЪЇ╗­ЪЇ╗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson We got your back Tucker, fuck them , Dems are looking to distroy anything and anyone that backs OurРђд https://t.co/8hARM4MLGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing beats a #LidoBeach #Sunset #Sarasota #Florida #TimeLapse #Video #Beach #Beaches #Vids #Sun #Sand #SurfРђд https://t.co/wtqBZf4wXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jflorez @magee333 @suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy @cazij @JackConnie @thatsVeryKari @ja2cook @CaraMiaSG @ccatmptРђд https://t.co/qbttorTWgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[IРђЎve accepted @GC_President challenge to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviewsРђћjust the cover.Рђд https://t.co/29cAa1O4P0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dangerbrosdnd @helloMCDM @Tom_Not_Tom @tschmu20 https://t.co/4nb54i1NMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daniel Simo - Me Borre (Bachata Hit 2019) https://t.co/tfECaRyrXt #bachata #musica #latina #danielsimo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a new bed. And this happy girl has claimed it as hers. https://t.co/Uw3zWayalo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jbrackets1 I don't agree with LSU over Michigan for a 2 seed, especially with their coaching situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its always changing, who we are supposed to love and who we are not. The only thing that stayed the same is we want who we want]]></document><document><![CDATA[IРђЎm tired of people stealing my lighters, IРђЎm about to start bring matches to the session]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHEdCommr To me, Learn Everywhere is leveraging the power of community partnerships, which will ensure both busineРђд https://t.co/y6BnGaTQOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking these couple days off from shooting to design a freebie for my website. Canva makes designing so easy. FuckkРђд https://t.co/BmWkEU3m2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU ARE YOU, BE HAPPY.  Everything you are, makes you magic. Learn to embrace every part of you. Stop bending overРђд https://t.co/ohF2NxxO0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThayanniRafaely @HandmaidsBR eu viii! bem no centr├Бo babado. fiquei louco de vontade de ir la]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeltelling @ChuckHellebuyck @Barnacules @SeeMeCNC Dude!!!!  That is awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycsouthpaw @Walldo That's a stuffed quesadilla. Where did they get taco from ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeremy_Woodall @BrodieT21 ItРђЎs the dance you saw on my insta story the other day ­Ъўѓ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliaEllermeier Someone does reply tho that logging in from outside the US then doing the VPN right after flaggedРђд https://t.co/9bsPKPXdce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colebrax This movie is in my top 5 Рђюput on in the background while I do other thingsРђЮ movie list. So amazingly watchable for a documentary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomStoup @Colohue I tried a couple of times through the years.  I just never got into it.  My parents used to watcРђд https://t.co/2UXCjGJhYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@FFBravesHoops, @mcspanthers set for #518hoops semifinal action tonight. Here's what you need to know: https://t.co/G2o96GsEdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cannot wait for all the #ConservativeParty condemn @fordnation for the current OPP scandal taking place, and call fРђд https://t.co/qlsMS70QEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @JordanSchachtel Your Dad is a despicable president and that is why he was trying to be removed from office]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RefAubrey Is this it Eventhough it says games or is it more than games https://t.co/OrV5XNkZQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was by far the worst period I have seen the #isles play under Barry Trotz. Looked like they were stuck in mudРђд https://t.co/rF9nefDN0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now you know how the wives feel of all the men he may kill in his jihadi actions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OttoKurect @MidasRex1998 @DanteRondo1 @JerylBier @AOC Yeah, and thereРђЎs multitudes of far right governments also rРђд https://t.co/823rphlPSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @Baby_BrandyX @Brandi_Love @AriellaFerrera @kennajames21 @JoselineKellyx @shylajdotcom @AidenAshleyРђд https://t.co/Vkbm5IQHhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Developer/Senior Developer, IT Applications - MicroStrategy -Рђд https://t.co/S4mpx5wzes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Solado32 @Johnny__Rage @Tactical_review I found it in pristine condition. DoesnРђЎt look like itРђЎs been shot many tiРђд https://t.co/ofK4xSLGzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel (@ Cinergy Odessa in Odessa, TX) https://t.co/uKbhtruHqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some girl is just walking through the woods in my backyard playing with sticks right now. Only in Mississippi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheStarters I almost quit you guys forever after that tweet of the week army featuring Mariah Carey. @LeighEllis pРђд https://t.co/gfwzzW9vs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManWestcoast @deniseparashac I donРђЎt think so. I think he is just a creepy bastard. Watch videos of him with womenРђд https://t.co/HiwBf1UcKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristendoute I love you boo, I truly do. YouРђЎve always been one of my favs but as a concerned fan I think you needРђд https://t.co/0dvEk169W2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not trying to talk about how I feel to anyone, I really don't think I'm ready for that so don't ask about it, bРђд https://t.co/ENX7cEJkSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey you, since I have your attention, I would greatly appreciate a follow on my newly created Insta business page.Рђд https://t.co/Hhq7sH033o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellie Welsh with five points, four boards, three assists, two steals. Lil bit of everything! Great season from ElliРђд https://t.co/EstpxP0go6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 watched me Cummings closing yesterday. I pray for you and your family I think you got a raw deal cРђд https://t.co/7le6cOk1zW]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a buzz in the air today!  Spring is coming ­ЪљЮ  @Szydlowskim @FVEFalcons https://t.co/H35AYQLt77]]></document><document><![CDATA[On todayРђЎs agenda, interviews with Apocalypse, Batman and King Arthur for a new Netflix film.]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Scholastica womenРђЎs basketball ends the season on a high note with the 61-46 win over Crown. Highlights at 6 onРђд https://t.co/jUd3ciVHz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone drive me to Edmond for class. I donРђЎt feel like doing it today. Lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dobbyloca Tiene m├Аs entendimiento una piedra que ese pobre cabr├│n. Lo digo con todo respeto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nowplaying РђюSeptember GurlsРђЮ by Big Star @ Tempe, Arizona https://t.co/E6yOpPcqtx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyCorben @marcorubio I could go either way on him, but, right now on Venezuela, he seems to be doing the rightРђд https://t.co/pevZBJDoc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Black History Month I Would Like To Honor My Top 10 Black Directors! and On This Episode We Are Honoring JanicРђд https://t.co/xztkeAAZLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dweeks821 @CFBM19 Do you have any images or videos of the Boise state blue turf??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christianity: Second Coming of Jesus Christ - Polar Shift &amp; Global Earthquake (NOT THE ONE ON JULY 29th) https://t.co/WNhDX3zU8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like the mountains to clear your mind.  ­ЪЊИ:tiffairydust #hiking #life #mtbaldy @ Mt. Baldy https://t.co/f7qt65nU9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitlockJason @marcelluswiley @SFY @Darnell_Smith95 https://t.co/SrS34F0CAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coby White has been the best freshman on the court in the 2nd half. Just dribbled around fallen teammate Brooks onРђд https://t.co/gR0asyF4GW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three Revelations From the New YorkerРђЎs Explosive Fox News Story  https://t.co/MONoqctbVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[­ЪЌБ A FATT AFFAIR COMEDY SHOW THIS FRIDAY NIGHT FEB 22  ­ЪЌБ GUEST STAR: @theantoinescott hosted by fatt.williams_  ­ЪЌБ BUРђд https://t.co/0ljXooEEFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mushroom, wild rice, kale soup. Third bowl. @ Molson, Washington https://t.co/IRq2CnB80g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red Light Photobiomodulation Buyers Guide ~ https://t.co/wNTvJJtzRE via @PrimalHackr #wellness #wellbeing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im thinking of recording and fixing all the vocals on the Album at this point..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realjefferyhess @nelizadrew @RonEarl @AlecCizak @StephPostAuthor @TerriLCoop https://t.co/3tElP2jrVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexiLalas @thesoccerdon @MLS As soon as the thought becomes an action, it should totally be controlled, and permaРђд https://t.co/Yx8273o5n4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My limit of caffine is somewhere between 200mg to 858mg. Cause 858 is fucking me currently]]></document><document><![CDATA[It arrived! #streetsects #limitededition @ Arlington Heights, Illinois https://t.co/qL57TzLybN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @EMluvsPibbles @msmorgan1968 @ChaliceGarden @Today2BcРђд https://t.co/ovKyaKXnMZ]]></document></documents></author>