<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RyanMykel Other than the crack of lightning and flash of thunder on Saturday were also gonna need to hold onto our… https://t.co/z1QS6Fs1tW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pro-tip: never read the @TheBattOnline Facebook comments. https://t.co/LV19F7wXXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wall seems like a silly idea to me unless it's used in a larger context Dems should put funding for the wall in… https://t.co/YVeYTL3Fbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGirlInPhilly @JimiHendrix @pandoramusic So I have to change my name to Joe 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@campbellclaret so I am innocently having a beer  in New Orleans and these two ladies interact with me . Turns out… https://t.co/qADJ21DXgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForecasterEnten @nymetrowx Three weeks to golf season, Harry. I'll take all the 1-3 dustings you've got.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yourgallerist @nytimesworld Vs the old normal of bankrupting your country and getting rich of it. Leftists perfected that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luxe. . . . #washingtonheights #inwood #manhattan #181st #sunset #nyc #nycphotographer  #streetphotography #street… https://t.co/ufg5iHk2ra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember this: The more you surrender to the process, the higher you rise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so here’s this dude trying to speak one of his many languages which he only knows 2-3 sentences of  each🤓.... us… https://t.co/YpnxzEYqlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that we have proof that Russia meddled in our election and it’s not a “ witch hunt “ like trump says, can we ca… https://t.co/KHoDfEYiIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in line for my first AAF dynasty league win today, but need some help from Matt Simms and the Legends defense.… https://t.co/oHTB5PpCD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Giants’ push for Harper falls short, he gets 13 years and $330 million from Phillies - San Francis… https://t.co/CNIewMYwsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BR_NBA And in other news we have athletes not showing up to work over 10 million dollars when they are already making 70 million 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gospel is preached for Salvation to those who are sick on the Inside. Stop judging by mere appearances ....the… https://t.co/sIUPAiyk5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YeetGrimes Whenever I did group projects in school, the more I understand why Batman worked alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanoconnz This tweet led me to finding this promo photo and I can’t thank you enough https://t.co/lwqh4jWIrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katepurchase @gmbutts One person’s opinion.  I am waiting with  anticipation for the  anti Butts tweets to come.… https://t.co/NhDhI9T3yA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StellaMaeve14 I find this amusing because John Belushi portraying Joe Cocker is my spirit animal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HUGE WIN!!! I feel a lot better about their tournament chances  #GoBucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[ピリピ人への手紙 4:6-7  Japanese    6 何事も心配しないで、どんな時でも神に祈りなさい。そして、祈りに答えてくださる神に感謝しましょう。]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT!  Jay Smith Group at The Mark Restaurant from 8-11 PM.  Fernando Montoya on bass, Cesareo Garasa on drums,… https://t.co/0ciGbGvygB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter how can you still support at man that has zero respect for you in @POTUS ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeelWillMahoney It's quite brilliant. Among other things, she gets the nuclear heat off Ronda. Long-term, that mig… https://t.co/85ejbJ104x]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, how was your night? Mine was pretty damned wonderful. #ThinWhiteDukes @ Lee Harvey's https://t.co/fcjkBEFNkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[SmugMug/Flickr is looking for a PM in SF.   #jobs #pmjobs #productmanagement #pm #sfjobs #flickr  https://t.co/uaRNSPxVkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__abmc__ Thanks that means a lot. I hope ur pharmacy education is going well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aria, Vdara, City Center, and the Shops at Crystals #dasvegas2019 @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/r0d3DqMY8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cant wait to see my friend @elisehayes on Friday at @listeningroom   https://t.co/29O2abaC8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonJHunter Good question. Why doesn’t someone in Parliament ask Ms May? @TheIndGroup]]></document><document><![CDATA[OREGON Law Makers ARE NOT For the People!!! THEY HAVE GONE COMPLETLY INSANE!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday! Currently,  its 31° under Cloudy skies.  Sunrise: 7:09am, Sunset: 6:52pm.   "You are tempted in the s… https://t.co/xLnEGt2kCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys fuck with me again im going to sue the ever living dog shit out of you...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Insane milkshakes at Sugar Factory San Diego before catching How to Train Your Dragon at their top notch Chinese th… https://t.co/3TGoKHNZYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator Flowers is out here saving lives with her passionate and powerful words. Thank you, @SenatorFlowers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido imagino tiene miles de cercanos asesores. Solo pido a Dios compres las recomendaciones acertadas para que… https://t.co/htoUwdkcjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Get honest people working the polls. No voter ID, no vote]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jennifer Lopez and Alex Rodriguez get engaged Jay"lo and A'Rod engaged Mmm mmm I'd give it 2yrs tops.....the mara… https://t.co/JK0dd0ppL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jiggy_lo Yea hoe sit in front ya tv bitch I’m putting you in the madden nation challenge this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[The big liar talks faster to make it appear he is right. Everyone listening knows he is twisting the facts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Pelosi better frickin APOLOGIZE to you to say    Pres Trump isn’t   WORTH impeaching    😩     Pelo… https://t.co/mJiwJxoZ1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Secrets of Tofu across Japan - Seasoning the Seasons - TV - NHK WORLD - English https://t.co/itAnUTkQyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally hooked on Hollow Knight. Why did I ever wait this long!? Lovely visuals and incredible sound design, thanks @TeamCherryGames! 🏅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WendyAn622 Good morning, Wendy ☕️ Hope you have a wonderful Friday!!🤗🤗😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen testifies that Trump paid for portrait with Trump Foundation funds  https://t.co/yJBk9Gczj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coach_whittaker Yeah I don’t think it’s a high school vs private sector thing because I work in both but you have… https://t.co/4N9FITkHwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@watsoncomedian @MikeTylerMagic We just opened as the newest residents in Las Vegas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[7th Grade Boys - Pool A - Cavs Elite def. Jr. Disciples by forfeit @exposurebball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganB_TV @1EverettAnthony @Hulkenstein13 Oh i already screenshoted 😁😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashtonpittman With good reason. He had a chance to fix the healthcare system but he decided to vote no as a big FU… https://t.co/KyA6IjaUG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Federal agents find $19M worth of cocaine in pineapple shipment at Georgia port  https://t.co/tzxSCoSwDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this is how it’s going to be, huh? Even down to the nonsense Trump tweets...   Kentucky definitely deserves bett… https://t.co/bLRhQ5Emw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC I don’t see the word “wall” anywhere. And I’d believe almost anyone who doesn’t sound like this https://t.co/AeFfTYzQQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qclarkson3 @VegaPerkins @RowdyDowds Not at you but there are a multitude of juniors that are ruining it for everyone else]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t decide if this is a good ruling ???  Let’s hope we never have to start the draft again.  But when you look… https://t.co/1KT4VjuxMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JemsOpal Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8Wankmaggot45 The last 2 plus years has been like the ground hog movie minus the laughs..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottWWright reports Clydesdale chief nets £730,000 of shares but all is not well in the camp!!  https://t.co/1JImEwAeql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters So they use a picture that looks like he’s already had a stroke, classy Reuters, real classy]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's mentally unstable! @realDonaldTrump  Nancy Pelosi is reveling in her glory after retaking the powerful Speake… https://t.co/o6tB85NZdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPDONeill @NYPDTransit @NYPDHighway @NYPDCommAffairs  Please get with the #NewTransitParadigm. It’s about… https://t.co/ah4VpVCtKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictorJoecks 1. "Education establishment" (Your words) is a thinly-veiled attack. Ignorant.   2. No, the money is… https://t.co/BTgmgkH4RX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in Solon Township this morning in northern Kent County where we expect investigators will return, searching for… https://t.co/u3x7gM4zcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gerketurkey195 @TheDraftAnalyst I still think Wennberg can end up being a very good player and Kirby Rychel ended… https://t.co/kh4xpgfVVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerformanceGov @uspto @USNavy Apparently inspired by piano notes played randomly, she and a compatriot, were under… https://t.co/ZQx0a0y6W8]]></document><document><![CDATA[ESPN just showed a graphic titled "Eastern Conference Contenders" it had Milwaukee Toronto Philly Boston Ummmm Indi… https://t.co/8PBkcHYiTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Completely unheard of... @dukebasketball down 23 pts and comes back to win it 71-69 against Louisville. Don’t care… https://t.co/NvVXsBPRcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@She_just_tweets @WifeSwap @paramountnet i would call mr. robot fairly exaggerated 🤔 perhaps writers are useful but… https://t.co/24x4tximpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido @Diego_Arria  @marcorubio @MariaCorinaYA @NituPerez se lo difícil que es tomar la decision de pedir que ay… https://t.co/r1Ug8xtho4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_bernie_bro @RiderOfKarma Sadly, we have became what we were supposed to be fighting. https://t.co/uIw7KN9gbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Ocean City Elementary School in Ocean City, MD https://t.co/UFjBzDMssB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiophysicalFrog @stephenfloor But this tweet perfectly sums up my experience: I never got a coherent answer from a… https://t.co/4qgqTdBIWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyMalone @LightAesthetic You do work on @Marvel games, you can’t expect your co-workers to pick up on a Batman reference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magagary687 @mikandynothem If liberals didn’t have middle fingers they would be mute]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting out of debt is NOT paying off past due bills. That’s just building you a clear runway to creat more. It’s a… https://t.co/ayeEjepYCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Demosthenes_Cle I believe they’ve asked a couple teams to go to the party with them to tango, cause it takes two f… https://t.co/uHVCKBSFSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[FUCK YOU DICKHEAD REFS @OfficialNBARefs NBA needs to investigate it and quit cheating on the SPURS 😡😡😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisisHog @BG_Red_22 @JFeinsteinBooks @thegax @chriskeiser @SBN_BillC Yeah. He's still there. The little wordsmith… https://t.co/zzDYDeUgRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The former @Unionmhockey standout signed with the @NJDevils after the 2010-11 season, his sophomore season. Played… https://t.co/ztObYoyJJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rafaelshimunov Read how regime militias of Maduro terrorize parishioners and desecrate churches whose congregation… https://t.co/VE3L9LRZpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjtruth @DailyCaller Why do I expect Avenatti to show up regarding this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[No need to look here. #fatpompeo tells @SenatorMenendez don’t look too closely as@th #American people don’t know wh… https://t.co/R3lRY36hV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great times at Blen Blen with MsMorales! 🙏🏽🎷💃🏽🕺🏽🎶😎 https://t.co/K52TIh9thq @ SoHo Dance L.A. https://t.co/dXCML64HwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImMostlyWrong I just saw this reply. I was like is this dude for real.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another killer batch!! - Drinking a They're Good Hops, Brent (Batch 6) by @voodoobrewery at @voodoobrewery  — https://t.co/RKHEln2fGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiscottiNicole @thewrightleader @DisruptedTv @lportnoy @TaraMartinEDU @mafost @pattersonaubrey @ERobbPrincipal… https://t.co/UuktjHmghJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fieryfalliblist @Intrinsic29 @theother_95 We’ve got millions of non-citizens working in this country without votin… https://t.co/Xc9ksMpMij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davemeltzerWON Hard to imagine when I turn on raw and see has been rousey and Charlotte flair that this used to be… https://t.co/l0Fi1g3qQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Justin...Prison won't be so bad...Hahaha  #canpoli @cbc @sun @TorontoStar @am640oakley @globepolitics… https://t.co/uCbYR2JlWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job @BG_Basketball ! Men’s &amp; Women’s Desert Region Champions. It’s a great night for BG Hoops. 🏀🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning dog walk in the fresh #snow. #Cranston @wpri12 https://t.co/qpUSWh34HG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #RealAsianGranny was relocated to Tule Lake internment camp during ww2, the family lost everything, including th… https://t.co/zOVDxqrlAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woot! Double OT and PG13 with the floater to win! https://t.co/Tz2EHKurGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Soon Pil Hongs Academy, learning how to kick better than anyone in the world. https://t.co/I7toAuYs86]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Wisconsin captain representing team USA in 2020. Already excited for the #RyderCup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlevinKelevra_1 Yeah I mean it’s a hit to his legacy in some degree but I’m just saying can we stop comparing the… https://t.co/9FmDD2mNpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetrudz Potatoes in any form are amazing. I'd enjoy mashed potatoes as a snack. Also, sliced cucumber.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minot State softball completes the weekend sweep with a one-hit 1-0 win over Dickinson State. #NSICsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[WB girls basketball was in the state final four in 2001 and 2003   Also won districts in 2012]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GChristCLE In violation of Ohio State Law... that puts the onus on the driver to stop and make sure it is clear before proceeding.]]></document></documents></author>