<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[gotta love the mirth #mirth #giggle #grin #clever https://t.co/kCJV8O7ZIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAMARA_SUJU @JMVivancoHRW Dra. Los Venezolanos somos personas preparadas,basta ya que Insulsa y muchos mas apoyen… https://t.co/xKVN7Ybul2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCAR @keselowski #DAYTONA500 That’s just heartbreaking. Brad couldn’t get his car back to the pit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I repeat, it’s NEVER okay to touch someone w/o their permission and binary standards of beauty are bullshit. This m… https://t.co/ZVJHDnru8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Keep fighting the good fight and doing what's best for America. #BestPresidentEver #BuildTheWallAndCrimeWillFall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kurumi_RL Don't worry I won't ask those kind of questions if you want me to know you will tell me. Hope all is well]]></document><document><![CDATA[#YalitzaAparicio's success has brought increased attention to 68 indigenous nations in #Mexico, where up to 14% of… https://t.co/yMWt1zwE4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of #NationalKolacheDay, here's a look back at the woman behind @koalakolache, who lobbied to get today dec… https://t.co/1QZbiLCXZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_B322 @OneMouse1Dream I do that at 5:00 today.. I’m getting anxious to see if I can handle it. Lol. These t… https://t.co/3DHT2sQlpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are y’all doing this morning?  I’ve studied my Bible, paid bills, and now I’m working while watching old episo… https://t.co/5XPEMmn0rG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will go to my grave not understanding why anyone would want this person to be the face of America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the littlest shit makes me too happy that’s why my feelings always hurt 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get it, I’m locked out of my Zocdoc account. Just don’t feel like calling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stella Naymik, freshman at Nordonia High School, performing her award winning @nhdcontest performance for… https://t.co/XkDGXZuG7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful send off for the one and only @brodyismefriend @thecomedystore @kenjeong @realjeffreyross and @funnyordie… https://t.co/tDJqLjmWIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I leave tomorrow ! Too bad I’m deathly afraid of airplanes otherwise I’d be more excited]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch This woman is living like a queen and we are paying for it!  She should be reigned in!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelfromSD @spitfirecos Was literally about to comment the same thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaBialkowski @provdcrumblover @Southeast70D @establishmentno @2tall2fall4it @DanFoc77 @akvawe66… https://t.co/HQ77XyWhqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando tocó fondo y ya no puedo más ,si busco a una persona ,es mucho 😪.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got the #RocketLeague Championship on easy mode. Yay!! (Like anyone really cares...) #GoIdiots https://t.co/NiveI6883Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just add another one to the list of fucked me over. When it comes to running a business, time is money and I don’t have extra of either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aug1405 @JulieReichwein1 @NJ_2_FL @sappermartin @jeffreysadezwi1 @DMShockley @roderunner01 @Rightwingmadman… https://t.co/QBynIbbnru]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had $1 for every time a dude called me psycho, I’d have enough money for a house in the Keys with 500 dogs, aw… https://t.co/ByrHIcV0O1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@607andy @danyelledrexler @bevandeveire @lindapaintgirl @RSun82 @evieyannakidis @1annoyingmother @mich_novelle… https://t.co/nTmwY14PJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@_arson gets out 3 on strike 4 and we're off the the bottom of the 9th needing 2 runs to stay alive. 5-3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I send you a funny video on twitter and you don’t react the way I expect you to, then I’m not sending you shit else 😂🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes This ads is really funny. Such a left wing reporting . Was a customer for many years. Our customers ask wh… https://t.co/vbUT7X40A2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllCharisma @AP I loved seeing him in anything. What a tremendous loss at such a young age.  I hope people afford… https://t.co/TtX3z0FqPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[ur parents should have never procreated you’re actually a walking abortion o:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders  You really are a Special Kind Of Stupid aren’t you??? 👎👎👎👎👎 #NeverBernie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Это Рогозину нужно так отправлять своих людей,  ракеты то не взлетают. Подпрыгнут как на батуте и в кусты. И освяще… https://t.co/kcCx2v8w4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up and left the apt early only to miss the train by a second and now I’m late 😭 lmfaooooo kms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a great day I just finished up with a editorial shoot for @DaHairGuru that is owned by one of the best pe… https://t.co/hNRCaWmPdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHeartRadio @TheStylesFandom #iHeartAwards #BestCoverSong #StillTheOne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jambie1017 @milesgrace77 @krissy9326 Billy had chemistry with pretty much everyone that he worked with on #Days. I… https://t.co/LvxHy6e8v6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stewpotfan @dinogcole @mcclellandglass @CalimityF @Sharksbait5300 @62Greenmachine @KimKawata Let's go racing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[tfw you drive 3 hours to see all your friends and all they want to do is sleep https://t.co/ynowedgECq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend and I have been having long ass conversations in his truck lately before I go home and its literally ever… https://t.co/3sRFBoT7n8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopCulLibrn Ugh I know this feeling and it’s terrible &amp; the result of racism &amp; simply unjust 😡 sending 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenziepass I understand! Nothing wrong with you. You have a big heart. Sometimes the bigger the heart, the bigger… https://t.co/vEPvNMuhgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY DO ENTRY LEVEL CLASS PROFESSORS INSIST ON GOING THE WHOL CLASS TIME? My junior level classes don’t even meet half the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m waiting to wash my car and I just watched some young girl accidentally soak her mother who was on the phone. I’m dying 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a friend tell me he had a nice camera but never learned to use it and didn’t see the need since he had his iP… https://t.co/KxuChgVYHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau  Your transparency isn’t showing anymore. Please fix this I DO NOT WANT @AndrewScheer as my next PM!… https://t.co/jRSOxUHJgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spurs @lonniewalker_4 teamed up with the Boys and Girls Club of SA to donate bikes and backpacks to kids! https://t.co/WXirGPCO8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that you are dust, and unto dust you shall return. #wordstoliveby #ashwednesday @ Syracuse, New York https://t.co/YIbwKZiazT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilriss69 i tried really hard to think of some fruit pun or even in my tummy digestion pun that would rhyme w stat… https://t.co/VrpObmDzH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone tell my why lexi and I are two weeks into our friendship and I’ve literally never laughed this hard in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A little loss of dignity is worth having a family that loves me... and please address me as Princess Sparklemutt”… https://t.co/wgf876p9JB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Omg how many #45 morons are there who will stop at nothing to protect his sorry fat ugly ass? You… https://t.co/wrKXhnJ5uK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love R. Kelly’s defense, it’s golden. “Why would I do that? Why man? It’s stupid man!” Yeaaa....everyone in jail… https://t.co/IRQFvykJou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes when you go through things your mother saved you find something really neat. @Macalester #heymac Mary Gwe… https://t.co/xjReJyDEyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is book cover #5 of my 7 Book challenge.  Post seven covers of books you love - no comments, no reviews just t… https://t.co/muaCljoqhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceMcdiarmid Oh, I usually buy pine or cinnamon during winter but this cheaper candle was amazing!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogie @visituenoland @uenodotco I would love to speak here as a follow up to my @Epicurrence speech?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making my own yarn. Time consuming yet satisfying. Plying the two colourways together is like going on an adventure… https://t.co/mdyKFleYUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I searched my House up &amp; Down for 2 hours trying to find my two Parakeet Birds...🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Traveling is about finding those things you were never looking for” 🖤 #travel #travelblogger #travelquote https://t.co/iahPOYuE60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wedding show with the best colleagues! @AndazOttawa https://t.co/KXbkya0C8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker I think Biden-Beto is the winning combination. Just saying...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post college: o shit it's 9pm I better go to bed soon or I'm gonna hate my life tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Adolescents entering the adult world in the 21st century will read and write more than at any other time in human… https://t.co/MV7ENdviOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, my grandma thought she heard Nick’s name as “Dick” and for a split second, I thought about not correcting her. 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitches be up until 5am like they ain’t got class at 8 and then complain when they only get 2 hours of sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[$1500 for summer term for one 3 unit class .....this is suppose to be a affordable ☠️☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c_chanter @YouTube Totally bizarre! If I didn't have a sense of the whack-o-doodles, I would have needed a sweat l… https://t.co/EDR7C84yoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[That sounds about right @USRepLong @RoyBlunt —you support a crook, liar, traitor. Have you no decency. I guess not]]></document><document><![CDATA[That last girl looked too much like a young Miranda to go with Blake... also pretty sure that’s why he didn’t fight for her #TheVoice⁠ ⁠]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited just noticed your on next in Just add love  woo hoo #LukeMacfarlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unless @NYCMayor plugged in his phone to the aux and hit play I don’t see how this is his fault. 🤷🏽‍♀️ if you’re lo… https://t.co/ZNLpM6bLFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabrielUrbinaTM @laurenshippen You’re both monsters that I love very much]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeculiarBaptist @VixenRogue Nope, it's when millennials cant figure out how to remove the pit of an avocado, are r… https://t.co/eTa5IcorKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been thinking about what @JCasaTodd said all day! We need to think about Digital Leadership skills!… https://t.co/69hFFcX8yO]]></document><document><![CDATA[MORTA A GLÓRIA PIRES  TO MUITO EMOCIONADA A PORTELA É TUDO   Ficou estranho pq a repórter tava esperando por mais e… https://t.co/wpbrkjzuBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My anxiety is through the roof today. It's the kind of anxiety where you feel stuck to the floor, and it feels like… https://t.co/gdKnls37VU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenOfGeele Are they also of the noncomplected hue? This sounds so awful and I’m sorry you have to go through tha… https://t.co/fSdW07qa9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well.. I made a vowel to myself! And because I love me so much now I must honor it! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cantero9Vega @angsala67 @Fernand71851410 @mainzina @LilianaSnchez9 @szalacain1 @jobragag @JSaintPastour Feliz juev… https://t.co/rTGDFOtuNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this is happening. 😳 Vamosssss.....   #lunch #BarçaValladolid https://t.co/fe10HKX5yk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tourangeau_lynn @janettemsu @erinkrakow @hallmarkmovie @hallmarkchannel My ‘go to’ was Taco Bell!! #Hearties 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeonWhi63670221 @Johndzergoski2 @SBDSoultrain @TT197 @RussellMace2 @ThereseOSulliv2 @Southeast70D @ACMeyor… https://t.co/58KfS6PHdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[spending so much time and effort making others happy and it just keeps on backfiring]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh, Henry, you’re so stupid... Seriously, Judith is the only #TWD⁠ kid who can handle herself!! #TheWalkingDead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MADLearn @AlefiyaBhatia @BuggMagnet @bynoemama @DriveMindGroup @stoneg57 Yes!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClueHeywood Asking for only feet — and without an unsolicited dick pic — practically counts for chivalry these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrestonSJohnson @GCTelegram @JandiRiddle @holubc Ugh I wish. Too bad because I’m pretty sure it’s just going to be a Gordmans]]></document><document><![CDATA[BIGBANG - KOEWOKIKASETE(声をきかせて) M/V [HD] https://t.co/cnspilUZM0 ❤️ una madrugada de martes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jewelsjadeee I wish I’d seen this sooner!!! I needed hugs from my kiddos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving the Jin fancams going around today  #SoompiAwards⁠ ⁠ #TwitterBestFandom⁠ ⁠ #TeamBTS @BTS_twt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shossy2 @sbaker209 Will someone please find out if it is true that Russian FM Sergey Lavrov just happens to be in… https://t.co/u10mBFN0mn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to go home tomorrow😊 have slept so terrible this week I just want MY bed with my animals and all my pill… https://t.co/U5n4BK8sOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleRScarano I only get a 2 day weekend. Still have work on Monday 😩😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[My recent #CDKL5 art purchases are finally one step closer to a debut in my home! Thanks to @ArtForHLC @sbculliton https://t.co/60G72sD1NG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Character is like a tree and reputation like a shadow. The shadow is what we think of it; the tree is the real thing. Abraham Lincoln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IkaRuss6 @PrimeCreator2 @MAGAforc @JeremyRobards7 @elskemccain @hmcd123 @mona_cajun @WYATT251 @staggerlee422… https://t.co/wWnnkU713z]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are 3 things I would never say no to. If you can name them all 3 in the correct order margs are on me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Rainbow by @KaceyMusgraves plays in the background* https://t.co/WC9UIElBPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews I wish outlets like yours would stop giving attention to celebrities.  I really don’t care what they… https://t.co/wGsGwv8WGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we’ve heard from our Indigenous partners is that treaties need to adapt to changing priorities. Earlier this m… https://t.co/eqKhdHCqxe]]></document></documents></author>