<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @FoxNews we in canada are worried if the lunatic democrats ever get in power we will have to build a wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmZachCooper @WithoutACauseWA I think you actually will! Let Max know you are a huge fan of @ImSteveMigs and that… https://t.co/tfmf1xg92r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully the #Daytona500 will be so much better than this, The Clash and Duels come tomorrow. I wanna see a lot of… https://t.co/xQEWhwrbvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TirzahMJ Hahahaaaaa! Oh man, I better keep you away from kids... I got one that is already recording everything I… https://t.co/DdZBQN0j1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timcast Thanks for your work. The world needs people like you around. Actual journalism!  #BeanieMan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy estaba hablando con una amiga, que me preguntaba qué destino del mundo le recomendaba. Es algo que me preguntái… https://t.co/tc1lluP1sb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Six Kentucky players playing tonight in the @okcthunder and @PelicansNBA game. @BBN #BBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j15royals @twarner50 It’s 20th anniversary is coming up in a week or so and I’m excited to revisit it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The newest member of our family! Haven't given her a name just yet, but she sure can sing. #newbass #schecter… https://t.co/Z1hhEDKXyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day in Denver which means I’m gonna smoke a giant joint before I go to the airport tonight lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[As An Army Veteran we have to thank Gary Siniese for ALL of the thinks that you have done for Veterans and their Fa… https://t.co/KYvRiZkOVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EitanBenezra Ojalá que le den la oportunidad a Hugo, si no funciona que lo corran así de fácil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AFreakyDude @RealEnli @newpatriot77 @dbroncos78087 @DeityOfGaming @ProSlayer @wweukfanatic @oldy75 @CardoHq… https://t.co/1hVcbpa2uv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@instagram  @InstagramES See this Instagram photo by @lil_jj96 @people https://t.co/X71u0citWc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#laherencia #outonasundayevening #readysetgo @ La Herencia De ybor https://t.co/gX7Xea6cdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mantle1956 @SkyArts Pinot Grigio, Chinese food, and of course all three of my bb teams on tv at the same time 😡.… https://t.co/oBArFlnZkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobWolh @DonaldJTrumpJr @POTUS Millions? More lies Jakey? https://t.co/PZtkFljr0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, no, no ¡qué belleza! ❤️❤️❤️ @Palomafaith no puedo de amor https://t.co/5f5eIJxRIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChandlerCBS3 just now. All lanes not moving due to a fire by exit 4A-B ramp 95sb Newark, DE https://t.co/5utZi7RGXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dragonflyeye You forgot the very special episode of Quincy which warned Gen X parents about the punk rock scene in… https://t.co/LkJ0xAOlY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoyoteDriverJR @TommyG You have no clue what this word even means. It is a private company.  No one is being "dise… https://t.co/WTFoz0eTQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entonces el pusilánime de @NicolasMaduro reconoce que en #VenezuelaLibre esta en una Crisis humanitaria terrible, p… https://t.co/bWu41DrKXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life hella boring bet ima find out I have cancer or some soon and I wish I was bored again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PuroBareback @hotlatinoncn Hola baby q Rica cobra y Rico veneno q echas yo quiero esa cobra baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenKamalaHarris then what are you? A #Dem virtue signaling, identity politics opportunist with Presidential aspira… https://t.co/AfnpkZrIs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya es fin de semana, saquen el pasito perrón... @ Guadalupe, Nuevo Leon https://t.co/QIj154aeAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/uKJrlUrbfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls be having a bf Sunday-Thursday then the second Friday hit they are back to single]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for interviewing my grandpa yesterday about the #StumpDumpFire. Good that the national guard is here but… https://t.co/8ZDxp4QRRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelleDbelle I feel kind of weird admitting this but back in middle school I learned that taking a simple string… https://t.co/z3GF4Ri40t]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they’re not actively undermining actual progress Dems enact thru working in real life, they will use right-win… https://t.co/qke5fVzfZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[No it’s a way to win again asshat, let’s face it, you can continue to resist and loose any credibility or respect y… https://t.co/raxz0Iik4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[60 to 70 percent day-of. That is how @GMA schedules social. #RaganDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yanawrites @moonasking2stay And especially not dead former characters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmariBetter Longhorns that are available could fill your teams needs 3 longhorn DBs are available Malcom brown &amp; Charles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Watch the language bro. Don’t go down to his level. 😎😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sammy_Roth And cap-and-trade is another example, although a less disastrous one. Hasn't exactly lived up to expect… https://t.co/uSHcFrRDKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[CARALHO COMO ASSIM A PASSAGEM DE ONIBUS EM CURITIBA VAI AUMENTAR PRA 5,20????? CINCO E VINTE MEU CARALHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st day of Spring Ball Mood: #FlashFAST #BeTHeA1PHA https://t.co/LlGkUEE8nm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriJacobus @OsborneInk Manafort proves that if your a crook, do it big, and wear a suit. so you are in the Swamp.?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacob Poetl needs more minutes with the #Spurs. His interior defense is AWESOME!!!! #GoSpursGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TurkeyCards Not so much at card shows- the one or two I may get to during the year have people selling things at a… https://t.co/gs8lr1eFss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJCharlieBlac @ByNickFarrell @GoldAndBlueZone @JordanMcCabe5 Thats a Huggins kind of player. This happens the next… https://t.co/QD0VzIFbVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be honest I’m excited about the 5G @Android is coming out with, I guess this is goodbye @Iphone 🤔🙈🤭🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Tuesday Night.  #photographyoftheday #photographyaddict #photographynature #photographyblog #photography… https://t.co/0c3hO76YIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[We know that You are making a way even when we don’t see a way...Help us to stand strong in You so that we may see… https://t.co/wW27EPBmM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbroadInJapan When I go to Japan I'm just going to sit on this corner all night long.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The road to the @American_MBB Championship for @UCF_MBB will likely be Memphis on their home court, then Houston, t… https://t.co/Wwn4kzdEU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave @LauraDarlin0163 @WashTimes Independent Conservative Women President 2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrBradJohnson I always allowed eating in my classroom which was in direct violation of my school’s policies and pr… https://t.co/qkhU9nYUP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newtgingrich If that's what Dear Leader wants, it MUST be important! #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 I tell people about white privilege and how I've used it to my advantage (sadly as a petty criminal and… https://t.co/HmUPaRyDdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__AllisonWeis @J_Worz Might as well carpool if we are all going to the same place]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prosthetic with Sense of Touch Lets Patients Know Its Location https://t.co/1MrtRaOOMH #DigitalHealth #AI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @Franovik (get_repost) ・・・ Support your local designers and Natural Born Artists. Purchase tickets at www.… https://t.co/UCAFnoefVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bruceonthel00se @soooooperslam is this the margaritaville patio? 🤙🏽🤙🏽🤙🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strike me down should, today, I read a second stupid question masquerading as a news headline. #mondaythoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmoknSara420 @Tinkerbell_High @AllVape3 Morning sarah , how are you hung ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DallasAJackson I play somewhat regularly on Xbox and am still a low level. Let's get it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RapidFireTruth @craignoteggs @fyrefestival Craig IS the next #FyreFestival]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn’t matter who we pray too. We all need to just embrace spirituality and become one who believes in a higher be… https://t.co/BoNKagGx2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMoody95 I definitely understand that mentality. But once you are established in your career and money isn’t a hug… https://t.co/xfVP58RRNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jspin80 @Jollybucnroger @KDPomp @damienwoody @steelers That's a false equivalency. Also, you dont think the Steele… https://t.co/G9m3eY3YiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmfa I think @LouDobbs is referring to #DisasterDonny #TrumptyDumpty #45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein Trump proposed the #AbsoluteBest reform to apply ON TOP OF THE #ACA https://t.co/v1D9x0N5UE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to start this trope on the asymmetrical brain! @postrestinst @RonHruska https://t.co/VrYDaKoG6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaiHsia @patrick_hruby Seeks like bribe to prescribe one poison of another]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The Instant by @newanthembeer at @BottleRevApex — https://t.co/KF1HQPJaX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBeschloss I agree Steven but now they are at a crossroad and their party’s relevancy for the next decade is… https://t.co/mdTH8DGKML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkittkat That I-man talking about don't call him and leave him alone. Psssh really he invades our show I'll tell e… https://t.co/F9Lmh6ApWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago race heats up | Lori Lightfoot campaign launches attack ad against Toni Preckwinkle https://t.co/9Qi0VFFXhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we've met at @MyVMUG #LeaderSummit, you've probably heard me talking about the @AsBuiltReport from @mattallford… https://t.co/6rTZcdhzDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to be so quick to move back to Florida when this whole grad school thing is said and done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CherokeeNewLeaf @jonfavs @pithypacky Obama knew what was in it. That’s why he suggested that it was expanded to se… https://t.co/DjsBOrzT82]]></document><document><![CDATA[The  frantic search for the buried victim turned into a grim recovery effort with cadaver dogs as night fell and re… https://t.co/eZO9i6O6bd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust @billshortenmp @NickMcKim @RichardDeNatale  &amp; it drags on again #auspol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz And wasting our tax dollars to do it.  Can we sue them to stop them from wasting our money?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 1413 Mendocino Creek Drive in Patterson, CA https://t.co/8yCauW2TRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNCastaldo @RyanAFournier She looks like an actual leader since Mexico is one of our closest allies, and drugs and… https://t.co/kU5Lrgze7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confronting anti-Semites on Facebook is considered "bullying" now? #cowards #trash #zuckerberg #naziagenda @ Etobic… https://t.co/0IzSPpqR9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qanon76 @realDonaldTrump If you think that autocratic leaders are about returning power to the people - study world history]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shego is so hilarious - I love @taylor_ortega! Hope this year’s Coke 600 at @CLTMotorSpdwy turns out to be the best… https://t.co/AqqIJKzhnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really doesn’t matter what a politicians says on camera.  It matters how he or she votes when the time comes.  A… https://t.co/xqmhtMHU2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobVanDillen Should have seen the same happening yesterday in South Central Ontario on the Queen Elizabeth Way and… https://t.co/9SOW2gSIWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good night everybody. Please take care you all of you. To my friends in this Twitter I love you guys dearly. You ha… https://t.co/9C9EhLJHu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffnoelmidlife @YouTube Love that you shared this! Appreciate your insight Jeff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone tells you that addiction is a choice, that the opioid epidemic is weakness of character or spirit, know t… https://t.co/bmnUd3Bmvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#job #mental #breakdown @ Blalock's Glen At Nathan's Landing https://t.co/MIH348aPtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una velocidad  muy decente (para ser gratis) la que ofrecen @googlemexico y @SITWIFI en el aeropuerto de Monyerrey,… https://t.co/BVC6Uso4D9]]></document><document><![CDATA[And with our campaign committee official with NYS we are officially open for business! Lift off! #RD2020… https://t.co/vjQCEeptvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @Sekusa1 @heyitsCarolyn @nancy_hamm1 @Rbigzs @Frances_712 @mymynags @AsiaTater @DoingRight1… https://t.co/Gfe8d143Mn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And...yet another tweet that Bif clearly did not write.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExactSpy9060 Yeah, you're not the only one that thought they'd be recolors]]></document><document><![CDATA[An amazing evening with #AlvinAiley in Chicago. Also got to see an old friend who has known me since I was a teen.… https://t.co/EYikdjp12q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachmorrisDSHS Great! Have a great day @JKatGB63  &amp; I are enjoying to Hill Country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joel_eisenberg How about Dan Crenshaw receiving his "Captain Marvel"-inspired glass eye?  He certainly is smarter… https://t.co/tdWFroKJ6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Few things give me more joy in this world than buffalo wings and craft beer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start up logo what  do you guys think?... 🎬🎞📽 #production #actorslife #worldstar #filmmaker #Film #talent #artists… https://t.co/QweevT2Oez]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have tea with the stars and swim with the sharks @ Margaritaville Atlantic City https://t.co/uYigUnTzGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katy_canum @ConnorR_13 wow katy not finding something funny... shocker (great tweet btw connor)]]></document></documents></author>