<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I should be pissed that I unwittingly received an embalming fluid facial but since it’s metal as fuck, I guess I’m cool with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalCaribbean Thanks! This is probably my favourite picture from my stateroom too. That cruise ship sailed next t… https://t.co/8m0Grl8MNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LavigneTv ‘Living thoughts by Lora’. New daily/weekly segment on @KLFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loganbnewby It’s looking like another match-up with Duke and Carolina for a spot in the finals of the ACC tourney… https://t.co/Y7FgL7ONku]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd? My guy this happened to snoop dogg. You just finally realized the pattern.    More like 6000th rapper 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMJimmy1 @jen_keesmaat The world is changing. There are new solutions to those problems. My dog’s food arrives at… https://t.co/y3GsRNB6Xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DillonMcCabe Tops. Been a huge fan of Welch ferever', when she hooked up w Rawlings just upped the ante.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An effective leader knows how to manage those under his authority and has the will to do what is right for them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to March 29th #WeNeedDiverseBooks #ChildrensBooks #libchat #walterawards # https://t.co/TKTKGze1w0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying and blessing land where we’ve started foundations to build homes for single Mother’s and others who need a… https://t.co/W8R7IFTtAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening night of the Holy Roar tour with @christomlin.  Don’t miss this show. @ accesso ShoWare Center https://t.co/TSwAWqq3d6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelindsayellis @ShadowTodd I was just ranting earlier tonight about Google clearly not caring about the pedophile… https://t.co/WtuVH9XzEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsleonleon I’m sitting at work crying listening to your album. It is so beautiful. Thank you so much for putting… https://t.co/HTOZ2VmSUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Arsenio Hall      #newps #newport #newportbeach #peninsula #balboa #ocean #beach #sea #talk #talkshow #comedy… https://t.co/2DyGaSDsst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanaVugteveen @Mcgalec99 @troyer_paige @John_Neveling @shannadl1 @rick_thd @JHarrisonHD @Travis0703 @homerth15… https://t.co/FzHTsamOCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thought_AtWork That’s like saying Tyrek Hill better than Julio cause he’s more versatile lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StonehamPress Thank you Tim! 2 years of busting my rump for this Command! Phew! 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want REAL long-term impact on wealth-building, live well below your means and save with discipline. You won’… https://t.co/qv0Ct0hJJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZephyrRz There's a lot of wonderful character interactions, and I think it peaked when Ichigo made that incredibly… https://t.co/pfY88xSq7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaddyJim52 @Yakekoge @JeffHarperArt @solomongrundy6 @rightatheart @MrsPerrin @DaniScotchIrish @FactCheckU… https://t.co/QDFqqAsL1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful opening night performance of Eugene Onegin by the Washington National Opera at the #KennedyCenter tonight… https://t.co/QXPkEv4Pt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m meant to marry someone who manages a hedge fund and live in a penthouse in between 70th-80th st/park ave… https://t.co/VrQ0M7rbWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so I'm going to need a tour featuring @TooCloseToTouch @OutlineInColor @MykaRelocate @PointNorthBand and @boysoffallband please. 🤔😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Taagol @urbanbarbarian Stop.  I’ve been looking at comic book art for 40+ years.  The cover was composed in such a… https://t.co/69J7wBP9h5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished up The Umbrella Academy on Netflix. I really enjoyed it! It had some slow parts but overall I thought it w… https://t.co/7RJRGGSSqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachAllwoodLax The officials that I see on a reoccurring basis I will tell my players in scout what they tend to… https://t.co/AFU9j9bOfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M_DelRay @TheWesleyWoods @PierceParisXXX @Dante_Colle @Draven_Navarro @rickylark1n @RickyRoman91 @BrandonWildeXXX… https://t.co/YY9aWROqrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsIzzyMania She is getting a bit heelish too. Maybe that should of been her role all along.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be fair, the Left does a pretty good job of making ITSELF look insane without the help of Ocaasional-Cognition.… https://t.co/JbD5yd2IxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still No MAGA HATS : I Live in Trump territory believe me. But in the 2 years since Trump got elected by the Electo… https://t.co/89QUccXFIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cellmavin @cedarflats @SierraNevada @CATbrew13 @ManvsAle @beerhunter74 @linda_lballis @JacobGrimes @zappafaye… https://t.co/ahdedOD3hS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonesCarter is leading the Harris County Pct 2 Bike Program that is adding 50 miles of dedicated bike lanes to Cit… https://t.co/kiN6YtEeqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NavygirlLaura Personally, I'd like to see a race where *the best, most qualified candidate with an actual soul* wins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[By this logic  #DenzelWashington  should not have played #MalcolmX..........😨 #WillSmith https://t.co/oDLOammT2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is this trash truck 😭😭 I could have been done dropping this pod off 30 minutes ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final destination. Unsure who am I rooting for. Guess will go for the future Knick KD. @ Wells Fargo Center https://t.co/vmdSqJgeWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCECassie As a Red Wings fan, one of my favorite memories was attending a game between the Wings and the Blues at… https://t.co/GolMhrH1w2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuSuBi19 @AddledPixie To my ears it’s a whistle, M. A friend suggested maybe a hermit thrush but it wasn’t a match]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elijahhughes4_ Happy birthday! How about 21 points on Wednesday to celebrate? We're all rooting for ya!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s all tied up at 15 here between JA &amp; Prep with 4:50 left to play]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelirioJennie What an amazing night you gave me last night. Over 3 hours total hunnie. Not bad for a man of my age… https://t.co/ckGF7fc2Xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son Clarke was watching a you tube video of @GoldenKnights @MFleuryFlower  We looked over and he was crying hard… https://t.co/AatY6lfKkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andrew Yang: the 2020 candidate warning of the rise of robots  https://t.co/E5X6CdlNzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome products!  I look great on the course until I hit the ball...I can’t wait until they create a product to co… https://t.co/OshZLo7obI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Linden Yard Fleet Operations in Brooklyn, NY https://t.co/K6ETw1Mbam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I just see @MartySmithESPN in the “Smoke a Little Smoke” video? Just now noticed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visit on Friday from Congresswoman Lori Trahan, MA 3rd Congressional District. @AFFOA_RFT  https://t.co/Qb27Wn3KPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeLibby2 And you couldn’t pay me all the money in the world to watch it 🤢🤢🤢🤢🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really fun session today finishing up tracks for Mark Christian Miller’s upcoming release. @remopercussion… https://t.co/g9NuuKRnEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1LLSMITH @BonnaWhite @MikeFord313rd Yall gotta chill on my eating habits. I was making 8.25 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throughout my experiences with trying new teas, so far the one from Long Island has been the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooner Lady Gymnasts dominate OUr Big XII neighbor Mountaineers leading each event:  Congratulations @OTrautman… https://t.co/uz2TpdZQm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not surprised when I see me and @Noter2424 having multiple convos in so many different places. I just started the third one here😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Almomentonet Y seguirá subiendo! El pueblo está cansado de la corrupción del PLD 12 años de Leonel un “ DESASTRE”… https://t.co/NVgOofd8pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelGrant_CJ @nytimes I went in having read some similar pieces and, honestly, wanting to hate it. It won me ov… https://t.co/aXFkBdXqB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freedom7930 @hoefsd They may control the Committees, but are Constrained by Laws. It is a violation of Law for the… https://t.co/65raaW1BY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I here someone call themselves an “influencer” I barf in my mouth a little bit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaycaspiankang @minakimes @JamesSurowiecki @kylenw @therealjjanze Blasphemy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSmashGordon @xactley @SportsTalkBarry Yeah I’m not seeing where he says “Lebron is the goat.” And if you’ve wa… https://t.co/aL0LQDTSR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Habs have been a pleasant surprise so far, but if they end up missing the playoffs and a high draft...well... t… https://t.co/j03PDTdR2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NopePierre Having spent extensive time around American Bison this summer, I can confirm that they are exceptionall… https://t.co/um2VVyAo5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaPavlovic destaca su trayectoria desde regidora hasta llegar a gobernadora. No ha sido fácil después de rese… https://t.co/bErBjxlBfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigitalTrends Ohhhhh I could totally make an SSX movie using that thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Small Giant by @TrueAnomalyBeer at @trueanomalybeer — https://t.co/liWqFonX07]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RafaDato2 @elcompitv @Rayados @ReneFdz @MemoriaFutbol_ @VerdirameSergio @sergio_trevi @Carlos_Ledezma… https://t.co/7Auc4ljw1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWThemeParks @derekburgan @Parkscope The Guardians show building is one of the least ugly buildings in Future Wor… https://t.co/7KqTWgVRof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else experience the new orange sour patch kids flavor lately? What the hell is going on over there? Asking f… https://t.co/OkTT4uuyj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier today I was mulling the idea of leaving all my bands. Depression does that. Five minutes ago I pitched a hu… https://t.co/KlMtSkFKJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colgados  en la pared como toda una obra de arte o estábamos  castigados???.... #pisomojadonopisen @ Magdalena de K… https://t.co/tuTPy2tPvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicole_soojung last time I got a ride from someone, the driver kept going on about WW2 and how evil the Japanese were.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night someone called me their “future ex-boyfriend.” I guess things are looking up oifstudio #bitterhipster… https://t.co/4ixHngO4kH]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/92qDM8wrwo So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew! One💚☯️☮️🤬! https://t.co/vMjkiUN80N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WildFacts @GodlyTeaching @AmyRoseKathryn @livepositive11 @JewishTweets ;)+]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pippenings Some good news that Greyhound racing is fading into history.   https://t.co/4mGDw8lTVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Badgerfan58 You forgot the first @F1 race as well! Big day in the middle of the month too!😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olinjoseph @marino420td @racerbluegold @AKAJeffBidwell @SiP03 The potential is there. Their enrollment is bigger t… https://t.co/0156mcBgFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I’m saying is that if anyone ever hits me in the face with cheese, it’s fucking on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[iHeart's Bob Pittman: 'Our niche is companionship https://t.co/CW2p35pLLH via @adage]]></document><document><![CDATA[Above all things I hope the education of the common people will be attended to, convinced that on their good sense… https://t.co/BetOVN4zs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wherefore, my beloved brethren, let every man be swift to hear, slow to speak, slow to wrath: James…… https://t.co/fHoQN2V6vz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_Gberg65 @NateT215 I’ll go back to my earliest comment about minutes with Embiid. The three games where Jimmy gai… https://t.co/HjoD9zV4Cd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Old Dominion University Constant Hall in Norfolk, VA https://t.co/z6lk6aLaZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaineIceHockey 's Devin Shore had a PPG &amp; an assist; @GoNUmhockey 's Josh Manson added a helper for Anaheim… https://t.co/HibiOyBAJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Senators Why was he not feeding the young guys steak? Smith and Boedker and Paajaarvi don't have the teeth to enjoy steak anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know what happened to my body clock but I fell asleep at 10:30. Woke up at 1 am. Worked profusely for 2 hours… https://t.co/RGvxMwn5F2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop watching this. My god, she’s so brilliant. I wish I had this capacity to get information so quickly, e… https://t.co/98R7Ur0S89]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are not consuming a broad variety of news and media(yes, including Fox News) during this extraordinary time… https://t.co/qNhJSF4vg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obxleatherman @HighHeatStats Nolan Ryan played 24 seasons after winning a World Series]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaMbINiT0 @1Fashionisima @NoticiasXtra @lacomayoficial @eramosnavarro Segun Quien????Loco Usted no Vivio lo q Yo V… https://t.co/Xe8AAfdgNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Medical Technologist - https://t.co/7cz26WAYAv #Healthcare #Gratiot, OH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachLockey We’ve had a full week of rain. Not golf for a little bit around here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thepetechapman @djnickuk @yourcolchester @MarkAlanCory @Tim4Labour Great post guys  Thanks For #RT @djnickuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgePaschall @williamlegate @realDonaldTrump You're not paying attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now wayment now.. This HORD because I was in middle school with one, and elementary with the other.. whew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe The Favourite was nominated for so many awards. This movie is baaaaaad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please take your time to look and see what's under the Reynolds Wrap. This is what they call delectable. This is wh… https://t.co/Ga8PRRGRSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ringer @celtics @sixers Big milestone for Ben though! Was -125 against Celtics coming in. Proving he should maybe… https://t.co/vADqfj5Cli]]></document><document><![CDATA[A year ago....when Phoenix was the center of the running Twitter universe! 👏🏻🏅We ran a lot of miles, and drank all… https://t.co/9PKZB0BN39]]></document><document><![CDATA[a month or two and i can do the same process i did to grow my freeforms. these days going by pretty fast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When do we investigate the @globeandmail for errors/negligence in reporting given ongoing evidence there is no wron… https://t.co/TiCm0h16it]]></document></documents></author>