<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@FiddleSabre @YouTube Lol fat fingers. What a lot of music is missing these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PIAABasketball brackets will be released today. Here are PCL teams that have clinched a spot in their respective c… https://t.co/PTloCj3Gr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbySchuller. I am laying in bed and I have an idea not sure if the idea is revenue to the church but you can res… https://t.co/47RYUFaV0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @kimloucoach • • • • • • What breakthroughs and breakdowns are you currently working on? ✨  Visit… https://t.co/tFWi480buC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SBNation Relax, the park is listed 2nd! Touch screen touchy! @ZionW32 @ZionNPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[big day for @SunDevilHoops !! ball out today fellas ! #nopityforthekitty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DD_Jessica_ Taking for granted A signed "[Double-u ( W )] contract..makes for A LegA-L Arguments of negligence, po… https://t.co/I6AnyG1plz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoChorus @hipped I have some space but I don’t know about the latter part ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW  Just got my first ever 4x5 images back from @OldSchoolLab - 🤩😍🤩😍🤩 https://t.co/0OPWAS1bc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once more, "a picture shows a thousand words."  Everything is still an allegation and innocent until proven guilty.… https://t.co/pDlsUrnwo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RB4420 @Thereal_vargas Gotta be a Charge, Seat was planted and not moving]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ash Wednesday  Altar Server with Father Paul Nguyen, Oblates of the Virgin Mary, St. Mary's Catholic Church Parochi… https://t.co/KmjKjQZVrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amvetsupport @brian_family2 I'm a Veteran..I'm  a Republican  but i have never supported Trump and never will he o… https://t.co/ukk2Lvyg6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[So nice for it to be 730PM and the sun is still out. Forgot what that felt like]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrismoodycom That is crazy. My cousins have been trying to build them a shelter in the woods up Flagstaff. Guess… https://t.co/g8a3KUSRP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNightEditor Awesome.  I grew up in Unionville.   Moved here back in '06.  Orlando is my home now.  My heart is… https://t.co/jlYU118heu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This probably means he's gonna fall off a cliff in the next month or two]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eclisham Well since it contains no caffeine, I’d have to agree with you. Doctor’s orders. Can we just call it a wa… https://t.co/BhwEj4SWO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @WashTimes Probably California. There a fucked up State.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is my ASK:   WHAT WHAT DOES UNIVERSAL ARCHITECTURE LOOK LIKE THAT CONNECTS THE BRAIN THE CITY AND THE CLOUD?… https://t.co/IAQtYbdfIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Many times I have agreed with you and appreciated your point of view.  HOWEVER, on this you are 100% wron… https://t.co/tKP84CyIfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will she make it? Tune into my Insta stories to find out!  . . . . #moma #cat #blackcat #catsofinstagram… https://t.co/qSV2jJd2Os]]></document><document><![CDATA[STP &amp; el zombie de Scott Weiland en Roxy Fest https://t.co/p5mf6cpNO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMRabbitt96 @BlogOfTheirOwn @StL_Braveheart @_FlyTheL_ @mmg49072 Johnny, what can you make of this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavisBarrs @Philipmarks87 @NickGunterGnG @DevilsDukeBlue https://t.co/tXRbyWjSz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starbeamart1 @skyvales Me too. It's sad to me she wants to cover up the scar in the shape of their hands reaching for each other.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 rings, 3 MVP trophies should WAYYY more than $3M😂😂 it’s for a good cause tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bone in chops on @biggreenegg.    Brined for about 4 hours before going on the egg.  Seated on both sides and finis… https://t.co/wGKyoaGs83]]></document><document><![CDATA[Student section should honestly wear brown bags over their faces for the rest of the semester. I would if I want to… https://t.co/cCtd8H2ol5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidMaherNL sounds right. the war will be won out here and on the avalon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#impeachTheMF @RepAdamSchiff @RepJerryNadler @RepMaxineWaters @USSupremeCourt1 @FBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxfalkowitz Lol i made claro stop serving mezcal in all the beautiful ceramic copitas they had]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epochblue @kennethreitz @veronica_hanus @PyTennessee Consistency is for the birds 😂 https://t.co/g3inNDlBIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffrey_white From the marlins “I think we can be competitive” hahaha that’s spring training speak for “I know we… https://t.co/nN9pl7IIz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, I give.  Places I’ve lived:  - Logan, UT  - Bountiful, UT - Clinton, UT - Busan, South Korea - Masan, South K… https://t.co/3MaaOz239b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, Down In The Valley, chock full of videos from all of the primary contributors. Covering ISU and the MVC in 20… https://t.co/TpZjUQrh53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanBrownWJOX @JayBilas @BhamHoops The G.O.A.T of basketball analysts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamAllen_1 @JussieSmollett Love @GrahamAllen_1 #tellnothingbuttruth!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lynn_Rose1 @AKraus59 @SwissTriple_M @AnnieReedSings @SenWhitehouse @realDonaldTrump @FedSoc @ReaderAdrift… https://t.co/lgSO26VGPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDotSportsGuy Tony Romo dated a TV host it was an open secret.. why does Josh and her  make it any different?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hot take on the Film Twitter Topic of the Moment: Evil Mega Corp Amazon frequently gives their movies theatrical… https://t.co/jMrea90gZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll throw @thepadge2u into this conversation.  Scored 2,500 points for @StHenryCRU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarTrek @ethangpeck @SonequaMG @StarTrekRoom @SpaceChannel @startrekcbs @StarTrekNetflix I begin my healing from… https://t.co/o0KSeg9ZJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awoozyyouth @PaulPromotes @superiorsadists @AdultModelProm1 @LuxGangPromo @robertgiguere59 @CMP_4U Nope. Grab a ra… https://t.co/2lTNHj1kN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The not so conservative republican President brings you blown budgets and bigger deficit. Reminds me of Bush 43.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VassyKapelos We all realize that it is to your best interests to drag this through the brush but it does not speak well for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baddestmamajama Reading, watching/talking to my parents, watching YouTube videos,]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Ken &amp; Dave's Bucs Oasis in Tampa, FL https://t.co/yTWvEWLUqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jscottvan59 I would trust you to operate on me. You’ve watched lots of tape.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSeigeDFS @ArbourPro You were literally mocking this 2 game Q playoff all day &amp; now you are touting it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[k.d. lang and I watch some @portlandia (including the episode she’s on) and we don’t die - we then jam out so hard,… https://t.co/fKUqRUoK8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMALifeOfficial Styles make fights. Connor needs a win BADLY. If he’s matched correctly-like say Donald Cerone-he… https://t.co/N2RdHfpycb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donmariogomez A  mi me hubiese gustado pero q gusto les a de verdad o a los q no querían q ganara]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big thank you to @RicksProTruck for working late tonight to get our new signage installed. Anxious to begin the 2019 campaign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ramses_Siverio Creo q llegó el momento de solicitar ayuda internacional!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSN1040  @DavePratt1040  This happens every year in other sports leagues, just first time it happens in hockey. Br… https://t.co/gXidQfRaDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pfmiller0 @AaronDConner @nytmike @maggieNYT @adamgoldmanNYT @anniekarni There;s still no evidence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s got two thumbs and is serving as a judge for today’s #IrvineBrainBee competition?! So thrilled to see so many… https://t.co/Fn26dmagQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If things are so fake why don’t you sue? because you don’t have a case and your gutless]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could maybe take Colin Firth (though he held his own against Hugh Grant in Bridget Jones' diary)  Colin Ferrell?… https://t.co/aGBh1HzccF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loathe poster sessions. Even when I'm not presenting, the crowdedness and commotion is too over-stimulating for m… https://t.co/gSLUcnvLIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝😍😘 https://t.co/1GfZDS1hf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Send us your favorite abandoned lot sign photos and remain #TogetherForBanter https://t.co/6MtJ3a83lT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people ask me if I even skate ... Do you even skate? 🍦 @ B &amp; J Skate Center https://t.co/pSFHmSKRRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corriendo en el centro de Chihuahua #correr #centro #chihuahua #cuu #entrenar #ultra #ultramaraton https://t.co/zqUvAnK3M5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, we are ALL couture HENNY. Happy Valentine’s Day from Nick and Amanda! We love youUuuUuUuuWAH!! ♥️♥️ https://t.co/OUDzOUC3GK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TennesseeBoysHighSchoolBasketball #TSSAA #Region8AA 2nd Semifinal: #WooddaleCardinals(black) vs @CovingtonHighTN(w… https://t.co/jkeMpqyCyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was able to get some studio time in today. @ Erie Art Gallery https://t.co/k6z48rQURo]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a few days off I needed to get back at it. Got a nice 4 mile progression run in on the Mill. I felt pretty go… https://t.co/cPt5STpwuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AttorneyCrump He should have Stop, when they told Him to stop. Black or White]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who has 2 pointer fingers, points, but still can't run... THIS GUY!! Yup still can't run, or do any form of exercis… https://t.co/YKcWgiA7Hi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Do you want a margarita to go?” I didn’t know that was an option. Yes sir I would like a margarita to go, thank yo… https://t.co/bdCiusEBdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[13 Canadian cannabis executives banned from entering US for life.  This needs to stop.   Federal legalization of Ca… https://t.co/AG0H9yPsiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little wunderhund decided to make a break for it while we were trying to move some donation boxes out to the c… https://t.co/X5nI9JYguc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bonnie the impact you have had on so many lives that have come through this program will be hard to be matched. One… https://t.co/URlC669tNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some cruel person slipped this into my feed this morning. It’s from 2015.  April fools is still a month away dammit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchTCole check it out. Quick trip to SoCal to check out a quality University.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pulling into work this morning and spot a dude wearing a Detroit Not Sorry hoodie 🔥 Ahhhh I was SCREAMING in the car! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bills to clean up and amend tax reform plan and state budget pass through House committee https://t.co/HGGevxFP0H #kyga19 #taxes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inbedwithsteph @uvgot2bkidnme Luxurious bedding is one of my main joy bringers, close second is #nopantssunday 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattzollerseitz @johnlk_80 @melvillmatic I watched THE BROADWAY MELODY (1929) earlier this year and it was charmin… https://t.co/r4OgNhJoZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time exploring Live Oak Trees. Each seems to have a story of their own... #trees #oak #live #south… https://t.co/pdemNp4Pyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[These three ladies...no words today! 👐🏿👐🏿👌🏿👌🏿💪🏾💪🏾 This is just a sample! They totally kilt that #workout! 👍🏿👍🏿🏋🏿‍♀️… https://t.co/b0JF3XinxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatiePavlich @Aungiexyz #Wow just #Wow good grief #Wow just #Wow... are you kidding me? 😳. #Wow !?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snohaalegra you got one here. Hit me dead in the chest. It’s beautiful. https://t.co/msbjRE1kY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrippyComms Go back to Cairn Lake. (If you haven’t already) and start the side mission of searching for the lost h… https://t.co/x7wJIlZilu]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was so much snow this morning, @EveForster , you can’t even imagine. I had to shovel a LOT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@s07777785 The one where they can block people in real life. This man’s wife blocks him so his kids and ex wife are… https://t.co/ObQwdcmlpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemocrats  What are  You democrats waiting for  Either impeach him or declare the 25th amendment  He is  Wastin… https://t.co/HgQJBhjNzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philgousman Blows my mind that they don’t do that either. That would be a no-brainer for me. But I’m slow and I can’t dunk 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbiRatchford Abigail you so Incredibly Grogous our Eyes are so Beautiful and Amazing😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘❤❤❤❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bastion is so cheap. Always guaranteed Play of the Game unless they suck. Grrrr #OverwatchComplaints]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Amazons logo is a #penis. The subtle message is you’re probably gonna get screwed! Viva La #Google!  #tech]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnHicks00 @BernieSanders I understand your perspective. Personally I don’t think the dems are gonna go with a ca… https://t.co/Xn79JwvGDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino What's new everyone hates him. He's being sued for everything. It's ridiculous. She made her choice she w… https://t.co/ZfYvYnDaPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pizza night? 🍕 Sign. Me. Up! Lol • #PlanetFitness #LasVegas @ Planet Fitness https://t.co/ij2cBCChdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pam_brundige @eqracer @TyLond3 @BarbaraMain07 @shopwithfifi @LisaFroghair1 @uniquesrw @sexyvenus333 @LisaHauser8… https://t.co/isMvl4fTWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runwithskizzers  !!!! Also, @JasonReynolds83 your name is in an Oscar winner!!! @SpiderVerse https://t.co/rYfxgrHiJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grant Williams has me convinced that he invented the “old man game.”  That’s how good he is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[9. PBTT - Old Pride  • Sleepshaker • Cripples Don’t Shiver • Young Fire https://t.co/hF4MUhuYQF]]></document></documents></author>