<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Start your #abm (account based marketing) initiatives toward your current customer base first. #B2BMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe my son opened a mf Pepsi while I’m sleep and downed that bitch ! I beat him burping and shit , I lo… https://t.co/wx9vznvymt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behold, my bedroom bookshelves. Next to my dedicated extra-wide reading chair. IN MY BEDROOM,THE HORROR.  Bonus sho… https://t.co/DgMUfbQL3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[How come a ugly egg and a fat spider can go viral but I can’t be verified as top mega twitter supreme thot and get atleast 3 retweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[ABSOLUTELY Incredible Coach Inglesby AND Thank YOU Chrissi for being there with YoUDee/Cheerleaders and Band!! Feel… https://t.co/5HCwCnUUTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[what’s it like to not have consistently mysterious or complex medical issues? asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoodMorningWorld Follow Me!  https://t.co/auKBcQURsx https://t.co/eX31Rtx0yx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go! @EdtheSock and @redlianak bring the #WarOnStupid comedy tour to #ygk tonight!  Doors are open!  Robbie… https://t.co/1LgOSKkSpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[STAGED HOMES • Staged To SELL • • • • #stagedhomes #stagedhome #styledhome #stagedesign #staged #homestaging… https://t.co/ge2yYkNxGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[We claimed the unclaimed! And you can too. Do you want to join us on March 23rd as we board our charter bus bound f… https://t.co/QnbYrKKrg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday Flashback to warmer days and Hudson Valley sunsets. #sunset #cornfield #dogwalk #sun #summer #upstate… https://t.co/hiVnZtQmjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Francesco Molinari on @APinv : “it’s probably one of my favorite weeks of the year. “ Getting better now. He’s club… https://t.co/tTJCjrFzes]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂definitely me 😂😂😂. I throw everything at it (misses every time.) https://t.co/WEBdHWGoMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending Delta Day at the State Capital discussing the State Hate Crime Laws, Redlining, funding for DOJ’s Communi… https://t.co/9vrBRmRjJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give Blood, Get Coffee! Still time to sign up for Thursday's blood drive! Link in bio. . #giveblood #blooddrive… https://t.co/QlVGtj2Y34]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans launch propaganda sites designed to look like local news outlets https://t.co/Kj8aEjh1F1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sammytwitted @Debbie77325438 @LogoTV @EllenPage @TheEllenShow God is closest to us in times of trial. I will pray for you. 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReelMusik The media outlet that is covering this story actually States exactly what @amandaseales says in her vide… https://t.co/oUhYnBXdzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got mine..he is going to Florida in just a few weeks! Pictures to come with Billy on the run!! Vacation style!… https://t.co/MJGq0UDy5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new do. ⚜️ My hair had gotten long and annoying so I took an evening and got out my buzzer and scissors and cut m… https://t.co/mEaZHftY4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fab #FF's @kenpickles @TUTNShow @RadioIMW @MessagingMatt @raine1967 @TomShafShafer @RockyMntnMike @GottaLaff… https://t.co/J4FJecmcBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry, where was this info when I was 17. Bad for you or not, this is low key genius @taylorswift13 😂 https://t.co/7wvXdmW66I]]></document><document><![CDATA[FASTER PUSSYCAT / YOU'RE SO VAIN - Directed by Rocky Schenck https://t.co/PPPN7MvAWu via @YouTube  @RikiRachtman to… https://t.co/ajaTbhTRfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattyskatin @redbull #redbullwallriders #venicebeach #venicepaparazzi #insta360 #insta360onex #mauiandsonsvb… https://t.co/xj0ImVGkyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drop dead gorgeous Oh how I wish it to be possible Just to hear those three words To dream it to be true To feel it… https://t.co/T5BK1L1I1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpbettger Way to go! Not only moving the needle for #WomeninSTEM but also #exercise 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StMariaGorett @DPwellness4all @DPCDSBSchools Great way to start you day... Goretti #healthyschoolpledge]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t realize it was St Patrick’s day so the Wonder Bar is crazy packed but... Bobby Bandiera 🤘🏻 https://t.co/0xT6QAhXOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know our girl @Victoria4Texas  is a public education supporter ! Thanks for meeting with us today! ❤️🙌🏻 #ATPE… https://t.co/UepG7V8Qqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump trump needs to testify...of course if he tells the truth he's toast...If he lies he's t… https://t.co/fOWI6IqrUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DepartureTheory the best thing about the internet is that eventually that an asshole gets owned in real life and w… https://t.co/wweFnF6DiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigManPauly @Redskins That’s how I’m thinking too. He’s a good young QB who can learn the Gruden system and learn… https://t.co/6LQgl1Mu4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Hint Hint* I would LOVE this #GemstoneHeart necklace from @kayjewelers for Valentine's Day! https://t.co/AeQcYpMtDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hence, if we want to find life and true freedom, we must begin to die to small deaths by self-denial and carrying o… https://t.co/LdKoctUieo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emocionante hacer parte de esta lista TAn divina de @SpotifyColombia @SpotifyLatino #MujeresColombianas Gracias por… https://t.co/rEoddxWrZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see that @pedialyte has finally begun marketing to their largest demographic... stay thirsty my friends 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TOKYO -- Belgian #Godiva said Wednesday it has agreed to sell its Asian-Pacific assets to MBK Partners, a South Ko… https://t.co/xeN7GNT5p3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st birthday to one of my favorite people ever🥰 I hope you have the best day! I love and miss you so much 💓… https://t.co/0mKc8sCif4]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they flew by private jet and are staying in luxurious accommodations @DailyMailUK  we are waiting for the cost… https://t.co/W7JtLgPfFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldorco1 @sharinyles Holy heaven for me. That is amazing. As if I didn’t love you enough already. 🤔 road trip? Come… https://t.co/CLiiw2BY2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was so great to finally meet Disney artist, jmaruyama! So excited to have him sign my “Kingdom of Cute” phone ca… https://t.co/CiRLUe4g4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I haven’t heard about your love life in a hot minute” “That’s because it doesn’t exist”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayer vi un juego de soft aquí en Hermosillo y el 1ra base usaba sobrero norteño en vez de gorra, te iba a etiquetar… https://t.co/o9nTh7DfD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her request for a mommy daughter date night was a must ❤️  Can’t love and admire her enough 👩‍👧#motherdaughter… https://t.co/PyAftHyrEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love women. Just walked up to a group of ladies and they go “ok we need to readdress how critical you are of your… https://t.co/4nKgQO9Kua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lately I’ve been in love with all things yellow. I just ordered the cutest @everlane dress that should be arriving… https://t.co/BLWgokWWnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaniKaiDuck @USAFF35 @ThisMomHCN @markjarthur @Vbalance03 @PharmaNemesis @mmelgar09 @ChrisJohnsonMD @PileOfGoop… https://t.co/BoWyH90Tsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[They may not have won.. but my girl @flanagko scored the goal of a lifetime!! So proud of you. #AllHeart… https://t.co/JsWPDhntU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for being my friend❤❤❤ Early birthday present from my Husband 😚 All seven seasons.👊👊⚘⚘⚘#thegoldengirls @… https://t.co/mKHntitF2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates My baby boy Casper...lost him 6/25/18 miss him so much.💖💔🐶 https://t.co/USKtF3ByOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tableau great job everyone, hope I win that ticket! #tc19 #data19 #AskData #DataFamSweepstakes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar These people believe, that because they have blonde hair that they can do whatever they want and get away with it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family Guy: The phenomenon that brought us Stewie. https://t.co/9W3y42pd3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatachaJaitt Que tristeza que tenga que ser así encontrar la paz que tanto nesecitabas. Besos a su hermano y hijos… https://t.co/2Mzarjqan4]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bad pic of the drawbridge on the way to MSP to see @mattnathanson @varsitytheater tonight. Sunny and a heat wave… https://t.co/N9t1FpBjVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elizabeth did not pay that woman the $100 to make the call Jennifer did......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ash_Baylor @SamKantrow @WTNH @gilsimmons @RyanKristafer Watching u on channel 8 good luck guys Happy St. Patrick's… https://t.co/uxQYKGlJLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m faded af and I came home and there was a big ass box of jack in the box pizza and i was like hell yeah and I opened it, it was empty...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upper Body blast~Chest, Back and biceps!  #upperbodyworkout #upperbody #biceps #chest #back #Sonmychest #killa… https://t.co/a5azoFjjG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kris Jenner right now while we’re all trying to figure out the tea of the Jordan scandal https://t.co/xmO5LTwFHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dj_Mcfadden11 @QBC_Charlotte Some cats really don’t know bruh. Act like we doing stuff for personal gains. We in i… https://t.co/x2y1cHQArr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Politicians that helped in getting this sham of an amendment passed. Greyhounds are working dogs that were bred to… https://t.co/cUIusqLAPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[made my appointment for my third(ish) tattoo and to say i’m incredibly excited is an understatement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roachies_way This journey is going to make you 100x stronger, I’m so happy for you and to see you accomplish this journey!! 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bill17761972 @arkiegal411 @kaci150 @TwistedOne96 @currie14_kelly @Jasmine8137488 @GKeile @CynthiaRunnels1… https://t.co/2vHKRmMHXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo único  que quería  era que me dejaras volar y abrieras tus alas junto a las mias...]]></document><document><![CDATA[You earn in alignment with the quality of your work, not the quality of your want. You can build a life on a work e… https://t.co/5aFWS2Bgqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardBTurner @charliekirk11 It's unfortunate her own father would have to say it!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got a Cameo from Greg Sestero #cameofameo https://t.co/o8TDfokjhM via @bookcameo Happy Valentines Day, Baby Girl! @skyyyrayyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[catch me, FRONT ROW, at the Jonas brothers reunion concert!! 🤩#jonasbrothersreunion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woohoo! Getting a full 6hrs of work today! 🤯 🎶 #listeningtovivaldi 🎶  How do you feel when you get more time to wor… https://t.co/QoXkBzStiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we could take the canes smell and make that into a candle, I’d buy that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 8 and final day of #ashtangahippies Pindasana Variation @ Peak Strength &amp; Conditioning https://t.co/XB4fPjBlY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 2019 has been phenomenal! I'm still flying high from this weekend at #empowermepink2019atlanta.   I made D… https://t.co/UJtJrQX5AY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WGK73 @ChadK426 @Chad_27WKBN @WKBNSports @eleanorklucinec Thanks for doing such an awesome job ! From a UHS patent… https://t.co/fmIp8DJA5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[These photos I have of them at work will have to suffice. 😻♥️ https://t.co/SuLfp5YwLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Turtlecat9 @FartyCheddarCat @cocoa_dot @ililita @A_affirmations @SoxandD @arkantart @The_Couve @timzmom… https://t.co/5TkroaW19o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @Jose93571656 @angela681417 @AnaAndrade305 @eiteamokarina @carolina_smal… https://t.co/5SznWr8B6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StarringSecond integrated LEGO robotics into our PA state symbol study. The kids worked diligently to choose, rese… https://t.co/ezkfwO3tB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The inner exercise track is reopen at @santaanitapark but main track remains shut down. Officials say small track… https://t.co/6mLA7KT3v4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LexisTV @SamuelLJackson When he jumped into Samuel L Jackson’s arms!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Within 2 weeks OM will be over and we’ll be moved into our house...finally can go back to my daily naps and not being so busy!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me all the time when I am home!!! . #momlife #momhumor #mommyconfessions #badmom #parenthood #toddlerlife… https://t.co/GYDzG1xAsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Keener13Fan Hey where are you guys having fun now lol keep it up life is short ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tornadoes kill at least 23 in one Alabama county  https://t.co/q2mSH1Hh3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OleanderNectar @BettyBowers Exactly. More importantly, Thursday votes count, because they are allowed to vote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noelle_larue @Lily_Renee1 It is, it’s one of the few written by the actual author and not a ghost writer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ppl are so stupid today I can’t believe how much shit they start over shoes my gosh]]></document><document><![CDATA[what the difference between a cheese stick and string cheese? like do people just call them different things or are… https://t.co/nBobjJMn2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo malo de levantarme más temprano es que sé que tengo más tiempo y me quedo valiendo cochi un rato e igual se me hace tarde☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best nights. 🙏⛪🐯🖤 * * * #BTSM #TimeForChurch #rottnroll #pnwraver #pnw #BassCapitol @officialbtsm @ Taco… https://t.co/olThv5Oq6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The human trafficking is happening among you greed rich weidos right here inside this country...... https://t.co/yOa9j27tcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericaNewsroom @MarkMeadows @SandraSmithFox @RepMarkMeadows Such an angry man. GOP enabler can't handle the truth… https://t.co/glOK0szpjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @sensanders @SenFeinstein @SenWarren @SpeakerPelosi https://t.co/RlFF3rzRqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oneunderscore__ They are going to be pissed when they find out AOC created Q as a joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GustavoArellano Trader Joe’s has really yummy  jackfruit veggie “crab cakes” ( frozen isle) and I’ve made jackfrui… https://t.co/gT4grNLLp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @TheJenya for getting my ass up early to eat biscuits &amp; talk business https://t.co/TWwuqrv9Uo]]></document><document><![CDATA[7th grade students @HopperMS learn about body systems through frog dissections https://t.co/OFj6TPP0dp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBLOODonly1 Oh how I wish I’d been fast enough to catch him on camera. It happened so fast and I laughed so hard,… https://t.co/ref8rmA6pP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now, 20 minutes later, the excuse is that there’s a train with mechanical problems on 7th Ave.  This happens Every.… https://t.co/NbsS9v3fko]]></document></documents></author>