<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael Please tell me they DIDN'T kill the kitty.. #StupidHumanTricks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also lmao...I am officially listening to the first episode of @smoochsquadpod (yes I co-host, no I didn’t listen ah… https://t.co/RjKrVegxmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randyfenoli @rustirose8 I do it all the time!  Yes @randyfenoli is the best. So nice &amp; sweet ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i will make sure that everyone everywhere will be able to see the inner and outer... https://t.co/0ByCLrBaea]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought rewatching Free Solo on my home tv 3 wines in would make it less intense but I was wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was only worried about telling my boyfriend I love him one more time before the boat leave 😂☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bravotv #Bravo @Kimzolciak Love 💕 Watching your family on Friday night. I get so many laughs 😂 Thank you for brightening my Evening ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[They all put their hands on their men too. But we not talking about they huh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never in my life been so heartbroken as I  am right now and for more reasons than one. 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[chose to not do any dci video assignments or college assignments today until I see if I’m going to be blown away or not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop Anything to do with reading, language,and speech.  I taught HS English, and I would have failed him....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Most all cancer doctors support the use of marijuana by their patients. If one doesn’t, find one that will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaySJX @RealJamesWoods If no consequences, it will continue &amp; only get worse 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see #EdmontonAllIn at Destination Showcase 2019 #DSDC19 Edmonton in a snowstorm 😀 https://t.co/0S5meRf5py]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaCBS3 Natasha, I think the time change has got you a little mixed up! It’s 4:30 am not pm! Downtown Natasha… https://t.co/4p1dfvAQ1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@addys_dad I accept your challenge as well. I am on Day 3. I will tag you in tomorrow’s post!! 📕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It's what they do. But you, I and most of America move forward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamiltonMusical why is your lottery ticket app not working?! It hasn't worked all day. 😲😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovRonDeSantis Please restore tenure at the state college of florida.  Value our professors by allowing them profe… https://t.co/7POWf5OZAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr When 100% of Republicans refuse to care about thousands of LIVING, BREATHING CHILDREN because they ar… https://t.co/QdRv2DGb3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[we’ve all moved 3 gates in almost 3 hours. and we finally get to board in 3 mins.  #  #weddingphotographer… https://t.co/trB9aafMyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[They make $80 an hr what am I doing with my life 😂😂😂 https://t.co/DTAw0BfesJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awonderland We love you and you were amazing tonight THANK YOU 💜💜💜 https://t.co/CU7EZmzH1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pics with my daughter Zion and her BFF Elin at Monday night’s premiere of Mhairi Morrison’s #DontSilenceMe music vi… https://t.co/xCVfwpswfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m down 43 pounds so I am walking away 😩🧁 #thestruggleisreal #goals #ireallywantone @ Fort Worth, Texas https://t.co/I5r4KQA8du]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my dad are literally the same person.. :) https://t.co/896SXkeJ1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing is going in my favor these days and it’s really starting to take its toll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CplBear @CivMilAir @ELINTNews Has absolutely 0 to do w/ oil, unless you are referring to the reason the country is… https://t.co/1lb3sTLqVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[WEEKEND FLASH SALE BOGO 75% OFF ALL PAINTINGS Offer ends on Sunday, February 17th Only on https://t.co/IWW7AdYH6p 🦋]]></document><document><![CDATA[i find it entertaining when girls post these long ass sob stories on facebook about how they have no friends and ev… https://t.co/ItreaAulZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarnessArtist You will fall asleep in the middle of the whole mess, with them running around you at 2am... https://t.co/VVULtNlT9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still haven’t figured out how old I have to be for people to stop calling me a little girl. #WomenInSTEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[besides ourselves.”  While an interpreter deals with the spoken word, a translator handles written text. All those… https://t.co/iuq593m9Pc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#amwriting #lifequotes #MondayMotivation #Live #adventuretime https://t.co/30PmpQbHo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddiMellencamp @lisarinna U are really not bright falling for the bs being dished our to u from Lisa R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeltingInMarana @rkline56 @KevinMFerrara @EinsteinMaga @sundance7055 @T_FLgal @nancy_hamm1 @WinnDuncan… https://t.co/SMQtBhFJr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prayingmedic Oh Ann, Rommey really.  Wherw are his balls oh right Harry Reid took them when he left Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian You are too beautiful on the outside and inside to ever have been treated like this! When you find… https://t.co/asBOcgkrE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jokes aside... on one hand, fans need to understand that the social media folks don’t have any power over in-game d… https://t.co/kdJhO5dHXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are absolutely correct and he did it all while working for mr trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol whoever works for the Chicago Cubs and searched me on LinkedIn, yes I do want the job. 😉 https://t.co/dqC6trJMuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @JoeNBC First Washington Compose, Now CNN today, then NBC.....For what you say?  What our @POTUS has always… https://t.co/ZxD6ufvjNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is on her way! #spring #vibrant #green #lighttheway #eathealtyfood #eatlikeyougiveadamn #eathealtyfood… https://t.co/VEfOhs0u2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy last day to my Boston Bestie @4AngelaC! We will miss you so much here in the Queen City!😢❤️ But we’re excited… https://t.co/bRrz90x92N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TickedOff6 I’m glad there was kindness in a world that’s been rocky lately.  Means a lot, doesn’t it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally after a long over do of taking this bestie out to celebrate her 40th!! Never too many celebrations I’d say!… https://t.co/wkRdglYauo]]></document><document><![CDATA[me and @shhhhabri when we almost got kidnapped in ghana by our uber driver]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tehnakki It sucks missing out but it sucks more to pay all that money and feel like you wasted it ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #livemodel came in all stressed out. For her facial, I used @Dermalogica calming, hydrating products + a 15-min… https://t.co/4gHK3DRAip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@athendoflight It doesn't cost money. Immigrants get jobs and work. They start businesses. They pay taxes. Immigran… https://t.co/LCDI1SQNy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[24 years old  1 exes  3 piercings  2 tattoo (3 tattoo coming soon) 3 hair color  0 dogs 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HometeamBleak @680TheFan @AtlantaSportsX @joeham14 @BJosephRadio Braves and Falcons. And never United. I prefer to fly Delta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erjmanlasvegas I only know the term thanks to @KevinNews3LV @KellyNews3LV and @ChloeNews3LV!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlogChurchWork @SteveScalise @HandmaidsOnHulu What is wrong with these people?  Vote them out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylamariebard THANK YOU FOR THIS!!! I have met people who act like anxiety is a luxury to have. like.. no sweethe… https://t.co/cL1OXBjcTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze These 2 should be deported asap, what were the voters thinking putting these 2 in our Gov't]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s do this! Today’s morning #carnegiehalllinkup #concerts brought to you by a good night’s sleep and… https://t.co/b2zwnzMAc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinHarvick good luck today, may you and the other drivers stay safe. #4thewin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would y’all give this whole “financial flexibility” a fucking break already? Jesus Christ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmoney818 Luke prolly ain’t making it through the week if the Lakers lose this too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiftCardSweeps I’m trying to help y’all out with my friends family back now please thank @Kimberl38218406 please thank you 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkahne I'm so sorry.  That is heartbreaking. Love and prayers to you and your family. https://t.co/Uhfmq9VeiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brian_abramson @chrissy_goss @Boxmenot @TsuDhoNimh @Melissa62263619 @TakeThatCDC @EmmaGPaley @AlexMurdoch7… https://t.co/k9eRTe8ESM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost my phone for an hour last night after dancing at Dark Entries dance night. Got someone to call me on it, and s… https://t.co/T0tKNrh7Ce]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Son just back into a park car. Looks bad. Love you all. Please say a prayer for the Lady Anna and my Son. No one… https://t.co/UbOut1liaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[finally catching up on @ImpostersBravo season 2!! @adelsteinPaul your writing together with ur acting has literally… https://t.co/QHe74BjkGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cindymclennan I have so been the class Disabled Person, or whatever...it's not great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was twin day! Look at my cute little twin!!!!  @koparker05  #wearepowhatan https://t.co/722e0jL1hS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starving!!!! 🙄 (at @JollibeeUsa in Union City, CA) https://t.co/qhmmjp7ICv]]></document><document><![CDATA[And upon Dibon, and upon Nebo, and upon Bethdiblathaim, https://t.co/BeDtR5ZQAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chasing a #hundo with a chance of it being a #shundo is what motivates me to try. #pokemon #pokemongo #machop @ San… https://t.co/HwGO2Epf2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Appalachia is a wound, a joy, and a poem. A knot of complication. But you cannot know a place without loving it an… https://t.co/y6nx0vmYtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I for one am NOT #FeelingtheBern  for @BernieSanders — STEP ASIDE, SIR. This is not what the Dems need again! https://t.co/TjkK83wdT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if you think it ain’t all for you You’re wrong  Baby, it’s all for you 💕  #CautionWorldTour #MariahCarey… https://t.co/cALF1nyWwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight my family and I went to @Walmart on Coit and Arapaho in Dallas. It was our first time at that location and… https://t.co/eUqFINNawL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TessFowler It’s so frustrating a situation because his abuses have been public knowledge for years but it took a v… https://t.co/qDvF063D8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[No manches Frida 2 premiere @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/Yp6ZQQy5CF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started wearing The Husband’s jeans. They’re not flattering but they’re comfortable and I am not killing anyone o… https://t.co/83x5qqUk4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs D. Why you be flexin' on me so hard today?  "I will flex ALL DAY!!!!  Get your work done!"  I have no idea wh… https://t.co/2X0xnTdVmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can the season finale be Grandma Beverly closing all of Pauly’s accounts?  #siestakey]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wonder what @kobebryant has to say so far about the @lakers season, &amp; what advice he could give to @KingJames #NBATwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capntransit @mikecherepko @ElizabethStNYC @EDI_NYC @yuhline @DeborahJGlick @willthomas_usa @GaleBrewerNYC Mindless… https://t.co/O10JQUNDVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[juro que tengo los ojos mas negros caca de america https://t.co/yaxmYpSE41]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can change the way you feel...by changing the way you think... EVERY SINGLE TIME. Try it! 💯 #thoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetestjjoy Lol so this girl followed me, and I was like oh hell nah, there’s only one Jojo https://t.co/lo4LxXISCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chloe_scaless happy birthday b, miss u sm and hope you’ve had a great day so far. Love youuuu💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrum I'm an independent, but if you wouldn't tell so many lies, or be such a dick and narcissistic maybe… https://t.co/URM1DL0S0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha hahaha hahaha 🃏♠️ is a ♠️ is a ♠️ ....... ThankYOU!🏏😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂🤙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kareem3gumbs I'm usually the one getting an earful and choking it down....you ain't the type to talk...and me? I t… https://t.co/qBZKmZtJE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andibeth012 Please. Help Ringo. Only 1 yr. old and scheduled to die sometime Thursday. Needs a hero ASAP. 💔😢🐕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GAWHeckman @worldinterRAI @trifectaRN @McArthurCaitlin @VBoscart @SchumacherCon @LSheiban This is our work and our… https://t.co/icBJ0fXDRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goals:   Drop my first EP/album - 2019  Be the face for a character in a romance- 2021  Guest appearance on NPR: Ti… https://t.co/F1dmdDjqsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayaoakes @NatashaOladokun Aria and Hound have way more chemistry than those two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petrie_marshall @Pointings @KyaeGunn @HootHootBerns @BernieSanders Large safety net? What country do you live in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 That right. Keep the right wing hyped up by deflecting from Trump. But beware, there are a lot mor… https://t.co/ZEEiSY2DRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SealeyGerald @luluHru @GARY1010 @DRH1959 @Lexa_Merica @JeanneInTexas @AngeleStar11 @PauWitkowski @gex_daniel… https://t.co/u86bWQzk7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[1942 Radio Orange calls for March 1 day of prayer in Dutch Indies  1942 Werner Heisenberger informs Nazis about ura… https://t.co/WSnBJ3j8rc]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least it took a few minutes this time but Rangers blow a lead because what else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I liked it without the host. That kept the time down to a manageable  3hours 18 minutes. They should do it without a host next year too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#iHeartAwards  #BestCoverSong  #StillTheOne  @Harry_Styles  @KaceyMusgraves]]></document></documents></author>