<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tom_watson I hope you realize the free world sees the UK as a dystopian nightmare. As a ‘what we don’t want to hap… https://t.co/Mrqy1znCJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rksimonlaw I said that kind of opposite. It’ll speed up the line zero!]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUYS GUESS WHAT??? I made it and it’s all gone I have to heal of course but it’s gone and I am on the road to recov… https://t.co/6KN8CnG0pU]]></document><document><![CDATA[tropical fruit and berries and citrus aromas and flavors with a good bitterness. very delicious. - Drinking a Prog!… https://t.co/ES69AikIG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed getting to talk at @NCATA1974 state meeting and learn to administer IVs #EBPs @ Carolinas HealthCare System… https://t.co/KTlJeGSgxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for the MN Legislature to follow suite and pass a transportation bill that will benefit our roads and bridges… https://t.co/Sf1qEvGuuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill I think trump has made a fool out of himself over the last couple of years. He really looks to me like a mob boss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit load of glare, but oh well. Done on my old friend, Jill. Thanks again lady! Made at brightmoortattoo . Thanks… https://t.co/BccmXHbtIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Code for The House with a Clock in it's Walls @ Plainfield, Indiana https://t.co/uqydGTxtml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timmz15 Thanks I love the Shawnee national forest in southern Illinois]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Airsuzuki @shrxfan89 @CurtisPashelka At least Thornton got the 🎩 trick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PennsyMtnGirl @AOC @algore It’s 7 degrees with the wind chill in Oklahoma and snowing 🌨 where’s that global warmin… https://t.co/gPXCBa6JDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[She doesn’t want to protect Omar any more than she wanted to protect her own sister.  Liz is certainly a chip off t… https://t.co/pXL4LUVPMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Academy Sports + Outdoors is hiring in #Katy, TX! Read about our latest #Marketing job opening via the link in our… https://t.co/Pytnp9IHqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two great mayor's!!!!  Nice to meet you @GlennJacobsTN come back soon! @MayorGorton https://t.co/9sewrxTanR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Palmer flew on his first triple jump to a distance of 47-02 and punched his ticket to New Balance Nationals. #KNOWmoore @kytrackxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dragged downtown kicking and screaming. #mardigrinch @ Downtown Lafayette https://t.co/G5ehnUZJar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReduxitSpem @DaveBen52466738 Is this presser televised?Would love to be there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One hour left @SundayStreets. This has to happen more often. https://t.co/QBMBAIUg10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins @WestYorksPolice Animals.... that's all. Need a wall for these ppl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Props To The Queen👑 @miilliemesh  #movesbybishop #hiphop #localartist #oklahoma #hubblybubbly #fashion #style… https://t.co/PV952Pjgqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 5 most common barriers for community college students:  1. Work (34%) 2. Paying expenses (34%) 3. Family and fr… https://t.co/CjRSvn1159]]></document><document><![CDATA[CB: Hey Mr. Rogers, you’re not in my 5. MR: What if I beat you in golf? 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next on my reading list... @ Springfield, Missouri https://t.co/Q46PL3gBB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harmony and I made a new dish from a recipe we saw on the internet. Turned out damned good! https://t.co/10LWep5MrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best band EVER!! In 1976 they were called Feedback. 1977 called The Hype. Settled on U2!!! 5 decades later still th… https://t.co/cwMCXBboxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel @teeheeheemcfee Suggest you read Christopher Hitchens' works, wherein he notes derisive humor's th… https://t.co/U77vj8NqsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[200 in a couple of hours!! Let’s push for 300 familyyyy 💙🖤🤘🏾https://t.co/6UGi2dyeIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Chicks, I admit that Lara has impressive attributes. I actually listened to the entire 3:39.38 long interview o… https://t.co/DgMpfQRAXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Case closed!    Suspect is arrested for murder of 11-year-old girl who was abducted and left in ditch 45 years ago… https://t.co/Y5S660sy05]]></document><document><![CDATA[This creepy fucking scene in "Deep Red"  tho. Argento really knew how to craft atmosphere https://t.co/CaBMNif8l3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRogerStone They weren’t crossing illegally, you MORON, they wete legally applying for asylum, per the constituti… https://t.co/FxYTboXli4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardAllenIDR @DrunkBrianF Yes at Bristol several times, also met him 3 times, and got to meet his mom at his de… https://t.co/gM88lOn9XR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The irony of someone asking Trump to autograph their Bible just blows my mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it waddles like... If it has downy feathers like... If it quacks like... If it DENIES like... #thatcism]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying hi again after many years!    The Cycling Legend John Karras on his 89th Birthday!!!  A founder of RAGBRAI.… https://t.co/zse6eRmCY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to hear how it went &amp; what they &amp; you learned. #doingwhatsbestforstudents]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing females working wit sumthing did you know New Orleans bounce legend Josephine Johnny lawd have mercy...on th… https://t.co/LIYIdnRAWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@questions_faith @DykeVanTom @God2Evolution @zalphaprime @yrysbryd @TertiusIII @StandBackUp2 @EveKeneinan @umfpt… https://t.co/4mY1hsnPuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't forget to register. Bring someone that you care about and enrich their life as well. Namaste'.... @ Roots Nut… https://t.co/fMMgVaY4n0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityofTampa is missing a great opportunity to create a world class park in downtown Tampa on this land.… https://t.co/y7JVoTRstT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Los Angeles Fire Department EPI-Center - @lafd in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/nMFaiu4FiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lynn_Rose1 @McCormackJohn @DanCrenshawTX @POLITICOMag @RepMattGaetz What he said in 2015 and what he does in offic… https://t.co/Mp2LHhRKEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @EPA has been so successful that we’ve largely forgotten rivers so polluted they’d regularly catch fire, superf… https://t.co/9UlO7jHFmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiKitten_ OK I'll set myself a reminder to get it done for you at 10am PST. We'll see how feasible it is. What time is your page due?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sethrogen @BuzzFeedNews Totally ruined it....can’t we just still believe the lie?!???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched BAD TIMES AT THE EL ROYALE and really liked it. It kind of felt like a Tarantino version of Mullholl… https://t.co/fDUFBnzQKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Citrus Gose by @SycamoreBrewing @ Koch's High Gravity — https://t.co/caq5iqeq11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CLE_CLCFan Appreciate that Paulie, better everyday sir. One step at a time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to win tickets to the BET Experience at STAPLES Center from @REAL923LA. https://t.co/3lttndNwPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you vote for the promises of the Dems, the only thing they guarantee is poverty and misery and that way they wil… https://t.co/yXT0syEQAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mynamejong @ProducerMike975 Sorry my bad! I’m tweeting about everything right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockChalkBlog @RockChalkPhog25 Sorry, disagree on that. Self is known for playing really tough non-con schedules a… https://t.co/wxy8EjabRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will literally listen to the same 6 songs for days straight and see nothing wrong w it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richarddeitsch Heard the segment driving home and it was fantastic. She needs to become a regular on the show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was up early this morning doing some work and finally awake after my disco nap. Meeting up with Sy later to get into shenanigans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, what work did she do to be born with the name “Trump?” #wonthespermderby]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Immigrant detention center in Bakersfield, thought to be set to close, will stay open: An immigrat… https://t.co/zSI7Au2Rzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @Cuse_MBB offense looks like this they can be a #SWEET16 team #LOUvsSYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[دليل مدينة الحلة لعام 1964.. طباعة أنيقة، معلومات وافية وغنى في التفاصيل والأمكنة والمعالم. https://t.co/P9IjVtNKBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be willing to have your ideas tested. Challenged. Killed off, if they can’t stand up to scrutiny. Have new ones. Be… https://t.co/GM6kp8jtPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsBBell Good morning Mrs. Bell. Have a beautiful Saturday. ☕️💙 https://t.co/gZZhPUdOWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praise Jesus, UFC 235 it’s about to go down! With my boy, Misha from the country, Georgia!  Proverbs 10:6 (NKJV) Bl… https://t.co/xqp7qhpZPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jyarg34 @FunkMaster_UFC I thought @USMAN84kg put in a #grappling and #bjj clinic. I appreciated it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, it looks like I’ve got a lot of Disney movies to buy before Fall 2019. 😞 https://t.co/M9dbzSofOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the champ finals of the 200 IM, Seth Krause of @FHS_Swim_Dive takes 3rd with a time of 1:56.18 and is headed to state!]]></document><document><![CDATA[❓Why Shrugs aren’t building your Traps❗️ ❇️Follow @CoreyPas for  Sustainable Fat Loss and Nutrition tips! - Shrugs… https://t.co/IaClIywGgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just took my dog out for the last time tonight and found a bunch of beer bottles scattered in our lawn and driveway… https://t.co/XWIp6oaGd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE sketches of savaging @MsCharlotteWWE and @RondaRousey at Elimination Chamber. https://t.co/AHlAuG6zOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO much happy tears. I’m so grateful to live that magical experience with my fellows peers, friends, animals. This… https://t.co/Zl4T9WYpUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This smile was before I started running lol Sunday Runday 🙏💜 @ Gene Green Beltway 8 Park https://t.co/iLwxndyF5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cinemex expliquen porque ofrecen producto de cinefan y en todo el año y parte del anterior no lo están vendiendo,… https://t.co/J9CMC9B2Kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@battletested5 @Cindystargazen It dam well better and we the people need to organise and take our country back this… https://t.co/snYkBc5g66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StSenka A pediatrician I worked with for awhile had kids chew sugarless gum for bowel issues, as part of a solutio… https://t.co/e4okOARI1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hanklandd We actually do, Foote's class was wild 😂😂 that shit was so long ago, damn. It's overdue at this point]]></document><document><![CDATA[11 years since @NixonLibrary @nixonfoundation #PresidentialLibrary 2/19/08; 7th grade. @YouTube:… https://t.co/1T5m1nIx3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Fiesta Jalapeños in North Ridgeville, OH https://t.co/QfM9BSBlE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElementalAmber I don't and I'm generally really sad!  (But I agree with your assessment, you slay, girl)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moiskd WHY DOESN'T PRESIDENT TRUMP DOUBLE DOWN ON HIS BIRTHER BS?? Obama's Kenyan Brother interviewed by Director… https://t.co/GpGOEbYGDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was me at 3 a.m. watching the recording when @TamarBraxtonHer’s name was announced as the winner of… https://t.co/nOk8Hj122D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlmartin_20 You build through the draft my friend lol. Only way to do that is have picks lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eastman CEO expecting better growth for remainder of 2019 https://t.co/4Uc4yIHpqU via @TimesNewsOnline @EastmanChemCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brookie425 You know Boras would love to do this just to upstage them and make it be about him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna find whoever called her “white mans whore” because they are they reason we have to deal with this shit… https://t.co/yjyJgLPsXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[These gorgeous 250mh inductors that have been custom wound by joe.gagan are on their way! Keep an eye out for the n… https://t.co/jv788umeG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s possible to believe both 1) Our economic system is deeply flawed/in need of a total reset, and 2) The reaction… https://t.co/vixfgaZdv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awkwafina @NY1 @NYBG Would love to have you on the morning show one of these days!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[show that Manafort was aware he was breaking the law and that he laundered the profits of his overseas lobbying eff… https://t.co/bXe3JLEMSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go show some support for our upcoming band B.J.R /Formed 3/3/19 at 6:32pm\ @BJR35174467]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLEASE BE ADVISED that you cannot consume any alcoholic beverages during this Challenge if you want to see a major… https://t.co/6uAgsArKqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna send my resume off to @CocaCola and @PenskeLogistics to work on there trucks still no word from Carvana but t… https://t.co/yQLIt04yYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattB_WOF Well then the numbers will dictate who was right at the end of the year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morg_schaefer15 @umcornell @nancyvo643 This happens way too much to us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Keg Tetris by Crooked Crab Brewing Company @ Crooked Crab Brewing — https://t.co/GM8431WnUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJudy Why should I waste my time watching your show if your going to simply tell people to go to small claims… https://t.co/IkPSNqfuSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[How cool is this! @cityofbell 🍾 @ Border X Brewing - Bell https://t.co/mBaqNNpkve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well @ThaGodMattV2 and I are deadass cursed in tourneys 😂 son of a man come on. Please ban the swordfish and double… https://t.co/zjChRHfZcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@In_A_YamChele @ayaila_sims my gf i swear 😂😂😂still got my adidas hoodie smh🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ron_ronka @what_if_history The sacrifices the #Russian people made in the fight against #Nazism is something the world can never forget.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students designing and printing their vinyl stickers at the Cesar Chávez Makerspace Club hayward_promise #HUSD #YEP… https://t.co/41tYS8SIG8]]></document></documents></author>