<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@StephsAmusic A person can only take so much before you punk there ass out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi America. Here's an interesting inquiry of self examination: which is most important to you – whether or not Trum… https://t.co/emjBEJChyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHIZMAGA @gallowaygirl9 How to joe to Congress without getting caught .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DillonElement my teammate is going 3rd map fuck, can you wait 10 min probably?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Har har very funny movie. You got Christopher Lloyd to voice a discount Doc Brown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics If Bin Kaden had flattered the egotistical ass, in a New York minute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day ♥️ with love from everyone at Major Word.  Find your next safe and reliable vehicle at Major W… https://t.co/uAq7UoRl5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at American Airlines? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and… https://t.co/8VAUaI6eXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every once in a while crime families get together. Maybe a tRump tower in Saudi Arabia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caseymckinnon Trying to wipe tears thru two layers of glasses is really difficult.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @chunter4444 If the moderates in that party don’t grow a set and stand up to the radicals it could… https://t.co/MTFJcl2xCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amber_athey And the men just sit back and let women get raped? What kind of characters are in these groups?! Oh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Warsteiner Premium Dunkel by @warsteiner @ The Abode — https://t.co/mENQyI5wrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you’re in luck @joelansdale is still writing the books! #LongliveHapandLeonard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Pater 6 by Brouwerij St. Bernardus @ McCoy's Beer &amp; BBQ — https://t.co/xlMyZ0TT95]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deja que La Luz del día ilumine tu espíritu 🙏🏼💫 @ New Rochelle, New York https://t.co/JXQWKBohJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azaryajason4 Yup &amp; we won’t do that. They’ll address CB/LB before OL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AfterShokz I am currently listening to a biography of Winston Churchill #shokzsquad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you want this feeling before you go out this weekend looking at houses?  Call me and let’s take care of busin… https://t.co/kgEWwFjONB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TotallBigE #Do you really think I give a damn what you ask for!?? I’m stating my take with or without your consent! Shut it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jzalkin @NoDesat I struggle with this as a person that wants to see the profession elevated and a hiring manager t… https://t.co/wcOHUNnDrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎤🎼 All the ladies #happy valentines #all❤️ Grateful for my ❤️’s @g_gallucci #JoveG @ Happiness is a Choice https://t.co/NAeoOAxycS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half those guys are not even in the hall of fame right now ...stop this it's embrassing out here for you LeBron fans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChinChillaaaa_ @MarkB_LifeStyle Nah it’s not.  Chicks who won’t give u a shot in nyc. U catch em outta town on vacation. It’s on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proof common sense is lost.. Writer to paper discribes how his son shows hik that the slit in the top of a plastic… https://t.co/62pcnUnlrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@opengovva Wow. There needs to be disclosure. At least we have it AFTER the deal is made. Would prefer right before. But wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[#liposuction of #brafat and #lovehandles . #txplasticsurgeon.com #scottkinfw@msn.com @ Dr. Scott E. Kasden https://t.co/1YH8GZBhXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgetKF30 @SpeakerPelosi @POTUS You are one tough woman.  Quite awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forced regionalization-they can withhold State funds which are declining anyway-big deal. And are you going to outl… https://t.co/ChbA2RI1wO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr7Renaissance @_BornOutkast @RasiqInTheCut_ @im_spiderman_0 @Superduperdope3 @eaphen @Krib7 I didn’t know they we… https://t.co/fO9OkeAcRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anniefofani @Cedepca @IlhanMN Yes, this fits within what I was told about the death squads in #Guatemala when I wa… https://t.co/BXDY6J5qKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[This large banner has been installed to get the attention of the community. @KCS_Johnson @KCS_District https://t.co/FFciPPBX9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holamexico @YalitzaAparicio Mínimo cuando @YalitzaAparicio hablo con ustedes desde Hollywood fue para decirles que… https://t.co/ZAhnMlwDjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz día a todos las mujeres del mundo en New York, New York https://t.co/boMLI0Ymrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the adventure has been fun and will require a return trip. #theprettyplacechaple and a random road side waterfa… https://t.co/xvgu7McIGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wonder what happens when the people who are so used to getting they’re ass kissed and getting so much atte… https://t.co/1Jb4UE9d8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBC News: No Evidence Of Trump Russia Conspiracy https://t.co/nsQhBROffk via @YouTube They have find or build somet… https://t.co/2UWgOmwWKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scarylawyerguy There’s a 150 billion a year that the pentagon doesn’t even know about.  They literally cannot see… https://t.co/4TMeqalO47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Outofcontrolgov @RidgeKayser @RepEliotEngel Liberal pass. Democratic two face. Never hold the Democrats to the same standard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a lot of fun on this home tour organized by Driggs Title! Was able to network and connect with other agents, ge… https://t.co/haxXCGOlHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[In all seriousness....this has made my day!! @LionsChoice https://t.co/ZyO3n55WYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBrust @Massawyrm So you’re saying Vlad and Cawti are getting back together! :p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyond Carbon is great idea.   Policies must agree  Oregon good place to set example .@KateBrownForOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAmerland @aaranged @bill_slawski @JohnMuirTrust @methode @JohnMu There's an old saying: "If you want to get t… https://t.co/kQ7B43rWXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[i talk to myself while i do my makeup like i’m recording a youtube video 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grocery shopping as we end our workday. (at @FoodLion Grocery Store in Forest, VA) https://t.co/A0nvzZOpG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lookitsdan Split-finger blues. 😂 Happy Birthday btw!  Hope you’re doing well, Man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between us, I think there's something special, and if I lose my mental Just hold my hand, even if you don't understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Kind of weird that people have a CHOICE to go to college but if they decide to they think it should… https://t.co/CPYAZajZaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rolls..yummy! (@ Jimmy's Cafe &amp; Fried Pies in Oklahoma City, OK) https://t.co/dYigUAQ1S6]]></document><document><![CDATA[.......ooooooooohh ☻COWARD pole smokin white trash ass wipe pimple dic glass the ass 🖕.....👂👂...🖕☻👋hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been working in labs for 5 years and there still hasn’t been a freak accident that gave me superpowers...   I’… https://t.co/hoJxIm03mH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@landorosario He’s trying to be a rapper now if that gives you any clue as to that guys intelligence or lack thereof]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HowICreateSuspense.... When my mother-in-law calls my cell and the Exorcist  ringtone I assigned to her number goes off in public.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Raleigh, NC #EventsMarketing job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: PRODUCT / EVEN… https://t.co/QxAkeHf1xn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYSenatorRivera @SethBarronNYC I'm all in. I get it. Be free to live your inner you. But don't try to disappear ar… https://t.co/LQkzjnlX6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump What is new here that we have not seen over the last 20 years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFLAJohn @WFLA sadly deranged fanatics being spawned from this "movement"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MolleeBranden @Triva08 @aplusedtech @hollysking https://t.co/tFEJbwfhCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bushyboy03 Caps tried that against Pens fans.  Bet it works out just as well for Wahoos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going live with Steve Kalayjian of @tickertockerapp on Facebook Live! in moments!]]></document><document><![CDATA[STAY WOKE PEOPLE !!!!! They’ve always tried to tell us about the rich people who are thieves and love to steal from… https://t.co/fcrpaP1oIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faced one of my biggest fears today! I finally gave blood! Feels so great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErwinSperisen @Sylvannahv Bendiciones bro. Todo cae por su propio peso. Un fuerte abrazo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth Right out of the Rules For Radicals playbook.  Feed controversy, divide factions and create dissenting action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#friyay!  5 hours ‘til March Break ⁦@MitchellDHS⁩ https://t.co/Mug4qF5BXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chance4gardener @JonAnthony7 @Riopedre31 @Beantowndougish @KingPeachDP @kaysintBB @TaggartRehnn @woodywood1999… https://t.co/oJc96Y78J5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Six minutes in, Mustangs trail 12-8. The TexAnns size advantage already evident early in this game. Coach Johnson s… https://t.co/yPa5AfaYiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG, I have 1,000 followers! Thank you. Think I’ll make it to 10,000? Thank you all so much! In today’s world 1000… https://t.co/yk5gsb1ap0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice Story. But Preven Not Stent. Death by heart attack, saved by firefighters: Bloomfield Township trustee shares… https://t.co/6bLKueEX8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RangersRul @BestBuy Yep completely broken, potentially series ending. I just couldn’t believe the collectors editi… https://t.co/SBd49ayV90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrMidLifeCrysis I wish my waitress liked me that much..I just get a bill for the food...🤔🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tshowlan This is not originally his. Pete Drucker. https://t.co/1l8kcsBL8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandi_love O M G     .. I can't wait to get rich this so I can marry yoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell #877877 Just Text Brady To #877877 https://t.co/XHLwGwdKFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter You dumb beaver he is five steps ahead of Nancy and looks like 25 steps ahead of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexiaameriica @mel_faith1 The dems are causing interference into presidential  operations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZGregJennings @TheDuckman22 Duckman you may need an eating challenge after this weight loss challenge at this rate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @max19219 @AOC @jeremycorbyn @Ilhan #truth #MAGA #Senators #Republicans @JohnCornyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBPundit I can’t wait till they roll their eyes at Candace Owens. Hey, at least she’s proposing ideas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Senator Burr is not highly respected in NC and is just talking the Trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elon Musk may soon master space travel, electric cars, and subterranean tunneling, but he may be no match for old f… https://t.co/MoRJBezUhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[At classic pizzeria Giordano’s in Navy Pier, Chicago https://t.co/eSwjKbvi9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeAllenPrim You do make a difference!  Glad to have you on my side and grateful for all the help you have given me in in Aldine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was actually a tough choice. I love shrimp poboys and hot roast beef poboys with gravy too. And I won’t say no… https://t.co/6LrPj9MzSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miabobeeuh i got volunteered to do a dunk tank for a school event at my moms school. it was the worst thing ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Roger Stone Threatens Judge with "Corruption Central" Crosshairs logo from conspiracy site that also… https://t.co/izRyrqCOO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freewillyiamson I’ll have to check it out dude! I’ve never heard of him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to anticipated hazardous weather conditions, all schools in the @ManhassetUFSD will be delayed for 2 hours on M… https://t.co/5m7EMmBJYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que porra é essa do Zé de Abreu se auto proclamar presidente? 😱 Doença!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kids are too young to challenge establishment and Bernie’s too old. Can somebody tell me the exact right age to do so?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinso76976605 He was just tryna get one last nut smh let the man live]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DDavis2016 I thought you were nice about it. Way to play hard, love the passion. #mrniceguy]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you win a Grammy, you’re important. When you become a viral meme, you’ve made it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyway, she throws up and then just steps forward and stands over her own vomit to try and cover it up. Nasty human… https://t.co/8zU8fppbMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Staff Feature Friday this week with Sharon Bailey! Thank you for making sure everyone at Franklin is being fed each… https://t.co/FGnaB3YCam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billsfanmonica Hell no I name most of my stuff too it's fun who cares what anybody else thinks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm waiting for someone to begin a line of questions by saying, "I'm a huge fan, thanks for being here today."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNMahr That Aladdin looks god awful. Will Smith, I think you're good on money bro. 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Dan Reaves. 2019 Jackson Sun Readers' Choice Awards: It's time to tell Jackson who is your favorite resta… https://t.co/KVzQ0OxdKK]]></document></documents></author>