<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett People have already gotten hurt: Charleston, Philadelphia, hate crimes… https://t.co/eNVrE11Tvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickPaulas @EastBayExpress Yeah, worth a shot tho. A real tragedy if it's all gone]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re GROWN arguing over twitter. Jordyn has no chance of recovering cause of the kardashian family’s control over… https://t.co/MrfgZ1qHqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_brumjo @jilevin Yes, I truly think that we have learned THAT, at least, from 2016.  We smell BS better, we ac… https://t.co/3ZhOHGbEZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Banned_Ali @Extinct_AnimaIs So far the only prehistorical one is the trilobyte, and hes the mascot character.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My partner in crime 👫 #ValentinesDay #love #happiness #adventures https://t.co/EayhlWhLTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/gP7fUhRBY9 "natural" does not equal "safe"!  #toxic #art #heavymetal #environmental #toxicworkspaces]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneak peak! W/ #xoxowithloveraj #westhollywoodnightlife #dancing #swag #beaches #makeupartist #love #weho… https://t.co/swb7QcmwFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes @DonaldJTrumpJr Pro life? Bitch, please. https://t.co/AFg6RlcRiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy World Whale Day everyone. I can't wait to see my boy Juno again this spring. It's been so long since I last s… https://t.co/QmGsUBaqUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Customers are so rude. It’s not my fault you put the wrong address on Grubhub home girl🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Gutiérrez NeuroCoach-Terapeuta-Conferencista Internacional. Teléf. +1 337-570-0617. Hasta Donde Puedas Ver S… https://t.co/1i08AygCLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bosseone2 @BuckSexton I'd rather have a nice RARE steak. With a side of steak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who recorded @BachelorABC episode from tonight to watch at a later date...  Take a drink every time you hear… https://t.co/BknWhJjFXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomBoi_BEE @Rod_J0 As he should! I got either the 12th or 13th tho.. and maybe a dinner or movie! 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @KamalaHarris Why are people just standing by watching this happen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We just confirmed Manohar Raju will take the position of the late Jeff Adachi as SF Public Defender. We will learn… https://t.co/17tqBYFE1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legally Blonde is the best movie ever made. Citizen Kane who?? Do not argue with me I will sue you]]></document><document><![CDATA[30x50x14 Metal building with 16x50 RV Cover Chestnut Brown Walls Coco Brown Roof and Trim @ Diana, Texas https://t.co/b50o0Q4IXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching ppl on YouTube go to 1 star  reviewed salons for makeup,nails and hair are very triggering like omfg🙃🙃🙃😑🤭😪… https://t.co/MqurtPzLyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueAshOhio please fix the potholes on Plainfield by the college. They are HORRIBLE on tires #tiresmatter]]></document><document><![CDATA[So important to know these signs @DPSNursing can you also share warning signs for heart attack? I know they’re diff… https://t.co/kxPSw8VTuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This pretty much sums up the last week at @syncrocks with a whole bunch of amazing #photographers and #friends. I h… https://t.co/K7mVL6a7X9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blessedisme2 @realDonaldTrump these undocumented ppl will have wasted it. Listen I’m not an ass. Why can’t that co… https://t.co/QHKsILWbOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch @rodneyscottsbbq. #discoversc #explorecharleston  #barbeque #food #travelwriter. #travelsouth southcarolina @… https://t.co/Bq3RbRV3it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShinySquirrel99 @jinbmore @imanewyorkernow @tomwatson Cloud docs shows 7 pages You need to up your game this time with the falsehoods]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA That is the true face of hate. Don’t trust her for 1 second! She knows what she is doing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[even just saying you’re gonna do it, that’s some pussy shit and I shoulda fuckin swung]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanhoneyy @Chilis I LOVE YOU THANK YOU for making my 21 years of life amazing. 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s represent #APEchatter at #SHAPETampa Home Tweet Home Social media party! Last year pic of #AdaptedPE voxer bu… https://t.co/xNzRpFwW5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[if anybody wants to donate $10,825 so I can go back to school that would be GREAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TraceyEllis19 We would love to have you!!!! But I do miss Dr.Evans, you and my kiddos!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is excited the Princesses are starting to arrive at @WDWToday for @runDisney #PrincessHalfMarathon weekend… https://t.co/7ooug1q7cM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Women's Day from Pookie and Sebastian!!! @ Pookie and Sebastian Boutique https://t.co/q0M0t2DPQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok I know this is lame but I just want someone to take me out on dates n hold my hand😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WaterNerds everywhere are watching Toledo OH today. Voting on Lake Erie Bill of Rights. #Ecosystems #protectourwater]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I go to Atlanta I don’t even be wanting nothing extra just give me checkers because that’s a place I don’t hav… https://t.co/sF8gLyA52f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I needed these quotes today. Maybe you do, too. #SundayMotivation #living #failure #quotes https://t.co/fM2UI5XND8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I slept so well last night, thanks Obama. Go Heels go @BarackObama go Franklin St.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmm somehow I feel like this is a giant metaphor about you and your career @boltyboy 😜🦄#WaitICantGetUp #HIMSS19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet tea brined fried chicken rootnbonemia #miami #friedchicken #miamifoodie #miamieats  #eat #foodielife #yummy… https://t.co/0zu0yJ6lKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention people anywhere lol. Mind your business. If someone wants to cut their hair they'll do it. No one really… https://t.co/7f1TxUPs1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[If i send you a video of me and my dog and you leave me on R, just know i’m highly offended]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t heard any Kpop song since jonghyun passed away, in 2017. It’s 2 years later &amp; I still cry listening to SHINee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love #snapchat with Johnny, the sweetest 13yo I have ever met, and he's all mine ❤❤ @ Layton, Utah https://t.co/YRVZ8fUGcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@49erCoug Ok sad. Stop that. I’ll make one and send it to you. One-of-a-kind!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to @K9Viking1 from @GuidingEyes Autumn🍁💙🐾 #livePD https://t.co/aUUYxGNM4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was watching this shit yesterday and honestly I would’ve threw hands with everyone lmao fuck that]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter was crazy about Steve Irwin. I remember having to break the sad news of his death to her... there were… https://t.co/OkTrLgdNoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ @TooFab She has nothing better to talk about anymore because we all stopped giving a shit when she moved overs… https://t.co/mIxv6K1zzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allvarado12 Prrrrrro si te pongo bien feliz cuando ando haciéndote show en el carro, kyt JAJAJAJAJAJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two of my classes have asked either who invented the printing press, or who Johannes Gutenberg is. Thank you, Space… https://t.co/9o1lWkSLoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is a tip.... They are not listening to you.  @mfannie #WSMI https://t.co/VXnGudyu8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[A couple years ago I was working at charter and I told this girl her and this dude would be cute as hell together a… https://t.co/33kyl953Jn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maria Iman Santoso crossed 6.2. Time 01:17:08, pace 13:30 min/mile, est. finish 11:25 am https://t.co/0sOApTW5NO #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know as much as I’d vote for either IF they were the nominee, I agree. The time for something new seems right i… https://t.co/LBuSRPTh0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want sushi and a pink drink from Starbucks is that to much to ask??]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The path of the righteous is like the morning sun, shining ever brighter till the full light of day.” Proverbs 4:1… https://t.co/NPmJ97rk1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk why I’m trying with these eye masks..the earliest I go to sleep is 1 am]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Ulta #TareCosmetics #Foundation (at @UltaBeauty in King of Prussia, PA) https://t.co/H9nttw7sSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding out new things about myself every day and being open to change is something new I’m getting used to. Thanks… https://t.co/cLb4w0lYME]]></document><document><![CDATA[always been real, promise you won’t ever catch me being fake to nobody 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is ludicrous. #funniness #chuckle #smirk #laughable https://t.co/t4YKcwJcPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsToldByJasmine I’m reading these tweets about being tired....what did YOU on Thursday night?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kweidleman @mikeyfranklin As 1 of 2 (and someone who still sometimes babysits), I am a firm believer that kids sho… https://t.co/hsKy8M7t56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson You are an attack on constitutional rights.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In all seriousness, I love when she writes essays and op-Eds. It’s just a reminder of what we already know — how in… https://t.co/il7109sJ3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom is going to pass tf out when she finds out my 25 year old brother got a tattoo ☠️☠️☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the groundhog said no more winter I did not think he meant severe storms and flooding for a week. I want a redo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Toni Morrison... May your legacy of suffering no fools live forever, as your work shall. https://t.co/b6p5sXO5j3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living in the Bay Area now and paying my sky high rent for a 1 bedroom apartment I know how accurate this is...😒… https://t.co/mJSlbgYn2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bout that eyelash #life 🙈 Got the cutest package today with the lashes  from #smallbusiness owner dama.gang  She’s… https://t.co/GaPdzMlco5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snoop Dogg doing the @RicFlairNatrBoy “WOOOO” was worth the whole night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EifertGrady the noun, verb and adjective in this Nebraska game. Grady is the #Boilermaker @GreggDoyelStar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uber'd the kids to meet closer, left downtown workshop an hour early, but here we are at dinner before I fly out to… https://t.co/kyc8dsYCGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soonerleesa Yes always watching morning after and listening to cam and Gabe in afternoons.  I miss Michelle,  and… https://t.co/KZTwYXHJad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hundreds of Young Protesters Confront McConnell Over Green New Deal  https://t.co/JYoKqoNALf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GingerGibson @KamalaHarris The average IQ of this bunch appears to be around 60.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old habits die hard, even for babies. Eddie still loves waking up at 2:30 to watch @abcwnn… https://t.co/V6Z44GPRmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel Naw... Harris or Warren. I'm all about the women this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[💍📸🤘🏻 delicate stacking rings #studiobluejewelry // Hammered  sterling silver stacking rings + Moonstone stacking ri… https://t.co/bZzJgB9b0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASOS Nothing bc my 2 day shipping order from over 2 weeks ago hasn’t been shipped yet 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kid also has 67k FOLLOWERS ON TWITTER. WHAT THE ACTUAL FUCK. THIS IS WHY I STOPPED PLAYING COMPETITIVE OVERWAT… https://t.co/NuO66VmSIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenslinn43 @Peeperpea29 @roads2 @Jimmysimmonds1 @Iluvinspireu @Jesus_Luvs_Us @ClockworkHamma @MyEngland2016… https://t.co/tVlMeIr9QS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should’ve chose this boy instead 👎🏼 treated me sm better now he boo’d up lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found the icing on the cake beaconscloset @UnrealFur for my outfit that I will wear for my show coming up in… https://t.co/OxQhRzG01x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Castle and Beckett were meant for each other Caskett always https://t.co/z4eDYZwWOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing redeeming about Bernie. He’s not cute. He’s not honest. He’s a wealthy guy pushing a philosophy th… https://t.co/ZlGHmxhNJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all my professors who assigned exams and projects due the week after spring break... you are the worst kind of people]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure winter hiking in 19 degree weather could be thought of as crazy, but these 3 crazies loved it!! Thanks Mer… https://t.co/56kJULZ7rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@escapedmatrix @AOC Boss, Your enemy is the NY Post, who chooses to do these ridiculous stories trying to shame a C… https://t.co/dV6H9eAuV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowlingQuacker I could keep the bit going with 15, 17, 33, 14, 37, 42... after that i don’t think I know the numbers either!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoezMcfLy Tell this guy Yankees eat 20 million per year bcontracts for breakfast]]></document><document><![CDATA[|￣￣￣￣￣￣ | |    PSSST.        | | @Lin_Manuel | |     (Are you     |      |   back yet?)    | | ＿＿＿＿＿__|  (\__/) ||  (•ㅅ•) ||  / 　 づ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pagetpaget @milfprentiss you're still beautiful, embrace it ❤️ but the little photo icon in the corner when you st… https://t.co/c7zcg5hLIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyGreier Did they release him yet? I'm told the search and lockdown ended at 3:45 p.m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BonvilleBethany and Gabby wins the 3 legged race 🏃‍♀️🏆 https://t.co/TAhzC5fwZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElFamosoFluffy I ain’t blind tho so I guess ima take that L real quick 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a powerful and incredibly important study- need to treat UTIs early in older persons to reduce mortality. T… https://t.co/QH3BOZhAQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fourth_stage @fMRI_guy @gays_irl @itatiVCS The irony of this not actually having a single citation on it is actual… https://t.co/oiwJkgmIk4]]></document></documents></author>