<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@kbrunorunner @Mayne1Carrie @FloridaJFuller2 @WeHo_1985 Not a bad one at all, I've only seen a problem from them an… https://t.co/0V4btm4fVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evan_bentley Guaranteed this is how I’m gonna feel in 1.5 weeks at @WestgateVegas watching the madness with y’all.… https://t.co/ImubfoGtTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for a very serious stop for ice cream at Husky Deli. husky_deli @ Husky Deli https://t.co/GdWoTfDvDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna get you to chuckle. #mirth #tee-hee #smile #absurd https://t.co/uJnn21CS7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpRussiaTies @RandyResist Nice chart! Well-designed. (I did this sort of thing in the 1980s)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anthony Hamilton and Fergie must’ve shared notes on that national Anthem 🤮🤮🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why tf do you think it’s acceptable to drive on the shoulder and bypass a backup 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twit_grim @Grahamskifalkir @theSNP Really?  It seems pretty pro-Remain to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Damn what a miscarriage of justice FB people of color get just Us in jail for a conspiracy charge gets 20 to life just US]]></document><document><![CDATA[We ended up  in the river instead...☺☺☺ @ Mt Baldy Road https://t.co/RXk2r8n0Xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prendi_gjon @LaVelleNeal I won’t cheer for the Yankees of NY or the Yankees of Philly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted that Mikal 3 to go in more than any shot in my life (probably an exaggeration)]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the world is ours, Like they say in Scarface kid, You can push your drugs and I can make it big.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Few clips from today’s workout... 2nd set of weighted pullups and dumbell shoulder press(80s for 4-6 reps, 70s for… https://t.co/5AMdiiRde0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pepperfire @suepeac @Ghettoman15 @Susann_G @ArthurAtkinson0 @trishkatree @MPxMcConnell @MaggieRicker @gtlem… https://t.co/ZNqdVVKICI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The shock-factor of this Robert Kraft news is off-the-charts. So many sleazy, sick aspects. He is worth $6 billion… https://t.co/EHHarrjaKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swinshi @JonCoppage @_TamaraWinter @CityLab Yup, but starting in 2010: https://t.co/0PlxWjKjPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLAIRONEAL @KarenMillen Only way to get to the weekend is through Monday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaysJournal Let's hope so, he has more talent than anyone in the system and seems ready. How refreshing to have a… https://t.co/zp4uqMcMXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My analysis is that he must have hired a Rudy-“quality” attorney, which will cost him dearly when the complaint is… https://t.co/tXpJfrzpsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have food poisoning and am currently in Florida but I’m still not bout to miss this game tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOldManClub Lynyrd Skynyrd, Aerosmith, Van Halen, Rolling Stones, &amp; AC/DC!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @Uber if we cancel after five min we get charged, but what about when we wait for a car and they cancel? What abo… https://t.co/oOva9M1Nrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#colorshop #resurgence #fxbr sexy ‘70’s back!!! @harleydavidson #borntoride @ Jackson, New Hampshire https://t.co/p25E2wKpPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it comes out of the novel, but from Gatsby, “And so we beat on, boats against the current, pushed back cease… https://t.co/TqpjDGg7Fn]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Côte d’Ivoire progressiste t’attend avec impatience ... N’oublie jamais que tu es l’espoir de la Côte d’Ivoire p… https://t.co/iuETSEepVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kwills21_ @kevolivee That nigga just be talking know damn well that wasn’t no travel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday to these awesome people &amp; friends. @sophvas @DudeMcIntyre @christoplack @Biggluvsbrkdown… https://t.co/dVbbTqg5sj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattGlantz @jaredjaffee21 Wow this sounds like a really good deal Jaf. You better jump on it (him) before @djmacjr… https://t.co/ImV103dFyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This really is the best UFC card of all time. Even the prelims are good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miamicurt @finebaum 😂 awww congrats.  What’s your record?  Save ya the time 51 🐊 18 the other team]]></document><document><![CDATA[Memories: 2013 It seems like it was just Yesterday! mrsbeckett43 Congratulations Mom to be @ San Francisco Peaks https://t.co/WVeAkEuCZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news3leah That looks like a Pontiac!  Did you see my old metallic green 2-door ‘52 Chevy?  Sounds like u had a great time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[O'Keefe's 6-point night fuels Tewksbury victory https://t.co/C64GGLwRC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trailsofsmoke @50cent Rap is best known for having terrible takes  The entertainment is seeing someone get so fire… https://t.co/MKaIbA6xmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinMacMahan hey Justin did you tell Harden to go back to Africa and say his kid should learn to speak english ?like the Utah fans did?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@targetingg I was the one who assisted the @JCSO_Oregon with the photography of my grandmothers dead body! Nobody e… https://t.co/Wj648q0hXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sexypontiff I grew up next to him until his house burned down and then in HS his cop dad got run out of town on a… https://t.co/rmpqnIYCND]]></document><document><![CDATA[They haven't missed on a song yet though.... so I mean how ridiculous is it really?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalLoveYourPetsDay YUH I luv you phoebe buffet crawley https://t.co/f1Pt1Th33L]]></document><document><![CDATA[All y'all need to give this a listen! — ♫Lost Highway by Jason &amp; the Scorchers, from #SoundHound https://t.co/KgBqdlYbXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow We don’t know what’s in the tax report until we read it🤪🤪🤪 https://t.co/unyAOdOk5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SIRIUSXM May be one of the most disreputable companies in America today. Their pricing seems to be based on whatev… https://t.co/qZPKU8pziS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 10am. I just ate my lunch. My actual lunch break is at 12:30 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Devotional of the day  Stages Of Grief: Depression - “You keep track of all my sorrows. You have collected all my...https://t.co/XM8MpU7lwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vocalminorityCA @TFCCobra I’m gonna knock you out! #MOMSCCL say knock you out! https://t.co/5BzkqxhyWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charles Whitman, el primer tirador. La fotografía es de la revista Times, de pocos días después del primer mass sho… https://t.co/GCA5r3GAET]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ameen✊🏿💪🏿 #AsaalamuAlaikumWahRahmantuillah #Alhamduillah #Allah #AllahUAkbar #ProphetMuhammad #PBUH #Quran #Hadith… https://t.co/WtpuoN8WnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAKE THE FUCK UP, THIS CROWD IS MORE DEAD THEN THE WALKERS ON THE WALKING DEAD #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WatWouldHovaDo @O_SawyerBOY Two ball handlers can hoop together, could of done a lesser Bron Wade Miami deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @CoryBooker Because jussie and cory are the biggest phonies in the spot light now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump If you cleaned the plexiglass, in your navel, before you stick your head up your ass, y… https://t.co/J51hhA8Zoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Talk about working on people’s fear. Climate change cannot be controlled without a mass reduction in… https://t.co/HIb0l3ya53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@booksNrulers WHEN THE EYES HAVE SEEN SO MUCH... then  ppl  got the nerve to think of morals...  notice  nothing sa… https://t.co/KbJk1iNHHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul B. S.  This is clearly within purvue of President and its time all Republicans support him or lose the country in 2020.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk @IlhanMN Be better than this @SkylerSBudman    Can’t “like” lies and untrue statements and really want change and progress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me confused af cuz i already been having So Far Gone on my phone for the last 7 years 🧐 pretty sure i bought it off… https://t.co/DApK9CL29N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi #Date en #Miami - Mauricio Mejia ft  Edd Garcia https://t.co/2vJISJBLOA vía @YouTube ❤️ https://t.co/4zNkEtNMmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[God i need a ummm uhhhh a uhhh a mothafucking a uhhhh shit what the fuck is it a uhhh *snaps* a uhhh shit its on th… https://t.co/dyyE52W4Xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RemiEnguehard @Mourad_l @NawakP 1998: entrer sur le site. C’est du texte donc même en 33k pas de chargement. Lire le contenu.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kalhiapaola @palnorteoficial Es ABQ que no tiene vuelos para ningún lado. Lo odio y lo aborrezco jajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Davidnic33 Thanks - right back atcha! Go Duuuuuuuke! What a game. What a team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I compulsively bought a graphics card for $420 and I don't know if it's compatible with my case or motherboard. Anyways, how was your day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@footballinfo I’ve always wanted to really learn the Shoot but it’s easier to find out how to stop the Night King. https://t.co/ZDkWvnu8E5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabrielmalor It’s cool that he got on the record that Trump joked about Russia finding the 30000 HRC ILLEGALLY deleted emails.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gregraham_1 To quote a friend of mine, “If she looks like she would cost more than $20 Dollars, she is a cop”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clive_owen @clauudianicolee @ClaaudThompson https://t.co/1cwjZliRjS, claudia nicole thompson 18 "clark county" mis… https://t.co/2h7WkNe3Bb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanGBetts RT RZ IS BACKED BY DEMONSTRABLE TRUTH, SHOULD call for Demonstrable Rebuttal, Just a Plain Piece of P… https://t.co/tqyqpOV22m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_Gabrielle_ Well fuck it I’m bouta ignore yu until you send me 100  that’s the least I’m accepting 🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to have finally found a girl that is crazy enough for me to put up with all my goofiness!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Blackhistorymonth2019  Day Twenty-Two “I had a moral obligation to step up. Morality was a far greater force than… https://t.co/0Sk3oa91e4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DEFYDragonSpirit Ultimo Dragon @defyNW in Seattle. https://t.co/7UgiCp4Ktg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Some very sick minds that thought that sending kids to pick cotton and sing slave songs is funny. Those teache… https://t.co/67vpT5Yont]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattingebretson That should be the first line of the new book you’re going to write]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes we do. Everybody is always quick to call every single album a classic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're right @realDonaldTrump , voter fraud is real. Its rampant among Republicans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chiefjustice06 Chief! Loving the pod and can’t wait for MLB. New to dfs all together. Any tips for gpp lineups? I… https://t.co/4m6zYVNuEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thucnhi21 It echoed the conversation in my house watching the game! https://t.co/gn720Y1aYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@molratty Yeah, but it’s a good point, and I was thinking the same thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can still hear last nights concert in my head..... 😅 @ Sunny Isles Beach, Florida https://t.co/Id1XbqtmpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Rawlings @sgoldstein Happy birthday Scott. You’ve been a great asset!]]></document><document><![CDATA[V from #dmc5 is op as hell 😂 can this man have a solo game? @DevilMayCry https://t.co/CqPmrz2hOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@617Report @realDonaldTrump All the evidence that “we” have??   I didn’t know you were on Mueller’s team]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could remove CT and replace with MA. Open road tolling coming. Peak hour tolling coming. Sad. #mapoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjhegar. Hi I got your Hippo card. My lantus cost would be 284.per lantus bottle. I already asked my endo Dr for… https://t.co/2s455zu35V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stengel @Sifill_LDF McCabe... disgraced liar. Possibly engaged in SEDITION.]]></document><document><![CDATA[yooooo caelynn from #thebachelor didn’t even deny saying all the shit she was accused of!!!! colton u dumb get rid… https://t.co/tQh0UF84oa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Trudeau has lost the moral mandate to govern #CDNpoli #pnpcbc #JodyWilsonRaybould #SNCLavalin #SNCgate #TrudeauCoverUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice work by @CCChronicle reporters and @chlawrence’s Columbia College Chicago reporting class for @WCRXFM election… https://t.co/LdPUHYPcOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllefsenAJ I'm off to bed but I'll bite. I can read the answer tomorrow morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bramasco launches an early offering from Kitchen to the gap in right-center. C. Carolina CF Rivers settles under it… https://t.co/GAxhq4z9Dn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 If there is you motherfuckers will get your asses kicked. I fucking  guarantee it. You don’t have the guts to win!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NSIP_NG @MBuhari @ProfOsinbajo Let the thieves congratulate themselves for a rigging well managed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dancing_dawson Playing this video with 'Moves Like Jagger' playing in my buddy's dorm room and we all died when it synced up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoiceOfTheStar Before reading this, I wonder if the "why now" part has anything to do with the team needing some p… https://t.co/iDw6CJNPhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcnhobbs @LemieuxLGM @Nicole_Cliffe I try to walk on daily chores. Austin has many obstacles between otherwise use… https://t.co/FuDjbXR9p6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMulkeyGT @marcjack845 @Lunch44 @timelesssports_ Yeah that dunk was in ‘04, the year we made it all the way to the National Championship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAD RESPECT to Otis Livingston II. @VCU_Hoops fans LOVE BASKETBALL, so we recognize a REAL ONE. And you been A REAL… https://t.co/qHL9CnStUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anthony 14 Brooklyn Ny  Model/Actor looking for a agent or agencies open for booking email in bio @IMGmodels… https://t.co/q0chvECha8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my poem “Everything to Me” dedicated to my beautiful and amazing fiancé chikadee12282! I love you, Meliss… https://t.co/khPE3peV9f]]></document></documents></author>