<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BritishProg @RogerHodgson R.i.P. Peter Halsten Thorkelson (February 13, 1942 – February 21, 2019) aka #PeterTork.… https://t.co/x6q7VFD1wV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It appears there's still hella traffic from gonzales to chualar so plan ahead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LockItInonFS1 @TheCousinSal @ClayTravis @ToddFuhrman @rachelbonnetta That’s funny shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good To My Earhole, February 20. #neworleansjazz #sonsofkemet bobbyrushbluesman #mottthehoople #albumoftheday… https://t.co/JzpTB3WwSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heads up: The @wcti12 feature on South Lenoir and UNC’s Hunter West is coming up in a few minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta tell ya, I never watch Reality shows but this season ender is riveting..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenjaminEnfield perfect example of the by standard affect in #Psychology - everybody around sees this going on, bu… https://t.co/DXbk0NIhMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thistallawkgirl God made Adam and Eve, not Adam and Edam. https://t.co/gz9OswQQm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADavidHaleJoint Gotta go Adam Banks for Grade School. Willie Mayes Hayes for Pro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MoASSP along with the Missouri School Administrators Coalition opposes HB 581.  I am asking @supportelijah to opp… https://t.co/Ml3qPMcJkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christianity: *AGE OF DECEIT* (FULL) Fallen Angels and the New World Order https://t.co/jEIScRiKHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmilliAura Seriously. Every time I tell certain people I would love to move to Orlando, they always throw some negativity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimTrotter_NFL @iamRuthECarter @TheAcademy Totally agree! Maybe I’m biased because she’s from my city, but I’ve se… https://t.co/Rupn1bKTuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPressSecBot @MSNBC Doesn’t that make her an immigrant?  Shouldn’t she have to climb a wall or something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This for a student section bus for the basketball team making it to the 3rd round https://t.co/8pc6whs6iZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppleMusic is there any reason why Alice In Chains album the devil put dinosaurs here is removed from Apple Music?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can only imagine if @Trevornoah had been a conservative... He would no longer HAVE a show to spew his garbage!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scary. Not sure I'd invest my money in something that's so reliant on China. Call me patriotic (or paranoid). 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austindillon3 meets the media @LVMotorSpeedway . https://t.co/vvwcICUYuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[WoW !! All the morning shows are salivating over #Cohen and his lies! Mueller finds NOTHING!What’s wrong with talki… https://t.co/MgacJmvZr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Setting up for day 2 of Mastering Index Tuning. @ San Diego, California https://t.co/1BRjVAjJSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[In #Florida I think we would classify them as traffickers, right @gnewburn?  https://t.co/1R3HOFtY9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Internationals, please spread this far and wide: https://t.co/gDWIJXxdLr  We MUST wake up the world to what the Hid… https://t.co/612VITAYod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RossTuckerNFL The current President of the United States has already taught me that the whole “Golden Rule” thing… https://t.co/W0B6Tl23bb]]></document><document><![CDATA[444 S Cloverdale Ave 444 S Cloverdale Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90036 https://t.co/8XGq2cRlb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I currently have the best American health care situation I’ve ever heard of (by sheer dumb luck) and it’s still not… https://t.co/RoGBvBqJA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me haces tanta falta abuelito, daría lo que fuera por abrazarte una última vez, por estar contigo. Nos veremos pron… https://t.co/aDV8uKLjol]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are not trucks anymore. They are luxury SUVs that ordinary average Joe's can't afford. They have no usable tru… https://t.co/IIYs0iyIXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VladimirBlue @kerrywashington Because it’s such a scandal! And she specializes in scandals!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crystalline_02 I suspect a self-respecting sinkhole would spit him back out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @elcitizen @vladimirpadrino Ja ja ja. Toma tu galleta y cómelo, delincuente de mierda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet Not sure he's a traitor, but definitely should be brought to testify why he acts like he is starved… https://t.co/KLt2UF7Bdg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 1st rave was amazing!! Definitely a new hobby of mine so GIVE ME SOME ROOM!!!!!  🤘🏾🤘🏾 excisionofficial… https://t.co/ff1ZtQFawy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Semifinal Saturday in the @TheMountainEast Tournament. Four what I believe are going to be entertaining games. Acti… https://t.co/y6dnHtyVoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FutbolBible Either Sarri resigns which is the least likely thing or Kepa is benched for a loooonnnnnnggggg time with a nice fine too. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting for a state quarterfinal doubleheader as the Spotswood girls take on Magna Vista and the Spotswood boys bat… https://t.co/b4L5QP3iOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MWharam7 Totally agree on all of it.  To add, RG3 was a linear, track athlete.  No wiggle, led to every hit looking like a career ender...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @CompanyTheater with get_repost ・・・ CARRY THE BANNER with us this April! 📰🗞🏙 @newsies #newsies… https://t.co/loOHD80ORn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Husky_Golf @PLHSgolfteams Chances do not look good...... crazy winter. #SpringGolf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump I got not give a humongous, putrid excrement , FUCK. I hope his retarded face gets the boot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oalh @aguahermosillo @VictorMendozaL @HermosilloGob @cynthiagarama @CARLOSEES @feroropeza20 @OmarDavila @Chaposoto… https://t.co/UtmtWaebS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clarencehilljr Would rather see Austin’s role expand if we have to let Beasley go. Hope we hang onto 11, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyitsMarkus @SpiritBen @AndyLeeWTVA You will soon find out you’re wrong about 99% backers.I probably have more Ol… https://t.co/nrOzbZQP5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julianahatfield I just read your interview in April Guitar Player.LOVED IT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cushbomb @banebutwoke Broadly agreed, but one day in the not so distant future, cinema quality CGI will happen in real time]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Wayne Gretzky debuted with the WHA’z Indianapolis Racers, the first attempt was to sell him to the Winnipeg Je… https://t.co/LxFhPeunEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethDavisHoops The love for Purdue is baffling. 7 losses, blown out by Maryland this week = 8. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@OntarioPCParty .@fordnation It’s time to change your party’s name to The Regressive Conservative Party. While the… https://t.co/K3cSMb8IZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelirioJennie i love my beautiful wife. YOU are also my best friend. I am so happy we found each other over 2 years ago baby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know no one cares but our car IG has over 1000 followers go check out @ BorderLineMotors on insta gram :)))]]></document><document><![CDATA[?!?! my professor emailed all of the students that completed college math or higher within the last 2 years and sai… https://t.co/AMc25UZebA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CleatEliteAnfro @jasondjarrett Also, most of the non-football athletes will need to keep their amateur status for… https://t.co/OQZwg1uxrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRWantsToKnow I seriously loved how they brought actors like him and Skeet Ulrich to be on Riverdale. Man that sucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got some shows coming up including a weekend at the always amazing funnystopcomedyclub with Traci Kanaan. And my co… https://t.co/Z1gHHpAl5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackmjenkins @rachelheldevans @KatelynBeaty @edstetzer @publicroad So sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ my future sugar daddy/momma stop playing and come to me already I’m tired of waiting.😔😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@potroalvarez Potro becerro pero esa no fue la rumba que le hicieron García Carneiro y @dcabellor @ConElMazoDando a… https://t.co/rC8kp7VZu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Issac11_fit @MelKiperESPN You really think there’s that much difference between 198 lbs and 201 lbs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVG @BH_AEberhardt @BritneyEurton @ClockersCorner @santaanitapark Rosie is the best! @santaanitapark icon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsmejjwarren Love it when we recognize the still speaking Spirit and leaders declare it with boldness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdbm5188 @tildegm @realmadrid @FCBarcelona_es @QUINTERORADIO @los4deldeporte1 @roberantolin @YamirHernandez7… https://t.co/y9Jiffk1TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have an orgy going on tonight. If i get tipped by 10 people, or reach 50$, in tips on this post, I will record it… https://t.co/J75YXpaMMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer @Dr_VanNostrin @BernieSanders He has accomplished getting rich off the public while doing nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet nightmares  I am going to bed and every day is hollows eave for me because I get the feeling that everyone ha… https://t.co/Xloj7eHQWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Center Hill Basketball: If you are heading to the Final 4 to cheer on your Mustangs you might want to check out the… https://t.co/LxdXE2QXs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halperry @RubinReport @SamSeder God dammit. Tell Seder to debate a fucking intellectual already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_cherryvvaves I jumped to another line after like 10min of boiling over]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys...DO NOT sleep on @FairladyComic. Brian, Claudia, Marissa and Shari have cooked up something special.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Trump will be out soon  Not thinking so is a failure of imagination and courage. The question is whether Fly… https://t.co/znfD3jsU7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mex. (@ McCarran International Airport (LAS) - @lasairport in Las Vegas, NV) https://t.co/jCZe2arfTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJacegg @GreggDoyelStar @MattGlenesk No the wat shot hasnt left your mind. You still celebrate it ten years later.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMarkovitz It sounds crazy, but not if they were to bring in other max players once he left. Their mistake was not… https://t.co/HxRcuAle6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@friend_feline He didn't just all of a sudden do this all by himself. Who is behind the idea? Y he didn't want to give up his phone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tank SZN and yet Miami will go on to win these 3 games and everyone will talk about how they can be good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Readerhal54 Then you have empty properties that they would sell. You tax them on that. Religion is big business, t… https://t.co/a7XmFOuPx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I’ve learned since joining #amwriting:  People who overshare are weird.   People who overshare about fiction… https://t.co/IYAU0syURG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy_Lofgren @po_kuhner I've been there! I think that's going to be my best option from these dates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juanxon @rafasanchez20 Tssss que honor se debe sentir llegar y tener un par de cheves pagadas... increíble! 👊🏼👊🏼👊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain’t nothing worse than getting out a lyft you all picked the wrong destination for. The immense feeling of bewild… https://t.co/cQA977FVlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caputo: "You've got to show up for work. You just do. And the governor showed no leadership."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meowwch @AOC Better delete this quick @AOC your stipends r set for each elected official The MRA for each Rep is c… https://t.co/YBnhgpsKfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattRudy1983 @Kent_Webb @JeffSchultzATL @TheAthleticATL I lived in Cobb in the same zip code as the stadium from 2… https://t.co/gMZiZGLdLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolyy2020 @EESCARRAJR @BigOShow Where the rapists roam free in woman's restrooms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedWingGrips @Swamp_Fever2020 Not to mention the problem open borders creates. What low life's. This shows what a… https://t.co/xKZPsBkLu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@panamaredhat @JillEnergy @RachelEGolden I totally agree we should electrify. Just want to make sure the numbers wo… https://t.co/LUD7QgWwCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[A suspect has been arrested in a Elizabethtown double fatal shooting. Stay tuned to WDRB this morning for info. https://t.co/TAwwbvu9fZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieWalton The whole package maybe?! Lol. So much to love here. I think it was coming to get Jack back and burnin… https://t.co/3Krp1zHcQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ganjly420 Thank you. On February 27th at 9:00 eastern I’ll be appearing on @VICE @VICELAND Live making a tasty little #cocktail]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @chadloder for the kind words! We @FoundationCap are excited for the future of #cybersecurity!… https://t.co/7Ufpf7WwyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great. Right on @RepMikeQuigley for doing this. There is no good reason to restrict access to public court… https://t.co/Gafquaitha]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHO NEEDS BEATS???! PURCHASE YOUR STYLE TYPE OF BEATS TODAY FROM #DWALLBEATS ON ALL MUSIC PLATFORMS  #BeatStars… https://t.co/H0Wpgv8euw]]></document><document><![CDATA[No me los pierdo por nada 😍! @ClubSantos #GuerreroNoCualquiera #Concachampions @TheChampions #ChambeandoAndo https://t.co/TbYfVWOgrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytopinion @nytimes @neal_katyal Mueller is a Republican  truthtelling unbiased professional Trump is an immoral c… https://t.co/5V7itPyHNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[todos esses anos de luta por direitos iguais, nada foi em vão. Vocês são seres magníficos, com uma história de soro… https://t.co/IyazRwRyon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swingleft @Paulasmyth13 @Jim_Jordan Does Jordan look like he would feel comfortable wearing a pointed hood?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In the absence of a district office, and with no way to contact the congresswoman, voters have resorted to despera… https://t.co/9QRruQOcqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanKey1982 @ROBINBKEY2 Good call on your part cause...... https://t.co/8qy0FjkRWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabYoung2 @marklevinshow It's worse than terrible. Her anti-Semitism is being recorded in the public record of the… https://t.co/cAHwsba1nM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7 Then, All questions on the census  are illegal. We will just answer PRESENT... Like Congress does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charlie26Adam Guys I remember back in the 70's your soccer pitches/stadiums had moats and or fences built around t… https://t.co/XFvsy25eOD]]></document></documents></author>