<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#bocabraves #bocabravesfootball #bocabravespopwarner #25 #patchreefpark #football @ Patch Reef Park/JARCC https://t.co/79YZgGnv0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lexie is literally the sweetest and best friend in the entire world. She surprised me with the most amazing early b… https://t.co/AGKddrk4KA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stylethread @vankapro @goldencorral @AARP @Luvs @GilletteVenus @Crest @Bounty @SharperImage @Disney @IHOP https://t.co/tk8ceNYlsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irish_titan Nice! I have noticed this with how some companies write their release notes for app updates. @SwarmApp… https://t.co/6GKAbdsfnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbpelham No problem. Also make sure that there’s nothing in the bag that’s on Disney’s prohibited list. That could… https://t.co/XE9R6f90yD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funkminister I gotchu... Surprise, they're all of dogs! https://t.co/JNlFBnq1yV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My great grandfather maternal came frm Germany. He wasn’t met with military might, guns, or had to climb a fence or… https://t.co/kwyxl6h8m2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like me by summer walker really knows how to throw you in ya feelings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @ThatShockratees You are doing a great job and I am so happy for the United States that we all have you fighti… https://t.co/B1Fy8zrfs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[cheetolini its time to impeach  him and put him jail congress this is dangerous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blancauzi OMFGG IS THAT HIM ?? UGH HE’S EVERYWHERE https://t.co/tTvcJwuFzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yzYQeGkqCO  @heydollcake and I are streaming #ultimatechickenhorse! Come watch us suuuuuck! #livestream #streaming]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning view...I seem to always find a Buddha...last day in Charleston. Cold and rain y   #charleston #buddha… https://t.co/NImZyAV4Xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelastduckoff @NYCMayor @NYCSchools @NYCDHS You’re dead wrong on that as well disrespectful with the “names calli… https://t.co/sRAi2vMr14]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Orange by Gucci Mane &amp; C-Note on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/VM3oCz4QpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonBallDM198 @CourtneyMKorkow @jennwhite_ Warmed my heart to see you! Family ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelschweitz We buy all of our sports gear from Dicks. They rock. We need to support them. They're supporting u… https://t.co/MxHxu26Xv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4judyblue @craftsman @dega_boy_87 @Pixxydoodle @NrsgJBHCtwmn1 @DannyLeBlanc24 @CMANGO @rottzillasgirl… https://t.co/0xe8kRfQ4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[#فاليري_ابو_شقرا ملكة الليلة على كل القلوب بدون منازع !!! تجرأت و نجحت 👸👸#ديو_المشاهير]]></document><document><![CDATA[@42PercentNative @realDonaldTrump How sick can you get it? It appears you have no morality and no respect for the p… https://t.co/FfKvEfNfQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormanixoapriI @youngoz1_ Then why you confused? 🙄 I was clarifying your confusion sis. 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Josh opened the window and within seconds Hercules dove into the screen and flew out the window..... I can’t stop laughing 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coachpump615 Let it out young scholar....Sugar, spice 🤣😂 and everything nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino I’m sure he eats out a lot... someone should take pics for this meat-eater]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miliman12photos @CharlesMcCool @columbiasc @RiverbanksZoo @TravelSouthUSA @Discover_SC @DarleyNewman @always5star… https://t.co/zdwAwOiMDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is truly a wonderful moment right now. I am just capturing this "present time" and it feels so grounded. It is i… https://t.co/s8Z1vrdYZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Wonderful Time With Angela Davis. THANK YOU https://t.co/BTSsx0cjOp. @ The Boutwell Auditorium https://t.co/evVo3DA03c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy hour on Madeira Way has been going strong since 2 ! Live music on every corner ~ NP I’m good at catching up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got back home from @ultabeauty and I’m so happy with my purchase. They feel so soft and look stunning. Excelle… https://t.co/9RwAp7cTfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WVLTCasey Yes!!!! Go!!! There is soooooooo much more that will leave your jaw dropped for days!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all wanna know about loyalty? I left my number on a receipt for my waiter at Cracker Barrel 6 years ago and he st… https://t.co/NkepfDZieP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living where white people are a minority is humbling dawg we really trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Blackhawks lead #RedWings 4-1 with 9:22 left in the 2nd. Shots 19-9 Detroit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZooWildlife @j2tyco @FOX10Phoenix Thank you for not doing anything to the jaguar. That woman asked for it by, quit… https://t.co/EOiJ0BaR5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[alitamovie  3D #dolby glasses are awesome @ Amc https://t.co/3SLHNmrEok]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Watch and pay attention!  Pray, pray, pray for the nation of America and for President Donald Trump, for it shall… https://t.co/rsQ6hLxWan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ash Wednesday #dusttodust @ Colorado Springs, Colorado https://t.co/YRusnKQROC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDona10468179 @GodsGirlSong Maybe we should change the hat color😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bittersweet night at the basketball banquet. Great group of seniors as players and as young adults. Cant believe th… https://t.co/ji1xwZuN9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Is this the drug company Customer Service? Them: Yes Me: I wanna speak to the person trying to kill my husband.… https://t.co/fPR4DnyWts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Paonia Peach (Blender Project 007) by @newbelgium at @maxstaphouse — https://t.co/k4xdtLcek2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a rule of no dog sleeping in bed, and I just came upstairs to Jake literally trying to hide our dog under th… https://t.co/RJg4MuNHQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LtDan1020 @realDonaldTrump I know they are trying because I see at least 25 applications in one day go out. EVERY DAY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red Shawl Fundraiser April 12, 2019 at Potawatomi Bingo and Casino benefiting Gerald L Ignace Indian Health Center… https://t.co/LMmZU06Zm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning and happy Wednesday. This morning inspiration for you and food for thought truly 🕉🐉 @ Lawnton, Pennsyl… https://t.co/RHtM4fAvOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen this guy he goes walking at NorthStar mall daily and he’s always wearing his anti-trump shirts and I give… https://t.co/Eg2kSDO2ew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ek_anderson I appreciate not being the only poet awake at 4 am, but I was out of pills. 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[It snowed in Santa Clarita the other day. Yes, that’s LA, folks. I also just bought crocs. I can’t tell if life is… https://t.co/9nk1XPtqP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham @JerryFalwellJr @FRCdc @SarahHuckabee @PressSec @KellyannePolls]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @whiteribbonusa ・・・ @GQMagazine gqportugal GENIUS! branislavsimoncik  Portuguese actress inescastelbranco f… https://t.co/gN3mGU4FYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready for the #MobbDeepForever tour!? CUZ I AM 👑 #ReignOn #ShowTime @mobbdeephavoc @MobbDeep @rappernoyd @… https://t.co/7zGBl6z4eI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time Spent On Date at Movies:  5% - Watching movie   5% - Avoiding physical contact of any kind (without being obvi… https://t.co/BTdmDdU3iK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Gigi got to meet her newest little peanut today! Heart bursting with love! Welcome to our world Miss Mila!… https://t.co/1Y86Mx2FIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Yorkers: Y'all look like a buncha Nazis in those Canada Goose jackets. FYI.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸Con Sue Photography and Design🇺🇸   🇲🇼Like our photos...Follow our IG 🇲🇼  🇨🇱This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 🇨🇱… https://t.co/lVVJzcLbTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThursdayMotivation - I know how blessed I am to have the love and support of my #husband 🙏🏽❤️ The past few years m… https://t.co/IAN5CltX1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutnumberedFNC this country has in the name of PC made one excuse after another for the extreme muslims in this co… https://t.co/YQstDXwaKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottMStedman Is there a Pathological Liar Scumbag magnet hidden in Trump's phone? They all seem to find him. EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM LIE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long weekends are all about creating yummy brunches together 😋#family #AvocadoToast #DeviledEggs #FruitSalad… https://t.co/cuBlpdJLgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working late tonight in the pouring rain makes me really appreciate my cozy studio, and especially my… https://t.co/6rgab9uHqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s safe to say that @QCTheLabelMusic is the new @deathrowmusic the homey @qcm_p and @coachk44 knows what they’re doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Iuo6312GPV  Trump &amp; GOP Block  Puerto Rico Disaster Funding...  1.4 Million Face Food Stamps Loss, Starvation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyHaddish @BrodyismeFriend So sorry for your loss. Just not fair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevDon Oops forgot "things" lol..😉 amazing how stuff from Seasame Street as a child sticks with you..🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and dyl are about to go through our first underway together... pray for me 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laciaustin0315 You wouldn’t have to tell a joke cause yo face issssss the joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lavenderpopin I know Lion but at least he is coming around. His voice can be a powerful tool in the #ADOS movement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Alden decided 2go solo he hardly mention ADN he’s back n the arms of Aldenatics Meantime Maine attended all AD… https://t.co/wgzWvl1zA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like it or not both Julio Urias and Alex Verdugo are part of this story. Both are set to be big part of the Dodgers… https://t.co/Wgh8oawvUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selena Gomez and the Jonas Brothers are releasing songs today..... I feel like my childhood is back and I’m so than… https://t.co/xBjozp1n4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning of learning resonates how quickly time flies when you are having fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miss_brown84 Agreed but she did apologize. Let’s see if it’s real bc if they have that -0 ur friendship then kimbella is gonna need yandi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uwharrie Marathon is in the books! Today’s goal - just don’t fall! The combination of super technical trail, tons o… https://t.co/4HInDfDAJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@franco_esca Ayer me dijeron que era agua de calzón :( le quieren hacer amarre :p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samueldennigan @NatProdExpo @StrongRootsUSA These look amazing! Sadly, I'm missing #ExpoWest. Tell me more? Where… https://t.co/253KxyWCWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinnieWoo17 @vroberts9 @Tonithecat32 @1gingerbeauty @AngusMcPussPuss @deborah26449389 @buddy_gizmo @Cleo_sMommy… https://t.co/oHHFMcI4Te]]></document><document><![CDATA[i spend more money than anyone i know, i really need to pull myself together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalibuMom62 @AP Um, thrown into the limelight?  I guess you missed who she was before her sugar daddy was president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your mind fucks with you, you are a photo of them and can’t do anything but laugh, cause your mind was trippin and… https://t.co/JeGEZpzMYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[i only subscribed to jeffree star on snapchat because i like watching people open makeup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Killing time at Matthew's check up at Vanderbilt 😉 @ Monroe Carell Jr. Children's Hospital at Vanderbilt https://t.co/4saZ6UTJS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaWark @MarciMiller We're not sure. He's always wanted to focus on movies at some point. No, they're not recast… https://t.co/k0hrESI3TC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heads up! A fatal crash has closed down the intersection at Indian River and Military Hwy! 4:30 AM Friday   Live NO… https://t.co/RyGb5hHogd]]></document><document><![CDATA[tangina ang bobo ko. sa isang pagkakamali nasira lahat, 🤦🏻‍♀️ nawala yung taong gusto kong makasama potanginaaa! da… https://t.co/gR3f7liqFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visiting the Brea Tar Pits. The pelvis of a giant sloth is revealed in this asphalt gumbo. #writeyourwayin… https://t.co/0GjGJkIvVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[A dishonor on so many levels. Having had the privilege of being there when The White House actually held formal sta… https://t.co/f8lrH5QGj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished and turned in my first draft of my senior thesis on @HamiltonMusical and let me tell you how accomp… https://t.co/6AkXPi4Gtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg What about a little scavenger hunt with photo clues during each city of #MixtapeTour to find a cd o… https://t.co/AxnFL1ixH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrong!!! Showmanship. Acting out!!! Foolishness!!! I could keep going. Dork!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShinsukeN Looks like I will only be watching the pre-show, again. I wish the company gave you a push for a title belt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traderjohnt1 @Nick_Clamorgan @TuckerCarlson This is what the democrats want for women!!! Thanks but no thanks🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why I thought I could handle sriracha sauce.. I'm dizzy and sweatin in a public area, if you see me please mind ya own]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THESUGARDAD1 @carlaportillo10 Please help me pay my tuition 😭 https://t.co/OueJKS4ED7]]></document><document><![CDATA[will never understand what goes through a persons mind to smash in a window and steal a purse w my life in it.. people are the worst]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ValentinesDay well, I did get a free chocolate valentine from @scooters today with my order.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😻 Meow! 😻 Loved having @ImAphroditeRose at last week’s Meowdi Gras show! ❤️🔥🐈  #catbaret #burlesque #aphroditerose… https://t.co/mqAl1F57K1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black History Performance is just getting started!  https://t.co/CPldZ5U0ks]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Peachy has to leave MeWe to try to get attention on twitter, someone needs to step up their morning game.… https://t.co/4G39r65GzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[PJ’s outside the house?! Finally a new idea I can get behind 👌  @davidgourlay - Matching Star Wars PJs? 👨‍👩‍👧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well here we go again. 30minutes on the hamster wheel as well. #fitbodyguide #fit #fitnessmotivation #cheflife… https://t.co/P4uk68Qkl7]]></document></documents></author>