<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@VFL2013 @TrumpGirlStrong @Jamierodr14 @ReneeCarrollAZ @SandraTXAS @GaetaSusan @LVNancy @jojoh888 @DonnaWR8… https://t.co/AH1rEJxRJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markwahlberg I think it’s Awesome how you always makes sure your family comes first no matter what is going on. Th… https://t.co/3WeyUJOmY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aDyslexicdoG The wrestler who allowed his students to be molested by the team doctor. Stood by &amp; did nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @LeadtoFeed Challenge is a win-win for students, teachers, and the community!  Sign up for this free digital leadership curriculum. #PBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't _stay_awake.... Have a great night my babies.  I hope and pray for a follow from @norvina1 because makeup is… https://t.co/bIwIS5UaE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernardKerik @CRYAPHANK @realDonaldTrump @BillClinton @BarackObama SO TRUE !!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that you look at me the way I look at mozzarella sticks♥️💞☺️ #oldiebutgoodie #repost #tbt #mozzerellasticks… https://t.co/Lwro0aGF6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m at a point where if you wanna talk shit then keep it up boo, not effecting me anymore 😘✌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hereby demand that we the people get what we want and we want a chinchilla emoji.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX Why does he keep mentioning magic?  I think it’s @donnyosmond too, just was wondering.  He still h… https://t.co/GEOeZvsCkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still 😂 @NolteNC sheep skin scroll 😆Must read 👇  Nolte: Jonah Goldberg and Steve Hayes to Launch 'Trump-Skeptical'… https://t.co/kdcNscfWNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The woods are lovely, dark and deep - and have some ghostly beech trees #SundayFunday https://t.co/tnM7bdmhab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoucantfoolmeA @AOC @AyannaPressley @IlhanMN Fighting in those wars is irrelevant in this context.  Read Latin Ame… https://t.co/m6cpI52YDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly so sad that in this world today as a woman, life can be a constant state of fear and paranoia. it’s absolu… https://t.co/jjcPPc1o5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago Police: Actor Jussie Smollett officially a 'suspect' https://t.co/GIxed16OGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just completed Smarty Pants Mission by shopping with Mobee and you can too! Download it here: https://t.co/DvZYKWXpH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marner93 your the BEST 💙we are blessed to have you in @MapleLeafs land]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karyn_McCarty @hgeluso @MrSamWow @samscott025 Sorry I’m late. https://t.co/O1LRv3brNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Successful candidate will possess exceptional leadership and management skills. Must be able to multi-task and oper… https://t.co/iszvLoyZA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanSchachtel @DonaldJTrumpJr He's the 2nd hero to try to save us from Frump. Comey was the 1st. All we need to… https://t.co/t2roNhUjBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eating ramen makes me think of Ghibli food, which makes me think about Howl’s Moving Castle, which makes me feel all warm and fuzzy. 🍳🔥⭐️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have y'all ever woke up on a Sat morning and realize you still have PTSD from your mom waking you up to clean. Maaaan]]></document><document><![CDATA[seven lions is releasing a remix of sahara love by above and beyond and i am so fucking excited oh my god😭😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[just had the best vegan scone 😭 i need 12 more before i leave they’re SO bomb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trafficmanmatt @NYC_AlexLee @jbelmont @ChristinaStoffo @DjEmpressNyc @Eaco_M @JFrommAnnounces @boston_girl79… https://t.co/qq4HS4qKN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayatcontreras @ProgressDems @BernieSanders Keep the @SenSanders cooties away from me ! Russian free my whole life and it works for me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[pleaseeee tell me yall are preforming boot it up in rosarito this weekend @OHGEESY @fenix_flexin !!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait wait wait ✋🏾 #followme #videoshoot #denearose #model #toronto @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/SfwDC7o4GG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moral of the story: I’m mad at him for growing up but he’s the best kid in the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day #7 with the flu, the end is in sight. Food tastes good again....if only I could do a load of laundry without needing a nap afterwards]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeGrimala Do you think we will get an invite to the CBI this year?? I mean we beat a lot of real shit teams in t… https://t.co/I9JF4JjL6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spin and make a pattern. Using our knowledge of patterns as we create a variety of different pattern types. https://t.co/ZMf5YOxRJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vickyweaver7 @kelly_clarkson She CAN'T,she's a busy lady🤯That's why @kelly_clarkson said(during her Minute+a glass… https://t.co/LSGofvOtcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barbara is telling important truths. I’ve worked for and with people living with HIV since the 1980s to the 2019. A… https://t.co/9wGDOCfXub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fine. But if those hurt feelings aren’t channeled into educating himself about racism and then not acting racist, i… https://t.co/vv9uAWuALb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to run away with it, Thunder!! Let’s gooooooo! Big 2nd half! #ThunderUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mismanaged socialist New York City is edging toward financial disaster, experts warn: https://t.co/OnFQB3RH14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xochi91 You’re the best Galentine a girl could ask for 🥰 https://t.co/EmIQKd8mrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnitedMermaids  Girl Twitter be getting all the back stories. You know that look!!!! Lol  Hope @GIPHY is getting a… https://t.co/JxQnH1GIRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! 11 years ago today!!! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/BELvSGPGgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#elvisallstartribute my favorite song EVER. #Elvis68ComebackSpecial https://t.co/XzgE1zTjAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timandsid my all time favourite female athlete is Hailey Wickenieser. She respresented Canada on the world stage f… https://t.co/EwUKvEJLVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this relationship don’t work out, I’m literally done with em 💯💯💯💯💯💯💯. The only thing is I have faith in God that… https://t.co/SRQu3CXv1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@herloyalsons @FrSorinRamblers I really hope I get a Winning is Hard heart today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealjdj74 @Mckinnley0831 Those waters were the best 😂 You never knew how much plastic you would get when you opened one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Tomorrow is Valentine’s Day are you excited?   Liam: Yes because we are going to get TACOS!   I guess we are getting tacos tomorrow 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murphizle @cnwiersma @Wendys There's a loophole. You can still consume Taco Bell's food just as long as you don't… https://t.co/IXMZScelef]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love shopping in Cavenders of good ole San Antonio when the city folks started asking if I work there🤗 like no I’m from the boonies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here in America we’re building silly walls and bringing back eradicated childhood diseases. The stupid is getting t… https://t.co/L3hvuk7EsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very scientific and politically accurate. @littletvis make sure you vote in these. America depends on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SotehPR @PhilliesMike @tjco1006 @KenCageRepo @HappyAndFreex13 @jonmorosi @Lakers @MLB @MLBNetwork @Bharper3407… https://t.co/KACq1FvUaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pass @NYHealthAct . And send your "I wasted-a-day-on-hold" stories to @nytimes and tell them to publish a counter-v… https://t.co/4CxjX5Y6I0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain Infanticide is already illegal. Please familiarize yourself with the law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @ChuckGrassley Check his grade school transcripts, parking tickets, there's got to be something!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost denverartmuseum erikaharrsch Very happy and moved by my dear friend and amazing artist's exhibition erikaha… https://t.co/CI4VGjvRr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ppl who don’t know you are so quick to talk about you lol like you don’t know my life honey]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC was picked from a literal “casting call” to play a part!!!  For REAL 🤣🤣🤮😤🤬🤬🤬‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[My math professor: "Did I mention I love putting story problems on the Exams?" The whole class collectively: "Fuck."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen Gave Prosecutors New Information on the Trump Family Business https://t.co/h9WdjPuI7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[ThorSport Farm is the host location for this years Horse Owners’ Workshop! Look forward to seeing you all there! https://t.co/DzwxBYf9MH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovTimWalz Thank you for supporting special education! #OneMinnesota https://t.co/SGM1x9JN8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's not true now? That's cruel 🤬🤬 wtf did he do... That's fucking bullshit... I cannot find words for it 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackRussellBro1 @medmonds29_ed Wow! She's even better than I realized! You are both so lucky to have such a true friendship!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caruso_BPMS Our teachers have so much knowledge - we need to provide them forums to share often. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite question of the event:   “Why is the impetus always on workers or jobseekers to invest in the future of wo… https://t.co/rDBL3DoBhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Handymen came to do touch-ups before we move out. Lovely husband-wife duo who have 4 grown boys. These are the peop… https://t.co/lGIDGUbIzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe this national emergency is treated with such passivity. People should be screaming from their rooftop… https://t.co/ROZfMopGkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music and Lyrics is on Netflix and I’m watching strictly for Pop! Goes My Heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[I personally felt it was disgraceful, and he needs to apologize, but I won't hold my breath. He was basically tryin… https://t.co/mg1d14Osfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[mans in my lab kept looking over at me so i let him copy my work cause he was cute,,,,but did he deserve it? absolu… https://t.co/38i9qoAII0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drolland @mapintar @mcampbellSD Haven’t seen either of those. Will see Can You Ever Forgive Me soon, I hope. Love… https://t.co/2RV5WKRdZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman This would have been so nicer if this idiot didn’t say...F...k Israel  Or F—K the dodgers directly… https://t.co/ARoku5Qlf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__JustLeena Hahahha yess the end !  &amp; we out here! Lol tryna make sumn shake!]]></document><document><![CDATA[how Dare iris apatow post a notting hill scene on ig n turn off the comments omfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 6'5" I barely noticed @Cooper4SAE on the Hill.... Now I am looking up at him and his wise comments...… https://t.co/3jYDdv7y0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[truffle shuffle french toast only at @MeemomsKitchen 😘❤ @ Meemom's Wall Township https://t.co/LmW1MxrHQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my sexy on...YEAH! 🙌🏼🙌🏼 @jtimberlake in #vegas #manofthewoodstour #livenation @ T-Mobile Arena https://t.co/hcqHH1Wrdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brockaletti @Scandianvia @JBOpi1 @shaunking @BernieSanders Conspiracy theory? Lol. Fuck off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Usd 312 Education Foundation dinner.  Always a good time and food for a good cause. @ Sand Hills Event Center https://t.co/LaR0MJsdhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump is this that MAGA thing you have been focused on? #SAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these fake or so called pastors in Africa, wonder why we still suffering.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smerconish @FoxNews has fed us @realDonaldTrump lies for 2 years now; sometimes they originate the lie; they are n… https://t.co/74sRledI8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is perspective and context. I don’t think anyone in New York is bragging about losing the Amazon HQ. May… https://t.co/4N5Pc3kBJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dizem que viajar é trocar a roupa da alma, então tô voltando com um look completamente novo! Quanta coisa podemos v… https://t.co/VHwHcP1eUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aravosis Check out their reaction to Joe Biden's speech. Applause when he says America will be back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caranotkara More listeners than you know. Don’t give up and keep talking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PARA SER BUENOS #PADRES Para ser buenos padres no es necesario justificar todo lo que hacen y dicen tus hijos, y no… https://t.co/xZ22ZsPzIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hikeii @mineifiwildout Dude his legs are too big. Maybe he is doing body building comp or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our teachers are the best! The Winston families had an amazing time at Literacy/Math Night!!! I just love my team!… https://t.co/gdGkJjFZRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s “National Love Your Pet Day!” I sure love these two pretty girls!  #GracieTesla #MaggieMarconi #proudcatlady… https://t.co/0eFN0citj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 With trump saying some members of Congress “hate America” and the free press is the enemy of the peop… https://t.co/m1uCkGAu2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@majosefl Pensé primero que era una hermana de tu hijo pero recordé que el debe ser el mayor, luego pensé que era l… https://t.co/okuPLVQgrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJerryNadler You mean to say you are going to continue to "investigate" further because Mueller seemingly has fo… https://t.co/hGzMIeNzeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cleaned the house, washed the floors, walked around target, did laundry, and went for a walk... let’s see if that w… https://t.co/2m1F29ygSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ken33Peterson My office got a call asking if we wanted to advertise in their phone book and I honestly didnt know they still made them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[whoever taught my mom the proper way to use these emojis is out of line 😂😂 https://t.co/P78LrwRKPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Squad on a Monday. On your radio 6-10 am @hot937  and @radiodotcom #MorningCrew #squadgoals❤️… https://t.co/GnbyNX6QiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took the dogs to the dog park today and there were only german shepherds and huskies there 🥰 it was basically my heaven]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Old Saybrook, Connecticut https://t.co/cSOgqCXyxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pixxydoodle @NASCAR @MartinsvilleSwy @bradk2fan @Team_Penske That is so cool. I have never been to a nascar race or Indy car. Just NHRA..]]></document></documents></author>