<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@kerriclaireneil there's no doubt that there was a market.... but it disappeared very early on.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[The near future will continue to reveal that Donald Trump is a truly evil person. A modern day Machiavelli who beli… https://t.co/Bc6rekGvHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorDScott @DonaldJTrumpJr He let you back there to pose, not for anything important]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MimiImfurst I really thought @TheGingerMinj was gonna take it home. Don’t even get me started on that bullshit. So… https://t.co/nOnA6Hff3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @AndreBraugher I have been a fan of yours since HLOTS and thanks to adult acne and the lure of the bass guitar… https://t.co/5zvVSOOHYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobmaxon Was going to say I remember countless times as a kid blown forecasts beyond belief - usually under predic… https://t.co/Vh148vP9zm]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s so much of my story that I haven’t talked about... In this video, I was a high school dropout, a homeless t… https://t.co/IBEOhFAmyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenbenthehen @agleader Water is flowing, Rivers in the sky so high, Ducks are happy now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChickfilA I’m at your location on W University Ln in Denton, Tx and your service was horrible. I’ve waited 45 minu… https://t.co/hg8rZBYNhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m captioning this for 300 dollar of rich ass Tai Lopez motiving asss🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAO GRILL LUNCH!!! #waogrill #nosomosunrestaurantemas @ Wao Grill https://t.co/iMGqQYWjCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more I spend my Sunday morning on social media, the more I realize I should be living in a small town in New Ze… https://t.co/1hvhNogYPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Galliano and the sunset. #beardporn #beard #muscle #musclecouple #swole #swolemates #tattoo #beardandmuscles… https://t.co/szrRdvLoRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just learned there's a real director/producer named Jon Turteltaub, which explains Lenny Turteltaub's name. https://t.co/N6nRGuGp6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Maple Leaf Section, Toronto Scottish Regiment, 1939. Includes Turk Broda, Hap Day, and Syl Apps among others.… https://t.co/bqNvz9Y8Hp]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he'd been in my face beating that drum I'd throat punch him n I'm mostly Indian heritage black foot hills of Can… https://t.co/iyivk0zwJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna say that, even though we rarely see it, I love that my Youk jersey has new life as Alex Cora's jersey. #20 #redsox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revrrlewis Please tell me these two are playing Fox they can’t be this stupid. In a year from now they’ll let us in on the joke right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza You’re a lying piece of shit just trying to cover up your own crimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_NSR @MLB Yup. They are not our parents generation that will forgive and forget. @MLB_PLAYERS they don't care… https://t.co/EJhZWsmWrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorldWideWob Chris Webber just commended Austin Rivers for clamping up Lebron when he tried to sauce him up. Refer… https://t.co/qSg9xna43W]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE MADE IT! #OverwatchLeague  This is my... eager face. https://t.co/iOuop766U0]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is sausage and Mac and cheese.  Shhhhhh.  I am on vacation! @ 3 Brasseurs Canada https://t.co/iW3Gt9wujn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woah woah woah woah. Two NC special elections, and TWO Marines!  Go get ‘em @bewforcongress &amp; @McCreadyForNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@somecloudguy @kapilvt @clare_liguori “We’re clearly the smartest people in the room” is a Google trait, not an Amazonian one. Dive deeper!]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMEN🙏❤ GRACIAS #SANTISIMO #DIOS #PADRE #JESUS🙏❤ BENDICENOS SIEMPRE TODA LA GLORIA A #DIOS #SANTISIMO #PADRE #JESUS🙏… https://t.co/miKvaAUO1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shortman5427 @businessinsider @realDonaldTrFan should be building a US-led Coalition with Vietnam, the Phillipines… https://t.co/0fafMrShh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonAnthony7 @KingPeachDP @chance4gardener @lynn_maryellen @TaggartRehnn @MynameisMok @kaysintBB @woodywood1999… https://t.co/2uFVun6weu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering what made Smollett come up with this asinine and clearly ridiculous idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Satan’s greatest weapon is man’s ignorance of the Word of God.” - A. W. Tozer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huggins’ outfit today might be the worst look in all of college basketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[“when I heard there was going to be a roast in my honor, my first thought was, ‘sounds delicious’...”  @ danny gare… https://t.co/2lEKkDAe03]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @HopeEmpowering •  •  •  •  • The revmikematthews has some harsh words for people who use the Gospel to off… https://t.co/qnST98sixs]]></document><document><![CDATA[A day at the zoo would not be complete without Roman Candy!!  . . .#spellphoto #ishootlouisiana #explorelouisiana… https://t.co/qgKl4oXi2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBethPhoenix and @NatbyNature gonna teach u girls some respect. RESPECT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bungarsargon Excellent. Thanks for writing and posting. Good ammo to demythologize the Democrats running for POTUS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sidenote: I think Cassius Winston is the best point guard in the nation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to be rude or anything....... but LAX is the worst airport I’ve ever been in and needs to step up it’s game]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between locations at Raleigh and Charlotte airports, we won 3 awards! Thank you to all who voted! #JrNation always… https://t.co/NGYbscRJBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can anybody be nominated for the Nobel Peace prize who drops bombs on civilians and shouldn't past presidents a… https://t.co/5AEgZk86er]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReeyahSDasoriya Now I can say that I have a new Senior Software Engineer in my network! Congrats @ReeyahSDasoriya !!! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dontshutusupp @KeyserSosse German people better wise up before it's too late, you are losing your culture and dest… https://t.co/0xjgMLhYv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[La sociedad tiene un ego bien frágil, dejen de darle importancia a lo que importancia no merece. Enfóquense en sus… https://t.co/Q4tR6CLVtx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quasarcoach Tim... Tim... Tim. I learned all my negativity from the master. #getoffmylawn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLeforce @village_terrier 10 more days until we can all pull against each other again. And then when we win, ETS… https://t.co/tXRjcHpeVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boss asked if we wanted to start working saturdays and I’m ready to quit lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport - @atlairport in Atlanta, GA https://t.co/kygvoPyVx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Love072110 @thomaskaine5 Thanks😢 I keep raising awareness for others still trapped in the dark.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinamash The big difference is that Obama overreach was for personal gain for himself and the Obama Mafia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marco Fabián vs Michael Bradley, the rivalry @MLS was missing 🙏#DOOP⁠ ⁠ #TFCLIVE⁠ ⁠ #PHIvTOR #MLSisBack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_M_Roth @paytonchung @balcom_holly The data is clearly bad. Which is frustrating because it undermines the argume… https://t.co/23izHA9L4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slow on I-81 in @Syracuse1848 right now.  Cars reported off roadways all over Central New York.  @MikeBrookins lead… https://t.co/I2MIcm6ZKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't see how people can make a list of the top 5 breakfast cereals without including Count Chocula.....people show him no respect]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who notice social media is getting worse over time should have a more Augustinian view of man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Liga MX was on ESPN+ I think I'd watch drastically more Mexican soccer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sin is . . .   earth's great burden,    humanity's deforming blot,   the enemy of God,    the transgressor of His l… https://t.co/nCXsFzDceC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coreyrab https://t.co/yU2GVZ5ve0? Since people can repost their articles there with a canonical back to their orig… https://t.co/17HNTT7WyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliviaMesser A requirement to be a reporter for @BuzzFeedNews is to fail a lie detector test. #FakeNews #Joke… https://t.co/Kdbe7YTNf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olgch gives us a serious deep dive into the challenges we need to overcome in an Enterprise Kubernetes world at… https://t.co/fL2OGKCfkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other munching still sleeping praise break thank god https://t.co/hXcfh1ccNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @TomSteyer Everything you wrote after the forst sentence is wrong. You spent too much time wrestling an… https://t.co/npUsBxjZKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you go for almost 2 days with no sleep...thank goodness I have friends that take care of me! rj_dunn_1k #tired… https://t.co/QQjOX28OOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adult.’s Life Kills: To take a synesthesiac approach, the music of Detroit electropunk duo Adult. might be describe… https://t.co/ksQSU4pVB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Consider Yourself Hugged by @Prairieales at @shakentaake — https://t.co/WrdyU47A8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottHecht33 @PGATOUR How about also getting into the modern era and let them use lasers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls like to fuck with yo conscience girls hate when niggas go missing and shawty you ain’t no different]]></document><document><![CDATA[This shot certainly turned into something that I didn’t see as I went through the camera RAW / DNG files on my lapt… https://t.co/yFvpAUeQ7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok after popular demand here’s the track list of Luke’s tape of not tough guy songs and it fucking rules. https://t.co/GlCdYr66xC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing I were at @sydneymardigras right about now with @DavidFrancis19 💃🏽🏳️‍🌈🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[And Adam Schiff, Swalwell, Cohen, Green, Jackson Lee, Susan Rice, HRC, Barry, Kerry, wow just getting started and r… https://t.co/5tET2kdSsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cowboys_2398 @jhanale Knowing your ass lol. Can never hear the song in the car without hearing you over the top of it. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broker Open House today 12-2 w/ lunch from Local Foods. @ Neno https://t.co/70C1KC3bxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JalterJay @cvp_theproblem It's just " Whack Mother Fuckers don't understand it! I get it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qanon76 @realDonaldTrump @nytimes America pays for Europe's cheap drug prices. How about Democrats. Let work on th… https://t.co/j98ImORlVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b1k3man_773 @777089965g @DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/2O8P4BrvfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardTBurnett @my3monkees YOU ARE REFERING to our president as such.. If he did not have someone " of color " co… https://t.co/AaHErFVsQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto I'm putting in jail that time a game cannot happen every act have consequences now he got to sucker up like a man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We goin sailing...NOT! LOL just there for the views! 😂  #morrobay #morrorock #bay #california #adventure… https://t.co/nMI7AkQaBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ National Museum of American History https://t.co/0BouVjkL9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Professional Footbal in #Utah @aafstallions details on #KSLTV https://t.co/h1t7YgtRMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pharmacists are amazing! Full Transparency: I may have a vested interest! ;-) @SoniaMota16]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph ---. Barometer 29.948 in, Falling Rapidly. Temperature 55.0 °F. Rain today 0.09 in. Humidity 97%]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BrunoMars @brunomars #24Carat #Magic #24CaratMagic  WORLD TOUR SPONSORSHIP AND INVESTORS OPPORTUNITIES FOR SPORTS… https://t.co/0RM7rBaPuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CDNPoli #ONPoli Yet .@OntarioPCParty cozied up to them without condemning those among them who made such threats.… https://t.co/N24JSuEezG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FCCdaytonGirl @Hangar937 @PBrennanENQ @thedaytonbeerco I'm still recovering myself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Teapot Dome Gas Station National Historic Site in Zillah, WA https://t.co/bLkGBbVISc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where did she get her training in being used as a pro? Seriously, how did she allow herself to be used this way?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting the #Prius C side by side with the @Kia #Niro and @mitsucars @iMitsubishi shows what real #FuelEconomy look… https://t.co/KwnK3PMcQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartenRobert @mendenhall_em @WHO Yes! Not sure when exactly but I’ll be in and out of Bihar a few times over the n… https://t.co/GslSHnsYaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynnShawProd @GMA @ABCNetwork Yeah @JussieSmollett is trying to get ahead of this. No 1 should give interviews unt… https://t.co/laC9YLx0bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is like that scene is ballers with the mother instead of the wife. Either way not good]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥The Denver Community Group: February Meeting was SUPER!  Big thank you to @SFDCDenver #TroLeaders and @melfellay f… https://t.co/DCdOX6DL3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cada día es una nueva oportunidad para vestirnos con nuestra mejor actitud!  Arturo Javier Duarte-Rodriguez]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s trash about her? 😂 Her Grammy nominations? Her winning a grammy? Her making millions of dollars? And selling… https://t.co/M6g8BZcvDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realmadrid @Benzema @AFCAjax VERGONZOSO LO QUE OCURRE ANTE EL FARSA, RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetrosiehotwi @hotwife @Slutwife @BBC @sharedwife @milf Let me know when]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VJlqnthygi    #Redvelvetで妄想    @REDVELVETnow https://t.co/t07WZvJzEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeanMisterGreen @davemeltzerWON He sure as hell won a lot of respect. That was an amazing performance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MotoGP #QatarGP combined FP1/FP2 lap times: #MM93 1:53.380, 0.474 clear of #MV12, only #Honda in top 10 All three… https://t.co/cn9wWBZnwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you #OklahomaCity for your love and support this past weekend. I had a blast performing for you, and I can’t… https://t.co/5kN9zIsHHX]]></document></documents></author>