<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hmmm @PressSec “Lock Her Up? “ “Maybe some 2nd amendment folks can take care of her?” “Very fine people on both sid… https://t.co/UHM0ZtGyBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rrbc #rwisa #bookboost #kindlebooks #circleofbooks #bookreviews  A nice warm week expected. Going somewhere? Here'… https://t.co/bhfug7ZFyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Feminist are only for other women when it fits their agenda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp In many, it’s how they see America as well. Loving the country goes against  some agendas and they can’t un… https://t.co/hiQkgyanjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[long distance requires a simple thing called effort. if you want to see your significant other, you will make the t… https://t.co/xVa26LknQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[BELIEVE IN YOURSELF AND ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE💋🕊🍃 #believeinyourself💋 #believeinyourselfalways💪#betruetoyou💯… https://t.co/m7MTcKbw2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day has never been so special. Thank you @carliejoprints for thinking of me😍👯 https://t.co/rKhTrxBRvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such beautiful company ❤️😊#fashionweek #harlemfashionweek #harlemfashionrow #bts #model #newyork #nyfashionweek https://t.co/ckuzFYfosG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queerfeminist @UMP45BAudrey @mcashmanCBE Tell me, if you dont engage the person in a way they understand, do you r… https://t.co/6yBHKYAghT]]></document><document><![CDATA[HA!!!  This. Is. Awesome!!! @RBlotske @SteveYagla @YaglaDan @DanProft @Holli_Rox  @the_amish_txtr… https://t.co/cWzksuBg32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Given that I would listen to Richard Dormer read a telephone book I am all in on this. https://t.co/G7VBCDx79t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar I bought 4 more towels this week and I totally thank you for that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now this is the cutest thing I’ve seen in my entire life 😍 look at his little tongueeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VSquad23 @BTS_twt Chicago...Floor sears right in front of the extended stage!!! I recommend saving time by choosin… https://t.co/1M1cFAZ94V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bits and pieces of the messy little life I love. @ Fair Oaks, California https://t.co/Xa1Ji2yPeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a couple different views on my daughters hair. #wandedhair #balayage #bronde #richness #dimensionalblonde… https://t.co/Z1DbdJfGJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Color corrector and free flowing layered cut. Before pic done elsewhere. 💁🏼‍♀️💗 . . . . . . #swipe #highlights… https://t.co/M9bY62tO0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 Running is not a walk in the park, it is demanding, expensive and I would NEVER VOTE FOR TRUMP and I… https://t.co/VVrcaiNID6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is interesting.  #WGAAwards winner.  I was the kid voted quietest in middle school.  Then in high school i had… https://t.co/Rx3tJNAaIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elijah kept feeling all on my scalp talking about he can’t believe this all my hair. Lmao I told him cause he used… https://t.co/A5TB99Rqcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact he felt the need to photoshop the already teeny tiny girl in the back is the most psycho part of this whole ordeal]]></document><document><![CDATA[WeHo GayBook: Saturday 3/2 – Brunch Service, , Cowboy-a-GoGo @ThisIsWeHo https://t.co/xSyxlT8xKs https://t.co/wUOCBdmQGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruinDre33 He did. He got mad when Prissy,Mammy and Benson weren't there to serve the invited guests the cold KFC… https://t.co/Z8YsTS0z4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how many glasses of wine I can down at the nail salon before they cut me off. 😂 I’m tryna leave with a hard buzz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been 2 years too long...SEE YOU ON SATURDAY BABIESSSSS @CHERUBlamusica 🍓💕 https://t.co/icotpmtoLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliverMcGee @TheAcademy @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse WOW that was great and that was everything in a nut sh… https://t.co/Rc6SaVhOjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hathcockroyce @F3Sasquatch @cmarshall570 @F3Raleigh @tylerDgrimes @F3TXPete @f3krabs @Sprague_Law @SamSregister… https://t.co/003Y9pPzoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta If a journalist is caught in one lie his credibility is gone. That is why fake news is so horrible. Rarely a… https://t.co/p8PTzhVjFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaharaReporters @adeyanjudeji @inecnigeria @MBuhari Nigeria knows ATIKU IS THE PEOPLES CHOICE!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[152 weight class WINNER - #WestmontHilltop @WestySports Hudson Holbay in a last second decision 6-4 over… https://t.co/lBg38eFh5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[My spiritual advisor reminded me of the night a stranger brought me a bowl of bison stew when I was hungry and alon… https://t.co/EJczVp5t6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would not miss celebrating this guy! Happy 50th birthday 🎂 Darren Carson. Friends 21 years and counting ♥️♥️♥️ @… https://t.co/BfjVnVVYTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scrappiedoodle @FunMoneyMom @Janellcp @MomItForward What a great idea! #Avocadoland #gno #ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grab and Go items as well as Chef Specials available today! @ttaymillek #plantbased #vegan #shepherdspie… https://t.co/vY0NZrF5bO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Copperhead Pale Ale by @FreeStateBeer at @yardhouse — https://t.co/Jr1SkFTA7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Props to celebrities who give photo credit. Don't forget to give credit to the artist / photographer. They deserve… https://t.co/uiesnUOVXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unintended consequences... a laundry list created by government interventionism over the years]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePrimalMan I get the issues with “Big Pharma” but your philosophy is the same. If the secret is just diet and ex… https://t.co/8xhuoQIOdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamKraemerTV @KOAA How can this be? I mean they must not have done a thorough look. Shoddy work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mejor nada más digan que es un cambio/aumento y ya! #att #mexico https://t.co/Tdzoq2DhXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen 😀 here’s Nina in the grass on a leash https://t.co/rOxkuNNLPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that they're declaring victory over US Gov. Proves they were trying for a take over and that means THEY ar… https://t.co/DeuWj4JNTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotACastASOIAF To be with a fire wight/man, I’m gonna say it would work as long as your dick wasnt hurt before you… https://t.co/7iEagXrIeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a pretty incredible historical document.  Will be thinking on this hard today.  A lot to unpack.  I think h… https://t.co/R9z6JVjsru]]></document><document><![CDATA[It may still be winter, but these ‘sweet’ daisies were blooming for the teachers and staff at Redeemer Classical Ch… https://t.co/T7hPRoLsfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kneale_88 @InfernoSons @EWUFootball @EagNationAth @EWUAthletics @CoachBestEWU @HEROSportsFCS We know you bleed that green and yellow✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJusticeDept enforce the law.  Do your jobs!! #indictHillary open #FastNFurious #indictHolder]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wander_beauty nude illusion liquid foundation is such a glowing, beautiful finish. Love it 😍 https://t.co/Owr8RVqI74]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY TOP 6 INSTAGRAM PIC LOCATIONS in BYRON BAY   https://t.co/uLBGn5XQQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bopinion True. It doesn't show party unity. Does each candidate have a DIFFERENT platform? If so, that is not exac… https://t.co/Kws9oXW1o7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#maniegrace #fashion #extra #instakids @ Memphis, Tennessee https://t.co/PeBEwulL1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[we made quite a mess babe and it's probably better off this way and i confess babe in my dreams you're touching my… https://t.co/zHzGhkEEgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amahnke @MostSavageQueen @AshleyPetroske @WineandCrimePod @fakemikeboudet @LucyFitz46 https://t.co/wvcEw0Pz1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan And Eric trump liked your tweet.  Nuff said. Like having hitler applaud your efforts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYRangers why did you trade @zuccarello36 why why why. Now you have a nothing team. Are @KevinPHayes12 and Kreisle… https://t.co/KVxzaXakaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[People will want you to do things for them just to leave you behind at the end of the day people only care about themselves]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith @JasonMewes @LegionMOfficial These two handsome and creative cosplayers need to be in the bad-ass r… https://t.co/MXrqxHWjjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knew I would love snowmobiling so much!?! Can’t wait to go again. @VisitUtah #snowmobile #Utah https://t.co/MZ3s7nEH3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SaturdayNight at the #theatre 🎭 #squad #family #friends #love #Hamilton #nyc #Broadway #musical #musicaltheatre… https://t.co/bhd9l7IhUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also yes someone filmed me for that gif, that is what I look like when I make internet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NanaTamara21 We all hope you get your birthday wish.  Happy Birthday !! 🎂🎂🎂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance Makes sense.  His rantings show he feels the walls closing in on him.  He already knows this isn’t… https://t.co/OMCU65sNtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait if lockheed martin is making paint that makes a plane undetectable by radar and only costs like $50k per fligh… https://t.co/kZ3ApSA89H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski Yes you should, don’t give that trumper a thought or a retweet. Her statement is for attention. Don’t fall for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like I missed a fantastic game by the @GoldenKnights last night. I’m in Columbus and was in bed over an hour… https://t.co/MMkDWgb3wX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dicklawfirm Oh, how I wish there was a thumbs-down button on @Twitter! I keep asking; they either don't read it or… https://t.co/ur3kxnLFP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking the halls of the capitol today with @melindalittle and look what we found! Guess who was one of the mascots… https://t.co/XyCGeuFLRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This one particular vendor gets on my nerves, I just walked away while she was talking to me. She’s probably still talking to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamhauckIII Sounds like something a loser with a peanut allergy would say]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fun parallette core challenge!  This one is more difficult than it looks. You may feel it in abs, hip flexors, qu… https://t.co/mLJpbfkr67]]></document><document><![CDATA[Initial observations of Tuscaloosa: everyone needs to re-take their driver’s test.   It’s like bumper cars out here. https://t.co/Iibaa3Ir0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone wanna help me with my clothes I don’t know how to style any clothes!!!!😂😂😂🤘🏻🤘🏻🤘🏻🤘🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻 @corbynbesson @bradytutton @InRealLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[I legit remember memorizing the choreography to this performance because I was infatuated with @ladygaga I was her… https://t.co/BDjowJeTPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @laterrazany ・・・ 🚨Latin Brunch Sundays Presents 💥Tomorrow Sunday 🍸21 and over 🍸 ⏰Brunch Time 12PM TO 5PM 🍽A… https://t.co/cXSj4gp7T4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @_omgigi_ !! one of my favorite people ever!! https://t.co/Tt3GL9HLUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems like some of them were jealous of Eric Braeden! Well jerk is gone now so Victor IS BACK!!!😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NYTF #NewYorkToyFair (@ Jacob K. Javits Convention Center - @javitscenter in New York, NY) https://t.co/ug1lZPDUGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[You all know I don’t wear black, especially to funerals but Simona asked for Miz Cracker season 10 finale realness… https://t.co/LsngLLej0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX19Joe Did the same with “45’s” back in the day. Felt like Casey Kasem flipping it over to find a hit!! Hidden #talent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JHCDESIGN @CycloneMBB @nickbabb12 @ChrisBabb52 I was thinking same thing!! It would be cool!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great poster for my March 23 program at the Chilicothe Public Library! #WomensHistoryMonth… https://t.co/Uy5eJOTtKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 years ago, while I was living in Dublin for the summer, Sal told me about this amazing singer. For 3 years I have… https://t.co/L2F0Qf7nVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The woman suddenly realized why she was so miserably hot every night, sweating through the sheets as she slept, and… https://t.co/qtLAv3rssN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I go to matts house tonight and he’s tryin to pick something on Netflix n this mans puts on an earth documentary an… https://t.co/TEQzN1wZHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I used to not be into Ariana Grande at all, but I’ve gotta admit I’m converted. I’m obsessed with this album rig… https://t.co/OB643ADXu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took my last drive on 280 today as a resident of Hell’s Highway. Def not going to miss that traffic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m not understanding why my father just can’t pay for my flight like tf he bms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abdelrdz_ @angelalvarez_45 Who wishes for snow other than Eskimos or Christmas Eve?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heather Keenan completed the Princess Fairy Tale Challenge! Time 01:37:06 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/E8xH2EUmXB #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this clever there's something wrong with you. https://t.co/bX1CLXBZSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MFOLDC has officially launched our newest campaign #LettersForChange to put pressure on the Senate to pass #S42.… https://t.co/6lMXpEovC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJGWrites @dbongino @realDonaldTrump Was a table shower involved and the happy ending or two?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Are all the drugs and human trafficking not an emergency Senator?  I am a fan but I sure don’t agree on t… https://t.co/s2tm4Pc3iw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been craving a large ice cold Hi-C orange who's bright idea at McDonald's was it to get rid of it🤔😤😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[People sit in the same seat all semester and then wanna switch it up on exam day?? https://t.co/fsq6eT48U2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sodasotta Yeah!! I was really impressed by it! And the bear scene was TERRIFYING but also that bear design with th… https://t.co/RAfOtPtDx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@therealjleyritz Thanks for the book Coach! I'm up to the part where you get traded back to @Yankees !  #TheKing… https://t.co/pNiUgF2MEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aw shit. He's sitting on the padded barstool. Now you know the Deep Rap is about to ensue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s How My Chemo-Moon Helped Prep Me for Treatment #ThoughtfulThursday #Charlotte #BreastCancer #LCIywbp… https://t.co/RKktUaQkaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patiently awaiting a statement from @the_ironsheik re #DaylightSavingsTime]]></document></documents></author>