<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I see we’ve already reached the point of Spring Training where people are already sweeping to conclusions about players...lol. “My god.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Think Like a Roman Emperor: The Stoic Philosophy of Marcus Aurelius https://t.co/ca8dcszEKX https://t.co/BGegVAWlAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @Toyota since you signed a deal with @SIRIUSXM and they bought @pandoramusic can we get the pandora app back in… https://t.co/OSrcrZayoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNWestPalm Is there a D) none of these. There are actually way better stories. Bell is gonna be the next Eddie L… https://t.co/sfTk41gEMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discipleship. This is what is all about. @madilynbouldin learning from @loveee_sarahhh #church #jesus @ Living Wate… https://t.co/Y85vgBe3v3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vacation is over... but I had soooo much FUN. If you’ve been trying to get a hold of me I’ll catch up with you tomo… https://t.co/I1LeeDDI0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chicago O'Hare International Airport in Chicago, IL https://t.co/zoHA5ViS70]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaintNickySaban @bmarshallwood @darrenrovell I’m sure he would be grateful for that]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the dangerous reality of hundreds upon THOUSANDS of women worldwide who currently are  battling #pelvicmesh… https://t.co/AQKjLacKHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh brother yall bout to have women on twitter tweeting about this all week]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s been 3 hours since they decided to tell us our flight was cancelled and now ever since we’ve been waiting on a cab to Long Island]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all don’t know how sick I am of school and going to classes. Dawg this shit not it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retweet if you’ve eaten McDonald’s    Favorite if you’ve NEVER eaten McDonald’s    Trying to prove a point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EclecticRadical I was bummed when it became clear he had no chance in the 2010 gubernatorial primary, even after h… https://t.co/6qXndiqZzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdutKevinAcee I was there and hour ago and I saw it as soon as I walked in. I almost took a photo. I actually boug… https://t.co/qWLChsCQ5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just awful basketball. UT will get blown out by LSU playing like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@KyleBusch wins his 52nd Truck Race passing the great @RonHornaday on being the winningest driver in… https://t.co/WKMAtzzChP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LATEPOST from Winter Beach Party!!! 🤩🥳😎 #winterpartyfestival #winterparty #wpf #beachparty #winterparty2019… https://t.co/UXjymfARLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rollbarann @MadelaneStander @Tmcguire_pa @ALLCAPSTWEETX @dianemariereid @CrusadeAtheist even with coffee...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damienleone @DavidHThornton @MadMonsterMag So awesome!!  I love this!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aplacecalledjer I’m sincerely thankful for having found your Twitter account. You are so kind and sincere, and car… https://t.co/ZqKhbYZyH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlswrestling soph. @BrettStanley30 (40-4) loses a heartbreaking 3-2 decision to Samuels of Hudsonville. Will wrest… https://t.co/3cUKzhCgvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought we could pull this one out it didn’t happen give MSU credit as they got it together and won the game. Tha… https://t.co/m3nOu6Wryt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveDuFourNBA I’m with you @DaveDuFourNBA, announced sellout?!? Clearly more open seats than taken. https://t.co/vqhtg6vXUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terrycrews The biggest problem is language I think, it’s really hard to translate an entire life’s experience and… https://t.co/B26CqW5G15]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @seanhannity I never got a Speeding Ticket from a Police Speed Trap because I didn’t Speed through it... Republ… https://t.co/CuQPkIKtim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytpolitics @ktbenner Gym Jordan is a clown and he is covering up a sex scandal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Yankees lineup vs. #Phillies - first pitch 1:05pm at @GMSField https://t.co/FT7GFvgFD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe tonight we’ll get some stars? @ Sutton, Quebec https://t.co/2miDAYSdSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re s knicks fan you’re a giants fan. Gotta be. Dumbest sports opinion there is is a New York sports fan lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s what @chesterlampkin is saying this morning... “A weak weather system is rolling through the bi-state today… https://t.co/KwMmTKCRVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[La pregunta ahora es, por qué se habrá molestado Maduro para retenerlos en el Palacio Miraflores???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love sleeping on ft with a female when she sleeps peacefully I sleep so peacefully 😩😍unless she sounds like two g… https://t.co/5XWrEdgN8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marie_skou @JAC1963 @GWA1973 So many equate “innocent until proven guilty” to not believing the victim. It does no… https://t.co/mPsBAmhbVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alice_Dairyland thanks Kaitlyn for the media training for the Wisconsin Farm Tech Days Team! Like you, we love to… https://t.co/Z5SqJveqvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why You Should Be Doing Unilateral Exercises @SparkPeople https://t.co/ELTcVH4gm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mindfulness is a path not a tool. #meditation #mindfulness #zen #personaldevelopment https://t.co/VyJVYzKpos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GwenJorgensen1 Nah. I’d use it for so-called “Christians” who appear to enjoy hovering around other Christians loo… https://t.co/WEqTRE8gjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@italiaricci I would pick your hubby over those guys any day of the week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByJerrySullivan The coaches aren’t the ones making bad passes and turning the puck over. Get ready for when they don’t re-sign Skinner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffSmithMO @T_N_B7 sounds like govt was going to make a $3B tax expenditure in exchange for $625M in infrastructu… https://t.co/WZbtyLYS2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chinese students should obviously be free to protest speakers they don't like. But providing names or videos to the… https://t.co/8OGhunOKMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngryBlackLady And A bag of https://t.co/I3WVg532ID never know when it's time to get lubricAted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ICC_00 The fact that ANYBODY has to put up with it in ANY situation sucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don't know if we'd get there," @CountyExecEvans said of a Guardian Building sale to Dan Gilbert’s… https://t.co/ruMdU5tNMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wemakemovies @WeMakeMovies #CHARLA by @CharleyFlyte with @krigone https://t.co/RypS33j1pX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t usually start my Thursday mornings with polls but when I do it’s with @jboxt1 #Reeds19 https://t.co/KT0oSEbYM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The problem for the Chiefs DL is it will need strong defenders on the edge in the run. IMO that’s why Dee Ford is o… https://t.co/ikFBDFnaSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@futrell_nic Well the beauty of the market is if no teams think he’s worth it he’ll have to eventually cave possibl… https://t.co/CewHfMAQoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJDrooghaag @CyberMindsChat @avrohomg @NevilleGaunt @KaiGrunwitz @mirko_ross @NeilCattermull @archonsec… https://t.co/ZRGgjnZQ1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where can I get Letterkenny while being a US citizen with an internet connection?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to an audition that I was ready to kill. Got out to do it and forgot it so so badly. It happens. That’s life,… https://t.co/9voEF6941r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm hooked on this shit. My to go IPA. @ Layton, Utah https://t.co/bLf0KRPjTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Libro 📚: Una Vida Sin Obstáculos  Autor: Erick Torres Disponible ya 😊😃💯👍🏻🇺🇸🇵🇷🇩🇴🇨🇴🇲🇽… https://t.co/NrReuI7CaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ImproveAMovieWithOneWord The Magnificent Seven Dwarfs https://t.co/6WqdfuRvXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If you can't take the heat, quite... #smallhands #smallmind #TrumpFakeEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got a decent job. I can get a place all by myself but rather have a roommate so I can save up also 🤨. Time to hit up some friends 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gordonrichy @8Abc88 @bryanmiller81 @FansOfKU I think last year... Vick was projected in the late second round, don… https://t.co/6hU15zjbas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @jdawsey1 Having a good laugh at the president honoring people's request to sign their Bibles I don'… https://t.co/BcO5uA7H5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justdawn_ @BeauGentryK9 @ava Was there a warning?  Do people have basements?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALBERTO_V8 @TravisJamesR92 @throwbackfuture @RealKKBundy Yeah people like Torrie Wilson .  What a disgrace to Bund… https://t.co/32fi4sM6iL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlSchlyter Det rimliga är att fastighetsavgift eller -skatt baseras på den köpeskilling som erlagts vid köp av f… https://t.co/awSr0FOdjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casa Maria packs hundreds of lunches a day and hands them out to people in need. Here’s a glimpse of what will air… https://t.co/QtZQTmc7lq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJ_2_FL @Sekusa1 @realDonaldTrump This bee-atch is insane as a shit- house rat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bilingual K coding in Scratch on Digital Learning Day at @LamarElementary! #iamwfisd #DLD19 https://t.co/mDLTagr49m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@summerasantos got so drunk that she told me she ‘lost her sandwich in the middle of the road’ and made me drive ar… https://t.co/h3RvX0QItK]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did I not know that either of these guys were coaching in the “Alliance”?  I am firmly against the Apollos and… https://t.co/32EFhduyd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know how you rednecks wear steel toe boots by choice my feet feel like shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skyy_L @JerusalemFury @StreetsAheadWV @shadowfuzz @ScottChalleen @AOC @DNC Maybe after all we are Capitalist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@98PXYRochester I met someone on this app and this person and I talked for a while, and we decided to meet out at a… https://t.co/ktNnid2KRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAFrench @TIME Good, we can yell at you when Jussie is named Time’s Person of the Year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Magical Juice by @18thStreetBrew at @18thstreetbrew — https://t.co/BqqWWThXpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLitrasx9 Really this drug addict asshole been arrested 4 times  has the balls to say anything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[• Apoyar al Presidente Duque por su decisión de objetar la Ley Estatutaria de la JEP. • Participar en HT que apoyen… https://t.co/nn8kFO2m3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaperKat @Montejp231 @Mandalorian_Ren @jeolmoz2 @LionCuban @Dubroq One can only hope we're wrong about #MarALardass......  🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these people saying they can’t believe the #colorado jogger killed a 40 pound #mountainlion kitten are the same… https://t.co/aC066DCf95]]></document><document><![CDATA[I send my sister snapchats of gluten free things, to let her know I’m thinking about her and she doesn’t even respond 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportsmediaLM As much as someone hollering out “this is MAGA country”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber This’ll be the 1st of many 2020 campaign lies by Fox News ?  Hell no !  Watch Judge Genine Pero - 100 li… https://t.co/KidaHK9QKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, winning #faceoffs is important! #SidneyCrosby 🐐 #Pens @penguins #LetsGoPens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schmeits06 @CmalryMallory @LukeMartinISU @SycamoreSID Yo we need these in hulman lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccothran985 Rigged up with 15lb fluorocarbon and a Gary Yamamoto 5” green pumpkin purple flake]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JustSayNo  #DontDoVegetables🚫🌽🍅🍆🥑🥒🥔🥕 #StayInDrugs👍🚬🌳💊💉  #EatYourSchool👅🏫 @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/XK2uIEuhjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobThePsychic1 @weaselzippers @FoxNews never provided any debate candidates with the questions prior to the event.… https://t.co/BYLtOST02X]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy let his friend's little girl paint and decorate his car. Pretty cool. @ Abbotsford, Wisconsin https://t.co/WvIjVvo2Qd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work was tough yesterday, even though the location took my attention from my troubles. I put my focus on doing my b… https://t.co/rRDlTwtcNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question:  Which duo would you rather have come to Leafs? #LeafsForever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Irish Potato Candy Stout by @flyingfishbrew @ A. Beach Designs — https://t.co/amClLaIiE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was the @ErikTarantino and @CHRISCARRILLO73 duo back in intermediate 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent job today. Especially pointing out that the judge was giving Manafort a pass simply because he was never… https://t.co/Ws7sf6za8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait...😂 Carlos boozer goes to tell Zion to get better soon and tags Zion National park. And even better they fucki… https://t.co/w1vma37XXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether due to laziness or arrogance, Abramson plagiarized. Clearly laid out by @mathewi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sether @LDEakman Suggest following @AnnieDuke if you do not already.  One of the most thorough and informed writer… https://t.co/ev7Fz4xpR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The period does not fall from the question mark.” —JRDjr    Beware of #entrepreneurs who declare definitive answer… https://t.co/aSKfvDG25l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I regret giving someone so much of me for them to just give up on me. That hurts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Porcupine project is sailing along ... Doug Oathout: A chance encounter with an Erie history project https://t.co/PuWr4e2DWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[In New York?? She very likely was Promoted and likely Runs the School by now!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you know it’s 4:20 and I can’t sleep. Maybe it has something to do with the fact I’ve been holding a phone… https://t.co/QG8N8Xv0Y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been a huge patriots fan since 2000 but this isn’t a good look for Robert Kraft as the details unfold. I’m her… https://t.co/IC1wOacNcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting #45… https://t.co/JfyS8igPnX]]></document></documents></author>