<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Sarahwaugh20 @hardhouz13 @L_a_w_a_n_n_a @Steelerschic85 @TeahCartel @TanziaMill @TalkToMeForReal @Suzyqfit4u… https://t.co/W4Utes6GMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The naming convention you give to smart home devices affects your experience with Google Home and Alexa. This artic… https://t.co/cfS1bcvpLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkbjournalist @itmediasentinel Alan Dershowitz is a child rapist just the same as Donald J. Thump and Jeffrey Epst… https://t.co/D6eY3VkzIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarrellShell @KyleZoomZumbach Too expensive, but I like their internet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobSaroya @NancyPrentice6 Fuck Canada. A shithole country controlled by shysters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerwhat16 @fordnation JC Penney is just USA as far as I know. The car companies are reacting to the changing bus… https://t.co/ykXCBYFKDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephanie Miller in the shower See this Instagram video by @stephaniemillershow https://t.co/UKlxhLq7Rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good reminder of what a great talent #JohnCandy was... Thanks for the post @Eric__Smith]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rperniaa @ReinaldoProfeta @NituPerez @garciabanchs @josegaroffalo Déjame decirte no se en otros lugares pero en Ne… https://t.co/VE9n13bNKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn't exciting at all. They just removed key functionality and made it more difficult to navigate. I'm all for… https://t.co/yVmVWb8OqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CYOSportsDOC Congrats Robert and Williams 5th grade CYO basketball team. They won all 3 tournaments that they play… https://t.co/DgpsmlwBtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The personality is infectious! Kinda reminds me of somebody else who loves coding and inspires newbies and used to… https://t.co/yETUIROlln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hogtrough Same size and height, 5’10 3/8. Murray is a bit heavier, bigger hands, faster and a stronger arm. Not to… https://t.co/mYr51iHr4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever experience anything as amazing as this? If you say yes you've either. 1) Rode on Unicorn through a ra… https://t.co/BVxKEk8VRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwcongdon Well, I think it is. And thus we reach an impasse. 😎 Blessings.  Out of curiosity, who would you list as… https://t.co/8o5Z7ljj1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreshWhittaker @mattgaetz @Prissytxn @RepRooney I would like to see a time chart on that factoid. Probably a lag b… https://t.co/14lj3xZsbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great day at the columbuspetexpo2019 doing what we do best.  We had a blast. #herculeslives #shortysrescue… https://t.co/AGos2HxPp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Já que a @ladygaga ganhou o Oscar meu #tbt é pra ti mulher! Joanne Trattoria é o restaurante dos pais da Gaga e tiv… https://t.co/MoFXi7cwb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson facial expressions is entire mood during this whole testimony 🤣🤣🤣 #CohenTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[May we shine:  "In the nighttime of this world, so full of dark temptation,  what would become of us without the La… https://t.co/4pTJHvYUY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisAbbott21 I think we should all follow Cinnamon’s lead on this one… #backtobed https://t.co/1WZT2oaKME]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish my wife would wake me up like that, I’d straight karate chop her ass in the throat for blowing all that morn… https://t.co/1Nz9i6jRlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If people are really gonna ban wobbling from melee then they need to ban shine spiking and meteors too.  What is th… https://t.co/KUhzNTMSOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dapper #suave #classy #fresh #grownman #fashion #menswear #debonair https://t.co/zpZtYhaSB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jack_Burkman jackie-i think youre just upset because she's  COMING AFTER YOUR HAMBURGERS !!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reason people seek asylum is because they are not safe in their own countries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaPaz @AOC No man that's the thing, Honesty is the new Greed! It's all the rate now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xvviel_ made binge watching it way worse. now gotta wait for a season 2, if there is one...]]></document><document><![CDATA[ESTO ES LO QUE SABEMOS HACER😁😍🤗😁 #VivaMéxico preparando un gran concierto😉🇲🇽🤠🤗 #JavierAguilar #Mariachi… https://t.co/oMRBPJXY8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnpfinch @EncouragingDads @thefathereffect 💯 Love you bud. Have fun in Baton Rouge with the family this week ~]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JannaKilimnik @DadFiction @MommedRealHard @jaxwax04 @Beagz @KristinaNadia @TwinzerDad @MelissaBeagley @sah_bsn_rn… https://t.co/n6NCjrhaTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go-  what could smart people do? C- have an above 80 iq club.  Share ideas and find a common voice.  I see other gr… https://t.co/O5og4Wpn2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Based on my viewing of MSNBC, all day every day, I often feel like I’m the only American who wasn’t an Assistant U.… https://t.co/G6PXjADd59]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saying. I like them big, but I also like them chunky. https://t.co/1ofnxHjOls]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way @SpaceX Dragon main chutes deploy in stages is super cool to watch. I love clever engineering.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @ThePassageFOX is dipping into #bournemovies a bit as well with a mix of #TheLastOfUs more pots of lose securit… https://t.co/qps3IB8WMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HRHPrinceFrank Would you rather hang out with me or rewatch those videos?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practice gratitude everyday. You may not believe you have much to be thankful for, but if you think hard you will f… https://t.co/fQ0cjPn66K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see @SteelArmy members today today at @highmarkstadium  between @RiverhoundsSC v. @TorontoFCII for… https://t.co/7kFu7jCkHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great essay.  Genre: 1st psych: Method A sucks, Method B solves A's probs. 2nd psych: Did you actually compare the… https://t.co/H01MmWLRYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump By the way, great job in getting nothing accomplished. The Art of the Deal was of no consequence at the summit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freebiesmom1 😎😎😎😎Left You  Message Reply soon. Migraines Pain full &amp; Scary]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/aT6RKosDRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders Screw all you little people, go to work, shut up and I will take good care if you... if you don't want… https://t.co/3q1vFAJSkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyAdragna This bill and the people who wrote it are flaccid climate cowards. Good list to use for who should… https://t.co/hLK0QrBHfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because your circumstances are hard doesn’t mean God’s purpose for you has changed. #ThereIsAPlan #ILoveYou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala Harris recently said on a radio interview that she "inhaled"! Question is what did she inhale given her method to the Senate!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanGreeneWDEL @DEgirlshoops @mlang68 @302Sports @DIAA_Delaware @StE_Athletics @ConradAthletics @PandasSports… https://t.co/8TUc970mNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day to my workout and life partner. I believe this is 32 years that she has been my valentine. We… https://t.co/WzUbPrbhT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday...   #Repost @DJMellaMayne (get_repost) ・・・ When your flight gets delayed and you're bored 🤣🔥 By… https://t.co/pRVmB3cHSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[As international womens' day closes... My Mom is an amazing woman. My wife is amazing. My four sisters are amazing.… https://t.co/Kn0HlKbVfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guy deserves every bit of success he gets. Couldn’t be happier for this man right here. #LightningAlum @Bromanzak]]></document><document><![CDATA[One last Birthday beer 🍺  #birthdayweekend #ottawa #beer #cheers #drinklocalbeer #drinklocalcraftbeer… https://t.co/yLNrrnyU34]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirtualMarketer @ElizStJohn @AuthorMBTosi @cselston @wbellauthor @Native_Shadows @CasamentoArrigo @CarolineMCook1… https://t.co/qVIIBwz3PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my day one brother make today great Mann. @BestDadof2019 https://t.co/KPmoh999zS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Autistic people should be sterilized” seems offensive to him, but it stays up as well. Autism is not a “protected… https://t.co/ZDL8rOa3Om]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t had this much fun on Twitter for a long time. If you’re interested in a funny exchange, read mine with an bootlicking Ohioan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCUWhiteTrash It was Gus making biscuits .. call.. I expect you been up reading the good book all night]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG, if @NancySkinnerCA manages to make daycare more affordable she will be a god.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every maple leafs jersey before the adidas ones look so plain and boring wow. The centennial ones are the only one exception]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was an honor to have Howard Nusbaum speak at the Welk Resorts 2019 Summit, and share his passion and vision of t… https://t.co/bQVKqBznPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kanye looks like he’s a catcher ready to throw out a runner stealing second]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesusWasARebel2 I should have worded that as I’m sorry for the behavior of some of his supporters for defending hi… https://t.co/vy6MLxakCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#msnbc #MichaelCohen It’s stunning to me that with the litany of scandals that erupted simultaneously surrounding D… https://t.co/rpHVpTWXt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLastRebel4 @jax_persists Russian nonsense. The stats show this just wasn’t the case. Stop perpetuating this lie… https://t.co/KovFHtEulq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FeitsBarstool In case you were wondering, this guy was most certainly NOT the Dark Knight. https://t.co/AzQ5Irq5RH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My safe place. I love music.  – ♫Do It Again by Andreas Varady, from #SoundHound https://t.co/ND3dDtUS1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[#airschmo redeye flights seem great when you book them #astheschmoflies @ San Jose International Airport (SJC) https://t.co/vxtXEHznZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrSmaashy321 @Alex451618 @bng2617 @henya_lise @AneSucre @castafiore31 @JoliePoupee50 @Marks5860 @Equita212… https://t.co/9U8q0mIRgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadJohnBrown @Statistar30 @debaptiste_john @BernieSanders I wrote this two years ago: https://t.co/sANd9KMV3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chainz_mega @realswagg410 @1YoungTakeoff Music is your life and you hated Last Rocket? You playing yourself bro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@KDOTHQ needs this tool in their revenue toolbox to move KS transportation system forward! #ksleg @AffinisCorp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antoniogm Easter is worse. When I worked in retail, we blended March and April together in our analyses. They have… https://t.co/wJT3D6zKad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former STM VP Marvin Rotrand says he is shocked to hear #stminfo backtrack on long-held claims of fuel economy gain… https://t.co/hlANHFu1tr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tdcanseco @SirPresidentty @susana_srz The southwest CC helps! Lol let me know if you need my referral code 😎@SouthwestAir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj Isn’t child care the reason we established families? If we want child care, we need to support families, n… https://t.co/cfgqVd69Ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Bday!  Model: @alyssajoycrane  Captured on: #sonya7iii Location: Venice, CA  . . . #sony #sonyartisan… https://t.co/BpOfzt7PuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Itopia Private Homes in St Petersburg, FL https://t.co/nKBvMkhMLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinceMcMahon can have Charlotte and Kevin Owens well take Becky and Kofi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a M-43 N.E. India Pale Ale  by @Oldnationbrew at @CometPubnLanes — https://t.co/rHVf19coDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me wiping the dog’s paws after they go outside on a rainy day: https://t.co/vQCzoSlJ7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a terrible video edit, because it cut the portion where Jack and his teammates stomped a mud hole in this s… https://t.co/9NfYJFeCCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Other than Call of Duty Gameplay, is there another game you guys want to see on my YouTube channel?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scaachi I read your thoughts on  #Oscars19 and, uh, bitter much? Next year, give your seat to someone who will app… https://t.co/NedQS1wBJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love seeing our @GarnerElem teachers share their passion for education.  Great job Anna! #FinestGreatestBest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gchastine @digmuzak @UltClassicRock Nope, if I want to hear the cd I’ll just save my money and stay home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My granddaughters (without permission).  I can’t help it. ❤️❤️ @ Lincoln Square, Chicago https://t.co/UUq0dx0KTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is a guy supposed to win his first match of league play when you give me this @CallofDuty @DavidVonderhaar… https://t.co/NW4uf5tPUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do active service members want more: a school for their children or a wall at the border? Join this live Dialo… https://t.co/rSwSj79B1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s my friends child 9 year old bday next week what should i get them  I don’t really know what kids are into  Out… https://t.co/gqoPYmEvZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustCallMe_Duce They do some sort of variation of a team celebration after most(if not all) wins at home. They’re… https://t.co/RzaBGcNUPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bakebomb That’s just an average company.   A great company enhances your growth/talents and rises you to levels yo… https://t.co/3EWYIVH3zW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFreeze7 always a special treat watching you do the weather specially in the week. Have a really great weekend :) #ABC7NY]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the last photo from that photoshoot. #doggiemodel #chipin #beautiful @ Denman Estate Park https://t.co/mSvX0fcsQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themojoguy @MercedesGlobal Well, if they genuinely want her to testify (big “if”) the PM/PMO can provide JWR with… https://t.co/QFlmubgaSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mnlauren @SpeakerPelosi Yes,can't stand the witch.She &amp; a lot of others,Dems &amp; Republicans,are ruining our country]]></document><document><![CDATA[I called it! The opening song! Skakedown!  Bob Seger is Da Man! Greatest concert....EVER!! @ Talking Stick Resort A… https://t.co/KR5AL2uZOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rund um seinen Geburtstag meidet sie Social-Media, weil Nutzer und Medien ständig zum Engagement auffordern. #SXSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattBarr_ @KBNFLScout I just read that Baltimore has their eye on Honey badger]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of Whopping Crane Watch 2019! We’re checking out the festival this morning and taking the boat to the crane f… https://t.co/CcQLsPRJ7L]]></document></documents></author>