<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[meu carro já deve me ver chegando e pensar “puta merda lá vem ela chorar aqui de novo”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Karma Kameleon Gastropub https://t.co/C6Mv7kJDSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_network @Writer_DG @SamHeughan @RikRankin I loved Graham Mctavish aka Dougal McKenzie!  He was my first love from Outlander.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh no Luc, go back &amp; get those beautiful flowers for her! 😀😀😀#LoveRomanceAndChocolate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to win this super protein-package prize from Nuzest! https://t.co/XVTXZ3w9X0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet RICO sounds good.   Probably very true, plus he never said "NO RICO!!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[After watching #Superstars on #WWENetwork never realized that Virgil’s “finisher” was a side russian leg sweep! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of The School Improvement Team! They are doing awesome things at DMS! @Miss_Sweetser]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s a good decision cutting someone off for good when as soon as it ends, they have so much negative and… https://t.co/6WkIZNjRlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sanchelli10 Don’t let it mess with you! I remember that arm behind the plate and your pitch calling got the better… https://t.co/4oeOIjE0Xi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two mysterious people live in my house.  "Somebody &amp; Nobody".  Somebody did it and... #laughter #snicker #grin… https://t.co/QVx5gpQOl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlfranz @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Name calling from the left as usual]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have I mentioned how much I love teaching!?? What a great day with some of the best 6-11 years olds in LA!! We lear… https://t.co/yDqfIKKSNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chacun d’entre nous est concerné...préserver notre santé est aussi important que préserver notre planète, a nous d’… https://t.co/DUXCLygiY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Court and Prosecutors office have evidence you engaged in a crime by paying Stormy Daniels. You ar… https://t.co/elf4s28YG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week was a busy time for our students and staff. Our first Annual March Madness Tournament took place after sc… https://t.co/wey5BmsxRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s exactly why you need a verify account. Scary to think some is impersonating you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic for once, I was able to take a decent selfie and not look like trash https://t.co/q23F80LuL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn! @cthagod you broke that little boy. He sounded like he wanted to cry 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalVulcano laughing is one of my absolute favorite things in the world 😂❤️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I even added my emergency @larabar bars &amp; truffles in case I’m on the go or under my deficit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great community partner opportunity on Chicago’s West Side. Due April 15]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMFG!!!!!! @jelseyyyy you thought it was over!!!! Yasssss i might watch AGAIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigStraw_real @UnlessPA @Talk503 @Iamfluid @CCL_ChesCoPA @ChesCoDems @BigMikeWalsh @annetteRmurray @justrighthomes… https://t.co/YcO0FMp6ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to go home. New York, you have been an adventure of exploration and fun. Thank you! I will be back! 🗽❤️… https://t.co/KLTivG7iXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“All I know is she doesn’t have terf bangs and she’s really sad” - @MrBitchin]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moment u ask ur self why u just smeared glitter all over ur self while ur rancid friend is just taking selfies: https://t.co/1L7MVS6cUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shamrocknshen With you I’m like “mom I’m five seconds away from losing it tell me you love me”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate working sundays 😩 but also I get too bored when I’m off on sundays. Where’s the happy medium]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whist pulling weeds today, my thoughts wandered to Benedict Arnold. Remember learning about him as the ultimate sin… https://t.co/FnzxJfycER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets We need to get the Clampetts out of the White House NOW.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVObsesssed 😂🤣😂 it has to be a good cast for me to even think about it. I quit watching fear a season or 2 ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HappyKittyShop5 I always get a random shiny when the event ends. This time it was budew lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 Months until “I Do”, Save Our Date 😍😚🥰 #SaveTheDate #GetReady #ThanksgivingEve #Round2WithTheRiveras 👰🏻💍🤵🏻 @ Ring… https://t.co/fDGcst5LPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent advice in job talks. #science #academia #PhDLife @legogradstudent @stevesoperlab @KUChemistry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor user experience can turn people away from a really great product.  Becomes really clear when trying to get sha… https://t.co/g12CGt9gbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PHXCards11 I don’t think so? Just Netflix and other streaming apps through the Xbox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash I knew he was close to being over the edge, but this makes him certifiably crazy! #MAGA… https://t.co/fKVBG9HRHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, Austin has turned blue and yet it’s a hundred times better than California. Not close!]]></document><document><![CDATA[New video edited for The Ultimate Bootcamp Challenge! Let me know your thoughts :) https://t.co/D8a8Mlsmmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to be able to go from one wardrobe change to the next and remain flawless. #brows #lashes #makeup #queened… https://t.co/xW9TopkcLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist @AlhamAhlam Pee Wee Herman. Alice Cooper. Don King. Carrot Top. Dog the bounty hunter. Chumley from Pa… https://t.co/j67xN3dRWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mattjewwwwww @CailaDanae see I’m not the only person thinking Boston men are shady at this point. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're coming to @ASCDconf #Empower19 join me from 12pm-1pm on Saturday to learn about #objectbasedlearning… https://t.co/EMhQw9SKCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time I go to Waffle House &amp; the cook white I’m walking tf out 🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just bought to write a book putting everything out there. Cause the shit I put myself in lord 🤦‍♀️ I’m glad you got me covered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Melva_Mud @bielzebuddha @KassandraSeven Autocorrect I didn't look carefully enough. I meant involved Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[#elliscounty #elliscountytv today's show is about feral cats and loose dogs... a big problem here in this area... b… https://t.co/Bvqp1nTAjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this becomes a thing @fuckdavo will be in the shower for even longer]]></document><document><![CDATA[the trio takes on the Make-A-Wish ball 💫 #makeawish #chiooo @ University of South Carolina Alumni Center https://t.co/AzC3QfMibL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando llamo a mi mamá NUNVA CONTESTA! Cuando estoy con ella vive pegada al celular 😭 #TengoQueSerAdoptada]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC The girl’s getting to big for her britches...hey, Cowfart Cortez, have you ever read about Icarus and his beautiful wings?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on a new bass house/trap mix. Which tracks should I include? https://t.co/wAJwJDG42h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erika_strahl @PoliticalShort @SebGorka @DevinNunes @MariaBartiromo They are and are not getting info they requeste… https://t.co/xetYDGX6jq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealJoshFis1 @emrazz See how easy it is to rile em up. Soon his "wife" will be cotweeting w him because he's such a wonderful man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all take relationship advice from single people &amp; financial advice from broke people then y’all end up being miserable together 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[if they want to call you crazy? fine. this needs to be shared. #justdoit]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother puts the #herinhero for me. Who puts the #herinhero for you. Shout out to my daughter, granddaughter and… https://t.co/9cmh7zpVwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[A child who does NOT pay property taxes, Payroll taxes, etc or even understand civics, should not be allowed to vot… https://t.co/ITRB19mM49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisLVale Why not? When you make that kind of money, have cities throwing incentives at you, and barely pay taxes... 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#8Marzo Día con nombre de mujer que da sentido a esas valientes luchadoras de las que procedemos. Las abuelas, muje… https://t.co/e9XEtLfnoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Super70sSports So this is where @rmdixon23 learned work ethic AND how to dress!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to start back working on my online clothing boutique and the re-launch of my teen ministry. #ComingSoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greezyM60 I really felt Black Panther was on another level. I think it would have been a better choice. I’m not sh… https://t.co/D18uoO7pxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton More Democrat propaganda!  Title X would only be used for health services and not abortions.  Every… https://t.co/Nl5krpip7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry kids! @SpeakerPelosi has no use for you guys anymore! She has moved on to better things: vacations, Hollywood… https://t.co/hlsKh8KDe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is crazy  Jussie Smollett is now classified as a suspect in a criminal investigation  https://t.co/GSK6G6uZGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jenna Coleman &amp; Peter Capaldi  #DoctorWho #TheUniverseLovesPeterCapaldi https://t.co/dbmH1YDNg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton BABIES SHOULDN'T BE MURDERED IN THE WOMB AT ANY STAGE, You are so concerned with illegal children a… https://t.co/CvV0mo6Jc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 What an idiot! The craziness has gone to a completely new level and this woman needs to be committed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[OUR KIDS WIN! It’s just the beginning — let’s keep the fight up for our kids!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait for a week full of turn up and bomb ass food!! 🤗🥳😎 #EPTX #imcominghome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamHillEDU @laineyleini @GaryRGrayJr @davidleeedtech @nbcsnl And when using design thinking the ideas will become… https://t.co/8gsSyXhlOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me encanta. Debe ser el próximo presidente español  @pablocasado_ 1095399762327674882/video/1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to the modern inventions of indoor plumbing and water heaters, this is the first time all day I have not been cold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My handsome man, Gus. Isn’t he so sweet. #GermanShepherd #topdog https://t.co/dGFAmVKsRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son became a trader today and fell asleep in the room 😒😢 soooo I’m up with no sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen We get it! He’s mental! Question is wht 2 do w/an impotent @GOP supporting a totalitarian dictator wanna… https://t.co/VJH20esb7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Wheeler My husband once forgot to get a fork for my chicken salad. I used my fingers. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Or more like... “I want to open a business that 70-80% of the minorities in your city support since it means c… https://t.co/ieCDN34Dc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schoolofanthens @SpaceX @Space_Station Russians have made it in 4 hours so it's possible just not this launch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The greatest thing you’ll ever learn is is just to love and be loved in return. {Happy Valentine’s Day @jmhinton13}… https://t.co/FlCWSNhmcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ight my dudes lets sum straight. Valentines isn’t about being in love it’s celebrating loving in general. I know y’… https://t.co/u8VUEXsjJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arayyay I hope survivors are believed, even if police with poor histories investigating on behalf of Black people… https://t.co/KYXnq3uRzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The love birds Depression glass creamer and sugar!!!  The PREVIEW has started  my Vintage Friends... 💗💗💗💗💗💗💗  It’s… https://t.co/mTDZceh8kZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking through  my cookbooks and found this- time to dust it off again. I just love all the quick and tasty snacks… https://t.co/whS4WHF6pH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NG_Hoops @tgood1110 @MDGarner5 @NGHSrelay4life @NGHSAthletics @NGHSFootball @C_johnston_10 @ConnorMcCormi16… https://t.co/LukjdDi9Fm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing this precious grandboy the best birthday possible!  Love you forever, Levi! @ Grenada, Mississippi https://t.co/7H8KCiqeXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Killer leg day calls for a killer pic🔥  wearing the new woman’s Ever Forward white crop Size:XS and this material i… https://t.co/UPSnwc1ohj]]></document><document><![CDATA[MORE: I approached Murch as she was leaving the courthouse and asked her to speak with me on camera to hear her sid… https://t.co/MdM7PeYkat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ca$H APP ME FOR THAT Shit I BOUGHT YOU when I was ignorant to you being a playa BISH THIS IS A SUBTWEET]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reaga needs to get a damn iPhone so he can use game pigeon 🙄😒  Peasant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adrian &amp; i argue for everything and anything i swear es un pinche cabron 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just praying I didn’t post any of the videos I only meant to save 🙏🏽 cause we all going down if I messed up ✌🏽🦍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonTallTaylor  let’s go climb a mountain again once I move. Okay? Okay 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandabatula_ is seriously the cutest thing ever 😍 #SummerHouse Mr. Batula is a lucky man👫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my Facebook page to learn what I'm snackin on this week! @MuunaCottage https://t.co/Ui3PT7dXXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonWestAllen @wests_barry Don is gonna walk out of the STAR Labs basement having been there the whole time running.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulbrindis mi nombre es Isaura. Pero tengo tantos sobrenombres Isa, Rosalia, Rosie ya que no pueden pronunciar/ni… https://t.co/Rtx3KX9g0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Viviane6677 @angela681417 @PucciaPatrizia @enriqueiglesias @TereOrt51687394 @ElbaklySami @janaplauen @ZoyaDayala… https://t.co/lX9aihqS1D]]></document></documents></author>