<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @IlhanMN When did Islam become a race? It may be religious bigotry but STOP using race for everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#captainmarvelchallenge captainmarvelofficial @marvel #superhero @brielarson @ San Diego, California https://t.co/nFtMdoABjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veggie64_leslie The use of reporting here is unwarranted for being personal with little connection to content conv… https://t.co/40dMlTiEZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another 3 from Max after two FTs from O. Also Ruiz-Ortiz hits a left corner trey. SM down 56-53 with 1:56 left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BWOOD X @VINNIESSTYLES ⚠️ celebrating 10 years of friendship 💪🏽 #BWVS #NODEAL #NEWYORK #TRENDS 📈 #BWOODKNOWS… https://t.co/mPcv5hsWj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/uTck5Vivhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well worth the time to watch.   All you need to know to turn [them] off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OurRevolution @BernieSanders Fiction ok stop with the moral approach you like all others don't care you can't go t… https://t.co/TGaWrTy34Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poppcorp Gooood morning buddy! It's another chilly one up here but yup...we made it! Have a great one!☀️👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[But can I get a hoodie though!? UC basketball, baseball, and soccer got all the hardest gear 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greencouch5 @mkh531 @jmartNYT @fshakir @AriRabinHavt Every candidate except Sanders and Trump released their taxes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidjoachim @hgoldman77 Damn right they should and limit non-country resident ownership. It hurts Americans who l… https://t.co/h5G14KJSYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LolaJeep48 My mom had a mild heart attack yesterday, so I am doing the wait and see today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me calling wwe when I was 10 to see when tf my spinner belt was shipping]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmartosko @nbbrdrf @RichardGrenell No. Wait. White people, Christians and the western civilization is the problem.… https://t.co/fDodB4HGwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWERollins That’s turn that into #BeastSlayer #BigDogSlayer #EliasSlayer the next 3 #Wrestlemania main events… https://t.co/lwIBEkyvdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[As someone living in buffalo being called "the nights watch" has never been do accurate but still hurt]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 saved today at Maranatha.  I am so blessed to Pastor this church that is Striving Together. @mbcjacksonville]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there's anything I miss about Christmas time, it Santa Baby playing as background noise to every awkward pause during a conversation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertDSullivan I remember the first time I went to Southie in the late 80’s. It was exciting, though I wasn’t sur… https://t.co/8B1uNbi6n8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DevilMayCry5 keeps getting dumber and dumber and I couldn’t ask for anything better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjoyceatx I’m sure pebble would wow anyone, but I’d worry a tad about the long round with people everywhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No VM capacity... hmm serious national security violation up there: https://t.co/iVvjE9OA25]]></document><document><![CDATA[More people need to understand this, but key part, "with a qualified s and c coach" @JBFootball3 @BHSBobcatSports… https://t.co/638xUb4NMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbyEberle13 @RyanAFournier @realDonaldTrump Happy he did. The sore losers are still angry. Get over it and support our president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning to some of our Men of Strength at Wiley College! #Wiley_RYS19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wrestlingbubble I wish Taylor Doose would replace the McMahons on WWE TV. https://t.co/aFDcIkE3UO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justinnfields heisman ha , no way ! U better hope u keep ur job at Osu, who s the backup ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mickey will end up being the most bloodthirsty capitalist we’ve ever seen 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim79016862 @ericswalwell @AOC No, none of that is true. You don’t have a shred of proof, let alone evidence of an… https://t.co/dHDw74Tq3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snuggling under Mom and Dad's blankie! @ Independence, Missouri https://t.co/rpNIrEQJ3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachHStewart @encorevbc Daughter played VB.....went through the whole thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricIdle @thevandykeparks Have you watched the Durrells in Corfu. And , if so, your thoughts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkyfstr Yesterday it was bad to call more than 4 times in two years to talk to your own family. Today it is a bles… https://t.co/ZGV266t055]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mistresslilith0 yes Mistress slave obeys Mistress always respect trust and honor his Mistress]]></document><document><![CDATA[What better way to end off #ValentinesDay2019 then with this handsome dork on my iPhone!  Day 14 of @MarvelStudios… https://t.co/1we18R9yO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Either this is an incredible PR move or possible wedding bells are in the future🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic because I’m always on the go 🤷🏾‍♂️ https://t.co/Cm74QXmEKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm making my bf nama chocolate for Valetines Day to celebrate our upcoming trip to Japan 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… With A Little Help From My Friends - Remastered 2009 by The Beatles https://t.co/wXo3XhWO16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omar884s @i24lx @iLamp4 ياخي يطلعونهم من البيت يبغونهم يعتمدون على انفسهم، ماهو من كره  بس اختلاف ثقافات]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atameAti @MD_HO_DrAaronFC @VillalobosE @Vikko77222473 @CarmenAColeman @AleFerruzcaL @SoyIsraman No esperaba menos… https://t.co/RqtzQfPMKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why so hard to understand the question: are Celts better w/o Kyrie? Being super talented is about 1/5 what it means… https://t.co/xKgEQCettr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @RepAOC  News flash - Nobody cares what you think  Not @realDonaldTrump  Not @JeffBezos Not @TomSteyer  Not… https://t.co/HU2rHvF8YQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevelukather @bobcesca_go You better stop you’re hiding or your country will burn! REO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RapSheet @Schopptalk @AdamSchefter How do you recover from something like this??? Poor Bills Fans—No, I’m talking… https://t.co/GqY8XiCfRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjackson Stupid that at time I couldn’t get a loan because I’m good at paying stuff off 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TFD4truck @cltobinstlfd @E4Capt_PartDeux @JimmyP776 @OnSceneTraining @MikeSquad1 Recycling]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a shift from the #Blackhawks top line. Ottawa couldn't get the puck off them. Kane buries his 36th of the seas… https://t.co/JqdAowEzvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[House passes broad resolution calling out racism, 'anti-Semitic' comments -- without naming Ilhan Omar.  https://t.co/dtXRtBTXkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rick_cleveland I thought you’d wanna know a Ms Sports Legend has  passed away - Joe Gibbon passed away this mornin… https://t.co/Yp49V1UQja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BibRave A1: location, location, location for me followed up by challenge of the course #BibChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turbotax Thanks for the 35 minute wait to speak to a representative only to be disconnected as soon as they called me back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I wasn't studying, this would be a preferred "chase corridor" across southwestern Georgia. Highway 27 offers man… https://t.co/r6uJOt2zbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonChampionJC @ATLUTD @MLS @espn @TaylorTwellman @SebiSalazarFUT Can barely hear @JonChampionJC ! Are there audio issues??]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StatusQuoShatterers: "Banking was broken and I couldn't fix the old system – so I decided to build a new one." - A… https://t.co/TdNPqrqaxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure to get in touch with me for all of your VIP needs at @11Miami this @MiamiMusicWeek #MiamiMusicWeek  56123… https://t.co/Mg4FwmPXdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RIPStanleyDonen it’s a rainy day in Tennessee anyway https://t.co/CbbhVN6BGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idiot fucking parents! They should be forced to pay all of the costs for the kid’s treatments! https://t.co/JFpC1o1NlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NowWeAreSoaked #EOretreat #MoriartyParty @ Hidden Falls Adventure Park (Official) https://t.co/t7UoLWUbGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of my guy 2023 Drew Steffe for winning Made Hoops League today.  Big time future ahead... https://t.co/FggdGdOGyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The big Old Death keeps coming up.  We're poets  We've been expecting you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good knews: I didn't owe on my taxes this year. That's about the only good knees. Probably the lowest my return has… https://t.co/AdgJUKM6p2]]></document><document><![CDATA[On hearing this, Jesus said to them, “It is not the healthy who need a doctor, but the sick. I hav… https://t.co/MVBG07Ftou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Because illegals vote for Democrats. This is the same party that wants to ban guns to protect childr… https://t.co/ljvqkzUQWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christyw277 @ProudResister @KamalaHarris @ewarren @amyklobuchar @CoryBooker @BernieSanders @BetoORourke… https://t.co/wkWB1SCDvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing new @IdiotPilotBand for the first time in 12 years got me like https://t.co/av1MADBj3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a French Toast Stout by @wickedweedbeer at @marlinsbrew — https://t.co/ithy95Sdq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’ve got a few minutes and truly want to understand the recent Rules brouhaha, read this. I guarantee not one… https://t.co/szmwchmUpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christianity: Second Coming of Jesus Christ - Polar Shift &amp; Global Earthquake (NOT THE ONE ON JULY 29th) https://t.co/vpQVRolx2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will find away.... tell yourself that and everything will be ok I promise]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badjamjam And when you scratch the surface it gets uglier. https://t.co/j9FrEZmM76]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theSantiChrist Can I join your wedding posse as Brother-of-the-Groom? I'm overdue for a trip to Colombia 😎🇨🇴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before seeing this video, I would have had no idea who ran operations at Madison Square Garden. After watching it -… https://t.co/0z8eV5NWb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andriuna1 @CASTORFAVELO @NicolasMaduro Muy bien dicho a esa basura comunista!]]></document><document><![CDATA[giggle and move on. Although this meme is ripe with bad spelling and punctuation, I had to do a Lori... #funniness… https://t.co/H9pBHdw3Ld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Post birth Abortion really is that evan a thing. If your not a Russian bot and you repost this it's… https://t.co/KOSid1sxLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiderofWolves Red, I know this is difficult... I find a similar need to share my emotional state.  ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndustryMonkey Colton and Ben would be super cute. https://t.co/uSJJ3rh9pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Northgate, Columbus, Ohio https://t.co/hg2aHHUBdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything felt off today. Still embraced the #FitLeaders mindset to #boycottaverage Happy Monday tribe! #4amcrew… https://t.co/aNoUy9v6So]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mega Garden Giveaway #giveaway #win #seedneeds #myseedneeds https://t.co/VjaEsMkpWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stay up until 2:30 and then wonder why I’m tired all the time. Oh well 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDavid SOLUTION TO BORDER WALL PROBLEM During WW II the Treasury Dept sold War Bonds. SELL Treasury Dept WALL BO… https://t.co/hj0mdt3yNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiaJaxWWE  sammy brothers Come #WWEFastlane @NiaJaxWWE &amp; @TaminaSnuka Will become The New… https://t.co/IoOJneeLUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Old Sage -   Rejects the decision by POWERS THAT BE ON BEING REJECTED BECAUSE:  CONSIDERING REJECTED BY "THE OLD SAGE"-  ?🤔☹🤐🤐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random waiting in an airport for ages tweet no. 1: Leaving golf aside...one thing I learned this week...I’m in love… https://t.co/81B1BdnwC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeeTimeTomTexas @AnnCoulter But... but... we do need to secure our borders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelastglitter I think a lot of it came between him and Vader in ‘Tarkin’]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The longer it goes on, the more likely (the China trade battle) becomes more permanent,” said Todd Stucke, SVP at… https://t.co/kx5bh8GaDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight my eyes are closing and we are ready for the dreams that are destined for us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@demi_burnett Will you please be my valentine? I’m a nice guy and you deserve better than Colton. You are worth the… https://t.co/ESqynE5AHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who ghost are cowards. Dating wouldn’t suck as much if people were actually willing to be honest and speak t… https://t.co/ilwea8waSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pensfannc5 @alittlerancher Same , I’m going Sunday with a squirrel dog so I should kill a couple]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniellim_bong Baca komen2 orang di akun IG nya. Mayoritas malah jadi membully Ahok 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thus was a fun trip! Awesome show. Thanks @wallythewallace for having me. Trinidad is a pretty cool town. Looking f… https://t.co/bZMG1UvYYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kapriii83 @7DaystoDie When you set your game setting. Are you recording/streaming. Sometimes people put in their p… https://t.co/XiUaRTarFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsideThePylons @jonvoightscar1 @BeemieAwards also heard were watching Carolina]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniellegold_ Drunk Elephant baby!! Best skincare there is :) 43 going on 🤷🏻‍♀️ I need you youngsters to guide me sometimes 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PollyThomsonStr @arcjean @maydaymindy9 Well, then your primary interest is not beating Trump. Lol.]]></document></documents></author>