<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@christnemaddela @VegasAnchor @FOX5Vegas Yaa you look so beautiful and refreshed from vacation and ready for BTS I’… https://t.co/9qKGXAdz7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[For being someone so social I love to be alone. I love my quiet time. I can never be around someone longer than two days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I met a new friend today @ISMRaceway Glad to lend my @SiriusXMNASCAR  mic for a photo! Lots of kids out here today!… https://t.co/b7LvWZXLK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loveliness  . . #mariascottphotography #portraitphotography #dunedinphotographer #studiophotography… https://t.co/7kl8P4m44F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagnusBjerg @harlo The slide was a safety matrix of both how platforms treat your communication and who can access… https://t.co/llSmJAuacV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I hate dating so much because the shit is boring ... It's not gone kill y'all to think outside the box ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[on wednesday the the US House passed the bill to update background checks! voting makes a frickin difference. speak… https://t.co/bojaKkKSz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlisaMurphy @Alyssa_Milano @JussieSmollett Attempt To make MORE PEOPLE "HATE TRUMP SUPPORTERS" LIKE WE DON'T  GET… https://t.co/3jOOUrawV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bravo #24/7 « Je ne me sens pas « Stoned »; je me sens bien❗️ «L’hypocrisie» de M. Carmant dénoncée #Jamaica… https://t.co/zggEUld1DQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brookstrawn depression works on it's on schedule sadly but i believe you can get back to feeling good soon enough :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to the @SouthCougars wrestling team including Cougar outfielder Caleb Copeland as they compete at 5A Stat… https://t.co/ZZ8U7gr2ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful truth I re-discovered this morning at my hotel. #infinitum #serve #others @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/MRNe83JCdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mingberg @DavidLogan2020 @PrezesPan @wecanmag @AuburnMaineDir @enriquillo2 @DanielBrasilia @XandraXandraBX… https://t.co/h6UiJxkuLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel What, does he base his statement on?  Democrats support, &amp; stand for minorities.  Inferring he is more pro-Jewish?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Do you think anyone is taking you seriously right now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EqualityUtah @afsputah It is my honor to work alongside you all. Dedicated to creating a better Utah💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS45 IS SENDING OUT #NOSIGNALS: MARLIN L SMITH1963 AGAINST ME. AGAINST US.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @FallonRoussell at sonic.   Me: I’m not sure what I’m in the mood for so help me Fallon. What do I want?  Fa… https://t.co/wpD0TrcBzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[George Lucas checking out guitars and amps w his son @guitarcenter . I’m #fangirling big time #guitarsandstarwars… https://t.co/sBPX6BbVXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellirayebarry It’s a cross on the bottom of my neck with the only scripture that’s ever really resonated with me a… https://t.co/y4LuAOw6PL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dawn07206822 @kateeph @heidi_ed @drvic @NorthMidNHS @RoyalFreeNHS Excellent idea!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve decided we aren’t going to quit our day jobs to become artists... but it was fun all the same. 🎨 🥂… https://t.co/jXD9Du131l]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Great Review of the Holistic Approach to Selfcare.  ▪▪▪ https://t.co/RmBsj4BWNT  #health #healing #mindbodysoul… https://t.co/Dg7fCyFq8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny how one night can make you feel some type of way. I needed this reminder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Integrity Martial Arts Cutler Bay https://t.co/xQiAANZdLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIopekis @dustyrosedream @RobGavagan Thanks for sharing, don't know why people bother - it's like 'why would you p… https://t.co/zbNxxfaafr]]></document><document><![CDATA[K.I.S.S. Keep It Simple Sometimes Lol. With #valleyvictoria @valleynyc @ Valley - Chelsea https://t.co/fudnyt94AB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clean eating! It’s not easy but it’s so worth it! Have the discipline to say no to those cravings.  #NotAnEasyFix… https://t.co/Hjt5w5AvPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna play my favorite game of “can I wake up early enough to get all of my orders out” tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKGenest IF/when a genuine mistake it bothers me too.  Anything mean bothers me.  Same w/ Trump though his cruelty… https://t.co/F1GIZfdGp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Bridal Boudoir Blog!!! Go to the SugaShoc website in the bio to check that out and more     #Boudoir… https://t.co/bTKAqQa5xW]]></document><document><![CDATA[To those who feel broken or alone: God never fails. His promises are yes and amen. God WANTS to pick up your pieces… https://t.co/CkRfh9eV7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol if you gone be on that weird shit steer clear of me please and thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[“How do y’all wear those lashes”  “How do y’all wear those nails” Bad bitch life ain’t for everyone sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello 👋🏼 (brands tagged &amp; all details on my ig) https://t.co/Yu8a9YNxsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being in the 3rd trimester of pregnancy during Girl Scout cookie season is soooo dangerous. 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a pop of colour!  Could not get enough of the gorgeous exhibits by glass artist Dale Chihuly in this Seattle g… https://t.co/pc7V1dPVbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤩Con Sue Photography and Design🤩  🥰Like our photos...Follow our IG 🥰  😍This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/SsqUXpkV36]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trendmood @givenchy That's a slap in the face to all people of color. https://t.co/AJpPM10RCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized that we are in the month of March now... I was planning a Bridal Shower for April. It’s MARCH. I ha… https://t.co/TWB84Mp6lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Grand Canyon State turns 107 today 🌵 #HappyAZStatehoodDay2019 🌵🌞 https://t.co/t5x8vQ2CS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@legend562juan @karlajonese How do you go about it? It really seems that I might be out there a lot so anything to make my life easier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I went to give my first presentation as a “User Researcher” today and said “patients” instead of “participants”… https://t.co/MgQyQ0RwJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshrogin @Top_Sergeant @JoeBiden Even if he signs it, he won’t honor it. He is completely phony!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wcannonw @JamiejUmaine @myakSTEM I teacher K too...it’s so important that we start the conversation from the start! #AppleEDUChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rettak42b @beckjeff2223 If he gets in the game I’ll capture it too! How fun!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmax4christ @PastorDScott Look The Booker Scandal lie for lie man https://t.co/QfndLkVj31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherLyWGRZ I love your 1/2 cup of coffee story. XOXO, LU-H p.s. Been on St. Simons Island for the month will be… https://t.co/iha9rPRaav]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleas pray and share... praying that this baby is returned home safe and unharmed pinklove8 🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾’s @ New Orleans,… https://t.co/7lVEQI1A6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biodiversity lab! #biology evidence of evolution stations #KISDLabStar KHSIndianNation @KISD_Science https://t.co/Ahq1jee7TE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paul_steele @Superealism_Aus Ha! I’m used to live in Ipswich, Massachusetts, USA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scotstothebone @TallShipProds I agree ! I didn’t like down the rabbit hole at all!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResnickElliot What do expect when you have a wanna POTUS that loses sight of whats important and relevant because… https://t.co/pRmxtNgUO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just as I was about to get up and get to work (I swear) Hobbes came and fell asleep in my lap...so, I guess what I'… https://t.co/pgAlOfYTMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[that’s what i’m saying , she clearly wasn’t ready ... i don’t feel bad we tried to warn him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out I won a drawing to chaperone a kindergarten field trip, and I don’t think I’ve ever squealed so lo… https://t.co/vFIYvqdPGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing all of the amazing women out there a Happy International Women's day!!  #InternationalWomensDay https://t.co/4COiOqDXh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Keep being you. We are so blessed to have you as our President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo I agree. Plus, whose business is it anyway what ppl do???  THAT'S the #1 question!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into a friend and first thing she says is “dude you’ve been drinking a lot.. like a lot a lot..”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewamiller @JaneMayerNYer Hard to keep up with other all the bad players]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisa_tyson @charlesharriso5 Wonderul news! Great work @charlesharriso5 Thank you for never giving up! All your har… https://t.co/ioaKxd1uY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoJoBelovee Yesss he is!! Him and betty are couple goals too, minus the cheating lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Antonio Rodeo with these gals @EliYoungBand! @lyperales @vmo007 🎶 https://t.co/tvxeSm25FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the love of my life🥰 I love you baby❤️💍 https://t.co/oKoHbu8CV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tammy_lanette @WVGovernor No I agree he should’ve known better,  not defending him, I just don’t think he said it with ill intent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have date day with the bf after work. Which means I'm attempting to wing my eyeliner yet again at an ungodly time… https://t.co/Zc1fjr1fb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WallStRique @Fan001Post @Hoops_NBA_ @MikeAScotto @TheAthleticNBA He may see some mins on wed, just like he did with @CreekMitchell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Naija_VoxDei @DirectorSolomon You are amplifying a tweet that is clearly not true with your added context because… https://t.co/9XcsHpULjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son and his teammates at school at 6am ready to play their favorite sport before classes! #soccer #GoBirds… https://t.co/uEGlcbTLkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[i knew today was gunna be a bad day when i woke up to yellow kitty eating my honey bun outta my bag😐🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once he had exchanged the gift of peace with everyone, he said: “Blessed be God, who did not hand us over to our in… https://t.co/NCJ3R3tm4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arizona’s loss is Chicago’s gain ✌🏻 @ Lucky Strike Chicago https://t.co/qa5Qj45JdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@existentialfish @JudgeJeanine should know that only hoes wear red dresses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@viet_t_nguyen Never thought of ever changing my name. Though, apparently, I have the same name with Hello Kitty de… https://t.co/E5Dhg2Jd32]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Joy how do you get to heaven? Do you get in a tube a slide up to heaven , like a waterslide” -8 year old at children’s church today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RissaReptaar I’ve got all@my alerts set so that I buy those damn tickets!!!! I’m so excited for the reunion 😭😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m gonna hate myself tomorrow morning when i have to get up at 6 AM 🤦🏼‍♀️😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very much looking forward to hear the talented piano students of NYU Steinhardt Department of Music! Thursday, 3/7@… https://t.co/MiIXsKFSZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katie_George05 @Bucks IN NO ORDER WHATSOEVER!!! He didn't even need the song!! https://t.co/6EOVL1dPAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannynrhall @Weinsteinlaw @JuddApatow @realDonaldTrump 1 of my favs!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxhwelll @HarrisonSmith85 @bryan_stumpf @frankdmon22 @AmityBoatTours Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BereaChorus @MrCCollington78 @Berea_Middle Thanks for having me! Around 4:30 and again at 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just to name a few...🙁  #tiredaf #stickwithit #worthit #hotmess #staythecourse #adulting @ Innisfil, Ontario https://t.co/nPiNchtObN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier on chaturbate doing a show #ebonybooty #ebony #camgirl #sugardaddytwitter https://t.co/gtdwNrsZ2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone just spelt ORCS with a “k” and assumed they were in space and I’m triggered]]></document><document><![CDATA[HERES A VIDEO OF MY COUSIN DRIVING WITH HER MOM. THIS SHIT KILLS ME. MOMS ARE WILD💀💀💀🤣🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/9Qu43o5mdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all, that’s the funniest GIF. Idk where it’s from but that lady is salty as hell lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Sale - 5 Acres Unrestricted Land. Only Deed restriction = No mobile homes. Great location for Bardominium or co… https://t.co/YYLM8MZXN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m supposed to be cleaning but instead I’m figuring out different ways to fix my hair]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I like to hide Smirnoff around the house so I can ice myself before important things]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start your morning right.   Email me- biancaisfit@gmail.com #ketogenic #ketosis #ketodiet #ketofam #ketocommunity… https://t.co/VbdtAoCw7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamanthaBusch Get back into the M&amp;Ms car next year and win Atlanta like you did in 2013!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IWD2019 #BalanceForBetter #LetsDoTheWork #ImCaterpillar https://t.co/jIIlBTa09N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need @AMCTheatres to tighten their grip on talking/texting during movies. It's at its worst right now and… https://t.co/CqEtwbSZLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laveybae If they have you working again while you’re still clocked out then yea probably lol, might wanna file a c… https://t.co/gdWMuQBBPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView Why can’t y’all get Megan to let someone else talk? I would love to have heard Sunny’s thoughts today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaisyFreakinLou Yesss and the best outfits too!! With these online retailers taking over they end up not making as much for it to stay open]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s right hold your fire! Use that fire for good! #dontshoot #brooklyn #nyc #newyork #newyorkstreets #bklyn… https://t.co/5CpjehyfTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[adding single cell epigenomics technologies here https://t.co/ECqa0u2C3P]]></document></documents></author>