<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Holding each other up. Literally. June 2017 we lost our dear friend @patsyterrell 💔 https://t.co/mYRFNpjnAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m going to get a tattoo of a black panther and it’s name will be newton seale]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alli_b96 @Tylerrr14 @Cameron8561 @amakayj @katieMW Nah I think you’re still the queen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yea, the Nike commercial ,that aired during the Oscars, is cool but women also dominated motorsports..Before Danica… https://t.co/KG6WqqZfyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi  How does it feel to lose your Speakership to a freshman?  How insulting?  You need to step down.  @RepAOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[time goes by fast when you’re in bed, tryna get some extra minutes in before work, but be extra slow when you’re actually at work!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smokey86950399 @nicj9311 @Beautiful_Waifu @AOC One of the theories of the disappearance of the clovis is scarce fo… https://t.co/mIaUfyxgoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great video featuring the important work of @mcgregormd and @tmadsenem on sex and gender differences in medicine, e… https://t.co/ZQ0CeZiE6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GCosans Thank you! Still a bad writer! 🤣🤣 @Zippy_TMS @bullpenbabe @liddyloree @SDDonavan  I will make sure to mention you all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abb_0312 That would have been awesome. Do you think she could handle our crazy family?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to know....what type of oil y’all fry y’all chicken in? Yes I’m going to judge you #Replytweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consider each person as a gift from Christ to our congregation, and equip them for ministry accordingly. #TrellisAndTheVine #DontFilltheGap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter literally destroys me. I’m walking around looking like I’ve punch walls for a living but in reality my blood… https://t.co/TTxr0HfEX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to My Faith In You by @BrantleyGilbert on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/axgFzjWx66 https://t.co/B1NSBXINSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since they called you in last week and tried to fire your ass. You would think you would stop doing dumb shit in th… https://t.co/wMnD8BExZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders essay contest with two SB students. @pburkevt https://t.co/4XEf9LkhDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[me because it’s my senior prom soon and I’m still : 1) single  2) single  3) single https://t.co/IGD2FN98aT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for The Man Show! Come see us at the t-shirt booth! #ErinAndMattInTheMorning #KATCountry #ZimmerRadio… https://t.co/cjrXw0mvD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had bulletproof coffee today and let me tell ya it was a lot tastier than I had expected☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to the airport now to @JeffIsRad , but made sure I stopped off to get the mandatory party platter! See yo… https://t.co/WP56OHIUty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Wah, wah, wah....   still calling Hillary “crooked” I see.  Well, most of us know that you are the… https://t.co/UD05TXPHRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pindal Concealed would have been better than sheathed. I think more clearly after coffee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @abbydphillip @TheLeadCNN Maybe s @realDonaldTrump ‘s Admin. wasn’t such a dumpster fire, he would feel differently.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ La Catrina Hookah Lounge &amp; Smoke Shop https://t.co/g9VChO9fkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you guys know that we had beautiful hard wood floors underneath our gross carpet? It's like a brand new apartme… https://t.co/s1F4llwZq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek Don, Jr is the modern day Teddy Roosevelt? Bwaa ha ha ha ha ha! 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are warm &amp; inexpensive. After a certain age, you dont care so much about status symbols.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is @NGPVAN coming to hang out with us ASDC types? I wanna be wined and dined...but actually I just want to ask a bu… https://t.co/xSChn7SB9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another successful blood platelet donation...  #ibledforthethrone #got #freetshirt #cancerkicker @ American Red Cro… https://t.co/LGcqgocDf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEAVE TWITTER^JOIN #MINDS #minds #billottman #OpenSource #newsocialmedia  Twitter is ineffective trash talk,Faceboo… https://t.co/UwJDArYRN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Completely unimpressed.  Now, if only we could have Ayaan Hirsi Ali in her place, I’d be happy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patriciaglane @dstluke @lizaanne42 @anthoknees @benjancewicz Well said.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dreaming of a redo of last week.... Sun🌞and Fun 🌴🌊with my love @ToddSwift3 💜 https://t.co/sPaUOz3xqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariah2430143 I had the biggest crush on @ralphmacchio when I was 13 -14 &amp; 15. #CobraKai is awesome to watch for all ages.]]></document><document><![CDATA[District's appear to have done a cost analysis from last year to this year. Rather than make best efforts to comply… https://t.co/YhsLw46bWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaByTiGer1993 Now you know you do nothing but make my ego grow and that is never wise but thank you xD &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ambop15 @anhelica_xoxo @sydnie_carrillo wanted to start working out in panhandle! Y’all could go together! 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[When J. Cole said “I roll with some fiends, I love em to death” I felt that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plan to get a Polaroid camera so I can take v cute pics with my future boo 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s crazy that Green Book received so much critical acclaim after so much backlash on its backwards history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lena Waithe would absolutely destroy me in about ten seconds; on the other hand, I could probably take L*n* D*nh*m;… https://t.co/Qcoc6jUy8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP: Dems soft on illegal immigrants  Reality: Trump employs illegal immigrants   GOP: Dems profiting from office R… https://t.co/6XuQbFb7cD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USC_Athletics @MarvellTell_7 #FightOn Marvell! Go get em tomorrow! ❤️✌️🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give yourself the gift of a perfect pout this Valentine’s Day💋 injectionsby_ashleylouise is a queen👸🏼#meimeiXchi .… https://t.co/K7ZIFsVisC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Filming a JoVE with @JBurdetteLab @katherineezink today, we are missing @DeanReproLab though! https://t.co/CYTkrDsQdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of February 25th #Days #dool  Mon Feb 25th Hope apologizes to Ben for misjudging him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelleyk525 @FastBridgeLearn Hehe I am definitely going to have to buy some warmer attire! 😆 I’m so excited, though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattMurph24 @VABVOX Griffin and I wish you a wonderful birthday, Victoria. I hope your biopsy is negative, too. https://t.co/Ye4N72gmN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a good point here. We need Christian women leaders in this space. I think it’s a growing blind spot. And I spe… https://t.co/wjqyZtRwFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast and Tea ☕️ (@ Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA) https://t.co/1pioMUpRt1 https://t.co/r2GOhNq3Qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What is it that prevents us as black women from stepping up and owning our power by speaking powerfully about it?”… https://t.co/SRxFqvghiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSBWDrea This is a place where people bring up what you tweeted 7 years ago. Very unsafe drea lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went home sick from work. Thinking a trip to urgent care may be in my future. I’m slowly continuing to feel worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronCh7Weather @DarrylTalley @varietywny @WKBW @DJJickster @NewsRadio930 @TheBillsMafia @DelReid ❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[One little two little three little dick pics four little five little six little dick pics seven little eight little… https://t.co/OLukRia71b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t underestimate someone’s ability to try an knock you down as soon as they feel threatened #bebrave #stopsayingimsorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wonvoyce #ThankYou 🙏 When I hit up ChiTown soon, Wonvoyce imagery is nxt up! 🙌📸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenWoody40 @StarTrekRoom Reshoot? You miss the point of incorporating the Cage footage.  It stands up; no reshoot needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We CANNOT lie down, go to sleep or half step.  We must pull together. WE can't fight amongst ourselves! Uphold WHOE… https://t.co/ceAlZGIPit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great first day!! #kdf2019 #knowledgedestroysfear #haircutting #hairdresserlife #neverstoplearning #educateyourself… https://t.co/Z2rbsZGccF]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a gentle snowfall presents you with beauty everywhere you look. And faces in the woods.   #iseefaces… https://t.co/bU3GJUHflM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies, we’ve got this! All day, every day. #WomensDay2019 https://t.co/WWPqsPLMXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthewcogdeill Will you Write up an FEC Complaint/Investigation For Foul Mouth, Disrespectful Rashica Tlaib WE HA… https://t.co/9RN6YiZ5rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @CovfefeKatie So he gets the attention he seemed to be seeking in order to use it to increase his sal… https://t.co/ggVAZWErvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealJeffKemp @POTUS @KellyannePolls She was putting her spin on dt’s lies again. Her eyes look like her soul is… https://t.co/n0yqcSDH83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameKween @carlyraejepsen @QueerEye Shinto cry to a damn commercial 😂 I’m a sensitive little flower. I heard #thisisus is really good too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3_PershingCt @KevThatDude Lol him and the family will see you soon 😂😂😂😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwithat @StromfieldAdvs @suzystories @globalmimiuk @capturewithdave @carpediemeire @KaraDiDomizio What are you up… https://t.co/XdnOunWSde]]></document><document><![CDATA[The word for @danabrams tonight on @LivePDNation should be #ItsMyChair 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so content with my life currently. I might not have it all, but what I do have is joy in my heart with all God… https://t.co/h0xmf2TWDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoursonFreda @TiptonHurst @KATVNews Thank you and happy Valentine’s Day! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to find out who the guy was at Wild West who gave me my last dance... he can dance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOfficerTatum @mddd3528 @realDonaldTrump It’s really hard to ignore facts! Our economy is great. His policies ar… https://t.co/vUfTKX9A5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever see someone and you have he strongest sense of affection for them and then...it just kind of morphs to the… https://t.co/ufYiPAov9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well her bro was paid 35 thousand to marry her to get her past IMMEGRATION Sick family]]></document><document><![CDATA[My tax refund just made me cry because it was the best thing that happened to me today]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏👏👏 YES @sallyeaves. As we look at #genderbias we have the opportunity to look at all #diversity and #unconcious… https://t.co/eZO5DQXTIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same bitch is also the one who lied to me about having cancer three months ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Airbus pulls plug on costly A380 superjumbo as sales plummet https://t.co/fC9m1CRpAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Much misappropriation of funds in government agencies.  Congratulations off to a great start.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMikeTurner More shocking than this? Trump Falsely Claims That Manafort Judge Declared There Was ‘No Collusion’… https://t.co/9APkBcESrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnSpiroSpero As do I. Believe it was after a Norman press conference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How tired I am these days I put my scrub top on inside out this morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Tell all the Vets exactly how disabled you are.  Go to Walter Reed army medical and visit and ride i… https://t.co/63NMZmRLuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaHFreeman @lejandroFranco Yes, save yourself the mental energy, time, and tears and take the GRE. (Pretty sure it’s cheaper too:-))]]></document><document><![CDATA[13 Reasons Why Libraries are Holding Us All Together https://t.co/W3QIi7j4cG via @ReadItForward]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking of my Guardians family and the Cavaliers tonight. Today, we lost Guardians 2016 tuba + Guardians 2017 drum… https://t.co/DytkgkpKXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last #SXSWEDU2019 keynote was the best one. Thank you @cultofpedagogy for the lesson in helping schools reduce drag… https://t.co/gbqyoe3Mgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ V-103 The People's Station https://t.co/4VeK8eQNsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My biggest flaw is I think I cant sleep without essential oils on my temples]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏🏼👏🏼🇲🇽 Guillermo del Toro será invitado de honor en un episodio de The Simpsons https://t.co/2EK3BusYjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stillxcold nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut nut… https://t.co/4nCK5PUIvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe he discussed it as a option to protect the American people from a lying, deranged, ignorant, out of control p… https://t.co/NMwSuUwl4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted @NYCVotes for public advocate #NYCPublicAdvocate #JumaaneWilliams. https://t.co/sK1QmUewyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncar89483445 @williamlegate @CheriJacobus @realDonaldTrump Calling the media " enemies of The people" is a Stal… https://t.co/ehwdWVmsuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you have an annuity but you need cash now... CALL JG WENTWORTH  (877)-CASHNOW!!! that shit was a bop on god thou… https://t.co/mR6XCF4X9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[*the whole class gets a D on the first exam*  Professor: clearly you guys aren’t doing the reading!   Honey clearly… https://t.co/gzRDRP9zaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do love that my @Phillies are getting Bruce, but that’s a ridiculous amount of money. So I hope it doesn’t backfire.]]></document><document><![CDATA[10-2 on the week but we got work to do back in Ohio ❤️🥎🐟 @ Plant City, Florida https://t.co/wZpkIFKmj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where to eat and drink in #Charleston during SEWE 2019 this weekend https://t.co/Xzpbr8FPem]]></document></documents></author>