<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Great read: For a Black Mathematician, What It’s Like to Be the ‘Only One’ https://t.co/24FO0Eoq1k @tony_prophet… https://t.co/nHLHGytSol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaredSandler @1053thefan Good lineup for our last game in Surprise! ❤️⚾️💙 #letsgoRangers]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the random ass convos that Tom and I have. From conspiracies , to beliefs , to relationships, sex, etc.. we… https://t.co/szPMApFeok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our weather team is tracking the potential for severe weather. Follow them for updates! @KATVMelinda @KATVJames… https://t.co/uiHrCVwqAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Healthy Ash was killing grocery shopping with berries and eggs and then Sad Ash was like, “But we also need a frozen pizza and ice cream...”]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #LoveYourPetDay so I had to show off my angel 😍😍 https://t.co/kZpo2CcMFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ncketters @GeorgeWill George’s clue are usually crystal clear. It seems that your clues are cloudy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkmzkt322 @FlakeOfSnow2 @krassenstein That message was meant for someone else.  He blocked me before I could block… https://t.co/6ddVHIXeK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneaking glances, thanking god that he drew you like that 🥺 https://t.co/WBFSmQGFSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you set your mind to it, this is the end results... A very Nice Humble Guy and not to mention a very handsome… https://t.co/1CfyvO2XO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mom always made me valentines and Easter baskets growing up... like that’s seriously one of the things I’m most… https://t.co/FmKM9X1gHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was an awesome experience to witness the women of UNH Athletics guiding the next generation! ... It’s only cr… https://t.co/26F5s6JoDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melissa McCarthy, I have loved you since 2000. But you just shattered my world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaledonianRoses @ElGiganteDiablo I like Armageddon, honestly. I don't understand the hate. It's a fun movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HobbesQ Here's them doing a cute version of one of their popular songs from a few albums ago that "babies and litt… https://t.co/fdylOiKE5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But did you die” is my new reaction for when anything bad happens in my life..  EVERYTHING CAN ALWAYS BE WORSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johndavidbreen @EugeneBu @emartinez78987 @Just2BiZI @Sheeple101 @HappyBigGrin @45HammerTime @Flwrgirl66x @CplBart… https://t.co/frQihtLByT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to pass the Celtics in championships and remain ahead for the rest of time. Truly what matters to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Überraschung: Auch beim Digitalevent #SXSW19 wird noch Gedrucktes gelesen. Ist das “Retrotrust”, der Trend in den U… https://t.co/dkHQ1QcrTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshboyer84 @TheView Russian bots can't get my attention... Keep moving]]></document><document><![CDATA[이 타로는 아주아주 오래전에, 한 15년 전에 한국에서 몇천원 정도 주고 샀던 것 같은데(정식 카드라기 보단 책의 부록같은 느낌이라 카드 재질은 매우 허접...) 지금 아마존에서 검색해보니 최하 70불 이상… https://t.co/FOYBDFFM53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul @KelleyAshbyPaul @LifeLearningCtr U RUN 4 PRESIDENT ! NO TRUMP NO PENCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makeup by meeeeee on Queen Tia! 👸🏽🎉🎊💙 #memphismua #memphishairstylist #memphismakeupartist #memphis @ Memphis, Tenn… https://t.co/LPxVwbB5pw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to my fans for making this photo shoot happen in the amazing ATHENS TX  Huge s/o to @sarahbmartinez… https://t.co/qmXG9f2d4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reneejess0205 @VittitoeBrian Yup Jessica!  That’s exactly what has happened to her, she was very abused and thrown… https://t.co/lEMCovZb9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhysRelations @MDAndersonNews Our Undiagnosed Breast Clinic patient satisfaction scores are off the charts.  Give us a try!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanted to send out a special shoutout to my officer team! While I was on maternity leave, they didn’t skip a b… https://t.co/PlCfJHrazZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[That damn Tristan.... wait... I’m not surprised Bc the mf done it before likeeeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachLopes480 TEN YEARS??? Between this and Billy getting his Junior Class Ring... 🤦🏻‍♀️👵🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone up for a book club!? I need to read and talk about this book with a Literacy Tribe!!#d25ItsPersonal… https://t.co/oSu8vI5Qrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#saturdaymotivation Let’s DO this! I’ve been working weekends for as long as I can remember and if you are today kn… https://t.co/rnaQaC5PwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Following on from Rory’s survey  on feeding choices at #WAS2019 there is a new product coming onto the market. Barc… https://t.co/nu8vCG2xvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Migos I know I know they’re not a band but idk what the hype is over these dudes 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kylie is the newest self-made billionaires 21   and at age 24 I’m contemplating driving an extra 15 mins to avoid a $2 toll]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to speak with these lovely ladies at the Women’s Impact Luncheon.  Thank you City Of Miami Gardens… https://t.co/vExICPVRDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see Drake McCain audition and see if he gets that golden ticket!! Bring it home for all of us small-t… https://t.co/x5GLQmewqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re thinking the US government is corrupt and you don’t have a voice, watch this video to see how one organiz… https://t.co/NSDPVMgoyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RootLiterary @TemreBeltz @EmmaDianne1 @mattiOgreen @rhievaluations @pdpabst Thank you so much! I look forward to s… https://t.co/k4wDtr8Fgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha well I’m going to Utah for 5SOS. Better be the best 30 minute set ever 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelleeec27 It’s literally the BEST feeling in the world finding yourself and doing what makes YOU happy again,… https://t.co/h97CrLjz9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@princessfemme Beautiful couple. They are missed and needed so much! Can we declare a national emergency and bring them back???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PWettlaufer @coojen22 @ruprosper Had lots of help from the Student Life team! Believe @TheBiznauth worked his magi… https://t.co/f68hhjgUDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDebateHitman @StephenAtHome @SenSanders @SenWarren Where we are has a lot more to do with people who don’t vote… https://t.co/4AH7ZCisNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TankSchottle ❤️ happy Valentine’s Day to you and your mom. Hope you spend a wonderful day together ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephsAmusic I can't agree with you more we should be uplifting each other instead of putting each other down ♀️power]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tresonstickers love your list ♥️@POTUS  ExecutiveTime agenda continued  16. a few more adderalls what the heck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@writeourhistory as if the book wasn’t enough, this documentary is IMHO the most important doc of our lifetime. I’m… https://t.co/TZ2wO28ecC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my @aerogarden started a six pod today.  I’m officially hooked, my next one will be veggies.  #hydroponics… https://t.co/Pzwftv7fm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE PROBLEM IS THAT I’VE HARDLY SNAPPED HER LATELY. IF SHE WAS WORTHY OF IT I WOULD BE OKAY. BUT LIKE WHAT? okay i’… https://t.co/MH5185evLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao I swear this was Demare and Shy in AVID our senior year of HS. It wasn’t funny then, it’s a lil funny now]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do YOU know about Louis LePrince? Excellent website entry by @ColumbiaCityHS student at #NationalHistoryDay ho… https://t.co/Nl95arRacH]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all be callin females trash, whole time y’all be cheating &amp; lying 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DjRmc @JewellDillon_ @lanavalrey It’s a horseshoe crab they’re completely harmless and are not native to the western coast of the US 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful for the opportunity to engage in these powerful conversations about assessments and professional learning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday i feel like doing nothing but it seems like everyday I’m busy af😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kima_jones Sounds like too much work. I prefer this kind. https://t.co/CyBsqk0LG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my amigos Dutch bros and Buttercream, I’m getting my amiga In n Out, but haven’t gotten myself anything. Get you a friend like me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out our NEW bachelorette video! 🎥💕 Dcottsdale is a great location for incoming bachelor and bachelorette part… https://t.co/SaztgUEmP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone else posting their selfies w/@Kellysue so I guess I gotta too right? I dont have the one from wiscon a cou… https://t.co/qukvYWC6a9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Earned It by @theweeknd on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/kxtrukenq4 https://t.co/VrA8QmCMBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[🖤 Hi sisters! 🖤 thank you @jamescharles for this beauty https://t.co/uJbQ9AopZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marley_ok Dear Marley me encanta 🥰 verte como care to Mirko really I love 💕 u  😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL, men that demand the right to gun down a person if they just  “feel threatened” are demanding control over a wo… https://t.co/hhCEhj9pGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sound up y’all! Hard-hitting questions in the morning with #skinnydad #whyyousoskinny #dad #mcnamara… https://t.co/vY3jR2ybsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep. That’s me with the stellar furniture designer brooklyn_gent @hellman_chang 😍😍😍 Always love seeing you!… https://t.co/6JmINZqTJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrdenDivino @GuarioCandanga Eso mismo estaba pensando yo. Qué chévere tener un maestro tan joven y cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Smithwick's by @GuinnessIreland at @celtic_ray_pub — https://t.co/wx8BB98xAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely love drunk texts and FaceTimes from my friends I live for that shit. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT REALLY HAPPENS IN SCHOOLS: "A teacher told me in 2nd grade that I was dumb and ugly. She told me that because… https://t.co/Py5PbIqOkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harry Shum Jr. Talking About The Final Season Of "Shadowhunters" https://t.co/XCdYmvNB0S via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready to go away from here. @ Charlotte, North Carolina https://t.co/yHp2BhD6mj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeticiaTweets @DawnSineya @Aspengardener @ScottHech https://t.co/kHqXqqjz2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so hard when you call me, your friends saw me with somebody but that somebody ain’t you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me extraña. La camarada Delcy Eloína solo usa accesorios propios de nuestras culturas originarias.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TBT to the lights, brights, whites and metallics from Burnett’s fall/winter 2019 show. . . burnettnewyork @nyfw… https://t.co/A1G696l6Tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancyjeanbird   I just saw rockhound on your bio. Me too 😊. People make fun of me all the time over rocks.   I hav… https://t.co/XBvSqVKDs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If basketball is all you care about, why you bonin' me? Why don't you bone Dick Vital? 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might be thinking too small with travel the country, what does this look like in the rest of the world? Surely we… https://t.co/Qq9VdDX1j5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lithub I don’t understand how you don’t receive something literary and lovely 24/7. https://t.co/mqP0IBmVYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexa1102091 Im suspended like fuck but I’ll risk it for a plate like that 😂😂😂😂 💍😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should really grade remote sensing labs today but feel like I’d rather do nothing like I did yesterday. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the best clients &amp; real estate team!  #HandsDown #WannaArgue #LoveMyClients #GodFamilyRealEstate… https://t.co/vU1SBn1lRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinstonWolkoff so glad to see you on Twitter! I think of you often, and the beautiful cactus in Arizona ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just spoke about this the other day 👑 I agree with both of you for sure 👑]]></document><document><![CDATA[this man is the most beautiful soul, i love u and your music plz marry me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im that friend that likes to hear what’s on my crazy friends mind cause they be making the most since]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atinab46 @sxdoc @POTUS @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Yes, yes, why is she allowed to be in Congress… https://t.co/vhUwawGKfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @GOPChairwoman Wait! What about the children separated from their families? Are they also part of the life and… https://t.co/PcU2ztoAY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adams drink comes in a smol fondue pot @ Melting Pot https://t.co/DRld6eqc2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about the babies you still have locked in cages at the Southern Border?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JiminsBookmark Me over here knowing I got a plus account: https://t.co/sN3OiEpr9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mitch_T13 @JR_24X I don’t believe it’s rolling over for preferential treatment because I feel that line gets used… https://t.co/4oIGQYUIwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love me a well balanced man... ballet shoes &amp;&amp; a hockey stick. https://t.co/TE3nV6JrCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I understand why they say having little girls is so much fun 😊😍😘😀 I hope I can get through all of the cutesy ou… https://t.co/OvrNhhbxpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've just been waiting for you to leave without me. It's probably greener.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BWTTRTB2019 from my point of view. Full of great  detailed information. Founds day was the start of a great experi… https://t.co/V2imWAnxZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cindy4419 @GenieFrancis Happy Monday Everyone. National Nap Day !🍀 https://t.co/5jRehrQBBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve come far and have a ways to go, but we’re fearless, relentless, and strong. So much 💜 to all of the amazing w… https://t.co/K6iNPTWd32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Said 3x that I want fries w/ the order my dad is placing tonight, the last was when he BEHAN placing the order.   S… https://t.co/NjABO20ltC]]></document><document><![CDATA[today it was 90* and all I could think about was going snowboarding for spring break...why am I like this]]></document></documents></author>