<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[First week of my new workout done. Feels great getting back to the gym after so long. Keep pushing your self until… https://t.co/EQPsFRebTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Martin leads in such a positive way.  She inspires me everyday. #TrueLeadership]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂 would you look at that? Why it’s my favorite thing (again); Conservatives lamenting over the runaway train that t… https://t.co/kTaTyWpDz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rubberducky2784 @DjDedan @MotherJones @realDonaldTrump “A report from someone about something”-you mean an article… https://t.co/TxDWbaFzSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamtheDiDi @PeteInPublic @the_ag_fox_1971 @HomeEcMel @yoopergirl89 @Marlenedougher Not sure why spitting on graves… https://t.co/Fjq7VkrnuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babal_s @tailopez Just going off of the statistics and the facts man. The u.s typically is easier in terms of beco… https://t.co/cL0mfMVE3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/2 Now the full number of those who believed were of one heart and soul, and no one said that any of the things th… https://t.co/AoYSBE1urx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baconelf @painting_tlc @AngryUnder @specialkitty2me @izzysick101 @PlainAngryinTx @ajwhitewolf Ewwwww!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockwellbeer have added to the fabric of this community . . . they are making St. Louis a great place to call home… https://t.co/VfCq7O6hhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PASBO2019 key note speaker talking about riding his bike for tacos.  He had me hooked]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GBPhilipSutton @shanselman @DotMiltonKeynes Urgh, *poker* Edit @jack, FFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jozsus1 @realDonaldTrump THEN WHYYYYY DID THE PAAAASS THE ANTI LYNCHING LAWWWW. Its hypocritical!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta look evil if you're going to Skee Town... @ Allendale, Michigan https://t.co/RKklwUutEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our doors at SDE are dropping some knowledge and inspiration! https://t.co/cYiENX36pg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somali Region + SL+ somalia+Jabuuti  =  OGADENIA +  Or  Ogadenia 2 Began 1920's General Governor  Mr. Workeh Yibirs wanted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trevor_fields3 @BostonDevore @Tanner_Moss24 and again...the rest of the Hornets who don’t have twitter or I couldn… https://t.co/5j2ASFjBYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaseliebler @MattGinellaGC @USGA @GCMorningDrive @GolfChannel @chambleebrandel @damonhackGC @RickieFowler Agree Chase]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rick03907 @EMC_Maine @Flroach @JohnBechard Yay, you're finally going to get some snow for the beach shots??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever wins the Djere-FAA final will be well inside the top 50 on Monday. Bit of a pointsapalooza.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm patiently waiting for media to draw the narrative of the celts going from broken locker room to potential NBA champs after last nights w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Neclovian @AustinDHoffman @geo_uiuc @uchicagogsu Also - we won the leeeeague #unionstrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was 10 years old and saw an ad for a two-week summer computer camp in the back of “Creative Computing” magazine.… https://t.co/UaoOCaKJD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Izard County Consolidated Family! The Cougars are State Champions! https://t.co/SuVYvulpFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that's my kind of color contrast!  Experimental kitchen has been very busy this month  #cellarmanearl… https://t.co/FAIsjQrw7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's lawyer Michael Cohen will serve as key RNC finance executive https://t.co/8npReOq4Td "I don't think my coll… https://t.co/7SdoYyk16s]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of people talk about how B*rnie hasn’t changed in 40 years and has always believed in his current platform. B… https://t.co/M6LEH1vsHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y un poquito más atrás están las dos mujeres con las camisetas más chavistas que he visto lol 👎👎👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[La belleza complace a los ojos; la dulzura encadena el alma. Feliz tarde!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow Steve Harvey....dude already had no respect for you and your book...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManuS_CCG @Kevmaxd @arenadecklists What's the board plan? I haven't beaten it once yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackGarcia66 @JamesAGagliano Because they probably promoted/appointed the heads of pre-publication review. The HQ… https://t.co/AonyTcQ44s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t tell @trevbx but I stole one his photos for my phone background. He’s a really good photographer 😬 https://t.co/ROW4a6e1ZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few of my homies from high school. This was our friend Kerry’s 50th BDay party. Man some things never change! Lol… https://t.co/Dr3yhUZfe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marianntabuchi @WellsvilleDCIT @WellsvilleCSD @mrscbowen @malati_reeve @LynnShanahan1 I am not sure send me the link]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atDavidHoffman There’s only one word that describes Trump perfectly: Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalMrBill @bleudawn7 @SDDNP @Wrath_of_Comm @_Carja @_Delathor_ @_lynnwolf_ @0yogini0 @1Nastygal @1SKERKRO… https://t.co/wzUBTEVZmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@byuwbb Congrats ladies! You earned that win today! #GoCougs https://t.co/8Pfm1ZOfst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a critical perspective. We must not leave the vulnerable behind. There should be targets on adaptation to reac… https://t.co/TxgT46lJHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump Obama had decades of wars and could not win anything he was dropping leaflets were goi… https://t.co/yZ4ZbfIZma]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Feel and respect of a great Mashbill #ryewhiskey  taking it to the Top #barrellbourbon your not just civil ..… https://t.co/dxxMLksh4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BKayZone THEY'VE BUILT A WALL !!!! ITS YELLOW. https://t.co/DkoB5syG1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brian_d_vaughn New music Friday finally got a chance to listen to the rest of the stuff.  Faultline, Vostok, and Cloudfist 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[there is nothing better than not executing some plans. god does that ever feel good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Beer Me by @oddsideales at @bulldogalehouse — https://t.co/cnv67nIlLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackdaryl @ericfisher @JimCantore @NWSBoston @wbz @weatherchannel Hello. https://t.co/dK59RGW104 (an IBM brand) wo… https://t.co/IL3sQ4sLAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoniCute72 Even Siri knows what a shitty season the @LAKings are having.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Make sure you vote a democratic candidate into office in 2020 and finally we can declare a national emerge… https://t.co/2sOJo9b8VJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Jenn, couldn’t happen to a better ambassador of sport in Canada!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkFaris1 @thejimjams That has already occurred due to the leftist indoctrination of our public school cartel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to nominate someone for an award this week, and (hot take) if your award nomination system requires document… https://t.co/UhSoTBhRDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rolling pin I ordered from Amazon was delivered three days after @USPS said they delivered it. I’ve lost trust in them:]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just in, .@BaseballJeff1 commits career suicide by (not really) speaking ill of Brandon Belt #SFGiants https://t.co/9lRA7fsp1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eso y todo eso. Hipocrita y diabólica "organizacion" desde el principio creada con los fines criminales que actualm… https://t.co/2O5LwM4zYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaddyJim52 @AllieKatz2 @DaniScotchIrish @eye2winner @Lonestarmomcom @Yakekoge @FactCheckU @lisalbarjas1 @waconia3… https://t.co/f4j2S2zEAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can y’all just learn to let people be happy and mind ur fucking business]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's late in the month and there is no longer any point to clicking links in tweets. I've read my maximum in all th… https://t.co/XwJjmeCIxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visited #AndrewJackson’s #Hermitage in #Nashville. @jmeacham was @dsmpartnership’s 2015 Annual Dinner speaker. I hi… https://t.co/s0Hiz5FB95]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to put it on the front of the office door... #wellstone #wellstonealumni #2016 #grassroots #wetogether @ Atla… https://t.co/cgaSWqVjpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playoff Gameday! Pioneers take on @TempleIceHockey in the opening round of @ECHAHockey playoffs at 3pm. Broadcast l… https://t.co/tDH6vhgyZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @robmurphyemu win over @wmumbb want a slam dunk by going into OT, but it was an important win near the end of t… https://t.co/Rm8eK6600E]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a rare occasion I'm able to snap a pic before Tayla realize that I'm taking pics!  Such a beautiful little girl… https://t.co/etM95I7Jtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #Leipsig, WI? https://t.co/WPAiat72hZ #BusinessMgmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am HONORED to know many AMAZING women. You ALL know who you are and I celebrate you today and EVERY DAY!! 😊❤… https://t.co/A4U8UrrIL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump ... looks like someone forgot to take his Adderall this morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kinkirky I don’t think non profits should be releasing commercials. Churches, Planned Parenthood, NRA none should… https://t.co/pyuWgEjnl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#YouArentTheOnlyOneWho walks here dammit! Pick up after your dog! https://t.co/MdcsJ67mCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my thought on defense as well. On O, I would lean towards Quick or Neal somewhere on the OL. Have a sneaky… https://t.co/VJp19BWd3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎵 If you're bored and you know it RT this tweet.🎶  🎵If you're bored and you know it RT this tweet. 🎶  🎵If you're bo… https://t.co/1ZVB6BuuJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeylogano @MW55 are we watching the Richard Petty racing experience? Just follow the car in front!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope this follows her for the rest of her life. Great job dad, you raised a racist. You’re prob one yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We've had 13 Raw women's champions and not one made the title look as prestigious as @AlexaBliss_WWE and @itsBayleyWWE did]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RykerStephenson @wvjoe911 Ah, the morning sex club -- I'm a charter member!  😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatherineKilmer @knockedloose Do it and then come to Europe with me. ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankSowa1 @seekerwisdom1 @JenniferADevon @MalcolmNance @BlueGhost40_ @amvetsupport @VADjude352 @AriMelber… https://t.co/V4bGBJ5kh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always nice to see my cousins because they will unflinchingly be honest. “Oh yeah, your eyes are weird right now. Very unsettling.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiegoArcos14 Inolvidable. Qué simpático ver las propagandas antiguas también. Por ejemplo la d Ocabsa. Por si acas… https://t.co/oO0fd6EY2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuyFieri @catcora @roccodispirito @FoodNetwork 🍀🏈 Great show!!! GGG &amp; DDD Rule!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Do what you wanna do, be what you wanna be” - Masters Apprentices https://t.co/FnaavwqqU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy March 1st Everyone! 🙂 Short months like Feb get one closer and quicker to the Summer☀️ Where did the winter g… https://t.co/ati3uNjfNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresenius Medical Care is hiring in Austin, TX! Read about our latest RN, Dialysis Nurse, Home Therapies job openin… https://t.co/sGCv0XKw0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoLayingUp This is like the #uber driver wanting a piece of the business deal for driving the exec to the meeting.… https://t.co/Wdev11yxMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this happened today, became a ski season passholder (capitalizing on the #marchmeltdown) for 19/20! 🙌⛷️❄️ And fi… https://t.co/MMnpvz23Li]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP What % of Hoosiers think this man is creepy?  #Individual2 https://t.co/rpfY82CvMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I appreciate people who ask you more than 3 times “what’s wrong” or “what’s up” ,,,,makes me feel so loved]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Claims To Have Listened To Snoop Dogg, Tupac While Smoking Pot https://t.co/glBqxrVwcS via… https://t.co/TGGWy3b3Vn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristenClarkeJD I have thought of poor Khalief &amp; his mom all day. Just can’t get the disparate treatment out of my mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cal Poly loses its season finale 92-82 to UCSB. Coming up next on @ESPNtheTicket + @tunein we wrap up the season an… https://t.co/0bnIfjUooJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is the billionaire who is willing to spend on philosophy? I am not holding my breath.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJuanVargas I dont question the relationship.  I question why the US gives israel allot of money to run amok in… https://t.co/R0K50HYHB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenMcSallyAZ @vpotus So, let’s be clear here, to you the only troubling part of this “National Emergency” circumve… https://t.co/lBpoXPUA8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[As an #entrepreneur, I completely agree with this. It’s one of my biggest arguments for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smalltownandrew @robjh1 I’m not sure why they say a failed deal. I don’t recall any Pres. before him, ever , attem… https://t.co/bHn4U1wpVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KikiD22 @GoWHSAthletics @GOWHS_Wrestling @KeiraBear825 Way to go ladies!  #ProudOfTheseBULLDOGS 💜🤼‍♀️💛#WorkHARDthinkBIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@no_face @sstrudeau Quite a bit of that land north of the freeway along Nixon Road is in the greenbelt, such as the… https://t.co/rWHeNFrb0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Possibly I should have gone on from Chile to New Zealand, to meet those nice solar punk people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los Martes maetabaco manito_menudo  Presentan  En madeinmexiconyc La Voz De tonybravo15 Y Las Mezclas y la Buena an… https://t.co/KKfdJ86GrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[...fuck #ValentinesDay! I guess I'll celebrate #SingleAwarenessDay with the rest of y'all, pathetic losers😒! In fac… https://t.co/elfvytwMoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even with the loss, Seth Cinfoni was impressive tonight. The uncommitted junior atyackman tallied 7 goals and 1 ass… https://t.co/UzNteLQUvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace @annhedonic Months ago on @msnbc... @mccaffreyr3 described Russia with an economy equivalent to It… https://t.co/fhjSMroFHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking a conceal carry class today. Excited to cross another item off my list of things Ive been wanting to do.]]></document></documents></author>