<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@shanehartman731 @RobDauster It started with a suggestion to kneel from a Green Beret. Honestly, kneeling is a grea… https://t.co/t42sreo8gp]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don't have to give people a reason to hate you they will make up one if need be!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karensfam5 Here's something for you Miss Heels  Up! https://t.co/UxTLkMP3m6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laplumadelpoyo Definitivamente, la verdad entre culés y merengues hacen una orgía de inmamabilidad y victimismo su… https://t.co/ZnNvloddlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennylattimore #kennylattimore #kennylattimorelive @ Chrome Showroom https://t.co/P9VUNiVy3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Holder is a moron. I wonder if he has ever read the Constitution.  Hey stupid, it is a separate branc… https://t.co/3XXCdQxlJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir question: we booked our flights about a week ago, since then the price had dropped significantly (abou… https://t.co/U7CPBkYbUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The -ism we should be worried about in this country isn't socialism, it's fascism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurbalEN @GuyInACube Memory and video card.   I am struggling to find a video card also.  Installed a GTX 1080 but… https://t.co/3m3jSLFEK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ethan Page Signs A Two-Year Contract With IMPACT Wrestling  https://t.co/SAeAowSCLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely more impressed with her as time passes.  Don’t often agree with her, but definitely gotta tip my hat to… https://t.co/kw3FDTVkOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Do not turn to mediums or spiritists, for you will be defiled by them. I am the LORD your God.”- Lev.19:31 #dead G… https://t.co/PjpEmIZrsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theoldgreywolf Nice bluff Rhynes, but hold on a couple tics. There’s JD on the other line. I figured he was monitoring your twitter feed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Akron o135 Toledo -4 Iowa -2.5 Kentucky o132.5  FL Panthers -150  “Shooters shoot”  -Uncle Dan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahéehe' @SGR4NM @GovMLG for upholding #NewMexico Governmental responsibility to protect our Sacred Lands!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone ever been so into a TV show that you refused to get up no matter HOW BAD you had to pee? #CohenHearings #POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veramagalhaes Em qual categoria vc enquadra o seu jornalismo Vera ? Eu diria, nível: Zé de  Abreu]]></document><document><![CDATA[For real baby that s*** ain't going to get you nowhere https://t.co/8qRDfXXxvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this is true, @ringer and others she cover this in-depth. It’s easy to assume as spectators that players are all… https://t.co/d9HI2OVhMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to pursue my dream or die trying... fuck what you think, it’s not a dream anymore it’s a mission.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@masaocodes Native google auth is only supported in standalone or unmanaged workflow because it needs buildtime con… https://t.co/YdK78fFSiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just sitting here waiting for the day the @PawSox open up in Worcester. https://t.co/1uZYZCEApN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders Don’t seem to remember you complaining when Obama routinely by passed Congress and the democratic proce… https://t.co/LRkYWf7eDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny as he'll, but all my Leaf fan buddies have one on the go for my Flyers as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cs00582scs @Jamierodr14 Looks like he's gonna be upset for 6 more years]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, thanks for reminding me, Twitter! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/0ilMi6iLl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemmiguel Omg philippine version of Venmo. Hopefully mag transition na rin ang Pinas sa pagiging cashless!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lying without considering the negative consequences.  Unfortunately the fallout will be buried but folks need to se… https://t.co/vY55vZGOM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time, it’ll have to be an illo of a name tag sticker. “Hi! My name is ..”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Culture calls you to #pride  Christ calls you to #humility. — @ronniefloyd  Rom.12:3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYGovCuomo I know, you're worried. Why don't you go down to your local @PPact clinic and watch a few abortions?  T… https://t.co/o85EhnNwzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoarderWall I use any and every news source and not one of them has said there isn’t any issue. Just because you l… https://t.co/87uDoCIkWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another one of God's gift that would have been missed if dems have their way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Anyway, we tee off in 1 hr 18 minutes. Don't get us bumped please. It might rain later.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defense pressing forward!  #soccersunday @ Scheels Overland Park Soccer Complex https://t.co/uYCJle7LRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pizzagate resulted in an armed dude showing up to a restaurant with no basement to rescue kids from a non-existent… https://t.co/4hvlPl5Xdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Entrarle a los problemas con decisión” manifiesta gob. @diegosinhue pero en el caso de Leonardo Reyes, con todo re… https://t.co/14EiCETzEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValueStockGeek What did you go with? High speed internet with YouTubeTV? Sling?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOBCC I had an amazing time last night!  Thank you @gobcc, @MizzouLBC, and the Big XII Council for your leadership… https://t.co/01FLhmWCaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaneTheStranger As a term, no.  But 9/10 times when the term is used outside of an informational context, it’s use… https://t.co/KheqLIfVUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mohdux2 @politico She was SOLID in this Role!!! https://t.co/NbRae1Yqty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllenTStClair And the book has a new cover.  It is nice when publishers and writers give serious consideration to reader feedback.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HanumanOlam @heretiiic guess i got no choice then https://t.co/SOaysbtwbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this ghostly contrast of Muir Woods from james.kilcullen. . I drove up and down this driveway twice (with far… https://t.co/c7D8F4W9hp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm looking forward to Captain Marvel, but I still think She-Hulk is still a far more compelling and inspirational… https://t.co/wmYvKOcM9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillWeirCNN Reading Of Human Bondage by Maugham. Never did before. Sometimes nice to go back to discover the masters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_tessr Would be very great news in fact, if we had a mechanism wherein demand for housing and other services could… https://t.co/J8LIaDmlB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bacchaus351 @SenatorCollins So I guess we just say it was money well spent 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix @tajjackson3 @michaeljackson We need an actual, fact based, documentary, full of evidence and from the Jac… https://t.co/O8SDLwf7qD]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUMMER TIME AROUND THE CORNER!!  Ladies, you trying to flatting the stomach, builds some curves and sprain some nec… https://t.co/qmb6Vo1A8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DancesWithTamis INFERNO? ONREFNI wH:Y             DANTE             d(ANT)e This note is DANTE tender for A-ll deb… https://t.co/19EVRQi2Cc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s snowing so is it a snow day lol 😂 I guess when u in your hood it do not matter 😜😛😋🤪🤪 @ New York, New York https://t.co/RIflqi12HD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we would if signed bro in December we wouldn't be having these issues]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But the Lord is faithful, who shall stablish you, and keep you from evil.” 2 Thessalonians 3:3 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oem_gee @Just1Shei Really time to load up the gat and make it sing like a choir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure sure, but the GAYS, we’re definitely the ones messing the sanctity of marriage 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor kid has been sick the past couple days. I wish there was something I could do to take it away. Link 👉… https://t.co/fVG9EMdUyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday 🎂 to the most beautiful and sweetest person in the world @Camila_Cabello #Happy22YearsCamila… https://t.co/rQUkSoQ4Vn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nellyy1997 @ReinertLuke Decent average. Happy birthday big guy! #LeftySwag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePulpEc Y la verdad que es todo lo contrario. La sociedad está de acuerdo. Cada vez que una persona se hace mill… https://t.co/gmM63x5iQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DomantayRecords is accepting bookings for National Recording Artist Bishop the Overseer @bepc99 https://t.co/6QaintRlXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @ChrisGuhy and the Cardinals on winning the Region Title.  Long overdue and couldn’t have happen… https://t.co/bvjZ6Wllgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @HouseGOP @GOP @seanhannity @IngrahamAngle @TuckerCarlson @FrankLuntz Exhibit A of what a dishonest liar… https://t.co/fpsMUMxkIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philsoussan I have been finding some good deals on Amazon in their marketplace through some Ma and Pa places I wouldn't otherwise see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who here in the #RGV lives streams on @WatchMixer @Twitch @OfficialDLive or @YouTubeGaming? Are you partnered with… https://t.co/MKbObGNjOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encuesta para los trolls y bots  Quien a sido el mejor presidente en los ultimos 18 años]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doubleheader (@ St. John's School in Houston, TX) https://t.co/HY6T234nso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laura_say @YalitzaAparicio @ROMACuaron Ellos?? Sea quien sea , mientras tengamos talento, todos llegamos !!gracias… https://t.co/zbv8UwA9tO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laura does the food prep thing. When I get home from work hungry, I’ll sometimes open her containers and pick some… https://t.co/RNpNuqj1cY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bourbon hits you at the start but as it warms up, the most chocolate and coffee flavors shine through. - Drinking a… https://t.co/OrvJFxioj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best halftime show I’ve seen in a minute! Congrats! 👏🏼 👏🏼 #NBAAllstarHalftime #NBA #NBAAllStarGame https://t.co/tAxq8Xinws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buffabro716 @ManagerEnrique @DetroitRedWings @RussianFiveFilm There were a bunch of Russian players that started p… https://t.co/V2UkJ4gUob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice goal by MOJO!! Keep making those moves these next few days. Nothing against him but we know what's coming up n… https://t.co/12yzDJVpeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this week's #AnalyticsNeat and learn more about Gartner's recent analysis of #analytics and #BI platforms… https://t.co/rAuu9LSn66]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandma talked my ear off on the phone for over an hour. Glad to see her back in action]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoannaMang Going to be Theranos-level bullshit artist on my resume. who seriously isn't going to find that valuable?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both city championships ended in buzzer beaters. Definitely worth watching in that hot ass gym. Congrats to both te… https://t.co/POJsLrd2pf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Liquid Spiritual Delight (LSD) by @2ndshiftbrewing at @design2brew — https://t.co/TyMoPJCoFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm feeling a Keith Tkachuk, Craig Wolanin, Jeff Brown, Dwayne Norris, and Brian Daccord staff next fall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If everyone wants hate gone, it’s simple to assume they don’t want you in Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulioBorges Desde KUMARAKAPAY, primer pueblo libre de la era Post ChavistaMadurista informan: Ya entró la Ayuda Hu… https://t.co/FJOI057IVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Пока, Чикаго. Привет Дубна ) @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/Ky2XvjiZtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StefMNicholas @cathfamilynews @MattGaspers @LouisTofari @acatholiclife Will do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my new single "Get Off My Line" distributed by @DistroKid and live on Google Play! https://t.co/jpBsGuFQWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliciakennedy We eat them at home regularly and actually prefer them to beef.  Had them last night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vinman905 @NikkF07 @heelEvan @mossow @KwnStorm @Beers649  WWE on demand has added Royal Rumble, 1990. 1991, 1992,… https://t.co/es90WdZXl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edsaldana60 Great picture!! Viva Los Doyers! Which section are you in? I’m here too. ⚾️💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liar from the start. Trump the father of fake news. https://t.co/6U6DDR1nIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The studio of Robert Loughlin with his work like this on sale. #artonInstagram #artist #artlover #artwork… https://t.co/ZkktOOkjme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repost @erubes1 with make_repost ・・・ Golden nights along the curvy California coast. Especially around this time of… https://t.co/bRZn4aJ6ij]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great Company wants to build. And assist Mr. Trump. THANK YOU. What can be done about Pelosi and the rest of fuck… https://t.co/DLxLTXIVcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nevaevapressed Go tell a doctor how to do surgery.... of course you wouldn't.   If you haven't put on the badge yo… https://t.co/OOQ0zFmYi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hockey? Canadian. Coronas? Mexican. Me? Ashkenazi Jew @ Madison Square Garden https://t.co/57WjvZpswA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at West Virginia Turnpike North Beckley Toll Plaza in Beckley, WV https://t.co/g6EJHdpc6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PWRevolver #ItsAlwaysSunnyInIOWA is going to be the show Iowa has ever had. Since the last Pro Wrestling Revolver show]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multi-level system of support for timeline active living in high school #physicaleducation at @AL_Research in… https://t.co/To3uMGPybX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to be a part of the Aquaflauge team!  The leader in performance apparel.  #aquaflauge https://t.co/va2fe6s6eF… https://t.co/GCOwyfE3RV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s idea was it to make Gatorade Zero? It taste awful and make sure to check to make sure you buy the right Gator… https://t.co/cVMU6shK1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beard_Grizzly @AnonPig Better question is what the nine have to do with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman Your sad and perverse "logic" is applied to any "ism" as manipulated by Leftists. It doesn't count if… https://t.co/6xeKyxX8mw]]></document></documents></author>