<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#Noticias710Digital radiomambi710am @rodrigoduranh @nelsonrubiotv #EEUU #Trump #Cuba #Venezuela #Guaido #Miami clau… https://t.co/h4I9z9zlfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[thotiana (w/ cardi b) the type of song to rival Play by david banner in vulgarity....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ New Smyrna Beach, Florida https://t.co/SPAZc9cnoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SD2019 Graduation ceremony @ McCormick Place West Expansion Area https://t.co/rcIaMl3JR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimgris @timbray SF has been changing for the worse for years.  I eventually decided I'm better off in a place I c… https://t.co/EYnYUszli9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get so frustrated at my own flightiness. This is the second time I’ve lost a merch shirt at a concert but I’m sob… https://t.co/3P0KluLSjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mostly impressed by the number of Walks less than the number Of relieves. #LSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am hoping to hear more from Bernie this time about foreign policy, where the differences between the candidates m… https://t.co/UlM2JYtfZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I had some opinions to share, but the last new movie I saw in a theater was “The Sting.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachAlexGray @ahenderson_400 Lmao I ain’t even peep till you said that 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnWallmeup @Herhealthynews @RussellFord_1 @RainDownFire @4x_Clubchamp @roddy202620 @buckeyejulieOH… https://t.co/B8Hz6A6dnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmpeyer They need to do a zelda game that is the entire series in order from start to current start with the first… https://t.co/VMp4hHXzcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Search me, God, and know my heart; test me and know my anxious thoughts.  See if there is any…… https://t.co/GePV564a7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I must have missed this episode of Drake and Josh: “Drake Faces the Blunt” https://t.co/FEw7XzeG1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcrowley413 Was another terrific last second Friday push by @James_Scully111.. Just caught at the wire at 16-1, bu… https://t.co/Dw88AepchF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FcomanuelBR @RodDelCampo @UFCEspanol Sus números y logros hablan por sí mismos, GSP para mí es el mejor peleador de la historia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in the parking lot of the hospitalthis morning ingesting lots of caffeine and I see the sophomore class go… https://t.co/Ie325fhWQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[MYRIAM HERNÁNDEZ EN VIVO DESDE WESTBURY  🎶  Nuestra artista @MyriamHN nos está enamorando a todos con… https://t.co/yhYzvRnYyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did that dumb one think she was gonna just head on back to the UK? Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is amazing Densie @caregiving! So humbling.  I just want to make an impact in people’s lives 💟 @CarelyApp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey girl, I’d protect and support you the way Diego loves and supports Klaus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lucas_Wiseman @SNewellPBA Definitely didn't know that 🤣🤣🤣 but he did that to many people coming up including myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers @TezlynFigaro @SenFeinstein Every time I see a tweet from you I go 🤢🤢🤢🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hewlett_Found and @knowledgeworks were honored to host students from @HSRA_MN and @bigpiclearning that inspired us… https://t.co/ByNyBGND72]]></document><document><![CDATA[also I will never be able to forget everyone telling me to change my stanky BO shirt when the whole time I thought it was clean]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s our story from last night on Terry Jackson’s final game. 48 years on the whistle! He made a difference in so… https://t.co/gsTcObZm63]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coryiskillinit Yo keep fighting that toxic masculinity 😂 this is why we’re friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sauce de mi amiga #maitee y su equipo. P. D. El hojaldre que me regaló mi primo compadre drbrooklyn me lo comí con… https://t.co/x4kBfJgQYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny to hear someone talk about something they don’t understand like they know what they’re taking about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@satinephoenix @CriticalRole @GaryCon @deathsaves @TitmouseInc @HobosMurder See you today!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@puck_20 You are probably not pro abortion you just believe people should be allowed to make their own choices. Tha… https://t.co/kLr8FCAknN]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man spent a couple of hours...  Defrosting his fridge last night… Or “foreplay” as his wife likes to call it.… https://t.co/jPnTnAs5LF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DarterPro update. After some field testing I am getting between 6-7 hours of battery life using normal settings ru… https://t.co/xPyvE9HC5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kidgolferman @LadyRedWave Not going to work...they will just go to another country to get their ammo, or black market...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanHenryB @JSimonovich94 @BruhReport I don’t know if I’m in Mexico or California at this point tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d3ink I know and that’s good and all but I hope the safety we get doesn’t have to develop like the other secondary players we have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Forbes seeks an assistant editor for media and entertainment: https://t.co/mk5Gbaps9G https://t.co/uuy6rTpejA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate rich niggas, god dammit  ‘Cause I ain’t never had a lot, damn it Who you had to kill, who you had to rob?  W… https://t.co/xjEAKO8Gvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The market has been going crazy since you became our man in the White House. That’s because your policies are up an… https://t.co/rFED6ceDac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well. THAT was certainly not something I ever thought I’d have to come to terms with. Thanks for that, universe. 🙃😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad that @peta kills animals and are raging white supremacy supporters. So happy they came out about this! #donate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love to hear from our #pathology colleagues what other topics would interest you! @IJGConline @IGCSociety… https://t.co/aqLdFYPkTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried to get all cute and flashy for my class today and that cold weather hit me like @humbled4beast]]></document><document><![CDATA[ethnically non-monogamous sapiosexual seeks smol kink-friendly pupper for cuddles, snacks, and firefly marathons]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step.” - Lao Tzu  Just keep going and do not stop. @ Los Angele… https://t.co/nSsg1uXXVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for watching The Dale Jr Download on NBCSN. @Blaney was a great guest. Will be back on Tuesday at 5pm ET next week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing unique to LA is that the guy belting Motley Crue’s “Home Sweet Home” outside my apartment at 9:38 AM could be Vince Neil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeMarini would you be interested in providing a donation for a silent auction fundraiser for my sons baseball team?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sure hope the news is exaggerating how bad the roads are this morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing @JBALVIN post “no creo en San Valentín” like same bro 🤣🙌🏽 it’s payday thooo 🤑🤑🤑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denvercoder Neat idea. I just add it to a special note in @BearNotesApp with the hope that, one day, I’ll actually get to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thblomme Het feit dat er een dode valt, is reden om in te zetten op preventie en testen, niet op repressief spierb… https://t.co/C0ve0jOJim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealTrupper @MVHSLAX15 @JakeGreene161 @SportsGuruNY @Yankees @DJLeMahieu Give him back then]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Brother Andrew my brother-in-law Carlos Santistevan my sister Michelle And my two nephews Mason and Eric. Having… https://t.co/eQZBPevx0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill #CPAC  @VP You two belong together, though I’m not sure which of you is the bigger joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[03/05/2019 Byron Center Public Schools two hour delay.  No morning ECSE or AM Preschool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting the work day started (@ Goodwill - @austingoodwill in Fredericksburg, TX) https://t.co/Ym70LDIiI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vince at it again there's a report now that john cena will host a new version of are ya smarter than a 5th grader t… https://t.co/liS0eYS22v]]></document><document><![CDATA[He could start the tour :Sing ‘Mamie’ in black face while three memberships of the Virginia legislative body tap da… https://t.co/w5HShSv5s9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGretz I think of your tweet everytime one of the two touch the puck and I know you're not right... But I am 100%… https://t.co/rSVDHB31yw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guy that sits in front of me at work has clamy hands and makes a weird coughing noise before he answers the phone.  🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 6 years, @jonasbrothers are back! https://t.co/9Uxb5sU6xb Did you catch cameos by the #JonasBrothers’ signifi… https://t.co/0w4qrUYzh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are many problems with equating abolitionism and environmentalism, but the larger point is that we know Ameri… https://t.co/Ae2AnimK8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aminadujean I don’t know, nor do I want to know either. That’s just getting too close to “ドスケベ世界” there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good so we can beat y’all again, just like last year and show it doesn’t matter if he plays]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CiprianIulian2 @C_Rich75 @Oprah Don't give that nonsense stats.  Make up by whites.  Yet all this rape culture sta… https://t.co/nF8Taj2pGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife and I are married 31 years today. Luv ya, Frau 😘🛐 https://t.co/JwY7YE3PKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practice with team in the morning. Outdoor rink in the afternoon.  Getting ready for playoff hockey. https://t.co/DhhHCRMvFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SECBarstool What? I am dumber from just reading that post. Obviously you never watched Jordan play. The G.O.A.T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fam Jammin’ at Fleetwood Mac! 🤘🤘🤘#rockandroll 💀 #itsaschoolnight @ Birmingham, Alabama https://t.co/IeH4OwaF3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Infosec_Taylor Same thing. Was driving me crazy. Then I found out a colleague had Registered a domain on our accou… https://t.co/7MbOuEpQ52]]></document><document><![CDATA[Russ and Daughters now in Brooklyn! What?!? Now BK really is the center of the universe! #livewhoyouare #brooklyn… https://t.co/zREDbEiwCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OHShirleyMAGA @LovesMDesigns @EricKohel @MarkMBC @JoaquinCastrotx @JohnCornyn @tedcruz @SenTedCruz Because someone… https://t.co/59iMrW6hYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is inconsequential that his prediction was disappointing. The only proper response from Giuliani, Dowd, Sekulow,… https://t.co/CwYcvEKmZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottlincicome @JonahNRO LOL, I always try to be polite.  No sense in being rude, especially when it’s my misunder… https://t.co/aN5Y4U0ZMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#theunknowcase #premier @TheUnknownCase1 elcaminoalcine @PaulinoYaniel @nanoprinting @cachapasymas peraltaenmanuel… https://t.co/xvj6ckrtxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dixie_picker1 @ScoutSteveR Chevy Driven 😂 Do you mean Chevy driving 😂😂😂 You make the Bullpups so proud! Where do y… https://t.co/hZezJZZ8au]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swipathefox @buddyhield @LeaderOfHorde @HGiiizzle @hbarnes Winning starts NOW! BEAT LA 👑⚔️ #SCORESHERE #BEATLA #PLAYOFFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pittsburgh mayor Bill Peduto speaking out against the border wall saying there are other emergencies  to address… https://t.co/rQT3MdzVx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good article explaining why the trade deficit has grown. It also explains what many of us know, the trade deficit i… https://t.co/Unx16hqhGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[get this ish off my Timehop I don’t need to be reminded every year that I was livin life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLGator193 @PatrickBuchanan The noun century is descriptive of a number, 100. There is nothing metaphorical about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a BLESSED and PROSPEROUS DAY. @ Greensboro, North Carolina https://t.co/krTGSd5GbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshtpm @FatesAndFuries @TPM My understanding is that there a lot of “social justice” costs to offset the climate… https://t.co/njtr8288Em]]></document><document><![CDATA[@6ixNuck @christoaivalis I think the NDP are irrelevant, right now at least. I agree with a lot of their policies.… https://t.co/OtYUVf9VXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fascinating. Funny how we imagine gender is only relevant when discussing the work of women. Surprise, all translat… https://t.co/yNYFbzfWIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 trends set to shape Southeast Asian e-commerce https://t.co/azyhyTyfuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoffThisHofThat @kevh14 @GoodmanHoops And lost to them during the middle of a 1-12 stretch during this calendar ye… https://t.co/Q3UDiJPDfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGeekzTeam @Manuel39503599 That was awesome!!!!!!! Loved it!!!!😎😎😎😎😎😎😎😎😎😎😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actores, músicos, clubes deportivos y autoridades felicitaron a Alfonso Cuarón y su equipo por el éxito de "Roma" e… https://t.co/mztim9zeyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomsegura and I laugh at the same shit on his podcast. People getting hurt and the noises they make makes me cry l… https://t.co/xO5XiTnvBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random arrows all over our kitchen. #Alex #SnowMageddon2019 #PargettPartyOfFive https://t.co/owaHncR3eo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders kicks off his 2020 campaign. We must work for a #GreenNewDeal, #MedicareForAll, #MarijuanaJustice,… https://t.co/EUcGPYGo4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gentry_johnny Iooono bout dat cuz. Dem dips out yonder down McCledon Chapel Rd in Bluff Ridge ain’t no joke hoss.… https://t.co/e8szUmi17Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s a life you’ve been given and a life you choose. Don’t let the life you’ve been given be the life you choose]]></document><document><![CDATA[From backstage at Sam Christensen’s memorial, Ken Cortland speaking beneath the image of a man who means a great de… https://t.co/eBcNM6bLDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vaughany9 @Cricket_TS Seen lots of names on here, for me it’s Arthurton, Hoops and #No1 Carlisle Best]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is a terrorist that was  or is on the side of killing our American soldiers. Show the images of her at the thro… https://t.co/ZIWsO2Olwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emtaylor1998 @_dimitric @NW_SMSTA I mean we definitely don’t choose to be teachers for the paycheck. It’s obviousl… https://t.co/FKs6yU8nxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tsvnekiM Lmaooo bro wait till I tell him that he gonna get tight lmaoooo]]></document></documents></author>