<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My girl hooked me up. Lucky to have someone that supports me and encourages me to leave my shell.  @elgatogaming https://t.co/d5SMU3OXyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that’s a headline RT A Japanese spacecraft has landed on an asteroid and fired a bullet into it  https://t.co/zFno8i5Coz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillMoehle1 @BobLonsberry @gcraig1 As someone that has to deal with 15+ twitter accounts on a daily basis, I agree with Bill and Bob.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jordamus_Prime I would say is inaccessible. For all of Fallon's fame, he's just dude "That dude", and Darius Rucke… https://t.co/pVcbqsPHv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s an honour to welcome Minister @Bill_Morneau and so many special guests to @CatalystFCAD for a special announce… https://t.co/8YLOEkUKpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all my Carolina friends @FlippenJacob @mattanderson88 @thedags79 @James_Eaton81 @CamilleHall31 @WilliamJHarris https://t.co/8YPydZJecI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rgoalie36 Agreed, but I also don't think that Hak was a good enough coach at the NHL level. You could tell that th… https://t.co/3uLLqgPY30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackimusPrime1 apparently it’s a class B misdemeanor to have sex out of wedlock in Utah too, the caucasity of Utah is wildin]]></document><document><![CDATA[WW has yet to comment on double A's release from the company hmmm wonder why that is what the fuck the point is vince]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bringing this back, and it’s still badass! Magneto’s line is still amazing 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilcar 👍🏻 Hay uno sobre cómo trasferir perfiles de un ordenador a otro en el que muestras brevemente cómo crear u… https://t.co/5enxilHZLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a little bit of footage from last nights #peopleprogram Office Grand Opening Event at ⁦@MilwaukeeMPS⁩ Rufus Ki… https://t.co/smGCR3sal6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DDaddyMinaj @BrianMcLight You need to eat with some more white people. Believe me,we season our food and we  know… https://t.co/uDSWPLiw3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apple Music has a 2012 remaster of the 1991 Massive Attack album Blue Lines. #NowPlaying #triphop Be Thankful for W… https://t.co/LH3zzXQh7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder: Wrestling (Coed MS) - Prairie Heights  Middle School 3/4/19 05:00 PM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shrimp, avocado and slaw on @califlourfoods mini wraps #lowcarb #cauliflower #ALToRnativeEats #ALToRnativeFacts… https://t.co/IXEuBis8gI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @Jim_Jordan Why did Trump employ Cohen all these years if Trump knew Cohen was a liar? Duh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHerreraReports @_MiaHolmes @WMCActionNews5 Awesome!  Next, to give her “real world” experience: make sure the lap… https://t.co/gqVpFQIT8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I was out running errands and capturing some Munzee myths and nomads, I decided to make it a two-fishwich day… https://t.co/mAR1T5PpVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one knows how much I love and respect my brother. Congrats bro, you deserved this. #chloeandjon #marriage @ Jack… https://t.co/x3Lvi8Ulci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seton Hall will be that #11 that a lot of folks put in the Sweet 16 but the #3 seed they knock out of their bracket… https://t.co/FaFmksKS75]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did it get really dusty around anyone else when Bryce Brown went into the stands to hug his family? 😢 #WarEagle]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one :  My dad: kids these days don’t know how to where a god damn hat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricRWeinstein @RubinReport here’s what I see... https://t.co/6NFPzzhQQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonnnnylingo I think people are less outraged at what Russ said and more upset that Jazz fans will probably get blamed for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 15,  and I just finished another amazing cardio workout Powerhouse Gym International rocking to the mix of… https://t.co/omvvvhvljT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The. Dems are giving the GOP more and more ammunition to use in 20/20 everyday ! Keep up the good work Dumo Crates !]]></document><document><![CDATA[So i just have to wish my coach happy valentine’s and i’ll get credit for the class?  Wow coach privilege 😂👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que gacho que a ninguna de mis amigas les gusten las películas de terror como a mi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgrahamspectre Can't do it.  I find the accusers highly suspicious, their varying stories flawed, the evidence lacking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELLO THE THIRD TIME I HAVE EVER CRIED OVER BB IS NOW https://t.co/cwQaQLVG7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/rB9pYbiA3U  #hyatt #worldofhyatt #freehotel https://t.co/kg4yB5qNcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Spike My Drink by Jacelyn https://t.co/FGhwCvWoym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJZNY @CNN @MSNBC @CBS @NBCNews @NPR In Portuguese Pedo means something else.. P peace is an E exchange D of Double O OwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parlaying w big homie @Yelawolf @J11isJayOnes @ #creekwaterwhiskey Carolina release after party https://t.co/PH1ENCHVqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it to the party! Well..sort of! Look behind me! #ECET2SW https://t.co/sEO4Nr7dMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Normie_Democrat Ike tried to stop Goldwater’s nomination, but would never go public with his oppositon.  And he di… https://t.co/EcBFIHQtpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and My Sweetheart on the Ferry boat to Friday Harbor 25 years ago...Still love this Girl...Happy Valentine's Day😍 https://t.co/FUmS7hfuZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Barrett 82A1 50 BMG Rifle from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $9000! #gungiveaway #winagun… https://t.co/BfXE5CzyZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fernando Chavez started the RnR Washington DC Half Marathon! https://t.co/SNnek2b1V8 #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg! My queen is following me now @SophieASlut #QueenOfCockdestroyer  Please follow her guys @SophieASlut  and give… https://t.co/DISK5oanzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usey0urbra1n @GutterGarbage @onederwood @Matt_the_Hulk @SenSanders James Madison was a proponent of that approach.… https://t.co/o5MBq3qTsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Para planear el futuro, también es importante pensar a quien le importas y a quien le vales madres.  Este consejo l… https://t.co/kib79H2hfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[My review of ALIEN DOMICILE https://t.co/ke4ZILfigw @RonGizmo @Talk2Cleo @sccart1 @palkodesigns @EmilieFlory… https://t.co/ae89gW3yea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KobeBackup_ A bunch of knowledgeable fans still acknowledge what he’s doing out there, but our bigs are bad and ou… https://t.co/KRuuF78Vj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megthaplug @BayFromVa Lmao if my dog ain’t riding for me like this I don’t even want him😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BearcatsRadio @gossmata58 @StewieGilchrist @ChadBrendel @AeroApe51 Definitely can concur!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went down an r/ajax rabbit hole re: FDB, and now I'm sad. from years ago amid 4 titles in 6 years, the only +'s I… https://t.co/cHgMbW0ZRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! Former minister at the former Methodist Episcopal Church now occupied by @NorthStreetCC.   Happy Anna Howard S… https://t.co/sO1n5gfSDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Warrior IPA by @HonorBeer @ Growler USA — https://t.co/D5Xnpx3uwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheering on @drurypanthers from Des Moines today via @GLVCSN. Go Panthers! https://t.co/p130K5wcBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems like football season just ended, but Clemson starts spring practice tomorrow. Here are five storylines for… https://t.co/Qr00JaKxkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanR_007 Match madness not all the teams but we can definitely host the final 4  And if we can hold ultra at bay… https://t.co/A4TkkjuMB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@subschneider I said “also” and having more than one example is usually considered@good supporting evidence when making a point, that’s why.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronCh7Weather @WKBW @KatieMorseNews @EdDrantch @ThuyLanWKBW @NewsRadio930 Nope! Got the day off!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even Fernando Llorente has scored now, Dortmund have really fallen apart this half. #TOTBVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm in favor of reparations, and I'm  currently leaning towards Bernie. I think the reality is that reparations is… https://t.co/qrpMlfh7GD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoyed meeting with my representative @RpSensenbrenner staff yesterday. Had a great conversation about… https://t.co/YUaAoAUo8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Secondly toriyama has said that goku lives for nothing but fighting as we all witnessed as he brought about. The po… https://t.co/rKgeFbF7FY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tokyolincoln420 Glad to hear that buddy I would also try to get hold of some RSO Oil or concentrate it will do won… https://t.co/nS4ZpvHB9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seadavis7 @chngin_the_wrld @tdbrothers @tmc_RN @rs_mcneil @alexhkral Happy to participate. Just let me know where and when.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Themedicalclips @ForTheMen That looks like you will break someone’s rib cage with that damn machine .   I work in… https://t.co/PsaIMHYdSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[New pics of @Compuware 16u boys now up on their @eliteprospects pages ... Check 'em out! #HicklingImages @mhick1953… https://t.co/SUGvYA2bLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notthefakeSVP For us, it is $1 for teeth that come out at home, $5 if the dentist was involved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BritBox_US He reminds me of myself and I sometimes get scared watching this show. I literally said a few years ago… https://t.co/fNb5xkIYGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something as simple as sesame seeds on the crust puts this over the top 👌 #pizza https://t.co/e4eHZHcUV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperEliteTexan @BlueSea1964 @IlhanMN Deport her back to her country. She does not deserve to be here. She is tota… https://t.co/MLAYjOkERq]]></document><document><![CDATA[CASINO is one of the biggest cod maps i've ever seen and they decide to make it a 5v5 playlist]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FanmadeHeaven Right in my back yard. #Tennessee literally paints the picture of my #HandmadeHeaven @MarinaDiamandis https://t.co/YfynqeJjE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EconTalker I believe it was the warehousing and ownership of those higher-risk tranches that we’re throwing the fi… https://t.co/ZkTZvcUssB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conner_kruger @TalbertSwan If you read what she actually said to him, it will make you even more furious! It did m… https://t.co/aK5l2GIjuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to "To the Kindness of God", the wonderful new album by @Michael_Card now streaming on @amazonmusic  Exce… https://t.co/nBsxIjJpGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #StargateRewatch continues with Universe 2x18 “Epilogue” it’s interesting to see how it could have been for the… https://t.co/dasHai9yaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reggieaqui it’s literally so gorg in person I can’t get over it/believe I get to climb all over it. And thank you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louisvazquezTX @S3kr3tto Yo también porque donde me tratas mal no me quedo no olvides que muchos de los que opinan… https://t.co/SwDKkIj197]]></document><document><![CDATA[Detail of a bat that is part of the chain walkway barrier in the Haunted Mansion #HauntedMansion #Disneyland https://t.co/yfUSzykdlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mathis dances when the office comes on. So yeah definitely Brandon’s child 🤦🏽‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OmerKFarooqi @ItsDavery Let’s worry about the Lakers making the Playoffs first... or worry about Lebron making the Playoffs. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSingletonxo @selenagomez Same. Alot of Selenas old songs got me through a broken heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOtherCoachA @IceColdJones_ 😂😂 oh my programs have been in A LOT of not just @Twitter posts but highlight reels!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auribes37 Sooooooo offsides but that’s the Premier League were officials are as bad as the NBA and NFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Polunatic @gordperks Don’t forget customized camper vans cause the big guy don’t like to fly🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Where do they find all the room for all the hate in their "Basket of Deplorables?" Maybe Meghan McCain… https://t.co/9qVoiJtkRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad news. 😔 I’ll be listening to @the_prodigy all day today. #RIPKeithFlint 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[MKT 4900 SKYPE TALK with OU grad Taylor Van Neste. Talking about cold calling, lead conversion and what it’s like t… https://t.co/8yYvMq86VG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life goal is to be as cool as the ref who just majestically ripped off his black jacket right as the national an… https://t.co/AJGq6dGJTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[What am I going to do with all this #NationalCheddarDay cheese? 😂 https://t.co/7iYOwrZXyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CowboysJJT  @190Mitch Good evening fellas. i am ready to charge my music battery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fernand25138914 @Raging_Stallion @ClubInfernoXXX @devinfrancoxxx @TomasBrandxxx @RoccoSteeleNYC Agreed 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoan Moncada from right side as Abreu looks on. #whitesox https://t.co/fviK4CgGPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marindmode @Corey1911 @TMZ And R Kelly knew what the JUDGE told him at the last hearing, the JUDGE told him if he… https://t.co/EGzWihXo9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[31 minutes into playing Watford, Liverpool was ahead multiple goals in each of their last 4 matches against Watford… https://t.co/wqzdWqT3Jl]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, here you are, impressionable 20 year old, and you have made it to studying with a Famous Teacher. Maybe you are… https://t.co/juCMwrms7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigitalTrends This is not good for the game of pool. I don't see the purpose. Like training wheels for your bike.… https://t.co/a1wi02DAQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pulloutday21 Is it too late to ask for “Working Girl” by Dolly Parton? Perfect companion to “9 to 5”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamLicamele that Bohemian was really good the climate is rich for the aforementioned also all the more reason… https://t.co/Ch7Tr4M9zN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Involving the audience is a key factor in a successful live performance. No matter what genre]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como treinar seu dragão 3 é emocionante por causa do final, mas o filme em si é uma bosta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't look now but #UCF women not going away in #AAC championship vs #UConn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Power of the purse &amp; rule of law threatened by @POTUS threatened move.  Resist.]]></document></documents></author>