<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@UPonMSNBC @lolaogunnaike Probably his career and life in general as he knows it.....it is over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the border line ❌ BH ⭕️ WeHo ❗️with two of my favorites 🌸 hotelbeverlyterrace  . . .  . #presidentsweekend… https://t.co/XllMozjcXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just spent an entire lecture talking about the history of comics and Captain America and how they’re all allegory’s… https://t.co/pZiTxYUk8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Annie_Andersen @RepDonohue Please post a vote board pic when they take the SB 150 vote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to bed on Sunday night knowing that you’re waking up to Monday morning is dreading 😓😢😅😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Gordon Ramsey’s daughter have the same name and are the same age ... i like my name so much better now]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Barnes &amp; Noble Café in Willow Grove, PA https://t.co/yCnM5bL3ZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Democrats, remember this....  “A man I’m proud to call my friend. A man who will be the next president of the U… https://t.co/b4nnDTr9Vb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @StrahanAndSara Where is the #ArthurAshe movie?!! That would be a fabulous biopic! 🎾🏆 https://t.co/nYDoZ3aqa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate your lady friends today!! Happy Galentine’s Day!! We all know how special friendships can be but sometime… https://t.co/BwGfU39UDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students from Urban Prep West are heading to Springfield to ask legislators to keep a commission intact that could… https://t.co/3tnTziSfNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisgirlsaam001 @ASimmons32 @tristenmadison Good Luck; Thursday  VS @byusoftball &amp; @AggieSoftball Friday  Vs… https://t.co/n0vvWrhF2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffP888 I just sent you a note yesterday! Great minds think alike! :D https://t.co/76k7NbIXc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[At MedExpress, we empower our team members with the support and resources they need to provide great care. We have… https://t.co/DO9B6zJYec]]></document><document><![CDATA[learnibg some valuable info about #IGTV at #HOME in #Nashville with @rickbarkermusic and @schzimmydeanie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelg_96 @tweetgrubes Well technically doctors are scientists soooo.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the latest graduate of Bell City’s Fundamentals program - Christel! ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ When you see her i… https://t.co/787L4YcOfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s not forget that before 1619 there was 1501!  I agree with you Bishop and as Brother Yusef stated, “ No one sh… https://t.co/33UAPzTCI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madisonchase69 Let me help ya a little. 🤷🏼‍♀️☺️ https://t.co/X0GkMtK1v5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never ate the chocolate. It was always something I could count on every year from my dad. Apparently, I've lost h… https://t.co/c2ytZFMeNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[And apparently he changed his mouth, jaw and eyes b/c huh this isn’t the same person...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Non_MSM_News That is ok, I read your profile and I thought why would a @realDonaldTrump suporter respond like that… https://t.co/hxgkd4awwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you watching tonight?  I know I am!!! #GreysAnatomy #Greys #MakingTVHistory]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basquiat exhibit was incredible. Go see it! @ The Brant Foundation Art Study Center https://t.co/JujZsGroKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump: Obama was on brink of 'a big war' with North Korea. Not true, ex-Obama aides say #Topbuzz https://t.co/Gyxo1CKGWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeicks @orgoodenough @VTLawSchool Are you and @harmbavinck still working on the Codex project?]]></document><document><![CDATA[How in heck does trump have a 90% approval rating among republicans. I will say it again. We cant let down our guar… https://t.co/Z0FBSlFxXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man got me a 3 day pass to 24 hour fitness to see how "serious" i am lmao i love him 😂😂👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @aprilbaxter Lock them up Jared sends people to the prince of Saudi to be cut into pieces while Ivanka laughs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like Mother like Son! Yuk. Luke on #MarriedAtFirstSight is just like his Mom. Fake and acts Superior. Stand tall an… https://t.co/NZv8BWdQ9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[In search of someone to write a 12 page lit review for me. Pls, will pay... maybe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all this girl next to me at work was eating flaming hot Cheetos at like 8:00 this morning...I can’t 🤦🏽‍♀️ high school all over again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the record I enjoyed Captain Marvel — back story good — but @Disney STOP PC — it’s killing the culture]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanMuskin @StumpforTrump Oh wow! These shills have been hounding me in comments. I wondered who all they were hara… https://t.co/UxQScXG9dJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best news all day! Get your fat ass away from your bucket of chicken and start digging that ditch that you will nev… https://t.co/eTGupJJJmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m seeing @youmeatsix and @DREAMERSjoinus in less than 2 weeks omfg i’m so excited!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Period 1 https://t.co/r9mRdsJgva via @YouTube my daughter’s high school creative writing class wrote a parody of “T… https://t.co/kl2T4Pj5V7]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m an introverted intellect who dreams of diamonds and caviar.” I’m available in Atlanta right now! https://t.co/yZ86HbPD3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! Pounding and tapping, loading red words, and other multi sensory activities from @BrainspringOG Phonics First… https://t.co/hFAqnLkBUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No se deja nunca y cuando uno ve esos videos maravillosos de ayer con el presidente encargado @jguaido  no sr puede… https://t.co/AdwaLg3ZJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Lol Shane!! 22 today!   #gingerbrew #hip hop #theresident #artsdistrict @ Resident https://t.co/h0LutjIEnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WardenOfNuts @IronsideBob @Budsmonkey905 @RpmacPaul @bironacad @LeafsLunch1050 @ScottieUpshall @AndiPetrillo… https://t.co/njiG9dSLGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yessssssss JOEEEEE! I see the growth in that man especially over the years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From this day forward AOC shall be known as....  Little Joe. (McCarthy)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delavegalaw I am homeless at they moment with a teenager. Not feeling Valentine's Day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up early today for the @AAA_AutoClubGrp #Employee event this morning.  ❤️ these guys!! https://t.co/gIt2s97QJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[......sadly proven every day here in....and only in..... the USA.  FANATICAL LOVE AND ADDICTION FOR GUNS....Not nec… https://t.co/Hw1saYegv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#boodupchallenge #boodup #challenger #challenges #propstyling #props #weightlossjourney #yass  #getitgirl #viral… https://t.co/4TfvIKBlyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little taste of a spring afternoon and a ride with Fairy ❤️🐎❤️ . . . #Fairy #arabmustang #halfarabian… https://t.co/G6Vy4EktzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie [interpretation]: “Sorry, I was a little too busy trying to show how much I care for the American people tha… https://t.co/JYtBM7Porx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyVisualXXX So scary... 😟 So happy that you and Pily and your family are okay though!! Stay safe!! 🙏🏼🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Me puedes vender” “Y quien te va comprar!?”  😂😂💀💀 mi suegro with the jokes!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump You and CROOKED TRUMP are an embarrassment to our country! RESIGN IDIOTA! https://t.co/UHFc6Jeanp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjakuba @Amin_Touri Love you SO much Jill! 🤗 I appreciate all you do and have done for us!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad and brothers each sent flowers to my mom!!😍 don’t tell me that’s not the cutest thing https://t.co/TSzxmIgH6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t usually let myself think about how much I miss my family but I had a horrible nightmare last night and it’s… https://t.co/s96sIFvbqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can confirm roads are starting to get slick. Saw a truck overturned on my way home. Drive slow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and the Moon and finished Another episode of Gothique Boutique  in the archives at https://t.co/HTBDynVtt3.… https://t.co/BtAlBQThr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DougAnderson @brahmresnik @ChadGuzman @Daniel4PhxMayor This conversation is not Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeattleCrewMom Clap Clap Clap Clap... Trumpster...🤣🤣🤣 NO WALL !!!!  Signed: Queen Nancy https://t.co/o8ZFzUk3BF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSirakas @AlexandriaVA @Ballyshaners @NatGeoPhotos This is way to many themes going g on here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lightning100 @thesisterhood The Sisterhood Band please play, "Half Way" #WomenWhoROCK. https://t.co/JurwvwLbVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NoWallEver #Beto2020 Beto O'Rourke says he would take down existing US-Mexico border wall  https://t.co/ff4z0YAOhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @ChipotleTweets it’s literally a Saturday lunch time how are you out of everything ?! 🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️ defintely goi… https://t.co/M96gJnasJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[VCS Admin Learning the Six (Un)Productive Practices in Mathematics Teaching (and what to do about them) from Juli D… https://t.co/RUYrH4u95o]]></document><document><![CDATA[if people realized how truly expensive hair care is, they REALLY wouldn't want curly hair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaizervonmaanen @strictlyHetero @IKhakistani @zarakayk @JanissaryGuard @Titan05376960 @lArRXJ04NthCLrs @Tokyogreen… https://t.co/cX4hKBGxlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day holding my own face. Some moments I can almost trick my mind, despite my hands not being big or warm enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from @C_Howard2005  -  Reposted from @C_Howard2005 -  @kids_jitta -  We are providing the vibes‼️ •  Y’all… https://t.co/mBBqSmq148]]></document><document><![CDATA[When legalism takes over our lives, we behave as if we are robots.  Things run efficiently according to the rules,… https://t.co/72dHCSVBzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hadn’t really bonded with my car and I was still feeling really sad about my old car but today I lugged the charg… https://t.co/p27DIwEVQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJWatt Sorry but you will always be a true Wisconsinite to me, and that doesn’t require wardrobe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just used "moot" in my paper because I've been really into @FriendsTV this week #Joey #moopoint 😝🐄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christraynor I get it, so far shit isn’t sticking to Trump, but the sheer volume of his crimes has to catch up w.… https://t.co/wzZHhGPOCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got it ... #fabfitfunspringbox .... @fabfitfun @ Woodbridge, Ontario https://t.co/ZSiNveOxjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[We cannot condone hate lets be better humans I know we are capable of being better and teaching our youth to become… https://t.co/T6ObmTFbKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Yawn! My friends suggest I stop retweeting to the nothing burger that is Junior. Too bad he couldn’… https://t.co/bUFRa4RdAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The really great #treetunnel trails at #bettysteflikpreserve  🌳🌲🌴🍃🍂🌾🌿 @ Palm Coast, Florida https://t.co/HnD5uC9a1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lexi_Lonas literally every single one of these is wrong https://t.co/HX4z0WWyMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FarahSoCal @BresPolitico @LeaderHoyer @justicedems I will do the same!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithUrban , @janson_chris (going to see him friday @The IP casino) and @ladyantebellum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Josh heard me crying and woke up to check on me and took care of me until I calmed down. I’d be so lost without him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo.... arcade challenge, let’s get it!!! 🤣 Yeah right, if it were anything like that livestream, all y’all would be… https://t.co/UVBoU8an01]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump What do you call what YOU as the NAZI TRUMP-PUTIN-REPUBL Party are going? YOU ENRICH YOURSELF… https://t.co/4owa9Pq2Zr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOXNashville Thank you to the gentleman who showed compassion and kindness 2 a individual down on her luck. Hopefu… https://t.co/rzJPX2VucX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it when elected officials quote the Bible during session. I’m so glad my tax dollars play a role in his ability to do so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The feeling of losing your best friend, your whole heart , the love of your life really fucking sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of seeing that Momo bitch on my tl she scary af I’m gonna have nightmares]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being justified freely by his grace through the redemption that is in Christ Jesus: https://t.co/D2XHwKzaQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[7:40pm: Cup #4 is a shot of pure liquid gold from Milk and Honey to get me “hardwired” for @haileyknoxmusic https://t.co/HSydJ51fDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M_Schnick @AshleeH27 @smashboardedu That's great! Let me know if I can be of any help]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gettin turnt while watching the oscars, anyone else? #tequila #photoitooktoday #allthesespeechesmakinmecry #blessed https://t.co/uMHp39SWFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen Justin Amash your question was forthright and amazing. Do not let the bots come after for " no" doing your job… https://t.co/tVK7OjN1Fn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyTstout @SotehPR @steven_seibel @KenCageRepo @coyoteweather10 @HappyAndFreex13 @PhilliesMike @jonmorosi… https://t.co/AaWioAZoQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at what our trainee @SamiYewman wore today on #InternationalWomansDay2019 😍🙌🏼  She told me she was treating to… https://t.co/cqb0Zcn0q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrunoFernandoMV So proud that you’re a Terp!  Thank you!  🐢🏀❤️ https://t.co/P7EQ7RXUoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever wonder how someone is doing?? Like, how do they really exist???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IIIDeaton These people are Satan worshippers no Christian worship Satan and witchcraft Christians worship God]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm missing a smile 😃 @ Havana Hookah Bar &amp; Lounge https://t.co/9JI84Pemba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlim33 @NewYorkStateAG @TishJames The current senate will continue to do Trump's bidding. They will never overri… https://t.co/QKleLkgJc3]]></document></documents></author>