<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Trump just responded to Patriot owner’s prostitution arrest with a shameful response - https://t.co/CBd1qcZG7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing to see where it starts and ends, I’m honored to say that I have been apart of a brand new store openin… https://t.co/Mp30d6jeFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me walking into work this morning after DanceBlue. https://t.co/oRkf463fNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenSterner @annajc16 You are so right Ken. I would not want any cruise. Lol I still love that NE game. Even if AB… https://t.co/LPLSbo0IBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDaveWilk @techboss56 How can it come back? That was a fear of mine...that the bill really wasn't gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Valentine’s Day my boyfriend got me a necklace that when you shine a light on it, it reads “I Love You” in 100… https://t.co/FBHXJt0wIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mejoshkirtley ummmm it DEFINITELY worked!!!!! lmaooo i’m like damn my shits look like m&amp;m’s hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greenville’s family Steam night was so much fun! Mrs. Mack and Mrs. Wolf had students create a chick house for thei… https://t.co/cdihbok9VR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though there are jobs, most are not full time offerring no benefits and many are mimimum wage requiring the av… https://t.co/DYQVcOlMGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sajazz @biaginger They need veterans to pitch innings.  he will have lots of time to pitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKayGranger $1.375 billon for border wall/fence/barrier is NOT a compromise, nor is it even close to a compromis… https://t.co/dwlpXHPSGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 91st Annual Academy Awards💫 @ Loews Hollywood Hotel https://t.co/jTHY05FKth]]></document><document><![CDATA[🕴Con Sue Photography and Design🤩  🌂Like our photos...Follow our IG 🥰  😍This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/5kp7T1i8L7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EastBayMajority @takebackousd And Senator Harris said she sees you, Governor Newsom has fast tracked regulations o… https://t.co/GkRgiBTA6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TorontoStar @MarilynLouise5 former teacher here and no fan of standardized testing. abolish this relic from Harris… https://t.co/Yjl2d2KpFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the opportunities that #misditech and @beasley_pride give my child! #codemonsters Happy to see this team gro… https://t.co/C6zO8woaF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecNielsen @fema You had this to say about caging babies. Nielson: "It's a detention space "Coleman: "Does it diff… https://t.co/xes4YJkuYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beers300 @Shawn172510 @CelinaSummers @madsatan6969 @Gina_VFL @BoRansom I'm here to serve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SedaRaul @primerahora @ricardorossello No parece que respete mi opinion, En todo caso le podemos dar catedra de lo… https://t.co/NjfvHPRnf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MckBecca @MiddletonJody Awe! That’s exciting - and no blurring you out!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPac94054821 Hell yeah. And it’s not greasy. Burnt and the grease is actually what I cooked my eggies in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It don’t matter where u work. It’s about to hustle. I know ppl making 25 and hour but only working 30 hours a week.… https://t.co/kgBUXfx2ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone ever look at your dogs and just smile and gush about how adorable and precious and perfect they are? 💕🐾😍… https://t.co/fHdezc5On2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hate guys that can’t take NO as an answer. Like gtf, grow the fuck up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenjbarnes1 @keckery Hey! I’m usually Row 28 by the toilet 🚽 And I bring 🍕 on board. As long as it’s aisle💺]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE MOST DISCUSING VOTE...EVER..VOTE THEM ALL OUT...DEAR GOD Dems block 'born alive' bill to provide medical care t… https://t.co/oIVvLwBIwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleasant afternoon watching the rain and hummingbirds chatting with my Uncle. @ Rancho Santa Fe, California https://t.co/0kzuMDGnhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimSchuss If you turn up the volume on that video you can hear me trying to hold back my giggles at the end 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay this is talent and I hope you made some mad bands for this &amp; every night you work 😍 just woww]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING: @NCPD and @NCFDSC on scene of a crash at the intersection of Otranto Road and Rivers Ave. Officers have… https://t.co/3UDw80NliR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kansaskim88 Wish I could say that,  but this is definitely the worst one in many, many years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paralyzed from the neck down in college which required him to re-learn how to walk, @Tali43 got involved in state g… https://t.co/JeENQHiqIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come help us @NMStateWBB celebrate these 5 amazing seniors today at 12pm vs Chicago St, see you there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rkelly #jussiesmollet #robertkraft Happening now ... Chicago police chase... 🤣😀😄 https://t.co/seiFnbvbj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KahleBailey That looks awful I do not miss the snow😂😂 but you look great!!😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought of a “hill I would die on” that I would like to submit to @GraceParra360,@michaelaWat, @DanaSchwartzzz,… https://t.co/jrprZgbaXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love being with @SBC_NOoltewah this morning for Impact Missions Conference! @ Ooltewah, Tennessee https://t.co/vGRagGhGcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wctfct you picked well! @RolaDagher is an inspiration and a WORLD-CLASS Leader. We @Cisco are so of her and the im… https://t.co/CkkDOkwd8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I switched my cell phone provider from rogers to Public Mobile and I feel alive. *this is not a paid endorsement*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaltCityGuy @Bethenny @AOC @SkinnygirlBrand What is sticking is vote for Trump not socialism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toni_poulos You should inform him if he would like to acquire the fake abs via sun tan he’s gonna want to reverse… https://t.co/tjpScU2TK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely a true blessing for me to compete at a Conference my freshman year as a team, and become the 2019 Southl… https://t.co/3cTwAYAXlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[2. Liv Ullmann is astonishing and all of her performances are powerful, including my favorite in SHAME. https://t.co/VmU2pNfnyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone needs proof the privatization of government projects does not improve them, please look at Oklahoma’s roads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megabus KINGSTON plz help a girl out with her thesis travel expenses ty megabus i kno you’ll pull thru xoxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhhhh happy birthday @tylerthecreator you fucking genius https://t.co/n7wjpqE6jB]]></document><document><![CDATA[God I know you gave these hard things  to use for your glory.   I had a girl message me about her PCOS today. I was… https://t.co/wPFpk6lGvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What hat are you wearing with this statement? You know that as @potus this kind of self promotion… https://t.co/tc7i0WpWQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/FUQWM48222]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT Everyone needs to stay alert here.  We CANNOT let there be another Iraq where there were no WMD's.… https://t.co/Xou7uQnOjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[played guitar to let out some study frustration but i still wanna take a nap]]></document><document><![CDATA[So grateful to be awake but let me tell you.. when that alarm goes off at 5’ish a.m. it’s pure abuse.. reminds me o… https://t.co/42hCVlNg6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone ever shave their cat? This is not a dirty/euphemistic question. Wilford B. has long been disinterested in gr… https://t.co/KwPHMHRdWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylanmsmitty @MitchellMeeks11 Yes but it goes farther than that, they are fake humans. There are some people who should never have kids!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So annoyed with @CassieRandolph like r we watching the same show? What did you think this show was about? Perfect r… https://t.co/AvpV0LZC8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebruenig It was great to meet you tonight! I hope you got some good things from Buffalo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Public_Justice @realDonaldTrump Thank you. I retweeted the article and this tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moving to Skyler and I’s new house today and only ended up on the ditch once!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjschneider_777 Sending you a blessing and energy to your cousin. Not sure what his prognosis may be, but, I can s… https://t.co/ouhsh4ugh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatBrzozowski I once had small children. Talk about picky eaters - one would eat only three foods for the longest… https://t.co/57kR1t6Q6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealPhilX @davidbergman You F-c-I- g  R-c-k Praying to god I meet you one day]]></document><document><![CDATA[the choir is rehearsing “spirit of the living god, fall afresh on me” and im already crying. so that’s how today is… https://t.co/epurSSitin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baemaxbb Don’t ever be embarrassed by someone else acting like a crackbaby mads ❤️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CattMcCreary @NicholasJOng2 @always5star @KKEntGroup @BCLONA @wordman54 @HighheelsDes @JeremyPalmer7 @SteveKubota… https://t.co/1f74cvOc2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know what is happening at Cameron but I know I like it! Go, Wake,  go! #WakevsDuke]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨"DNA links man to 1997 Medina County cold case rape, 4 homicides https://t.co/8nluIZzmIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my brother helps me plan the trip to Seattle if my best friend and I get tickets to see @maluma next Friday lol 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#miamiff #afterparty #knightheroes @knightfdn @MiamiFilmFest me_3.769 @ JW Marriott Marquis® Miami https://t.co/oB045j1i2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anton47492193 @TonyaRBlue1 @JessieLynnJL @JessieLynnFans @BradHeyden @KFearri @RoverDov123 @petergraigs… https://t.co/6JitAEWCxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnieRiceStL @WJohnson68 Agreed! My 6 months in Cape Town were life changing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agent provocateur used to be the sexiest, most provocative luxury lingerie brand that cost $1200+ for bras alone, a… https://t.co/AuqFJcjxxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear to god if someone touched this black leopard! You gonna be extinct😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me going crazy when my friend is 30 mins late to a fucking 14 courses meal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I had on the A/C but this morning had to turn on the heat!!! Good gracious!!! I wish the weather would ma… https://t.co/mWuHgiMhL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyInternationalWomensDay #QuoteOfTheDay ❤️ @ Braselton, Georgia https://t.co/MYOYgQLhfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have some really great friends that I’m forever thankful for. But I wish I had a best friend that I can hang out… https://t.co/rVLiDU5Y6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamBroadCity on @TyltEnt—I will miss ’Broad City’ the most https://t.co/FSlmHvAdyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[man look this why im glad ion fw messy ass girls 😂😂😂 y’all worried bout everything I got goin on but not worried bout YOURSELF. tragic]]></document><document><![CDATA[The calls are coming from inside the house. (By the house, I mean the music industry.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[NASCAR MONSTER RACE 🏁🏁🏁 (@ Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA) https://t.co/9UHFEYPTKN https://t.co/LchXv8PSs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is in the air! Get ready for spring at gallery andrea! #luxuryhomes #scottsdaleartgalleries #interiordesign… https://t.co/g7visQivvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iownjd 1. Being surrounded by my family and 2. Taking time to hike outside and soak up fresh air!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Southeast70D @Creativempathy3 @PwrCane1 @joshua_nimmons @ACMeyor @establishmentno @Mattytwo2 @LeonWhi63670221… https://t.co/miWILnGaqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[we have @MissioMusic, @bunburyfestival, and @twentyonepilots happening all within three months of each other and i honestly can't deal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dunesgirl1 @LMAO_in_Fla Sad. It’s not what god intended when he said love the neighbor https://t.co/KgeQJAG7zf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is me tomorrow ‘https://t.co/pl8CV1Ix00 #CAA2019 #lasimaginistas #RevitalizeNotMilitarize #ABOGfellow #]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨today is yr last chance to see me at @RedTieGentlemen for at least a month ✨ 15832 Stagg St ✨  ➡️ I’ll be dancing… https://t.co/DKYB4NprXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao I was scrolling through old photos to look for something and I found a screenshot of when this boy I liked rej… https://t.co/du5z91P3zZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkepticReview89 @pammalamma Maybe we can cut in @SamHarrisOrg or @joerogan to help us develop it. They're straight… https://t.co/WV97opjpqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIVEAWAY: Win a Haltech Elite, Wideband, Harness and Tuning Courses https://t.co/QkNZCl2nYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Career Less Ordinary: Pioneering Lesbian Editor Judy Wieder Tells Her Tale https://t.co/n8cH4UVdhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get home and realize you’ve had mustard on your shirt all night/day. #winning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_ast777 @satribesman @Jj051301 @CatholicForLife @ArleneKowalczyk @CatholicPierogi @DavidHarris707 @AnneKabes… https://t.co/6Xke2yOZPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monstervoyage @caribpearltours @tripgourmets @CultureTrip @MadHattersNYC @MyVirtualVaca @always5star @Sostraveluk… https://t.co/PWxI6jOZW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que nuestra oración sea por #venezuela y por la pronta recuperación de la democracia y la libertad. #filvex… https://t.co/Kjkris7nmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite places. Tonight we’re seeing Goodfellas on 35mm. 👌🏻 https://t.co/CJ27qiHeUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#weliketoparty @mandy_fish jatemelon _llomy_ @Latina_Fabulous @ Birmingham, Michigan https://t.co/YBnk9soERt]]></document><document><![CDATA[An important reminder, especially since the trend of consumer expectations of transparency is predicted to continue… https://t.co/hxyxIURdCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at FAA? We're hiring in Birmingham, AL! Click for details: https://t.co/rKQHtkXaID #aviation #WomenSTEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vaya Isss mamita ahí le dan la plantita para que produzcap más leche para su bebé... El chiste de la noche de verdad 😂🤪🙊]]></document></documents></author>