<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DustyLost300lbs Damn! The left pic looks bigger than some of the others I’ve seen you post. As always, well done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awillgrapplin Hope you everything turns out ok, get well. Always a message away if you need it]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% worth standing out in the cold lol @ Holey Toledough - Handcrafted Doughnuts https://t.co/VKlRNvh4dx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougdirt24 do you think Pete Rose reads Reds Minor League blog?  its plausible, an old handicapped is a glutton for information.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Collier Regional Park - Rec Plex https://t.co/nZbqZFAIXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[de eso q descubres q hay un nuevo #fan para las carreras 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻 bien atentó mi compadre viendo el recap de #baja500… https://t.co/O5NFSw6WUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope everyone is having a good week! If you or someone you know is fighting a custody battle, well there is hope! W… https://t.co/QEkk0Q9vyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack @9975Ts She has altimers, getting sicker too. https://t.co/9wSM91ol66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro, I posted this on FB today. I would sure love help articulating a response to the absolute beating I am… https://t.co/2zIhkVti4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve met Latour a couple times at conventions and words fail to express how happy I am for him. He’s a great dude a… https://t.co/lQHXPSIBgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fake pain cream sold at The Arnold, to Columbus first responders, local cuple admit. https://t.co/hGcwIwbPIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young Zyire turned 1 today. bandupzy congrats nephew. #FamilyStrong #GreatNewphew @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/TPsMCdETH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbominableFuzz @giggleloop You would think given what I eats and how much I run I’d be skinny by now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump Do you even know the history behind the nobel bomb peace prize, nobel invented a… https://t.co/mbhDok2bpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JamesHarden #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP #MVP… https://t.co/IW6JoIz9dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AMEN and God bless WORLD have a great day don't forget to SMILE @DennisJBolt 🔱⚡BOLTIBOLTZ CAN'T STOP WON'T STOP Be… https://t.co/bYJZcmfOlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigCo62 @FoxNews You gotta be kidding? #Nonononononooo! https://t.co/FKJjjOqn4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t matter how many ⭐️ you had, how many offers you had, or what you were ranked in HS once you get to colle… https://t.co/SpeN8rqr4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to Disney for like the 5th time In less than a year. And I still feel like a excited little kid every time https://t.co/wYe6Qs2pAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ethel_Soriano Muchas felicidades que sean muchos más compartiendo información y ayudando a la gente ... Abrazo reg… https://t.co/7sBknAeUbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you imagine how painful if would be to hit ya leg on that bed at night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinHuff @kmartel_sports @AdamSparks @joerexrode I love this thread. Especially as it begins encompassing more p… https://t.co/tmuZb4v6ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemiFiendRSA @BigOnAnime Did you try 3 or just hearing it’s bad? If you liked 1 give it a try. It’s great. Most pe… https://t.co/srpJM6BCAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjornorama @rogbennett Fair play on that comment. Not even our great #9.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChacocII @SuchockiJason @CigarCosmonaut @catclawtheatre The best part was , I got them for about $100 of on an auction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC I DID NOT SIGN ON FOR THE VINDICTIVENESS !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC CAPITALISM IS ALL ABOUT SUPPLY DEMAND AND PROFIT BEING THE BOTTOM LINE .WHEN DOES GREED FOR MORE BECOME A MAJO… https://t.co/UlAqPRc9yS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a great night hanging with some of the coolest! pulpogajate bravopercussion quimcastello #musicians… https://t.co/y9MrSM7yRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exhaustion. Photo Cred: @evanmichael/photobohn • • • #Jumpsuit #Insomniac #Zara #Mirror #Sleepy #Instamood #BedHead… https://t.co/lB3ScQvhjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[this new alexander mcqueen is fucking garbage.... y’all need me on ya team]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pbaez87 Pull or get shuffled. No follow the leader in Ohio. They come to race.  #PlayMVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everytime I look up from my cubicle I see someone staring back. #3rdshiftlife #dwightschrute #officelifeatnight @ D… https://t.co/v6jFm5Mz0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNEWS @FOXNEWS Trump have signed a bunch of meaningle… https://t.co/Tq033ThNZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @ALaForce @WWE_MandyRose @KaceyMusgraves @KelseaBallerini @MarenMorris @Danielle_NBC4… https://t.co/lCCUo9id8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyIanStein @Jilchrest @CAGVNews looks like the law breakers are the ones demanding more laws, that infringe on… https://t.co/ZhZZ7UtPRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTilehurstEnd This season I only care about being 1 point in front of 22nd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God, I hate Nick Stahl. Here’s a hot take for you. the best version of John Connor is the unborn fetus inside Sarah… https://t.co/5LSkX3heay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@captainshimmy @strangefate_dr @DCComics @TomKingTK @Walmart Where did you read or see this??]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIRLS GO TO COLLEGE AND GET TAG TEAMED BY A FRAT HOUSE THEN THINK THEY THE SHIT 😂😂 sorry luv, you’re just a whore...😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇦👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss Anna! anna_daschenko The White RACE Ukrainian BLONDES👑🇺🇦 Women Are The MO… https://t.co/DP3j99Z7TQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[That POS just got up on the House floor and spewed his venom, now let’s see what he’s got in his closet!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you know ANY family that has been effected by drugs?  Stop the flow of drugs by a STRONG border security and bar… https://t.co/X60OoHjNL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slump3r @CCSesports @TyTangles Thanks for being a wonderful liaison to the French community. Your job introduction… https://t.co/QG1cCC4Frr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because Trump=Controversy =Cash. It has been that way since the beginning. The MSM will do everything it can to kee… https://t.co/y5SMLPfg4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit this thread! It is an intimidating amount of cool manga written by women just ready to drain your wallet.… https://t.co/aruF4X0jRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix I want to give a huge kudos to Kim Joy for helping me battle hackers from Egypt and China to wrestle my ac… https://t.co/MY8vRYLXCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big - 12 basketball,  West Virginia at Baylor on ESPN- U. #GoEEEERRRZ  11:11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikMatthews16 @chicagotribune I don't think so. Its in ya schools, but not on the news. Day1USA HISTORY 3/5/1770… https://t.co/8qOMLfhM20]]></document><document><![CDATA[These headlines are always so dramatic with fentanyl because they know that saying “a gram” wouldn’t be as shocking… https://t.co/SrkY7RLNrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh some hilarity. Famous Movie Quotes | True Cute Best Love Quote : Famous Movie Love Quotes::::::: THIS MOVIE...… https://t.co/a00tRN84tt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaron Mosby, 12/20/18. #photooftheday #photographer #photography #treyvisions #treyvisionsphotography #Atlanta #ATL https://t.co/YbZtPCWMVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re at @TheSecondCity talking improv and making it in the comedy business with director @anthonyleblanc, part of… https://t.co/Ga2eTIN3uZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You definitely don’t want to hear this but, truly, sugar is the enemy. Stick with real fruit if you ever want somet… https://t.co/AqV2EJRXlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hands down the most exciting basketball game I’ve ever seen.  Congrats @BC_Hoops well deserved! #statebound https://t.co/MgSUqpaNmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Algo a se pensar Galo levou 3 gols do Danubio....Vamooo treinar e prestar atenção Galooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right outside MuchMusic on Queen West, @MarvelEntCA has a "Stanley Video" pop-up shop for #CaptainMarvel !!! Love t… https://t.co/l5FJZGvs7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump SK really has nothing to worry about. The drills didnt keep them safe, it just cost us… https://t.co/Zkv6DLWVJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterSupport : I don't understand. Everytime I say something bad about President Trump that are negative, you ei… https://t.co/MwIcJIw1DO]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's the difference between a Defined Benefit and Defined Contribution Pension?  https://t.co/GyKtVSYzAh… https://t.co/nIUy1D2cH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYRARACING: NO TRAINING AT AQUEDUCT OR BELMONT. WE PLAN ON RACING TODAY.  Reply STOP to opt-out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se lè moman malè pou w konn si w gen bon zanmi! #AyitiNouVleA #fanmdjanm #DemenMiyò #SaturdayThoughts #ChimenZansèt]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’ve pretty much given up on this season, but the bleakest thing going forward is that even if we fire Luke (and… https://t.co/WzcF6aBhrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since my job is giving blessing me with overtime, its time to buy some studio/dj gear and collaborate with one of m… https://t.co/Cwua1LtbqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ One and Only Computer Solutions https://t.co/bDiat8HjFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am proud that I don't leave used k-pods behind in a communal Keurig. #coffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday Riviera ⛳ tourney 1.Ricky Fowler (16-1) 2.Brooks kopkea(18-1) 3.Henrik Stenson (66-1)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to say WINTER over SUMMER  my whole life and I finally Can SAY summer over winter...thanks to my niggas this… https://t.co/ulahTq8vQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelixirofLife28 Omg I had the ponytail™️ too. This is the only surviving proof https://t.co/DWz6I1hyn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[An evening downtown cheering on the @Avalanche! #GoAvsGo https://t.co/d2LpkjCmCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is a complete embarrassment to my city, he has done nothing for his district,  except blame white people f… https://t.co/N9Z5l0IdTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost a Black Clover moment. #RisingofShieldHero https://t.co/vHJWN37dSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[“That I may know him, and the power of his resurrection, and the fellowship of his sufferings, being made conformab… https://t.co/taTE3fvI4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hey Donnie ... I got say you look pretty stupid here ... you set up SNL with that ridiculous news… https://t.co/hYki07ryGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, apparently the Steele Dossier was complete bullshit  Michael Cohen just confirmed he never went to Prague  I th… https://t.co/EwsG4gIcBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DPsouthtradtion Few followers that never ever like or reply to any of my tweets.. it’s not hard to figure out if y… https://t.co/vQ9XAGyMyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MOMiSHStyle @JakotsuReborn @WWE_MandyRose Yeah, but that was not just some heat. To be honest, I felt for Ronda a… https://t.co/0xoQBxC08s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y la 4T cree que sigue en campaña, ¿qué coño con este video ‘promocional’ de Turismo que no promueve nada? Ah si, s… https://t.co/lx3KC5KzOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is that scene in the first Lego Movie where Emmet discovers what his construction “pals” really think about him]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are heading to... @ Kansas City International Airport https://t.co/ejF7V6KnxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I currently feel bc WTF happened to my glasses. https://t.co/xPG0gR7KKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Krisha 😁😁😁😁 deeper and cooler in tone.. . #hairbyangel #godisgood🙏 @ Hair by Angel Mendoza https://t.co/OgALNeDOOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@franifio And I thought he was going kioken he got so red. https://t.co/4161r5DNcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeMarcusRFNET @GAlexander21 @FB_FilmAnalysis @LeviDamien Five Guys. 😂 if you can get past the stench of moldy potatoes...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold Rainy Day with Thunder and Lightning in Decatur. @ Leons FullService https://t.co/F40qPcerrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check this out!!!  @HilzFuld is da man about tech-town... in THE Start-Up Nation!  Kol HaKavod Hillel!]]></document><document><![CDATA[JFC. It takes less than 30 seconds to wash a nonstick skillet. 🤦‍♀️🤦‍♀️🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobNEastSac @JillAdge lol I remember coming to Sacramento when the planning was done for the old Arco. I was worki… https://t.co/MsLUXKSU7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few clips from today’s very muddy race seeding and best whip contest. Look for mat_spong in the blue jacket (well… https://t.co/ocePkJgVCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AskJaclyn i luved the episode that featured Your Kelly  Farrah's Jill in the army do you remember and/if is it 1 of your favs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csszrr @Swazi4 Would be very easy to change that post affiliation and have the league bank some good PR in a clima… https://t.co/pfINHrqWJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aVeryRichBish It’s obvious tho.. if you can’t see it it’s because you don’t want to]]></document><document><![CDATA[El PAN esta actuando fuera de sus funciones al presentar un extranjero en los recintos plenarios y apoyar a un gobi… https://t.co/yzEHvDyenx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWS_MountHolly @6abcWeather 710am update (new wind gust) from N. Catasauqua, PA (Northampton Cnty): Top wind gust… https://t.co/6ziAuvrgZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always great catching up with my buddy kerrygordyofficial so great seeing ya! @troplv laughfactory_lv @ Tropicana H… https://t.co/v5FCMg8nqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SpoilerAlert  after beating Red Dead Redemption 2 on the ps4 I really feel the ending dragged on too long]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seattle, Washington 🌃 . . . . . #seattle #seattlewashington #longexposure #exposure #freeway #exposurephotography… https://t.co/OBC8RGnmuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethLevine2 @MacroVoices @ErikSTownsend @PatrickCeresna @ritholtz Do you hear the people sing? 🎶🎵 https://t.co/ntXWx6gLbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a short girl is all cute and games until you’re a full grown adult with this childish ass height 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Distant_mirror @Pappiness Can you tell me what Trump did to help put food on your table I'm trying to figure out who to vote for in 2020?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I go after unions because the union I was in for 30 years did nothing for me but lied to me and take my money.… https://t.co/fGw6C4gdzk]]></document></documents></author>