<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[its been at the top of my head since i found out no matter how i try to distract myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newborn ~ musical instrument ~ hobby ~ acoustic guitar - Raising baby to love music, a... https://t.co/LTPacRdQqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shoutabyss I have never agreed with you on anything more then I agree with you on this. https://t.co/fQX4leulIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly this is why I made “Subway” I wanted to completely disassociate myself with tha artists in this.. it’s jus… https://t.co/9r99ydphxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayyy me choca que la gente se ponga lentes que son muy pequeños para su cara.. Se ven ridiculos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshRamsay who sings With you on the bridge for Wish You Were Herr? I can’t figure it out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can sleep at night when you take the time to seek the most peaceful route in life. Seek and you will find the p… https://t.co/5N6j2aJpdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Church. Just drove home from Nashville. Now rushing off to Sunday night church for a few hours. Then work tonight.   I need a nap lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I try so hard to be okay. Every night it's the same routine. I'm sick of it  :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[loswalters beatkitchenbar #felicity #candydelight #chicago #boricuasenchicago #desdepuertorico #sabrosura @ Beat Ki… https://t.co/uGy1gpflZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo! Someone just took a pic for me and said “tell your mom i said hi” 😂 He told me he met her at a show in LA lmao!… https://t.co/haVR9U8hU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So these 2 beauties bought 1 #sundaeexplosion from #cookietruckblanche and came right back to get another! 💗🍪💗 @ Th… https://t.co/PBctOiJ0qv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi! check out how i did in the latest GuruShots Challenge   https://t.co/5b1dMw1LBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love Frenchy but adore Joe Simpson’s sense of humor. It just won’t be the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hotzler Thank you, @Hotzler! It was always great to work with you and your team!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#downtownlife #stairsworkout 👍 (@ Stairs of Death in San Diego, CA) https://t.co/ReQN0jJVx9 https://t.co/zMPpXVFcc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YungGodMarquis @NOOKY954 No one said Obama was stupid ! He was greedy and selfish and willing to give away our lib… https://t.co/xNTqkAeJn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who was front row center at Lemaire?! Is this a lacquered metallic over cashmere/wool? @VVFriedman @CathyHoryn… https://t.co/kaJ1yARG8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyBollard Don’t put me in a category. 🙄 you asked a question, I gave an answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @BreneBrown at home thanks to #SouthBySouthFlu2019 #SXSW https://t.co/AzuGiVgzuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RestoreTrustOrg @SecAzar If only he cared about family separation as much]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thoughts on Lange curling wands? I’m seeing mixed reviews online and don’t want to spend the money if it’s not worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyvewire @ChadLabrie Supposed to be from blocking a shot during VGK game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DominiqueKDoug1 @DavidMora @ShowtimeJones24 @Charlita12 @chestnola @LynnTalks2Much @ladcoleoutda985 @MargaretOrr @RobinRoberts Thanks Dom💞🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great night out! Planning for our dreams to come true with some amazing women at the #canadianladybosses networki… https://t.co/Lwj1raXkGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone link me to video of Gaga winning for Shallow right now. I need to see the speech. You’re an academy award w… https://t.co/SmmsTBP1uh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HappyHippieShan @Sue05471005 @fordnation @MacLeodLisa ALL kids with Disabilities deserve a chance...They ALL deser… https://t.co/0PbDjUWS0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonoatwork @theofficenbc @netflix @thewestwingTV I LOVE the West Wing!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you God for another day please keep Andruw safe and dry working help Shelby give my husband strength and help… https://t.co/wrna7vvSXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murph_mama Yeah I have a ton lol roses and stars and the kids names but not visible lol I don’t look like I’d have a ton but I do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tsmola01 @USGeocaching Bummer! I set my alarm and everything! #usgeocachinghour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisKairo @joanwalsh @pacelattin @TuckerCarlson Thanx, every now and then I say something that makes sense 🤔🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a proposal tonight!!! She said yes!! #bombeauchocolat #caraibechocolatemousse #saltedcaramel… https://t.co/KWzMjWK3wL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My foot was always too big for them, but I always managed to walk around with them💀😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@dinero_diva is giving me life during the @LIFT_Labs @AmplifyPhilly storyslam. https://t.co/QqXU6JPInR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to The Thunder Rolls (Cover) by @ATRhq on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/LDzK0jFAbn https://t.co/nbAX9pRhQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi media naranja El sol a mi luna  Feliz día del amor y amistad!  I love you more 💕 @ Guadalupe River https://t.co/AvD4Fsbpf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you registered?  I’ll be talking about #artsintegration and #steam!  Hope to see you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the Hunt ...Grind never stops🐺 @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/s2tTBmn5f6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clipping your nails while sitting at the gate is kind of weird/gross, right? ✈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter Hay Roseanne you must be related to Ann Coulter and Kellyanne Conway  you all are such high class bitches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone is going to be in Epcot this weekend, you should definitely go visit @ashley24taylor! Her art is pure mag… https://t.co/MdCfnkVYbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #WomensHistoryMonth! Can you name #5WomenArtists? KAM can help! Follow us on social media, and/or stop by to… https://t.co/XqNWbfZAgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[...makes getting to us during traditional hours hard, etc. Why are we not looking at this saying huh, maybe we need… https://t.co/M9kjUFDlPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[brendan chase my purest form of love was shown to you  but now i am letting go i’m releasing the attachment  cuttin… https://t.co/XPZItdnKVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need a better #choice for your child's #education ...learn why you should #ChooseCompass ! #CompassExperience… https://t.co/MlFLMXuyH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YanaizaGallant @OrloAve Thanks to the staff for working so hard to make the data look this way!  #anythingtomakeadifference]]></document><document><![CDATA[SEEING @MumfordAndSons FOR THE FIRST TIME  EVER TODAY AHH https://t.co/sumJSMGA19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottPresler @Davebhaase Hilarious! I won't buy or read lies he told! Lol 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whooooo I can now watch @BranCutler kill it #cutlercomeback  And the best 3 man trio @FrankieKazarian @facdaniels a… https://t.co/8aYOeMMiTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[laughter at it's best. Funny Pictures: 18 of the Weird, Wild &amp; Wacky #laughter #lol #smirk #merry https://t.co/DN3BEmFuBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#movieideas Since Hollywood loves remakes.... A remake of Fritz Lang's 'M' (which is already perfect btw), but Stev… https://t.co/1dbGp7B9E9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ Beto is toast, Why? Any thinking, informed wise person would never want to live where there are no protective… https://t.co/IQSNaCbkba]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @bradmceachern, and congratulations @hjisd!! A great leader for an outstanding district!]]></document><document><![CDATA[so that they can return to their lives as soon as they are able to do so.”  Comparing the number of refugees up til… https://t.co/GruSn5wuR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows @ddale8 Well, NC is quite a distance from Mexico on the geography I studied and I live near the bor… https://t.co/kXFsIYXmkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SprakerLarry Hi Larry! I hope you are doing well. Things are great here in Lynchburg!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom ugh no just no, like who would wear that  Me: I would, it's cute. No? Oh ok ... and you're walking away now I… https://t.co/HZEbKjQu3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfSchlitzo7 Thank you for following me. I appreciate it. I hope you have a blessed afternoon.🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Game! 🏀🙌🏽 We stopped the chop in Miami! #womenshoops #universityofmiami #ncaawomensbasketball #acchoops @ Wat… https://t.co/UZuP8wjBXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtheneTrek You can RT w / comment and say "This thread …" or something along those lines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#michelleLaVaughnRobinson IS #ALWAYS #PERPETRATING THE #FIRSTPERSON THE #LETTER #I, OF #SUBSTANCE.  ...WELL #OUR DE… https://t.co/xiotBsRi6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why don't you just give it up? You will NEVER be the man Barack Obama was and the fact that you al… https://t.co/urFv0qZlzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire @SebGorka Yes, of course. They spew hate to their followers, results in hate crimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 @MitchellMeeks11 How do we sue her out of office? Can she be impeached?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day!   We are Thankful to all the extraordinary women that have Empowered us with their… https://t.co/HceKrgSqCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@progressiveJem @AP_Politics I will vote for that jackass if he somehow steals the Dem nomination because that's th… https://t.co/N4jsdFDYJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that I married someone that won't eat groundhog if I cook it really bothers me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start doing what you wanna do 🗣 because at the end of the day ITS JUST GOING TO BE YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Bernie preaches Socialism after he purchases his THIRD home.  What happened to "Spread the wealth?']]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact: 2 hours after having an iron infusion I can still taste and smell the iron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gibsonsilva06 omg yesss 😂 or i’ll be watching makeup videos at like 1 am and be like “I need to order that pallete right now”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessBravato Never would. Tried a former friend's. Shitty pillow. Overpriced. She's a trumper, of course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you call your mom &amp; she doesn’t answer https://t.co/jMeaFmQZoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkahne What a terrible ordeal. I cannot even imagine. Be kind to yourselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allinwithchris @RashidaTlaib Isn't she the wedding planner turned head of HUD? https://t.co/x772ZTyP2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaPustorino @Doraguevarat @leighduvall1 @AGuirado5 @SonjaNi41294318 @Goddestofhunt @SanneBorsti @APeijer… https://t.co/IUxBdN2yjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OwenSoundST No fire service cuts should be allowed, why not ask us the people that live here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActNow_Climate Climate change is all b.s.,FAKE.These changes happened every 10,20,50 yrs.We need to build better h… https://t.co/2mmq9JIvVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[asked my little brother what wthese were called...he says “air musicers” ... https://t.co/tRkxpBIYck]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always enjoy opportunities to share HPWD information with civic clubs in the District. My thanks to the Littlefie… https://t.co/SLAxDs8XiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Like you care!!! You hold our country the US as collateral or a wall. You didn’t care we went hung… https://t.co/a04cfXam9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsTPickel @mcampbellteach @EAHS_MiniTHON thanks you @MrsTPickel and @mcampbellteach #partnersforacure #ftk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether you like me remotely or not, when you peer into my life unknowingly, I am technically our President and ser… https://t.co/QoBtLV4iyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[he didn’t know about the prison camps in NK. Either trump is lying or he’s the dumbest guy on Earth. So bottom line… https://t.co/g66CHY5Byn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherorourke7 @ShirleenAllicot @AmyFreeze7 @KenRosatoABC7 Good Morning Happy Monday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go horseback riding, fishing, hiking. Forget the Netflix, movies, fancy dinners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[REMINDER - REMINDER - TODAY - RAIN or SNOW- WE ARE ON - Please attend the Council Meeting for TONIGHT, a public hea… https://t.co/IxzDQRQ5F4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powerful conversation. Isabel Rojas Williams, art historian and curator and Noni Olabisi, painter/muralist on publi… https://t.co/KW5nY05Pdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevRigatone @JanieAtlanta @PissTrumpArt @BeccaMarshall12 @Anne_TX @The_Vagitarian @APoulikakos @Melbajapan… https://t.co/NMbtDnH18T]]></document><document><![CDATA[West Metro Family Docs - our chapter has 17 delegates for the #MAFPHOD on March 30. Please consider joining us - em… https://t.co/K5gjN6KKVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan Actually Kylie manufactured a makeup line right at her target audience tween girls who mainlined their… https://t.co/vDiMrztIqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[So everyone is asleep and I’m 99.9% sure I just heard my front door open... It’s been fun y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Jesus #love #Bible #verseoftheday #God #christian #bibleverse #inspiration #verse #grace #hope #arkansas #b #read… https://t.co/akOBptUkfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stand those students that ask you questions after you present in class 🙄 “get a life”!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[{\__/} ( • . •) / &gt;♥️ u want this?  {\__/} ( • - •) ♥️&lt; \ what do you think of O'Leary Mondays?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree it was refreshing to read just the facts not the made up narrative the gutter U.K. media prints!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActNow_Climate Oh my goodness!You can stop hurricanes, tornadoes and snow storms with more tax dollars?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Presidents Day... @POTUS @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/XAkLOJUWkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaggsclarke @CanadianSyrup @MrsGeorgiosP @LilyYog83 @loonamine @AmazingLovelyGM @GillDoc5 @myaddictionGM… https://t.co/3P9mYxNgQ3]]></document></documents></author>