<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[News articles need to start showing photos of what the disease looks like instead of crappy stock photos of needles… https://t.co/oGArl4inGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Because it's an option he wants on the table for targeting enemies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I rejected a man because I didn’t like how he was speaking to me. In response he decides to call me all sorts of na… https://t.co/9PKa9Xplqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowing her she’ll find ways to help more students get college assistance that is short of free but expands opportu… https://t.co/fKLYW4gPzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnakarenRamon2 Jajajaja pues si me hago pero igual tengo manos de vato lit se ven como las de mis hnos pero en chiquitas. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[6th graders enjoyed #ReadAcrossAmericaDay with some former teachers!   #VikingPrideP3 https://t.co/4fHUVdYVk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you wanna get bitch slapped just smack some food or gum around me... I might seem sweet but I will fuck your shit up lolllllllll]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For @tictoc we don’t want you to think of us as a social brand, we want you to think of us as a news brand you can… https://t.co/OSVq2jWpy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The end of the #ElvisAllStarTribute gave me goosebumps!! A beautiful special]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know God is working so I smile. Even though I’ve been here for a while.. I’ll smile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry, but why would anyone go on the radio to confront their husband about getting drinks with another woman?… https://t.co/AiZXveRCcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fav way to spend Thursday nights? Taking my dog to the vet for a confirmed UTI at 11 pm and being worried sick e… https://t.co/fWkfkv5d5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT the fuckery does this twatwaffling douchecanoe need to say before our CONGRESS and America DEMANDS HIS RESIGNA… https://t.co/841Hb4DjdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePdBlueLine @Chewy May be old age.Some are allergic to litter. Check with vet..male cats can get urinary infect… https://t.co/elAQ2TS9BK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liltaquiito Girl@send your cash app 🤣🤣🤣.  When they come at me crazy that’s what I do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dru_Johnson Although I guess the problem of evil was solved already huh]]></document><document><![CDATA[YelaWolf "Bloody Sunday" Freestyle | TM3 Coming Soon https://t.co/TBmh4FU668 via @YouTube🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can rush reuse propositions.  Maple Leaf Gardens didn’t have a home for a long time says George Baird. #ontarioplace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianWCollins I love Netflix, where everyone “grunts” and “scoffs” constantly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I tell u this class energy was on 💯 I’m not lying lol 😆We had so much energy that the floor was bouncing and t… https://t.co/FPL0v0NU0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patriot League Championship Day 1, Marina anchors with a 2:16.01 split. Indoor 800 PR, just shy of her 2:15 goal. R… https://t.co/YgjWSKq8y2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bullshit! When it's truth and there are facts to support it,it is not a conspiracy theory. That's just a term DS  u… https://t.co/P5vzMREGAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @NBCLatino Their crime is illegally crossing the border. Build the wall now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra If you believe her bc she's young or female, then you're as uninformed as she is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usatodayopinion @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows OH... But It’s Perfectly Fine For You And All R’s To Lie Your Own Lies… https://t.co/wwxecCgAvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_UnSilent_ And the next thing she said was, “Can I help the next person in line”!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElbaklySami @Alcioni5 @GizellaGerics1 @gabryluce @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @mich_onelove @Jose93571656… https://t.co/veKmdmlFWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lancaster Tx @  Strain Farm It is a  sign of spring when first baby calf is born  #GoBrangus baby boy… https://t.co/aenAZu9Jxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANK YOU @moe_harkless #ripcity #directfan @ Buffalo Wild Wings https://t.co/FM8OergWiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realMrJones_tm @GeraldoRivera @seanhannity @AOC https://t.co/F2begZnE1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlLaw33593987 @NARAL It literally grows INSIDE  a woman's body. So why on earth would anyone ever have a say bes… https://t.co/MHXYFp5HyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finishing multiple stories while sending out new freelance pitches is peak Freelance Life™️ for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[That will be a lot of tweets!   Can’t wait.  Bring those flags to #novaseas19. @NoVAOutside]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, I’m not gonna tell you how to live your life, but one of these @CaneRossoRescue puppies is AN INFANT WILCO [… https://t.co/sBDcysFNdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read about the mismanagement in "When There's a Heartbeat: Miscarriage Management in Catholic-Owned Hospitals," fro… https://t.co/Gcp05Ol3rV]]></document><document><![CDATA[TELL ME HOW COULD COHENS CHARGES THAT HAD ADDED TO LIKE 70 YEARS....END UP. TO BE ONLY 3YEARS  HELLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raducom @whitewingdove70 @realDonaldTrump You fit right into the ugliness of the Trumpers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImmigrationFac2 @AnnCoulter @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Nothing like twisting the truth about what was said at the SOTU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching the Elvis tribute on NBC and honestly I’m salty I wasn’t around when he was big. I’m pretty sure I woulda been in big time love]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in? Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Project Manager/Senior Proj… https://t.co/joln6CL5Td]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewPerry I wish I could talk with you, as a mother of an alcoholic son I spend 90% of my life worrying about h… https://t.co/aBpDi5VBUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chick_in_kiev Не пои красавица при мне и песен грузий печальной. My favorite Rachmaninov song.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdTxAnn @Tommyspall @FRESHthoughtEDU Thanks for the shout out, Ann!!! https://t.co/a4dAmGSXVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud to coach with the best! Congrats to the coaches and athletes, what an unbelievable achievement! Girls Polo… https://t.co/il3lgUMhbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caitlyn_1177 is on the phone with the SWEETEST apple support gal right now @AppleSupport]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just threw a bunch of sauces and cheeses and noodles and chicken  in a dish and stuck it in the oven. Result TBD...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo solo quiero reiniciar la vida y ser joven de nuevo, con acceso a estos gadgets desde la época escolar. https://t.co/CZFs9KoPuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[wish my bestfriend loved me and posted about me or something 🙄🤷🏻‍♀️ @kayy_tylerr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight was as wild as the horses that couldn't drag me away ❤️ #buffypromnyc @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/ZHJWbG0Cig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus is #1 in my life....everything is 4 HIS KINGDOM....I make no decisions or moves until you tell me what to do… https://t.co/Svejy5e0Xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I saw a fox playing w/a dog toy on social media I set up an  experiment in my own backyard. "Will my backyard… https://t.co/rnu8mx9zGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikayla_Tani When you #oscars look at what the “like” heart does!! https://t.co/VnpqwAD1Wf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelodiousBree I didn’t know her but it is always hard to lose someone in our group. Cancer is a cruel bitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this cold and snowy day in NY, I am missing the warmth of Puerto Rico... or maybe it was just the heat coming of… https://t.co/7WmEI256Yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving Amy Klobuchar at SXSW.  #texastribune @MOBLYN foundingaustin @ Moody Theater https://t.co/yqRRAn25YO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at CCF Akron General - @myakrongeneral in Akron, OH https://t.co/95y4T6v5QD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never Met #AlexTrebec never was on @Jeopardy but having watched it almost every night with my family  for the past… https://t.co/qwsXoiJ2y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Calum5SOS thank you for being my inspiration and helping me through the past five years. i honestly don’t know wha… https://t.co/Sc87mEgRqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“bitch put down your camera and live in the moment this shit right here everybody gon' want it” — logic @ Dadz Bar… https://t.co/2r00bUYcQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimruehl Agree. Plus I’m desperate to have the 2020 election resemble the 2016 was as little as possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[stupid ass refs had the audacity to tell my parents to learn English and to stop speaking Spanish, wtf man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamalifewithme Yes bitch you gotta go I’ve gone three times and I’m going again next week I love it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning sunlight (finally) and everything from last night is clean and dry💜 #resin #resinmolds #resinart… https://t.co/6rsCkVxl9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence I am always so engrossed In what you are saying that I don’t hear how you say it 🙂 Also your interview wi… https://t.co/iz8sxsqPZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin Sex trafficker at Mara Lago? Could it be that this has something to do with the fact that children ar… https://t.co/6JtUbB1ZLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveSchreiber3 @AmericanAuburn @Olivia2MAGA @heyitsCarolyn @Puddinn_Head16 @sianetta @MAGAgirly @tammyTrumpedYou… https://t.co/Rjbi3WNPod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsmebeccam @dougblandry @_allymaldonado @caththegreat012 Who’s from NJ? I was lookin for a fellow Jersian this weekend! 🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[dai eu penso “porra eu sou uma fodida” e sou mesmo  mas sempre bom reconhecer os privilégios e agradecer a vida boa… https://t.co/ogKselpJiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another cool thing I think you should do today. LISTEN! Maybe with a beer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The countdown has begun!! T-minus 15 days till the #besttimeoftheyear @WMCtweets  . . Grab your badge before its to… https://t.co/FjcXDuEFoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#madonnasummermusic party today at #faultlinebar #FaultlineBar https://t.co/Qr8lIaSu2U https://t.co/xGAsisKElK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IrinaMikhale @FrannyWild @sadydoyle @JessicaValenti @daveweigel This is what I'm referring to https://t.co/85B5zh5aMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blvck_Bleach If you take that man vs machine class they show you this, it’s a pretty good technique]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump now this is a real emergency why hasn't anything been done about this👇]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atejano01 @CandaceOverall @deja_benefield @JL0DucaBayPoint @josiejoh @TJMartinez1000 Beautiful leaders! 👍❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lhcountryboy @scottykokefm @KOKEFMAUSTIN @EricRaines1 How DARE you?!  🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @roads2 @KarenSLeonard1 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Iluvinspireu @AnwarManwar004 @MelindaYoe @Jimmysimmonds1… https://t.co/J2CAcqXvBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kangoojumps (@ Cardiff-by-the-Sea, CA in Cardiff-by-the-Sea, CA w/ @thegreatwax) https://t.co/fYblxhKNXh https://t.co/NtNRY6AJVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord, I want to thank you for allowing me to see another marvelous year. Thank you for all your blessings, thank yo… https://t.co/f8ICWqAhwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to meet Duran Duran @ The Cosmopolitan of Las Vegas https://t.co/Jgu8InoOXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@From96Till Lmao I’m not even gon ask nobody no more. Ima just be like “sahdude” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a Fiesta in the kitchen!! #fiesta #mexicanfood #guacamole #tortillas #party @ The Well Seasoned Chef https://t.co/5YkuWOcb3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay 💪💪 You are strong, capable, intelligent, beautiful... just the way you are. ✨💞… https://t.co/G5pzHd8SWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations, Kate! I have enjoyed watching Kate over the past two years since becoming a superfan of… https://t.co/cb8aSoRMla]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @justinbieber I literally love you more than you’ll ever know bc you have no idea who I am but whate… https://t.co/lKBLSzrdLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally watched this loop for like 5 minutes examining/imagining what it would be like to jump into… https://t.co/yOK4kDCxoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHANMINA – Doctor https://t.co/MqgY8GHbCA via @YouTube all bout Celina ain't I Foine yuppies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFAN1003 @PowerTripKFAN @AjKFAN @MeatSauce1 @Chris_Hawkey @MarkDParrish #PowerTrip  @AjKFAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ohionascarman @markymark930 Congrats!! A new journey for u!! Awesome! As far as u.. hugs u silly man. I saw thru t… https://t.co/2OxJLrZig0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meghan_Trainor I love your music video for #AllTheWays and I’m so proud of @BaileeMadison for doing such an amazin… https://t.co/5rOL8I4wku]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why everyone was so shocked that Captain America @ChrisEvans helped @ReginaKing @theOscars. Pretty sur… https://t.co/S7eZfqiQzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my favorite doc - Dr. Harden (@ 14th Street Medical Arts Center in New York, NY) https://t.co/EFhwBfYCEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because you’re a good man doesn’t mean you’re a goof partner two different things. https://t.co/lopxnbmf0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[i didn’t want to get a first shift job because ive been known to sleep through alarms, here i am, it’s only day 4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaiNesbitt Maybe Osman is still carrying some old anger from what he did to Sanem, and he dont see him as the nice guy 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know the colab I really need? @powerm1985 &amp; @thefarmbabe together talking about #GMOs &amp; #farming myths.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mingberg @RobertW48787695 @LiverDiseaseSup @Snapchat @DavidLogan2020 @DanielBrasilia @enriquillo2 @wecanmag… https://t.co/7z1Yrvm0ZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rick_H2Os @TheNerdyNegro @ambergurl75 @wendicc @sianoresist @BernieSanders I have no idea what this is supposed to… https://t.co/EaOVq3dHZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙏🏽To all my beginners, 2️⃣ new chances to get a jump start this week: 2/26 NEW 20-minute Beginner Ride and on 2/27… https://t.co/0KB8zlxUaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump I thought moments of silence were usually reserved for dead men.]]></document></documents></author>