<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My 9-year old son and I have gotten to this part of The Lord of the Rings. https://t.co/Bkv4TmZP0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[It Took Two Months and Nearly a Million Dollars to Save an Unvaccinated 6-Year-Old From Tetanus https://t.co/mV9uH12hfG via @gizmodo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Squirrelpion I'll eventually get it on those too.  PC will be the last since I do want to upgrade my pee cee beforehand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_dcastillo08 Head up Big bro. If you ever need anyone to talk to I’ll be here homie. You got people that care abou… https://t.co/oBlro9hVPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mustang Taylor Reich got her first collegiate draw control for @LeMoyneWLAX as they handle their business with… https://t.co/afhApZ38VQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ceo_diego Thank you so much Man! Bros for life and that’s not even a question]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no saving for Salt Lake who can't extend the lead because of their kicker Taylor Bertolet it's embarrassin… https://t.co/brZT5ZxIhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deadass about to just go on a drive and scream to this, fuck I'm in my feels now https://t.co/6bmRGolzfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #LGBexit #TakeBackPride Recognition of The True Gay Community in June by @realDonaldTrump is imper… https://t.co/v3R0GMAyf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goats #tooshort #icecube @tooshort icecube #legends @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/NCensqLEz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was going to like this but it’s sitting at “69” likes right now and I can’t bring myself to break that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bgood12345 @ROHLL5 Cohen and another 12 million Jewish mossad are not getting out jail free over the marilyn monro… https://t.co/Xsiz2rNnKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda in the same boat now. Maybe I need to keep a cot hidden under my desk at work. https://t.co/8aqQiqWyHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmccbyfaith @TheMiddleMan19 @AMErikaNGIRL07 @Tweets4MAGA KINGS? OPEN A HISTORY BOOK TO PAGE 1.  I got fake news. M… https://t.co/XfwPcpeqZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is getting the Full Monty in Dallas, as they should. #RidersOverHere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKellyZZZ @ReporterJim You're calling it blame. A cause isn't the same as blame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexWitt just wondering why you have Michael Caputo on your show when all he does is tell half truths, lies and mi… https://t.co/agkzlcYKtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Well you support abortion. What's the difference killing with a gun or killing with a knife. Shut up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back when the east wall of my home office was still open, before work began on it. https://t.co/Jq1tJjnT4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incendie au centre-ville de Trois-Rivières https://t.co/xV1UkrP3kV https://t.co/EKVorvuhIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am sorry Folks; but, the so-called, Reagan Revolution is responsible for setting the wheels in motion that has le… https://t.co/oOjs8kgToX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your wcw thinks it’s bad to be submissive to a man but still wants to get married]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimerrikin Thank you. Much appreciated.  Thankfully, I have ol' faithful from my profile pic. But still...  Need a… https://t.co/NSo9ooYgTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Thursday morning Coach’s Bible study mariettahighschool ! These are my friends! @ Marietta, Georgia https://t.co/OztpbuZPB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The people on this terrorist's HIT LIST included Nancy Pelosi, Maxine Waters, Kamala Harris, Cory Booker, "poca war… https://t.co/hc8Nq6OwUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just in from @RussianRiverBC #happyhopsipa #craftbeer #pacificheightssf @ Ales Unlimited https://t.co/TNFKaDm6BM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AvantGardeGoth @jaykisokay @sprinnyC @catmancatman864 @tousleshommes This tells such a beautiful story]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool ironman suit marvel_robertdowney @ Bedford, Massachusetts https://t.co/p6nrk17rbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ethicscrane Been the case for a while (Chick-Fil-A is "famous" for its religious values, hence Conservatives tend to like it and buy there)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BubblyMoments Thank you for following me! I am very excited to connect with you on topics such as writing, bloggin… https://t.co/dCCU00Yaw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My inner 9th grader trying to understand string theory’s Graviton, Quantum Gravity and how Einstein’s Relativity ex… https://t.co/dmzoB4rJvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelleynapier @Chis68 @Ilhan Never forget the Holocaust. She doesn't believe it happened. But she believes that th… https://t.co/1uTQ872nA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hiphopmix2 Word! They pulling him out ASAP! Cant been seen getting dominated by blacks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thereidfeed @paulludwig There are many better Midwestern/farm themed pickup lines. I’m frankly disgusted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thirst for God, the living God. When can I go and stand before him? https://t.co/rhHm6emV2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ready in #miami see you tonight at Sport Salsa Café 33012 #hialeah with drbrooklyn @djtavopty and Waca Firu Waca e… https://t.co/O7cPjTFyvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alita: Battle Angel is 1000% better if you just imagine it as the most expensive Disney Channel Original Movie ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikefreemanNFL Clinton came back stronger after impeachment and won re-election.  Don’t make the same mistake the republicans made]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Right swipe, right, right, right, right, leeeeeft- nah right. We desperate.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HOldtheDo0R @Floridateach38 @RepDanCrenshaw Oh and tax fraud.  So many crimes it's easy to forget a couple]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aboutcock Aw Fuck dude your Cock needs to be in fuckin filthy dirty RAW Cock sucking Hard Core fuck Porn, you do l… https://t.co/wK6vuAwLTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les arde que diga que esos 50,000 pesitos saldran de la partida secreta]]></document><document><![CDATA[The search for my car went on for 2 weeks until we found my car for sale on way fair...idk why 🤷🏻‍♀️ so we call the… https://t.co/kaQQgZnCP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red-breasted Merganser diving at the Cape Cod Canal 02/22/19 #duck #ducks #ducksofinstagram #redbreastedmerganser… https://t.co/AlIci2gU7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattdracing @mattdracing it was so cool seeing you out front today. Tough break toward the end but I think you pro… https://t.co/INgnVf2D32]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WarriorPresent The title and pic are okay, I guess, but the true blessing from RNGeezus is that fully crafted Mk3 Carbanti Sensor Array.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You really don’t understand how bs and privileged the notion “money can’t buy happiness” is until you can’t even afford to heat your home]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voting for black candidates. If anything this article reflects my sentiments   https://t.co/7emOA7rnWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just witnessed a lady in the car next to me in the wal mart parking lot clean her ear out with a q tip and then proceed to sniff it.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimayello @IndyCar @GreyhoundBus  Bro..? Way cheaper than @Uber ..???? @IndyCarRadio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matty_S2S @dubsfans02 @evansilva My belief is that a lot of smart people have already cracked the code in describi… https://t.co/26I2OwuMRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peter_Bukowski Last year I think they thought they were fine.  They had Haha and were counting on Jones to have de… https://t.co/YkSNVs4hYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of these days the world will come to my way of seeing the Oscars, which is an overrated artsy party in Manhatta… https://t.co/exxmB6bnvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[DuKE CAn’T WiN WitHoUt ZiON  #dukenation #KistheGOAT https://t.co/984RvYbwo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join me at @UDelaware for a conversation w/ @JiSeongho1 regarding his defection from #NorthKorea . @UDGlobal… https://t.co/ODepPjfXNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIDS_United Lol @RepBradWenstrup doesn't care about sick people. Brad does what his Republican masters tell him to… https://t.co/tmHThZhzfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreashockling I see that you are not so familiar with teenage girls?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the reminder @JonGordon11 “If you can see it you can create it.” #Vision #FCA https://t.co/tqWaLg4ktj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shouldn’t the backer sit in the hole in cover 3? If he does or plays run due to seeing low hats and the flat defend… https://t.co/S8SLwDdbAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GopherPuckLive @VintageMNHockey Interesting discussion on three regional locations. A location you guys didn't bri… https://t.co/ufBcJ0xAjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being dumb enough to trust Don Cherry’s research and arithmetic: pathetic 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizzyTDmb @chris_drake Hahaha fair enough, I’m sure they are. My kids are just stubborn and unpredictable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/kF41F1grIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the bois 26/02/2019 @ Cathedral City, California https://t.co/Gxq9PISfnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe it cops 👮‍♀️ are the worst criminal ever if you ask me I remembered a police office called me a stu… https://t.co/goCdoNdJ8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[You attack a media reporter but at the same time support a resolution to stop the President from doing that exact s… https://t.co/FoKYy44DXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Considering the fact that Obama moved billions to Iran, securing a few billion for a wall should be easy]]></document><document><![CDATA[RSD1369: 12 miles easy. going for distance.  Feeling stronger and faster every day.  Thank God for the gift of this… https://t.co/4LZgVtr9if]]></document><document><![CDATA[#projectrunwayallstars is on! I’ve never missed a season of @ProjectRunway or #Projectrunwayallstars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuisDiazLuna habría que adentrarse mucho en el tema;la derrama económica de esos eventos debe ser mayor que lo “in… https://t.co/Za8pY11zBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeweedon @dcpublicschools @leahrenzi @srwteacher @madisonteacher @BruceLesh @ElvidgeKathryn @lizhiler @GaDOE_SS… https://t.co/7cCtQRhUOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Travon Washington, the James Island forward responsible for guarding Tonka Hemingway, picked uobhis their foul and… https://t.co/0O87rA1RQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbetterperform @byron_ledbetter @LoneStarCamp Congrats Byron. Well deserved]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are leading this effort.  Guess you thought it was Mexico leading it.  🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday 🚂☀️ #RailLife @ SunRail Operations Center https://t.co/8xxRNrjFHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiggr_ @JaqubAjmal I’ve seen this micro stutter happen in the game every so often since launch on PS4 Pro and pres… https://t.co/G0PT5l1jYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reports of a standoff between police and the suspect on 125 one street up from grant st(my house), activity started from 2am to present]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck Braves 💪🏾💪🏼@Brodycolbert6 @Tay_Rob132 @WHSWrestlingNJ @jljernegan @ChadTracy1 @Jacob_carr2765]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Now fix the VA’s broken Vocational Rehabilitation Program pathway to self employment. https://t.co/G1ZpfX4nny]]></document><document><![CDATA[temperature down 49°F -&gt; 45°F humidity up 81% -&gt; 100% wind 3mph -&gt; 7mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPaulGosar @RobBishopUT @AOC You looked like a fool on national television and you followed it up with this tweet… https://t.co/UPizBrcIgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebradfordfile I believe that #MaxineWaters has everything needed to be admitted to an asylum for the criminally… https://t.co/Cf5j2STXVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: "If I was trapped in a cave, I would eat my own throw-up to survive."  Bartender: "One IPA coming up."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelmanDC @BryanBroaddus Looks like they might be trying to extend. Cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely the best series of talks I have ever heard since being a part of Passion City Church. There’s still time… https://t.co/9G6uXh4D8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished watching. Good movie. Tomorrow’s live tweet film: Romancing The Stone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chudio @WWEPR @WWE @MinuteMaidParks @HoustonChron @astros Hotels will be super cheap right now to book. Think I’m… https://t.co/cvsD2J7aiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petition power breakfast at Bountiful Bread before a morning of meetings and petition day #2!  #ReidySetGo https://t.co/tiEqxrbzFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody wanna talk about how MJ got that way or are we all just here to rage fuck a corpse?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have tentatively rescheduled tomorrow's Region Basketball game against Murfreesboro Central Magnet to 2:00 PM. #jacketpride]]></document><document><![CDATA[@headlineplanet @ArianaGrande @KaceyMusgraves @halsey @garthbrooks @johnlegend @aliciakeys YESSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/9R0S65nWAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 annoyances:  1) dudes with ear muffs.    2)  people on the train enter then immediately stop.  Like hey there are… https://t.co/OsMakEYiji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briantheguppie I’ll take “Over 14’ tall and can’t wrestle worth a damn” for $800 Alex...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happiness #stress #yourchoice #affectyou @ Brooklyn Park, Minnesota https://t.co/EBcl9jK37R]]></document><document><![CDATA[This video makes me LOL because something always has to happen to me 😏🤦🏽‍♀️ https://t.co/E3ziSgrrBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WatchTime Magazine, why don't you guys do a story on the #WATCHES of power brokers in the hit #SHOWTIME Series… https://t.co/rFBz4EWtID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pregame playlist #at BU vs. Loyola definitely poppin - #Coulduse #somemorerae #sremmurd and maybe a little… https://t.co/CJjZvjr8QN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HermesRomeo @zayne_09 @BlackedRaw @GregLansky You should join the team victor all you gotta do is sign up 📝]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 10:26 AM CST, 1 SW Great Bend Airport [Barton Co, KS] AWOS reports NON-TSTM WND GST of M52 MPH. AWOS STATION GBD… https://t.co/tUmjkMm2nc]]></document></documents></author>