<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@NWPinPDX @musicrocksit452 @B52Malmet @MatthewWolfff @ChocoHarveyMilk @Alyssa_Milano @DearAuntCrabby @brycetache… https://t.co/1cCNRzvfHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettyBoy888 the face you make when your x girlfriend fucks your worst enemy. https://t.co/j8JYe0ooPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyBWhite @LorenaSGonzalez I just don’t see a substantive difference between the employee vs. IC discussion for… https://t.co/HBO9VKK08m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrShakeNBacon I didn’t even know he wasn’t coaching in the NBA anymore. Turns out I don’t watch the NBA, so... makes sense!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias In the United States with virtually no welfare, laughable unemployment insurance that women are dispr… https://t.co/ke2asgFpEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol.... From the walking dead calendar. Day of week placed perfectly.... Caption should read "I'm sure everything w… https://t.co/mZyZZ4MsrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s your top 3 Girl Scout cookies? Mine is thin mints (frozen), lemonades, and tagalongs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now it finally makes sense that I own a parka! Good thing because it helps me to stay focused on getting to the gym… https://t.co/fCsZavIdN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Alex Meixner Polka Pils by @FaustBrewingCo @ McAdoo's — https://t.co/WnnkIFAG7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopChassid Here’s something that Jews and Middle East Muslims can agree on.  This defiles hummus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from westsideknowledge  -  25 Lighters Wesside Bari ft YellaTape #WestColumbia #Wessidemusic #Localartist… https://t.co/i9KIYUjk9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MondayBusPics #Bronx #NYCTransit #NYCBus #TransitFan 🚌🚌 @ 149th Street https://t.co/5DbSGELLdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Starbucks? We're hiring in #SignalHill, CA! Click the link in our bio for details on this job and m… https://t.co/vctXZBfxGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anthony Morrison “I do these live events every Thursday for my students. Come, listen, learn and get free gifts alo… https://t.co/nFPA2r41KJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeerhillGangTV That was a epic battle between those 2.. Shepard's interview afterward was a classic also]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace Wow!! This is only the beginning of shining a light on a disgusting human being called Donald Trum… https://t.co/4RFPGs67yF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the most amazing, loving, beautiful soul on earth. You have a smile ready for everyone  making ev… https://t.co/bCWakjM65n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @barstoolsports, but the central office looks so messy in videos and photos, it’d give me anxiety if I was ever there in person 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ORNL_CISR @ORNL_Careers @ornlfcu @INL @JSS_Community @ILARNGRRB @ARCYBER @ArmyFortLee @FtHoodExchange @PantexPlant https://t.co/oXwYrc67B0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a hard night because I miss my baby brother so much and idk where he is or if hes safe...i just want to hug him and hear his laugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenWickens1 @311 @mattgallowaycbc @jeffbutlerto My catchbasin ice fused w the mulch of leaves so there is only… https://t.co/8FyHFTplJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ William M. Powell Bridge to Key Biscayne https://t.co/AlrvVB0CXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two words: Steppy Pants.  Get this free game today.  You will be hooked in 2 minutes! ;) Thanks @meganmorrone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natashante this shit make me wanna talk to you crazy. lol gimme my fade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[El burro hablando de orejas; que no sabe que la corrupcion es cultural y se adquiere desde que naces. Y la trae con… https://t.co/6Hli7oGGQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeGiglioSports How can he not be? He was grossly over matched last year]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you allow it, you condone it.  If you condone it, you endorse it.  If you endorse it, you represent it.  If you… https://t.co/bD5UfrFyPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOOOOOO many psychological levels to this HBO documentary #LeavingNeveland ... Sooooooo much going on. For all part… https://t.co/1Ik9VZnZWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rbjames09 @LouisAColello @realDonaldTrump Is that a Canadian flag? WHY ARE YOU EVEN IN THIS CONVERSATION?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[KYLE GRIFFIN PUSHING FAKE NEWS...SAID FARTING  COWS WAS DESTORYING OUR O- ZONE. YOUR A SICK PUPPIE..]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s 325 million people in America. That’s $0.51 per person... what’s the problem?]]></document><document><![CDATA[the united states completely fucked over haiti, just like it did to every other place the united states expanded th… https://t.co/1V5kIZ0wDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[animals you have found and laid to rest on the side of the highway or perhaps a love note written in ink made from… https://t.co/pqBBouC4os]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should be no surprise here. It may be passe to read a book now and then but if someone were to read a little histor… https://t.co/IuKUyJ49aW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miamijj48 @leebellar Yeah?! Well "Allah" those jack-offs can kiss my lily white ass!!!🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Steamy Hallows in New York, NY https://t.co/Tl82lLHKk5 https://t.co/0FX6SmuhXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNewPI @KimberlyNuggets you people do genetics VERY differently from me ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChefJTaylor Sold 16 for stubs last year. Wasn’t invested in the community then, had no clue https://t.co/LovuMDZ3Z2]]></document><document><![CDATA[God tries to teach you lessons quietly at first, then he gets loud. You’ve got my attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[15 of the 36 @GirlsUAA clubs represented here (Six in the top 20) w/several others being breakoffs of clubs on this… https://t.co/UpBBqLewf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This day @IamJalenBurbage you will always remember “YOUR FUTURE STARTS NOW” don’t ever forget what got you there… https://t.co/uLqC2FMfV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are y’all dumb ?? That video that @BeautyByKieshh of that bitch tweaking looked NOTHIN like her ! 😂 my bitch is thi… https://t.co/TqPJbFJzby]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHO COMING to @Lakers with @KingJames ??? @kawhileonard @AntDavis23 @KDTrey5 @KyrieIrving 🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀 #NBAAllstar https://t.co/quhwHg3sX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan You would believe that. You're all too familiar with all things terrifying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @CodesTrump @Jeanleonetti1 @CommonCause @joncoopertweets @wikileaks @Snowden @RIPsethRich @FBI @DNC… https://t.co/b22gDBh2qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm pretty sure Bob Murray was in line behind me this morning. @AnaheimDucks where does coach get his morning cup o' joe?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks coach and you was there you know what I went threw 🤧 but I over care the adversity 🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m doing French tip acrylics on Madilyn this evening for something to do, anyone want their nails done for free ju… https://t.co/OumpZDVGjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes you take a pic at when you’re having fun Mardi Gras and then you see something that shakes you to your ve… https://t.co/DrruimnKLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Inexcusable would describe ALL your corrupt dealings against OUR country!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cgj_Crypto Not so sure it would as one would have to consider accumulation vs where else would the investment be?… https://t.co/f8fT6K5Qz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdc @codepo8 WHAT TOOK Y'ALL SO LONG???  BTW, thank you. Love the flexibility this will enable https://t.co/cBwMY9Nlet]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are Beaver in the Rio Grande at Lajitas, Texas. @TPWDparks @TPWDnews @BigBendNPS @GregAbbott_TX https://t.co/olqoLjiCwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[How 'Bout Those Hogs...they gigged them Aggies! What a 4th quarter, and what heart they showed tonight! #WPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to Walmart this morning to find clearance valentines but theywas barely changing prices. 😩 hopefully I find things after work 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[and might I say, I have not seen one piece of plastic on the beach but cigarette butts are everywhere . . .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennhendry @mattallott @CraftBeerBeaven @Van_Man76 @manantler I'll talk about it.  Being there sucked ass. End of story. 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Badges21969682 @3YearLetterman @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Sounds like someone doesn’t have a corner apartment… https://t.co/2ha6XUEzsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s face it, for some of us, there’s only one reason to go to the fair.  https://t.co/hxNgykUkfc  #manateecounty… https://t.co/mBzHUQqPm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OSUCoachKDub &amp; @CoachTreyHoltz are cooking up something special in the TE room! Stay tuned! 👀🔜 #JustWin… https://t.co/pcnUU4QX4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southberryst Harder on me than the calf. Couldn't get the little devil in the pen. Had to go old school]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@lyft and @RideRTD are coming together to help #Denver residents get across the city more easily. Try the new ‘Nea… https://t.co/7WbKQmLJU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapNegative @obj I'll play devil's advocate, how can you draft a rookie QB and trade away the teams best WR?   I'm… https://t.co/hYIKkme5MV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Moonshine Patio Bar &amp; Grill - @moonshinegrill in Austin, TX https://t.co/1hrcpDWM5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport Why y’all did @KingJames like that https://t.co/OlEYthw8Ez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Folks Please share! @ Emmanuel Baptist Church https://t.co/Sh69qWOuR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abcnews4dean @WillMcAvoyACN Apparently he didn’t go to Iron Works BBQ or another 1/2 million awesome spots around… https://t.co/0stZuSvxRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @TEAMHOSFOREVER @realDonaldTrump Time for the Big Stick Mr President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@britdjmatt @alancross @strombo thanks for being such great influences on my music choices. Happy Radio Day… https://t.co/92vPEtVwMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveThePuck Don’t care for animation at all but after reading your timeline I’m going to have to give the new Spider-Man a look]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatGeoChannel has been my jam this weekend. Watched #FreeSolo tonight. WOW @AlexHonnold an amazing show of strengt… https://t.co/bSDFSqFARB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just gonna be the bigger person and keep my mouth shut and let it all play out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone with information is asked to call Miami-Dade Crime Stoppers at 305-471-TIPS. #MDPD FBI Impersonators Sought… https://t.co/FiZxTrI7zq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coconut French toast time. @ The Hibiscus House Bed &amp; Breakfast https://t.co/yxrFvWqgVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEY @USPS! What gives on this delivery! The box is torn, looks like someone tried to open it. This is ridiculous!… https://t.co/ggq9wXxSLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StellaMaeve14 Wait!?! I thought you had your own, natural, personal, heat wave that follows you everywhere!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews @RealSaavedra What’s it like going from “hacker group” to sassy tweeters?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boston...you are...thanks! @ Pavement Coffeehouse https://t.co/1teFkehztq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mnot @mogsie I'm dwelling on repudiation rather than privacy given that I see the main risk being individuals havi… https://t.co/KodQnZSEhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr There’s plenty in the documentation Cohen provided about you and the Donster too Jr.  hehehehe You… https://t.co/H6naFZQchY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will be a busy day for the hard-working Senate clerks and bill processing folks. There will be a rush to beat… https://t.co/SnKk28Zz5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[God bless my child’s mother! Ion know what she going through but she has me every level of fucked up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobGarof @BabyFrieds I would cook this guy all day, he wouldn’t survive a day in the Big Ten]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mason Rangers signing night. #baseballseason @ Marion's Piazza https://t.co/oQZwLZu5kR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harryafc @ackneythfc1967 @JamesOlley Your mob were standing next to Harry when he took is, he just didn’t bottle it 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rachel, can you please explain to your audience in laymen’s terms what impeachment means etc we need a one hour cla… https://t.co/pno8fxfh3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Belvidere Discount Mall https://t.co/9aM9UBkfpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NWAHutch I know the 2020 class for baseball is insane. Which of the recruits are least likely to make it to campus?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday March 6 - 3 O'clock Stir:      Colorado killer's daughter, 4, knew her mom, sister were dead, attorney sa… https://t.co/y3dJIoh9Uk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought humans were smart enough to curb their addiction to a life of misery provided by toxic Christian capitali… https://t.co/FSTW4jEXZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpencerG76 Ahhhh it’s not really the poll just the FPI. Still though. Little surprised]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always document what money you handed to the gas jockey. @ Baja California, Mexico https://t.co/36I3FXLeKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamgoldmanNYT @SarahConnor2017 It’s like they think they have an impact on Mueller. Lololok]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep seeing people say that the Black Panther should have won the Oscar .. that movie wasnt good I’m not big into… https://t.co/9VK19tROUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_priory @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump How have I never seen this before? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to see another home and away jersey all star game before I die]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday afternoon... #snowscape #deervalley @Deer_Valley #parkcityscape #parkcitygram #verticallandscape #landscape… https://t.co/BwBu3yAdpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I kinda wanna drown your memory, Kinda wanna raise my finger to all them used to be's” 🤪🖕🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hope012015 @medwoman1 @HuffPostPol I've seen that guy somewhere before.... https://t.co/5SM0dna1jQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[PJ Byrd rocking that headband #LetsGoVCU #ThisIsRamNation #sportsphotography #sportsphotographer #pentaxk3 #pentax… https://t.co/dax2gP8rnm]]></document></documents></author>