<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[ANOTHER BIG WIN IN LA!!! 🙌🏼🙌🏼🙌🏼 Grateful for everyone that has been a part of this campaign and everyone out there… https://t.co/gdZmZLavXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSThisMorning @GayleKing @rkelly Bravo Gayle for creating a safe space for @rkelly to unload his raw emotions and… https://t.co/mjQi292Elp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hiramboyd @ArmchairQBDan @cavs Players routinely get better at shooting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This wine goes deep and dark...the darkest of the red fruits, meeting up with some serious darkly charred oak barre… https://t.co/9tewhzj1Gb]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to lose your voice: 1) Spend a week screaming like a fangirl about your favorite 3D CAD software and over 80s c… https://t.co/7cY8z10Q5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[“English is our first language, so you need to speak English,” the woman, identified in the video as Jill, screamed… https://t.co/Fk3GMJIiYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Guatemalacoffee @behmor @PerfectDailyG @handclegends @CoffeeOriginsT @CoffeeGroups Very effective way of re-using… https://t.co/sYRNwPSjaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump just quoted Dr. Seuss in his #ReadAcrossAmericaDay message: In the timeless words of Dr. Seuss, “th… https://t.co/TlZAaICGEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maynardo961 He wanted the most years and the biggest guarantee...he got it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oy... These types of games don't end well for Oakland usually. This is really concerning even though they are leading at the moment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final from Lakewood: Tommy Sala drains in 2 free throws in the final 1.5 seconds for @LkwdAthletics as they edge @BayAthletics 52-51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qshe is a LIAR just@like Dad. Jared got clearance on his own. LOL I am waiting for your daughter and the whole fami… https://t.co/6v9weB7RUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bot106 @Dirtybird Found my tweet of my time its really good also Teddy’s red is great https://t.co/qdsH97KaC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone doubt this Weasel is really doing this? "Pharma Bro" Martin Shkreli is being investigated for allegedly… https://t.co/cqD6V0FQCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@don_allain Yeah who cares the islander player ran Sparks the same shift, our goalie didn't flop like he was shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días Me gusta disfrutar de música tranquila al amanecer, le da sabor a mi café  https://t.co/KftcRPeTBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVietor08 @RepBobGibbs I especially liked the part in which he admits barely meeting Trump but that that brief mee… https://t.co/7S1qwnTMxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump-Kim summit: White House says no agreement reached as talks cut short #TrumpKimSummit https://t.co/DmUDLF4j2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grahamctv @PatriciaBoalCTV we saw you both on TV last night!! 😎#CrosbyAndKid]]></document><document><![CDATA[GET IT "ALL NEW 2019" #TradingViewTOOLKIT! #cisTOPIX #tdameritrade #thinkorswim #tradingview #thinkscript… https://t.co/E8QbDCsQeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting down to have dinner at a bar and a NCAAWBB game is on... one team just entered the locker room with 7 point… https://t.co/4lkLjE645N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last 3 largest MLB contracts given out have been by Marlins, Padres and Rockies]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m disappointed that a sentry gun doesn’t pop out from the trunk and take care of the threat. Tesla really out her… https://t.co/C6eInlQhSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[😇 GOD'S DISCIPLE MINISTRY'S Psalm 40:1-3 NIV I waited patiently for the Lord; he turned to me and heard my cry. [2]… https://t.co/TEnlALIEgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made me think how much are media consumption habits have solidified themselves in recent years. 4 years ago I don’t… https://t.co/Il3RExB3rs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sketches and canvases remain in the shed behind the studio. https://t.co/q3YvAlTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My debut comedy album Unmedicated: The New Fragrance is out this Friday produced by @howl_roar Records ⭐️  #comedy… https://t.co/UGit8dHOvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[One characteristic that modernity in architecture should aim for? „Design to the specificity of the place and the setting,“ said Mr Safdie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Schwarz_Sarg What ? Supongo la batería exploto y por eso morí (?) https://t.co/2avyqD3G2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Urban_Wolf @WolfVivienne007 @ramonaa1yahooco @isabenfica51 @OfficialGRT @Rubiconski @bergwolf12 @zazabelou… https://t.co/U6txYcPmHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacquezGreen @ColeCren1222 Him being at North Carolina will explain a lot of why Ole Miss had an issue with him. I… https://t.co/4UfWQQOsJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KilroyFSU @JohnC1908 Well. Watch closer. Most physical team in nation. Have reputation of "never fouling". Shit do… https://t.co/jnaNwcwHK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Here4Grace I could not agree more. Trump is a jerk for brevity.  What concerns me more is a belief that misuusing… https://t.co/l1KjfSUU79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaueErick7 @benjaminback garoto vai limpar seu bumbum pq ainda esta cheirando a leite ele e um dos caras mais inte… https://t.co/ErGWzgZVnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[📝 Playoff Game List - UIL Playoffs Area 6A – 4A @PrepHoopsTX https://t.co/LvNpYbvFhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Microsoft’s #AI pipeline, from research to reality https://t.co/zzxkrLXkTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob is out this week/Not much progress has been made/ We have a new plan #staffmeetinginhaiku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any veterans of #providecomfort remember how many hundreds of locations had landmines? Trying to remember dates and… https://t.co/4crTpGNB3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope one day I can be as organized as Lisa Stokes is with her spreadsheets. This is literally amazing!!! #rootstech]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ToyStoryLand offers some of the most remarkable #sunsets in the entire Walt Disney World Resort, #fact! #Studios… https://t.co/oNt02v84fA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndiraHuilca @milagrosmedita @matuk Indira, esa propuesta realmente es innecesaria además de populista. Implementa… https://t.co/o7F8lNnIJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’d Have to Be High to Buy American Marijuana Stocks https://t.co/p7zHzwhg81 via @BarronsOnline]]></document><document><![CDATA[POSITIVES, NEEDS and HOPES   ‘Should have been easy, but just too difficult ‘  @leemarkjudges @LeeDixon2… https://t.co/Fgn55GE5Bm]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ClubDV8LA w/ @ChueyMartinez &amp; @IMDJDREW is LIVE!! - @1027KIISFM (KIIS / KVVS) | @iHeartRadio: https://t.co/VCcbukmiAu 👍😀📱📻🎉💻🎧⌚️🎙🏖🏝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growler is flat despite being filled on 2/1 - Drinking a Triple Mt. Nelson by @cellarmakerbeer at @TheBeermongers  — https://t.co/kjlqXvinC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to the protestors, It sounded like they needed to better educate themselves and implications.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bomani_jones Damn @bomani_jones everybody knows your hobbies include knitting and crocheting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is your happy place? The red rocka and green river banks of the Utah desert or the high snow capped peaks of… https://t.co/bT2CqjFudN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewArticleSZN @Jahnx @iGruesome_ @Ebron85 I played a couple of years through school, but played basketball. The cl… https://t.co/0fZA1AnGfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimMcNiff1 @Vikings Yeah, ‘cuz we’ve got all this money just sitting around.   😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katemonster20 @Goalieman_PHL 8 years for me too. He and I were joined at the hip for 17 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GordonRjag Correct. Though considering it is a recommendation from both the Central Bank and the Minister of Finan… https://t.co/wZQKDwibph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Business isn’t easy.  What are the traits you think need to be present in every entrepreneur? #business #finance… https://t.co/zzMcA72oLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop holding on to ppls mistakes, like y’all don’t make em. We say and do dumb things while learning in life. Shit happens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WitmerCarl @jjauthor @KayHair1 @SharylAttkisson @r98121261 @larryelder @adjunctprofessr @IsraelUSAforevr… https://t.co/7qr6cABUYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miami Beach fun. #sun #southbeach #miami #vacation #bearded @ Ocean Drive, South Beach https://t.co/efowEpd8Iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once this beard comes back it’s over for y’all #NewProfilePic https://t.co/qqQzThMDqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance Not-Florida has been heard from now. (see pretend protester #6) Thanks, Mrs. Betty Bowers, America's… https://t.co/oMjXTfDgSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beware of haters who downplay shit you wanna do/are doing for your self/life. Deep down they be wanting it for them… https://t.co/o2NEU8Xzx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alguien me puede decir porque de momento veo tanto odio hacia la persona de la derecha que lleva un vestido?]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Bruno Ganz, the actor who launched a zillion memes.  I have to admit that this internet search was the first th… https://t.co/fBbKsR4bZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pocos lugares en el mundo Apoyan tanto a un artista como en MTY!!! Puedo decirlo desde mi experiencia Solista , con… https://t.co/uKEmLdaRHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daryl Morey has been contracted as Czar of Analytics - Gaine is O’Brien’s “Paulie” who will throw a golden Rolex at… https://t.co/d4se8uqaxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp it's surgery day. Been waiting for this for about 15 years... #LetsFixMyHeart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DetLionsGuru @WillFTB @Ebron85 @AdamSchefter Same player with like 3 times the opportunity, I don't get why that's… https://t.co/XN0XFBJIyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @Morning_Joe @KamalaHarris @JoeBiden   Look at history. It was Harry Truman that 1st recognized Israel as a… https://t.co/r9vtUi4IqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disgusting. Every cop involved should be under arrest for some level of homicide - non-policemen doing the same thi… https://t.co/LtknBHeB1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dream job flies me around world which allows me to fulfill another life dream of training with other martial art… https://t.co/0cohWNbUpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. mar­kets are closed for the Pres­i­dents’ Day hol­i­day. Dow Jones In­dustrial Av­er­age fu­tures were up 0.1%… https://t.co/4xF9bBcVp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarthGandalf1 I think those of us not really vested in the Hollywood movie scene just assume this kind of move is very normal in Hollywood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Let me hold thr doir open so Cory can leave and find another place to live where he can be a freeloader and parasite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travistritt @CNNPolitics Hes toast n sinking fast, blah, blah, blah is all I hear from him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCVB the kid was kind of asking for it if he went into a cooler and closed the lid on himself]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u bitch abt coworkers taking smoke breaks just start smoking and stfu.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am the married - kids - monogamous version of my idol @danbilzeriandan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crogthefrog @SjwSpiderman @renfamous Thats not a nice way to talk to someone im just trying to get both sides thats all]]></document><document><![CDATA[nyxl was the best new york sports team for much of 2018 and i expect the same for 2019. and lol the mets https://t.co/QfZMou6ROA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Mike Illitch were still around, we’d be having a dual Bryce Harper and Dallas Keuchel press conference right about now. #Tigers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preparing for lift-off!  #LaserHairRemoval #Laser #ObligatorySelfie @ Texas Laser and Aesthetics Training Academy https://t.co/Ql64arT4Cp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo This ones easy! My dad, he retired and turned 65 in back to back days. If it wasn’t 30 degrees in AL… https://t.co/vhHCDJWPeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re really bored this morning, you can track my race in 3 hours. Hills and it’s going to be right about freez… https://t.co/8aJIFarZ7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends @FoxNews @OutnumberedFNC @TheFive @BretBaier @TheStoryFNC @TuckerCarlson @seanhannity @IngrahamAngle… https://t.co/3mZk8IfOzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 Look this is America Land of the Free, and Home of the Brave. We fought and died for the freedom to we… https://t.co/m0Bk9iTMWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The car is certified pre-owned and still under warranty until August 2019.  A little more than 3 weeks ago it was t… https://t.co/UhwwC6dJkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a day late but I wanna wish a huge happy birthday to the homie @NANCEraps! Hope you enjoyed bro!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good example of Filthy Craigslist and the lack of law and order.  Bankrupt Media. Scam Poster. https://t.co/R4Cp2ePOXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude made numerous throws like this, that were near perfect and were dropped regularly. Then we got to listen to fa… https://t.co/VBsluykV98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@popculturecube I know they have a cruise and hang out with other comedians I like, such as Big Jay Oakerson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenManzano Karen , te ves preciosa y muy sexy como siempre en Súper Estadio me encantas que tengas lindo día besos 😍😘😘😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AWardSports Is Wisky a win to get in game? Or do they just need win their first B1G tourney game?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@intense3698 @Cruz_Azul_FC @peladoalmeyda @RicardoLaVolpeG Almeyda no creo , la volpe tal vez , tal vez ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw @realDonaldTrump @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong… https://t.co/OSJijHFKrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkBourrie Controlling southern Ontario to First Nations also meant the control of fire.  As huge flint deposits… https://t.co/msDvtdIdNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GopherBBallFan @SJayToday @pauljohnscott If I didn't eat animals I would be a dead human being. So I will continue… https://t.co/aHdYQDQuQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccdetroitGCS @Squares2Circles @ZaneMoneyEllis Great hole! Good risk reward design, some of the bunkering has chang… https://t.co/mxDDtPfcq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AggieBaseball Fingers too far apart, clearly you don’t party @mchoehner]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a fan of the guy at all, but how can you be a fan of CM and call the police when he becomes violent when you pi… https://t.co/JP03jq3K6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frugalphysician @Orthofacts Not to be mean, but emergencies are unpredictable and unexpected. We willingly sign up… https://t.co/igRiJDtQnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LlLWALMART I eat before, during, after. I am eating or drinking all day to be honest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonBritsch1 @Pluckers I cannot disagree what-so-ever!  That's why I need an @Pluckers some where here in Central… https://t.co/cSGMqZhEtJ]]></document></documents></author>