<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[my urge to nap was interrupted by the idea of some big ass spider being in my sheets i’m scared and cold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra SHE IS NOTHING BUT A BIG MOUTH HYPOCRITE AND A LIAR!!   IF I WERE A DEMOCRAT IN CONGRESS I WOULD TELL… https://t.co/tyh6E63037]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobeBrick @Johnway44887993 @DonaldJTrumpJr And u would be a trump koolaid drinker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's an idea. take your kids to an actual snow park to play in the snow. Not on the side of our fucking highways… https://t.co/Th9Hok3iHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This makes me question every female’s picture on the internet. I didn’t even know this was possible.   What do ya’l… https://t.co/DjfxXMlsCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, in season 5, ep3 of Friends, when Phoebe is admitted to give birth, we find out her doctor can't make it. Why,… https://t.co/KlnTfcBf3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the first officer of this flight had to have his mom drop him off at work this morning #pup #offtoNYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super happy my kids aren’t here to listen to the Marion fans yell disgusting things about the refs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @VP @StateDept #diplomacy @Pentagon @Deptofdefense @TheJointstaff. Fyi.  Retweet. Gloria]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the epic view on our way home from Omaha, @SouthwestAir https://t.co/8PCavn9S02]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Vitamins and Meds 💊 💊 💊 (@ Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA) https://t.co/AW7Ysfo8TJ https://t.co/sNm2wmfxo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Mom! It’s snowing, let me in!❄️🐶💙 #loveyourpetday #littlewitt #cute #dogsofinstagram #havanese… https://t.co/v4Dlo28OK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackInkCrew I’m white and I use the word nigga all the time and I live in the projects. #blackinkchicago get it r… https://t.co/Tvd8JfMT4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FierceEmmy Home from rehab, 21 days clean today!!!!🤓 and saw my sponsor tonight for the first time since August!!!💛 feeling grateful😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if financial predator angle plays well in middle America #Sxsw #demprimary it’s one thing to think, it’s n… https://t.co/95L74Onwd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stonekettle @IvankaTrump   Just like you did, right? What a crock of sh-t!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SerenaForCO for your yes vote on this life saving common sense gun legislation! #EndGunViolence #ERPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[ugh i eat like garbage one night and the whole next day i feel awful. why cant i cheat a little bit in peace:(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encontramos un encantador restaurante middle east en Beacon. https://t.co/mgN9HMQHxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaG2772 As long as it’s not a herd of thees https://t.co/a2ylDDJs6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just cause he’s being super cute this morning! @ Saint-Bruno-de-Montarville, Quebec https://t.co/Y3qgOUYwAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wes Anderson Curates His First Art Exhibition - https://t.co/tMO0sE01Ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[broken clouds -&gt; smoke temperature down 56°F -&gt; 49°F humidity up 67% -&gt; 81% wind 2mph -&gt; 5mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAArmijo2 I used to read Green Eggs and Ham to my brother when he was little, definitely my favorite❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy 18th ellie!!! life would be dull and boring without you ❤❤ love you so much sis and can't wait until you're a… https://t.co/vQE2Fj4TRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanRenner2 @NoahReed23 By you airing this episode tonight you poured salt on old wounds, and have disrespected… https://t.co/7YILploHzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Echo:  A Dystopian Science Fiction Novel https://t.co/pJCF9ifcWP via @kentwayne108]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miss_Placed_ @realDonaldTrump @BernieSanders Yikes. Old man and the sea (of whiteness). I got some good music in s… https://t.co/JjwRzrOALl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WBIRAbby Marlon Brando wins hands down, dead or alive. If you want living, Leonardo DiCaprio. 🥰🥰🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tweetyourunpopularopinion I didn’t like A Star Is Born. It’s the fourth rendition of the movie, I’m not crazy about any of them. 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn. I still can’t believe I got fucked over. 😂😂 Lowkey hurt but whatever. I deserve better anyway lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge adoption event at the Norfolk Naval Exchange!! Come say hi, find a friend or maybe help the cau$e #petapalooza… https://t.co/OrepR4QcJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[An #AACPSAwesome morning at Belle Grove ES where Arts Integrated (AI) learning comes to life throughout the school!… https://t.co/n21mFEmnEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Literacy Lowdown for March focuses on engaging reluctant readers. Check it out! @LTPS1 #TLAP #LeadLAP #4ocfpln  https://t.co/oeRvfGBBJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1972babbbby No, but the two men the documentary hinges on lied under oath. One of them was shopping a book deal. R… https://t.co/nT4rZ4a5Q5]]></document><document><![CDATA[if a guy tells you he doesn’t even mind kissing you when you have morning breath, would that be considered a compliment orrrrrr?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Century Orthotics - See Why we are trusted for Medical Equipment. We are the leading suppliers of Orthotics equipme… https://t.co/9O46rUcGOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen up Bernie supporters. You’ve had three years to work with the DNC and state legislators to learn about and c… https://t.co/DG2xzVtcnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doug_Lemov Bc from what I’ve understood from #CogSci is that just copying/writing isn’t challenging enough - must… https://t.co/MyegPfThDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come join us #mickysweho #oscars #gatorosso #mickysweho #gatorosso WATCH: https://t.co/dggXKC0iMU https://t.co/1ldhsxgQwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guy who won’t stop tweeting at me. Please report for targeted harassment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets go Jayhawks!  Got my lucky Star Wars pants on so we good👍🏻 #kubball]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is dedicated to the Lover in U ... Press Play ▶️  #RotationsMixShow ♥️It’s a Love Thang ♥️ #LiveMix up now (cl… https://t.co/jJk4YYAP6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeepsGreen @Legendary1941 @TopJeepers @wve1022 @steelecreations @XBullofficial @Shelli69jeeper @KrawlAmerica… https://t.co/bpr5ZvU74i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm  not your normal 24 year old because some of favorite XM stations are 70s on 7, 80s on 8, 90s on 9, pop2k.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lively_Ghosts Nice! I’m in bed on my phone because it’s midnight in Atlanta. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[all the 80’s were missing was us and Rihanna @ 80sthen80snow https://t.co/hBvKssVWIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe it or not, a social media agency can strengthen your brand. How?   It’s simple. Visit now 👉… https://t.co/BKEUvhkQQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Geographic Photographers Show Us Their Selfies  https://t.co/wKqDcIaYth via @NatGeoPhotos]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone told me that I will end up in Vegas to "relax" I would laugh at them. I'm in Vegas for relaxation. If yo… https://t.co/iByHNnbfUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turquoise Earrings 💙  Turquoise offers protection, healing, self-forgiveness, acceptance and peace. It releases reg… https://t.co/EjWll96v82]]></document><document><![CDATA[my friends always know what to say to make me feel better https://t.co/rTiXCtyvM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepBrianFitz As my representative I want to publicly thank you for voting for universal background checks today. I… https://t.co/D3KkQmqaXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diamondzz16 @RylieHowman16 That’s funny, this is her mom and I don’t think we’ve meant!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough travel day but we made it!  . . . #johnfrancis ✈️☀️🏖 @ Fort DeSoto North Beach, St Petersburg, FL https://t.co/31iRmfCzQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course the night wouldn’t have been complete without a Little Flower alumnae photo! 😋 “Fore'er we will be true!”… https://t.co/fmK1Udvys6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justuseapen @JackPosobiec Sapiro is too insulting to everyone.  I agree with him but he insults people.   He's lik… https://t.co/MkjlJiktUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[that include cheaper generic medicines and faster access to new cures than in many foreign countries, said Zirkelba… https://t.co/yNqfc3ktTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyDm101 A significant portion. A lot of people did vote for him so they could do things like take their kids to… https://t.co/23X4bPwFn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your pussy basura, my pussy horchata. - Cardi B had got to be the best line I've heard in a while 👏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[What rain? #kreweofnyx #hailnyx #raingoaway #mardigras #waitingtoroll @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/7qNDS6ihQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CensoredSammi @ThePaleoRider @newell601 @promax4Trump @SALUTETRUMP @vision835 @Koolmoe21 @bamabeckygirl… https://t.co/g8eile9zoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBloomberg : good morning Mike. Here's article about #coal &amp; #climatechange. Fyi. Retweet. Gloria]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know what a bring the table and if a mf can’t see it right in front of them , they can get up and walk out the do… https://t.co/QTtBLGi7qv]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a special treat from Misss Wheeler’s class today! A smiley face piece of pizza they made for their “How to” wr… https://t.co/m3qEhjN555]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SignYouKnowYoureGettingOlder Attended a space clearing workshop on a Friday night  (It was A+) #BluebirdWellness https://t.co/gCXw42Z2LD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Selfmade_Niquaa Lmmfao 😂😂😂 fuck that shit y’all look good &amp; y’all both look happy ( just make a baby already )]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PageSix @nypost @AOC obviously they could have used this money to fix the 1 train. What were they thinking using t… https://t.co/Nb6EDNLTru]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to lace my guys as the home screen🖤💛 @Cantguardmike https://t.co/oL9N5dmW4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started throwing up, Jeff walks in with a water, grabs my hair and rubs my back #keeper]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how many times I’ve tweeted about how leggings aren’t pants. Anyways leggings aren’t pants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanSalazarCO @emmyruiz @vvaldiv @alanamounce @natimontelongo @HillaryClinton Love this pic @AlanSalazarCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa Unfortunately if you don’t side with them ,  you wrong🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter, Tiffany Manning, in Dreds. Geraldine Manning https://t.co/071fiXaccF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Namecheap Trying to move a site using duplicator to an addon domain but I can't get the installer to run and I'm not exactly sure why]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honoring one the favorite author of all-time. #DrSeuss https://t.co/AafOh73JFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[4. TONY TAKITANI completely wrecked me. I cried as I walked out of the theater all the way to a restaurant down the… https://t.co/YlB81QvqVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desde que llegue todo lo dias he comido comida chatarra. Mañana empiezo a salir a correr acá, o bueno, eso espero.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When to see Frozen on Ice with the girls and my aunt. It was absolutely amazing. #mommysprincess👑… https://t.co/SZbkkRYVWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ldogls @oldmanliver @EveScottGarner @HondoResists @ldog562 @gtlang74 @RealAntHen @Jessie092859463 @Uhuruhsiempre… https://t.co/KVdtKP3w4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_pence @realDonaldTrump @MattBevin Are you as two-faced as Trump is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found some pants! (at @LaneBryant in San Marcos, TX) https://t.co/ljn6WQyk20]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing “I miss you” from a guy you like deeply really does something to ya 😩🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[But can we all agree that the final season of House of Cards was just...weird?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sa d’laire brûler mais omg le brûler est la meilleure partie avec le fromage! #foodporn #sundaynight #oscarnight @… https://t.co/lqdgVplCPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The refusal to provide adeq funds=(@CPBmedia),CBP,ICE(detention/appreh/reg+CBGC+asylum assist services+HR 3772; No… https://t.co/YdYe6EtHnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adnilxa @ivyjofreeman @Jamiebabiez @american2084 @cornish1969 @CIAnderson3 @JohnRaimondo5 @flyaway_k… https://t.co/sTDyAnJjQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@satanicswift13 @katiapadillaa She’s also a western feminist who doesn’t know when to stay in her lane some times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, can we have a discussion about how awesome it was that she ran around in a @nineinchnails shirt?]]></document><document><![CDATA[can I have a do-over for my quinceañera so kacey musgraves can perform at it pls thx]]></document><document><![CDATA[May be a new book for my art history book club @ Fort Mason Center for Arts &amp; Culture https://t.co/5OBgNYbhgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hawkbr549 @TweetyKat1005 @sissypuckett3 @lesleyabravanel @MichaelCohen212 @POTUS @realDonaldTrump And you can leave! Bye 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayserlein The ironic thing about the lead in “Fastest Finger First” is that she’s a legit and decent onscreen act… https://t.co/zyyKuq4In7]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GeraldoRivera @kuamejackson_ @marthamaccallum Once the media that's been sued for libel in the attack of the… https://t.co/D633Ng6SQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for letting me go on vacation with you 😜💙 @NJOMZA https://t.co/QTAEcHGnKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moonkat1234 @4GISHandReedus @i_GhostTwd @Heidi_Eileen73 @Stef_Helen @HeyMo517 @AntoniaSchmitt4 @smoking_reedus… https://t.co/A5RAyPkAOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsklinkreads I actually have to read one today for AP Lit! Getting my study on ✌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyMissCarly He was so gorgeous. I know he had a wonderful life with his human family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteReweetsDogs @HoneyRamblings @tomas_today @gucci Says the person behind tomas today ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VolunteerFla @AmeriCorps @MetroMinistries PEACE N LOVE EVERY ONE  AND HAPPY MENTORS YEAR ❣]]></document></documents></author>