<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Coming up at 4 — Residents in Clifton Park are on edge after a series of break-ins. Captain Brown with… https://t.co/VIydYRuoHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the outcomes of the #SchoolHealthChat was the  @schoolnurses #Tweetiatricians were from all parts of the cou… https://t.co/sNmgDQ4i1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nature_pixxx Tell that pesky Mockingbird to knock it off. Maybe if I ignore it long enough it will go away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@husky_superman 80's kid here so I'd have to go with this one if I were doing this challenge. He's got such a disti… https://t.co/PgH62Vaz9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TinFoilAwards @tharon_pleiades @Awithonelison @RogueTrader84 @urbanx_f @KrochetxKorner @EmmaGPaley… https://t.co/cbyaVKxNMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikesacconetv I know. Miserable. I’m not typically negative, but as a daily commuter, happy to provide any additio… https://t.co/7fjg543d3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[How the fuck you gonna get an attitude after you hit me with the door..? I should have slapped the shot out of you, but I’m a new man lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ingebear09 @BlindMelon1967 @MizzLRenee @stuarm2 @BeautyAbounds4U @KinmartinTori @CajunBlueAZ1 @Sarahwaugh20… https://t.co/tVYS9FWUrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to get it done!@brennanm_1019 @Treystokes3 @metzican10 @cadevernetti @MillerAbernathy @Nick_Williams35 @kolestewart_23 #ATbaseballfamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Love Your Pet Day! We are doggie lovers here at The Crystal Clear Team 🐶❤️ • • •… https://t.co/yGMlIYIJ7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danusiafrancis Is it possible to do a round off with an extra half twist before your feet snap down and then tumble forwards out of it?🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[in anticipation of feeling extremely lonely next month, i have opted to take in an elderly teacup chihuahua named d… https://t.co/6pPtTvjDj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I reaching for being annoyed that it took someone that you’re trying to get to know 3 days to hit you up? I bloc… https://t.co/ikkqwVNsJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely right and the same empty promises the Dems and Republicans have made over and over. They have political… https://t.co/OmQfqnLcjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m screaming! Once again @79SemiFinalist has included #Deaf visibility with her latest issue of #CaptainMarvel! Wi… https://t.co/4aeicj7FxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Are you some kind of a moron this president haven’t put America fist since he got electe… https://t.co/23Sl3CIP6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PFcardinals Heard that the hockey game for this evening was cancelled... can you confirm?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErwinRWB @JetsPrincipal @PosProject @JaBry20 @kerrileewalsh @justinahrens @_Brian_Johnson @MicheleCorbat… https://t.co/SND5K1T7RD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorksConcierge @TracyPereira20 @jillianne_gray @Fiery01Red @TheSavvyChef1 @Julianna_glass @DivaVinophile @magee333… https://t.co/SCf1zHq91V]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brain has too many tabs open #Repost @kiffaniestahle with get_repost ・・・ My morning: Random music playing from s… https://t.co/5Lx0sBOjtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[3.5M The number of pounds of neonics that were applied to 127 million acres of crops as of 2011, double t… https://t.co/FGVyQkuv2o via @nrdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Squirrels and birds gather, and now my watch begins. #lovemyWillowPickle #guardtheperimeter #nosquirrelsallowed🐿… https://t.co/xtJ80db87J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omm if i don’t get to see @destiny_nnicole whenever she comes back to Oklahoma imma be MAD mad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5: Steam challenges.  Ss who never speak are often the ones advertising their finished product.  Also incorporatin… https://t.co/Ttrr6Yu74r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would get in so many accidents if I lived in Dallas. I have no patience for the traffic]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so very #AliefProud that the outstanding @MrsAVega will represent @Aliefsneed for AISD District Teacher of the… https://t.co/L8Y2BBV0TN]]></document><document><![CDATA[📷 mibeachtowns beemanpam I would love to take my hammock to #lakemichigan and set it up like this!  . . #Repost mib… https://t.co/qJgNF04kYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[breakfast of the kings (@ Hash House a Go Go - @caesarsent in Las Vegas, NV) https://t.co/zsY86H1ZbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[oregano            my dad                               🤝               leaves]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely love this 1795 Mexican 8 Reale . . . . . . . . . . . . #coins #coin #money #instagood #instadaily… https://t.co/ya1dGtYjXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrouciDjamila @DailyMirror @TheSoundOfAnim1 That is great Michael saves animals I only wish more people could be l… https://t.co/NzvD6w8q3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Announce Ole, Woodward! It's been like 45 minutes. Lifetime contract. All the transfer money. Get it done]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daytrip to Niland aka Slab City #SalvationMountain  #nerdygirl #inkedgirl #desertliving #SoCal #ImperialValley… https://t.co/km9zriXbed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all don’t know panic until you forget to lock the bathroom door, sit down to poop, get on your phone and then BAM… https://t.co/ha00QlTrQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up early to finish work is NEVER the move &amp; for some reason I always play myself believing that it is 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metheridge Safe travels! Have an amazing time :) See you and Linda on the cruise 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donlemon @ChrisCuomo Why hasn’t #CNN given more coverage to an actual case of #VoterFraud in #NC09 ? GOP have been… https://t.co/X62oHMUNBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our snowy Superman! He told me he wanted to dig out the firepit (since it's so nice out at 25°) so we can have a "d… https://t.co/WBCbBJiJ5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sorry President. These people need to go to jail with Hillary and that Corrupt Obama who almost took this Countr… https://t.co/RO8cwOUPL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[GREAT meet for kacie._.niehaus !!! She got 1st on Vault, 3rd on Beam and Floor and 2nd All Around!! So proud of you… https://t.co/RYgORdlVAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Digging in with @AussiRc fanfic while I wait for my valentine reveal 😜🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[How are we just now starting our night?! This 12 hour road trip kick my ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My special hearts #HappyValentinesDay #vizsla #happypups https://t.co/CDYQowNIUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I practice yoga with my children in my classroom, every Monday and Friday. I’ve been doing it for years. They love… https://t.co/cBujnEbwoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[She needs to be REMOVED from CONGRESS and DEPORT her she's NOTHING BUT a radical islamic terrorist who has infiltra… https://t.co/Ln5i40xH8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CashMooo @CashMooo come on, you can wish, pray, beg. It will never happen because even Andrew doesn’t know what he believes in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you haven’t even been separated from your husband for a year (divorced like 2months) &amp; you’re already engaged and pregnant 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is s #throwbacktuesday to honor a special week for @TheRealLukevans   Cymru am byth #Luketeers https://t.co/VaVPDgMJNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeriBrown1 😂😂 Girl threw some mad shade at Robin. That was so good. #TLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when people confide in me and trust me. It means I’m doing something right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the spirit of Valentine's Day, here are a few ways to show your friends that you care, including free valentines… https://t.co/Zyp431YbcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stand before a governmental body as a real victim of voter suppression? I'm called and discounted as being a 'myt… https://t.co/SPVocjjpVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJasonJohnson @hiramcollege How many will blame Mexicans? Too many Dems have failed to say that NAFTA did not req… https://t.co/D4JjnbvxX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few things needed (at @Walmart Supercenter in King of Prussia, PA) https://t.co/kfXI5Z8hD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein Every 11 minutes someone in the USA dies from Fentanyl Drug overdose.  And the Democrats don’t see an… https://t.co/QdFdRPhgRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharonainvegas Never been a fan of Rod. Like some of his songs but no - do not think he’s sexy. At all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleighPanetta That’s definitely you Ky! The moment @iamcardib comes on lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cptnmarv @SanAntonioFC @toyotafield I sooooo agree. Everyone in San Antonio should be there. Fantastic Family Fun!!! ⚽😊👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AMTRA2019 @AMTNYS Elementary Teachers Represent! https://t.co/2u9QNHI2mQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hosting our first party in our new apartment I am so excited I am going to explode @Mandizzle1294]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianefallon @speechboy71 Were all crushed that the Senate is controlled by Mitch McConnell - but it doesn’t make it less true]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my happy place! Of course painting new things calls for new brushes! ❤️❤️🧜‍♀️🖌🎨 https://t.co/thUI20TuCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 That puts it right out there. Repuglicans only believe in a democracy owned by them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr How do you explain the Socialism in the Scandinavian countries?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amasonic I think so.. It makes someone to unfollow you without them knowing.   I have noticed it more within the p… https://t.co/XfUBhzM2rw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been waiting for a business call since 2pm today.  It’s 11:45pm and all I want to do is go to bed but homie ju… https://t.co/IY1lW8UGUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lena_valentin_ Good Morning, never concern yourself. Lell said it best for me. Good friends always pick up the con… https://t.co/n55JD6EbJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya never realize how much you take breathing out of two nostrils for granted until you have a cold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardi B x Bruno Mars! Yass! What a bop!! Giving me r&amp;b vibes #PleaseMe 🙌🏼🙌🏼😍#cardibxbrunomars]]></document><document><![CDATA[+ my response to @brewstea so many years ago when he got me a present for our first valentine's together: "Only inv… https://t.co/xQ1UzXQJ9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SealTeamcbsfans @David_Boreanaz @SEALTeamCBS reminds me of my days being a cook in the military, but we were not c… https://t.co/cltEkWR1vV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The National Guard has been activated and is ready to help clear fallen trees and keep roadways safe @SPECNewsBuffalo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday celebration with the kids! #Fratellinos @ Fratellino's Italian Restaurant https://t.co/q9POovGtib]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the world coming to? Today’s top story... #Jaguar selfie gone wrong.   The zoo says this lady crossed the b… https://t.co/xhVsB3Ljgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Independent And it proves they need a host. It went deadpan after the music!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Documental sobre el gobierno argentino custodiando la verdura  https://t.co/PY7kg5V8w0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsBAB77 @douglasrayburn @father_kipz @SoulfulStitcher @NixonandIke @cnnbrk So, that makes this ok?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heartbroken to hear that Luke Perry passed away.. BH 90210 was one of my favorite shows 😥 RIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[• Greetings From Me To Blue 💙 If you’re looking for something to watch on Netflix, then check out Ellen’s stand-up… https://t.co/iDdwujcute]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby fever hit me right in the uterus with this angel dancing right here]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vending spots are 1st come 1st serve. Only 2 spots left! Send DM for more info.   Tickets are selling for the Ladie… https://t.co/GiW9KWaCZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once I get that sense of people doubting me, then I’m out. Don’t don’t me nor test me. #ChildishGames]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep running into the cute guy who sits next to me in class...what if he thinks I follow him?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[and i’m just gonna take a guess here and that tomorrow is gonna suck too 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re not best friends if their mom hasn’t tried to adopt you at least once]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, everyone may hate writing papers/reports but we need to in order to do something about Officer Tucker. Yo… https://t.co/gsuhR33orf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump When a president can have the most intelligent and educated people around him and he chooses his d… https://t.co/9huSJ3bgc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It has happened. I honest to God can not remember the last time I had my period. #old #menopause]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just the type of luck that we have fuck Pittsburg and all these robberies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine signing a baseball player to your team for 13 years that’s so stupid you better hope Bryce Harper doesn’t s… https://t.co/8F3jf4vo8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished up! #orangetheory #keepburning #fabruary https://t.co/X28WLZR1kR]]></document><document><![CDATA[“oh well i live eight across the street from you guys, i thought you would make an exception.”  i still told her “i… https://t.co/wRgUAHxTsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@countryboots126 @CBSTweet Yep mine too!! All I look forward too on Friday night's is a new episode of MacGyver. Not a stupid interview!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starofthesea007 @FionaMorgan79 @thatsVeryKari @suziday123 @CaththeWineLady @SteveKubota @joneill55 @Cbp8Cindy… https://t.co/5ZyuTnXgp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm on a weight loss program and like 5 girls just walked by me with boxes of Girl Scout cookies lol total laughtrack moment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited to start this year's #the100dayproject and I'm going with 100 days of gouache florals using only my n… https://t.co/3GravKwETf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinbieber happy birthday. plz drop another banger. it’s been a minute.  ily.]]></document><document><![CDATA[About a year ago... I lost Leia Organa and had to put this awesome, beautiful, vivacious soul to sleep. I was there… https://t.co/2YB7IcQ4zV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wfaa if the wall is such an emergency, why has it taken him so long to declare it? #iamup]]></document><document><![CDATA[O Lawd in my sleep all night long I’m hearing 🎤 @DArealBBJUDY Baby Shark, &amp; @InayahLamis N.A.S. Both songs playing back to back! 🤷🏾‍♀️😆]]></document></documents></author>