<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Sixteen Degrees  . . . . . . . . . #iowa #hawkeye #hawkeyestate #sixteendegrees #farenheit #cornfield #winterseason… https://t.co/Ak07Wrah5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[there was so much trash in the ocean when i was surfing this morning it’s so depressing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll take the win, but this Auburn team does not have the mentality or focus to play a 40-minute game. All we can h… https://t.co/pvHIsnVTaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinecenega @EWErickson We’ll never know.  Fine one day, autistic the next.  The only thing that was different was… https://t.co/LGK2NJ77Re]]></document><document><![CDATA[/Me-coat, peacoat./ A quality pea coat can last for a long time, so consider investing in one that looks as good as… https://t.co/JFOyco9D5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luke_J_Lowry_23 @52Kevo Looking like your home !!!   I     -     L     -     L     !!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[1956 QSL card Postcard Bulawayo Southern Rhodesia Giraffe Monkey Radio Station  https://t.co/gSeHL14Ima via @eBay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SotoColor I once had an inker call me and apologize because the editor wanted the final art to ape the regular pencil artist on the book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amazon abandons #NewYork campus plans. They should come to #Kentucky instead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bang and a breakfast taco, getting this work day started right. Hopefully I stay dry 🤦🏻‍♂️💤]]></document><document><![CDATA[#jazz #keeptheartsalive dianeschuur sing #coleporter #charleston @ Charleston Music Hall https://t.co/qItlan0ZAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The molinaboys and that would be #JordyBoysSnickerDoodle trying to give me a kiss. #MolinaBoys #JordyBoy #Shmeedy… https://t.co/tNvx91bFtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hawkins sinks both. Timeout Northwest. Bearcats lead 82-79 with 2.7 remaining. Hornets will get one final shot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting in our boats and getting as many fish back to our camp site as possible! #GoingFishing https://t.co/48tZZJU03L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcnees I've been so out of the loop that I have no idea who Joey Baker is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #iie100  Cheers to another 100 in fostering human relations and cultural understanding accross nations.  I su… https://t.co/QH5Kq1z2t3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AikmanCMU @tw_simpson @SinBinVegas Moot point now he’s a San Jose Shark]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young, Crumly Take Top USA South Men's Basketball Honors https://t.co/LWCzfsY1hR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaMoeX @scarletestrada @AbbyMartin @SenSanders https://t.co/QuSWlWAFfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess he was right. Slavery was a choice just like you signing that contract was a choice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really wow you gonna fight a woman 2 yeah u a thug dude Joel Embid will beat that ass shit anyone of us would. U ar… https://t.co/5BqaHwvP5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulZeise Don’t forget about (financial) flexibility....thanks for answering my Pitt mailbag question.  Saw last n… https://t.co/qAKHmtL18j]]></document><document><![CDATA[The question mark was suggesting debate, not a judgment. But your point is taken. Thank you for giving it a shot an… https://t.co/M74bknWkzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting external traffic into Kubernetes – ClusterIp, NodePort, LoadBalancer, and Ingress https://t.co/xsgM0Sj7Cp v… https://t.co/dFTpQhvBNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up to the news the #Eagles extended Brandon Graham @brandongraham55 @Eagles @4thandJawn https://t.co/vJdlQl3Pw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PnPCBC @Paola_Dec1231 @scottbrison @Puglaas @JustinTrudeau @JustinTrudeau @Evelynne24 @AndrewScheer @joeblow745… https://t.co/7wEHTxndOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christopher_All Hanging in there. Lost a student this week. Been a rough time. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Stronghold of the Syndicate in Walker, MI https://t.co/JNi18QrOvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1043TheFan Well, I love the other fellas but Big Al was my favorite and he and DMac has such great chemistry on the afternoon drive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zekewatch317 @BuzzPatterson @Acosta @realDonaldTrump Your correct only CNN is enemy of the people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveG_79 @ochocinco Congratulations man. Great to hear kids giving back and helping out their parents!]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPS drivers are the equivalent of the US Navy Seals in the package delivery service world #badasses]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cate_stein @mr_jacobson Shout out to all the KC-area teachers working their second Wednesday of 2019.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I ever get big enough to have a stage set it’s gonna be the WWF In Your House set and we’re coming out to the DX theme.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftwardSwing @SenSanders is the only progressive candidate in the race and that’s why the DNC and MSM will make s… https://t.co/0PvgXzCR5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForzaCorrado It would not surprise me if Jenner entered the Olympics again as a woman🤷🏻‍♂️. He/she would become th… https://t.co/9wKPQl5Wb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flipper frenzy pinball tournament at @ArcadeLegacyOH @arcadelegacy Newport, KY sponsored by @MWSmithRE… https://t.co/cFmG8UaOlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitaniumHammer There are plenty of Catholics on the left. Only alt right Nazi’s fear them, but then again, you onl… https://t.co/MRTzN3HwWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn right. Adults are in charge now. @RepAdamSchiff @RepCummings @RepSwalwell @MarkWarner]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Paris but I’d be afraid if I were in the passenger seat and she was driving 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m listening to killer #music on the #BassBoosted YouTube channel! It’s epic stuff here! #Sounds great on my… https://t.co/SPV1tLf3uG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@destiny_houchin @geethangbabyyy I dunno, you tell me https://t.co/ZOk9S3Kx2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Quest for a Universal Flu Vaccine - A step-wise approach to a universal flu vaccine is necessary to prevent us… https://t.co/mlM0vnrXiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll say it again, that place better be packed for the seniors.  Got my tickets already and so should you… https://t.co/sgHnwJjEpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 51 of 365 Days of Strength:   6” x 5/16” Carriage Bolt crushed to 1/4” gap.   Today I went back to basics. I wa… https://t.co/duY7h70elg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how low our program has sunk - I’m liking a Duke tweet #GoDeacs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanLerner @Rosie Yes, but old corrupt Mitch will not put any of it up for a vote in the senate. So all these bi… https://t.co/Vvc4saeVU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this ain’t me &amp; the homies 80 years from now I’m keeping the reciept 🤟🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's like a Skeksis is on a Mystics' head, just chillin'. #FThisMovieFest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game one of the double header will only be seven innings. Will Proctor is on the mound for Georgia. Freshman Robert… https://t.co/ZSrr8Wi4J4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanadaLove2019 Just because he is prettier than you. That doesnt make him a femibist]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING:  Roger Goodell suspends Patriots owner Robert Kraft for 4 games, names him President of the United States.  #RobertKraft #NFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@francesgates54 @Glurgmanx @geeksabre @GustavoArellano @Scrface87 @MFBALLAM33 @HerringerHeide @ForAllTheMarble… https://t.co/4d6j8XiVTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the weapons of our warfare are not carnal but mighty in God for pulling down strongholds, II…… https://t.co/AR4cZjCPQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted some action shots of a #runners stride. The #rockrollmarathon just happened to be down the block from me.… https://t.co/RLcFsbBWhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Algo que me ha enseñado la música es la constancia y la perseverancia. #musica #música]]></document><document><![CDATA[*breathes*  AMERICANS SUPPORT ISRAEL BECAUSE IT IS A VALUABLE ALLY WITH WHICH WE SHARE COMMON INTERESTS AND VALUES.… https://t.co/wcN6GV36w0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Sustainable Cleveland Center in Cleveland, OH https://t.co/5oa9SBlMAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALSMD_Indy @SusanWBrooks Geez Alan. Didn't your msm news show you the massive size of caravans streaming to our so… https://t.co/esNKkKST9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAG4All @HLAurora63 How come he isn't holding his booking number n where's the side profile. Special treatment aga… https://t.co/HLTTMMJcTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NIK_VENTURE Covering up Congressional do nothing Corrupted Criminal! https://t.co/MEzgHa1YQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valenciam07 Esto sencillamente es estar DOLIDO por estar fuera del presupuesto (chayotero) pues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saying but if @mulaney hosted @nbcsnl every week (like he jokes in the monologue), I would watch it every week. Just saying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quieren venir a presumirme lo logrado Quieren venir atarantarme con mentiras Hagan memoria cuando les di el empujón… https://t.co/qAO1YqxBAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Southwest Highway &amp; Central in Oak Lawn, IL https://t.co/OlXybCm4wO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LawWorksAction American people paid for . . . Well, yeah, but the SCO also has been a revenue generator -- restric… https://t.co/ZbRYA11lTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePhantomFriar @MutCallahan AS far as I know yes,,,, but, I am still trying to find out to be 100% sure,,, check @PShep326  tweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Are we readyyyyyyyyyyyy?  *hair dyer turns on in the bathroom*  Me: I guess not]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanJones A school friend had one in middle school. Kicked out the plate glass picture window during a thunderstorm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great thread with lots of great tips for traveling https://t.co/dgDLmOvtFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing our creative work influence other programs and teams creative!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidChalian for the people of venezuela we should have a massive air drop all over the country of food and medica… https://t.co/QaruzmK8cS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_Priester8 I’ve texted “AB to the Bills!!” to too many people for this trade NOT to be true. And I refuse to beli… https://t.co/gykuFeKPdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an honor for officers_mnm to meet Mr. George! @ North Little Rock, Arkansas https://t.co/WK9FVjDrn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at @CapFriendly, it appears that Columbus only has its third rounder and Calgary’s seventh in June’s… https://t.co/V74MLAOXa7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever realized how different is the learning process of a new skill to a child? Check this video to see the… https://t.co/nWWp3Tznvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulianVevster @iDrewwy drewy u act like I didn't see that clip https://t.co/6o3cnBR7WJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mothersdream @CMHammer732 @masonjar92 That trauma is very often independent, ie it develops later. There are more… https://t.co/9jTrvEGKj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Oreo Tucker!  Couldn’t resist last night.. out with friends when these two beautiful giant black dogs came up.… https://t.co/6pqQMlhpiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[As someone with an addiction, who fell so badly back into it thinking I wouldn’t, I can say I understand so much mo… https://t.co/gAOborxA4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KManriffs @Savagesheepy @loinclothnation @doomedparade @MoMetalTrax @HellionSocMedia @HeaviestofArt @PMetallist… https://t.co/ArsjM0KzcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @geneglobal for making the  #familyday long weekend an extra long one so we can spend time with ones we love… https://t.co/bG7dzL8FNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandakeelley Wait these blow up too says owner of 2  Note 7s &amp; Note 8 now...plus wanting Note X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strass32 @cyclones84 @AwardsDarwin @BrettSchur @dbuck58 @tanker7979 #overserved]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IconMale @DJChiChiLaRue @jesus_really_ @MaxAdonisxxx @ZachCovington25 @JackDyerX1 @scottrileyx @ColbyTuckerXXX… https://t.co/Hw96rqpc61]]></document><document><![CDATA[aldridge_121 vs @noahvonleh I think Aldridge don't want that smoke 😂😂😂 #nyknicks #knicks #nbabasketball #nba #2k19… https://t.co/5E0cr1q709]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to continue to serve @UNCC_SGA for another year! https://t.co/lvEOQjLWRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravodicus1 @NBCNews Fuck off. He gave Kim Jong Un a free pass on the murder of Otto Warmbier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @jorgeramosnews Brian, WHO F@#$ CARES ? He is just like you FAKE NEWS IN SPANISH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He contradicts himself in this tweet. Democrats have absolutely no control over confirmation of executive branch ap… https://t.co/SDZGAHt5qJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Farm to table from the Family Bea: Set up for the Panthers 1st ever 2A crown]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol. Is she going to be handing out be best wreaths made out of pencils? Who does she think she is, running a best… https://t.co/vc8WbY6bHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m973974 @badlemonlax 100 percent. Should not use a stick that’s taller than you untill ~ 8th grade is not HS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @Outback @ZeroWaterFilter @Progressive @CapitalOne @mitsucars @GreatCallInc @onepeloton @Coravin https://t.co/p4JtjANYx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twiggyoffthepat @mingchen37 @michaelzapcic @sundayjeff @Chris_Laudando @franknumberfive @TellEmSteveDave @BQQuinn… https://t.co/T3NEcLAQwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBB: Halftime - C5D6 championship - Hazelwood Central leads Francis Howell Central 30-26. #stlpreps #WeAreSTLToday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Canucks @tannerjpearson Looking forward to seeing him and Bo carry the team to previously unseen heights in sports… https://t.co/1Xfx2BRLxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachGrayvold Terrible by the DE.  Dictate to the offense what you want them to do with the ball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone do not forget to set your clocks ahead 1 hour at 2am on Sunday as Daylight Savings time starts and we lose… https://t.co/9YDhwTZ650]]></document><document><![CDATA[If republicans will just focus on dealing with @SteveKingIA and not letting @mattgaetz drive that would be great. D… https://t.co/oVfIkAfv88]]></document></documents></author>