<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[And yet people think he’s leaving Cash Money (YMCMB) he bout to resign and bring Wayne back in the fold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joey_Baddafuko @USPS I got trolled by some asshole in SF that has nothing better to do than waste his companies time and money smdh 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look man I wanted a piece of that since I was 12 and she was maybe 11  sue me..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who Is Gay and Has Two Thumbs His Guy #InstaGay #Gay #GayGuy #GayBoy #GayMan #GayTeen #GayTravel #GayCute #GayWorld… https://t.co/sZho9IsTG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#centralpark #manhattan #newyork #usa🇺🇸 @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/KXl4J61MkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍 Wishing the birth giver a HAPPYYYYYY BIRTHDAY! I wouldn’t be here without you beautiful. You inspire me! Here’s t… https://t.co/j8oDtJ3YGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrisiskingx There are no replacement adds out there that the AAC whiffed on. The western schools didn’t want to c… https://t.co/MesnrUZCix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_sirhampton_ Lmao nope. Black cement. Few colorways of 9s. 11s. And 1high. All valid. The rest would never make my… https://t.co/lH0WKY8yy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #WeWantNCAAFootball on @tyltsports. It’s the best video game! https://t.co/85h9OLqZAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok Gorton. Today is the day. Trade Zucc trade Hayes and trade Mcquaid. Today. Please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tdonzzz They’re seriously the Tampa Bay Rangers, we have Kreider, Staal, and Henrik left and that’s it, it’s so de… https://t.co/CuF0R1ScWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tariqnasheed If the suspicions are true, this "boy-who-cried-wolf-story" will have negative consequences for years… https://t.co/xRHhVuaQNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACTBrigitte @AgentSoulful007 Bridge.........the democrats aka socialist are going to tear the country apart. Illeg… https://t.co/WYyrL1AHa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frank Gehry has an unending thirst for new work, new ideas, new forms https://t.co/irnRiqWlgg Aaron Betsy via… https://t.co/1EUoaA6dRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s get on a plane. @ John Glenn Columbus International Airport https://t.co/v9E8TIKQ5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alpert Same right winger worried about that also wrote this gem. https://t.co/ywJmaRVdBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found something better than a bae on Valentine's Day...  😅  A little less fulfilling and not quite as fun, but st… https://t.co/NjfU2l4WWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOEL9ONE Maybe you could take Jay Huff under your wing and get him on the buffet line/weight room program. He’s got great potential.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLoveBel0w He also dismantled Cross Fire in a matter of minutes: https://t.co/0Xc30Lptvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[For people going to the #MardiGras parade on Tuesday:  Protect yourself at all times!  Coconuts hurt!  #Zulu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealLucyDavis I wouldn't care, just to have my picture taken with the Etta Candy (the real hero of Wonder Woman)]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all, there is no wall being built at the present time. You are lying again to the American public and we a… https://t.co/QFNq6yrpoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Syracuse’s zone is about as aware of shooters as their Coach is of pedestrians on the highway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family will always be the first to backstab you and talk shit!#FuckFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I do get frustrated. I get frustrated all the time,” Dante Exum admitted. “Just some days I come in and I’m just l… https://t.co/BkdqA7RP5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clippers turned the ball over only 3-times and lead the Jazz in Utah 56-49 at the half. Winner will be #6 in the We… https://t.co/wr3ZwtLgxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @JPrstojevich YES KEEP TELLING US THAT THE GREAT GREEN DEAL IS FREEDOM AND WE SEE SOCIALIST FAT AND TAXPAYERS BROKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS SHIT IS THE MOST INTIMATE AND SENSUAL SHIT I HAVE SEEN IN A WHILE! NEED THIS 😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I used to call them The Peking Press as a 10 year old in NJ, ages ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Marriott, it would be nice to have a room since check in was 4pm and it's now after 10pm.  I booked my room we… https://t.co/4wStlOplw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC Katy back to school learn journalism or reporting. If you wat to be a gossiper join Chrissy Mathews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cameron_kasky I'd go back to 1955, knowing what I know now.  Oh, the MAYHEM!!!! &lt;cackle&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's snowing right now. Seriously? But, here comes the sun. Honestly. Here are 10 tips for brightening the dark day… https://t.co/NbwVbA5Goj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Press Conference Cold Open - SNL https://t.co/TBmzOy8oWM via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[With that said, I’m not going to walk away from the team I’ve cheered for. I’m not going to take it out on the play… https://t.co/am6heDgRlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wiskysin @RubinReport @Timcast Those are some pretty big words he’s tossing around there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you #scotiabank for assembling a perfect rink for the game. Yes. Sarcastic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big thanks to Miguel Bahena for the purchase of his new 2012 Chevrolet Silverado! EVERYONES A WINNER AT SHOALS TRUC… https://t.co/sgBy2Aa3LA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog Hey Matt why don’t you tell us what the author’s “point” was instead of this righteous indignation v… https://t.co/LONFJ0d1To]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You idiot, Kim Jong-Un played you like the moron you are! After, with his approval, they tortured… https://t.co/ILZQUtL2To]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the amount!!!👏👏👏👏👏Covington High student's legal team sues Washington Post  https://t.co/KUrmqhKeCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifethruglasses I’ve always been told I sound country lmao but apparently Midwest niggas ain’t shit but a bunch of… https://t.co/EfDURdQCyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benji963 @slimmo_de @IronClawGaming @BeastFireTimdog I am not going to try to enlighten you. You already have the… https://t.co/hk7YGVn0NK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rocknrollchem @bat_rope My turn at bat was the first sports book I ever read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gate they move us to is a plane that just landed so now we have to wait for that plane to be prepared for the n… https://t.co/ESKmnqt7xD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck @DonaldJTrumpJr @RepAdamSchiff Name calling is the final refuge of the rhetorical bankrupt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC “Until then, we’re in charge - and you’re just shouting from the cheap seats”.  You’re speaking like a true so… https://t.co/ETCFZX9FgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cs00582scs When did they start appointing pajama boys as high school principals? When I went to school that scrub… https://t.co/QOJYOnkVQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anything, it should be raised to 25 when the frontal lobe is more fully developed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adrian "Duncan MacLeod of the Clan MacLeod" Paul is on Arrow?!  Cue "Princes of the Universe".......now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honeyyyyyyyy, please provide us with specifics. I want an address. A neighborhood. A nearby landmark. I’ve lived he… https://t.co/3QWsUREzZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will never see The Riott Squad recruit so many members it becomes irritable like the nWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lou_quittin I never got to swing it... but yeah the F2 was comparable to the orange stealth. DoubleWall technology man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeighRamsdenPGI Limited no trade.  For him to take that, they need to give him term and money closer to what he co… https://t.co/l445zb8bdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[what’s up with comrade Graham. ?    Pentagon chief briefing irks lawmakers, draws expletives from Lindsey Graham… https://t.co/AhZTfPoa5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent. Another taster. Goes great with food in their taproom. - Drinking an 4th Anniversary Belgian Quad by… https://t.co/AeDS4InJ9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madison_lillyy It’s all wack dude🤦🏻‍♂️ doesn’t make sense to me either😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ztrussell @Yair_Rosenberg @jaketapper You understand "saving Jews" means they convert to Christianity, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DomHaskett Speak for yourself. I need the sundress and big fro combo ASAP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarymAlDossary 😅😅😅شر البلية ما يضحك. حتى لو، ممكن تروح للقاضي و يطلقها. فأنا أتوقع الموضوع أكبر من الزوج. ممكن نظر… https://t.co/KyTT1Xbd2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @RicFlairNatrBoy Happy birthday from Arizona. #RicFlairDrip WOOOOOOO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🛑‘It’s on videotape’: MSNBC’s Morning Joe stunned by Trump's obvious lie about ‘Tim Apple’ #Topbuzz… https://t.co/Ag8ESoqW6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RocksBoysXXX @RockRockafella @Rockafellaz Morning rock ..let tweet for a minute..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VSullivan4NH @Oldwvbroad @rickmcd_atx @shannonrwatts @MomsDemand @NRA Google it the pearls are a symbol of a pro g… https://t.co/6KovT1jYsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Doors - Love Her Madly 1971 (High Quality) https://t.co/un0ZJuidb4 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that they changed it so they shoot the free throws after the media timeout now and not before. 🏀 #MSUvsUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen the video this picture is taken from. 7/10 would not recommend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimonMaloy @mmfa She means that any math where you have to carry the 1 never made sense to her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OminousTX Look in the background of the Johnny Cage trailer, standing by the railing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Numb skull never read the Constitution. He needs a political spanking endangering all of New York states population… https://t.co/p8pan76fTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday nights 20 years ago sure were different! But homework’s fun, and my head won’t hurt tomorrow! https://t.co/a859zSt7e4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um...I guess we can but that’s not really our thing. Now, if it were a meteor... https://t.co/sJl5yhbUL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianJMather Different story. Nothing compares to this. F’ing a 7 year old and constantly buggering little boys is… https://t.co/0i7GspLlfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamThomasTSM @Tyler_Lennon You sound like you're firmly out of your prime CT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t seen #dearevanhansenmusical go buy your tickets!  Very talented cast and I can see why it won the To… https://t.co/RpdfTE2lOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5NEWSLaura That is like asking me to go thirty days without breathing! It can't be done! 🤣 https://t.co/Xef0Rq7RUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaySandlin_WHN @nationofnerds @MrNiceGuy18_58 @mrjafri @skywalker_saber @CBNostalgia @WolverSteve @MikeSchmidt09… https://t.co/S9K5dLkdQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m way too invested in this Jeopardy All Star event than I should be. #JeopardyAllStars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picking up lunch (@ Hartz Chicken in Liberty, TX) https://t.co/A64GhfL2iw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The challenge of ‘new life’ is learning how to breath again, walk again, speak again, only at the Spirit’s compulsion and not the flesh’s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebruenig @McKelvie @HowardSchultz I haven’t had a cup of his crap coffee since 2001... I’m not about to start drin… https://t.co/RVJ4uP53TS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to be the Overall Player of the year on the All @ysn365 team https://t.co/pacNVA0XsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Of All, PLEASE Leave Him Before You Even THINK About Cheating!! 😱😰 And Second Of All, Why Is His Potna Your F… https://t.co/8WqhnLSjPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradParker_ @bobbygoode @GavinNewsom He's a Democrat, he spends too much on illegals.. You won't get your rail line....sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[1241 E California Blvd 1241 E California Blvd, Pasadena, CA 91125 https://t.co/CaToVqmthT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some flashbacks here. #Astros #SpringTraining #2007 @ Osceola County Stadium https://t.co/NnLMfykPXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter Sounds like a homosexual thing. Not that there’s anything wrong with that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N_Podralski Not a fan at all. They definitely should have also gotten a pick along with talbot. Doesn’t make sense… https://t.co/iL3IfS61Lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Concord River under snow. Leica lllf, Summicron, 50mm  #leicausa #leica #film #leicalllf #filmphotography… https://t.co/bilXbUkVH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these ALIENS that  chain migrate, keep taking hard working American jobs.  Ask @MichelleObama her job was taken… https://t.co/dItajL3uE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Tower Mobile Home &amp; RV Park https://t.co/ALUNcescHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police and fire crews are on scene of a vehicle fire at the Seven Oaks Motel ( 2331 Princess St )  Update to follow #ygk]]></document><document><![CDATA[A woman is like a teabag, you never know what’s in her until she gets in hot water 🙌🏾 #consultpositivity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Comet IPA by @foundersbrewing at @foundersbrewing — https://t.co/hUs9fdUZow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maaaan Jim Irsay out there in Indiana be cheap ! SPEND THAT SHITTTTT , go get @AB84 !!! https://t.co/sj8phARhvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 142 Austin Niblock of @Phillipsburg_HS comes from behind in the last seconds with the takedown to defeat Billy S… https://t.co/d27u8lG0fe]]></document><document><![CDATA[CRICKETS! #FakeNewsMedia #FakeNews #AOCC2019 #CoreyBooker #NancyPelosi #ChuckSchumer Jussie Smollett’s celeb suppor… https://t.co/71HgPfw8SK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewBerkshire Look at Anderson,if he’s on HABS,they’re not making playoffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald Luckily some of us are old enough to have lived through the period, and to have observed the whole awfu… https://t.co/5sCD50vR2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving Emilia Clarke's dress on the red carpet on @enews coverage. #Oscars #OscarsRedCarpet https://t.co/9I3aKQ6eDw]]></document></documents></author>