<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Democrats are a team that works best when all of its member work together. #MichaelCohenTestimony #StrongerTogether]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s that time of year again! Looking forward to seeing all of my friends in Vegas for the annual WPPI “wedding and… https://t.co/8gPiCKOsUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elitegamerr4 @ThorAnderson8 definitely asked if you him and meangun could join box up. We didn’t want charged so w… https://t.co/leeweLuyYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't ever ask 4 my autograph homie,  you'll be the only 1 that has to pay now. How much!!??? That elbow you owe 4… https://t.co/Dv7wbnkdfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Score, rebound, score, rebound, score, rebound, score, draw foul, rebound, score, rebound, score, rebound, score, r… https://t.co/jLg5MsktGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dreamt that I met @TeamVic and that I was excited to meet him and yelled out "Cruuuuuuz" lol #NYG #randomdream]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOUR IT SIS THATS WHAT THE FUCK IS GOING ON YOUR SNATCHING WUGS ALL OVER HENNEY!!!😍😘❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s not let up! Put pressure on your Republican Senators and Reps. Keep piling on with Social Media posts tagging… https://t.co/8ezoAU7nqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/e8rjg9wOIs   Hi $Biz,  Have a favor to ask.    -Steve  $Biz = @biz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickfrDoylstown Went about it the wrong way.  Let's be honest if said can you play Mr Worldwide it would have been played.  #amatuers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveFurst @IHSAA1 @rtv6 @carmelathletics @CARMEL_BBALL Oh I thought it was you I saw you in line me my son was rig… https://t.co/uhNQSMT0dO]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a commercial driving me crazy. The script and voice-over are desparately trying to sound like Chicago, but… https://t.co/Jsxq8NnmNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowellJerod @ECW4OU The insulting thing is his assumption. Would he make that comment if I were a white male? Prob… https://t.co/rkAW5N71Gf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phillyceltic Now if they couldn’t add someone else because they spent all their money, that’s another story.  Youn… https://t.co/D19bCI6r5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mulanishere If this rain keeps up, your dream might become a reality 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find your best shot with the #GalaxyS10 pro-grade camera #theGalaxyShowLive @theSamsungSide @kn_blurbs… https://t.co/AXA3yNawEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnOpenSecret @tulsaworld Please GoD Judge our House even more , please reap the tares]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS WEEKEND!!! 10th ANNUAL WEST TEXAS TATTOO CONVENTION LISTEN ALL WEEK TO WIN TICKETS! https://t.co/Rf9f7JacRu TO… https://t.co/3I8csKASDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall Hear that Angel’s Laugh in the end😭😩. Last time i saw Rafa.      Rip lil homie👼🏼 @rafaeljaimejr https://t.co/eJqbKRFPxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s two..  🏀VCU -2.5 1H ✅  🏀Wright St. -4 1H ✅  1H bets are 🔥🔥 tonight. #cancelthesecondhalf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluelightdiet @bulletproofexec @TrueDark They block some not all correct?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fascinating how many people swear by Georgia, despite it being a screen font optimized for fairly low resolution ou… https://t.co/WA3Q1106ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RFM275 Funny thing is @Rich_Pietras just calls everything ridiculous without providing any empirical information w… https://t.co/CaEW7f2o7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HernanGomezB A NO BUENO, ES QUE ANTES LES PAGABAN POR MENTIR, AHORA QUIEREN EL MISMO TRATO, DINERO PARA MENTIR RT… https://t.co/Hm9A3BZg1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to order a plate to see what's on it. #ncpol https://t.co/MDyMAmY3uu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The teams played an even quarter. Gladwin holds a 37-24 lead after three https://t.co/i2cjPgX0ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello, Austin.  #sxsw2019 @ Justine's Brasserie https://t.co/gdSZbxUcsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop listening to these folks that tell you all you need to do is drink water and mind your business for clear skin… https://t.co/XpSjVkV5pE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be covering the Pediatric ID/ASP service for the next few months so I better crack this open 👶🏻… https://t.co/e5t4EKMQdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in the day, I used to get excited for a Saturday night after buying a new bottle of whiskey. Now, a new set of… https://t.co/ZnIfg6gdLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AltmanErin @Caz_U_L @JasonSCampbell @realDonaldTrump @IngrahamAngle Outliers like him always want to apply their c… https://t.co/J712G1CjAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchMossRadio @paulyhoward  NHL 2 teamer BUF ML -130 TOR PL +1.5 -215 = +127]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie? Hilary? Beto? Damn y’all really loading a nerf gun..... well there is always 2024 when trumps second term is over 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen! But bring a lot of Vaseline  when you stand before God with because He know where to put.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danbayens Every time UK wins 10 games in football they win the National Championship the following tournament 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SundayFunday I'm serving Hurricane cocktails all week. #IMakeDrinks https://t.co/TM8CI3X5R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum @chrislhayes You should be strung up at The Hague you war criminal]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone always argues, Messi or Ronaldo. shit, im just enjoying the fact we’re getting to watch both of them at th… https://t.co/SSBBVcAI0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the @azcentral. Hopefully we can see similar aggressive coverage in California.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight Chicago Kingston Mines #blues #chicago #chicagoblues #kingstonmines #lincolnparkafterdark #livemusic @ King… https://t.co/dsMXhbIWMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonHulud From my two days in Fargo i came to the conclusion that Fargo and Milwaukee are petty much the same]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’ve had limes...and I’ve had cactus. Both are delicious. And I’m sure together they’re confetti...but in a beer… https://t.co/d9ORuH0sOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You are a public figure now stupid... your address is probably readily available to those that want it.  Polit… https://t.co/Wu1Rt8ofpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch "Kanye West Sunday Service - Father Stretch My Hands PT 1" on YouTube - https://t.co/QKCvX6vSrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OxyMLZ Wooooooow, that's awesome!. Will be open access?. Congrats!. To the team]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phillies are 1-0 in Grapefruit League play without Bryce Harper. Just sayin......]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you need another reason to travel to Greensburg tonight, Preston Bailey will be inducted into the 5th Region  AD… https://t.co/1QzWxBntq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come and see me at LB51 to hear about model selection in ion channel models today at #bps19 https://t.co/L9OKodKagX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weston Mckennie starting vs Mancity in the Champions League   Show them weston!!!! 🇺🇸⚽️ #UCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just submitted my dissertation to my committee!!! All 265 pages!!! "Of Nobler Song Than Mine": Social Justice in th… https://t.co/FfMpMU2PFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the airport. I think my plane is full of some high school trip to Amsterdam. I wonder who my seat mates will be]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raggedtag As long as Pakistan has snakes in their backyard, nothing good will come out of that country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started college in August 1998. Just paid my final student loan payment today. Just in time for my oldest son to… https://t.co/J0iY2BzSP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[giggling &amp; singing fearless  life’s good🙈🙈 @hmsteinnn https://t.co/9ZBcvgpRBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wiselatina626 Studios don’t count!!  I’m talking about when they are on location! LOL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s cold, and wet, and gray outside. So, time for sleeps. . . . #kora #schnau #schnauzer #schnauzersofinstagram… https://t.co/ZmNb8G3I9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOVTWINE Yummm. My mom made the best nasi Goreng, fried rice with chicken, ham and an egg on top. Spiced with sambal oelek.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still not sure why the @NHLFlyers made Tony Beets from Goldrush their mascot #NHLStadiumSeries #PITvsPhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me atrevo a asegurarte que el castillo no es de arena, yo si te amo. Encima de todo esto emerge una verdad que libe… https://t.co/XbM3lfBiKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings @TheLawmakers Are you so full of yourself that you need to justify yourself. You’re an elected officia… https://t.co/DMu0HlCyPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they call on me, I will answer; I will be with them in trouble. I will rescue and honor them Psalm 91:15 NLT… https://t.co/h1N1eb2MCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder why airlines don’t just board people in the order of row and window to aisle, that way people dont have to… https://t.co/YQKmLeFsHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to convince wifey to go to this place for lunch tomorrow. Visited in the past without her.... was divine.  https://t.co/fzSMsArpHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebron finally got himself another superstar teammate, about time @Lakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dnlao Because I’ve done this before &amp; that’s how I finesse the system 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernsySmiles @seanhannity Uhhh no that's a fact..and just for the record Bill Nye isn't even a scientist..thats a fact too lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christian parents who fail to address the chief desires of their child’s heart should not be surprised when their c… https://t.co/wu5zuGxAu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kamitell Communication needs context regardless ...and dude was dm texting while driving... #poor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshMartee @ThomasSowell Perhaps. I understand your point. In fact I agree, but I would argue that they think it is… https://t.co/BaU4OnLkFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Table side prestidigitation this evening @swiftandsonschi https://t.co/lUhgzM6K2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neither rain nor snow nor sleet nor cancelled flights will keep me from the #salesforceohana  3:30AM but I made it!… https://t.co/7FZRiwKDAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone know what pairs well with a @WhiteClaw? Asking for me. https://t.co/j3RKwqhYiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProducerAllieCD Haha fair point but they tend to keep to themselves. Plus they have these big noisemakers on their… https://t.co/QhTIJXKKG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJerryNadler says, “[his] job is to follow the rule of law”.   Apparently, Mueller and the other Congress commit… https://t.co/cAURoRjNlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of these amazing young women! Way to represent Austin HS with grace and excellence. You are so inspiring!… https://t.co/znQ3pySE2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell @NYPost_Lewis and unless Shelly Silver gets paid under the table sports betting won’t be coming to NY… https://t.co/PBw1dmwiNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberBinGA @BrunusCutis Great dog is rollin' 99.99-100% w/ Ghandi &amp; shit..]]></document><document><![CDATA[banana nut bread &amp; almond breeze chocolate milk    https://t.co/9q7calKAVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice save by @FlowHud goalie Will Hannon on a pair of lasers by @GALancerAD's Dominic Casamatta. Hudson kills 2nd p… https://t.co/yhXP7NArQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpbrammer @JoeJohnsonIce @IanABoyd Just like his deep-edged movement over the ice...his rejoinders are vicious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[mine: i need to have weed delivered but it’s raining hard and i have no cash and they charge 5% on plastic #emergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep last night with zero chew toys on my chest and woke up this morning with two chew toys on my chest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing more rewarding than seeing the smile from hard work and progress. Great work Matt, down 65 lbs. in 4 months… https://t.co/SvkubAkrIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have Avengers Endgame tickets gone on sale yet?! I refuse to have this one spoiled]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrIAmBoxing @TMZ 30 divided into $200k = the mark of the beast $666,666😈🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Khanoisseur mankind’s negative environmental impact. After studying the feasibility of using thorium, nuclear scie… https://t.co/d2W12JHjfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#4favs from the first half at Marquette! #LetsGoX https://t.co/JaUNy8e36Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Jake starts using the usual BS to cover his tracks, we’ll know where he stands. He might have, and the key word… https://t.co/YfVqeWb6Jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MongoGoesInsane Come on, no one cares about a 3rd or 4th place team like the Mets!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Gotcha Smokehouse Bar-B-Que in Orlando, FL https://t.co/s6BT3YFatd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lightning are scoring so much I’m gonna have to turn off the alerts on my phone...#constantbuzzing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonassiegel Is his dad still freaking out he’s not being considered for Captain]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I saw Ultimo Dragon wrestle. This is real life. #DefyDragonSpirit @ Washington Hall https://t.co/M5Ny5b8u6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alyssanicole727 We are celebrating ella’s bday tonight 😅 skip school and come w me soon 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessieLahrr I go there five days a week. I do the half hour fitness classes. The trainer gives me direction and a… https://t.co/lT1zoSO41Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m most offended by the @SenFeinstein video because I can’t imagine being that dismissive to any kid who w… https://t.co/UkGKyHp28b]]></document><document><![CDATA[They need to hang this in every gym, so when you feel like you're gonna die... https://t.co/Z44PiltT4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlyingWithSara @lucymcbath With what airline? Has this been written about much?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph ---. Barometer 29.987 in, Rising. Temperature 53.3 °F. Rain today 0.00 in. Humidity 79%]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @MandrakeRadio She doesn't give a shit about infants, just about pandering!]]></document></documents></author>