<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I play Irreplaceable at the bars on repeat. That's how you know I was there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband told me when on the road traveling for work, meal planning/prep is KEY to loving a healthy and balanced… https://t.co/n7KOgD4A88]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eyerolI How about you stop using pictures of and impersonating a 16 year old without their permission and tweeting… https://t.co/13EtOLFvBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Labradorite and Sterling Silver Pendants at Objets D'Art Store #sterlingsilver,#labradorite,… https://t.co/02Kgz17Mgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist 1984. I had just graduated High School. Just turned 18. And I had just enlisted in the Army. I was on… https://t.co/jFzKJ1vSmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The chocolate 🐊 mommy brought #AddieFrances is just as much fun to play with as it is to eat. Poor little guy no lo… https://t.co/dPzdwYUE8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Kass @chicagotribune I believe all white police are child molesters they talk to everyone in a child molester… https://t.co/PUEuGQyTSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[DEMOCRATS ALWAYS BLAME THEIR UNLAWFUL COMMUNIST ACTS ON SOMEONE ELSE!!! THEY'RE NOTHING BUT COMMUNIST SOCIALIST TRA… https://t.co/AfFcY8VkAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett You should be SO proud of yourself. Lying about racist comments, the noose and MAGA! You have manag… https://t.co/twC8nfWhlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllisterDen Ummm, sounds like Mr Mason needs some more practice! 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvaShadowgirl18 @kev13F @Putneyman Pic of Anhinga will follow in due course; Brian will be away today helping a fr… https://t.co/CKqVrvYPZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealTayChaTLC @ASavageNation Wake up!He needs to go to jail for perpetrating a fraud upon Americans. Besmirching a… https://t.co/wazt5ZnZT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[85|365  His first big Valentine Kiss. 💘  . . . #chaseyfefe #mysweetboy #valentinesday2019 #herseykisses #fromgabby… https://t.co/6UuIZFcLIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I found a list I wrote a couple years ago that had different companies I wanted to work with as a consultant.… https://t.co/ahtibTZgeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear niggas will struggle just to be able to say they struggled growing up. That shit ain’t nothing to be proud… https://t.co/SXUTwMIBrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CruzRojaVe Cuando cambien la DIRECTIVA venezolana tomo en cuenta la Cruz Roja. https://t.co/iVfWX8LkLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Trump lives in mortal fear that people who work might get paid for their work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TEN DAYS UNTIL IM AT A METS GAME I REPEAT TEN DAYS UNTIL IM AT A METS GAME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh wow in 2wks Bambam will turn 5yrs old....WTH? js realized my oldest is growing old on me too fast😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[My IG feed is making me lw sad today bc it’s all maternity shoots, gender reveals, baby showers, baby pics and I can’t handle it 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I think I’ve hit rock bottom I slip even further down. The great news is no one cares. And no one likes… https://t.co/9sB8EcnTy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliantinaFans Siento mi corazón 💔 @macabeso y @barbara_lopez21 invertí más en esta relación que la mía  🙊   TE AM… https://t.co/hh3uHYgbsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[if one more person comments about how Lucy by Seven Lions didn’t go “as hard as they thought it would” i’m gonna FR… https://t.co/1LpTpXF7WA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahdunavant OMG - you are on vacation and it’s #NationalNappingDay !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattdelapena you have inspired these 5th graders to recognize and identify love in their own lives! @angiekwhite75… https://t.co/nUIPnf9b96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisChristie You were pathetic on @foxandfriends . Your Guy is destroying America. #TrumpLovesDictators]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again @jonathanymusic plz dont hate me for showing your video, Your just a very talented artist who deserves to he… https://t.co/YXlRU6JUFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my BF is on Twitter but not very actively and I’m wondering if he’ll ever follow me. I brag about having an awes… https://t.co/PmLy1qR0Hs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods Kylie did the same thing to Blac Chyna and Khloe did the same thing to Tristan’s PREG… https://t.co/TStlfZOURx]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HEAhT19luU . First 2 shows April 6, 8pm and 1030pm. Only 50 meet n greet tickets. Get your tickets now… https://t.co/kcCsgUH1q5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol how do I apply to be in one of @Tyga music videos asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still need to find a frame for it  I’m drunk in Nashville just wanted to vent that out]]></document><document><![CDATA[No screaming...                           ~ #LAPokerClassic @WPT https://t.co/LPyRmnjONB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its give away time again! Everyone who would like a change to win., please like,  share ,tag or retweet. Tag two fr… https://t.co/5fFgW2CVeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow @BernieSanders Who cares how much $$$ you or @potus had growing up, or what you did with it.  Howeve… https://t.co/4wDg5Rlmqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dumper_trump @ENBrown @swin24 appreciate my personal information floating around Twitter for all to see.  Trump do… https://t.co/p9IbGBlN3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimDayTV I keep up with 3-5 different ones that I listen to weekly at least and every time a new episode is available.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer @DonaldJTrumpJr Schitt needs to be exposed as soon as possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstherRight @senatemajldr So you admit that we're going to get crappy, rationed care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uhlexeeyuh2 @untnabj Why not get a good grade on your midterms AND get ready for your future career 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NEFIRST @RAGE173 alumni at SE Mass cheering from the stands and volunteering at the event! https://t.co/zx14pMNRGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Harrison: Do you still love Colton? Hannah G:  #TheBachelor https://t.co/KJVUvOsURl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a pandemic with American deaths on a daily basis  and their children becoming orphans .  Staggering statistics… https://t.co/FnbA0C7G2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dorothy’s boyfriend is going to buy us Seattle hot dogs, bitch I got dreams!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janet_sd @DierksBentley @KeithUrban @mirandalambert It was an awesome show a wonderful concert]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PickleAndNancy Pickles and Nancy have a wonderful #KittyLoafMonday glad to hear pickles loves her tree stand all l… https://t.co/XRIpLQ8g30]]></document><document><![CDATA[just thinking about the word document I had filled with really bad have heart tattoo ideas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@otayelementary We are rolling out Profesional Learning Cycle #3 (math small group instruction) and having a good o… https://t.co/YwTnZPAqpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Kirk!!!! I’ll retweet this one too. Go team!! Sharing the Kool Aid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Car_Porns @Mark_R1_5VY Wow. My back hurts just thinking about getting into that beauty. 😉 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_whitejoe_ @basedcam this is the exact book I gave you. A dogs autobiography. Read it! Joe: Art of Racing in the Rain]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥒 #Zucchini noodles #Recipe These are amazing, delicious, super healthy and so fast to prepare! Ingredients: 3 Zucc… https://t.co/u8xvBDMXOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyallantdf General question. If you're an Empath, is it possible for too much negative emotion or energy to make… https://t.co/t6upxhCp5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Google Play Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below… https://t.co/aRjQGQeuoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fak les jeunes portent des salopettes maintenant? 1991 a appelé, elle veut ravoir sa mode poche.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend just sent me a snap of her bloody tee cause her 8 month old son ripped off her nipple piercing. I. Don’t. Can’t. Omg.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Converted @kelseypermar into a @kanebrown fan by taking her to the concert with me. Who’s next?💁🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I just say......  sometimes being a woman totally sucks. Y’all expect wayyyyy too much out of us. And we are fu… https://t.co/tn67zi2Mk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_better_off_red @ABHcosmetics @tartecosmetics @MorpheBrushes @jamescharles @LashKitty @LuxieBeauty @bhcosmetics @SuvaBeauty Thanks girl LY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImZachHerron I literally can’t wait...I almost had a heart attack in my chemistry class today lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[O sea amiga si me atraen los de cabello largo pero ese no mames jajajajajajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dope is from wa st , the first thing he did when elected gov was abolish the death penalty, I moved to Texas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@georgiasmith87 I lost my dad also, both my parents actually. You are entitled to talk about him. And yes, you are his mi i me!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like couples who go on dates to the gym don’t even know about ice cream shops. 💁🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Hey Dems , ya know what they say about payback. It's a bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[February was ROUGH, one thing after another each week. March better be all about the positive news]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weaselette @mkraju I spent a sleepless night worrying about the boxes 😉 where are they? Are they being held agains… https://t.co/rIvIV0ScPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRFelisilda @marcorubio Yes, that's true.  We really have no business evening being in that organization.  It' a w… https://t.co/p0us7FuyPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Classic Tennis Bracelet GIVEAWAY #giveaway #win https://t.co/SavlONDXEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need teachers! :) Join our CPS community as we ensure that all students graduate on time ready to pursue their c… https://t.co/fdS2YlClL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you still have emojis in your snapchat name preset you need to check yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is @JensenAckles so damn adorable?! I mean it’s pretty annoying, I can’t pay attention to @cw_spn and I’m reall… https://t.co/vWoRu5noHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@disfan59 No need to restore what is nature’s way of dealing with strong tides. We partner with the Ocean. It will… https://t.co/1bxRPMH4yP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CncBhDdubminion @DonnieWahlberg @JennyMcCarthy @shergiggles @anneemull @tammywalker2334 @lovenkotb4life9… https://t.co/9cLEJemx39]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jojoh888 Terrible.  And those Bernie followers want this here??  NEVER!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabitoviajero @MFB1965 @reddit Afloja man esto es tw te hacía con mejor sentido del humor pero bueno .... mala mía (me equivoque )😉👋🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nafleky Yeah 💯 allegedly the tickets are on LiveNa+ion AND +icke+Master ?!?! So like how is that even gonna work.… https://t.co/Het48XgCv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @MrsH_loves2read !  We are so lucky to call you ours! https://t.co/PPYxIGSfRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoover Dam and Las Vegas @ Planet Hollywood Resort &amp; Casino https://t.co/kmUUleTxDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lovejackpearl @WhiteHouse Well do you have room for them in your house dumbass]]></document><document><![CDATA[My look for Women's Day Makeup: @bieber03_01_94 Outfit: @fashionnova Event: frescoscantina Backdrop:… https://t.co/ICTrZs1fhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frankstero @winewankers @JeremyPalmer7 Thanks Frank. Have a great weekend🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iambeau listening to Vday podcast...if you won the lottery, you wouldn’t buy the @RamsNFL ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's to cute. He doesn't like crunching on carrots, or shaking, ice in cups..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti I guess the Ralph Northam yearbook photo taught these young adults nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have dogs they said. It will be fun they said... until the blind one locks himself in the bathroom while you’re at… https://t.co/BNGCxpbIbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[As usual American car manufacturers are way behind the manufactoring of #ElectricCars @60Minutes @Realdonaldtrump a… https://t.co/1aUOtd7j9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[So also Christ did not exalt himself to be made a high priest, but was appointed by him who said to him, “You are m… https://t.co/mzHB65HRkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great show tonight with Illusions &amp; Beyond! @ Dolly Hand Cultural Arts Center https://t.co/UmyQKl5bB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[New music from @jakescottmusic_ @TheArcadianWild and @JenniferNettles 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Apple could not autocorrect my language, that would be great  Gawd dang it, just let me be ducking mad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veronica_b77 @tmihollywood @jsampancake @AMillionABC Are you all caught up yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the beard tickle you while they eating it&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; https://t.co/ZhNm6KNTTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dislike when girls dumb themselves down for a guy. Like girl, you have so much potential in you. Don’t let some bumb tell you otherwise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MegLaTorre @kaitylynne13 @LyraParish I really enjoyed it! https://t.co/S2mAK4vIYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gruman Skytyping fleet getting prep for digital Skywriting aka skytyping in Chino, CA.  Beautiful blue sky day! @ C… https://t.co/KUctRlgxoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your girl is upset I’m trying to get these warped tickets for Ohio and jersey and Ticketmaster is fucking up and I’… https://t.co/Vu4vZast8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: Geoff and I aren’t friends anymore. If you see him let him know I’m pissed he didn’t answer my FaceTime today. Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see this as a lot as a technician.   “Why so much?” Is a very frequent question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyKadiK @wildwillow65 @SecretarySonny @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Hope it's not a forest fire in cally...next time… https://t.co/IjokaH8HeA]]></document></documents></author>