<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LaureenPinkXXX @Big7com @CMS_Stars @CourtneyCummz @creamyways @Culonasexxxy @CumshotClips @CumshotsDaiIy… https://t.co/e96fhnsmsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jasminedlt_ Or if I’m at work... I’m like don’t you have a section you have to be at ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Allergy Partners of Charleston in Summerville, SC https://t.co/goqrf1Gbzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBC News - University teaching grades invalid, statistics body says https://t.co/nqUZ8EOp1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been a Twin Peaks fan all my life. I didn’t know how incredible of an art form it was until about a year… https://t.co/NuD4XZe8z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miss__Yolanda  My beautiful black sisters Only the black girls in America would take up after you all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scijimenez @GiftedMrsGuzman I don’t know what I would do without you Two! It’s an honor and pleasure to work along… https://t.co/9xXKz8chqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PierreVLeBrun Hate to say it but I have been yelling at him for weeks through the tv... not an NHL caliber player right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SooooSleepy but i have go in a little earlier than usual, got some @GenesisUSA training to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan is a disappointment and should not be in Congress, let alone be on the Oversite Committee. He is just t… https://t.co/Shr3uYQePD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaChavarria Good morning, Lisa! Have yourself a blessed weekend! Thanks for always being awesome!⭐️👍😎 https://t.co/tvIDxeiDWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MilitarMaduristaNoEsGente ya se les dio oportunidad, se les ofreció amnistía y garantías. Llego la hora de la verd… https://t.co/A5qQdKPwjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizgarbus As an ex-bartender, myself, I'd always stick up for her. Bartenders' Code.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MUTGuru Here, hoping you guys fix the challenge 3 for games 1-3 in the UL solos on Xbox One ☝🏼 @EASPORTS_MUT… https://t.co/JLXgNPPJeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most entitled and, literally, stupid people I have ever seen elected....]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Treyger suggested that the program’s bumpy rollout and the stigma attached to schools targeted for improvement hav… https://t.co/WDpT8KfUJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MikeCairns5 opened an important psychological floodgate last night.  His question to Chris Archer about the #Rays… https://t.co/Xt3Lm3ANnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davdavies I saw him at Lifetime last year. Amazing! I acted like a 5 year old]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Julius by @TreeHouseBrewCo @ Orangewood East Club House — https://t.co/GWwCg9tMJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tidy up your writing with Ben, tidy up your room with Marie Kondo and Jordan Peterson, and don’t forget to wash you… https://t.co/LtiPfZpCBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StirringSoup1 @Pontifex I think that I’m the kind of person who doesn’t call the head of your religion (the larges… https://t.co/7e29DQma71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAPDChiefMoore @Dodgers @LAPDHQ PSA:1609BELOIT AV LA CA #9 GEORGE RUSADZE-KIDNAPPED KIDS. FREQUENT ELEMENTARY SCHO… https://t.co/0or4c0HCWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psutitan @no1lion Is it? The “last tweet” from 2,000+ days ago threw me]]></document><document><![CDATA[It pains me to say it but #Blackadder Season 1 is not very funny. (The other 3 are genius ) https://t.co/2Fjx0BQFtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday at The Rock!! @ The Rock Faith Center https://t.co/5l6AiSss9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneGun45 @FogballRuben @Indians @MLB @Cheatcode07 WAIT!!   Is this MATT DANIELS ANNOUNCING A COME BACK!?!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@tesla @elonmusk feature request:  good sleeping position seatbelts and airbags for all your vehicles. Especially… https://t.co/Kik4amiIQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zer0Dotexee I already blocked him. I searched his psn name on facebook first 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MurrietaI Jajajaja eso mismo hago yo  me preguntan que tiene que ver la musica con el estacionarme ,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogerdmayo @NASCAR They just showed it...but I guess they used CGI to fake it 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger Grahm Ledger is about as truthful as you nadda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Applications Systems Engineer 5 - Cyber Security Innovation Team" at Wells Fargo by… https://t.co/ogzA2GdlhE]]></document><document><![CDATA[A social media platform for people to just post pictures of their dogs I am willing to pay monthly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GordonRamsay Im watching this right now #rerun #lol https://t.co/MuCrUR25O9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidSraw1892 @ZeeInTheMoment @Happy19111 @Luckydawg @philip_prebble @MistyMa45875193 @Lucille77316971 @BertJ4411… https://t.co/fOyErFyEuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwampPump @SenKamalaHarris And just how is the climate changing Kamala?  It was hot, now it's cold.  Ever 50,000 y… https://t.co/b0UqOs7v1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halemc Striplin didnt come close to shaking like McQuiddy. They had white lights too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BennyTheKidd @DonaldJTrumpJr WOW, I'm not rich, but sounds like you're jealous, get a job]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read and learn about the solution to #GlobalWarming.  Bill Gates's solution, the #GreenNuclearDeal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God my abstract made it through the sleet and hail. @traumadoctors https://t.co/jI2wzjCl67]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fashion Prepares for Brexit: Featuring @daveemersonSEKO  https://t.co/1plcLQsYSG via @BoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMageeSports Ok...you can have Jose Bautista this year and I’ll take Bryce Harper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC How could this be? Trump is a man of the people! He wants to put America first and make it great again. Thes… https://t.co/pGa4CsplwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrong set of values and understanding what is right and wrong. #sad #fail]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods She says the word "like" a lot. more than my 10 year old daughter does. Scary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[el PRIAN no regresará a los pinos por lo que me  resta de vida, no es amenaza es presentimiento]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorCharles Nice author's site, better than my BlogSpot site.  Robert Morton, spy thriller author https://t.co/mnEB9rwfGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirkmin I just listened to your interview with Thomas Stackpole...I am SO FUCKING PUMPED  that you are BACK. Not o… https://t.co/cX1Bc0AyzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSandmanEsq @Buekish @The_Tology @poetgambler @capefearcadaver @theami5000 @TheKenChilds I was just trying to en… https://t.co/f6GXHdpEvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamCJMurphy @EAPepper @ScottWalker Maybe not in Wisconsin, but there is real problem. I had a video of a trump in… https://t.co/4wuaIccwoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanngibbons @tuckerwood12 If Tennessee can find a way to beat Kentucky, I think they get their mojo back and make… https://t.co/Y2qpoyxN4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX Oh the eye-rony of this tweet. *waits for triggered fake high mindedness.*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vmsalama So he will instead join the Trump 2020 Fox Propaganda Campaign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamCarlsGhost @THR @KamalaHarris I'm sorry for your loss. Your mother helped shape the minds of many.  Her studen… https://t.co/qirjQt1Bm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you think you know someone like you know yourself, and your tricked into believing that same person is still t… https://t.co/aE5xvFEUy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PlayersOnly sucks!!! I can’t take this anymore!! They never stop talking. There is an art to this and they don’t h… https://t.co/oNGzCOybM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie’s track record on gun rights is EXACTLY why I refused to support him in 2016 and why I refuse to support him… https://t.co/HeAgEy0aGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulsperry_ @vbislands Great ! Truth will come out..!&gt; and boomerang back to POTUS Trump who believes his buddy PUTIN over our DNS 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear none has ever said Kobe didn't call out or challenge his teammates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_H_Teacher @KindnessLDNONT Thank you @Mr_H_Teacher! I’m grateful and always learning from you since I started in… https://t.co/K5HdaK7nq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@farmingsim There is this company named John Deere, maybe looking into that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dual meets need to mean something. They’ve lost their relevance the last couple of years thanks to EPC scheduling.… https://t.co/r5SnzedkDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rose215 @acoyne @AndrewScheer I’ve got nothing against the other two. I contributed to ndp and green campaigns last election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatholicCoaster @JdLauscher @romancircuspod It usually takes a dark turn around 38. Keep us posted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Let’s keep criminals in prison to make the streets safer. That’s common sense gun control.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mundodeportivo Este árbitro hdp. Siempre favorece a estos putos madridistas]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to Camden at Camden Catholic basketball in clash of Top 6 teams with Olympic National title and momentum… https://t.co/ETbbL6VSxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OriginalSTP @MartinsvilleSwy @MartinsvilleSwy @TM10Era @stimz13 #BestWeekendOfTheYear #276 #MartinsvilleHotDog #JessieJones]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's a good start now can they finish? Who's your daddy(s) CBJ? 87 n 59 that's who #LetsGoPens #nhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darla_Crane No argument, but he is also attacked by weirdos which many of us understand.  If he gets one or two wr… https://t.co/VEsC2qWw9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[House committee prepares to request Trump's tax returns from the IRS  https://t.co/JVFPhMFgrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBThursday to 2012: @PCACanada and former @OntarioPCParty MPP  @RodneyJackson first exposed the impact of closed t… https://t.co/WsexOuzDxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have been enjoying mild mornings across the Capital City, but we will wake up to temperatures in the 40's to sta… https://t.co/BiRPWgZWmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just now getting out of my last class for the day and it’s relatively warm, the birds are chirping, and sun is… https://t.co/7kyKcwpxGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaser 6/10 for @vocon. More at https://t.co/8vnJ1HXsx3 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/Mqr7HpCspc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@10Cagle @KamronSullivan My biggest problem with this bracket is how Zaxbys isn’t even on the list like... WUT?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Swinbun @cmccollo I had a really, really, really excellent meal there about three years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrej_muzevic @US_FDA @origin_trail @ethereum But blockchains as publicly verifiable timestamps is the oldest use… https://t.co/XYJehQEcfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Struggling with the paralyzing fear of scarcity, I logged onto my iPad, transferred funds from my money market acco… https://t.co/aOU7n5P0qD]]></document><document><![CDATA[i loved scandal so much i think ima watch all over on this overnight shift.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A todo vuelo arreando a las legendarias Vacas diablo!!  Saludos Master @FerNunezV  Aquí te va una canción para ti…… https://t.co/Rk41ar9wlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EQUIPTO What!? You tweet 1 tweet then fall asleep!  You frickin' tease]]></document><document><![CDATA[hands down sa mga prof na ginahimong easy ang lesson para sa mga students 🙌🏼👏🏼 you da real mvps. dili pareha sa uba… https://t.co/p1GegWAx6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr This is why we need a litmus for POTUS. You are five minutes from being indicted of several felony… https://t.co/9SG2NN477d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn, Tristan Thompson cheated on Khloe Kardashian with Jordyn Woods and Lady Gaga and her fiancé split in the same… https://t.co/eyApoXKpX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My one and only Valentine 💋❤️💕 karine_greene @ Apple Hill https://t.co/0RC53GjB4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesJonathon3 @CNN @CillizzaCNN and for what it’s worth, here’s a much more intelligent and thought out, and deta… https://t.co/98PMhUATSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can take a few more artists for Jeff Hein workshop in Tampa, FL March 18-22.  This painting is a finalist in the… https://t.co/SN9485JTTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @Renee_Stimpert @TheyCallMeJodes and all the members of @AshlandWBB on another GLIAC Championship! 🏆🏆🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m prolly gone be up all night blasting music. I really missed my speakers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Después de un día de mucho jale, unas respetables serpientes bien frías...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penelop06848466 @Thattinyassgirl @bri_sacks What they owe and even if they are in the child's life they just aren'… https://t.co/tDCr6KhAyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is not defined by us. It has nothing to do with our desires or social constructs. It’s a magic unlike any othe… https://t.co/UcyV456Jz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Greensboro, North Carolina https://t.co/Lcjf7yY9po]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaseConnor7 @AllenTStClair Gabe, your heart is big and I'm overjoyed that it's full.  I can hear the tone in your… https://t.co/HzVGfZkoiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @RobinhoodApp and we'll both get a stock like $AAPL, $F, or $S for free. Make sure to use my link.  https://t.co/BqHl5Irons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld Disgusting to even hear such a statement. Teachers have got to be the most underpaid profession, requir… https://t.co/o2rvpgYi3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter Is Tinkering With How Users Share Photos and Videos https://t.co/0yvF5orNHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking into work earlier and I saw a dog had just peed on the side of the building, and I wasn’t even mad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SokeAnshu Didn't get any . Too many doctors appointments and then an unscheduled trip . I'll look at these beautif… https://t.co/OTXFR37L5i]]></document></documents></author>