<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Been up since 2:50.... start boarding in 45 minutes..... then a 6 hour layover in Chicago...... 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenSoutar1 @kerry_a23 That's what I thought, too. So then technically we are both right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was  going to mack this   haven   macking a   changel for them but not  😣 I'm harting now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendSprings teachers are together at The Summit on PLC to better help our students be successful!  @DVUSD… https://t.co/TS9SiKsaVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@etnow Out now! @HomeFreeGuys bring us a moody video for a cover of a wistful country classic ...… https://t.co/jGXlMk8STC]]></document><document><![CDATA[H💓PPY VALENTINE’S DAY! ————————————— Just so you know... we love you!💓 All heart centered offerings today. 💓Last cl… https://t.co/Ujb7iJujZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my cat is goin into labor any minute now and my bf doesn’t know how to act 😂 https://t.co/gYk9e2k0GG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mehdirhasan Yea let’s talk about the apprentice set. This is dumb as shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@sxsw⁩ #BrighterAI #Anonymization of facial recognition ⁦@CentrepolisXLR8⁩ https://t.co/J0hBjIwJ2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #SocialWorkMonth2019 to all my amazing @SyracuseSchools social workers! I'd be lost without you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And year 3 is officially #finished #fresh15 @KathyRuth9 #JKR my work family is #thebest #tylerisd https://t.co/WNMUlzJklR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmweissman @AOC Laid off and more and more automation appeared everywhere. There is now self checkout at my dr… https://t.co/8j4IhXHbzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going through my old photos in my phone/Facebook and I realized how much of a band whore I used to be 😂 I’ve met qu… https://t.co/TBb1Ly3IUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[MERRY CREWSMAS! 🖤💛 @CrewUnion @ColumbusCrewSC #Crew96⁠ ⁠ https://t.co/hrP0uixw02]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Mardi Gas everyone!  #mardigras #owenmcmartin  #cutebabies  #kingcake   #jacksonsquare @ FrenchQuarter NewOrl… https://t.co/I3pOPFLNmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThinkResist @itssuzann @BEEBESD @modified_waffle @DirkSchwenk @LouiseMensch @AngrierWHStaff anyone's imagination..… https://t.co/unbQr04nbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also: note the absence of trans folks from this initiative.  Shocked. Shocked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dteeflame If you ever need a friend to talk to, someone to have your back or]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mötet mellan Kim Jong-un och Donald Trump avslutades i förtid. Över en timme före schema.  Oklart varför.  Trumps p… https://t.co/3lFavjuDwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FTFonFS1 @criscarter80 "Gotta an issue get some tissue" @criscarter80 https://t.co/B9U2g0RBOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throat started hurting in the middle of the movie. Now running a fever. I DON’T HAVE TIME FOR THIS AND I CAN’T AFFO… https://t.co/BWlgktCeED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadLindberg Fresh Mozz, pistachios, red onion, and balsamic reduction... no sauce  Smoked mozz, prosciutto, honey… https://t.co/vGCduz5zWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully I can sleep tonight but I can actually FEEL my lungs expand and contract inside my chest right now, and a… https://t.co/dTtbylToSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best supporting female #IndieSpirit goes to If Beake Street Coyld Talk’s Regina King who is also up for the Oscar t… https://t.co/tbIqJvVEtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[How the fuck am I supposed to sleep when Four Brothers is on tv 😭 #favoritemovieever]]></document><document><![CDATA[My immune system watching me trying to absorb nutrients and feel better https://t.co/rPkffTQUjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what happened when I first flirted with my bf, and now we've been together over a year. Just do it yall… https://t.co/57E8hDhb6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[So hyped to see @ShawnMendes again #shawnmendesthetour https://t.co/7J3l85W4Sg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonesAngell @GoHeels Player if the game has to be @KWill_24 great defense and sweep]]></document><document><![CDATA[People in Almaden are about to lose all of their transit service, seniors and students who take the 65 will have to… https://t.co/EgkY4UQml7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah Sanders: "We're not going to comment on security clearances." Is Sanders still collecting a salary as Press Secretary?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradley cooper to lady Gaga during the Shallow Oscar performance https://t.co/3gowtLRDeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop thinking about that time pete wentz was on californication and now I can’t sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[She said there’s a chance i can get either or !!!!! Aggghhhh, I’m so excited!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McWoolley3 @RebekahODell1 Love this. It provides some excellent ideas for building on the powerful magic of studen… https://t.co/GovXcMVtmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vorrathpaddy @susanasilvi58 @EllaCantaloupeH @cevalloslaura @BlancaNayelyNT3 @diprietonayeli @Katsuragui… https://t.co/w9LIlivUla]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kraft going through a Mid Life Crisis 😂 he took that rapper life to the head]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally had that exact one on the left Hahahaha https://t.co/3E0V4KxoyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAcesUpdate @cristalramirezn @Alisa_M_Ramirez @theacesofficial @mckennapetty @kt_hendy What did the signs say?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So who does tucker and hannity work for?  Oh, did u say the Fake news media, all news outlets r fake news u said.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcharlesworth7 @ShirleenAllicot @heatherorourke7  Good Morning today is Carnival Tuesday in Trinidad my birth place lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CIAnderson3 Trump Wanted to be one of the Monkees but they said heck no!!! https://t.co/UZmQhaxcoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonicaBisha @benshapiro @PPFA Same!!!! Never had an unwanted pregnancy, never would have considered an abortion...… https://t.co/Se4gZ6RiGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holylocksleys How about some infectious laughter from Rise &amp; Jazzi? https://t.co/dL3GODMUKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a very special team and a fantastic season  lets get one more win tomorrow guys @DU_MensBBALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can honestly get through the day listening to @OfficialSoMo , bless you🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kebuenatuxtla Voto X #QueNoTeFalleElCorazón  de @AlexisMusicMX  en #ElElevador  @lacademiaazteca  @sonymusicmexico  @MapachitosDeAC 🥰😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @marc_lotter Whatever  Rep. Omar has said does not even come close to the horror of @realDonaldTrump .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crespoj85 @joeysaittaa @realDonaldTrump You can join the "human wall" that Trump once proposed in a tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madShana @enelra5 @Fridaygirl1969 @Cricket6 @mia_nj @hannadjh @nm9139 @pm3900 @ThePhightins33 @davisis1… https://t.co/kKtNAQWVyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimKelly1212 Happy birthday Jim and to Hunter!  We think of  you both always and hold you in prayer as we keep up the NBS work. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss all of my babies at Sheltering Arms 😢 but I had a better opportunity. I feel bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day!  Love,  Oliver  #stealinhearts #makinfarts #oliverthewonderpup https://t.co/uQSu6q1fOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zeusFanHouse @PatrioticCindy @TWPundit Murdered and she asked for help and why did not get]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got some major beef with the groundhog that said spring would come early]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/17/19 bike 35 minutes 200 cals 7.30 miles #motivateyourself #morninggrind @ Mac At Harbor East LLC https://t.co/ZWDdSsGD4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMAZING JOB @2604vmDavid  @JanelleCob !! It looks fantastic!! #TeamWorkMakesTheDreamWork 🤗 #T2604🎯🎯🎯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @Cbp8Cindy @Julianna_glass @ccatmpt @CaththeWineLady @thatsVeryKari @AkronWineGuru @SashaEats… https://t.co/59KOitn0Na]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve started to police myself when I try to tweet when I’m drunk and now my drafts are just full of subtweets to the boy i like]]></document><document><![CDATA[The train never came 😂 @ Rebecca Winters Historical Marker https://t.co/0vwGBCJCSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC We must cut the illegal entry,NOT ENCOURAGE IT! RULE OF LAW. No laws=ANARCHY. Help fix the problems in their c… https://t.co/oiWkyJOD0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wasn’t allowed growing up to describe my hair as nappy so when I hear it now it bothers me]]></document><document><![CDATA[John 8:36    So if the Son sets you free, you will be free indeed. #Bible https://t.co/UJrIAg4rjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thereemdaly  “hang on, help is on its way” ... in the words of the poetic @littleriverband !!!… https://t.co/VaLjVQdU8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MindyHussain @Rachel__Lander @nitinramrap @dawnvegas @VMinuz @CarlyCompass @KarenCherwinsky @leslieann_100… https://t.co/8sF3nWdUwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how it feels to be in love but not a fan of what it takes to get there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OversightDems Why not more border judges to handle backlog of asylum seekers jumping fences vs waiting in tiny, da… https://t.co/sqVtmnUriv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my myself wasn’t going to eat as much anymore but I couldn’t refuse tacos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeJohnsonIce This is hank. He chews the tags off of every blanket in the house, but he also dances when you come… https://t.co/GA0knuW2kE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anytime @omeezy_ mama comments on my pictures I feel like Regina George during their performance in Mean Girls. I j… https://t.co/Pzh9B0odSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you see when you look in the mirror? #lionqueen #kimba #newmusic #WomensHistoryMonth https://t.co/0nM19MBRy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahDemp That, coupled Amy's vaguetweet from earlier, makes me convinced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna say that Jaquelyn Bouchie is the best person I’ve ever met, and whatever guy ends up with her is the luckiest guy out there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheryll1950 I found a couple of sources that 12,000 in current caravan are due soon. It’s only February. At this p… https://t.co/afjiL2y7cb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitches really be mad bc a nigga don’t want them anymore 🤦🏽‍♀️. Stupid ass hoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fiona Goode deserves an entire season just about her. God I love Jessica Lange]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey sun, just wanted to say that it’s 6:30 &amp; i miss ya already. feel free to start staying longer ((;]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of my HOTTEST Videos if you guys want to feel feel festive &amp; Horny ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the City of #Pittsburgh and ⁦@mayorpeduto⁩ for standing up for women’s right by adopting… https://t.co/QO2HKgN5Lb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how I have tennis elbow and swimmers shoulder yet I don’t do/play either of those things. #AutoimmuneDisorderLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanmdav @DonaldJTrumpJr Dignity &amp; honor do not describe McCabe's actions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MFournierWatson Phew. I thought I was going to have to spend the rest of the day in bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder @jmksd @realDonaldTrump Nope unless they are blindly following him and then yep]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beautiful glasses of @markverling 🖤 @ Tørst https://t.co/99GaNcO6co]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindsheartstayx @SoShameonMeow @taylorswift13 @taylornation13 @MegEHarris @swiftie4life13 @sweetx0love25… https://t.co/GGeY8HzFVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyOphoto @AngrierWHStaff @janet493 Impeachment is totally a political move.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerseymikes always comes through for us! Thank you to everyone who has worked so hard with inventory this year! 🥪… https://t.co/lNtEOwVIU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sunsetmeditation at the beach #islandlife #meditationspace #namaste🙏 #vacation #annamariaisland #meditationtime… https://t.co/GkmeuDo11L]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT SCHOOL BOARD MEETING TO ATTEND ON MARCH 5th at 11:15AM at 600 SE 3rd Ave, Ft Laud  School Board members w… https://t.co/QvjowwV51G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kb_augiewbb @shelbyselland15 @lynseyprosser @v_rabb21 @hanametoxen You have more nicknames than James P. 😂😂 @SusanLamb65]]></document><document><![CDATA[This woman will become Manatee-Sarasota’s first female chief judge in @12CircuitFL this summer https://t.co/iVXHjufNh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macabeso @AmarAMuerteOf @EnlasByEnlasM Ya lista, elloa serán mi compañía!! Te amow ey!!! https://t.co/pJ10sBs9dX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YesMomsCan @ChelseaClinton There is no apples to apples comparison between Chelsea and Ivanka, because Ivanka is s… https://t.co/L9dKjTvPvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeoliberalFed @simonlevans @guardian Hell, I figured you didn’t give a crap about anyone, I was right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost said “why don’t you explain this to me like I’m 5” to my TA in lab but don’t know if he’d get the joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙 #california #sandiego #kissingstatue #ussmidway #downtownsandiego #longweekend #sunday #seaportvillage en Kissing… https://t.co/WS80FahCLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeRichardLong They don't even believe in it! Gotta believe in order to change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 #springbreak2019 - a chill day with great grandma ❤️. . . . #tennessee #grandma #chill #travel #travelvlog @… https://t.co/QzydW0WwTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are trying to spin a really bad story around.  #ResignLisaMacLeod #NotForThePeople #ONpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have the ability to make your life however you want it, so why waste time in doing things that don't make you happy?]]></document></documents></author>