<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SpicyBotrytis Hmm. As a coauthor of one, and not a plant person (neither is Dan Hartl) I need to think about this.… https://t.co/cAEntXday4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good  point. Once the yuppies take over I'll have to move more East again since rent is already going up  where I a… https://t.co/wtP6couNct]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the most talented St. John's team since 2010-2011. For them to not even finish in the top half of the Big E… https://t.co/D6Ta39Dfmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was from comparing a solid background color on iPhone X to Pixel 3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump live in 2 minutes from the Rose Garden! Everyone tune in! #QAnon #TheGreatAwakening #WWG1WGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This picture just asked me for set times and a plus one for the all locals show]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshtweeterson Damnit Tweeterson! I guess I’ll give this show a go tomorrow. Stupid live tweeting suspense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillClinton @jguaido Is this going to require a "fast track" ruling to get it by the citizens?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VegB23 @marTW33T @dairyuk Thank you Martin. When I was last in Switzerland and Italy, veal was a really big thing… https://t.co/quXjKuG5KS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DWrightislove5 No. I get anxiety when the other 4 pitch... I can’t even watch Vargas pitch without needing to get bombed 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolinaHuddle @KarlSakas Only we only get a day of actual Spring, please revise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincipalSJV @Asael_Ruvalcaba @PhilEchols @ctopher73 @tyarnold18 @NickHoltvluwer @elemz5 @EricEwald_Iowa… https://t.co/o8zCkEnzlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting article!  I’m a Neuroscientist. Here’s How Teachers Change Kids’ Brains. https://t.co/Ihq4R1iCJl #edtech via @EdSurge]]></document><document><![CDATA[No le dejaban ollas o vasijas para hacer la comida... agarraba las charolas de comedor, y ahí hacía la comida. https://t.co/7BHVayNjFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The good news is when the courts stop Trump’s “emergency declaration,” that we now how a precedent to prevent a Dem… https://t.co/iyC5xHr0Z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/mSHGJJQdv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re gonna say this is the wrong franchise to let distractions get in your way, you should not be doing this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesHicksUK Me Looking 10 years younger mean I will still look Old just not as bad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Have to go after them with the same. Investigate until they stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiyokotown @ban_sidhe Worst job?  Not customer service related.  I was an accountant.  Alcoholic and abusive boss.… https://t.co/rynZRfBGQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @jimcramer why doesn't the market like $GOOGL's 20+% revenue growth and fortress balance sheet??  lots of criti… https://t.co/JCZpkX6cHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@livestrong Damn I live in Arizona I wished that I lived back in my home town chicago Illinois]]></document><document><![CDATA[New double is a joke. Green circle @ Camelback Mountain, Poconos, Pa https://t.co/god4eLP0vK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoanneMacIntyre @thelukealbright Aren't we? I only unfriend annoying people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trk2der @mommagonzo Very eloquent and very well said! Simple Common Sense! #secondamendmentrights]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nausea... Noise hurts... Lights hurt... motrin &amp; Tylenol don't work. Gotta go to dr's for dilaudid and phenergan]]></document><document><![CDATA[When traveling excites most, buying new living room - bedroom &amp; Patio sets excites me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelzegler I’m so excited that you got your dream come true role of a life time. I love your singing and I know… https://t.co/rXawnzr3l2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ashley Young is a liability every game but Kevin Friend giving two yellow cards already is a joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MPSpellman @CBSEveningNews @SteveHartmanCBS He is a national treasure with a skill unduplicated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher Cher like so many other independents, I use to be a huge fan. However, you are losing I this part of your fan… https://t.co/yr8Ky49SgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAGA idiots will actually believe this bullshit. He may as well take that pistol to fifth ave at this rate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDailyDopeShw @AlexisBortell Are we talking about Hemp or Cannabis now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadlerVaden My immediate reaction to this news was thinking up Shred Flintstone. That’s on the house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Papi you’re not sick, you HUNG over!!!   Boyfriend: https://t.co/0y99lNmzJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people hurt you over and over, think of them like sand paper. They may scratch and hurt you a bit, but in the… https://t.co/phUxnrO0Lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Titans_Notes @diamondhockey They will be fortunate to get out of the first round this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[La HIKES. . . . . . . . tedidadoodle  #lahikes #minigoldendoodle #dogsoflosangeles #tunacanyon #daysoff @ Malibu, C… https://t.co/FuthsXlHid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nate_Paz Santacon is #5 on my list. I love your dedication to Thirsty Thursday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrizzlyCanadian Poor Ron!! But absolutely right. Bad as ppl think Ron or even Gards is, studs, absolute studs compared to Marincin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubblewars YOU'RE HOLDING THEM BACK!  Just kidding, that makes a bit more sense. 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin @EllenPage @DanRather Maybe a wall on the northern border isn’t a bad idea 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnehoover Moral victories do not exist. that’s what’s wrong with this participation trophy culture. You don’t ge… https://t.co/YJjsAi5Kp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @BoysWoden defeated the @TENAHABALL,  58-55, to move into a second-place tie in District 22-2A 10-4. The  teams… https://t.co/vSYDF9Hhb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we need to do isn't complicated... Stop the human traffickers. Stop the drug traffickers. And #BuildTheWall!… https://t.co/fkY88Z3mRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanJones68 And now that I watched video...why do you Van assume Jussie’s been in pain? Greed and jealousy as motiv… https://t.co/DdOe5x4NR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rob5Chief Oby ta holota zyla jak najdluzej i przygladala sie jak my Polacy budujemy Polske na miare marzen Lupaszk… https://t.co/NUVn7eSe4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeirdMovieBros That just happens to be my Limousine out front.  Right out Front?  Yeah!! https://t.co/aWShdkvA3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Verse of the Day: All God wants for us is joy and prosperity but only if we are putting our focus on Him! Whatever… https://t.co/dy7kXBCsvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmeMescudi @JorgeMescudi He’s gonna bust this bad boy out https://t.co/uFFLOOf7vE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s gumbo weather. And I’m here for it. Having fun while helping to raise $$$ for @CMNHospitals Cenla! https://t.co/30avfBJvnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tgif 🍋💜🍆💚🍏 #Fbf 👏💫 #FridayFeeling🤳 #FridayFun🤩💍 https://t.co/yOyIkk5zfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StouttVan Replace us with UC in latest Lunardi and smooth sailing to matchup vs Gonzaga in Great 8!!! 😋https://t.co/shPi28UD7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[A marathon Uber day included an early trip to Rumson, NJ. So as soon as I saw that town pop up on my phone, I said,… https://t.co/1muORMUmrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing gets Instagram gays more angry than commenting "girl you're pushing 40" on one of their posts]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is disgusting!! #BIGfacts #FOH @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/flsz3JAMnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MegaConOrlando any chance of @undertaker or other @WWE stars this year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @UGAFBEquipment had any extra big hoss sized stuff that might make its way to a dawg in tennessee, that’d be cool 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[النصيحه الأولى والأخيرة : صلِّ جيداً ، واسجد طويلاً وتنفس بعمق ، وأقرأ القرآن بتدبر ، واذكر الله كثيراً ، وتذكر أن… https://t.co/n8oYXURd9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonwp41 @greenlightgg @realDonaldTrump Every one I've seen so far has that information.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏈🏆 #pressplay: Good times speaking with the crew of @nflnetwork! Recently, I spoke with “The Playmaker”… https://t.co/10rwlzh2CR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise When you can show that is more about correcting a wrong than using your pulpit to condemn All Muslims… https://t.co/0Vmazkku2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Cut the manlier-than-thou bullshit.” Well done, Admiral Badass (@thejaynebrook). Such a great bulkhead-rattling sc… https://t.co/3LeeOezggG]]></document><document><![CDATA[jesseatswell made the harissa-inspired bean dip. I just brought the wine 🍷  . . . . . . . . #foodie #delicious… https://t.co/Cx1erHPPTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMVivancoHRW @robertoampuero Y como la harías?  Porque Maduro no sale a las buenas, y si votan con su control de todo gana al seguro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMaddenX Both of you guys need hobbies. Or to get off social media. Stop acting like high school kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Donachie Lol. I keep telling my daughter she could write a book about the stuff she says to my grandkids. Rec… https://t.co/Z1fO3F1ysg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maravillosa música de mis queridos mariachivocesdemexico @casasanchez @ Frazer Park https://t.co/OK5KuHt0LJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enough already, @ProFootballHOF   Time to put Ken Anderson IN!  Long overdue!  And don't get me started on Ken Rile… https://t.co/KeDqMMWGwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THECJNeuman @VMTNcommunity @VMware I’ll be happy to help and provide some suggestions as soon as possible. I’ll do… https://t.co/qNN2pIkYmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[21 influential black professionals in tech https://t.co/KASpd8EA5s via @usatoday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inhsedems Please stop HB 1138 from becoming law. This is just another "Stick" to destroy the lives of Indiana Home… https://t.co/R9J4P4hdaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexCheremeteff @OTBaseballPhoto @PhilHecken @thorn_john Rough looking bunch..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJStephensVP @vicking02 @Shelley_Emslie @RosaIsiah @meanwheel @julnilsmith @iste Appreciate you, Dr. J! Always a… https://t.co/fP49oYmbKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Many U.S. Cities, There's a Big Mismatch Between #Jobs and Workers https://t.co/ZZNoYFrFeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amys_Kapers Sport something durable for trip to Minnesota. https://t.co/fotqmTsenR  Duluthpack is amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had the honor of meeting up with @motoridersd tonight while he was on a three hour layover. He’s even more lovel… https://t.co/30u1LjafJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeBatardShow pulling a city wok owner right there... “the shitty” hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[In HS the first song i heard from @Nekromantix was "Alice in Psycholand" and i got hooked on them. HS really was a… https://t.co/DaieisIPMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mberlea_ YES! Go watch!! It’s about superhero’s! I’ve been binge watching since last night 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA It would be juvenile to allow one persons comment separate you from your ally. Ilham can say and think what… https://t.co/aalQhin9j8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This may be old news, but there is a city in AR called Weiner. Guess who inforces the law in that town? The Weiner Police!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kpf09 @BPlanutis33 very good call on him. definitely excited with what I’ve heard and seen with that kid even though he doesn’t like pizza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsDeFriese @AdobeSpark Uh yeah lol. We need to exchange #s! https://t.co/XDaGIQmiQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#milwaukeetoolsaus #milwaukeetools #milwaukeepump #milwaukeetoolcontest @ South Los Angeles, California https://t.co/JBn36Mg6bW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattEvansKMBC @kmbc Yeah I was coming down 435 from Claycomo and I hit ice on the overpass and almost lost it so close take it slow]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what you call Presidential @HillaryClinton #StrongerTogether when we work #ForThePeople]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liberty Union Schools will be CLOSED today, Wednesday, February 20th, 2019. Announcements will be made in the early… https://t.co/DsWLi6bPKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re in the LA or LB area hmu for shoots 📸 // @erin_datuin https://t.co/AZbjntElzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Why would donnie jr break away from a meeting with Russians to post this crap?]]></document><document><![CDATA[the sound of eminem’s “till i collapse” plays on a tinny speaker in the undergrad dorm bathroom, as an inebriated r… https://t.co/6jpwgaZjvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for Resident Evil 2 remake to download while doing laundry with this mug. https://t.co/lkNXS0oHjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[SÓLO GANAMOS CON PAPÁ, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/fjXjPWB2LC]]></document><document><![CDATA[so much laughter so little time. Oh I love this kid :) #funniness #chuckle #smile #farcical https://t.co/wrQpf6vVF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been almost 4 years and I still die on how @youfunnyb did a front flip after gettin smacked by some Downy 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only there was an excellent attorney Jussie Smollett could call in this situation. https://t.co/RVj7QDBhNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for GI Update right now on @NYUDocs @SIRIUSXM ... GI questions? Let me know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite all the odds running against her, Sammi has managed to accomplish a feat that I am especially proud of. She… https://t.co/GteUw21Ejy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeLoAndDibs @JoeFortenbaugh  Pregnancy simulator on Impractical Jokers 🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/yYM6nJ0hhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aubawn @GeneLoblaw I see Samir playing the 2 more also. Only way he would transfer is if he is going to graduate t… https://t.co/4s68yRuHpN]]></document></documents></author>