<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The first day it hasn’t rained in what feels like a month... this is a big mood https://t.co/52v5U17JdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walk - @KODAKUMINET And most songs Taemin has ever put out during is solo albums.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow He just lost any vote from me that he could have hoped for. Shame on him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harleygurlHOGan @MauriceBenard @NancyLeeGrahn I’m so excited to meet Maurice I know im gonna cry 😢 I cried when I… https://t.co/NFBq3lI50d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janettemsu @erinkrakow @LoriLoughlin @hallmarkchannel @SCHeartHome She is looking much much better !!! He skin was glowing !!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young Republican's City of Tampa Election Recommendations - TBYR https://t.co/O6ixMUiFLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConanOBrien @MichelleObama Would she please be a mystery reader in my 3rd grade classroom?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhlpalmieri If you’re under 18 they disqualify you from their contests I found that out the hard way lmaO I kept h… https://t.co/zwit3TdLmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MightytitleMax LOOKING GOOD ‼️ Thanks for the awesome picture @G_Martinez3!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself I like you're headshot. The hood is way cool. I'm sad today. My Yellow Nape Amazon fell and broke he… https://t.co/RpTiOHZVML]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing more fascinating than the mind &amp; emotions of your Creator!]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚾️🚀Support Raritan Rockets Baseball! Get your tickets for you baseball Comedy Dinner! 🚀⚾️ https://t.co/egnAMoZGpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsBlxine @BarryMurphyPT @writtenoff_mufc How many of their players that Berta brought in would really work here?… https://t.co/tUDAqNijxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honoring the legacy. Succession of Dean of women and Dean of Students at @lifeatpurdue advocates for students, equa… https://t.co/E9VW8gj44W]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can tell if someone is lying: if they take a long pause before answering question. Cohen didn't do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPAC this where conservatives gather to try out new propaganda and repeat old propaganda and the more asinine it is the louder they cheer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eminem &amp; Boogie Issue "Silent Ride" Dance Challenge In Strong-Willed Push https://t.co/EgZwpxZkan via @HotNewHipHop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby P must have known I wanted to watch the #IEM Challenge, so he woke me up at 4:30 😵 Let's go @dignitas Fe!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grahamruthven I like to imagine the people in there saying "my word, there are some men running in some sort of at… https://t.co/IkHd6prSeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@captaincrook920 @Bmallil Nice thing to say about me an my daughter who was killed by an “illegal” felon immigrant.… https://t.co/9VP07gbZ4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Staciamichelle2 @BeastModeGran @ChrisCuomo @CNN I have a thousand times more  respect for the criminals that lied… https://t.co/Aewilkrjpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[In fairness to Pompeo, Trump says so many contradictory things that it's hard to keep up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful for the endorsement of the Faternal Order of Police.  We look forward to working with officers and the com… https://t.co/JBfEbUAck1]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's the thing, those women sit in the pews thinking about having Father in their bed instead of thinking of Jesu… https://t.co/uK4eOMVypj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi baloncito se llama Nico, y me duermo con el porque me lo regalo la persona que me gusta ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Hey Mama, today is gloomy but tomorrow will bring a little sunshine..... and much laughter you are so l… https://t.co/4ZLySvUEQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shine was probably offered the same deal as Omarosa, $15K a month to do nothing, but no blabbing or books.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panera Beard is always a good idea! 😋🍞🍗🧀🍓🍌 @ Panera Bread https://t.co/6WwnjWN7MA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelDMann I get paid to walk as much as I can in 8 hrs......I’ve hit 36k once.......!! 👍😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@som_bill @mattwilstein @thedailybeast Must be a reflection of the mean spirited president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrantMillerNBC in case you need a reminder of sunsets; Anna Maria Island, Florida https://t.co/e9Z8IkFp0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been converted in hives all week. No idea what is causing them and let me tell you. Hives are draining. I’m exhausted from being sick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The US has the largest trade deficit in our 243 year history. Trump has made it worse. With the missing school reco… https://t.co/U3lrfVOJH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BlackLivesMatter Is Making Single  #Moms Homeowners  https://t.co/3dthLyWFZI via @truthout]]></document><document><![CDATA[plz stop shaking my hand and giving me your germs, it is yield season and I don’t have time for that @AdmissionsHell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fury. Today’s art. (also a scan of hush money) @ Art Projects at Studio 103 https://t.co/myq1WF7IxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_toritos I can’t believe this is ur pinned tweet. Every single person who views your profile immediately sees this… https://t.co/ylk1ATllkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra HILLARY, COMEY, OBAMA, STRUZK, PAGE, ROSENSTEIN......THETES YOUR COLLUSION.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *looks at empty basket*   My girlfriend calling the waitress over for a refill on breadsticks: https://t.co/CdZeTeXZ50]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Rachel!!! 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻 Way to show up &amp; show out! 🔥 #gojags 🐆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusanKim4 @ShaunGalNews @tmj4 Where in Waukesha? My heart is thumping- daughter and family live in Waukesha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I consumed caffeine, sugar, nicotine and ended it with spinach dip I am disgusted with myself 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UT_Grad_Amy @neilschori @MancowMuller @jamesjyers @getfitbill @PamCapitanini @reachjulieroys @charliekirk11 So sad for the students. 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practice a #PositiveLifestyle to live a #happylife   #positivevibes #positivethoughts #positivethinking… https://t.co/vQ8dqhRg8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zedunow @ria_dancel Perfect emoji &amp; gif.  Tegaderm is pretty common! https://t.co/iKfLrfMiou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmm. Now we know why he grew the beard. So no one would recognize that he was the one who said this in 2014.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AROD I know you're celebrities I don't even really know, but I'm happy for you both. Wishing you all the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is the one on the side  My age is so cute omg  I was born to be a good thief  I like to the gym   Wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three levels of writing workshop: pulling teeth (which is start and stop workshop teaching), good student (complian… https://t.co/sWHReOdsBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbyfram On the edge of my seat waiting for the next enews story to come out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG! The buying. The selling. The carpeting. The packing. Storages. The moving. No appliances. Hotels. Eating out.… https://t.co/SiLYzD5Inx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedWingGrips @IlhanMN @DHS She is trying to throw our Government over Arrest her send the special forces and bust… https://t.co/clJoLjAuvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, other than our current so-called President, can you name a US President with known ties to massage parlor propr… https://t.co/b8aMiAI6gy]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANYWAY it's 2:36 am and I have far more productive things to be doing in my life than continuing to be annoyed by i… https://t.co/tOdZUiiwdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to order a McRib and the mcdonald’s employee immediately kicked me in the stomach]]></document><document><![CDATA[For teachers preparing to teach #TheNamesake, emcee a graduation ceremony, or even just take attendance, read this… https://t.co/GqBWB9DEBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TariffMYtaxCUT @cspanwj @kathrynw5 @CBSNews @StevenTDennis @business Honest people do know that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @NBCPhiladelphia for sharing details about #networkphl19!! ICYMI: ⌚️ TODAY — 3-8pm 📍@FillmorePhilly in Fi… https://t.co/t0oWDqKcCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duztyrozello No, I have a friend connected with the show who arranged it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen. Clark, please don't tell Sen. Flowers to stop. She is right - and you know it. #internationalwomensday… https://t.co/hXGsnZNpSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMCoulombe @markmacpherson Excited to meet you both.. and looking forward to a great conversation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitaniaMcGrath @TaylorRMarshall Are you the Phil Henry of Twitter? If so then you’re kinda funny sometimes.  Other… https://t.co/TmXQBSvOuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@there4igraham @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett You seriously do not understand that Jussie betrayed blacks, betray… https://t.co/Kj5dxLOZ2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can gain the whole world but is it worth the girl that you losing? Be careful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_gxannx yo why people been doing this to you since middle school tho wtf lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InqPotosky @LVann_Sports @cgboan @TonyCVSports @JHWreporter @epjackson @normacatalina12 @_nicolesaavedra… https://t.co/fP0Lzfe9NR]]></document><document><![CDATA[They ate rest stop ng evil imagine c and cultural successful.  Hard to beli ve isn’t it ?!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[$1 from each drink is going to @threesquarelv  - a cause near and dear to my heart! @ Dutch Bros Coffee https://t.co/5huiz5479q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teacher snow day..yessss!!  Celebrating w/me-enjoy the song😀❄️! @takethat @GaryBarlow @OfficialMarkO @HowardDonald  https://t.co/p3PlCbxLdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwroutledge @intheglare @calibasl @M_Bellanco @ClandestineRos1 @martingeddes He and Bundy,👿👿s]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are three kinds of questions I get about grad school:  1) how to get into grad school   2) how to survive gra… https://t.co/GfjktVxoDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pray for job openings and economic growth in your local community.  And my God shall supply all your need according… https://t.co/NyUyTeDepq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mhebern @eduprotocols @jcorippo @CoyoteRidge_ Absolutely! What an honor!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer Yes the Dems are desperate and only want power and control and care nothing about th… https://t.co/tRSwt51HmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning more about poetry this afternoon by examining different types of poems and finding examples of a variety o… https://t.co/jyxwts8EA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[John wick is on at the gym and I’m about to flood the place with my tears]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day of being 25 and I’m heading to my math class. What kind of torture is that 😂😂 #adulting #birthdaygirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[URI offering counseling following sudden death of student - WPRI https://t.co/s88L2Bnx6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bastilleaud i mean there's two sf shows, i kinda wanna visit abbie in texas and if i go to dc...... (but flights are expensive soidk)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nashvillerican6 Shariah Rule would never be permitted in this great country. This law would never get close to bec… https://t.co/CkLFhg4Ulu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro They’re the best 😂😂😂. Can’t even say Beto’s name right 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShellyParks5 @JessicaBulva @MsAVikings Any of your Creative Writing teachers or senior level teachers interested i… https://t.co/9IoDBTE2Xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RT_Miller Right, which is valid. But this person walked into an ER after seeing their GP and expected to be in and… https://t.co/jEwXnzrhOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lifestyles of the Rich and Socialist: From Chavez to Castro, leaders who lived the high life  https://t.co/c8ZVWGkW01]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hootsuite Q6/A6 I’m in accordance with  @eskimon . I constantly explore new software, but recommend free tools suc… https://t.co/RQPyaSd4dQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone talking shit about demi I don’t even remember so #thebachelorabc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok there’s some serious mind melding going on right now on all things #CX and employee experience with… https://t.co/Q0D7kby5hx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoundationWohl @kimmyifuplease @KoukasHassan @Debjohnson12708 Reported and blocked!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't have the US press to close to the seat of corruption that is Trump.  #ImpeachTrumpNow #ImpeachTrump… https://t.co/tadpxwxIST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNCastaldo @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump It’s a nickname dummy.  Go learn something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the red feels! @ Color Envy Salon   'Hair by Yvonne https://t.co/spxgvPPw6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Ms. Bug Eyes's mouth just blabbers and blabbers. Her mouth never rests, just like that tip top brain… https://t.co/KXDg9yTBig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noahcent It’s crazy how true this is I honestly can’t remember the last time I had a genuine conversation with som… https://t.co/CxA9hEOBZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UberEats please help. The driver just drove by and took $100 worth of food, cancelled my order.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy early Valentine’s Day❤️😘#Calentinesday #WeareUK #Gocats https://t.co/ivpLmVBXr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GameDay Caniacs.. Let's Not play in Nashville like last night. #TakeWarning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pliny the Younger (right) Pliny the Elder (left) thestuffedsandwich stuffedsandwich #sangabriel #thestuffedsandwich… https://t.co/bYzRTQfeeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have a travel mug for my iced coffee so I just poured it in an empty Lacroix can and THATS innovation babey!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Arrest him he threatened a member of the House of Representives. Arrest him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhoCheeMama The Last Ship was so emotional &amp; fantastic. The show has a limited run in Toronto. Sting was amazing.]]></document></documents></author>