<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DJConradFilms @Zap5000 @TheSimonWade @ChristianDemuth @connorhalden @BosseAshton @AHittel @PilotHunt3r… https://t.co/cWqTI5up0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @RepSwalwell passes on Trump coffee, Trump passes on $1bn in CA Bullet Train funding... #fairtradecoffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hate it when I’m being called a failure is because it really upsets me a lot, and somehow I just feel like… https://t.co/uYgoPcsvDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeAintReally Not down with “the R word” AT ALL, but yeah, Pizza Hut is trash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[popping 🆙 in #charlotte ⚠️🚀♻️✂️ @nyknicks  @washwizards  @hornets @ New York, New York https://t.co/DzcT5fEfkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller @Eddieonfox @uhbroncofan @raider_rob24 James Harden shooting 0-10 from three? Clearly he’s activated his playoff mode]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyNatta @WWE @BeckyLynchWWE @MsCharlotteWWE @RondaRousey RR lost to Becky. Triple threat Ladder Match, Lost to… https://t.co/3KDaIhsy3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Empanadas Imelda in Francisco G. Sada, San Nicolas de los Garza, Nuevo León https://t.co/XioBxWqwFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniellemx_ Danielle , te ves preciosa como siempre te mando besos 😍😘😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[No excuses philosophy: “we have no excuse for student failure.” This is a valuable paradigm shift to focus efforts… https://t.co/t1iLTusmmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Betty_Nguyen So pretty but, you know that...... I could only hope to turn tour head..... if we were still single.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@e_oxman @Chuckles152 Not a “happy ending “ for Mr. Kraft. https://t.co/xHDLyR3k0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently at work and thinking about becoming a happy ass motivated bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Pibb is the best soda ever made.   *now waiting to see if I get kicked out of Texas*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tagruber @01_zebra @ATFfish @misspunk63 @FPE66 @AW95NJ @raducom @trumpAngel45 @conservativma @PaulieD55 @FantWest… https://t.co/Yu1eoD0S7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Johntrae @Manateeschools However it’s not SO WRONG that many students that are zoned &amp; attend Palmetto High DO NOT live IN Palmetto?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melifix The smoke detector network becomes self-aware at 2:14 p.m. Eastern time, March 10th. In a panic, they try… https://t.co/7SdwWH7tC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@55true4u @Herbert_L_Reed @TMZ Unfortunately, the media will get the liberals in an uproar and the public outcry will get him off the hook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fulton County, Turner, Wrigley, Dodger, Global Life, Camden Yards, &amp; Old Busch]]></document><document><![CDATA[59. Still, cut down in his prime. And pension reform! Only SF pol to try and take it on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inecnigeria THIS MAN CAN NEVER BE JEGA. His CREDIBILITY is very shaky. This is the time NIGERIAN YOUTHS need to pr… https://t.co/nEfkE3LuiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time to lay my ass down I guess 🙂 I wish we had some damn creamer would have had some good ass coffee ☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amtrak regular crew friends on #50 congratulating @local12jeff on his retirement! #tweetsfromthebird https://t.co/M5jS1yIMgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoodySHW No. You HAVE to like everything I like.   Including axe throwing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @JudicialWatch The Clintons and Obama’s of the Democrat party have been able to deflect criticism/justic… https://t.co/h4IsOUjP3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders It works for you at other peoples expense, not yours! Douche]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArikDar @meheran_evan @JGreenberg11 Facts, like actual numbers?   Just a presidents trophy, and a Western Conferen… https://t.co/1Ns0FTaSdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to have @TheEllenShow On our podcast. Having Ellen talk with our students about the power of standing… https://t.co/hy0l5vqso0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It shocks me when people are dumb as hell &amp; refuse to learn a better way. But I ask me for money on a begging level.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@birdie1974 @rationaldoge That’s why I think we ought to invest more in transit. It’s a benefit to everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolSC @AB84 @Raiders I’m wit you on #✌️ business. Not this. https://t.co/QPSc4hzjcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safe_its That is my biggest problem. Finding a group that really wants me. They need to want me in their group. Th… https://t.co/DOPk27yGta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coachlazar Outstanding !! Congratulations !! Wonderful news !! Great legacy !! #GoEagles #GoNuts #SursumAdSummum… https://t.co/QFbrSzndva]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like today will be my last day at the black gas pumps, moving to the big green handle 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need more Cattle in Iowa. 50,000 to reach One Million. I'll buy 2. Who's in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going back over The Dictator's Handbook.  A must read for anyone looking to lead anything. Or, as it sometimes happ… https://t.co/GqdFLGVUyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IPrevailBand the 2 songs that are currently out on y’alls new album are on repeat. I’m ready for the rest and I ho… https://t.co/ZgbavU0Sb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! #grandmaraismn #sunrise #lakesuperior #exploremn @ Grand Marais, Minnesota https://t.co/d4rLQcVdGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@truebluela These people are fucking crazy!!! Harper could've been the lynchpin!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best video you will watch today. What a story and inspiration. https://t.co/aJvHTOsyNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alexis_Cossette Bientôt faudra enlever ou changer les noms de rue et ville qui commence par Sainte ou Saint, Jésus… https://t.co/xnoFeJ1Er4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@memphisnick Stop it. Grabbing iPad and now tailing if I can stay awake]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is there n*ck r*bn*s*n on my timeline I thought we left that shit behind us]]></document><document><![CDATA[⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ Cooking is at once child's play and adult joy. And cooking done with care is an act of… https://t.co/MKNQpXUmAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, brought to you by of #SingingInTheRain, one of the first movies I ever saw, or at least consciously r… https://t.co/CwmrrpgUSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ktsul139 That counts how many people listen to them, haven’t seen anything about the amount of people who don’t li… https://t.co/BmdUXorL2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EstoPasaAhora Murió Jorge Tassara, uno de los magistrados que debía juzgar a Cristina Kirchner en los casos por la… https://t.co/qX6q22WddG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@black_rayne @MrCEOLongStroke So much better then the last one lol no shade, this is fucking getting straight to th… https://t.co/klBOVD70aq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iron_lombardi @Mel_the_geek @HillaryWarnedUs @HillaryClinton Is the economy good?Yes but he didn't do it by himsel… https://t.co/gfBYlc8tbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another 12k!! ⛹️‍♂️Keep moving.  Keep fit.   👉👉https://t.co/e47vfc6LTk . #health #fitness #fit #fitbit… https://t.co/UktLiBbF2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValleyHoosier @SecretMarquette @Jones1213 @Snewb22 The majority of brackets have them out. 2 doesn't take you from… https://t.co/nCe25lsNS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warrenwansfam3 Doing the best I can my friend... some days are hit/miss though. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jack_Septic_Eye This was my pinned tweet for a little bit... https://t.co/ziDl95SOuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Increíble lo del nuevo spot de la Secretaría de Turismo. Parece más un culto a AMLO que un gobierno]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you go to UVA and drive a Jeep or BMW you are either from New York, Connecticut, or Massachusetts. There is no other possibility.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinjm1 Unlike Presidential candidates who wish to legalize the objectification of women through prostitution?]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just an all-around good guy who you know is never going to get into trouble off the field.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jannarden At least they didn't eat it did they? https://t.co/RSUO90RtHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Go pound sand I and anyone breathing air have never had anything to do with slavery.. More democrati… https://t.co/US8867s2MC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a great experience getting involved with the community tree planting day! @ Dallas, Texas https://t.co/tqSDgPiEyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe your dream home just doesn’t exist yet. 😁 In this case, 🛠 #building a home on a piece of land may be the perf… https://t.co/6Uuo7pswFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grand Central Terminal @ Grand Central Terminal https://t.co/GE6CuuH5DY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TONTOKAWALSKI Ok. Mind if I call a couple of my friends? https://t.co/oc2xd4Y6a8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmykimmel Shut up  u liberal jackass u help nothing for the problem but run ure stupud ass mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact for all our fashionable players at @ohioelite who rock these gems...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dfpalmet @realDonaldTrump I'll keep fighting but I won't let my kids live in a place where their future is determi… https://t.co/xmfjJ27Ta1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awaiting the #FutureSkills Centre announcement @RyersonU.  Great seeing so many friends and colleagues from across… https://t.co/8qW5dRCgvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salaam Remi - Find My Love Ft. Nas &amp; Amy Winehouse https://t.co/09I97poTOu via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jugbo You liked it ? This is really what I look like https://t.co/a99bee66SH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbyBigWheel Don’t you DARE insult “The Conqueror” https://t.co/3Ieb4SpDU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Let’s investigate Nancy, is there anything between her ears? What’s wrong w/her dentures? Is she drunk?  So many questions!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Pale by @MadeWestBeer @ 16100 West Sunset Blvd — https://t.co/cMA4bTxXwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los Angeles Scottish Rite, Honoring Most Worshipful Stuart A. Wright #californiafreemasons https://t.co/oSYTrPu3Di]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MD_TOMLIN @SmithsStationBB The was about having an updated twitter. You pulled resources out of the sky. Plenty of… https://t.co/cokWOCvW6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fishers won on this morning’s Battle Of The Burbs!!! https://t.co/5EohO5nBlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Looks like a Joey Tribbiani sandwich” says @GSAUCE_  We were at the SF MoMA. This is a ceramic sculpture. https://t.co/hzkXlOrKhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[All day today, I've been loading into #ApexLegends games on #PS4 with just one other person or alone. Has anyone else noticed this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kismytats @leeleebb21 @Blue_Rose173 @TheReal_TMcG @TattedSoldier83 @tenacious_tiph @seraphicpetal @JJRossReaders… https://t.co/DLdh7xQpwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith @JenSchwalbach @captainmarvel @MarvelStudios ... lower your... #IphoneTypo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wx_rachelj @ShannonClowe One of my favorite words is, "Oinks't-ma'brisket".  Fun? 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[2017-18 Lakers Record (thru 64 gms): 29-35  **signs LeBron James**  2018-19 Lakers Record (thru 64 gms): 30-34]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACarterglobal Clearly, you should have called it 'The Ass Factor' #ThatsGold]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hermanos mexicanos cometimos un crimen gravísimo al elegir a otro chavista populista en México los hermanos venezol… https://t.co/bBHQhXW1sR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zach Lavine is really nice. If he gets consistent with it, he can be an all-star.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gerryfreitas We played Ribet this year. It was really bad. I'm shocked to hear this.....  Truly shocked....  I can… https://t.co/TmnidHZYfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @SherrodBrown Has anyone even investigated El Paso  Tx,There's thousands of illegals who have babies… https://t.co/M6mDAxtGpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never gets old... Liaisons Dangereuses - Peut-être Pas  Live.  https://t.co/zhGWqn1YRd via @YouTube https://t.co/JXX4nUIMDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kordell_theking @Cashhman_ @aaleah_ When I addressed how fast they did these endorsements, it was mainly because m… https://t.co/dcVB11ZtbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ltdsoltd @WhenstonedC @TresaBridges @SSG_Davis_Ret @Birdseye1 @CarolGarofolo @intelligent50 @Whichsideareuon… https://t.co/UR3xEjS6JI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheQuartering Getting worse with the deleted reviews... https://t.co/nFJbb4FdxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thing Manafort didn't sell weed, he would get a much longer sentence]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow @Billsrock82 &amp; check out his gaming vids on @Twitch   https://t.co/Jac0FXgnxJ  Do it NOW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the love of everything good Dallas Mavericks...please dont send finley to the lottery....send luka please]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parkland: A Year After the School Shooting That Was Supposed to Change Everything: Those at Marjory Stoneman Dougla… https://t.co/AepRlOoBap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OmarKelly Hey O, any FA thoughts? I hope we only sign cut players but I’d make an exception for CJ Mosley]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOrangeCone Cup Series Booth = Bob, Ned and BP Studio = Bestwick, Gordon, and Larry Mac  Pit Road = Jerry Punch,… https://t.co/IOrOO7LsfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[| have we met? | ・ before we get started there are some things you should know...  i might keep you up at night, bu… https://t.co/jp8K7EUtl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams You are wrong, Socialism is for people who do not want to work. You have no idea how taxes work, a… https://t.co/oRLlYkRNaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I no longer have faith in the team that is managing #CA34 both in DC and Westlake. @RepJimmyGomez, @JimmyGomezCA ha… https://t.co/sJzYdbeikt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Operation Enduring Freedom U.S. casualty statistics for "Afghanistan only" show 2,216 total deaths (1,833 KIA and 3… https://t.co/8bNLZ2vHd0]]></document></documents></author>