<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@horiMahato @CNN The myth was white folks weren't junkies and thugs. I'm glad reality cleared that up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 I would like to thank you for your testimony!! Although you have lied before you sounded real sinc… https://t.co/U7ehzQXfr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rrfosho72 @alegriselle @astros_dude So I say that isn’t him because it’s a heavily edited picture of a person I do… https://t.co/YV46Qpy2xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it comes to my mom it’s ridiculous it’s like certain ppl act as if she never mattered so fuck y’all 🖕🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I done had so many scuffles I take licks ion even be dodging like that my Niggah you gotta show me something fr fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ah_occ_o @Paladiumcrayon @jjz1600 Bernie has finally broken with democratic support of Israel and the criminal actions of Isarael]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my clients come for lashes they think it’s their venting time... nah man it’s mine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayPFosgitt @CarlsAmateurHr @DynamiteComics ... ... ever tried drawing the characters from Peanuts or Wizard of Id… https://t.co/jGUb9nq6JZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus, how many stories like this have to be written before WA starts to truly take this seriously? Because we have… https://t.co/60ziy28Elz]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are handed everything on a freaking platter..... You take more than you can chew, 45 a lesson for you. .@POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had a dream last night that luke hemmings followed me and i am still so sad that it didn’t actually happen :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people are reminded of the things they owe you, sometimes their day is shitty, they’ll get over it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solid start to the weekend, scoring a little Saturday morning double hat trick #HumbleBrag #NoBigDeal #ThatsJustSixGoals]]></document><document><![CDATA[at #NYC🗽 during #NYFW 📷 taken by @8and2  #YuFujiwara —————————————————————————— #FashionWeek #documentary… https://t.co/wvtaGwgEAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagicLady3 @acnewsitics @AOC I say this with ❤️ @AOC is a little #spitfire that is a Texas compliment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grlonkindlefire I need to get caught up on this show. I've only seen the first two seasons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenna_Marbles if you don’t have an idea yet for your video maybe do one about the plants you got😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked my daughter about Momo, she Immediately dropped to the floor and started looking around. Scared for her life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fumble recoveries in basketball really should be a foul on somebody.   2 guys on the floor and a 3rd dude jumps in.  Come on man.  #BBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DondeHayFeria @MoratBanda @EdithMarquezL @JM_Napoleon @_CarlosRivera @CHAYANNEMUSIC @OficialYuri Lista para la vis… https://t.co/GNl2hgg35H]]></document><document><![CDATA[My crazy, beautiful people. https://t.co/WUC2xAvlJa  jennavecdeuxns enmancharles @ Ottawa, Ontario https://t.co/lWG8Cn5u4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me give yall ya daily dose of his fine ass. 😍😍😍😍😍😍😍. Wherever he at, I'm booking this plane ticket to get flewe… https://t.co/YGEd7o0oqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1 question from Kim Jung Un to Trump: "Who is Michael Cohen?" #summit #HanoiSummit]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little man working hard with his grandfather to clear the drive.  #childhoodhome #snow #victorny… https://t.co/rNm8FX9Lef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeebHandsom @UPS I’m gonna try and see but no I don’t think so, I’m super pissed dude 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[New renters insurance, freshly waxed brows, clean place... *kicks up feet* https://t.co/uPsaknpsPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I would like it of you took some time and placed a vote for me. That would be #SoChoice #108Tourney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Combs___ I thought it was an accent over the last e but it’s actually Renee’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acabo de ver un foto que me apachurró el corazón y me puse a borrar todos mis tweets estúpidos en los que me quejo… https://t.co/Bufok2f8G5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations and Thank you for your service and contribution to the store Barb  👏 👏👏. We are fortunate to have y… https://t.co/Y2pGLzVuFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jordan_Sather_ @WinThePennant Darkness is absence of light! Only light {good} exists {oneness}. When we take light… https://t.co/ed3MPmD2Fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCStar Obviously a wall would not have done a GD thing about this. A legal crossing a truck and it got caught by more advanced technology.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Typical. Recognizing that not everyone is a piece of shit is never good enough. It must mean you excuse all negativ… https://t.co/IlQSEkYliF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do find it oddly comforting, though, that it seems like their logarithms don’t know everything about me, like how… https://t.co/kwHgpkV2n7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vampire 🧛‍♂️ Pharrell didn’t disappoint, here a picture of him from 1967 https://t.co/efJ8RsvM9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. @KaohlyVangHer points out we don’t need to know of a specific ethnicity to know that it’s included in equal ri… https://t.co/OQKbjeE6Ao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joneill55 @Julianna_glass @thatsVeryKari @ccatmpt @AkronWineGuru @cowineco @CaththeWineLady @Cbp8Cindy @SLBriscoe… https://t.co/BiytuyFX95]]></document><document><![CDATA[somebody tell meeee, why I work so hard for youuuu https://t.co/t3lwfZweE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump This is what you are defending? You’re as nuts as he is. https://t.co/5390mccjNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate homework aghhhhhhhhh but also it’s my own fault for procrastinating aghhhhhhhhh but also why is it even a thing 🥵🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scott3sa @advicesisters @askTrustHR @KyraMatkovichHR @access_fulfil @NewsNet_NY @Dennis_Warren @Hempstead_News… https://t.co/fXoYPSAZli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosenhausSports Needs medication as much as his lying client does. #GrowIntegrity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @tmotsenbocker why does ‘Something in the Way’ sound just like a @davidbazan song]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying beautiful music from Whitman’s Womens Chorus during the choral festival today. https://t.co/n6ICbR4Bf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE SQRLLLLZZZ 🐿🐿🐿 #sqrllslszsss @ Corralitos, California https://t.co/maNPxtzG6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spokesmodeling/acting is one of my greatest professional strengths and joys! Pic 1: a still from a client HR traini… https://t.co/K26I4Yw0jo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaxrafferty I agree about sleeping. The U.S. changed clocks this weekend. It's always a hard transition]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Angelina Howard, new President of #Amazon Black Employment Network (BEN). Fantastic job leading… https://t.co/Lru8btTEaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump says that often.  Maybe the terrorist watches @FoxNews .]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BelleOfBatonRouge #Casino #Hotel #PlayersChoice #Gift #GiveAway @ Belle of Baton Rouge Hotel https://t.co/6vHrW4njpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Wonder if she and Al Sharpton talked about the millions in back taxes he's never been made accountab… https://t.co/1SR26NL10L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tastes like a lemonade. Very sparkling lemony, like any gose. Very spritzer flavor. Delicate. Recommend to lemonade… https://t.co/sfZSpvF7Ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[my biggest mistake is thinking that people care for me as much as I do for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sucks when people treat you different but you don’t know what you did wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PICTURED: Daycare owner who bailed out R Kelly with $100k https://t.co/6udpwR31lH via @MailOnline]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wyer222 @lorenzofuentes6 @AussieDebBell @CajunBlueAZ1 @HarryWiener4 @kodiak149 @KinmartinTori @Jae72333190… https://t.co/1Kulz9XdBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelDEsposi1 @SenateDems @SenFeinstein Whittaker will be in front of a committee for most of his time left. Bar… https://t.co/9Av7foy3p1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This past year i gave away a lot of whitening kits because i couldn’t use them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj Let Disease cull off the ignorant, and the ones who are Anti Vaccine...I got my Vaccinations...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thefanarthub @AmazonGoddessD @Rexy_panther @_BrooklynBatman @pyrobyrd @IrishPatti1 @deezel21 @Leahlangleben… https://t.co/FwjBNECynM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sex with kids is NOT okay. Molesting kids is NOT okay. Incest with your kids is NOT okay. NOT THEN. NOT NOW. NOT EV… https://t.co/Kt5pjD7Iar]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was born six weeks early and was v tiny. And the nurse in the hospital brought me a bottle and told my parents to… https://t.co/WAhqhQTNVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceCarolOates @MotherJones Always good to hear or read @JoyceCarolOates]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m actually so disappointed in myself.... this is awful   pls forgive me @justinbieber]]></document><document><![CDATA[I go without eating for a day or two then I eat like a grown ass man after🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeDoesStuff I started counting the suicides of my friends this year.. I stopped when I needed my second hand. All our relations. Love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when clingy friends get boyfriends because then they leave me alone lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandeldoys @mickeyd489 @JamesTurnerYT This is made funnier if you follow Hermitcraft.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been a SW for about 10 years to date, how about you guys? (I started young 🤭)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to this tonite it reminds me much of our Cin baes💔💔😭😭 #Cin https://t.co/snW3Qrr9ce]]></document><document><![CDATA[miss you squid💛🖤 #stadiumseries @ Lincoln Financial Field https://t.co/AaRuPeVYGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BachelorChirps Nothing here! Nothin'.  Got nothin. Nada. Zip. Zero. Zilch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna go to France. They just banned all the stuff that kills bees. So this means they love flowers and honey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂 OMG!  These two! 😂😂  #lilyandyodasfunnyfarm #pairadiceranchtexas #minidonkeylily #yodadog #fureverfriends @ Pair… https://t.co/K1OB3ZLL2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first ever showing of @BanffMtnFest World Tour in Rhode Island last night. It was an 11.5 hour day, but the cro… https://t.co/uIAUMPa6EO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting it done in the classroom and on the track! #TraditionUnderConstruction]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hanklejawn3 @RearAdBsBlog @penguins @ryanwhitney6 @BizNasty2point0 @MikeGrinnell_ @spittinchiclets https://t.co/mVeUWhF0IR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DontBugMeImInMourningOverArrow 😱😭💔💘🎯👓 #Arrow #Olicity #OlicityFilled2019 🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot and cold. Dead hands. Feel the love through spotty nerves. We never give up! #DimpleVerse #MySupportHeroes… https://t.co/OstHGufjGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[She turns heads with all her clothes on... Imagine that 😘 . . . . . #KatrinaMay #women #strength #power #class… https://t.co/oVTIzCGtng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @TheRevAl Equality, respect, and humanity are not required in his world. Diversity is scary. All minorities… https://t.co/UB9nMWuYq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 6: I have accepted a challenge from @sgregorybcps to post #7BooksILove-no explanation, no reviews-just cover(s)… https://t.co/CUKRjUbnSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Forest Ridge, Orlando, Florida https://t.co/7YNnotsuPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickADougall I’m in San Fransokyo and it’s driving me up the wall...literally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClemsonColorado @DMORTON43055307 @geoff_deweaver @RepCummings @HouseDemocrats @realDonaldTrump Elijah Cummings is… https://t.co/edZ15S15Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to this!!! Epic!!! All this amazingness on one stage!!! ❤️❤️😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[bumping an @UbbidubbiFest playlist for my all-nighter before my exam 👾 APRIL HURRY UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my first and forever friend - my sister Jennifer.🥰 feel so lucky to have you in my life. Xxoo 😘😘… https://t.co/2l7XLa0Anf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hopeless_10 It only counts if you get a gold medal. You can’t just do this shit and come back with a bronze. We only like winners]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire Pro life candidates must win elections to effect change!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeebsFLA and feeding the dog and waking up and going to sleep and eating dinner or breakfast.... I hate it all...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just gorgeous! ✨ For this #surelybeautiful brides look I used one of my new FAVORITE eyeshadow palettes, the 24kt G… https://t.co/A4JjDZcXHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love listening to @HezekiahWalker &amp; @RealFredHammond while driving to work. #filledwiththeSpirit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Bhz/bwx Coffee Bean Stout by @beer_works at @beer_works — https://t.co/DyruCWC4JT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing some of my favorite new products from @bathbodyworks on https://t.co/OjIekPZEgz today - from lotions and ca… https://t.co/HZmyFwRp98]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Candy by Cameo comes on its gameover. I’ll dance you out of the building.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite thing is searching weird things on Amazon that my mom then gets recommended for you emails about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC How anyone can believe that one person has the absolute power to scare off Jeff Bezos, is beyond comprehension… https://t.co/D0V2jnb532]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s in your medicine cabinet?   #xoxobogodoterra https://t.co/NHzKtNlkVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace @WhitfordBradley How can it possibly be risky?   They “fell in love”...they’re “besties” (Insert eyerolls &amp; laughter)]]></document></documents></author>