<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So the update on Tea is 🍵 @KendallJenner followed Jordan back . So everything is probably fake news. My receipt 🧾 i… https://t.co/yCu1gnBcFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsungMobileUS I can’t wait! 🔥 I have a bunch of clients preordering tomorrow. I hope we get a Demo COU… https://t.co/XXLwfyeXee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SNYtv Let’s see if we get Zach and what free agents before we do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenWillRock  son was so excited to get @BoRhapMovie today with the queen T-shirt he’s so excited wanna get him t… https://t.co/FUXq1MQbYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, the Kenderleys like to celebrate with the best food and drink in the world, each to an excessive degree. But… https://t.co/YdsGdp16gr]]></document><document><![CDATA[How was this a  real ad? / Rest in peace Ken Nordine  https://t.co/lamk3sDpOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeltelling Ha! How about an email every week asking, no begging me, to promote thier sales and tech. I blocked th… https://t.co/3aGykiGmHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love where you live!! #SunValleyResort @ Sun Valley Resort https://t.co/tHQr21iQXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForbesTech I never understood these, especially in a household with curios children who like to...push buttons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Mark now you wonder why many supporters and contributes stop giving donations this guys another Bene… https://t.co/v1KkkJpm0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuettaHusband @BoDietl Better than you telling her the whore was a democrat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my newest listing in #Eden! Tell me what you think!  #realestate https://t.co/swwrp2HZIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at North Carolina / South Carolina State Line in Charlotte, NC https://t.co/MxtO5RJibC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PG_Brasil pelo shampoo head and shoulders. O único que não me provoca alergia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeoffSchuler @Boxmenot @mimetic_ @Just4TheCause @TakeThatCDC @itsmepanda1 @Eventhedogsabo1 @drfixus @VeritasEver… https://t.co/Anp2pf84xs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My quest in Utah for a coffee barista that makes #bulletproofcoffee has been unsuccessful so looks like I’ll attemp… https://t.co/HNsLppkEhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[All lies created by CNN watch fox news and get all of the.sides of a.story not lies created by CNN and others]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp 12.5 percent. Tops. At least half of his base know he’s a lying sack of shit. They’re just happy to have… https://t.co/81To7oKDUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I was so hyped at having an actual valentines this year lol RIP to that idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Armageddon . . #dinosaur #spinosaurus #fire #flames #smoke #clouds #trashtruck #steppedon #firebreathing #mountains… https://t.co/WKHoowTUkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got mines when he was still doing door to door deliveries! Go support my guy and Blimp Apparel!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nofilters the blessings will be THAT much sweeter🙏🏿🙏🏿  . . #keepthefaith #staystrong #stayhumble #pray… https://t.co/C4TT3YozSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussellFalcon @TheAdamSass Featuring a voice performance by Julia Child!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[First they someone who is broken hearted and rich.    Then you go in for a hospital visit then when you wake up you… https://t.co/PMI6pcn1VO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexaBliss_WWE I guess this is our #MomentOfBliss for the day? Skipping #RAW tonight Lex? 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolWSD I see you’re all gas no breaks in your workouts too. Respect]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't drink wine like a normal person. The only reason that I bought a bottle of Rosé is so I could say it like t… https://t.co/LbZlzq7PyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOLAZODEPABLO Coachella se pronuncia cochlea, yo vivo  cerca de ahí ,  pegado a mexicali saludosss]]></document><document><![CDATA[No trip to Disneyland is complete without a visit to our little plot here. #mosibsdodisney #disneyside @ Disneyland https://t.co/rbag222eZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reggie doing the cut throat is an all time baller move and in today’s league he woulda be suspended for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3_Jekyll @SirTophamHat_F3 @F3theFort @F3_ablock @dkgray92 @Double_D_F3 @zonasc35 @GuelcherM @vinsonizer… https://t.co/c8WZMWXlNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Bublé just said “Pittsburgh is a great place and Antonio Brown made a big mistake “.  😂 @MichaelBuble 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was great to have Julie Reid of Nehemiah’s Vision speak at Pilot Knob tonight to a group representing various… https://t.co/jEtu5bNaxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Minnesotan aspired to be Brandon for obvious reasons, but Dylan was just impossibly cool #RIPLukePerrry https://t.co/9srbEyZ4vr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing as though AP classes got 41 credit hours out of the way for me before I started college, I’m gonna give this… https://t.co/bd3CJNiJKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WxShield Snow just now got here is serious, already light coating in 5 minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[They just asked Joe “If VCU isn’t going to win the A-10, who do you see winning it?”  Joe “I’m gonna go with a litt… https://t.co/wtYpAoiwiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASchwam very few human eyes looked at the letter. look at the bar code at the bottom; it has a valid zip+4 encoded… https://t.co/TcaEsTKtSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol Tristan Left his GF while she was Pregnant for Khloe 🥴 How u get em is how ya Lose em 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one can give you the answers you seek all of the time. Sometimes you have to look within to find the answers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Let's talk on those points in order. + More people should have gone to jail. + Guilty. + Homelessness and ment… https://t.co/bv2BeMsFlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to cover more @IvyLeague games next season. What I saw at Levien Gym on Saturday showed me how exciting those… https://t.co/QcHiXTCWPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[A band of moderate snow will move through Central Iowa this morning. I expect another couple inches of snow with th… https://t.co/5tUcSnEQuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jen_Hauser Yeah of course! I know this probably doesn’t seem like a lot of snow to you all in Europe, but for us i… https://t.co/cj0p8B31TU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nextdoor we have a new Property Manager in charge of 3 adjacent communities. How do we give her a user in Nextdoor… https://t.co/y6cVPAoXye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBB_Central That game also featured future 1st Team All SEC Kassius Robinson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deadpool let vanessa peg him for international women's day safe to say I'll never love a woman that much in my life 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gadiadelman How many times, has  the UN ragged on Israel? It’s time for the USA to stand up, on the UN floor and stop this insanity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peachylaurey @BusyElves fake news? Most valuable thing on Earth?  Day1USA HISTORY 3/5/1770 Boston massacre Soldier… https://t.co/jB8W0kHE0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CJArndt @RubinReport No: it was meant for its director, the teen POC was her authorial insert]]></document><document><![CDATA[Key Class Projects - Intro to AI Product Management   1. Chatbot - Eliza2 2. https://t.co/c008qTcPKb AI Guardian An… https://t.co/xFSjKp6Ajk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pollitosanchezg @oncecaldas @cdtolima si ves no es mentira hincha de finales, , siempre los mismos los abonados ,e… https://t.co/FjDO0EYKkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Murrayott Let's see his Taxes .Rhan this part of the dramas over with!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joerogan CBD administration before vaccination? Or better yet, let’s use Baylor’s excellent sequencing capacity to… https://t.co/UwWTYrVWlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful rainbow spotted over the Central Valley this afternoon. Just so pretty! A low pressure area was moving… https://t.co/48oiOLuBY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoctorCigari @velvetsugar76 @morganisawizard @JoeSilverman7 I highly doubt you’re a real conservative or an actual… https://t.co/qbRlDbow4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlakeTOliver @FischBooks @AguillardAcct @davidleary I’ve been impressed with what I’ve seen from Ituits TurboTax l… https://t.co/Ft3km3Q5X2]]></document><document><![CDATA[how to eat *store-bought tomatoes. most of y’all never had a real, home-grown tomatoe and it shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyahDickland And girls are dicks when it comes to taking care of us when we are sick lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WIPMiddayShow @JamesSeltzer I wish that I could call in... how about Batman’s Utility belt as an accessory? 🦇 https://t.co/hFsgw8SNTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DentonDevelopment #EatBigToGetBig #EatRightToGetRight #EatToCompete #GMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes sense the Dems need to stick with outlets that will feed the questions to the chosen one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein And this political cartoon will become relevant again, and again, and again... https://t.co/rwnCElimyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Davison has 16 points, No. 22 Wisconsin beats Northwestern  https://t.co/RKQwnDL2ZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AwkwardAndOdd That’s having fun and exercise at the same time..... get the Ben Gay out after you get out the hot tub 🛁]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what happens I’ll never put my girl aside or make her feel neglected]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BishopJakes @PastorKeion @LHHoustonChurch This is awesome 👏🏾.... giving my kids a bath, Can Still make it⁉️⁉️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNotoriousMMA #WhoIReallyAmIn4Words is a #PRPR12 connoisseur #SmoothIsFast https://t.co/6aAsRyP1R4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Christmas with my family this weekend and I still haven’t finished shopping or wrapped any gifts 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Yeah. Her lawyer[Mueller team] let's her know what's going on.  SHE KNOWS EVERYTHING !!! What is wro… https://t.co/6yn1TkeagU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I CAME TO VISIT CAUSE YOU SEE ME LIKE A UFO THATS LIKE NEVER CAUSE I MADE YOU USE YOUR SELF CONTROL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry guys... I’ve been extra busy lately. I have a lot of things going on and will have some awesomeness soon!! 🤫🤫… https://t.co/4lPJWZv7Ez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JewishWorker Mixing up their muslim congresswomen of color to own the libs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bergopolis Oh, woe unto you! The spirits whisper into my ear that the next pair of glasses you buy WILL NOT FRAME… https://t.co/QSsnZsYqj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[We agree. @base11STEM @ingrid_ellerbe @deanjmarsh @SOLIDWORKSedu @SOLIDWORKS @3DSNorthAmerica]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soy 0% heterosexual, 100% homosexual, lo que me coloca en el cuadrante homosexual. https://t.co/KHTAgvHxvN vía @idr_labs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noetic: Song of the Open Road, I by Walt Whitman (Analysis by Charles Cl... https://t.co/GaLZr6zMwk via @YouTube… https://t.co/9wSHrD0WwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davebudge Looking forward to following this project, may consider it myself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Officials investigate report of active shooter at Norfolk Naval Shipyard. Told by people outside it’s on lockdown.… https://t.co/C2Jsg4td81]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahahahaha.  Somehow not surprised.  #ottawa #autowa  'Unreliable' LRT trains can't handle Ottawa winters, intern… https://t.co/6ryAA62VgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[La pornomotora tenía la instrumentación de NIN pero las líricas de RBD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Event replay available on demand on the RACE DAY app Powered by NSAF or https://t.co/HVsDKGCmoz. Congratulations… https://t.co/sBO3v57apN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you had to take Lebron James or James Harden right now, to build your team and have the best player- who u choose? Me- Harden easily.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see join other members of @ECUPublicHealth faculty for @uptowngville First Friday Artwalk at… https://t.co/ImPtwrjQmj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worst thing about this: she accidentally drew a dot on the iPhone Notes app she used to write this nonsense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iima_priince 😑 black and yellow &gt; anything written by drake... “yea I said it”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elaine_burk @libby_poche @radison33 @Renevelation @Franklin_Graham 1. There is no proof of a holy spirit. 2. What… https://t.co/K9jgIj7ugZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDJack5 Thanks bro. Means a lot coming from a connoisseur like yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports #BERNIE #BIDEN #JusticeLeague #CoryBooker #Warren Trump is a formidable enemy. Why go it alone? Wh… https://t.co/veLA6AMMuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin You know your doing something right when you trigger so many!]]></document><document><![CDATA[TFW you’re talking about track ids and DJ life, then something actually important happens in your life]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Brock viciously smeared Anita Hill and now he’s trying lecture Bernie Sanders on how to run a fair campaign;… https://t.co/NZpMwVAD5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker substanceless on @MorningEdition   Think I can cross him off the list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rayjon_ Yeah I mean I’ve seen him notch 20/20s in his sleep he’s a beast on the glass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helped Jessica Stanley purchase her new Traverse today!!! @ Vaden Chevrolet Pooler https://t.co/0jKXmiIOyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyReinke @FredFredSanders The most beautiful thing is the love the Father has for the Son, and the reciprocal lo… https://t.co/vwWj9UGkRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFMSBen Interestingly enough, some people thinknyou need to wait wait wait until your kids are ready for it. Me, I… https://t.co/jAqa8bjcud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like my mom are used to tell me, when God made me he threw away the mold. I see He’s throwing a few more away. Than… https://t.co/4UpWjj6LNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I love that Alexis and I just impulsively buy concert tickets. I’m so glad she’s back! 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeNewsHQ I miss Ronald. He was the President of my childhood. If he were alive today and saw what they're doing… https://t.co/JKb7UBBxs4]]></document></documents></author>