<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@The_Meathead @timwilcoxtwit @Robb_Ellis @MikeInBuffalo @JoeShedler @JohnVillella7 @cshanny55 @Dudgee @Tea_RedRose… https://t.co/1kt9aR79tF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently snowing and schools still happening :).   Washoe county school district is officially retarded https://t.co/zyansTwWNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bpwedge @WVUFLU @WVGOP Because unfortunately we as a state forget and return them over and over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jykrgr @RickMailhiot @BT_Drumz @CaptainBetty @JonBoyDavis @SouperDrummer @muxmike @rbeef81 @mattdudleydrums… https://t.co/quhdBA371F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never liked @budweiserusa. @MillerCoors is far better if it’s a choice between the two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's day  😁😜 @ North Little Rock, Arkansas https://t.co/fHVma6dDK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/8/2019 - 22:25 Temp: 51.2F   Hum:  90% Wind: 0.0 mph Baro: 29.882in. &amp; Rising Rain: 0.06 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeELtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow this is pretty bad/sad. I lived next to nhhs for a couple years and went to samo (similar beachside wealthy pub… https://t.co/R8dKaxNKxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are all equal: we all breathe the same air and bleed the same blood, when we die the same ditch gets dug.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham @BillyGraham @TellaGraham @hillsong @RealHughJackman @Australia @JewishTweets @AustralianOpen… https://t.co/YIeaXXVYY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatgirlKacy12 @ribeyeszn @Ange_lala_La @gr8tvaluebiggie @ashholesimmons @samtheaustinP1 @Tier1P1 @nikiornicole… https://t.co/nsAAynMRIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE: EXCLUSIVE: @WWE_MandyRose &amp;amp; @SonyaDevilleWWE are NOT worried about meeting @SashaBanksWWE &amp;amp;… https://t.co/z0wFWHOtqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to meet one of the all time @Broncos greats @richkarlis https://t.co/4M9o7Q5nzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrBig4NYGov @placardabuse @chesneycheckers @NYCCouncil It was easily the top 5 total votes of any council candidate, dope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Metra - Arlington Heights - @metraupnw in Arlington Heights, IL https://t.co/RVhy5oFmpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sports girls that will fuck your life up in order:  Softball girls Soccer girls Basketball girls Volleyball girls C… https://t.co/0OGGuwlvf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Round 2 for Sunday Brunchfest...Homemade sourdough croissants 🥐 🤤 @ Grand Rapids, Michigan https://t.co/3Zfk1wb1Pt]]></document><document><![CDATA[today my parents scoffed about it snowing and started joking about global warming.   my mom said she doesn’t believ… https://t.co/8wxxBslo4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Akviko @jessica_r6s Yaaaassss I love our posture corrector so muchhhh 😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@venuslvnda @NinodaFilipino MINES LITERALLY 0 AND NINO IS PRECIOUS SO STOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Azizw22 @brfootball @neymarjr Hey, cut that out trying to be logical. You know if a pro athlete is injured he must… https://t.co/11wjFMkD9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vaughanweather @bradrousseau @matt_grinter @blizzardof96 7 cm of new snow in Milton; I received a report of 14 cm… https://t.co/SmqHzpiTUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHOT IN THE DARK:  I’m coming up to NY to see a show on Saturday, May 11th.  I would love to do some comedy on Frid… https://t.co/P1dnWnIIIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really 42 degrees in Tally right now. Karma is telling me to stop sending screen shots of 80 degree weather to my northern people 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only ring the #Steelers or #Bengals will see in 2019🤣 https://t.co/3N4DF9lZkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Quick one night #WorkTrip to #Atlanta #ATL and luck out to see my #Aunt #Charlotte and #Uncle #Tom at their gate w… https://t.co/J2MXvuz5gu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scifijunk @Jewelsquest Students below grade level require local intervention. LOCALS should appreciate they have authority.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cba_titans workin in the COLD  @Brandon54308122 @JaredSclafani_2 https://t.co/B1LiYZrcVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the great Old ‘97s once famously predicted: “You’re gonna crash on the barrelhead, son / You’ll regret the thing… https://t.co/lvFElydDmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaThompsonMPP  @fordnation  is this true?!?!? Could you be selling lies when you have said you are #ForThePeople… https://t.co/Ng2eVL2GFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreeSpeechGirl Nice goebbels pivot!  “Accuse those of which you guilty”.   Free lesson is over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the @Ldn_Labour for the respectful and honest tweet that recognizes the points I made at the meeting.… https://t.co/ztKmLjlZEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliseShrock What do we expect from a guy who was on @FullFrontalSamB at the RNC saying that black lives don’t matt… https://t.co/zhGfJAV2Ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaneWritesStuff AB has a blonde mustache he needs to stay up north preferably in Buffalo 🤣☹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Event Photographer 4 Hire! @allswagga #KennyBeanPhotography #Photography #Nikon #ATLANTAMODEL #PhotoShoot… https://t.co/9Dr3Xx4bBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larssolarsen @Liz_Wheeler It should never be allowed to condemn a people for their religion or ethnicity By people… https://t.co/eQnn5sgry9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@globalnews That should start out like this instead: ..more people are going to be injected with unpredictable gene… https://t.co/T3zB8IBSTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is asking if I like the new season of drag race as if I am watching it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fumée Dramatique #FujiXT3 35mm-1/30th@ƒ/1.4-ISO2000 #smoking #smoke #winter #streetfashion #NightPhotography… https://t.co/NAuLTWf97L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerbusJames @forthemasses @LogicalReterg @DSDW30 @badibulgator @hugh_bothwell @JesusHealzSaves @BenjaminGladst1… https://t.co/E3y5WsUxAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetrueschuh @failed_q The Proud Boys are too busy fighting each other these days. Too bad. They were fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women's CIS Final 8 in Toronto, same facility as OSBA Final 8. Excellent chance for coaches to check out talent to recruit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a lot of Denny’s out here.  Maybe a new tradition for Ohio wrestling trips? https://t.co/Idja5eNJ09]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tchrs at #MAMSlearning I’ve been blogging with my students and @edublogs for 10 yrs now. If this article inspires y… https://t.co/erD7OpcTYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lambofgod South Florida, WPB @Slayer @lambofgod @canibalcorps1 May 11th]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe has something special going on.  If you want a Ridge Market Brand But are struggling with money, @YME_Ballers i… https://t.co/0VLlBWAtc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kid remembers the steal then kicks Sid to the curb with a “see you later.” 👌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spare us your outrage. You are propping up a proven liar and cheat. Your birther  history is not forgotten and only… https://t.co/JMEOPEjftR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Piece of advice @everyone! Stop the drama and say it to their face, I promise life is much better that way 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘America first’ increasingly looks like America alone: The annual Munich Security Conference is usually a somnolent… https://t.co/B9S17997rb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoneyResists @NitwitTV @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Are you thst dumb ? There’s 320 million people here and on… https://t.co/MPl8ykFNjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such an honour to be in the room with some of the most amazing, inspiring, encouraging and thoughtful leaders (and… https://t.co/hRklxWAvIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karl20013 and i’m going to see it live weekend one https://t.co/aikfdWBkqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fahrenthold @business I used to walk by it every day, after it first opened. It was surrounded by scary Russian bo… https://t.co/8MJNtktNyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@howardeskin Harper is West Coast Guy: Philly = Lousy weather: Latin players prefer Latin Culture cities]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicole_kaylee17 I just know Valentine’s Day ain’t easy for everyone so I’m just tryna make people feel GOOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldskar @franfraschilla @dandakich @WVUhoops @BillWalton @JayBilas @DickieV @Holgorsendana @JMUFootball… https://t.co/m97CDIfdIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[You might want to ask our state senator @janmetzgerny what she thinks of this.  @NYSenatorJordan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I responsible for my child’s choices?” Ultimately, no; potentially, yes! If you want to determine the spiritual health of your family]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two unbeaten women’s champions in their primes: @Claressashields vs. Christina Hammer for the middleweight champion… https://t.co/FU44yXLeN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatsfraziness @LeBatardShow If they dont theyll try to sign him in the offseason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IJefTomI @chrislhayes I'm supporting Kamala, but I gotta give Elizabeth Warren a lot of credit.  She has a whole p… https://t.co/bkLyLtdUgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD TUESDAY MORNING TO ALL of you my very special BEST FRIENDS, may this day bring you peace, grace, love, blessin… https://t.co/VSNehyubBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekMaberry @TPDDavis True, that’s one of the reasons I unfollowed him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just received my @ADEAGoDental badge for the #GoDental19 conference! Ready to learn and connect the @AmerDentalAssn way :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @photoj_eric and LHS Positive Choices for coordinating today’s very thought provoking Safety Day assem… https://t.co/NNOprWRBlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸 A Niçoise-style salad is the perfect meal, with the right amount of protein and vegetables which your body needs… https://t.co/i8wv9RTh5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thenerdrm @PureGeniusLego I was also leaning to the UCS Slave 1 over the UCS snowspeeder, but the rumoured 20th Sl… https://t.co/myGlDidDWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teleSURtv Guterres. El pobre no tiene la menor idea en donde esta su tracero como va a saber quien es el AZNO maduro!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA He’s going to hold the date for Christmas ... and when he takes credit for it, Republicans will appl… https://t.co/dRYlpj54IY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Harold, Tony, Heather and all the @BGCKingstonON staff and Board members for a wonderful evening.… https://t.co/YIIfqtEcU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Illinois State coach Dan Muller said sophomore Taylor Bruninga had surgery Friday on his left foot and 2 screws wer… https://t.co/EQqDO3FsQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many Thanks here @WERC , we love ❤️ and promote your organization worldwide 🌎]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump Even if you aren’t caught by Mueller, I will always believe you are a Russian asset because of your behavior and words.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FeeAngel223 @OldManStoneZone Shes in a dark place with her soul .unfortunately there is no one around HER to wake… https://t.co/HZXAHrfnIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before the election voter identification is needed or the election will be stolen!   No one in there right mind wou… https://t.co/Plck82eODN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We broke down what climate change will do, region by region Spoiler alert: We are all f&amp;÷ked! https://t.co/ldUA21Urmd via @grist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Screw you. You're a liar. Guess what? We believe McCabe. All you Republicans do is lie. @FBI @RepAdamSchiff… https://t.co/RzuPhkdIv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamnDeShawn How I feel about it. My mentions and DM be on FIRET when I say I only like lightskin men.  https://t.co/pWsv4SttxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If members of Congress believe in God how can they not believe in the lives He sends into the world? How could they… https://t.co/sQtlb4b0t0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hall_Jeremy @GeorgeSavaricas Adam Scott called it out publically and he’s playing with him. Unfortunately Scott is… https://t.co/mdP0bHHKYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@occupied_stall On my way. But Chiken wings,and Fiddle Faddle easyer on the soul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It always made sense to me for the Blue Jackets to land Marty Brodeur ... err ... Keith Kinkaid. I just always assu… https://t.co/kWbh2PkfnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m born every day 👶🏼 I’m a great garden fertilizer  I keep bugs 🐛 away from plants  I’m organic and all natural ♻️… https://t.co/lXZj4x4KtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am Kenyan.  Feel free to investigate my forefathers origins.  Mine are at Ngong Town, at the end of the road..eve… https://t.co/76L914vm1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta be bead up on Fat Tuesday!!!!! @ Albertsons https://t.co/uL0yUeiwAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realest words any artist ever put in context: “I am a sinner, who’s probably gonna sin again. Lord forgive me, Lord… https://t.co/CNzmxthOE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@followtheh bravo... novice NY politicians blew up the deal, now trying to distance themselves]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump Please stop speaking for everyone  because 54% of the population does like him and… https://t.co/qX8wSgs53M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight was even better... i told you. !! @ Baton Rouge, Louisiana https://t.co/AXtvkIs6eJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman These Lemmings will except anything Trump the rapist says, they’re blinded by the shinny object wh… https://t.co/5SwAh5NuEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pedro Strop: “I don’t care about that. I don’t care if we’re on the radar or not. You’re still going to have to pla… https://t.co/xFSSEU1GLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made the article!! #ASU #CurtainOfDistraction 🏀 https://t.co/oCcQm99Tg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well worked literally all day but we’ll worth it. 8-5 and then 2 basketball games after 😅. I - AM - DEAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[$184 = Approximate $ Bryce Harper will net after Federal, State and Payroll taxes. #Phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of @zshort_20   BB and a run scored in his first game in @Cubs major league camp. Keep grinding Zack!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zach_Whicker Agreed. And I don't fault the coaches who have adapted to it. The kid will go elsewhere so why not bu… https://t.co/mJW2rAbcy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KHQATegan some freezing rain / drizzle and sleet at times. Cars are glazed with ice!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lazy Sunday morning.  Of course they were up a 7:30 this morning. @ Hudson, Massachusetts https://t.co/YyvT24Q5cu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real thanks goes to the @BarbaraWorthJHS Principal, staff, and students who helped coordinate this and make it… https://t.co/8irjKMKrNK]]></document></documents></author>