<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#NationalNutritionMonth  🍒Make half your plate fruits and vegetables.  🥦Fruits and veggies add color, fiber, flavor… https://t.co/hOs3nIZzXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews How? I mean if they're just sleeping, how are they eating? LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't want to be *that* sports fan, but Wofford scored every time I left the room... Score was tied at 55 with 2… https://t.co/ZjmW2B2Bwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josh_Smoker I’m going to need to be a #hockeymom in the future. Thanks in advance for your cooperation 🥰… https://t.co/EAlibzql9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ai que alívio o Café da Manhã dessa sexta feira não ser mais um baphão do governo!!!  @mageflores @rodrigovizeu  [O… https://t.co/HTVM4JX2sP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mymcmedia @MoCoCouncilMD Great, Now let's ban Roundup in our @MontgomeryParks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karahvictoriaxo 12/10 recommend, yes...Canada is always good too, we love Canada]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paris__G My dad got scammed into buying Google play cards. He thought it was his bank. 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love sociology and people and faith. At the largest Hindu temple in the US right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another assault and lack of understanding...On Disability and on Facebook? Uncle Sam Wants to Watch What You Post https://t.co/IO1LudePGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[today we are listening to our body and being kind to ourselves BUT NOT BEFORE absolutely chugging some dunkin iced coffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[A gente bebe vinho doce já sabendo que cada gole é uma paulada na cabeça amanhã]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMurphy With it having that much liquid you may want to let it do a natural release at least for 10 to 15 mins or longer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nargie123 I just...... he’s acting like everyone says racist shit in their group messages.. sir, stop exposing you… https://t.co/3Idlzzn8Wr]]></document><document><![CDATA[captivate me one more time, show me how I’m divine 🖤🔊 https://t.co/uI2S9x3jan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome to see more pre-competitive collaboration to develop best practices and solutions at scale.]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you text your five friends on capus if they're free and non of them responds 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bts_jjimni_ @babykookie119 I can see how much you are. If you are dirt, u have an idea when he found out that mayb… https://t.co/YDS4Lif1OH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nativeesoul Of course he did the right thing , if he hadn’t he would have been a heartless soulless excuse for a human being.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you don’t need to waste your time on someone, who only wants you around when it fits their needs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drew_NearPost @Jeff_CCTuba Understood. That’s why I was saying it’s absurd.]]></document><document><![CDATA['It's a Fan Thing" so we #FightforWynonna  @IDWEntertain  @IDWPublishing  #earpers https://t.co/Y7KtJ0T6fl]]></document><document><![CDATA[100%. It’s an Olympic medal they played a part in earning. Just because it’s new doesn’t make it worth any less. Gy… https://t.co/Uf6090aM7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not fair! I remember when using the “N” word , 27 years earlier, cost Paula Deen her food network show, and million… https://t.co/7wHwUymRkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2: I have accepted a challenge from @CFletcherMiller to post #7BooksILove no explanation no reviews-just covers… https://t.co/MHE13nhBmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFerrerMHS @Tom_phly @Moskohistory @mhsmrlawrence @Mainlandhigh And thank you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WhatWeLearned on @FallonTonight #TonightShow w/ @jimmyfallon guest @pattonoswalt on his #SexLife at #Fifty50 (… https://t.co/hSPykGWxM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do kids have imaginary friends anymore?  I had an imaginary friend named Jamal when I was young.  I also wanted to… https://t.co/YOiFhIZqBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So grateful for these faces 😍 .... ❤️❤️❤️❤️ @ New York, New York https://t.co/dwQT3dDUmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhannahjones Teach! I had to learn from a friend and I thank her. Respect is in language.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because you always grew up in a black setting doesn’t always make you understand the “epitome of blackness”. Knowin… https://t.co/5E6diAXRPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise at the track @ Saint Petersburg, Florida https://t.co/x3sJHggb6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saving time?  Speaking “Cook and Of” takes less than a second!  It makes you look silly to make this statement. Sho… https://t.co/kvZKjRuXA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeedBen @TheRickWilson @nacion Important to recall that US  Chamber of Commerce opposed e-verify until 2013. C… https://t.co/yd9IkDesNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tato_NK @DrogasMx @dpccolectivo @eldaamolina @mijisoficial @claudiarodzazu @atiempomadrid @NoEstaChidoOrg… https://t.co/qHQ7LYKBIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigbabybutler @madelineannm Just not Madison Reed at home hair coloring pls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Spicey is so small! Remember when he was hiding in the bushes in front of the WH ??!!  Hilarious stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sostraveluk @chancetotravel @Nicolette_O @SouthernerSays @Poland @ewarsaw Cheers, guys 🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnRHinton2 Sometimes, things aren’t always as they appear at first. Authors use it for detailing.We need you to… https://t.co/VmqlRiaCCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[the one thing i do when i’m drunk that i will never understand is just add every single person i remotely know in m… https://t.co/i4VEP4rV7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_snoonian Weird, sad, shocking, disturbing, infuriating, mystifying. So many adjectives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rawkinsb @SenSchumer Yes, you do creative writing, as your tweet attests.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So after my boss called me out for not being where other artists are ive had the sudden urge to do something about… https://t.co/KnsKb03rfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Human Resource Assistant - https://t.co/ubd9VER6rx #KellyJobs #KellyServices]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain marvel opening night at @SeattleCinerama and we ran into some super awesome local cosplayers and they were… https://t.co/9R6ZZz8Nrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amourcarthy I discovered how to do my do by going to a Deva Curl Salon (don’t use their products - use what works… https://t.co/RC0BvNhD6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, Matt gaetz your alternative facts won't save you, nor individual 1.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 Why do you need a hairbrush you don't have any hair  NO HAIRRRRR FOR MY HAIRBRUSH NO HAIR FOR MY HAIRB… https://t.co/ZJLNjybVTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kimberly_Inc He ended up switching later but he was basically just an extra in the film lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[greetings from #neworleans. #travel #vacay #vacation #duranie @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/IH2iR1NDj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty sure this whole scandal they are amping up for the Liberals is straight out of their how to beat them pl… https://t.co/4muMoqAzSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bounceback #comeback @ Greenville, Mississippi https://t.co/kKHlhn6tI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kissycv i literally flew from atl to phx in january for a show and i would do it again in a heartbeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, the #BreakingNews today, from Paul Manafort in deeper trouble, R Kelly charged with 10 counts of aggravated cr… https://t.co/EXyWVHOKaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated One other comment, he’s not an entertainer, though he’s trying for an Oscar.  He’s an unabashed snake-oil salesman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halftime. The Alumni has shown up and the Lions are showing out. 57-41. @YatesMagnet @JackYatesHigh https://t.co/SYV1hSGqKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recently, you mentioned your ex-prostate and radiotherapy, so I figure she's still trying to hang around and bother… https://t.co/3lXkimsmBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day is a new day, and you’ll never be able to find happiness if you don’t move on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[School run on this dreary morning. Mr 12: “What do you want to listen to?” Me: Unenthused... Mr 12: Puts on @oasis… https://t.co/OUtTDhfS9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chloeeguillen So go join that crowd &amp; when I get back your ass is going with me to the gym to die]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @yashar why isn't she just throwing him in jail? What's with all the warnings?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#teambeagle #damsam @officer_jill @warwickripd Dam Sam says thanks for checking on the pooch. #arooooooo https://t.co/KCiwzT3Cx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snapchat showed me a year ago today I was reading a book in a beautiful garden in Spain and today I found out that… https://t.co/BiSx4Bydz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genesis 4:2-3 (KJV)  And she again bare his brother Abel. And Abel was a keeper of sheep, but Cain was a tiller of… https://t.co/KcsFTnq5aB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Acting Director of the FBI all but says the president is a Russian agent.   The FBI thought the President wa… https://t.co/o9U7klK0Zk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officiallaxgirl @kateleavell You need to try Outdoor Voices, especially the leggings. The fit and feel is like not… https://t.co/co7rTgBpll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AyannaPressley @LaurenUnderwood @RashidaTlaib @AOC #girlswithglassesrock https://t.co/Mu9U6aQhI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[First tennis practice is Tuesday, March 12. We will start at the weight room at 3:20. Practice will be over at 5. M… https://t.co/HUn6JFQSCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[love sleeping more than 4 hours bc im well rested enough to listen to trap music at 5am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh @Delta  what a disaster of a day - first  flight delayed because of mechanical now second flight to Kingston has… https://t.co/91socoPY7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brycetache  Unfortunately people are burned out.  It's the weekend, shouldn't the imbecile STFU?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been with Today RE for 20 years in September. That says a lot about a real estate company. We would appreciate your… https://t.co/KuHASOEaog]]></document><document><![CDATA[Total shade but I hate working with people who beg for hours and complain every minute of their shifts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LingerieLayla BABE! This is what happens to us too. We’re on a well and when the power goes, we have about 30 pres… https://t.co/ZQVFVjkqwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tag a loved one for a chance to win a pair of skincare gift sets ♥️ #happyvalentines #healthyskin #seakelp https://t.co/xxLPqmKvdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder—Lady Bengals- your paperwork, photo and tee shirt money are due to Mrs Morris by FRIDAY, March 1. @BgBengals2019 @Barnegat_HS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MannyMua733 6 or 7 with regular bread. 9 if it’s Ezekiel bread. That shiz has to extra toasty or else it tastes like cardboard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafetyPinDaily This “School Voucher Program” is unethical on every level!  Public tax Dollars go to fund Public Ed… https://t.co/vbiMdEryLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[And infusion curiosity and a love of learning must be part of the curriculum for the learning disabled or Dyslexic… https://t.co/VTRUuFkT2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm pretty sure all my fresh 48's have the same style pictures for each post, but I don't even care - I just love a… https://t.co/JjZc9h3epo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Katie Krueger crossed 5K. Time 00:40:42, pace 13:06 min/mile, est. finish 8:38 am https://t.co/4VruWfgOW6 #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @CAGlobalAffairs for a great panel discussion on trade &amp; diplomacy today. #cdnpoli https://t.co/Kr1qHPFaMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[How are mfs so mother fucking sprung after only knowing I exist since last week and not even in person, THROUGH A D… https://t.co/hBe5dG9aDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only w the palm thing cause I think it’s common for people to get a tightness in their throat when anxious or sad o… https://t.co/7Xcmw9H7Zy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Endithinks @Patrickesque But, who held office because GOP controlled the Supremes who were appointed thanks to GOP winning Presidency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmdm1 @TeddiMellencamp Did you see the smirk on Lisa R’s face when it all started up at dinner]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMAZING! Believe in the impossible!!   #FreeSolo adventure film &amp; adventurous filmmakers for the win!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or is it easier to come up with tweets at night ( ya know for da drafts )]]></document><document><![CDATA[iridescent head and infantry belt. she hit the DC at the beginning and that was the only down she got for the rest… https://t.co/zlM305LYJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um 911? Im lost in Minecraft im just like running around in circles ... help me]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Hendersonville Inline Hockey Association’s 2 rinks took a hard hit from floodwaters last week. But GOOD NEWS: t… https://t.co/KpTbCANeYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking creepy ass men staring at me at the gym. Back off you nasty, ole crusty crust. You piss me off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌲Con Sue Photography and Design🌲  ♥️On-Location.... March 9-14, 2019♥️  🌲Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌲  ♥️This… https://t.co/fn1kSqDjVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump...let's talk about 'low';  YOU were overseas...with your tongue down in Kim's throat. And...… https://t.co/y3AZJno4tQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when my friends add my brother on snap or any social media cause he’s CRINGE 😂😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is me when i tell kyle they messed up my order and we’re in drive thru &amp; still continues to drive away...]]></document><document><![CDATA[im like a little caesers pizza.. i be hot &amp; ready. https://t.co/50vNPW9kdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunflowers Bucket Hat. #handpainted #paintedhats #deborahwillarddesign #willynillystudio #winstonsalemartist #Etsy… https://t.co/iK1VfVytDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aunque si fue un día lluvioso, fue muy lindo haber podido estar ahí. Te lo agradezco tanto Clio! brunettefashionfol… https://t.co/hiUo7rY9tE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Quamthebomb I make a lot of sense my views aline with our TOP INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS. Read up about the facts. ins… https://t.co/AYDR7hGatB]]></document></documents></author>