<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LetterkennyProb is one of the best shows I've ever watched https://t.co/AIDfrhQm5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[As in Friday Saturday and Sunday, also worth noting I working 15 on Thursday too and also got next to no sleep Thursday or wednesday RIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Givemeabiscuit His work is inspiring, I wish that I had the time to focus more on photography... hopefully I will someday]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@UberEats @McDonaldsCa Well, this is McStupid. The only thing they got right from our order was the two drinks and… https://t.co/bixSE3nApH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports @SecPompeo The world demands full transparency directly from #KimJongUn   The list, locations and… https://t.co/HtGbGLeDHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eek! Time to get the registration in folks! The discount is a significant one! @AskNancyO will be sure to help answ… https://t.co/ThZvm7vUwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ivana Santilli -- Sun + Moon = Tomorrow Official Music Video https://t.co/BK7tSIKFuX via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 3: Cardinal newman 25, st Joseph’s 39 @pdpreps  @NorthBayNews   @CNSportsMed @CIFNCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArnoldHSchultz1 @atillathehun412 @laraluv39 @fearnothing23 @sundance7055 @LauraDarlin0163 @SewWhat18 @sappermartin… https://t.co/LlVRJJOqzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McCoolBCB Agreed. You also cant look at it on a one year basis. Have to look at the next 5 years out at least to u… https://t.co/00NUa1kHho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeufelTitan09 @Alen__1991 @RapSheet At least we haven’t lost to the same team 3x in one year. Oh yeah we have not… https://t.co/WoguT62sGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DecadentDefiant @harriet48252998 @TheSWPrincess @tommyxtopher @SenFeinstein Because Diane Feinstein has been doing nothing for 30 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkRuffalo Hey Loser stop praising that MOON CRICKET, he's a fucking loser who was a nobody before he became A Ja… https://t.co/U4SCAYhYWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my treasure! #HikeitBabyUtahCounty #HikeandPlay #highlandglenpark #Dragon #kidlife #momlife #rainbowbaby… https://t.co/AdmVdcET2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@homelaber @GreggRobertson5 @vExpertPRO Hmm - I don’t recall ever saying that. It sounds like something Val would say 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbendery This is their pattern. Approve unqualified nominees, the big donors will pay for their think tank courses… https://t.co/lLZVdOO8pd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lurch98Robert @SenTedCruz @realDonaldTrump @HoustonChron It’s called capitalism. If it’s nationalized oil companie… https://t.co/0hs6mhK5WL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJr definitely cool to see your dad loved and recognized by all. @elitomac tribute helmet last night at Daytona… https://t.co/74YKSup1jf]]></document><document><![CDATA[2:35 3P | Riverdale with a 7-0 run over the last minute and they run their lead up to 45-32 over Arlington. Alasia… https://t.co/9cMQIkDxZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@francismmaxwell @Kaepernick7 Bad businessmen get my https://t.co/QufWFcOaMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalkBikeTampa is this how you felt after Amsterdam too a few summers ago too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course, the smart money remains bet on Kenney. We've had Democratic mayors since 1952.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aurum_mty Tú crees que Rusia y China traen mejores intenciones que USA? No me digas que Venezuela está prosperando… https://t.co/RuOENFPfZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willasmith38 @RiskyLiberal @RepMarkMeadows Like any good businessman he paid off the democratic politicians]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Somewhere, oh somewhere, there’s a Law against what this tree swinger says. Sedition? Why isn’t it e… https://t.co/2NYeItP0AU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day in Paradise! #Work #EarlyMorning #Ford #Focus #RS #NitrousBlue #AWD #ParkingLot @ Sherman Oaks, Califor… https://t.co/XhfeYpZFKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tobias47Rieper @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/ArCQUZIr9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODD WILSON COVER SONGS - YouTube https://t.co/HAZukh6QPo @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Believe It" https://t.co/bDxVkdIjRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IslandersGolf CONGRATULATIONS Autumn!! Great job! Keep up the good work!! 🌊🤙⛳️🥇]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also if you are the first person in your family to pass down your name you become “Senior” but like do u have to ch… https://t.co/yj6AZVodmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonpurser Men, don’t do this. Don’t. Ever. Women are not bets. Women are to be loved and respected and treated… https://t.co/OA4tuVziCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in for Pete let’s go we need leadershipfrom people who will be around for the consequences of their actions #PeteForAmerica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthemYour - Loot had been fine, got a Legendary and a ton of MWs on "Hard" and GM1 from quickplay and Legendary c… https://t.co/sAzxf7QyiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[in preschool during recess i saw a kid in the sandbox building a sand castle so i walked up and stomped on it. and… https://t.co/6Qnek15yLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stupid, arrogant immigrants need to learn American history before spouting bullshit   "A Florida boy was arrested a… https://t.co/ZkaJLX5Mjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@houstonpolice Thanks, HPD....keep the info flowing! We the traffic-burdened public appreciate this morsel of info!… https://t.co/W4bMAp0fHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepLaMalfa Hey Dougie, I see you're the ONLY California representative to vote AGAINST the House resolution condem… https://t.co/0PSQZBV6fL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaBSounds @GovRaimondo We have since added a tax on summer rentals. That money would have been more than enough t… https://t.co/0gaL7X9GnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My exciting day "fixing" cumulative records folders between student appointments... "after" photo to follow... @ Sa… https://t.co/vgGt7nqouy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier @MikeJohnson2025 That's why @FoxNews will not exist in another 3 yrs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moments before execution, Texas killer tells witnesses, 'That'll be $5'  https://t.co/rIqTRRScMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 Can it just be a really great pair of shoes that go with every outfit that don’t hurt my feet? 😬🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know the avs lost but like can we talk about Gabe Landeskog I like love him? https://t.co/R1VIZUZ65D]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UNCvsDuke biggest game of the year in College hoops, possibly in the last 10-15 years. It’s going to be hyped.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernice and I are becoming each other slowly lol. I am turning into her and she’s turning into me. You always need… https://t.co/06PnBekw7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickQuinnTV @komonews That truck belonged to one of my clients. I remember him sitting in my office showing me… https://t.co/t1lwPDRaB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm offering a free recovery coach/sobriety partnership for someone interested. No, I'm not a credentialed mental h… https://t.co/OC2e0AXOU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya los vi  en especial a las de familia misionera y misiones https://t.co/Z5gX2ywNYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wht a HUGE BUMMER!!! @donlemon  boy @JussieSmollett just got the plug pulled on his last 2 episodes?? Don’t worry t… https://t.co/tjYNkiIKQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful to @JohnTylerLions and @deeitude for sharing these great future leaders to help welcome and care for stude… https://t.co/7AAIaEkWkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse The simplest question that never gets answered by a southern strategy denialist: We all agree that the… https://t.co/2PwNYPSTZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[الله يحفظ الامارات ومعازيبها واهلها وكل من فيها من مال وحلال. @ Allen, Texas https://t.co/TfIyi7iCsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenhorRaposa Look deeply inside my home 3rd congressional district!!  Personally, that’s where I feel this state w… https://t.co/iXddhyWxFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Honky Tonk Man has been announced for the #WWEHOF. I'd like to remind everyone that Rick Martel has yet to be i… https://t.co/wFjmiwUQja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USAttyHuber @doj Do You believe the timing is coincidence Q sent Me #WWG1WGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JewishWorker @LeftistWriter I’ve watched the whole video. She’s doesn’t seem like a very nice lady.   Anything beyond that is manipulation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go listen to Morgan Wallen’s cover of cover me up, you won’t be sorry 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[CBB  Record 111 - 66 With a split yesterday were going with 4 plays Penn St -1.5, FL +1, Utep -1.5  Tulane +8… https://t.co/UCL9cx9Jsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewrunsalot @RustBeltRunning @impactrunning I’m sure he has a reasonable explanation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge congratulations to Shawn Oakman, we need to focus on False accusations just as much as real sexual assault. Th… https://t.co/Tn4RT1zQqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soon the idea of wanting to live in California is going to be considered a mental illness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you got that Q-Tip in your ear and you turn it just right and your knees buckle... mmmm https://t.co/jxymF4pM7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[People slam her but she seams the norm for Congress Left or Right...she just gets so much more press. Venezuelans d… https://t.co/6qf28mJvC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everadiva I felt the same way about 5 months ago. We had too many instances in our neighborhood where people are… https://t.co/UjaluuoHAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @DisneyFoodBlog for all the amazing tips. We did our tour of Epcot now we are waiting to try The Hollywood Brown Derby lounge!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The view from behind the mic in Jupiter! @MetsBooth @WayneRandazzo @wcbs880 #Mets https://t.co/jOZTs61B0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[richest ppl in the world really be wearing button downs and slacks lookin too clean]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world is Better with you in it. - On the Walls of United World College-USA. @Africarisingorg @NdabaMandela… https://t.co/lf9vS5Iy2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the past decade, I’ve become more focused on my journey, which has helped me in my everyday practices which ha… https://t.co/7U5MY468UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valeryyanez_ 😂😂, I’m actually kinda “tall” for a Mexican or so I’ve heard]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ramneekxx3 I get the Powerpuff Girls mixed up all the time https://t.co/JEEOKTr6qH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed the heck out of watching seniors @a_lee1012, @_kj_17 and Tayshaun Bradley play basketball for Glasgow throu… https://t.co/3qXdWFchqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn't see this coming.  Turnitin, the software company that allows teachers to check whether papers submitted by s… https://t.co/hJbARzqGeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[So i see that apparently it don't matter how much sleep I get once my alarm goes off I still want to throw my phone across the room]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes he is bringing shame and potential economic disaster to my great state...and then he wants the taxpayers to pay… https://t.co/bCCgq7MPa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuicedUpK9 Enjoy your visit young man!  Just know that #DawgNation would love to see you sport the 🔴⚫️ #BetweenTheHedges]]></document><document><![CDATA[The underlying problems of persistent and expanding consumption patterns, wants far exceeding real needs, were not… https://t.co/HnaZC4NFqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RupiOrReal  i was going to call you but i didn't know your number only your twitter handle odd for lovers-- i cried]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoreniaValles @CelidaLopezc @alfrgs @HermosilloGob @JuntosAguilar @DiputadosMorena Saludos Lorenia un abrazo a Alfredo también]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VOL_de_MORE @JonRothstein Idk if that’s sarcasm or not but i think that’s an incredible team and i can’t wait for… https://t.co/5Uj3iCfbV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss @_ElleJohnson The White RACE BLONDES👑Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UN… https://t.co/Abx2cmsxAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[no i deff dont want the brain surgeon boutta cut me open to be blitzed on some gas. i want his full undivided profe… https://t.co/nib36lTGT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn she’s so hot 😍😍😍. Screw this PG-13 horror movie. https://t.co/DbiKZhY1cN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m leaning more towards Scorbunny, but Grookey is also appealing to me https://t.co/RnVc5BJBbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[princess_kenda11’s twin sister Katana was back in town Saturday so I took her to @warwick_la and showed her how we… https://t.co/pVPyvlhit8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NozomiNeko @WritingRobot @jjulienauthor @jmsullivanbooks Welcome to the Jungle or I feel pretty.  Kind of a tie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SacBee_JoeD @SSchust15 @2nQue @CIFState @Golden1Center A popular theory has been posed where SoCal has pitted them… https://t.co/dqtaUwX75m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reservations are open for Passover this year. April 19-20. Seder catering in restaurant or for pick up and limited… https://t.co/S7aXocyexU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao dawg these white folk next to us really bout to build a wall and get us outta here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CREWcrew @realDonaldTrump @JohnCornyn Socialism for the few, the wealthy, the GOP-connected rich folks.  Hurry Nat… https://t.co/9SsCq7rJZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss you so much. I love you more than you will ever know. 💙 https://t.co/HcR7f8R4df]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is breaking news... Might need a special Sunday section to get to the bottom of this...]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I can tolerate being left on delivered or read the you really are special bc that a pet peeve of mine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker Feeds upon criminals too.  Why don’t you concentrate on the true problems of the inner city?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m Chris Ward and I approve this message. Btw the casts are 🔥 🙂 @unrelatl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitch_Pink I’ll.... just..... leave this here...: https://t.co/5il7WOpo4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an impeachable offense. The House Judiciary Committee should immediately subpoena Cohn and Kelly to testify… https://t.co/C44Ihz77Jg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @SnoopDogg I’ll pay you $10 for your tickets, never been to a game lol #Lakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jason_eist Jason you are an amazing mentor to these kids - Bullis is so lucky to have you!!! 💪🙏👍💯❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need to just invest in a complete software program to do photo edits but in the mean time here is a new on… https://t.co/0QG6nA88HE]]></document></documents></author>