<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I live in a desert to absolutely not experience 40 degrees for this many days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHELAVSTAN Waiting patiently basta ALDUB.   #ALDUB189thWeeksary  #ALDUBxDGArtistTambayan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @AOC @errollouis But our congresswoman gets testy if anyone says same to her? Classy! Build the wall now @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASimplePatriot She has horrible taste. Ugh, it is ugly. Probably was expensive too, on our dime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX  I’m sad it’s over already, it went too fast. Great show👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davenewworld_ @FranncescaRobi1 @Cruellaisdevine @Doramary @ShannonRitenour @LibsInAmerica @parkse @nyc_erik… https://t.co/M6PdgPxtBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJudgeLynn My mama taught me long ago what words were NOT acceptable and that was at the top of the list. And i… https://t.co/CySmht2ihh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me get this straight; this guy replied back fast, asks me genuine questions about me/my life/interests, doesn’t… https://t.co/AXuUgysIDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[During weekend Ilhan-Omar was doing her I hate Israel thing attacking Jewish Members of her own party on Twitter wh… https://t.co/8EXvM4aucq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindsReichardt Not my XPS with all of my footage on it so thats good 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLEASE KEEP AN OPEN MIND WE ARE SO CLOSED MINDED TO LOGIC AND REASONING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emackeycreates I feel like by saving your back  have saved your life and now I have a G-d complex. Safe travels Mackey!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adi's parents continue her fight for justice https://t.co/SaKy6xHyOp via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dapper_Phil They are dealing with food contamination, and niggas fighting - plus the dorms being half burnt down w… https://t.co/UnlFiUyqC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nobbel87 I'm loving BFA! I thought I was starting to feel a lull right before 8.1, but the latest content has real… https://t.co/HhkC2VjNg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALWAYS good to see one of my boys! Good Luck! GOOO DAWGS!! #teamspencer #ugamensgolf @ Dunes Golf &amp; Beach Club https://t.co/QI4OhS3EMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to this ignorant delusional idiot he just proved our point a wall isn’t needed produce comes from legal port… https://t.co/59rbP7RxZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop the fall makeup 😭 I need a tan! #mac #MACCosmetics #mua #texasgirl https://t.co/NPCemsxcA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @TWITMO_INMATE @cindy_nurse @SickOfTheSwamp @DeplorableJuJuV @winstonCovfefe @mymynags @PauWitkowski… https://t.co/gqUdRm0Gxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[❄️ "Success is where preparation and opportunity meet." 🤑  Meet the teen who made $35K in 4 days plowing snow durin… https://t.co/37pxi1yFv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity The Muslims have some taken over our Democrat party. Thank you Obama]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for Tabbies to come back to school! @LindseyElem https://t.co/aACCYYahma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bagshotrow @SybilleAbed @rozie2travel @amgilstrap1964 @MotherJones That answer really makes no sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElbaklySami @TereOrt51687394 @Viviane6677 @SimySemsem @PucciaPatrizia @enriqueiglesias @mich_onelove @janaplauen… https://t.co/NcdoQsRktx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wholesale Womens Dress Manufacturers &amp; Suppliers in USA, Australia, Canada https://t.co/MZ5a63xCOf #wholesale… https://t.co/LEzEGXblA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My go-to note taking strategy is to type up my notes on my laptop so I can print them out before an exam to highlig… https://t.co/eRbKcbDHPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rave review in Hi! Drama last show is Sun 1:50 p tix https://t.co/GCcIovaREW @ Kraine Theater https://t.co/s4L4ASqYhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy leyendo un tweet, escuchando la voz de la persona. Hablando su discurso y yo en atenta.🙄 jajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Again please take time to find out the facts, your a bit off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMightyV24 @TMoephulusi Also me :-). Grew up rural poor so I have seen poor, middle and upper class. The poor wo… https://t.co/ilIEAMUbzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s joining me? International Women’s Day 2019: Creating Gender Balance In The Biological Sciences https://t.co/0bQVlPm74I]]></document><document><![CDATA[#todayatJE On 2/13/19 Ms Lewis’s 4th grade performed a Valentine’s Day Readers Theater for Mrs. Doyle’s Kindergarte… https://t.co/UftuCyKiL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve done my part to contribute to $ success of NBA All Star weekend. Dinner in uptown Friday and SouthPark shoppin… https://t.co/HJ7cTD12Vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday night shenanigans with @emiliebernard #outandabout #fridaynight #singleandfabulous @ Darling https://t.co/eiuTzc0BlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessmarsh83 Fans pleaded for #Morcia 2 happen 4 years. Instead we got Morgan and Savannah Hayes forced down our th… https://t.co/HWu0z5Rl0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out our new designs. #denver #colorado #denvercolorado #coloradolife #coloradoliving #coloradolove… https://t.co/irP2Wl4oVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southernwayjim Jim, that is fantastic. Can you tell me how South Sarasota Republican Club gave those away? Members… https://t.co/6SJq7lHeRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Strandjunker @letat_lechat Why is she still in jail? Is their entire judicial system filled with rednecks? Where are the protesters?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rick Gates Gave Mueller ‘New Evidence’ That May Be Favorable To Paul Manafort – Talking Points Memo #SmartNews  https://t.co/1HqEsbheIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OUDaily Inclusivity Retreat™️: 1. Exclusive clubs fleeing meaningful acknowledgement of their key role in upholdin… https://t.co/FoYzImMxMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say this time and time again, segregation wasn’t that long ago. Green books were still published in the mid sixti… https://t.co/JmShEZG6LO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smith just appeared in court. He would like to address the court, his attorney, Stephen Funk, said. @ThePressofAC https://t.co/WwkuaNulYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach Bracy says Thank You!! Last night was all about Love. We knew our girls would need some extra special love an… https://t.co/DjHxM6MYEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ice skating at the Wharf. The last chance before our neighborhood rink closes for the season. #wharfdc… https://t.co/SpItvKmb2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewgurza @MrEugeneGrant Can I ask what the tattoo is a reference to?  I like the color shading on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 10th 2019- I attended the the #Unicorn phresh off the runway fashion show looking for some diverse content… https://t.co/kPMIC9XmJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys I was just remembering the time that I went to butt fuck Pensilvania for a video game convention to meet s… https://t.co/YhUycwtoSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The PlayStation Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below… https://t.co/8wiR8ec51q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reklisss Yolo murder on my mind was a hit, maybe you can make a song after]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachMollet @EdKrassen I will repeat: stop tweeting your ignorance.  Keep it to yourself.  If your want to stifel… https://t.co/TMZyofah3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s hard to believe we are already halfway through the 3rd quarter! The struggle can be real some days but we have… https://t.co/dJqlF0qbdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s dance to @IbibioSound - your free #SOTD @TheCurrent: https://t.co/nMaSlWhaTL https://t.co/mT0bJPBInM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un día estas en shorts-calzón disfrutando la vida y mañana la mínima de temperatura serán 4C. Que pedo Mty como tienes esa habilidad ??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is joking about Kraft. I'm sickened and appalled and disgusted to think anyone would make a joke about this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me tee-hee. Cause and Effect activity with "A Bad Case of Stripes." Posted on 2nd grade blog, but... https://t.co/T7wd3VsSq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have mulled it over... and Ellen Pompeo did not enjoy that kiss after Meredith told Deluca's they had rules. Like… https://t.co/Hpg0zxHpC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to be with someone who will participate in nerf gun wars with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just clicked and helped for free at The Alzheimer's Site https://t.co/f7xgJ0FkdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 4 year old nephew was in that airport today. Reports say the man had a grenade. What in the fuck. Massive Panic… https://t.co/g9EYPjM599]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching Syllable Division.  Although rule #3 makes me laugh.  "Pumpkin" is the best example... https://t.co/n3HJ2O5Llk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late Post: I was thankful to celebrate a wonder Black History Program with Samoset El @Manateeschools. Student essa… https://t.co/36PCHwTrNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My special sauce was helping a woman realize she’s valuable and amazing AS SHE APPEARS TODAY @susanhyatt… https://t.co/WLWymdTk3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiTotaton Aun no llegas Haina linda, pero te dejo saludos de buen día y feliz viernes. Voy a trabajar un poquito.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With hopes you’re on the other side talking to me too oh but who, who sits alone talking to the moon? 🌚🎶 #BrunoMars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkhtx @HillaryClinton @SuMoh7 @GOP @realDonaldTrump Does it hurt to be that stupid?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“AI frees people to be more human” @chrishoward88 #GartnerCIO #Keynote #ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[it is 58 degrees and humid as hell you do not need a down jacket rn wyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch BULL SHIT THEY HAVE NO RIGHT IN OUR COUNTRY.  TELL THEM DONALD TRUMP!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaywonk Once the world addresses misogynoir and anti-Blackness in this conversation, things might change. Hope so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Quit going to Mar a Lago. 4 of your trips would cover the war games cost and be better for the country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been super light headed and dizzy the last hour. Plus I’m super tired. I need a nap or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MargaretJosephs is this not the creepiest thing you have ever seen??? I don’t know if we should be worried for HIM… https://t.co/BJDOPN4YDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating the time change with 10 cups of coffee. Lol!  Being an international band manager the time change in th… https://t.co/myicKtFJp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarciaMentor @MrVaudrey @dhabecker @alicekeeler @robertkaplinsky @jcorippo @KevinMonsma @mavenofmath Choice and “f… https://t.co/XPQiBQ11pk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daniel1Teach Lucas told me he wants to do a project about “disability people.”  He wants to, “write a grant to the… https://t.co/xi0XBZq6Wa]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's raining so hard I'm thinking about calling an Uber to take me to the car in my work parking lot. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized I'm still wearing my magic band. I guess that means I'm still on vacation, right? Please?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life! There’s dog hair &amp; drool EVERYWHERE. #bloodhound #plotthound #labschnauzermix #BIGlapdogs… https://t.co/sXLtcmz0d9]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just saw someone call the n word a “gamer word” https://t.co/43Rp7w6amt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPintsylvania Hey there!  This ships to Pittsburgh this week, so it hasn’t reached the PA market just yet:).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah my classic awkward picture. Love you ash glad you’re in my life 😍🤒🥰🥵🤟🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marine biodiversity is crucial for human life, providing us with food, jobs and enjoyment. @SylviaEarle,… https://t.co/1XFUy80YfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think I’m going to watch the entire “Metal Gear Solid” trilogy on YouTube instead of taking a well-needed na… https://t.co/j7y7VLEd9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FranncescaRobi1 @electroboyusa @saltymom51 @Billy_Ray28 @TeaSippingBarb @tizzywoman @realdebfarmer @Spartan2dn… https://t.co/Bg46qN9uMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[summoning circle, hope this works:                         🕯               🕯              🕯         🕯… https://t.co/aGU0yJdk8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUST SEE @ArianaGrande in Portland, even if I have to go alone! I’ve spent too much time learning all her lyrics to… https://t.co/XQbVo6uc1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Querido Jumex: Mejor regala fondos de pantalla de Erik Rubín. Gracias 😊.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chocolate and ear buds. 🍫👂  Samsung knows how to swag bag. #SansungEvent #Unpacked2019 https://t.co/E6ipGLVmtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katewbauer @ibddoctor @nytimes Great question. I’m not an NIH administrator so hard to say which would best increa… https://t.co/BHoTJBaCEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s so freakin cute when @BlueMoonGoon88 looks over at me &amp; sees Jay laying all over me &amp; gets mad/jealous that it’s not him 😂💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[They should want to speak with me, I pay for five drivers and three of them are teenagers who need a lift all the t… https://t.co/Bl1BAE3Vrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DotTaint @SecondLady @VP Sorry that is exactly what gov Northam said that is twisted make them comfortable and the… https://t.co/aXePKT3Ax6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InterfaceInc #sustainability #rockstars #climatetakeback #carbonneutral Great lunch update today! #carpettile… https://t.co/2YChKEzXNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving these sexy satin jogger! #is #want #fashion #ontrend #jogger #caminyc #satinblack #blogger #sexy… https://t.co/Kp8UF4eKM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never imagined I would become obsessed with #marblecollecting @ Chandler, Arizona https://t.co/tdNP3llcj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyBentli Out now! @HomeFreeGuys bring us a moody video for a cover of a wistful country classic ...… https://t.co/KypOHHcP1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[“That dude so stupid you could punch him in the head and he would be just as stupid..”]]></document><document><![CDATA[fuck you PETA. Steve Irwin and his family are the real heroes in wildlife conservation and you are insufferable, an… https://t.co/cgK8CJMj5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes he is a liar remember what he lied about? Oh yes! He lied about the crimes you two committed together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine The Bronx bartender has a very high opinion of herself! 🍸🍸🍸]]></document></documents></author>