<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Genius wedding amazingness!  #pianist #piano #pianistterranea #weddingmusic #pianistaweddings #musicianforhire… https://t.co/CIhynxFAOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔴 YT: CHINA OWNS CALIF THAT'S WHY THE FIRES ARE HAPPENING❗ 🔴 https://t.co/99WRupHgSv YT: NOT GOOD❗ CHINA IS PREPPIN… https://t.co/p48tU8vKbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[0700 end of watch, everyone goes home, safe.   Here’s to my million dreams 👍🙏 @ DFD Company 15 https://t.co/9qTeaA0kH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darrell_Clarke 76% of those surveyed were in favor of the JFK bike lanes. You have the chance to make them permane… https://t.co/bVWV7Uqiwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Is ground you REALLY wish to tread, Mr. President? I just want to make sure you're clear about wha… https://t.co/2mcW8LuO2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning tavolampls @ Minneapolis, Minnesota https://t.co/vOunEVx3s6]]></document><document><![CDATA[They take an oath to defend the constitution against all foes foreign and DOMESTIC. they were doing their jobs Lind… https://t.co/WQPW3GAgVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[What y’all are doing to the English language is beyond deplorable. The word is “I’m “]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out at Robust Coffee Lounge Bar (@robustcoffee) in Woodlawn South Side Chicago.  #Graeginator #Sega… https://t.co/Yw16hNXTsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida Eels Elite continue with offensive attack with 3 more goals in the 3rd period to raise their lead Final 7-2… https://t.co/yTo0fYayj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vQBHNjlhzc  As the war dragged on, soldiers caught #malingering were hanged for cowardice.   “It drain… https://t.co/5oBhVCrCsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could totally see John Middleton doing 400 Mill for Bryce. His reputation in the city is at stake]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCLA This has creepy written all over it thet could sue for a billion and get it. I would]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to have @martinwaxman, APR, MCM presenting to my 4th year @StoryArtsCentre Bachelor of PR Management stude… https://t.co/ciJDxowMZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[spent the weekend diving deep into @MarenMorris new album #GIRL with @ciaramichelle_2. As far as country pop is con… https://t.co/qDbFvEWsNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Third night in a row with the $2 bill as a dream catcher. Konked out after just 5 minutes. Half credit to the elect… https://t.co/WkbqvJ0fWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[PG on officiating — It’s just got to be called right.” added —“There’s nothing we can do, I’m going to lose money o… https://t.co/kssCq5v4ry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillGRinehart @PipeClubOTR I have no idea what that gif is from nor why it is important. https://t.co/QL8RsvmJKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crysiii_17 I whipped my wax pen out in class thinking it’s a pencil🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#laneyanne and I been scootin’ today #family #work @ The Boxyard https://t.co/XOi9yLY9Zk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess that means i can tweet what i want and not get a phone call about it👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GUnit_81 Greg-will miss your in depth Saturday podcast. Hard drive cssh sucks. But no apologies needed. Your daily… https://t.co/l0AGbqz1Kk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xenos_RIFS @RandyHu87093758 @thecjpearson @AOC Happy ,, the point is it is worthy of reparations , also no one is… https://t.co/4WHm5dtPMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bz- how much would that be? C- over a thousand dollars Bz-  what else could do it? C- no one sane will walk up to m… https://t.co/RNd5OkXSOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[HONORED to let Healthcare providers know that my Harvard online Lifestyle Medicine CME course, “Nutrition and the M… https://t.co/ZDemVuV4PL]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6MY6HCROIz Internet Explorer Help is effective and reliable to connect with 1-855-479-3999… https://t.co/xEXnPUf98d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @magnetdoctor122 @realDonaldTrump Putin's pet POTUS, an aggressive-ignorant limelight-addicted suicidal ana… https://t.co/4GPRgkXSlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanMcMullin There are more than a few GOP MoC defending POTUS out of Party loyalty. But, don’t you think that man… https://t.co/yx3EkPUngQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KE4611 @MikeLaBelle @eMLS @NewYorkRedBulls https://t.co/iFolXF6YxT at 7pm ET (6pm CT)]]></document><document><![CDATA[One last pic for today-tonight during soccer practice. @ Arcadia, California https://t.co/8ettYtZR71]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks man. It’s like a live sports game. It gives me a thrill. Appreciate you checking in and the support also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedskinsRant @RedskinsRD21 Second and subsequent year hits get high though. https://t.co/n5kaBP2jru]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obj hey Odell, watch leaving Neverland, you'll be proud to have that M.Jax tattoo . Goofball https://t.co/2V1ztdsqTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j0seph_anthony Sometimes I post immediately(usually drunk) or wait months lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Hello, Big Bill says back to school for you to learn finance! Did you graduate with finance degree? Was it Bos… https://t.co/cLeHH3m4J4]]></document><document><![CDATA[California wastes most of its rainwater, which simply goes down the drain - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/hzaw94BCXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CJSprigman That must be a mistake I thought we were the greatest country on Earth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that I’m back on IG and I guess this applies to twitter too: I like pictures because I like the picture not bec… https://t.co/2yQGKZpMVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Internet: a massive repository of knowledge. And knowledge is power. So let's keep that well away from the pleb… https://t.co/rZrHuI83VU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect lighting day. 🌅❤️ Rattlesnake Canyon. #arizona #rattlesnakecanyon #adventure #naturephotography… https://t.co/PBHwYd2leK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Listen2Lena @krist3n_xO Start the day with buffet breakfast but once in awhile will have room service Mid day just… https://t.co/Im5mktTrA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[12 years ago this moment my first born daughter was born ... incredible how fast they grow up ... she’s a very smar… https://t.co/W1pXiganDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[SMOKE EM IF YOU GOT EM, a song by Koss on Spotify https://t.co/FvQ5zya5Fo @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Believe… https://t.co/7UyQC11lb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[God will give you a purpose that is not based on your time, talents, and treasures, but based on His!… https://t.co/1W5Nr0nLrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @HouseGOP  Very disappointed in the bills to support the presidents border security… https://t.co/ubAUJFa693]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jazminfinn Currently working on it. I just don’t like spending 20+ minutes to make myself look presentable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyBirch Sometimes it's a word at a time for me, clearly your literary skills are finely honed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulianFMartinez @IvanDuque Y el video completo?.... como va ver el contexto.... seamos serios]]></document><document><![CDATA[encouraging strip tease and aftercare: cum together is being recommended to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoBoe92 @AndyCarlsonShow A restructure makes total sense they have all the leverage, but for the “cut Griffen “ cr… https://t.co/X9NXCBXsmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the long journey to #5G #orchestration #automation  See where the #distributedcloud expands to the edge a… https://t.co/9XY0BVXdTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kkkevin47 @Rghoe they still got the high school mentality too, they lazy as fuck and don't wanna do anything lmao… https://t.co/LH3wQ97wzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[・・・ Oh yeah IT’S ON! #cbgBlockbuster begins This Sunday in #lakeworth    10a / 11:30a @ Church by the Glades Lake W… https://t.co/5uBJuzUPPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of last nights cocktail soiree for thirty! . . . . . #carlosaystable #onthetable #privatechef #cocktail… https://t.co/IY8nRxGo9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright west coast. Enough waiting around. Turn the sun on so I can watch @TigerWoods @GCTigerTracker let’s goooo @genesisopen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@watspn1013 It’s all FAKE!  Jussie helped the shows ratings. Every bit of this is made up!  They’re not going to pu… https://t.co/MZ99akAP8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abusados... Cuando anden contratando @gastelumg76 @salejandroc10 🙈🙈🙈 https://t.co/DaSOeZyKDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo, thanks for helping to spread my demonetization stories! It seems to get more confusing by the day, but I’m not… https://t.co/cm395qeFHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Malia Obama knows she loves a good core group of snitching White friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rob_O_1977 @UMichFootball @Chase_Winovich Do you think he survives the first 32?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game of Thrones, heavy naps, and pho delivery to get over this cold and fever. 😷]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Fitness Family. Who wanna crush some Arms with me this morning?😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[With @fullerhouse about to go into production on its final season here are two posts I wrote in 2011 on FACEBOOK th… https://t.co/AZiBLsRB3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UberFacts All my life, I have never found a dime. But, lots of pennies. GEE, "$950K." https://t.co/XJYE9SSJlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanMartini1 Last Jedi was good and solo was decent. The only true piles of crap in the star wars universe are lots… https://t.co/znJRDRgwOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwing my hat in with this is easy. Totally there already. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarEnergy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gingerbums @Sphere3524 I sound like a gay New York actor and right now one with a bad cold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve lived dangerously for years by not turning on the light when I go downstairs for my nightly routine of water.… https://t.co/Zmvm8uTZyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The economy is doing well, growing steadily since 1980. So why are so many people dissatisfied? One simple chart te… https://t.co/myrIhE4xeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisatoluna @MikeFromMA @ikkegoemikke @The1Hamp @Cineluctable @Moviesontheway @cam_junge History *]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Look, Trump is already flattering his next employer. I hope he gets hired soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/goFC4Ay8Sy @DDayCobra, an interesting review of our least favorite Captain!  Let me know what you think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had a nice conversation with former number 1 pick of the 2013 nba draft- who is widely considered the biggest… https://t.co/blfVFIor97]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re a fool if you think slaves were eating fried chicken, Mac and cheese, and yams. So many African Americans do… https://t.co/G73JRHhR5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[another thing i need to get back on top of is getting back into skating vert so when it comes down to it im fully r… https://t.co/JBbSo4TC3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuffaloSabres @AcademyOfHockey How can I become a Coach for the Academy of Hockey?]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW JOEY DIXON BEAT "MADE IN COMPTON" #PRODUCERLIFE #FLGANG #MPC #FLSTUDIO #NEWYORK #LOSANGELES #MIAMI #ANTHEM… https://t.co/tzT3sS0A3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hellgate shocks the Double A and beats Helena 54-50!  They will face the winner of Capital vs Glacier. Helena faces… https://t.co/5lZx8nifRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke Perry hospitalized after suffering a 'massive stroke,' according to reports https://t.co/mRjyzwzYD5 via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CNN ACOSTA-Ask Democrats--why they want to Impeach Trump-When He has Accomplished --What "No" President has--Like… https://t.co/LU3f4YThFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barracuda_Bella @RealMAGASteve First of all how is she even allowed to serve being a full blown Muslim?  Second di… https://t.co/zvnpgUkBfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe in doing whatever makes you happy and freedom of speech. But this tik tok shit really needs to go like now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ccs Comfort inn New York Department of Homeless services HRA US government Justice Department federal bureau of pri… https://t.co/eTXzV8iiZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LevyDavidC 100% agree. Let’s change all the one-way streets to two-way while we’re at it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luxury and Sustainability: How Pininfarina Is Cracking the Code | Jing Daily https://t.co/4ntTyYrvS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSPhilly Wow! Wouldn’t it be great if NBC Sports Philadelphia had an hour show every weekday at 5 pm where we co… https://t.co/KSxoYRqEUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[How the regulations in #TR68 fuelled Singapore’s autonomous vehicle agenda. @SoumikRoy overview. https://t.co/W7DSY7wZVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeymourZoe Company politics are frustrating for sure. Tough to excel when you feel like it’s not your ability hold… https://t.co/mCJF77uZUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello @realDonaldTrump why do you avoid me? Are you scared of the truth? Are you scared to be the laughingstock of the world??? Do ya????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson Tells Historian To 'Go F**k' Himself In Spiked Fox News Interview   https://t.co/v5fLp6pB0J via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[You really don’t read history books don’t you. Why don’t you try telling me What Joseph Stalin’s Political leanings… https://t.co/IfOkfQdnNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 Why not. The communists and their minions in both political parties have been hell-bent on lowering the… https://t.co/mCioEeLYh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Stanly boys have won 3 road games as 21 seed. Tough to do. People finding out how good Bryson Childress reall… https://t.co/VkE1o5mWKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoBolts He wants to sign there after the way they treated Shipachyov last year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help the @BostonKMen K ALS by supporting researchers searching for a cure! These shirts and hats are a good look an… https://t.co/kaxVQIVaCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ragley @cassielcope I’ll add to this. You are also a European import. You were also raised a Yankee. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KJoyGFM @MKGenest I started watching it last year from season one. I was in denial before a friend at work told me… https://t.co/rLCiqBveZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Murphy The #Boxer 🦴🐕Says 24°⛅️ good morning all☕️ and it’s supposed to snow 💩🤦‍♂️tomorrow🤢🥶🇺🇸 https://t.co/r5iUXxUymq]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s not Boyds PK to take cmon now! Oso, Bradley.... not the guy who’s been here for 15 minutes. Alas, we move on... lots of game left]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday!! ✝️ “Faith is the realization of what is hoped for and evidence of things not seen. But without fai… https://t.co/3p3e7EGTKX]]></document></documents></author>