<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe I rear ended a man. Dented his car.  No damage to mine. I was in a rough time he knew nothing about.… https://t.co/TE2E0hGzVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @nkcstricia @missb911 @Katie_Lawson3 to post the covers of 7 books I ❤️. No explanat… https://t.co/6HfI6TVQH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then you will walk on your way securely, and your foot will not stumble. https://t.co/rCFgzCbfqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mean besides creating hate and racism wherever he goes? Hate crimes are on a rise for the last two years coincidenc… https://t.co/LFAsCqlDKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirkhawkins @TheRickChambers @courtneyfriel @cannonhartman @KTLA Definitely watching Y'all right now!! Great seeing you back, Kirk !!! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ces couleurs sont tellement douces 💕 @ Nassau Bahamas https://t.co/3BqL2kdb0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I care what you think about politics :) please reply with all your important opinions!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWENetwork I wish the WWE network would have a contest, for the people who subscribe to the WWE network, like mayb… https://t.co/KCliogm6Bb]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 4 years...   Halfway through fellowship definitely, maybe a family... At that time, like now, would not give a f… https://t.co/1yQvvR5UfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tygerlylly So that's an S a K and a J all next to each other so that's a no... https://t.co/CkqzQWMvd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Jenna_Marbles can you army camouflage your whole body and try to hide in your house from @juliensolomita and the dogs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at our upcoming lineup for @lapaulee “Off the Grid” tasting has me thinking “Off the Rails” might be a more… https://t.co/6RdQVSkyJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl said “happy birthday , fuck me in the ass” LMFAOOOOOO why’d I think of you @ogivonne lmfaoooooo 😭😭😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reunited with my girls Celebrating one day late 🥰#InternationalWomansDay2019 https://t.co/RrK65dTjZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[For personal reasons I will be diving deeper into a depression and sleep my life away]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite brain is coming up on @foxandfriends @cvpayne !  The voice of reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fkajack The amount of times I’ve liked and unliked this tweet just to see the star pop up is kinda ridiculous...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: at the airport. Slightly more sleepy but very much more excited]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the convicted lying conman Michael Cohen hearing. Even I can tell he's just telling the Committee whatever… https://t.co/5S8LejsJFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely. #StandWithTrudeau I won't be budged from a gov't who wants to do something about climate change, Indige… https://t.co/Qw7Mh08vGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliGehnLEX18 @KlineCelia @TUWBX @LEX18News Stick to lifting weights, bruh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dayo could not even recognize Julia stiles in a photo.   Tragic. Tragic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a Great Time w Family 🎰💰🍹  Tag: Mark, Jenny, Chris, Michelle, Debbie 💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halperry @ThisWeekABC @Jim_Jordan @GStephanopoulos He won't. For some reason, they've given him a pass. Those youn… https://t.co/KwB5hsc2UH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all. Tell me why I thought it was a good idea to do free weights AND HIIT with battle ropes. My arms are rubber w… https://t.co/uMQRRln0nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chocolateearper @DatelineNBCProd @MelanieScrofano @Kikipithecus @KdWool_11 Ha! Love ya too mom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADDcrafter Nice. I still wear saucony after all these years. I just need to run again... 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattLewisAuthor ALSO Richard tends to be blamed for EVERYTHING!! that’s crazy!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jancoferstevens @aldi You go to the grocery store?  What?  My family would starve if itw wasn't for grocery delivery! And pick up service!]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: the skin on the outside of my throat is hurting  southern: you mean your neck?  ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conference champion !!!! Rookie season keeps getting sweeter and sweeter🤪🤩 Next... NATIONALS 🐉 #TUTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay Hayward wasn’t the best city but so many famous people came from there damn we breed stars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wah?!  You lost by 3 million votes!  How many times does it take for you to get it through your thick head??  Oh, j… https://t.co/yX9nXBkTWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #JohnsCreek, GA job and click to apply: General Manager - https://t.co/Jt1rY5FhwU #IAmUltaBeauty]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY BABY IS HAVING A BABY 🤩🤩🤩🤩🤩🤩🤩🤩🤩 @kirsten_smith03 i cant wait to seeeee you as a mother you will do greatttt ily!! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's just this waiting game &amp; I don't know how to play It's enough of a fight staying alive anyway]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA https://t.co/YXPpBssu3L https://t.co/tM5xZKQw5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ValentinesDay2019 What every #RomanceWriter knows.... https://t.co/lqcAd3S3Rt via @peggy_jaeger How do you show yo… https://t.co/g5qsdp2Y0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChynaJoanLaurer It's about freaking time!! #DEGENERATIONX #wwe #raw #SDLive ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaddyDrax @RiskTravis @schuelkecorn @bmronn02 @NoDakTrav Most of the time they don't or they leave most of it. Fu… https://t.co/qvdHSgoTlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet there’s no concentration camps in China 🤣 people will post anything for a retweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jungkook_USA @BTS_twt Read this : he blocked me from everywhere, don't have access at profile his profile, I can't… https://t.co/bOofqzLFrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cute humans 😍❤️ love love love you TY!!! @trishayearwood @chanfrost2 @Katiemae1991 https://t.co/SxDlAu8GE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wanna go home and eat cold pizza and play sims and lay in bed and snuggle with my dog]]></document><document><![CDATA[EVANGELICALS THIS IS WHAT YOU UP HOLD TO OUR HEAVENLY FATHER? SELLING OUR AMERICAN SOUL FOR WHAT A NARCISSISTIC EVI… https://t.co/wNTsPuLkFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manure serves a purpose. Nothing this cheap bimbo does has ANY purpose. And she is the grande dame of capitalism—fu… https://t.co/5f8Zp8cde4]]></document><document><![CDATA[No hate in Long Island but you have to get out of it eventually to realize you’re fucking so lucky]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s okay for girls to show off their curves, but when I wanna show off my legs it’s a bad thing??? https://t.co/wj2Tvrab4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamVTV @suzanb1776 This is the one of the worst things I’ve ever heard of!  The person who shot his dog should be… https://t.co/N7a6kUrwJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacticalDogLive @K9Dasy @LivePDNation @OfficialLivePD Heartbreaking 💙🐶🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pilayscortez DEADASS OUR FACES WHEN WE SAW THIS SHIT HAPPEN AT ROSARITO LMAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biforyou2 anyways I’m out of this conversation. I can’t argue with someone who defends people like this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino The downside of more than doubling minimum wage from $7.25 per hour to $15.00 per hour.  People lose their jobs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I need this app so I can avoid giving my custom to such places]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book character day @Gwoodelem #violetbeauregarde #harrypotter #lucky https://t.co/AONIYnDCcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart @WhiteHouse Grab a clue Sarah. People don’t believe your FAKE press stories anymore. We’re sick and ti… https://t.co/zYcx92Ik7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upnext: Itchy red eyes, heart stopping sneezes and a stuffy nose. #OOTD #Pollen #ThankYouMotherNature]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally just wanna listen to @ParkerMcCollum  Friday night after this long week of losing my grandma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikaishii @TeaganMorrison This is the most “you guys” thing I’ve ever seen. Perfect. 👌👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[The man who hates and divorces his wife, says the LORD, the God of Israel, "does violence to the one he should pr… https://t.co/0OXp9QOFia]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was brought up to take being called white as an insult. Most children that come from immigrant families are taugh… https://t.co/6oKxbbMpyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geraldhampton @Kimwyattsart @TalbertSwan @Travon And believing liars means you are a liar too]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand how someone can say they love you , then break you down like if you’re nothing but a piece of  d… https://t.co/M93weWDHGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished filming this month’s online cooking class and I am currently savoring one of these amazing brownies.… https://t.co/Nea25BfygT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking pictures of the Mississippi River. #mississippiriver #river #nature #canont7i  #photography @ Wickliffe, Ken… https://t.co/1eN2LBa69E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk if any of y’all remember this commercial but I know every word and it was a mf BOP https://t.co/wosjLCnPO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CohenTestimony Its been very interesting, but majority of this info about @realDonaldTrump being a racist, conman,… https://t.co/CqMMae1zY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolekf1973 @GinaPustorino @Tina_Bradley27 @fee2360 @AthanasiaTrian1 @LiseNilsson2 @MakkOlga @NancySimonds1… https://t.co/Oaxy1gzaRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump i can not believe you're trying to call your former lawyer out on lies. You are the biggest liar on earth .]]></document><document><![CDATA[roses are red FeCl2•4H2O solution is neat Quick! Load the sample into the SQUID before the oxidation’s complete!  #AcademicValentines]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walked into work with a [🍩] on my desk like this https://t.co/A8JKvBq3Ez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ocorromon I definitely do! Though I don’t draw a map until after the rough draft is completed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tick season is coming.. I bought @nutiva #coconutbodyoil #lavender.  I could use it as a tick/ bug spray @THRIVEmkt… https://t.co/Jrh7qLMlPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see Legally Blonde Tonight: 7:30 PM Friday: 7:30 PM and Saturday: 7:30 PM at Washington Township High School!… https://t.co/MkfIYUi2Ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a friend I had in middle school and I can’t remember her name and that legit makes me super sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just enjoy the trip 😏 you don’t know when you would to wake up 😍💋 #sunday #lovely #miamistyle #instagood #venezuela… https://t.co/j3akyTjAWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please stop degrading fellow Christians, we are all in this together! We should be building each other up, not tearing each other down!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr So? I certainly hope a traitor like you isn’t going to start attacking a decent American. You’re go… https://t.co/IWUCIYyqoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torig217 omg so true u literally turn into such a brat about ur water when ur blacked!!!  like ok then be dead tom… https://t.co/ts1PoshbNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone’s playing scott joplin on the piano and now i just wanna play cooking mama https://t.co/OCfIJG2KL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Yes and they just migrate all down interstate 10. Columbus, Houston now New Orleans… https://t.co/t9hqhB7zeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @trumps_feed @Lagarde @LindseyGrahamSC @MorganOrtagus @IvankaTrump Go away you utter and complete fraud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elder_jodi   Hi Jodi.  Can you please follow me back?  I would really appreciate it.  Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosebud702 @andrerucker51 @machonejack @hey_butter @SarahGould_SA @terry313401 @delgeo1 @poppij @MarilynHallett… https://t.co/Oczr89nAjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Pathetic, so thirsty for any kind of attention... You'll get it, just hang on a little longer. Jail… https://t.co/Jzot82lADO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving that Knoxville Tennessee is a great showcase city for music and musicians, even @Wendys  Don't be bashful, l… https://t.co/5V1WevFH0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samhusseini I remember this creep well from the beginnings of Cold War 2.0 with the stuff he was trying to push on… https://t.co/SfYDO5vbWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Goodyear unveils Wingfoot Two airship in Akron | https://t.co/qLdxsNKJWm https://t.co/NMvq7D0SuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Memories pt2 2019 NCA TopGun OO5 @coopercontreras @ Dallas, Texas https://t.co/0HpyUhgViV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robsox04_robert @realTylerZed Very similar to the Morton Downy Jr TV aggressive talk host who pulled a similar PR… https://t.co/yvjXIvY0WX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @MarusaLaura I'm still trying to figure out what she did or said..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Cross every line to get to the truth One Exception the little kids, like Barron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rest in peace Norma perez.. you were an amazing family friend and you left us too soon.💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yourleoness Sammy said they’ve pushed cars out the way with the truck before😂💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobPeek1 @NancySinatra @BarackObama Thank you, Mr.President for everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@devawells @__MattzD Yes I agree. They should have let @TasiasWord do her thang by herself! She don’t need no help!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the Allstar game &amp; waiting for my Chinese food. Issa great Sunday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t slept for more than 4 hours the past 3 weeks. Been thuggin 🦍🦍🦍. Will I be burnt out for Spring Break? Stay tuned...... 🦍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMSImpact Will these talks be posted online or available to access after #StoryMovements2019 wraps up? Thx!   #storymovements]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande whistle tones are still giving me chilllllllsssssssss 🌬🌬🌬]]></document></documents></author>