<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Let’s see, of those who are married or in a stable relationship—-Who Has Been In Their Relationship/Marriage THE LO… https://t.co/MnpdPEM5nV]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we are preparing for landing at @dfwairport ... and I’m only about 40% of the way through ‘The Thank You Economy… https://t.co/1myZmUgl2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra USA is an embarrassment.  But not because of the efforts of POTUS.  It’s because the left is powerles… https://t.co/qEXAXJQ7lw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@55true4u @jhjulian1956 @gatewaypundit Nancy and Hillary are drinking the same kool aid.  If we can get Trump six m… https://t.co/KkyOzWBzO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LorettaKillian This not Nancy is it, b/c look like TRUMP shot her down in the middle of 5th Ave in DC. Hell Nancy… https://t.co/rOiFPqjyEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Collusion he says. No Collusion with Russia, No Collusion with #Putin #Trump repeats daily Day can't come soon… https://t.co/86x7PL9qiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mehdirhasan @MarkSZaidEsq @AJHeadtoHead @AJEnglish Can you train more U.S. political  journalists, please?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Don’t use a long open on YouTube. You have 3 seconds to convince someone to keep watching” @2HungryDogs #vidfest… https://t.co/SzFMxlRyhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sea Cow Milk Stout by @SaltWaterBrewer @ Len’s Seaside Bar At The Man Cave — https://t.co/MmuChD1nru]]></document><document><![CDATA[Está en Góndola...como cantante estuviera muerto de hambre. Que le de gracias a dios.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope Dealer Ricky Aiken Endorses Paula Ryan FULL HD https://t.co/vwyCb11I1u via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetingclip This guy should be banned from social media for his ignorant response.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Otto abs his family deserve better. @realDonaldTrump is a truly #Deplorable excuse for a man and a leader.… https://t.co/kuEmKxGRbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EeeJaye9 Haha! I hate that Twitter isn't always chronological. I'm glad it subsided, though. Have a great Sunday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes God will take you rock bottom to prove he is the rock at the bottom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBC10Boston @MattNBCBoston  Jr. Weather Spotter Michael measured ~9 inches of beautiful, white, heart attack induc… https://t.co/STWELEG9bY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part 3 of @RichardPF's 'The Mind of a Sommelier' series featuring #Boston area #wine #geeks. Meet Christopher Willi… https://t.co/54mck2Hmb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LunaLeso @Spiros209 @simonjetz @Amyperuana @neblaruz @alleosa @barrywyman2356 @marmelyr @ampomata @agustin_gut… https://t.co/0wcVUr0GSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_willco94 @insideyourfuego @GMA @21savage 20 years and no application for citizenship. Follow rules]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love METAL UP YOUR PODCAST - All Things Metallica | Episode 78 - Freeze 'Em All, let's play it! https://t.co/vacuI9g8sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PennyAllenCook @MIAA1888 All the missed free throws are giving my anxiety watching! Great game though. 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenaharper Do reprisal bands play gigs in retaliation for something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Living_Legend8 @thezakary Yea I know what you’re saying but I think it was different tbh, Holgs inherited a much b… https://t.co/fko6FMFxCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[As much as I love the #NBA, old man DOB just can’t get into #NBAAllStarWeekend. #DOBservation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrdavidchaney @amharvy Would kinda dig it at the moment since I REALLY miss you people.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Star Trek: Discovery review https://t.co/VZQAxEJkEx #StarTrek #StarTrekDiscovery #DISCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zypisfy @zapher134 @yourmumspants @Cern_lXXl @mikenedie @AprilLigeia @garym9999 @paulmpet1 @PrinceOfAtheism… https://t.co/rFYyyPIPxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se nos viene semana crucial en Venezuela, ruego que un manto de sensatez y patriotismo descienda sobre la tropa mil… https://t.co/Z4UvhRHw8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @GeorgeWBush  Stop sniping OUR President George. WE elected him because we are sick and tired of fake/pho… https://t.co/xsI4e9JYzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many ways to perk! New video up on the @Patreon page about how you can now gift your perks, or save them up in t… https://t.co/iRRUMqWuYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJ84 Sign me up. I could care less about fit this early in the rebuild, but I think it could work---def worth the risk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElTioMaxiMeza @donsarajevo @betorayas86 @aIex_doe Entonces si ganaba Tigres rayados descendía 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@medicalaxioms You mean like as a nocturnist covering floor patients? “Patient in 6143 has a HA and the day team di… https://t.co/AKh5TM43Z2]]></document><document><![CDATA[one day, imma get facial hair. it might be gray, but still 🤷🏾‍♂️ https://t.co/gFo5Tv1OAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KBAndersen 📣I have lamented this myself, and wished that we could have a parliamentary system that elects parties,… https://t.co/4te5g0q1bD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanSchachtel @vjeannek I don’t CAIR. Might as well get an endorsement from ISIS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryjduran @DanaPerino @JaniceDean Just saw Shannon Breem’s interview and don’t let anyone bring you down. Your pe… https://t.co/KFzQw5fKbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you actually try things out of your comfort zone and put yourself out there and it backfires on you... What’s the point of all this 🌎]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a clique full of shooters And I'm in your dreams Freddy Krueger https://t.co/Wmh8qxn1gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump I’m afraid you’re talking about Barack Obama the great traitor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to everyone that interacted with my post yesterday y'all rock ! 💯😎💯✌ https://t.co/dM4ilKmAyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosedixontx Look at all the heroes of the Left that are blatant lairs and supported by the media  ... they've been… https://t.co/SS0nqYHYgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VonteWrld @JxggDontLose @TheRealBandit_ @HoodieBxpe @CruxifyDaGod @ControlluhTNB @IceyNgl https://t.co/vgOxqHMLrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gingerbums This hurts so many people on so many levels. And he did it for a pay raise? 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJ66616 @raulmares72 I love these suckers. Star Wars Titanium Hasbro from 06-08 👍 https://t.co/Ujdohczve8]]></document><document><![CDATA[... took a beautiful drive down to Santa Cruz today to meet my luthier, Chris Holcomb and have him contour the ‘Kod… https://t.co/cy6Tilm1ZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for your insight into the NFL Ben!  One of my favorite follows.  You deserve whatever opportunity you get.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all remember when the GOP pretended to be about doing the right thing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bucks continue to make my day. Bledsoe has played fantastic this season. May it continue for 4 more years.… https://t.co/W7T5AOeDR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukestephh10 @WinksThinks Yeah I don’t care about that. The bucks have more important things ahead than this game.… https://t.co/UhtVP9KXGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You’ll get that smile taken off your face when u find out YOU MUST PLAY BY THE RULES. Alexandria Ocasio Cortez… https://t.co/G1baJYyt66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCPolitics Well, we need people to think past this corrupt @GOP administration. Eventually these fvckers will be… https://t.co/ThREIPi9JX]]></document><document><![CDATA[〰〰 👁👁   🌴    💋  #Mooning #Utah #TaylorSwift #Chevy55 #Smoking #Yellow #Sebring #Florida #Butt #Michigan #Home #Red… https://t.co/x1IN7mOOaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GotNoSperm @HalNiederman Yeah, yeah, once upon a time, we heard the same thing about Gregg Jefferies and Dave Magadan, as well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yankeesin2019 @NFL @Raiders @steelers @RapSheet @AB84 what??? they got a 3 and 5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#throwback too the time my teammates tried to kill me - #haha #tbt #gymnast #tricking #cheer #fitnessmotivation… https://t.co/ZtpSjBGBpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys rankings by Cantrall. @MayfieldCards is atop 3rd District with @gravescobball second. Only .1 divide regionall… https://t.co/qTPh3GfXtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[All workers are paid less than the value they create. Surplus value of labor—the literal exploitation of a worker’s… https://t.co/3T83gu9Bao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gutierrez__00 @call_me_lemus @vvsderek @Daavidg10 Sure Jan https://t.co/YTJMRZfiOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ll forever be upset if you wait for people to do things the way you do, stop expecting the most out of others❗️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReallyAwakenNow @peachy_witchy @SpeakerPelosi She is a supercilious POS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this ilhan omar stuff reminds me of that scene in the sopranos where they’re arguing about whether or not columbus… https://t.co/Jh74EvuCoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #FF @jthooper @tvmartha @MelissaStacy90 @WFLAJennH @annasmills @TheKatLewis @Kate_Chastain @Katie_Madisonn  … https://t.co/4QgReOM63K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation @HelmanDC Twitter can a bitch! But good for you for taking the short road... I mean the high road! 🤣🤣😂👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got Kentucky today. I’m watching Dusty Rhodes promos before his program with Superstar Billy Graham. Let’s make… https://t.co/AIZMROwKBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[His fist time at MARION High and it was to a Giants game to see jalenblackmon1 thanks to my bro gbazanjr great hang… https://t.co/xIdpufXWKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JoeNBC @morningmika @SenWarren #PresClinton met the Challenge of #RepublicanCongress Investigatio… https://t.co/xThPRgoBOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 down - 13 more opportunities for recruits to come visit @CincyChristFB and experience our competitive process to… https://t.co/0m0GCXuSKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terodan @aj07336074 @WilliamPatriots This guy must have missed all of last season, they’ll be fine is correct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Ann what happened to you? I don’t get you!!! I followed you and now it seems you have jumped way to the left!!! 👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[That FriYay feeling! ☀️😎✌️ I’m hoping to check out some of the @_desertx installations today in the Coachella Valle… https://t.co/Bsy2ANuqxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without a forced construct i am stuck in limbo... i am not going to poison my self to force it or hurt my self.. i… https://t.co/cu5mcXmuxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just witnessed one of the most ugly sequences of college basketball .. and I am unsure which team was the more ugly Louisville or Duke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodaertStijn @NBCNewsHealth The whole thing starts with concerns stemming from the anecdotal evidence. The Wakefie… https://t.co/FvjM1QpXsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 4:43 AM, I’ve been awake since 2, and I’m craving cereal. Pregnancy probs to a T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muscle Shoals police: Woman slipped Girl Scout troop fake money for cookies https://t.co/osN2gfX3Uv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@huybelieve put a post up about whiphandsd   My boy willie_watkinsbailbonds saw the post and hit me up for lunch. I… https://t.co/8UbxZwOFkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop the Parameters from @roncarpenter really inspired me! https://t.co/TJHiVCJ2ZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kickazzkurtz @rex_rexchapman @WhitlockJason @Michael_Mcpher @Dave17824012 @mattschieber The light shattered for dr… https://t.co/KrZStsIkTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[They updated the graphic today... 🤔  Same poll. Same responses. https://t.co/OWrozd5Y0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[NCSU legend Dereck Whittenburg!!! GO PACK!!!🐺🐺🐺 @ PNC Arena - Official Home of the NC State Wolfpack https://t.co/GppPlcVfYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t have to be that fancy to be really outstanding and the grilled calamari with roasted garlic, capers, oli… https://t.co/UrKMIMrES7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dpbrugler Trust me, as a former safety, I picked a pass once on my way to the end zone, as I felt the bad guy comi… https://t.co/WVDrSf8Vj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickZircher Spidey (Peter), Ms. Marvel (Kamala), Hercules, and Nightcrawler.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do we really need three hours of the #Oscars ? How about a nice 30 minute recap and do the show privately between colleagues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wildcatnews @cooktpc75 @SethDavisHoops @marchmadness @KentuckyMBB @Vol_Hoops @DukeMBB @UVAMensHoops @SEC @espn Sai… https://t.co/n27zUZJn8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qtf Jajajajajaja!!!...como les puede en vdd que este haciendo cosas constructivas, el detalle que no podrá quedar… https://t.co/IKyaKxUSbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Premier League is back! #burvtot #coys⚽️ @ Asheville, North Carolina https://t.co/WzNRX6vwXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[see, now this is a cool product with great design. #CasperGlow by @Casper  https://t.co/iU28YFbZW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BWVS #NEWYORK POSTED 📈 #X @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/SHs7Di8M8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boo hoo hoo! Should've thought about that when you decided to break your deal and lie to the people who wanted to p… https://t.co/FaTGYU28OP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHoff305 @SenGillibrand @nytimes You crazy. I will never quit Not ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elenitamontanez @Fabrici17741808 @Jaime_BonillaV @lopezobrador_ @JesusRCuevas @yeidckol @AlfonsoDurazo ¿Qué sabes… https://t.co/BaGJ9SgpNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris just throw them in jail kamala, then you can have them fight the climate disasters that your inaction caused for free]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can be with a partner for 2+ years and they’ll STILL do you wrong 🤦🏽‍♂️🤦🏽‍♂️ bye bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnriqueB07 Takeoff album already came out?? You meant OFFSET? Lmao https://t.co/ulQsnwkyKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 Reasons Why Content Experience Is the New #Content #Marketing https://t.co/T792r6nngJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arianaaaag @TMZ Does he play anymore or sit out until the draft is now the question]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Domenic_Toronto @Michael_Voris Each council operates independently from the Supreme council.  Each council is a su… https://t.co/Jox48bYgvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@willcain yeah ur big mad dude, signed for 13 years with no opt outs but he doesn’t wanna be here ok dude suck me]]></document></documents></author>