<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Callum, thank you for always encouraging and supporting each of us!  Truly a positive feeling and a great group to… https://t.co/RjrhqvG7xX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great weekend for the Lions! #Clawsup #Holysweat #GSAC #Goldpride #Godsglory]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve procrastinated a lot, but now I feel focused. I’m still young, but I won’t be forever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GandySteven @Jamiewho0924 @chelzyb20 @EFisher8445 @ballew_mark @Fuerstenberg15 @bsw224 @GitzMichael… https://t.co/jPfSQfSvW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougPolkPoker I have some vegan friends who  make snide comments cuz i eat meat like"oh no, Mark  doesnt eat good… https://t.co/4zKgCEfWra]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you think @mariekondo does this sculpture spark joy?🤗🤗🤗 #joyspotting #sparksjoy  . . . . . Sculptures by ke… https://t.co/wsVkNAHl6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklaureano989 As a mom to 2 adult sons w/autism, I loved the way you treated Mr. Rocky tonight. The manner you s… https://t.co/NhjhfAf57l]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOLY SHIT! IT WORKED!!!  WE’RE GOING TO @theghostinside, IN JULY!!!  I could fucking throw up, I’m so excited!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este camino lo camino yo solo🖕🏻👺 • • • • • • • #balenciaga #hypebeaststyle #inspiration #inspiracion… https://t.co/5WqKMIQiaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MajicSwanson I had a private gig in Landisville but I stayed in Philly for the weekend just because I like Philly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreatDismal @middleageriot @gillyarcht Not in a font large enough for a middle aged person to read]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 6-seed in the Random Everyday Thoughts region got me blocked in ~2012]]></document><document><![CDATA[I smiled at the mirror and people thought I was crazy. You make my days brighter with your appearance. But never co… https://t.co/6KoBUv7Ukn]]></document><document><![CDATA[P.S. RIP John Hurt. I’ll be thinking of you when I watch whatever the next iteration is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tkweaveractor *Happy Saturday* TK! #ActorBuddy 😎👍🌈🧒 https://t.co/gZmBLhwoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein This decision is wrong and it will be overturned before the 2020 decennial census is deployed.   Ille… https://t.co/nbNIgTRtit]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate got the most obnoxious ass broke ass musty ass bum ass friends and that shit is aggy aab like who has 6… https://t.co/eYUpeMhOAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter Hitchens @ClarkeMicah defends coal as an energy source - take *that*, Hillary!-]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nsaidian Probably not you🤣Confucius says. I Remembered a couple months ago saw a tweet like that invading sight 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TopherNowak @WDWGolf I need to check the card had a few pars and...a few albatrosses... #WDW #wdwgolf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a racist bone. Just lots of fat, cartilage, skin, tendons, organs, etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that, a week in #Reno at Western Dairy Management Conference comes to an end. We had a great time ent… https://t.co/dkiDYRPz7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Megs_ISU @ArnoldtheThird I’m probably +40 in the lb department https://t.co/O5ZzRgoaq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerryiannelli @TheTakeaway @WNYC Hey  @marcorubio que intereses creados tienes ahora con tan REPENTINO interes en… https://t.co/OuG5rDMUPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think what people are trying to say if MJ played in 2016 2017 and 2018 at the age of 54 55 and 56 he would not be… https://t.co/I6rX316WHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSThisMorning @CBS @CBSNews can we get an update on this lol this should be national news if it’s a true and bein… https://t.co/EDBCropUY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL @jzion65 @JasonPaulGilch4 @wisigoth70 @MissAuroraSnow @mudcat93 @ProPainArmy @brianslagel @FINALLEVEL… https://t.co/QbjK34zcDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@G_PaidInFull08 Facts. Everyone knew he was under 6’0. The eye 👀 test TD you that]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Jews do not or do not want to understand is that this women will slice your throat when she gets a chance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about a pre-flight breakfast slice of pizza? @ Southwest Terminal Orlando International Airport https://t.co/gf7dQJZCny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders enters crowded 2020 presidential race  https://t.co/hL9teKB17t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RondaRousey Ha ha hell yes they are marks ...they can’t handle the truth! Ha ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fasulo_chris @LaborPressNY My position hasn’t changed. I was born and raised in a union household. I support the workers on strike]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Heather_Horton Wow! Gorgeous. I think I have been following you for 8 or 9 years in Twitter land and it has been a… https://t.co/kdYfDpCq9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[He wasn’t on the schedule for field work today, but Jordan Hicks did just finish up a side bullpen session. C-Mart,… https://t.co/BiGdoIALNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of the first Period, Wildcats trail 0-1. Shots 7-10 in favor of Westside. 37 seconds left on the wildcat PP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m officially an old man. Today I got a new furnace and smart thermostat put in our house and now I feel cool. 😎 😎   Also, I feel poor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow.... will be hearing this name a lot on Sundays. This tweet will age well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤ “Fit Is Not A Destination, It Is A Way Of Life” . 💪You might set some fitness goals for yourself and work really… https://t.co/OEWS8WAGeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What’s dangerous about conspiracies is that they hamper sincere mobilization.” https://t.co/2gRza7wU43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WNDU @WSBT @ABC57News @46Sports @BremenBoysHoops leads @CulverCavaliers 33-16 end of half https://t.co/7RGcHwLVPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This message from President Trump pointed to the truth which EIR and LaRouchePAC have been fighting to get out for… https://t.co/WiE6cP1LYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being REAL is when you tell it like it is even when peoples feelings are @ stake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone said she looks like the rat from flushed away and that obliterated me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hanhtbui @SedanoAndy @HeinzKetchup_US Yes I ran out of ketchup today and said it out loud. Later checked my Twitte… https://t.co/JJTtHmgxav]]></document><document><![CDATA[about time, finally, now all we need is another couple thousand cases just like this one ,to look back on, I rememb… https://t.co/SmU9yhh08j]]></document><document><![CDATA[pf was cool when i first started getting into working out but now that i’ve been into it for over 4yrs i’m starting… https://t.co/ak1LosZzAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonH1187 This is what disappoints me about arm chair Christians like @DonH1187. They are the first to throw stones… https://t.co/KhXvAxwYqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oghonor Oh boy u know know I’m ready to go 🖤❤️🖤 😈 u need anything from me u give me the word]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez believes we should be excited about automated jobs https://t.co/dzc9kBDpwJ via @engadget]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all that supported yesterday’s Packing Party. We are grateful for your support to help our deployed so… https://t.co/0Fqr8g1HhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Subject was no doubt on “The Path to Targeted Violence” #IntentionalViolence #TargetedViolence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilentH46662994 @Independent @EUCouncil @EU_Commission @GermanyinUSA @GermanyDiplo @UKinUSA @10DowningStreet… https://t.co/WnL8QB2OyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan No way. Trump would fall apart if confronted with the facts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ocjacobmorris77 @Coach_Timmerman @CoachDubMaddox @aafiron @RunThePower Same concept as double post shallow. Allows… https://t.co/QctV0JDieZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendanCase6 I actually find myself wanting use "ratio" in my own writing when I want to talk about a particular g… https://t.co/GYY4EDZDuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBSchnitzel @lindahd41 @SSS_gov Yes. They’ll be counting the Democrats. 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanneLenzer1 @FibroidNetwork @FDA_Track @US_FDA @SGottliebFDA NOT ENOUGH! #OpioidCrisis is NOW putting victims of… https://t.co/z5QICNRSic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markjournell71 UVA is two games behind Duke for first.. Why would you pull for Duke?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the truth is good news and the truth is Jesus isn't coming back, then Jesus not coming back is good news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAFMaster @Jesterehs i’m on xbox so y’all will have to wait till tuesday but yes carter pls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emergency Pakistan cabinet meeting: Okay, Sachin Tendulkar hit me for 5 sixes... what do I do for the last delivery… https://t.co/w4P9V0CmAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come watch @ThoughtInUrHead die with me on @Twitch! 😂😂😂 #ps4 #playstation #psgamer #ps4gamer #playstationgamer… https://t.co/zf6zLSZxKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[PAINT NIGHT🖌🖌🖌 @ Coupa Cafe - Stanford Golf Course https://t.co/gi2ZoogJC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my favorite photos so far @BNPPARIBASOPEN https://t.co/3ZsnSRgUtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Christ working through me the #clay of my #body, my #flesh, through my struggle, my #brokenness, through all of my… https://t.co/KEpttWCuEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[She wasn’t compliant with a man’s request. That means she was yelling and angry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IndependenceHall 02-23-2019 #Philadelphia @ Independence Hall https://t.co/iiIueuYdsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kongo hurt em whenever he threw, the problem is he only threw like 7 punches the entire fight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay BB, you get a plane ticket to Australia for 16k, you fly first class. The NEXT DAY it drops to 10k I’m sure yo… https://t.co/uaY6pJ1oEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorCollins Dems are unconstitutional in NOT protecting us. Find the money or back Trump. Kids are getting sexu… https://t.co/I2moyPQEQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BV_Museum FYI, Twitter has upped the number of characters allowed in your display name. If you go on desktop to yo… https://t.co/HkmQGdZEHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceBeckhamXXX Let me underneath it while you dick dance so it slaps my tongue. 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hear @hausedave Address Mental Illness in New Song ‘The Ditch’ – Rolling Stone https://t.co/kckQQxc88A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could never cheat ... like it’s not physically in my bones or body to ever do that. Betrayal hurts why would I everrrrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miracle on Ice 1980 tribute......#coldwarvictory @ Hockey Hall of Fame https://t.co/utC3FHrto4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitanfallBlog NO , people need to stop complaining and hit their shots , they want it nerfed cause they cant use t… https://t.co/HGB04Ji4iz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ruso_tv 😍😍 yo kiero saber si ami tabien me amas ??? Erse el mejor https://t.co/8LQiLjWhBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisneyTory We don’t get debate now. We get soap boxing, but we get days of it. We have so many bad habits to undo…]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisa_h_cox @lizschloss Whoa! Not “retired”! Just on a ‘sabbatical’. 😬. And still a consultant to my former team 😏… https://t.co/PDktbWL6Of]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one has my actual nudes and no one will ever get them. I’m going to be famous and y’all ain’t about to leak my stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to R. Junior Pacheco, A Warren HS student candidate for Presidential Scholars #txst23 https://t.co/XR85hOyzKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[May we continue to pray in the heart of “Even if.” May we be open to what God wants to do through us as a denominat… https://t.co/Zje1tQaUGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[how many queers have experienced Diet Homophobia Lite™️ in the workplace or classroom or some sort of profesh envir… https://t.co/t9wwU9p6uH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatsJacqueline Oh yes.  Powerful.  Tripped some triggers.  https://t.co/sOpE0pVxNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mawaldman @BrennanCenter Factual allegations with no proof. And you believe this shit! I think your a pervert but… https://t.co/mViLjB6lRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@topherSZN @supremekhalill @IamKrisLondon Until drake responds to Pusha I’d take him serious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan , back in 05 in a prison in Iraq, the best pleasure I got was laughing at the detainees pain as I ripped off… https://t.co/luR90qNb37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MabelLaraNews Eso solo significa que te leen mucho, las explicaciones los amigos las necesitan, los enemigos no la… https://t.co/w1udIxQXbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vikingbeau @veggie64_leslie She still would have made a far better president than Trump. It’s not close.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump tRIMP can't score with his wife, so what makes you think he can score with any world leaders?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao, you’re obviously more interested in being an asshole than actually discussing anything.   Like I said, if Lo… https://t.co/fp0r4ZN349]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans No! 4 it is you! Who shall be damned! Or was it me!? 🤔 I forget]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanebacon @Titleist Veal Parmasian...with rigatoni al la vodka... a Healthy greens salad...and homemade chocolate… https://t.co/3xCnCkMbaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Fans” call them a terrible team with a loss in November but jump on the bandwagon come February/March. They never… https://t.co/VblwSv7egr]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU HAVE BY NOW CONFIRMED THE LAWS OF ABSOLUTE SAYS. THAT WHEN TBE NATIONAL ABSOLUTE AMERICA LEGAL MARRIAGE TRUTH J… https://t.co/6YNIq1Y0Xl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCocoShea yea, but i was brought up to respect a female. maybe i'm weird for believing that, but i couldn't do i… https://t.co/qoMOrnfflm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrummerBoy2112 Some private msg for you on your twitter account. Don't you get notifications? I do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKingCenter In the face of personal threats on his life and on to the ones he loved mostclosest… https://t.co/vLB2kEeEJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump These 8 Senators are in favor of MAWA (Make America Weak Again) like it was with Obama.]]></document></documents></author>