<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ejensenNYC excellent post about vaccination coverage (or lackthereof) today. Also, vaccine hesitant are not the sa… https://t.co/UCSCLcqvTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[-yelling from the bathroom-  “Hey, Hannah! My pee looks like honey!” -5 y/o]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great and surely a long overdue conversation. And the realities of this over-connected-but-also-isolated ag… https://t.co/KsRFdvwMat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emirsader @maurosgs1108 MANE MANIFESTO. TEM DE PARAR ESTA MERRRRD TODA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The comedian wanted to greet him but did not exactly know how that would work, so both the comedian AND the bishop… https://t.co/odP8KO4Y2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm socially liberal, but fiscally conservative. But at the end of the day, an admirer of those who stand up for wh… https://t.co/QM9FPu0vCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[am I gonna do every single festival one of my friends is going to again this year? none at all? ones I haven’t been… https://t.co/VyfJUF8t5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods This happens in people’s lives everyday and they dont get nearly the punishment that… https://t.co/eGrKJ4d9ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely WOW!!!! Great night of Christian music, worship, and fun! @tobymac #HitsDeepTour #JeremyCamp… https://t.co/fI5tu3cdwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[So... moved to AZ and need to know... @ASU  or @UofA?   My fandom for College sports is up for grabs. Your opinion matters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[”GIᗰᗰE TᕼE ᒪOOT, GIᗰᗰE TᕼE ᒪOOT”  #ᗷIGGIE @ Tribeca https://t.co/tNOfQuSWLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toppel_ELD @teacher2teacher @aliceaspinall @carlota_holder @ValentinaESL @MsTarynWall @jennajdavis @emilyfranESL… https://t.co/MnLTh9eERU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John242Ti @TobyandMel Splitting the state in half with the east side called Liberty, on the face, sounds like a good plan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once I’m 21 it’s over for me cause I can easily satisfy all of my addictions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikespeedTv @MyiPhone6SS @itsKrisStar @fallenangel8504 @FelishaHunters @fun_eddie @outlawscalper @StorySpirit4U… https://t.co/R38fPyiFIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This month’s Minecraft community suggestion theme is... ores! In addition to tweeting these at Tanner, check out ou… https://t.co/gpO6pYMRwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #StormJavelin is my @anthemgame exosuit of choice. Make your selection to unleash your power and watch your suit in action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot to tweet about it but ALX SERENADED ME for Valentine’s Day (hence the trajes) and I’ve never been more in lo… https://t.co/Sk1i9q5F8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @WillGuzzardi @Delia4StateRep @BrandonCCD1 @CDRosa @UWFIllinois]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fordnation @MacLeodLisa Many MPPs know that the OAP changes are violating children’s rights to achieve their full… https://t.co/4PaoUvcbg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LamorneMorris Mine was Pacifico. I drank half felt ‘so wasted’ and fell asleep. Lol https://t.co/M4gPhQnxXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a day that’s set aside for showing love to others... make sure you set aside the time to love and care for yours… https://t.co/RElso5oNRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Team Memb… https://t.co/OMfFv6n4OY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guillermo del Toro le entrega el Oscar a Cuarón. De mexicano a mexicano  #Oscars2019 https://t.co/6CXGP4WqlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom keeps posting on Snapchat like it’s Facebook and I’m uncomfortable]]></document><document><![CDATA[I leave for Florida Saturday morning and don’t have a single thing packed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I wrong or is mental health easily the most overlooked part of successful entrepreneurship?   Once I started put… https://t.co/YSKOHyWuaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday!!! CHELLE B in this thang invading your airwaves doing it like #ItChelleBDone 7p-Midnt on the BIG St… https://t.co/TvwDgMI6s5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronniecorvette @sacbee_news Awww. Thank you Ronnie. I love my friends there, but I’m very happy not waking up at 2:30am. 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[#retuit Un placer verla disfrutar... hombres interesados, info solo por mensaje directo! https://t.co/RDhfqBQgHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we are being honest, self-care is actually kind of boring. https://t.co/sfcYmNUN6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queerfinancier @KateMielitz @okstate This is so cool! Congrats, y’all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@payourinterns loves @LaurenUnderwood she is indeed a superstar, @ZerlinaMaxwell. Takes one to know one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah definitely good for her, her company grew so fast and her product is really high quality. But she’s not self-m… https://t.co/2BrhaAjFqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally have lab and can’t be late. Not even two hours is enough to get to the city IM SO MAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never forget about Jessica Mauboy though!!!!!! LOVE YOU LONG TIME. @jessicamauboy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m doing a review of @daisymarquez_ pallet tomorrow, 🥳 for my yt channel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nozrati @LaureRoch1 @HuffPost Interesting.  You of course have proof of this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspf42 Not apples to oranges “friend”. Crying over a loss years later won’t get you the W. Move on. See where the “annoying” part comes in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomascol @RichNChrist57 In Jesus we are not viewed as sinners saved by grace. We are saints who will always need J… https://t.co/rP55HwhYDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister sends me dick pics that dudes send her. WHY SHE DO ME LIKE THAT THOE.. #BLOCKEDBITCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[i MISS SO MANY PPL RN AND I WANT THEM BACK IN MY LIFE BUT A SIS IS SCARED HAHAHAHAHAHAHHAHAHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does Chuck Todd not realize that Commiting Treason with a Foreign Enemy is a Hell of a lot more Serious than Clinto… https://t.co/7MgXJqJShw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really appreciate @Starbucks because the barista let me try something and said if I didn’t like it I can get my usual. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aljndraln One to dry you the fuck out and the other to clog you tf up. Damn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2015 after my breakup with my ex.  I moved back in with my parents. It was definitely a low point in my life.  I wa… https://t.co/k9stidVeA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Onetrackpunk @swordchomp I remember really enjoying the first two games but it was a really long long time ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[He literally threw a TANTRUM. LIKE A 4 YEAR OLD and smashed his keyboard and broke the space bar off of it. Now he… https://t.co/NqEOMlvP8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting, coming on the heels of the Twitter/FB takedown of pro-gov Iran influence efforts this month. On the fl… https://t.co/4aBSweMvsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my most favorite things to do on a Saturday morning is Brunch 🥂What’s one of your favorite things you like t… https://t.co/emPqPLrtKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using the Letgo App to try and sale some stuff for a little bit of money or whatever we can make kuz well ya gotta… https://t.co/pum1XnCedi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided to take the week off from the gym...... but as the @survivorcbs premiere approaches tomorrow night, I’m tem… https://t.co/DSuRuhgqlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[im about to send everything you want!!! selling here but i can sen preview hit me uppp on kik!!!!!  kik 20skylive https://t.co/JwCYH1Whou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok @palladiumshows funny joke where are the rest of the Have Heart tickets]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's this 2 day old news got to do with the price of tea in #China? Plenty!  #fordrecall #tradewar #leverage]]></document><document><![CDATA[INTRICATE series 40x40in vinyl on canvas gold leaf modern western #calligraphy #arboriginal influenced… https://t.co/WBWU2c2oJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inezsneks We should register under an alias at the hotel so our fans don't stalk us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love him soooo much Izayah Ivan Gutierrez ❤️❤️😘😘 my prince mommy loves you to the moon 🌙 and back to infinity ♾ a… https://t.co/SI3rR50uax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get to know the wonderful Caitlin Kinnunen, starring @ThePromMusical on tonight’s #BroadwayNames 8 ET… https://t.co/hh5ZBFhWZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day !!!!  #happyvalentinesday #malachi1_2. “I have always love you “ says the Lord .… https://t.co/xGySs7G3l5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnterToScore  VeSunny 14inch Balayage Clip in Hair Extensions Black Fading to Medium Brown Mix Black Hair Extensio… https://t.co/lVwtDQIwcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rockey_And Thank YOU Rock Star for being the ultimate colleague and literacy partner. It’s not about me. It’s abou… https://t.co/mF2qf9wJ2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up at 330am cause ur NyQuil wore off just to take more, pee, get some water and eat a whole orange 🍊 Back to bed I go 😷😴🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love taking my ASL class wit my sister she's so supportive n cute wow i love her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@everton137 Normalmente, todas as universidades têm uma clínica escola a preços simbólicos então acredito que sim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tori_centeno Me for the next few days (at least) https://t.co/SBJ4N3kP4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hurricanesadie @owhmusicguy My 10yo plays Imagine Dragons nonstop and I’ve yet to hear them encourage her to “teas… https://t.co/YNRkSTkogt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BUYMYPREMIUM @2KCrewFinder @2kCompGames @Big_Brudda_PURP Me too send me a request. DweebDestroyer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Key West Lighthouse @ Hemingway Home, Key West, Florida https://t.co/RDVXbLceTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello my friends! My friend Cassandra is reaching out to friends and family to help her #rehome Brodhi and Olive (h… https://t.co/s2ACJLJwIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agentredgirl w hat happened to your videos on porn hub. Are you being sensored??? Know your Patreon is being revie… https://t.co/9n744XLgR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brand new wolf 🐺 headband called myself The Wolf Phoenix 🐺🔥🦅 @ SU Falk College Department of Sport Management https://t.co/C9SxgfUdwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReflectingMan @MelissaJPeltier @SaysDana @LouiseMensch @snowknuckles @JenKirkman @lauferlaw @911CORLEBRA777… https://t.co/2w237AVh94]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CupcakeLady27 I really shouldn't complain. I think I've worn clothes 30 minutes of the last 13 hours. 😂🤣 and that… https://t.co/F2mg44kiY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sal_castaneda My office is in Pleasanton. Feel free to drop some off. #yum #rocksandsalt #andsomechips]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS Give it up already. It has become boring and annoying that you keep trying to take off the… https://t.co/ZI7MipFHeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because Canadians are very funny!  And good at making fun of Americans!(we need taking down)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tenho q ir no banco, mercado e comprar uns casaco amanhã. Não sei o que fazer primeiro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que risa que el highlight de la mañana es @_Maaxx22 decidiendo si se toma foto o no con @Juliobracho34 en el Autódromo de Guadalajara.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ZtDmINNCGa                #wow #wowapp #Fiverr #freelance #website #WhatsApp #LinkedIn #email… https://t.co/MRBu9teAPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AletaCannon I wish I could retweet this but also lmk what you find out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight and goodbye! I’ll miss you! @PascoSheriff  I miss you already #LivePDNation #LivePD https://t.co/UyFMcgPYFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabiMccauley @CIAspygirl @tonyposnanski Don’t know if you do nuts, but have you ever tried incorporating ground ha… https://t.co/BwwhaPh936]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama was a complete pussy when it came to dealing w other world leaders. The apology tour made us a target. Trump… https://t.co/S24vrnnWTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[AP professional development. @AmyLGrosso fabulous information that everyone should hear @sfloresRRISD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAG4All @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @LVNancy @LadyRedWave @SiddonsDan @SweetKat111 @KNP2BP @ECHOtheCALL @Maggieb1B… https://t.co/zuFIoSmO17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amy, here's my reply. I was thinking I'm too old 2 say more than you, but I'm old, not dead. Yes, @brennan_elliott… https://t.co/zhueVX1e2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love you so much!! thank you for treating me like it’s my birthday everyday 💓💓💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tsturgie @POTUS @JudicialWatch I’m waiting for NY to find him guilty of things that will lock him up once he leave… https://t.co/1Nk2MrrRr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcusGreenWDRB @CoachCarbello @AaronMatas ...until we meat again, my friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drogersuk Take your students on a field trip to the John Snow Pub in London to see a water pump and talk to them a… https://t.co/vurLdlep3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[While I was making breakfast this morning I started thinking that I could get more out of my spatula. As it turns o… https://t.co/6TVIA1lDH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotiUno Zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Now you see, I am a descendant of the so called "Night Rides".  All I can say is this..May God Bless you and J… https://t.co/JBsZyDaz9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ish_lopezzz Do you like chocolate, caramel or vanilla? Or all of the above?! lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My one woman show Newfie Electra is happening @TalkIsFree in April. It’s double billed with Alyssa Wright’s show ca… https://t.co/5EJuuCupE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#liveradvocate #hepatitisc ask your doctor to be tested. Millions of people do not know their status.  #gettested]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kindergarten students STEM activity Cat in Hat cup stacking activity. @racheladamstn @GrandviewEPTA @GrandviewES… https://t.co/JcVhcHlfbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarianoArrigo @gromeroar @negritomolinero Yo creo que hubo un acento mexicano ..... creo ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump Foreign government. Orin Hatch was going to set up a appeals case called gamble to c… https://t.co/8AXEDZ05yP]]></document></documents></author>