<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@frankieonye @Lyssipe @sir_squiggles_ @jamesxingleton I agree that paedophilia is not and will not be part of queer… https://t.co/81TCIA0wkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/16/17, 5:47am, my apt...nothing new. Got up about an hour ago but I’m going back to bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[STUNNING REVERSAL: @Amazon pulls out of plans to build second headquarters in NY, now democrats are blaming democra… https://t.co/SIC75jrxQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolinskiBraden 2 for 4, 3 run HR, 4 RBI’s.  Go Raiders!!⚾️ https://t.co/2UmC9nu93u]]></document><document><![CDATA[the people who choreograph water fountains to go to the music are the thankless heroes of our world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said I was going to bring heat to the radio when I got on . My people have to be heard . Only way .]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve come to the conclusion these bitches are really delusional &amp; i’m sticking with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Baumann_ Lol, good luck. Country shows at that house are quite the event]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueStB_ My girl actually and she was pregnant just found out , BDs ain’t shit bro .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now selling tickets to the shit show that is my life...hmu for pricing and details 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pink, it's not just a color, it's an attitude. #party #style photo shantiknight @ A Perfect Event https://t.co/5Xh3H419gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ACArtshow2019 originals in the works... #Quentin &amp; #Terrie #WiPs @ Fairland, Maryland https://t.co/MMbXg8TGpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zestitude BLESS YOU FOR THIS LMAO I got so excited I misread it &amp; thought you were someone else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heartshaka @7PurpleHearts @WGNNews Sorry I said nothing about them wearing makeup. I, personally, love men in make… https://t.co/7OoaGg391d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyGros_WMBB @mikeda71 @ErinMorganTV @wmbbkelseypeck @wmbbchrism @SamLuceyWX @Whitleyweather @carlymascittiTV… https://t.co/vsxrPAydEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️💯✌️🔥😎😘  I Just miss him that all summer can't even get here fast enough so I can see this Gorgeous man… https://t.co/HQdaXPNsQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for our partnership with @TuskegeeUniv which has made this program possible @AmmsEufaula #WeAreECS]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone doesn’t realize what day it is .... HAPPY GAMEDAY TO MY SARALAND SOFTBALL FAM #finish 🥎❤️ https://t.co/6VPk3F8iHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjolds @cspanwj Imagine if it was Donald?...You are going to try to reelect the guy. Donald isn't apologizing for… https://t.co/SqWc2ADjTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need some more Volunteers for our April 1st PD. If you could help, please check out the following links:… https://t.co/GMxAOaWn7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maaaaan I NEED @shotwithsoju and @NinaWest to stay! They’re fucking everything! #DragRace]]></document><document><![CDATA[There Jacob the younger used his first-born brother’s clothing to trick his blind father, here the father-in-law tr… https://t.co/x5kZBllwme]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t want anything to do with people anymore and it’s sad, because I just woke up with that feeling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyfarr @ashleymayer Also going through it. Add “wedding” to anything and the price goes up ten-fold! 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[AT JFK THIS MORNING EATING ALMONDS AND GETTING READY FOR CHECK IN my lil carry on bag that was ok on American airli… https://t.co/v5QquQCjrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wildehout @__megankimball @WNYC @boyscouts So bring that up to local, state, national and international scouting organizations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tiffany Tygart Tygart started the Princess Fairy Tale Challenge! https://t.co/f11SrlQDa3 #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@legant66 @UniquelyGillian @acoyne If pmjt says he thought she was still open to change and clerk knew she wasn’t h… https://t.co/KbIlPKLNX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardinalDolan What about infantacide, Cardinal?  Jesus must be grieving]]></document><document><![CDATA[@learnandteach04 @rhondajsp @LRobbTeacher @BiscottiNicole @aweninspiration @heARTISTatWORK @TanELLclassroom… https://t.co/gTeFQTlfyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was a great insight into who @Enes_Kanter is. Can’t wait to see him on the court.....P.S. we’re not all hipste… https://t.co/n9IKuajm61]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey girl.  Yea YOU! 🙌 way to muscle through it!! You did it! Fasted walking, Core, Bodybuilding Regimen of Hamstrin… https://t.co/dB1PFzXvE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[And anyone who married or not and deliberately goes out of their way and I do mean out of their way to cause tHIz👇🏼… https://t.co/LlvTXjgFAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally watched A Start is Born.... Wow... Simply wow https://t.co/IDnX4WG2PP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on in!!!! Hillsboro Home Depot is hiring! #jobfair2019 in full mode @bdesigns03 @bamanda1214 @tiana_martines… https://t.co/T8Z4LHIuxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I freaking hate how emotional I’ve been lately. I cry at any sad thing that happens in real life and in movies.. and i mean i bawl]]></document><document><![CDATA[love by lana del ray always hits a little differently when you’re blaring it while driving home from being with your significant other]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone can wear "crazy colors" or out of the box looks. People of any age, gender, etc. ALSO, makeup shaming is gro… https://t.co/VM8E2aYwkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spend hours researching fitness related topics in my free time. Going to start my certification course this month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So it’s “woke” when you hire minorities, and “tokenism” when we do? And anytime you see ours we’re just “parading”… https://t.co/QunEfYFzRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me on March 27th at 12 pm PT as I present a webinar on Keys for Mentoring in the Legal Profession. | Registrat… https://t.co/ZSqwOU8TpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at John Glenn Columbus International Airport - @columbusairport in Columbus, OH https://t.co/5XfqWa0s8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating my birthday with @8aequitas8 and @rogueman  bjsrestaurant @bjsrestaurants #bjsrestaurantandbrewhouse… https://t.co/8RyR4RH9eZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s one thing you used to enjoy doing all the time, but haven’t done in a while?  For me: fishing, surfing, read… https://t.co/RcqBez7tJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pray that I get this job. If I do I will be able to not only work full time but go back to school full time 🙏🏼🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayiiee so true.. Gling nila lahat. Support ko c Morisette  Wrong spelling wapakels]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel free to cashapp me so I can mend my heart break with retail therapy please 🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello March Break! We have transformed into a play dough colour lab today to apply fractions to cooking and colour… https://t.co/tu7RkUIOm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep waking up in the middle of the night and can’t go back to sleep 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bane of our community. And who am I to be with all of you convincing. Love you back. @ Boulder, Colorado https://t.co/3xZGa2mwyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@techspire @pearltrees !! I was skeptical are first, but it's amazing, mobile app, browser extension too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[True, true, and true!! My mentor is very busy, but always has time for me. It makes a big difference in your gradua… https://t.co/SWCApz9KAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LATigers_ @2a_class @KPLC7Sports @LAHSGBBFANPAGE @LakeCity_Pride @swlahssports @SWLAsportsTalk @JeffDavisParish Th… https://t.co/8IsX55lreA]]></document><document><![CDATA[never settle for less, remember your worth and keep going with your life ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy international women's day. "Women are the real architects of society". – Harriet Beecher Stowe… https://t.co/ZwsTTkjbp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Note no orange color just pale pasty old man color. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustaPack @spain @visitseville @LanguageAct I want allllll of it on my list. I want to see it all! Can tips for th… https://t.co/WbZ5uhIvMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume Would they do this with a male candidate? And besides, that jacket is hideous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenidcm @yourgayaunt What a hard working woman. Working early mornings]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It is the same in the other GCC countries as well, so any expat who is trying to find a job, in say, for example,… https://t.co/1fmLdr9X77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeyersLeonard11 @MLBrand11 @PitViperShades Woulda been a beautiful day for a hike! Soon I hope we can go on one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A collab I did with musicians from Bulgaria, the Netherlands, and Japan 🙌🏼🙌🏼 https://t.co/p1mbYRN0bX #bandhub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carmen Vargas started the Princess Fairy Tale Challenge! https://t.co/Qo58q3YBwq #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@502Heathen @replouisville @UofLWBB Yeah, I remembered after I asked that he does graphic design. 😂 https://t.co/PthgupMmNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending the most super hero, positive vibes to my sisters family today. Need some extra prayers 🙏🙏My brother-in-law… https://t.co/0mT3ZUvpjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BEASTMODE @ScottAdamsSays So the release of electronic waves may harm the brains of people? Law suits are COMING]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Canal Street, New Orleans https://t.co/tDU77bUe7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when ppl like text messages in the text. #fuckingstop #noonelikesyou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump No that's not true. I do not believe you speak for the American people.  Nobody does. Y… https://t.co/Hd4B85qg4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a long night / morning I just wanna sleep but thank god for dutch bros!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Crawfish #HappyFatCajunGirl @ Disney's Fort Wilderness Resort &amp; Campground https://t.co/jheIPjNuLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else remember this jam? This was my shit in middle school! https://t.co/yIkvDhqi3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrgifford @dave_bainbridge @saoili @f3ew Which is why they are so bad at it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherPurdon you guys don't have visual voicemail?! I get voicemails as texts. Best invention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just talked my husband through fixing a formula issue in Excel using find/replace and his excitement has me feeli… https://t.co/r5MW0fFwFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OPINION Love them or hate them, the popular Easter candy "Peeps" is releasing some new flavors this year! Orange S… https://t.co/k2gwdcWZwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoshWithTyler Me sprinting toward another hallway https://t.co/VCKHgd9av2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmeDyckman @TweetOfSpirit_ You can totally handle it. I believe in you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haleaziz @KateNocera trial at The Hague. Trump has already so intimidated and made life miserable for one of the j… https://t.co/f71o5LRMIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are a treasonous liar and a snake @realDonaldTrump , slither off because #MuellerIsComing for you and your fami… https://t.co/vumnvx8zRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@genedblocked i read this in ur voice and I am cackling! ugh the caucacity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love Shane but just because you’re not offended, doesn’t mean others aren’t. Let’s stop discrediting others as bein… https://t.co/6R9ssG8w5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep trying to tell myself to stop caring but it’s so hard because that’s just not who I am]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODAY IS A GOOD DAY:  @GrantJNBC5 just said, “If you’re looking to maybe go out and have dinner on the patio with y… https://t.co/0E4tpbzdNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reynolds9047 Ugh every damn time I have to remind him and his practice is mostly men so it’s not like he has a lot… https://t.co/VGTwnNglFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@godjihyo i do only because i usually wake up with a gross feeling face and i need to wash off any left over acne medicine off!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichHoivata Are you part of the YNAB Facebook group? I just searched in there and there are a couple good discussions about the flags :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[We ♥️ representing clients purchasing or selling residential real estate. As the #realestate transaction becomes mo… https://t.co/tqbOjTbDzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFLMal I see the electrical outlet your mic and CD player was plugged into behind home plate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People keep asking me how’s it going, what are you up, and the answer is always “I am spending all my time working… https://t.co/mOvmxciJ0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaQuetteWrites @RWANYC @jellybeanrae It HAS to be in a book! It was so serendipitous and lovely:) I guess we shoul… https://t.co/1FVkgztxZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[HANDLEY STAFF: Don’t forget that today is “GREEN EGGS AND HAM DAY”, part of Dr. Seuss Dress up week!  Tie some gree… https://t.co/RIQxyGK7Wi]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Louis Fire Chief Dennis Jenkerson &amp; Meggan from Ameren collecting for @Heatupstl https://t.co/qFD3DbTUom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emanningwriter @SketchesbyBoze Yeah that would have really ruined reading for me https://t.co/fHuRyZNTYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drank too much coffee I feel like I’m on crack AHAHDHDNJSBFNFJSHDNDJAHDJRJDBFHSJDNFJDBDNFJSHBFFKSHFBSK D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter fashion be missing you soon! #furvestseason #coloradofashion @ Boulder, Colorado https://t.co/IjHsEkrLKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[life might seem peachy keen in marialand lately but reality is im currently balancing 4 jobs and my last year of un… https://t.co/QkB3R6ZYpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gop @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @SenatorRomney @BenSasse @lisamurkowski @LamarAlexander @SenatorCollins… https://t.co/VplZiyE6RN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@historylvrsclub Brain surgery, 1000 years old.  Trepanning.  Those holes are very precise, too.  Awesome. I'm impressed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have arrived ! We left snow in Denver and arrived to some light rain at Salt River Fields in Arizona. Fields are… https://t.co/snq5UqBywg]]></document></documents></author>