<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Alright life bring it on! I am willing open and ready. For both the blessings🙌🏼and Challenges💔because I know they b… https://t.co/1zyDqB0FPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[255 current pr   #teamogre #theogrecompound #nutrishopmtjuliet #shr #superhumanradio #beverlyinternational… https://t.co/3K7w5ElDfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me tell you what we’re NOT going to do. We’re not going to talk down to a QUEEN like Lupita Nyong’o by asking h… https://t.co/2FkQzwvHE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@momurda_eternal @vero_c8400 Fuck yeah....we will probably be hitting up the river but let me know where you guys want to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I buy futures on people like I can companies? If so I'd like futures on ones @MarissaMets and @Jacob_Resnick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimesOpEd @Judgenap I’ve noticed that this pseudo judge’s opinions have proven to be wrong most of the time fo… https://t.co/o0jVmXD5fN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrowofJustice @ETSshow @reverendofdoubt @MenInNursing @dr_larryi @PheoCoffee @sweetmarias @WrayCharles @cjchiu… https://t.co/LuUazdSsMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the winter rain we've been getting is gone, and it's a good time to visit San Diego.  Have fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LENMILNER @DailyMail @MailOnline A quick deadly shot to the vitals results in a quick death,no suffering..and does… https://t.co/Yy2UxmJ6vJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[١- في هذا الزمن أصبح البشر لا يعرف ثمن الكلمة ! ولا يعرف ما تصفه هذه الكلمة. الكل يطلق على أي إنسان جيد في أي صنعه… https://t.co/7S1dSVXSGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMA about Python or Brown v. Board of Education https://t.co/hkEQrr24am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcelodacruz @JJ66616 @rianjohnson @SuperBroMovies Your waisting your time on the wrong people bro. We all love Star Wars Correct?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bisoye_ The first step has always been recognition and accolades. In this case, done and dusted. Is #Bisoye2023 in order? 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollyhood4ever @HHlibertarian @realchuckbearry @stranahan @ali @GarlandNixon Yes just like the sons of Jacob took… https://t.co/zQ0WjDQyey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Twitter is your papas only platform wtf are you talking about. Lame!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshMorris33333 @von_tann @LASeoulGuy @phillysports81 @maria_torres3 Hahaha!!!  I don’t care about deferred money.… https://t.co/b8vZ8Qqpmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c7b0e11fb71b40c @Terebzz @qtf Jejeje.. ingenuidad, bueno fuera y 60 millones estuvieran observando, con responsabi… https://t.co/Hir9hGw4OA]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to risk getting your heart broken once in a while. But you should never risk getting behind the wheel afte… https://t.co/SQbzJGzE6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Singing Shaving Cream on @TheGongShowABC as an encore for Hot Dogs and Applesauce... 🤩 https://t.co/7uC86OFMQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sassymomof6 @sweet_an_sexy26 The 2 of u together scares me right down to my core 🤣🤣🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump You and your father are vile, disgusting pieces of shit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In #VISL #JacksonCup action tonight from Westhills, @vicwestfc #Div1 survived a @HighlandersFC #Div2 comeback and w… https://t.co/NLN7ln6A7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComcastCares #mobile_Care How can there be a cable tv outage when interacting &amp; phone service is still working? Highly Disappointed....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmartNYT @SherrodBrown Sen. Sherrod Brown is right.   Democrats need to win the 2020 presidential election with th… https://t.co/ddunMfw7ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Political analysts predicted recreational marijuana had a shot in the house but would die in the senate. Now we’ll… https://t.co/R3F0YNvYBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@consmover @AZWS Traitors!! Every last one of them. A war is coming. Count me in. #DestroyEveryDemocrat]]></document><document><![CDATA[This amazing young lady turned 13 today. Happy Birthday Bridget, we love you beyond measure.  “May she become a flo… https://t.co/p6mVFIqREZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah. This is what you say when you know little, if anything, about the past 500 years, the political/intellectual a… https://t.co/RXFNz1i0Lg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wasted 2 hours of my life Roma is the worst movie ever made. #overhyped #groupthink]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone gets to have a great spring break and I’m stuck taking responsibility for my roommates animals 🤷🏽‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@s0daft @Galaxians @MagicJohnson @MiaHamm @WillFerreI @MLS Because they come to our field and bring this trash attitude with them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys hoops- Geneva 22, Downers Grove North 19. DGN in bonus for rest of half with 7 mins to play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fans of Twizzlers, are you not bothered by the fact that they taste bad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends Happy Mardi Gras,  Today is Fat Tuesday a little chilly but mostly sunny and dry. The Mardi Gras Ind… https://t.co/69cJG6cFRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DustyLeeCook Wife is an attorney. She will not watch ANY law shows on TV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two years ago, every month for 9 months I was on a vacation.   Now, I can’t even even get to the other side of the city 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manlikeralph 💀💀💀💀 niggas be jumping in front of bullets like they have a death wish]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert Lapenna crossed 5K. Time 00:31:02, pace 10:00 min/mile, est. finish 11:25 am https://t.co/7sfVgMx1Ip #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimbal Then you would have to do the math for the terminal velocity against the force of gravity to see if they wo… https://t.co/hOlm0Kgg9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParisHilton  happy birthday Paris with love from your fan with Autism Jared 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WesClements22 a winning team could not have defended that last shot more poorly and get away with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachWallace30 Implemented to protect players and I’ve only heard of one person getting actually hurt because of i… https://t.co/Sb36DGgL8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not speaking at all politically, but there’s no question that this @CNN town hall with @TulsiGabbard highlights… https://t.co/0jlZrSGuE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily practice 👉 “Work ethic is the most important component of being successful”. -Kliff Kingsbury  #business… https://t.co/eBQIj65FhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a BOOM Dynamite by O.H.S.O. Brewery at @mlb — https://t.co/qCH5k5fthO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows @realDonaldTrump Time to close Mueller down. It’s a disservice to the USA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Prayer is not merely a task of ministry; it is a gauge that exposes our hearts’ condition.” Francis Chan #LetterstotheChurch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricBlackwood10 @GroverNorquist Because Reagan Economics has redistributed all the nations wealth to the top 1% Am… https://t.co/AIlCdy4kko]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always do everything from the heart because I remember all the times I wish I had that help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es el mensaje más directo que me an mandado hahahh. Una serie de eventos empiezan. Vengaa! #LeónIsHere]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would recommend that affected physicians first make sure they have correctly defined your “cohort.”  I am routine… https://t.co/E1wbPMhyuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many Gaga - Bradley Cooper snaps did i get during the #Oscar2019 https://t.co/9C5VC4M5AG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @MariaBartiromo @SundayFutures Ty sir, for your service]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kyle Wade able to get inside and finish for @CalMumHoops https://t.co/YqtGKgxrA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckmoffat @King5unit9 @Lenslinger @13PhotogWillie @13PhotogAndre “Soup’s on?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. @mcleodkr made a very bold statement, "A teacher can't just be sweet, they must be confident and comp👏🏽e👏🏽tent!… https://t.co/0aR504Jyui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TofuRE2 @UiroMochiRE2 @Zehb_BR @ImKatastrophe Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool rus… https://t.co/qDiwCZ0gQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the guy that made THIS pass somehow isn’t a Cousy finalist.  (Yes, I’m still bitter. You should be too if you’v… https://t.co/DKOinaCQiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was great to see this @whsnjwrestling alum and @pennstateWREST win over Sparty last! Thank you Higgins Family! https://t.co/tbTWN1v4OL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiCaliberLilGal You can't prove I'm not any more than you can prove you have a religious bent in your body.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben sipped, sunshine in bands along his liver-spotted hand. “Augustine, the day I hired you, I sensed in you the wo… https://t.co/0fMqHq7wgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TurkeyLegJeff When I was about five, we had Pizza Hut the night before Thanksgiving, and everyone got sick as hell… https://t.co/3ArBJ6WqJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KostelecPlan Well, at least the prioritization of that Tampa freeway expansion makes sense.  They've got quotas to… https://t.co/DJ6ipGO9aE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonnieWithTide @PresidentPerine @realDonaldTrump Lil cuz been putting it down a long time to be so young. #251 MOBTOWN kids watching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 7th at 10 PM PST on CBS. I'm playing "Ronald", (The Live-in Boyfriend). Thank you...shawnry arthomastv… https://t.co/QXNiwtXhl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[On her 18th birthday senior @Erika_Cortez5 goes 6 IP, 1 H, 2BB, 9K’s and a shutout. Post game cake afterwards with… https://t.co/SpkY4JcgoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teacup Candle in a Hand Poured Beeswax/Soy Candle https://t.co/293Dx6XXS3 https://t.co/PCaBs3xbv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Madres! ¿En que nos estamos convirtiendo?  Así como esta mujer, seguramente hay miles que están en riesgo de perde… https://t.co/uhM3cVWfgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_lilierenaee Yeah it’s not comparable but that “boys will be boys” statement has never been heard on this side. It… https://t.co/PRdDKwDT9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwestr @estima94 @ConsumerReports What does aluminum have to do with it... I've had zero issues with the aluminum.… https://t.co/abgQjz1u76]]></document><document><![CDATA[Building with @thechike @NesbyPhips &amp; @blackloveprjct. Can you imagine the conversation? 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieD296 @RepSwalwell @NRA @GabbyGiffords @SpeakerPelosi You are a special kind of stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photoshoots starting at $10 DM for details! . . . . . . . #photography #photos #photographer #pictureoftheday… https://t.co/hxfwViM4XL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating our @CreedsES artists at the MOCA this evening! #simplycreeds https://t.co/Uqnty3QjXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[But really watch your puppers and pets bc something’s out here killing cows and llamas. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s @ericchurch covering Bob Seger on Saturday night of the #DoubleDownTour in #Detroit at @LCArena_Detroit https://t.co/lSodjGcd4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paul_beaudry She’s just against people who have little or no idea about what they are talking about, ‘mansplaining… https://t.co/htynDwfz8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus, animate Christians with a sense of forgiveness. https://t.co/ysms8yyu9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy was good. I now even smell like a bonfire now. 🔥 #MBRW19 #BallHoggerzBBQ https://t.co/p34bnocfKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @AmbJohnBolton Has he mentioned this to the Russians?  Maybe Trump can send Putin a big Hallmark card.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passing up an open three for Happ to get fouled is not optimal efficiency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mfishbein44 @a_becks22 I know....  My point is given the MTAs inability to properly budget and manage construction… https://t.co/Nu9dwg4rTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Wizarding World Of Harry Potter - Hogsmeade - @universalorl in Orlando, FL https://t.co/gJ8RjAhU2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXCITING NEWS - #ANewEra - #JonathanStafford &amp; #WendyWhelan Will Lead ⁦@nycballet⁩ - per ⁦@dancemagazine⁩  https://t.co/RJUffS8tCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doomcock @CaptainMabel @DisneyStudios @RandomMnky @JessiMilestone @GospelTha I feel we should spread the word! I’l… https://t.co/n21LYziExI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SampleSays for your amazing @overleahs scholars who came to #OurElmwood today to read to our young schol… https://t.co/ZQ087mKVV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanKnightly Agreed. I'm cool with him being a third pairing d-man in our lineup. Seems like everyone wants to get… https://t.co/xYULvvUgId]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a microwave to remind you that your perception of time is off]]></document><document><![CDATA[La china me mando un audio donde dice “Te amo” 😍🥰 https://t.co/Ew7WbURpKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @RJ_Sproseph! One of the baristas cited your work before I could even tell everyone to read it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some world art I made for a video game. @ Seattle, Washington https://t.co/kMKBXYqUtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesOKeefeIII Sell out  Van Jones drinking Trump turd shake, he is one sick joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TenochHuerta "Somos"? Con tu nombre recortado, Tenochtitlan, me doy cuenta de quien es el Racista.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitjobnews Because it's a five pound note! If it doesn't weigh five pounds... not cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradLow67169907 @Eurotrash007 @StocardApp Google Pay already has this feature to store loyalty cards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not that I care about the Kardashians and their stupid drama BUT I am tired of all the tweets blaming the girl Khlo… https://t.co/8utTxrHjBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anaro74 Si aman a su país, protéjanlo desde ahora, después será muy tarde. Disculpe que me haya atrevido a dar mi opinión en su TL]]></document><document><![CDATA[True athletes love competition and if you think you are the fastest, jump the highest, and the strongest then you h… https://t.co/D7vU7ZBrIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst part of ADHD is losing interest in a project you spent 3 hours on Wikipedia researching]]></document><document><![CDATA[The squad got the “W” today!!! 👀🏈🙌🏽 #Football #Goosey #Besties #LifeIsGood @ Bellarmine Football Field https://t.co/wi6AqcckHu]]></document></documents></author>