<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ChipotleTweets Ummmm but like the world knows Aires doesn't like surprise's. We're very blunt people so there's no… https://t.co/4U4Fz6TuWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QMAYpuuhWE Moscow protesters rally against Russia's 'online Iron Curtain']]></document><document><![CDATA[Great getting to meet and chat with the dean of the soccer media corps, @pkedit. @urichmond alumni gotta stick toge… https://t.co/y5RBd3V9ZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easy Street records Lansing Michigan... @ Southside, Lansing, Michigan https://t.co/xmjCopuYJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner tonight crispy parmesan chicken with garlic herb couscous and lemony roasted carrots ... Ice tea. 🍵 @ Reddin… https://t.co/f66QtBNs2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to this storm my Cruces trip to see @NMStateMBB is cancelled.  I will still cheer you guys on yelling at the… https://t.co/1gZHcTNgnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[reasons I hate myself: “I’ll get in early tomorrow” *sleeps through alarmS* *takes a shower* *lay on bed for 30 min… https://t.co/BKZCh4MOUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 1124 COLONY DR #Quakertown #PA  #realestate https://t.co/04H1Iz2PwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amaristocrat we're speaking to each other in a yeehaw accent from now on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just kicked off "Black Women Writing Black Histories: Uncovering and Narrating the Enslaved Past," ft. my colleague… https://t.co/MCU6WFPgw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what’s annoying about being the planner? People not knowing why planning early is important.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here reminiscing about Luke Perry and @SnuddenChris tells me he never watched 90210. Now I'm just sitting h… https://t.co/UUzaEjupBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine being unable to articulate something that you don't even quite fully understand yourself. in addition, imag… https://t.co/i9zyfOBqVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real girls go fishing!  Learning from the master fisherman.  #baitthathookgirl #catchandrelease #nolucktodaythough… https://t.co/ROBhhsCscE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll head out for noms in a bit, I think, but in the meantime I’m just gonna chill a bit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GAFollowers @GAFolIowers @Yo_bino @ATLUTD The Best!! He's a smart guy 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trbouma We love Boston Terriers! Pugs are the less energetic, likely less intelligent (still cute as heck) version… https://t.co/pWro9pk4pW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like Trump’s base is jumping ship, he’ll still win the election sadly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I came to the conclusion that no matter how hot, tall or big his shit is, if he doesn’t have game, a chick wi… https://t.co/YmAmPuVtsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi So basically our president is a pill popping #junkie https://t.co/wF447KPGaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aeconnelly @wdjordan @wecoalesce @axios @maggieNYT https://t.co/9tCRgKQqfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scenes from the city. Y’all are crazy. #krewedevieux #mardigras2019 @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/PayWAC48Ar]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wore hoop earrings and really felt like the baddest bitch tonight. wow. life changing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yeah... like saying “here, hold this stick of dynamite while I light it. It’ll be ok.... trust me”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Belated Valentine’s Day date in Philly! 💕 Amanda and Ryan, thanks so much for hanging with Link! Now he wants to na… https://t.co/kiaBdqq06x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noble prize is said be suggested by Japan,the possibility is zip,it's not for anything positivr,just a way to strok… https://t.co/Y97Fp1uTc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[At thekfwe from @royalwinecorp, discovered HEEET, the hot #cinnamon (w/ #pepper) #vodka by merrygospirits; organic,… https://t.co/LFAxz5JbWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThankYou to all who care enough about #humanity , about #freedom , about #Venezuela #FueraMaduro #EnoughIsEnough… https://t.co/24jjZ2nCC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtracey Bust a gut. Farrakhan invited a major Holocaust denier to speak at a Nation of Islam event last month in C… https://t.co/PAUJ5BNXMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisRey19 @geegeebythesea Good morning, G. Maybe it's because she was old, cranky and quite the Liberal. Like me..… https://t.co/jEnPv6fUcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CohenCongressionalHearing #CohenHearing #CohenCongressionalTestimony Hey #MarkMeadows what about this time?? It so… https://t.co/KKNLDMVp3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevDead2 @HaveFaithArthur Ashes to ashes.  Dust to dust.  The Rev always gives all he has.  It is a must.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveAndyC Oh DAMN...Nothing like your child trying to set you straight...lol. Been there, done that. I think you a… https://t.co/ASnGl3WUMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crunch crunch creak squeak.  #zoelyla #purplecation2019 #summerplacesinwinter @ Jordan Pond Path https://t.co/Gp7yuUPA4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt Gaetz may be handsome (I don't think so), but he wasn't elected to for that! He was elected to help the consti… https://t.co/gE3hvooU4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samswey @Bakari_Sellers Maybe Dumb Donnie should have smoked marijuana. Whatever it is that he's inhaling is destroying our country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods More waste of money! I wish they would do something constructive with our money! Instead of all thi… https://t.co/SFsbhiRlaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Open your eyes. @GOPLeader is grasping at straws. There are plenty of legitimate is… https://t.co/rGoABf9uq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conforme van pasando los días de la semana se me dificulta más despertarme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations! You are such a beautiful couple. Best wishes for a wonderful life together. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BauerOutage First Tribe Spring training game in AZ.  You are on the mound today!!!  Wahooooo Life is Good!!  Get’e… https://t.co/f3f2C4l7Nt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw #CaptainMarvel Will someone please tell me why the cat scratched his eye? It's bugging the heck out of me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @KrisGorman52000 and @mightyscots! This is awesome. (When my son was at McClintock Mr. Gorman was h… https://t.co/NWZYRammPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Reaction to #TheShield reunion*  🤜🏼👊🏼🤛🏼   @WWERollins @WWERomanReigns #DeanAmbrose   #RAW https://t.co/56JDWTofiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[No way.. this girl just really called campus safety to pick her up from in front of the pool to go to palm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But with no Brenda? Forget it. There is no #90210 without a Dylan AND BRENDA!  Why tho @DohertyShannen??]]></document><document><![CDATA[my Pisces moon is fighting my flighty tears with great fantasies of what CAN be rather than what IS 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earpers NoChill  We still here waiting @SYFY @IDWPublishing fulfill your commitment to #WynonnaEarp and put our cas… https://t.co/7o69TUotSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eight week old Aurea, a Siberian Husky puppy, not to be confused with the Alaskan Husky. She is bi-eyed which means… https://t.co/vg0jXt2B1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did Bill Clinton. lie about where he stored his cigars in the Oval Office?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikaAnderson3 Ok. Personally, I would buy it for my Mom if she needed it and didn’t have the money.   She’s gone… https://t.co/Ue4jYdO94M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Com_Tech1 @NWSTucson Everyone is guided down in a very slow caravan, and headlights are only covered for 1 mile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[CJ majors have such different views on things. Like people want to spit in my face sometimes. But, trust me I’ve co… https://t.co/HUTNGSlVz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only traveling that Trump does is to the donner table, the t.v. room and one of his golf resorts. As far as tra… https://t.co/CzazhKtumm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThrowbackThursday to a year ago, today in #Denver with joser44ramos 💙 #Colorado #DeniseBuddePhotography @ Denver,… https://t.co/6EuPJDUP2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMahurin26 @HeatherKTVU @SomervilleKTVU @VickyNguyenTV @TheEllenShow Wow, let’s do a story about her! 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theipodteacher There are some wonderful read to me books on https://t.co/iULxd5zEqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ibtchwhruvacay @CoffeeLoversPR jamás un químico podrá sustituir un café hecho de grano natural.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roywoodjr @hodgman Trying to imagine the reaction when I  show up at Planet Fitness with a claymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kelli_savannah It used to be, but it now tells the sender when you unsend something! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TereOrt51687394 @PucciaPatrizia @enriqueiglesias @Viviane6677 @ElbaklySami @janaplauen @roberta_lanzoni… https://t.co/9J0ETY48LZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeaTacAirport  this is ridiculous. It’s been +40 mins since landing and still waiting to get to the gate. What is… https://t.co/A5LwC9LSys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HardballChris We missed you Chris!! Phillies got Bryce Harper.... speaking of Hardball!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC To the Green Peace guy. Mini van gets better mileage than a cow or horse drawn carriage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFBKTerriers @NECsports @SFBK_WBB Take care of business today &amp; let’s get ready for Monday! #BrooklynTough]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s qwhite a few people that are showing what really matters to them and in this case it’s shut up and catch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fall TF back. You went from hero to zero in no time. Devin Nunes is a facilitator of treason and will be indicted s… https://t.co/B1Zr66ly2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at all of these positive, uplifting, lunch bags made by our students in their advisory classes! This was an aw… https://t.co/scZPmPK0PS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riding round with my homegirls bumpin oldies. This energy is unmatchable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just going 2b a cow next month....I shouldn't let things bother me, but hey I'm human.....What kind of person wil… https://t.co/DMcyJC6Y6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[stood for 1 hour and 20 minutes outside the door before the doors opened and i didn’t regret any of it 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonicaV_B I'm not trying to be Billy Badass, lol. I'll leave that up to y'all. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Mark Meadows what does it matter that you have relatives of color? You are using them also for your o… https://t.co/TjnPW1pmUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[God can set you free from anything!.. trauma, heartbreak, pain, hurt, fear, failure, mistakes, addictions + more. t… https://t.co/kx0glc938C]]></document><document><![CDATA[was showing Alis grandparents photos of my brothers the grandad swipes to a photo of me n my mum n turns round n go… https://t.co/jC6ExQC72E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate traveling during the day with Cait. She stay up the entire time and ask every 5 min, are we there yet 😭🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Life is a mind game. Push yourself past your mental limits if you want to actually achieve what you thought was impossible.” LH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cerebral Palsy ✅ Wobbly Legs ✅ Heart of Champion ✅ @Huntwallace170 you are everything a parent would want their son… https://t.co/S5r5CfytKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be live tomorrow on the @TubeBuddy channel at 10:00am PST talking about how to spring clean your YouTube chann… https://t.co/K4e4XNB0aE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyYork18 Hi Becky,Would you like to get expensive battery charger case for your iPhone 6 / 6s / 7s / 8swithout… https://t.co/s4S9krd4LQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bill to rezone the area around St. Laurentius in Fishtown has passed in City Council, without opposition. Story t… https://t.co/p2BYg0Fgbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing captures loneliness like sitting in a cold train station by yourself in bumfuck Indiana bcuz ur train is 2 hours late]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WHYWHYWHY #saturdaynight #Taxpayermoney @RealJamesWoods @DiamondandSilk @seanhannity Somebody be accountable for t… https://t.co/xoObAv3KsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lady on the train thought the guy sitting across from her was dead because he wasn’t turning his alarm off. Sh… https://t.co/VrcMFVhXJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @CraigCo62 Only if he gets shanked. He'll be out summer 2020 and helping trump steal the election again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosieBarton Sorry m, “tweaks”?? They need to fire the design firm and start over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to Target for one thing and left with one thing. https://t.co/rixifwImZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Patriots ALWAYS knew that. Could have used those millions spent on Meuller investigation on WALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC wow income equality does that mean we all  get the income that Lawyers get because $15 an hour doesn't pay the… https://t.co/pz8GwxB6iO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KP06108051 @IAmmSlimmm That'll be nice. I'm excited for you just thinking about it.... 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pizzafriday #TQOFE #blogger #writerslife #whatitsliketobeme #lovemyjob #dinneralaDonna @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/gUk0A2veHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then in the gospel, we find again and again the position held by St Peter as the spokesman of the twelve. In utteri… https://t.co/o9pJA0yrA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 @MalcolmNance There is more important things to report on/talk about than the ravings of this malignant narcissist!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to this ICON (18 min too late)   Ps she willing to fight @heathersharp23 https://t.co/IsiOYhvTl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsTeal_Missy This is the positivity we all needed to see today💕 #largeseniorlove]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatSkoor @Jhogan552 These people are not smart.  Or is stone just playing dumb.  I don't think he's sorry either.… https://t.co/gD5QZSIpzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave778967 Go ahead and OPEN THOSE BORDERS WIDE OPEN AND JUST SEE WHAT HAPPENS. I'LL EVEN VOTE FOR IT,CAUSE I WANT… https://t.co/cC5jFR3QRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UnitedStatesVSEngland #WomenSoccer Go USA Go !! https://t.co/5d4S3Q8ql1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate just woke up out of a dead sleep and said “It’s almost Father’s Day.” https://t.co/WcBc9TwupN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Addiction has such a grip that nothing else matters. Addicts love their kids. They need serious intervention and su… https://t.co/CCayOarJCE]]></document></documents></author>