<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[fathers of future presidents (Prescott Bush, Joseph Kennedy) (and grandfathers of future American automobile magnat… https://t.co/16rGk9dy2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaWhitney59 Four multinationals and multiples of his body weight in gold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Thanks for the "Breaking News". Only the 28th time I've seen this in an hour. Keep up the good work, graveyard intern.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very successful day for Elizabeth! Took a bath, went for a walk and of course took plenty of naps. :) jbs1711… https://t.co/ZpOWzyUAXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HyacinthBouKay @h8Wankmaggot45 That is good. Hopefully enough of them jump ship to really make a difference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyWorsham UTenn/UKentucky/LSU Win Out this week....what seed do they get in the NCAA Tourney? Or will the SECT b… https://t.co/7zX1eWYCrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_RodSportsLA @reganteague @SusanChatzky @MattWalshBlog The Bernie Bro left:  this country is so amazing that midd… https://t.co/Uw0qnQGmnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill trump looks like a poor man’s Alphonse Capone. Too bad Alcatraz is closed. https://t.co/AiKwanyPru]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miguel, es el comerciante político más grande que tiene nuestra política, vendió las tres letras, el PRD, el orgull… https://t.co/TY8eFTTK2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ercaaaaa @Krista_Marie86 Last week the Omni in Richmond was..... 🥰 https://t.co/YiEnBITR5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[2005 Malibu! Needs a hub replaced. $1000  #malibu #2005 #drive #buy #takehome #waterloo #pixies @ Wilber Auto Body… https://t.co/l6VA6Q1iUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cali_kiddo @JakeWCTheFirst @BustinArown269 Tried but they have a bad schedule when I’m there. I’ll be in fort Myer… https://t.co/2wMOI26tZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TuesdayThoughts  #TuesdayMotivation  https://t.co/gGEvg1OonM https://t.co/nWf3QtuBxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way techno snobs hate on people that listen to dubstep is pretty wild. It’s not your life why are you so upset… https://t.co/GLTYw6tjfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLdotcom And not losing anything to state taxes, some get Biznasty on the line!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe Charlie Kirk is Skynet, remember it was the Russians who were the first to notice Skynet's awareness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[we all want some humor. #funniness #tee-hee #grin #funny https://t.co/rbmwn7VPa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would’ve been a perfect 5 Tech fit for #Titans up front...Philly continues to reload]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished our first commercial for @4ROceans !! Everyone check it out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and 8 of my closest friends had the most incredible experience at @ScofflawBrewing today ... They are legit AF..… https://t.co/iSLo9FpojV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark your calendars for the 2019 Cardinal Classic Golf Tournament benefiting Jewell Athletics to be held on Monday,… https://t.co/Pq5BKTSjzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intro 2 Autumn Dayze, a song by PhillyBlunt2000 on… https://t.co/iuiUji26cU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn lonzo not even going to get a chance to guide the Lakers into the playoffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[19 years into the new century this is even more important. @ TLGCoaching/Transformative Leadership Group https://t.co/RSwijz0mY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is the OFFICIAL ENTRY LIST for the upcoming weekend events for @NASCAR at @amsupdates in Hampton, GA featuring… https://t.co/tRQvTEdKnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShastaFromNE If he was a gentleman he’d do a load of laundry for you “as a test”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinVizcarraC @PoliciaPeru QUE FUSILEN A LOS CORRUPTOS A LOS SOCIOS DE ODEBRECHT  GRAÑA Y MONTERO QUE NOS ROBARO… https://t.co/Py8pctYaSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeff_deeney @alexhkral Injecting in the neck is more dangerous than injections almost anywhere else on the body.… https://t.co/UA5d2flk0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a vet with partial disability and a lot of records as a result, I’d rather Apple over google build something lik… https://t.co/uH5gQCrfx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I alway enjoy the Polaris Lounge at #EWR.  Well done @united #travel https://t.co/StGioCoDWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t regret loving you, marrying you, and having children with you. . . I regret not realizing I could’ve found… https://t.co/QgkDmmnpRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you saying he’s acting? Whatever it is it worked for Justice Kavanaugh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disturbing / Who thought of using Yellow on jackets of OUTSIDE workers ? The more I see it, the more disturbing I find it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsNadia_Ew I didn’t buy a ticket lmaoo I’m a cheap hoe! I just don’t get why you have to get all uptight over NOTHING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRather What an ignorant woman. I guess Kellyanne told you about alternative science.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fourth morning in a row with below-zero temperatures. This morning was the coldest at minus 5. Hopefully this is it… https://t.co/3OKkvpZpMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billybunzari Slaves basically built the entire place too, import people take there passport off them and give them shitty jobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnpavlovitz @Rosemarie4311 @AOC Kiss my butt. I’m an old, white, male, liberal Democrat. There is danger in stereotyping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao I rarely go now tbh, tonight was the first time I went in a long timee]]></document><document><![CDATA['He Outfoxed Them': Bongino Says Trump 'Owned' Dems in Border Wall Battle https://t.co/T961mXmHim #war]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino The real cause of the brain washing of our children into antifa members has made our children week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_JD3 @tracyguns I’m a fan of steel.. nothing beats the satisfaction of hearing that freedom pellet ring that l… https://t.co/KCyRsDsEJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows @DonaldJTrumpJr Complete A hole , how do we impeach that scum bag?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trojan nation, please welcome @KelseaWinkle to our football staff!! #FightOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Razorsmack1 @pjbowles4 @shell0131 @callawaykeith @DebsSweet @PayItForward213 @StandUpAnne @raducom @J_G_E_O… https://t.co/zVE3R8oP5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[#productivity @ArizonaMonthly @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/j2gSMAyfa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A shameful thing. People of privilege dooming their children to sicknesses that we effectively and safely eliminate… https://t.co/ywWmi3zA1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome back @BGSchools ! Hope everyone  was able to rest and recharge!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little salty language at the bottom, but it does drive the point home, one that should be painfully obvious in to… https://t.co/0bkqjwGW7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder I would never want my child to emulate the Obamas. They are a polarizing family and I would rather my… https://t.co/9lTxAzKose]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylviaEllison @kmurfitt1 @brianrozinsky @jenladd @conniehamilton @EllenFeigGray @LFlemingEDU @Ms_A_Yeh @pammoran… https://t.co/982sPTIVt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I was a dem in the primary trying to separate myself from the pack: 1) Pledge to eliminate spoofed number roboca… https://t.co/pa8T96NoAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonWyden @Mediaite these people lied so much they believe them selves https://t.co/7lHZNdK5OP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well... wanna getaway (@ Chicago Midway International Airport in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/rfu7PElELe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amberindigo How do you remain so thin?  I smell that KitKat and my fat multiplies exponentially.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump is an absolute pig. Nothing he says is to be trusted or believed. Especially for the next 3 days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favs on International Women’s Day and every other day! @ Coconut Joe's Beach Grill https://t.co/VJAE98t8BT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelEMann @dwallacewells @MSNBC @Morning_Joe Well done!  Looking forward to seeing more coverage like this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKGenest Take two aspirin &amp; two Tylenol up to three times a day. Get rid of your pillow and sleep on your back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman @Laurie_David So much more asshole-ish behavior to exhibit, so little time. He was once on PBS expla… https://t.co/bno1fBougb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKGlass @andylassner @JadedCreative He was a big choreographer for nsync and bring spears and a movie director. Wa… https://t.co/9AnYttsA6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comparison changes your FOCUS, and your FOCUS determines your DIRECTION.  • Comparison shifts my focus from the thi… https://t.co/rrrHcPOMgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewLoveVA @DavidWald_VA @marreropatrick @SentaiFilmworks Things must be lookin pretty well huh Isamu?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be the first to earn BAT with Coinbase Earn You are invited to learn about Brave and the Basic Attention Token (BAT… https://t.co/47fpqtNGJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJoeKennedy @AlOtroLado_Org @togetherrising @fams2gether Joe stop supporting murdering the unborn and infanticide]]></document><document><![CDATA[But He would go on. And time and human history are all we can see of that on-going...This is the story in brief tha… https://t.co/xGvVXcR7XM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Soggy Coulter.  Get your thesauruses (thesauri?) out, folks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregbradyTO Hahaha.....Classic!! And Jeff Garlan shows up with a neck brace in the last scene.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@campbellitstrue @wess413 @trudygonzales @eugenegu @realDonaldTrump The issue isn’t petty by a long shot — just his arguments on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASU @Psi_BetaMCC @dpsmccaz we need more advocates! #MentalHealthMatters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joanigerber @MarvelStudios @captainmarvel @Gubs27 @Avengers @CaptainAmerica @Iron_Man @theblackpanther You’ve got… https://t.co/R1ZGj1lZXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously for the #Titans it came down to the money and not the draft picks. Can’t say I blame them.  JRob now must… https://t.co/sSetqOTD8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Said a liar, representing a liar who hired the liar that they are accusing of being a liar peddling lies.  Ugh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @AkronWineGuru @magee333 @ccatmpt @SLBriscoe @thatsVeryKari @Cbp8Cindy @suziday123 @cowineco… https://t.co/1cPm9M0Cq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank u, next is knowing bad idea is your favorite but buying NASA gear in Urban Outfitters in DC while humming 7 r… https://t.co/JTIKF9C7HR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZackRepEM @EMEducation Your point is valid, but the goals are connected. Halo Effects can ruin honest assignments for the smart ones, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbariankb @trinitykstudio Newspapers in the U.S. were paying freelance writters 10 cents a word in the 70s. 4 cents is ludicrous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHaleyBaby Racket ball nothing better the beating the hell out of that little blue ball to let off steam and work through things]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirmaEspn Hola vikingo, como te sientes, que le pasó al mejor equipo de la década,  jajajajajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanmarti18 Is it really as good as people say it is? I never tried it before and I always feel douchy when I consider ordering it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karunchandhok How much does testing actually cost? Seems that teams getting minimum 50 mil from the sport can affo… https://t.co/xBgus5q1bD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosLoret @lopezdoriga @CiroGomezL @VictorMendozaL @elalbertomedina @feroropeza20 @elchiltepin @michelleriveraa… https://t.co/VOHFz1OWKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is somehow pandering to black people harder than Clinton, which I thought was impossible.  If I ran for office,… https://t.co/JC48IQDS6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rj112712 @gabe_prewitt @IsleCasinoPP Good luck Robert. Really was hoping Sgt Papa Daddy got up to win]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 Illegal use of the hands? How much community service will that bring?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished filming the weirdest competition ever; uber stoked to spend the next 2 months logging + transcribing. . .… https://t.co/KcweTkP3ru]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently snowing this fast per minute in Marion #mawx https://t.co/giZWqTP2S6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus..., get this, Jussie Smollett is the Nephew of Kamala Harris! Right, Democrat Kamala Harris! I wonder who put… https://t.co/2goGeBWGD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HJPreller @bcline760 @thestevenwoods @leisurefriar @MLBONFOX @fenwaypark @RedSox I went two summers ago. While the… https://t.co/T6KKjSwVaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee really needs to look into this fine organization. @HLERadio is the real deal.… https://t.co/Vcq0owuOJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren I see you.need  your safe space to tweet this....because you never have the balls to deal with the public...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, which happens to be my birthday, is also the first day @bryceharper3 steps to the plate as a member of the… https://t.co/2paMQqp8Qq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bserviss8229 Dobson isn't Brannstrom. Brannstrom is a slight bit better. The team is still growing internally and… https://t.co/MwwNswI3DO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerSaunders @KishoneRoy @LandlordRescue @cryptomarkets2 @416_Perp @REWoman @brad_barrett @catosletters… https://t.co/rO24RUVc8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib almost made @MarkMeadows cry and just for that I donated to her re-election fund]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Transformation❤️TODAY! 🏆FREE Weight Loss Seminar: Tuesday February 19th 2019, 6:00 PM. Hawthorn Suites Mc… https://t.co/HIWoosHZ01]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't miss the Comics Battle tonight at 9:00 at the @alexispark! 4 hilarious comics will hit the stage at the same… https://t.co/QADkoq8Xr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davereaboi @SebGorka Living near New Madrid fault I have taught my kids that everything could change in a minute,… https://t.co/RPd9OILrr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I den picked on sum Louisiana mac, Ima see what it’s hitting for all week 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude should be arrested for filing a false report, and be fined for all the time wasted on investigating this hoax.]]></document></documents></author>