<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[FDLA shows experience! Get your tickets today!  Go to https://t.co/VwHGMdCaQu  . NYFW is around the corner again  D… https://t.co/W9G7RLdAND]]></document><document><![CDATA[You females be full of drama and be wondering why yo relationship don’t work 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yosemite Raven at Degnan’s #raven #winter #yosemitenationalpark #yosemite #yosemitenps #yosemitevalley #YOSE… https://t.co/s3TpADGYdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun walk down memory lane nonetheless. Charlotte Sports Park was a total white elephant back then and it really loo… https://t.co/bCYRxgfTUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garrettlittlegd @TheMikeBaldwin Agreed. Kinda like the old time paint stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchellTsudama @GillYama Wow you saw right through me...God is that you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gestern war eines der Tage wo ich dachte, warum machst du das, 250kg Schaltschrank auf 6m Höhe montiert, 3 Leute, u… https://t.co/aF0rW66q49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 @IlhanMN One doesn't have to always say what one thinks .  Often times , we are our worst enemy .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stow_bb Keep up the teamwork and great things will happen.  Trust your teammates @lexpetit3 @Eandrassy15 @StefanovLizzy @LileeCarlson]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, Senator, that would be directly unconstitutional. A national emergency declaration, of which there are 30 curre… https://t.co/SabTrc9ySd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s WVU and I know we’re at home, but the vibe for this team sure does full different today. #kubball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cpk_diecast I noticed that prices for shipping were going up too. I'm trying to make a decent profit off of diecas… https://t.co/XaWHtLQ9Cg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well mom hands down wok on the best gift ever. Teddy bear made out of one of Blains shirts. The same one in the pic… https://t.co/3dgoaO6ypV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllenTStClair @silvie1111 @missmikkinoble @_carmenadams_ @JessShaut @sbaileyauthor @RH_Author @WillmoreLauren… https://t.co/Mv0oAjF8ua]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s dark. It’s quiet. We aren’t at a station. And it’s not moving. I think this is how horror movies start. #MBTA https://t.co/yShjBs4kWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Time!!!! #kombatkast #Jade   Side note: this current music is incredible. @MortalKombat https://t.co/ZVuNwh9kgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gaying up Universal Studios for the day krp489 . #gay #universalstudios #wizardingworldofharrypotter #allthesekids… https://t.co/QUtbaB0apH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TRAFFIC ALERT: CONSTABLES ARE WORKING A MAJOR VEHICLE CRASH IN THE 18900 BLOCK OF TOWN CENTER BLVD/ E FM 1960. EAS… https://t.co/gGIPPJ4wLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josevalgut pero si ya hicimos un Mundial sub17 y no habia ningun requerimiento. Ese tipo no sabe nada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoMexicans @juan_the_bean Props for him standing up and protecting his teacher 😤👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disgusting cretins. Let’s stay in the EU and evict these arseholes from Britain #brexit #YellowVests]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDeedles @AOC @RepSwalwell @tedlieu @RepAdamSchiff @KamalaHarris @MarkWarner @SpeakerPelosi Nazis shoved Jews i… https://t.co/9nzLbDJNkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bmerino_ The spread in basketball has make grown men cry around the world lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved that country duo on @TheAcademy #AcademyAwards2019 — what was that.. That was so sweet..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComicCrusaders he was really good in the #GoodnightForJustice westerns.... #RIPLukePerry  #LukePerry #Westerns https://t.co/fC0vX7dC6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concerns being voiced by committee members about issues that may stem from an Equal Rights Amendment. Several Repub… https://t.co/P73oLoFnlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Kenions...  Look, It's YouTube personality, Ken "Geek Demon"  Bouchard!  #TKBOS #WTS #geekofalltrades #Kenions… https://t.co/S16YzhLsXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it! @sxsw #cwdaretodefy #crazyexgirlfriend #sxsw @vrodrigueziii panel today at 3:30! @ Downtown Austin, Tex… https://t.co/prjGaj9TZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Tuesday Night.  #photographyoftheday #photographyaddict #photographynature #photographyblog #photography… https://t.co/WFe3vjHgOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to my Beautiful Ray of Sunshine. @ Brentwood, Tennessee https://t.co/kcIB2nBr0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deerhoof &amp; Tigue! (@ Merkin Concert Hall in New York, NY w/ @emyeags) https://t.co/G4DVyArZ2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you driven and motivated? Does uncapped earning potential interest you? Do you thrive in a competitive environm… https://t.co/ZlgfQWVLM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jack__XOS @Coach_Shideler @Coach_Elby A possibility. But I would still move the F across and run an rpo if so.  Ex… https://t.co/oV7hRPS2ib]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Doobie Brothers - It Keeps You Runnin' (1977) https://t.co/dciNbi5JK9 via @YouTube great song.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the answers right in front of my face of how to get my family back but my dumbass lets myself overthink and… https://t.co/Vu57Q60tVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[No le voy a tener compasión "Le voy a arrancar la cabeza" esos si eran peleadores y no chingaderas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An incredible man, give him the job #OleOleOleOle #OlesAtTheWheel #united]]></document><document><![CDATA[@googlenews @LEX18News any updates on the truck fire at the #Lexington Gas Station? Everyone alright?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamkevingates has a new song out with juicy J and now I need more music, Kevin. Get to the studio 😂 🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hunter_James33 I’m extremely happy about it. February is the worst month of the year]]></document><document><![CDATA[US Olympic cyclist Kelly Catlin has died at the age of 23  https://t.co/14W1XVhHsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do most of my mayhem and shinnanagins on Facebook  until this world reacts to me more lol I do want a celebrity friend tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessTurnerCRU @NPR @MarketUrbanism They’re not even claiming white folks are *causing* pollution or shoving it int… https://t.co/87eAfk53dK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SabearcatNathan @DarkRefreshment @Jacobonaut @BryanMinehart @yarmiganosca @teb_art @AOC And that is the problem a corrupted court system]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GailSimone I think he's best used as a foil to an existing hero to ask all those "how much is too much?" questions… https://t.co/6qfWY8cgex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilypetterson @madeline_down Sold, though to be clear, Emily's cut doesn't come out of my 20 percent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all gotta learn to live without your phones for a little. at least an hour a day or something]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza During this period, the Democratic Party controlled state legislatures; most local and state office h… https://t.co/eoqyXmcc7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylon_ray I’m not saying he was bad for the party’s ideology, I’m glad he dragged it left. But he also riled up a… https://t.co/90fLBTBK7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 34 more days till we hit the ground running in 2019!!! #dirtlatemodel #teamkryptonite https://t.co/NcLqIUNLje]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband loves shopping for our daughter #ColleenCoco at @happyhannas  😍 #lifeasleo #Leonardodalmagro… https://t.co/11m7UHifvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gleeunion. New Orleans style. 🙌🏻❤️ 🎺🎷🍤 @ New Orleans Museum of Art https://t.co/jHbaHgvpJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @ufc is next level disrespectful. @TonyFergusonXT has earned the right to fight for the strap! Tony vs Khabib https://t.co/FNiF6HVkhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't get me wrong, I like modern praise and worship but there is just something about classic hymns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritYah 3) And again you like to use a tactic: "the same thing you accuse me of i will put on you!" You do this… https://t.co/D6y8q1ZH9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycSassenach @ursusdesertimus Thank you. You really are my biggest fan and I truly appreciate you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spy three of these bad boys at the show tonight. Love y'all https://t.co/GSw4nQ15sp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaraGay @jbouie Try re-reading the Constitution instead of rewriting it ...and then memorize it.  ~Diamond &amp; Silk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I burnt something but the wind keeps slamming my windows shut - Now What]]></document><document><![CDATA[Testing ... Testing ...  @Ava @Oprah @QSWriters @QueenSugarOWN https://t.co/0pToNTFOYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @SpikeLee (get_repost) ・・・ Brooklyn Wins @ New York, New York https://t.co/zArOr5erY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Rewrite the Stars.” Part 2 @tlcat06 @starwarsromance https://t.co/wx0KGIQqkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indígena y calavera, graffiti en Santa Catarina.   #graffiti #indigena #skeleton #esqueleto #calavera #streetart… https://t.co/2TwPHiDl4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrspearing I suppose you would say YOU didn’t do it. But we should assume you are guilty, because anyone in the ci… https://t.co/d0xCiF3lC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichHomieJuice Bills are actually built for a better situation top 5 defense solid Young qb in Allen and if they c… https://t.co/P5oFJgA03k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy B-Day #smite fans, you gotta see this. So epic. 🌹 What is Love (Cover) 🌹 https://t.co/bAWKWcHhb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump All your friends are going to prison. Getting worried for you and your kids?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donwinslow Don, I love the new book. And for a brief time...probably very brief, I am #35 on Amazon and #4 on Thri… https://t.co/TUaPvCXT9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @CodesTrump @Jeanleonetti1 @CommonCause @joncoopertweets @wikileaks @Snowden @RIPsethRich @FBI @DNC… https://t.co/p1FjkH36eD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juha_the_Great @Ajatar71 Understood.... Easy to say, harder to do. But, it is a must. In God We Trust https://t.co/wa1gAMfZ43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonasigo Jajajaja Luego luego la agresión !!  Mira el lado bueno del comentario que todo el estadio lleno apoyará como antes]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODAY - BOYS 1st REGION CHAMPIONSHIP. (24-7) Mayfield vs (31-3) McCracken County. You won’t want to miss it.  📍 CFS… https://t.co/XwDSP2HlGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissainJax @rick_mullaney @DanielSCronrath Still waiting for... https://t.co/FEE5UNtTy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s the bunt!!! Way to go Keaton Weisz! #RoostersWhoRake Bases loaded! 0 outs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Divine_knives Haha I haven’t decided yet ... they both make good points 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanFonsecaNY If they split with Xavier and beat DePaul they should be fine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a yearly pre ordered (if that’s a thing) and a #MNTwins fan. I would like to see @toriihunter48 or Kirby Puckett… https://t.co/Lq4OH9pxW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Gilbert Tigers come back to win the championship, 38-37. https://t.co/odfQRPHG1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PokerCentral Will there be any live updates of the US Poker Open besides @PokerGo Final Table streams?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1c3p1ckL0b0t0my @BuffaloSabres You can teach her about hockey rage. How did it go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anonbinary @TulsiGabbard Are you gay? If not, stop talking. Are you Hawaiian? Did you bury your Hawaiian friends b… https://t.co/Yx5tzxG2zb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musiccharleston You should come to a wedding when its Philadelphia based couple! Oh my god! Its off the chain]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s what I meant. Don’t care about sharing the title. I’ll take it. Purdue having a shot is a joke. Only played… https://t.co/jAnVgoXKFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aleris is looking for teammates like you. See our latest #Sales job openings, including "Claims Analyst (Customer S… https://t.co/xAgsoUU6vG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertOrtegaES1 ¿Para cuando multa al Barça por las pancartas politicas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have got to start saving my money it’s a damn shame how bad I’ve gotten with this spending]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marypcbuk @nickromyn Yeah, it’s me being not helicopter parent but very protective and knowing the harm that can come from such activities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think @PlayApex needs an actual training mode where we can practice specific characters + weapons, but I have no… https://t.co/j0BeRY1ibh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t swipe up and respond to your Instagram stories, we’re not friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninahawk_nani @mmpadellan @DaisyVivaldi @AnnCoulter I have an idea! Instead of focusing on the $5 billion or so Tr… https://t.co/mHsYoWqXnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edolnx Wait, really?  Okay, reviews say if you liked the first two you’ll enjoy this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 Marketing Trends Guaranteed to Shake Up Social Media by @NikkiElizDemere https://t.co/dxJs2dDdYb via @B2Community]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh how I wish the nearest @Skyline_Chili was not across the bay... come to Tampa!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daniel Sloss’s X ... bloody brilliant ... @ SoHo Playhouse https://t.co/x1XZrPMTgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBechard I'd say the Ig Nobel is more appropriate, but he doesn't really make us laugh at all, either.  https://t.co/cu40gMnKMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come support @ESU_AKL on Sunday March 3rd at your favorite local pizza buffet! https://t.co/28nMOyH5he]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @HosteriaRomana in Miami Beach, FL w/ @maggielevine https://t.co/Is71tcuqoZ https://t.co/Mace0EtpZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_dam_Aguado @NHLFlyers Cause we're still playing a hockey game? Pretty easy concept to understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Dance basics become coding basics!” @HF_HITLab #STEAMShop2019 #BlackGirlsSTEAM @excitecenter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaf84 @CoachNRizzo @CoachMattConti1 No problem. My way isn’t the way for everyone. But there are loads of kids wh… https://t.co/X3tFPdCLJF]]></document></documents></author>