<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#duck #waterbird #bird #swfl #fortmyers #florida #swflphotographer #photographer #photography #wildlife… https://t.co/jERpuxGfPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lno09281978 @JeremyGregoret1 @ByCharlieRicker @MsAFromBK @JustPlainT @rob_gregoretti @DragonMom98 @SabreKevin1639… https://t.co/XZ9DObX7XI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hackr04 @p4rzival0ne @Pwn20wnd @iBSparkes I didn’t say he had to and I have said thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get home and have a huge headache from everything that’s happened lately and have no Advil PM left https://t.co/s37cJjxQq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A year ago...My bro Rick Lepire painted this pix of Sheena...We love it and have it hanging in our kitchen now ...😎… https://t.co/ZbnyfLVfff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Yesterday's hearing demonstrated conclusively that you and your staff are consummate professionals prepared to… https://t.co/gl4UNa3C8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[3. Israel has extraordinary leverage in Congress, because of the evangelical vote among other reasons. Proof? Durin… https://t.co/RXVU2fuMfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FallAgainMJ She is a typical phony ass white liberal. White Liberal women like her  can be more dangerous than the… https://t.co/8ot2xPKxHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[But if you do not do so, then take note, you have sinned against the  Lord; and be sure your sin will find you out. Numbers 32:23]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun! Vibrant! Natural! Get the Hair you want with no damage! Paris Wigs and Extensions. 480-758-5185 @ Paris Wigs a… https://t.co/qxHcz6iH4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teejay3232 McDonalds was one of my first jobs!  Great experience that led to more experience and higher wages.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcchicago I'll bet the Milwaukee Police Chief is thrilled to learn that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should only post pictures of the sky from now on. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/MmI6vRE7H2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A gorgeous group of student work! Showcasing what is beautiful about winter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ni el muro de berlin, he dicho, y si m la hacen de p2 hagan fila jejejeje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Data can be a weapon or an albatross depending how it’s taken. #abm #results]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @johnfel202 @intelligent50 @alllibertynews @Ltdsoltd @Birdseye1 @SSG_Davis_Ret @TresaBridges… https://t.co/xIu2f8i2Wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UsmanButtPTI @Victor_ighoo @ilcano22 Certainly Jorginho deserves criticism but judging him on assists shows a comp… https://t.co/ZdLkeiFTfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for some #storytime with @stevenrinella and the @meateatertv crew.  Bummed the hats sold out before I could g… https://t.co/huafjiCLal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drina12 @tscribner @james_bourned @RealCandaceO @realDonaldTrump Putting salt on slugs is exceedingly cruel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Imamofpeace Tell him to relocate to Mecca and take Rob Emanuel with him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really excited to see MLB #1 prospect Vladimir Guerrero Jr. play third base today for the Jays. He is right in fron… https://t.co/DTqU0YOe0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is coming.  #ontheroadagain @ Chattanooga, Tennessee https://t.co/ANxzO3jL1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@instituteofplay The webinar won’t load! Help, I’m missing all the good stuff!]]></document><document><![CDATA[a male writer: Ah yes. What women love most of all... is you sniffing her personal affects. why are you dialing sec… https://t.co/1JCpbMEEsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vladimirpadrino Se nota!!! ¿Ustedes no son los encargados de la protección del sistema eléctrico venezolano? Porqu… https://t.co/wigz9l7kYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattowanHP @BobbyGavin @mmpadellan @IlhanMN Watch the YouTube clip again.  Bigotry 101.  Nothing the Big 3 have do… https://t.co/q1U4i6iuR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wen we on I ain’t finna fw nun of ya other rappers ya fu as fuck 💯😭🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougblandry @mikehtrujillo @AdvanceGuyNotes @GregHale1 1,350?!? Good lord that's a lot of per diems...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SierraTufts @nicholasweather No shame. Just surprised. https://t.co/1jfN4ErxEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magnolia hits a 3 to beat the buzzer and they hold a 57-47 lead over Mills headed into the 4thQ @THV11 #PrepsOn11]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a Sunday night. First, we saw #GreenBookMovie which absolutely deserved its #Oscars (Best Pic, Best Supporting… https://t.co/G3Zieg8Cvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ll almost always catch us in the studio setting #diamonds in #gold #grillz when you send a #DM. Get yours today… https://t.co/C5aWw6Kste]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OVVikings I won’t ever forget that ride to otselic valley! Always seemed like it took forever!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[as we head into previews and opening on Thursday, I find myself wildly emotional at the end of each performance—the… https://t.co/K7lPeakZP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenIgoe So when is this young talent going to equal a winning program]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaHaspell1 Be very Careful With HGH at $ 25O Rubens a Vile. Out of Sweden.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMandOscar so i want a remake of the 1992 film, Death Becomes Her with Emily Blunt (Meryl) and Emma Stone (Goldie) !! what y’all think]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @AnnCoulter I just want to ask her. Would she rather  that Hillary would have won ? Seriously. Does he… https://t.co/PK9j4xMs4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes!!!! live science, https://t.co/3X9CWUe7ZZ and the other Future plc properties are unionizing with @WGAEast. nic… https://t.co/wTzbrNPPrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The FBI continues to investigate Trump’s collusion with Russia. Can the FBI be so lost on the track? They can ask a… https://t.co/vV1Tbwby1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VaughnHillyard @stacyfmitchell For those in Iowa who are sick of being screwed by the Right, now you have a chance… https://t.co/T65ZlrBdU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsJayLee22 @15and9smom @beckresc @indomituslifts @LuAnn_1970 @OSUmommaDOC @BrienneOfKitty @d_me_and_d… https://t.co/E3mP4eGPxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlainRayes Parles en au JDQ...pour eux, c'est Cohen l'histoire de l'heure...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc how this sounds but my woman and I cannot have the same looking nails]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoghornBLeghorn @awstar11 @The_Petrichory Either Jesus is wearing sunglasses or that’s the fourth member of ZZ Top.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's a wrap from San Francisco #Unpacked2019! https://t.co/69IYblQFwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkTaylorNBC4 @worldmarket Go easy on the statement pieces and go directly to the food section for the kickass spicy ginger ale!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz innocent people don’t “dip their toe” into situations like this.  Just heard that now YOU ARE under investigation 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterHoskinsTV At the rate we're going by 2050 there'll only be 8 gigantic corporations left to do business with e… https://t.co/sehhGcWimD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anything more “dude” than playing the air drums to “In the Air Tonight” by Phil Collins?  I’m gonna hang up and listen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danny_Quest_215 @Crazeydeafgal @Darthbaxter @MattWalshBlog Dude. Excellent 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the Hustle  #FujiXT3 35mm-1/60@ƒ/1.4-ISO640 #Candid #streetphotography #child #sleep #Fujifilm… https://t.co/qEyeBvm8Wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This photo from Oscars 2019 says so much.  We are here. #asiansinhollywood  👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾💜💜💜‼️‼️‼️👊🏾👊🏾👊🏾 #onward… https://t.co/UncQIscs5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieTrunk Did you see Queensryche's post about Pledge Music? Definitely a big story. Can't wait to hear your thoughts...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upset. I got upset when I ate them leftovers for breakfast. I couldn't even count the look on my face before. I hit… https://t.co/opyOSyYrWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Where’s the liberal outrage over this crime that was driven by creed and hatred?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylehillman @mdoukmas In any event it looks like I have some more research to do. Thanks again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to the @CAGOP meetings in Sacramento ( as an observer) but 🙏🏼 for a @millanpatterson #win for CHAIR !]]></document><document><![CDATA[The artichoke plant is a perennial thistle originated in the Mediterranean, producing up to 20 artichokes per year!… https://t.co/8JmnsECCn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[E7 | @brendan_beck3 trots out for the eighth, career-high 7 IP already in the books. 🌲: 0 🤘: 0  #GoStanford]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister Funny that they did so almost immediately after he made the remark. Joking, my ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHROpinion @NHFDRicci @nhregister Didn’t know you were such an expert on 9/11 and the VCF Frank]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimmaicutler Yes, but this is pretty divorced from the scenario in the original post. In 2009, it was a statewide… https://t.co/J9bfRqVNcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[After rewatching #BullDurham, I’m disappointed the 1980s didn’t give us a “Showtime Lakers” move with Tim Robbins p… https://t.co/wIHM54z14q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier at work couple of my employees came to me nervous they were gonna get fired lol I’m not firing anyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexHolleyFOX29 Yes, when the two Harry Potter lands opened, you needed to have a reserved time to come back into the land in the beginning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying 🙏 is always the best answer/Solution! He will hear you and answer your prayers! God works in mysterious way… https://t.co/XuJBqzJgjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@edis knows that we are better when more women are involved in decision making.We also know that there aren’t enou… https://t.co/WvP8BtbIfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1070thefan @DanBart4 Kraft just needed relief... https://t.co/EM2h4UHNtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennJacobsTN @amazon @JeffBezos See if @VinceMcMahon has a connection to get you an opportunity to be heard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si hay final regia en la #SCCL2019 en que estadio sería el juego de vuelta? @SancadillaNorte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@incoduce @showupforthis Happy early birthday wishes! Hope you and Mariah own the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This can’t be any truer❗️With that said, CALL ME‼️I would love to chat 💭 • • 👔 Brandon Mondido 🙋🏻‍♂️ Your Favorite… https://t.co/gOXVjEosZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔴LIVE: President Donald Trump URGENT Speech to Venezuelan American Commu... https://t.co/qk2pjIpfDy via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahn on Machado: "We try to be disciplined with our focus. We tried not to spend too much time trolling around Inst… https://t.co/rYMipjmT3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosedixontx @SavingMinnesota @AOC He rhetoric rapes my Logical mind! I won’t sit and listen! I’m standing tall. Fighting back with Truth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcblackrob It’s a trait I could use when somebody brings up Sugar Ray.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As always, if everyone took one giant step backwards, everyone would get their bags quicker. https://t.co/ftWOReVOrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This $BA $ALK air biofuel  announcement I think pertains to $GEVO don't quote me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JHowardBrainMD I’m sure there’s merit to being there but I find it interesting that they poison your G.I. tract an… https://t.co/0jWLjGjj41]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got stuck in the snow last night driving back from a friends. Within 10 minutes I had 8 people helping me dig my ca… https://t.co/X1srqfaPud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drew_Davis32 He’s doing it and I’m taking it to the bank. Brooks is thiccc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DragonsWizdom @Giants2019 @TheNonsense44 @mrchris172 @DoughboyFresshh @UncleGusNyc 😭😭😭 you think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we learned from the #Packers at the #NFLCombine today:  1. Gutey and LaFleur are working together to find the… https://t.co/h7hm8z0xHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyengineer @sqlstudent144 If blaming the database Is where you start Then writing software code Must be close to your heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScrewedHumans @Distinct_Words I guess it's ok win an election then go on national TV and speak nonsense without an… https://t.co/fPlHDIpw2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctor @20c109 Until another level is gained they can't wear the other jacket in their inventory with a higher cold… https://t.co/Lm9jcI5tlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does activism mean to you?   Learn the history behind @johnlennon @yokoono's bed-in and what #lennonbus is doi… https://t.co/4jY9g2NegI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Why do I want this? I want to make bank bro, I want to get ass, I want to drive a Range Rover”]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For a great door and effectual is opened unto me, and there are many adversaries.” 1 Corinthians 16:9 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 3: Latin Academy leads O’Bryant 47-22. Fiona Mannion 22 points for BLA, and Jordan Bellot has 11 points and 6… https://t.co/uFpKQfWFNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chiefchuck2k Uncommon people are by far the most interesting.   And they are often misunderstood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThoseMeddlingKids found out Ralph Northam's plot. https://t.co/d7SUp0Ljj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adrelthi @dataspot1701d @TeltheTrekkie I liked Jungle Book, except for Christopher Walken’s singing.  Alice In Won… https://t.co/GWp7lhE8ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brian_Haenchen @thesummitleague @SDCoyotesMBB @GoJacksMBB You work too hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best background ever @MarvelStudios @brielarson @captainmarvel https://t.co/XyRu821lxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angelina Meola finished the season with 651 points. I don't know what the Iroquois girls basketball record is, but… https://t.co/reDuv38moQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWil_AU @flippedhatnupe This account that I flagged had over 5 Million interactions operation under ADOS according… https://t.co/Lb3iTUqG4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crafting some #interiordetails as the #DonleyResidence project continues to progress.  The Clients asked for a full… https://t.co/0N4PHPl5u6]]></document></documents></author>