<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@OfficeOfMike @NevadaJack2 He just needs to tweet He enjoyed Tucker tonight 😉  @realDonaldTrump  @DonaldJTrumpJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latina Leaders of Solano County Video #kristianmedinadocumentary #latinaleaders #solanocounty #leadership… https://t.co/n5sgYWRsgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Malcolm X Biography for Kids: Black History Month for Children (Educatio... https://t.co/zA1my5Gdzk via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlecCurrier @MaryMiggins1 Document was agreement between Trump and Stormy signed by both parties. #Aveneti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters Oh please.   Just words.  Totally disband the whole fking religion.  So sick of men using power to exploit… https://t.co/0yzqrHfWxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my cuz chilling on the Bay boat cruise! #black #oakland #blackfilm #youtube #femalerapper #neosoul #hiphop… https://t.co/0JZFyir1k3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martindsouza @fuzziebrain @devnexus Yes please! Not sure if I’m going but I bet I could recruit someone from YCC t… https://t.co/wwGA7eIFES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being able to explore new possibilities &amp; #goals today is my #SundayFunday!📒🖊 #goalsetting 📚 👩‍💻 #HappyMe =happy life!🍵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diggymoreland I am going to need you to get me through the next two nights. This season has been too much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great tool for a lesson on inferencing! I’ve used magazine pictures glued into construction paper as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RikRankin If you can make it through the pass... #LakeTahoe is gorgeous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bmarch63 Marshy. We ❤️❤️❤️❤️you!!! I don’t care about anyone else when I say you are the little ball of hate for a… https://t.co/NrjWWEg9q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙🍼❤️👶🏼🖤 #babyonealcomingsoon2019 #maternitypics @ Holliday, Texas https://t.co/tiUPg5v3fk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hire back whoever did y’alls makeup at viceland because this ain’t it 😪 @DesusandMeroVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m literally getting my two of my friends to give me a wake up call so i can take a test for a class i never go to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza I’m telling ya. The left would love NK to nuke us so the can blame Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw She’s a blond.  Donnyjohn likes blonds. Qualified. https://t.co/x20I8MHiFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry One would hope that “we” wouldn’t vote for the establishment again. Some of us aren’t that smart! Apparently!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mind you drastic to me is like cutting it up to my shoulders or putting color in it. I’m so vanilla lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr I called this , and everyone said ohhh noway ....lmao , he better be charged with a HATE Crime !!!!… https://t.co/hNO7ij41Rk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoFrechette Oui, je l'avais essayé deux fois et c'était dans ma liste d'achats futurs. 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aramaithea @9975Ts Muslims are not allowed to hold Office or to stay in this Country permanently. That Resolution… https://t.co/Hop1gwLcrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lilokus0069 @M4AllNann It happens. :) He didn't understand what happened. Thanks for the response.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@getLauchlan Excited for the future. 😊📈 #ThinkPartner #DigitalMarketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Что Случилось в бассейне? Катя проучила брата! What happened in the pool смешное видео Мы семья https://t.co/R0mjZePmzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woohoo!  I’m so excited for today!  I’m inviting everyone in my community (that includes you) to take the next step… https://t.co/KF2BFFhnHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moría por mariscos, aguachiles o algo así y lo más parecido que comí fueron pepinos con gotitas de limón ☹️, odio estar enferma 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElJefeBanos @ClubAmerica @DiegoLainez10 Lainez es un super jugador Juega con pasión eh instinto como ya muchos no lo hacen!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I learned half my random fact knowledge because I would watch jeopardy after school with my gram, learn som… https://t.co/v1YEvg7jfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any chance you’ve moved on from the Gaga/Bradley performance yet? Yeah me neither 😍💯 https://t.co/wo8X61uwpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like @jamieleefinch would be proud about the fact that I listened to my body when she said, “were not ready… https://t.co/1aRWfddVln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has a Mediterranean flare I like, this is 1 of my favorites Listening to En Algun Lugar by @duncandhu on… https://t.co/IhiivwCZmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[To say I’m excited it’s #NationalMargaritaDay is a slight understatement 💃🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me voy, para luchar por todo. A veces así pasa, tienes que alejarte de las bases de tu vida, para reencontrarte con… https://t.co/BbS9SBCjCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pocs80 Hello there I hope you're doing well I'me glad that  you liked the picture of my dad and also what I said a… https://t.co/1bf9Xq5rBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy happy birthday brother😻😻 I hope today is the best!! Miss you lots💙 ily @MarkSexton30 https://t.co/qk7SJiiJuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICE REPORT: Check out the ice dripping off the trees in Harrison, AR last night! 📸: Ellen Muncy #arwx #kolr10wx… https://t.co/J3xdYsK5am]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really just can't not bust my ass at work tbh. I like when people depend on me. I like being the first person peo… https://t.co/5wqz0P0e0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ellen92553170 @AppSame @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett I haven’t heard Anything about that. What’s this lieutenants name?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an amazing day today with my family. Had the chance to get outdoors and spend some time with natures beautiful… https://t.co/Q8hCdT5etA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentines Mood always #wcw😍 with these baddies and some LA forecast for ya💦  🔥 briannapavon rubypappan cherryboomb… https://t.co/A3odwip5w1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerontheair Loved hearing that On Golden Pond memory You have had a busy week and weekend. Difficult to take the… https://t.co/5CIGPqnXSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kawy @courtneymilan @herhandsmyhands @theknot I am super confused...is this...a novel? Or some kind of memoir? The… https://t.co/jGwiXITkDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today there were some lucky winners during breakfast at Brook Avenue School. Students were treated to a special bre… https://t.co/6rjJRa5q2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bsw5020 @AmericanAir @warlickswarrior Not speaking for either, but the aviation industry has been extraordinary su… https://t.co/4gnf2J4BFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's FINALLY starting to warm up outside, but snowy sidewalks are still a pain for those walking around.   So what… https://t.co/KaTn0LCrTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MyPillow do not buy anymore of his pillows @boycottmypillow he needs to realize that America doesnt support him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Janice4Brexit Harry doesn't seem able to control her. No class or dignity - she should keep her nose out of British politics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nywolforg @JohnEMarriott such sick S.O.B's. they probably lured the poor creatures. Someday, they will get theirs.… https://t.co/DaKBHNJODC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok this wind is super annoying but also I slept SO well last night listening to it 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking on ☁️9️⃣ today after finding out I’m a nominee for @hercampus Beauty Influencer of the Year 🥇😭🎉 I am kinda… https://t.co/YkLwbiJwO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up this morning and started shouting Good Morning @maddav343 start of soccer season! 1 week until you turn 16… https://t.co/QRzkDDQ9Be]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveHammActor Excellent Steve! Congrats to her and you for being supportive!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[General Secretary Marshall Jarvis delivers his final report, setting the stage for what the future holds. Thank you… https://t.co/dSqyz0KLeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's funniness all around us. #hilarity #snicker #smile #merry https://t.co/EXyeZiHjjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ocpsPL administrators deepening their learning about how to support new teachers in OCPS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJenniMurphy @lucastill @JustinHires @Trizzio @MerEaton @PLenkov @CO_MacGyver @rjallain @MacGyverCBS AAAwwww!!How nice.:-D]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's humor all around us. English Bulldog Birthday Card Card 26 / by BulldogGreetingCards, $3.00 #hilarity… https://t.co/rW5vwQ1XYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh, I'm very tempted in accepting CSUSB offer and moving to San Bernardino. I can't continue living here. It reall… https://t.co/Q9B81UmUCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[She can’t get enough. #snowangel #rescuedrottie #bigheadbigheart @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/aSrA0PeJzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um yes hi, I need the Norvina palette. @norvina1 🙋🏽‍♀️🙋🏽‍♀️🙋🏽‍♀️🙋🏽‍♀️🙋🏽‍♀️🙋🏽‍♀️🙋🏽‍♀️🙋🏽‍♀️😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning stretches. #AgsWin #Astros #TakeItBack #MLB #AstrosST #STBaseball #nobaddays #YODO @ Fitteam Ballpark of th… https://t.co/gtsqVvVYee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parenting is perpetually having your lukewarm cup of coffee waiting for you in the microwave until you have to reheat it again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually a big crowd here....obviously giving free tickets to organizations around Broward county]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheamus2famous @AbeclinicsUSA That's my daughter. My son though loves to sit ina quiet spot and read :) i am ever… https://t.co/2PZsOYNW8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my large tribe. Some of us share DNA. Some of us share matching tattoos. All of us share in love and liftin… https://t.co/YgMCStNKK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[His album is the only music that plays on my devices. 🔥🔥🔥🔥@sanbenito  Benito ahi te veo en El AACenter. 💋🔥🥰 https://t.co/aoBS2UGJPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyndseyfifield S A M E  Also, while watching voting take place on @cspan, I couldn't understand seeing senators vo… https://t.co/E5K82tm5T3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ahmadinejad1956 Cool! I now know the rate of deterioration as Satan slowly sucks your soul into hell. Good to know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RegisNisengwe Well, if my tastebuds prefer the taste of chocolate than that of vanilla, and if at a restaurant I'm… https://t.co/EU8IYsgSYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottHech @ruthbenghiat And when you throw on top of all that SC Justice Thomas's recent opinion that providing pe… https://t.co/7un7NBuev3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Universe:  This is entirely unacceptable,  FIX IT - NOW!  #CohenHearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a lot of different origins but none of them is Armenian. Because my name finishes by -ian a lot of people th… https://t.co/fmhMEQUkdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PureManhattan @quietconserv @Alyssa_Milano @IlhanMN No, no... she only hangs out in the bougee parts... You know,… https://t.co/VC7SohB5uW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Netflix Listen to the Fans !! Bring Back This Awesome Show!!  @Netflix @SYFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Catlady628 @kimmybeaa @dorisat58862534 @ReporterPhoenix @kennethfawalter @LifeOnTheBeach7 @nl_misstanden… https://t.co/ttscBEeJWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your #overhead is TOO HIGH and your #smallbusiness is looking for a way to reduce and #save 100s to 1,000s of do… https://t.co/GjLlrgch44]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusanDanzig219 @tedlieu @POTUS @JillWineBanks @JohnWDean He resigned th day befr impeachment was 2b proposed. Repu… https://t.co/WXQuk2i5rL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSEMPLE28 @PhilippeReines You must be a bot , at least I hope you’re a bot masquerading as a black woman because w… https://t.co/YuSyaxfIxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tail wagging experiences have a huge payoff; Increases customer retention by 1.4x, return on spend by 1.9x and sati… https://t.co/rY1jTQ4YRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth.   When we worry about only ourselves we do the world immeasurable injustice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day everyone! 💜💜💜 #BTSARMY @BTS_twt https://t.co/SEuCU9E4sW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is time to fix the voting process. They want illegal immigrants to vote. Photo I'd. Drives license should show t… https://t.co/EPy5A3nAq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun color shoot with these Petite cuties!!! @ Veterans Park https://t.co/2WJUYbuaui]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't understand some of you females pushing on 30 still on section 8 but got the flyest clothes but not worrying… https://t.co/Jl0751QQwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelinaVader Gotcha, I worked in an OB office for a bit and it was a common symptom. But I’m talking stinky stinky.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t mind my humble brag, but I have SEVEN fans on TikTok. @SugarBearHair, where’s my sponsorship?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RC2DA @Bakari_Sellers https://t.co/j5mWfG0FvQ  #Bernie2020  #BernieWouldHaveWon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DetJoeLocus @K9starSarge Praying for them both!  Hey Sarge, how bout an update on y'all?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#vape #vaping #vapor #vapetricks #vapenation #vapeporn #vapejuice #vapepen #vaperazzi #vapestore #vapefam… https://t.co/3dZHlhAamX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RIDeptEd @MaryannSRI OMG, don't go! Although will this free you up for us to have coffee and meet for lunch more o… https://t.co/jsirUgDb0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allahs_SonOfMan @netanyahu @Pontifex I can see that point of view. I do not have any emotion for the wicked. Be Me… https://t.co/qMObs6WOF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KlasfeldReports @CourthouseNews Ok..Adam.. Thiel..and Musk..Turkey...fusion.. satellites.. I mean these guys are d… https://t.co/OEJsnmyeKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came home from that trip and cried my eyes out for days afterwards due to struggling to comprehend the immensity… https://t.co/ld1YuWyuf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #readacrossamerica2019!  From the @WHschools #whhs #Library!  #DrSeussDay #readingrocks #StPatricksDay https://t.co/5p2QzhSunz]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Great thoughts speak only to the thoughtful mind ... but great actions speak to all mankind.” -Emily P Bissell  ..… https://t.co/cu5psoB9v8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, Alumni Chapel at SBTS is really up to date.  They have cell phone holders. https://t.co/4BUEZ1Dcv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandiRedmond @cdllive143 @iJoeyHdz @melissamccarthy @stephhollman So ladies and gents, This is why I just love… https://t.co/6aIjztHrbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then I will encamp at my house as a guard, so that none shall march to and fro; no oppressor shall again march over… https://t.co/Q08jo3S8e4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialRezz Hey - if you need to cancel you need to cancel. Thousands of shows only one Isabelle. You are so loved by so many. ❤️]]></document></documents></author>