<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Paísley with her Grandma until tomorrow and I`m off work sooo idk wtf to do with myself rn honestly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my lord...what sick people.  Anyone connected to the Clintons should be looked at, the Clintons should be in pri… https://t.co/vi2FgmZtNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle Oh God! Can this woman get anything right! Democrats darling!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankConniff NC Rep Meadows definitely wants the Klan to ride again. His face is so red while he’s grilling Cohen.… https://t.co/CWpPtzPNjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine's Day poem sent to my lady love some years ago ...  #writersofinstagram #valentines #poetry @ Smartpig Wo… https://t.co/9HJZ8aPm1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaththeWineLady @SteenbergWines @winewankers @DemiCassiani @wineworldnews @Julianna_glass @suziday123… https://t.co/zzmdmemBRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdyBarkan I live in Santa Barbara too.  Please let me know if I can be of any help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Pay attention to this thing I love because I love it and if you don’t love it too it’ll make me upset”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathieLGifford thank you using your platform to remind us that we can find STRENGHT in the JOY of the LORD. You al… https://t.co/7UPEMlVquA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stroker_deep @Lesbian458 Damn 🤤😻🙏🏿 I hope one day I can get a piece that size that knows What and how The Fuck to use it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Allow yourself to daydream, for dreams give you creative ideas and solutions and produce wonderful results.  7 of cups (motherpeace #tarot)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow falling from a blue sky. That’s tricky. Taos is tricky. I did a blue run in Taos. I guess I’m tricky now, too.… https://t.co/QR2G6nJol4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, so what nickname are we giving Jurickson Profar? @BrodieNBCS @DALLASBRADEN209 #hurryup #weneeditbytoday @smallswise]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vroberts9 @MissytheB @lynda3035 @sharon_cantley @BloomNight2 @GordonHarmony @Marina935home @Palmolive_S_Pan… https://t.co/SC7Fqhycec]]></document><document><![CDATA[The final chapter #bsbvegas (@ Backstreet Boys: Larger Than Life in Paradise, NV) https://t.co/PLhgp8O6CJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hapiness ! Finding your #passion and getting to do it every day! — Happiness Is Always Best When Shared ! Thank yo… https://t.co/1F9tDZGnRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dejaff @realDonaldTrump And what about the DemocRATS paying illegals to enter our country—numbnut 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[An echo from 2 Corinthians of God’s sufficient grace! “The foolishness of God is wiser than men; and the weakness o… https://t.co/XrDW6Ofzen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColinESeale The triad Renzulli model of Giftedness includes persistence as one of the traits of truly gifted peopl… https://t.co/xrBZGkCJtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@toniforchicago casting her ballot at Shoesmith Elementary! Happy #ElectionDay! #VoteToni4Chi #VoteHerIn… https://t.co/IRFyLMvYCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing brings me more joy than seeing friends smile and laugh all day 😃 What a great way to start my birth month.… https://t.co/unLLRVzWlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrushingOnSaban @mbtmom2000 @KTeems87 Today was truly the day for it friend —]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephenson is now talking about the impact that OU has had on his life, including meeting his wife at Bizzell libra… https://t.co/pEWLgmhV2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning to everyone except the people who don’t believe in climate change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool things are happening in my life rn but like I’m still sad?!? 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students: More and or better commuter parking lots on BGSU’s campus - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/zK1NLzaK1f via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Staciem82795013 Can you pls send that video in IG or DM in twitter? I’ll post on all platforms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aria asked if we could watch Pretty in Pink 🌺 oh she my DAUGHTER daughter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh when did they ever say that bruh they used to carry me and smack me to the ground]]></document><document><![CDATA[His finishing move is the Shock Arrow, but it seems he had a challenge against a song with a similar name! ⚡️🤩⚡️  #SHOCKARROW #シビれる]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tech bosses taking a dance break. @Sphero @pivotal @volunteerBGCLA https://t.co/RgqZJMzARo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macjudith I continue to believe if you want to escalate digital adoption in key areas - take things away. Fax mach… https://t.co/D6u5mxe8gV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bonray and me! JoyFm Sofa concert tonight. This family is so talented!#joyfmsofaconcertseries ##joyfm #bonray @ Fir… https://t.co/sMUiKLy5ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your life seems to be turning upside down do a handstand push up to keep on pushing thru!  . . . . . .… https://t.co/6RV60MLC0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever just been with your loved one and took in the moment,  realizing that you’re really living your best… https://t.co/aTEkRYW8MC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I initially ran to him, where he came to rest was still in the roadway. He ran back to his car, turned on blue li… https://t.co/Lt8BJKY43y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bduty47 @PudLightLime @violasmart4 @HHS1DPU @rudepundit @RealSaavedra @AOC Seriously BillyBob, you need a reality… https://t.co/xpbYRhm38p]]></document><document><![CDATA[“She’s Always a Woman” was definitely written about an enneagram 3. this bitch is clearly powerful and plays her ca… https://t.co/iRojGBMFRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilevin @we_dems Psychiatric evals are conducted for high-level execs at corporations that will have a certain lev… https://t.co/QBesmsge4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been raining for the last week nonstop, and we’ve been having flash flood warnings for the last few days. Lots… https://t.co/XlE5as8dUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be honest, I think I’d be much more successful if I was an extrovert. But I’m not.  I’m bad at networking. I abs… https://t.co/18XAd9c8I3]]></document><document><![CDATA[please keep my pupper in your prayers 😔 had to rush him to the emergency clinic tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camp1955 I bought Wi-Fi. I am on line with DT 24/7. 🚢 is packed with his supporters 70 percent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel He can get help while in prison. He wasted $$$ in taxpayers money with 12 detectives investigated his… https://t.co/hr5bfOaF9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay so now that the jo bros are back together I’m gonna need them to make a 7th album and outsell kelly clarkson s… https://t.co/I9UU4gRbxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TennisChannel @BNPPARIBASOPEN @Kohlscribbler Happy he’s gone.  Cannot stand him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babysgramma @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump I've put myself through college twice and I have a good j… https://t.co/ZGyo6pc1nc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@W01Melissa @RelieaYuell @SHIESHKY @SwordAndScale @amahnke @rabiasquared Next we'll be burning books. What happened to censorship is bad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grey_Obelisk The burning hypocrisy currently is majorly disturbing. When will it be kick azz time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[unwomen I am lucky to travel in this life accompanied by great women, supportive friends, exemplary warriors, profe… https://t.co/ar3JiAcWdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drunk way too much last night/ this morning. I’ve missed overnights like this 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wordpressdotcom TY for building an awesome platform. Been using it for 7 years &amp; love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[and being questioned about his identity, declares, “I am your son, your first-born…” When Esau realizes what his yo… https://t.co/UGFdGfv9XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OffField_Mascot @tomgreenlive @CBSBigBrother Try to find “Subway Monkey Hour”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @50cent Must have been the only way he could get well known to attend.   Ha ha so it’s true no one re… https://t.co/aTYR0EBcUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always like oh I got hella time to shit I’m gonna be a few minutes late lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be honest, it’s hard for me to watch this and not focus on the negatives that I see. My weight journey has bee… https://t.co/meos0DY8b0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TxBornSooner @GabeIkard @FranchiseOK @BSO Yeah, I only got the two before he went private real fast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls trip with my mother and daughter.  This is my first course. https://t.co/Yw8dTLV4a0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m guessing she doesn’t realize that almost 99% of farms are family owned. @AOC come chat with some folks who are… https://t.co/b54Z5lnujK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caroline_Bartma Are you sure you don’t want to study the kidney? #NephTwitter is very friendly, and the kidney is… https://t.co/2ydXG2Zyar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinbieber happy birthday. You have no idea how many years I have defended and obsessed over you. That is all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ETE361 takes over The Roebling Museum today for “Kids Create STEM Saturday” until 4pm.  #tcnj #iSTEM #TechEd https://t.co/VsG1XQOTJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USWRep @MR_PRIME69 @milesjreed @Ireland0828 @JimKilbane  The only negotiating technique he seems to know is get up and walk out. So undergr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irshad_imr I figured it was some reality show contestant after winning a challenge.  But ya, maybe...she looks pretty pleased. Ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tommy hanging with the boys #bnpparibasopen  #bnpp019 @ Indian Wells Tennis Garden https://t.co/oLe4WGXojh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The shorts of my choice for #Bellator215. @ClinchGear not only makes some of the best gear for fighters, they also… https://t.co/jISxu2cFAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s SENIOR NIGHT TONIGHT!  Come and watch these Senior MIC Champions as they battle in their last regular season h… https://t.co/kIttnfikN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those @IAmEliasWWE verses slamming all things Cleveland and Ohio were hilarious #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBU_Austin I’m so honored to receive this prestigious recognition! 💙😊👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[A shoutout to @kingswift79 for being such an awesome friend!🙌 I really, really hope both our dreams of meeting… https://t.co/tmj5oiViwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The city should just issue every one of us our own personalized pot hole filler thingy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuuuuuck as if I didn’t love enough her already !!!! Houston Rodeo Selena tribute by @KaceyMusgraves nuttttttttttttt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mekosoff @lil_yenta Abe Fischer is the same chef as Zahav and I actually prefer it...it’s elevated/fusion Eastern… https://t.co/N1yZYLW5PH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a beautiful day here at Bayside Hooters! Swing by! ☀️ https://t.co/Wbgq4rmomW]]></document><document><![CDATA[i assume if an account with a large following, follows me back that they mute me and it’s just a curtesy follow or… https://t.co/mb6M4p375e]]></document><document><![CDATA[#newhome #homeforsale #listings #realestate #realtors #luxuryhomes #bluffsideatcountryclubcreek #homebuilder… https://t.co/PMr96nOkcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haught Dimples are are Everybody's Thing! 🔥💕 @SYFY @IDWPublishing fulfill your commitment to #WynonnaEarp and put o… https://t.co/yWDhGIG4DD]]></document><document><![CDATA[2020 WORLD DISCIPLESHIP SUMMIT REGISTRATION GIVEAWAY! #giveaway #win https://t.co/VjiP27uRwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHNOLAgroninger @NewOrleansCAC You are starting to sound like a true " New Orleanian"]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Bernie. But Bernie running for President 2020 is giving Trump a free pass for re-election. 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland One person commented that "she looks like a seasoned outdoor gal" while another said, "those little ad… https://t.co/EsitMjqXtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuanashillus Now you're just luring only child Julie with promises of siblings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hdoniss This tweet read my mind. As soon as I read this tweet this dude who lives on my floor who always jerks off… https://t.co/mrrE2fivc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk who needs to hear this but... focus on being around the people who appreciate you for who you are b/c there wil… https://t.co/UuwkmuZorN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneak peek of #Dundas Inspired exhibition opened @DundasMuseum  till April 26 Happy to see my #dundasforever waterc… https://t.co/fbO86cqFG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter @Nike is tripping bra they gotta put more $$ into quality samething happen to me the other day while… https://t.co/i3o56HAvat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGillycuddy @notelewd It's about as dumb as the claims that its a political game that somehow has communistic unde… https://t.co/icK9ultFa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are do proud of the whole team, but even more proud of @_jayynicee and all that she has accomplished the past 4… https://t.co/kBzLnl5SPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[😭😭I hope they find the person(s) that did this to Tommie! This poor animal should have never had to go through all… https://t.co/4u6rMGi2Ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCThisisUs i gasped when i watched this. we need to see more young beth and randall, please!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anti vaxxers are like some strange weird new colonialism bio-terrorism with a dash of obliviousness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earth to Alyssa, come in @Alyssa_Milano. These are the kind of monsters your constant fear mongering breeds. But I… https://t.co/Pk344jDvHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @colonvalbert @realDonaldTrump No the letters from Kim Jing-Un are manipulation and trump walked right in… https://t.co/PbcO4Wanqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Metallica was GREAT! #metallica #worldwiredtour2019 #kfcyumcenter #louisville @ KFC Yum! Center https://t.co/V1n7XKWsNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was definitely a family and friends affair that made it all happen @asc_bakery @HaleyLarkie… https://t.co/od6vn8GKVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Prospects Baseball And Softball in Randolph, NJ https://t.co/al4hcanEvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManMet80 We save everything , so we could produce about 30 years of records.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarkAndreFurry @VGKWarMachine @GoldenKnights @goldenpipeslv @VGKFlamingo @VGKCrossbar @TheGildedJester… https://t.co/wLYjDStRZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all obsessed with Demi and I’m sitting over here with the OG bachelor drama queen like   #WomenTellAll https://t.co/fbuZNajHlQ]]></document></documents></author>