<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:44.6°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the second week in a row, I have fans giving me their opinions on this new package in the first 35 laps of the… https://t.co/8WvtVRdLaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well the #Steelers sent AB to the #Bills @lilboon @BrooksMckyla 👀 good luck signing him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRhyheim @timtales_com @ReddzLeon You fuck like a beast the more resist the harder you fuck 😘😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moses_FPS I agree with that, but then there’s streamers like shroud who aren’t very comedic but are just insanely good at games]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Nope! Crime is way down. Stop your lying #FoxPropaganda #SeanFoxPropaganda https://t.co/4zG4XziFwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty excited to see @ShazamMovie   I’m interested how @ZacharyLevi Intersects with the @DCComics Universe. https://t.co/5XwjMUvqEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BNev4666 They worked against the will of the American people. https://t.co/GjRnlg4jEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nooch is so dumb, he thinks Cheerios are doughnut seeds. #InsultMadness]]></document><document><![CDATA[This pretzel hot dog was really good! #disneyfood @ Disney California Adventure Park https://t.co/X281LR1u28]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Give me a fucking break! Why all this venomous hatred towards President Trump. Leave him alone to govern the USA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhafner @austinseminary A full dozen!  People across America are opening their Dropbox and going “Where did this come from?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our EMBODI “I AM” conference was one for the books. Thank you to our volunteers, community leaders and speakers.… https://t.co/ElPmKddtQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to see what it’s like to travel in Star Wars light speed?   Try driving through a midwestern snowstorm at night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I really messaged a private lash bar asking if I could get in for lash extensions tomorrow at 1:00 even though… https://t.co/jSJp8nLFer]]></document><document><![CDATA[👨‍💼 Good morning world! Let's make this day our b!tch 💪  #business #morning #motivation #entrepreneur]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump ends Obama-era policy on stating number of civilian drone deaths  https://t.co/oxqGqMd4r4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to all of the CSRA artists that will be performing at SXSW 19 this year! S/O to the team roundhereradio… https://t.co/XHRzcJXp72]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow @pa52783731 Get out of Congress and keep walking...and don't forget to swim when necessary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel this 100%, but at the same time I was trained to smile at everyone. Even going back to work after my mom die… https://t.co/kf19NNrwTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging at @BraxtonBrewCo and tweeting just to get on the screen in the taproom.  #Vanity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mathis gets nailed in the nuts with a baseball, Mathis nails baseball over fence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rictictoc see bro this is what we get from dc fam. I never realized that the kn nightmare scene was a 1 shot smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreyAdell @advancedstats23 That's actually one reason Smarf probably ends up getting included, tbh. Harder to make… https://t.co/3ovzLfScpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hello_im_riley @TMeltonScouting At least there's that one Kmart though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@consvforbin @DR0girl The host resort is expanding and building over the concert beach area. You can see the new bu… https://t.co/MsmYonN30t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mehdirhasan In the Marvel Universe you would be the CREDIBLE Hulk. https://t.co/WJNxHOdyTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amberoneal1 thanks for the follow back! Can I get a add on Snapchat too? https://t.co/puUqdWU1N5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Openings available; dm for scheduling... #tattoos #Raleigh #NC #northstartattoo #tattooshane #instatattoo… https://t.co/htT0QNYJ3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[In fact, it looks like all 8 Rangers defensemen are in that "bad" quadrant. Which, yeah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am brown immigrated in USA now I will be forced to pay for it it’s my hard-earned money WHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clymer saying “geometric abnormality” after the puck rang off two posts makes me want to take a screwdriver to my ear drums.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alex Robinson, Kendric Davis, JD Miller and Desmond Bane all likely will play 37-40 minutes today. RJ Nembhard has to be a factor today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@static4tw @dbongino What’s your point? Are you saying the leagues are going to crumble because the players and own… https://t.co/5zXI4X98XF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chan_walk14 @RowdyDowds We know you try &amp; so does @KoltonSirWelter who doesn’t even go to south]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Intimidate the Hell out of Us  They won't sit down  They are polite enough to make you think they are at Ease b… https://t.co/OxJjpPY8c3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RKSBandOfficial your encore last night was crazy good! thanks for an amazing show]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC @mattgaetz The Daily Beast: Matt Gaetz Under Investigation By Florida State Bar Over Michael Cohen Threat. https://t.co/C8jG92sCt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeitnerSimmons @kohenari @UNC_Librarian Your profile pic should of been my first clue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que buen proyecto éste. Ahí los invito a seguir la cuenta de  @noticonquista]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hotel Emma . . . . . . . . . . 📷: Sony Alpha A7Riii + Sony 16-35mm f/2.8 GM 👤: vincentyangphotography 🗺:… https://t.co/3czx4tsGQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBA All-Star Weekend: Steph Curry falls short in championship round of NBA Three-Point Shootout - San Francisco Exa… https://t.co/9uKSzwZzji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daddy and Daughter Day @ Bixby Park, Long Beach https://t.co/DdL036lg50]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regardless of one's views on this specific issue, this observation is apt:  "It’s good that Maryland has a governor… https://t.co/IuQcfeEMTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@navyhato @JackPosobiec Reminds me of adult men on Liberty in Thailand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do wanna go to Philly this year to see the #NCAALax championship game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is always looking to the future, how can we improve the future, what can we do to make sure we have a comf… https://t.co/F2THYTh45o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnleedumas crushed it. @ Wyndham Orlando Resort International Drive https://t.co/OaRPHDU2nA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patrick Mahomes is live streaming games of NFL Blitz and I’ve never loved him more than I do right now. My QB for l… https://t.co/eG9Aksk2aj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Max Murphy, @PVXC5000 achieves the @DrakeRelays #BlueStandard of 9:35 for the 3200 winning the @DickinsonRelays in 9:34.71. @ankenyarrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bohemian Rhapsody was bad and problematic and Rami Malek wasn’t even that good at it 🙃 #Oscars https://t.co/QoaPSmfHHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s none of government’s business to invade the realm of personal food choices, whether Booker’s veganism or Bloom… https://t.co/cOrXmoKr8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlanetComicon @PlanetkcChris Will we be lucky enough to have Photo Op options with @RealMickFoley as #CactusJack,… https://t.co/YgWXnBKH9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NebulousNikki, sunspot cycle is 11 years in total. Every ham radio operator will tell you that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repost antenorefabio with make_repost ・・・ Epic light on an epic spot! Taken last year in Oregon.. ☀️🌻📸📸📸📸📸📸📸📸📸📸🌻☀️… https://t.co/A3OnCxPu8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gained 37 pounds and i was wearing the same 3-4 pants all the time. They were squeezing my fucking thighs. Today… https://t.co/llwiUDoiGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final game as UTA closes out the Maverick Invitational, facing Abilene Christian University. Follow me for live upd… https://t.co/zrnnpuIN0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdjennings @AARPLive @OfficialRFDTV @Christina_Loren @GregMarchildon We know you and @GregMarchildon will keep eve… https://t.co/Try2dkpMBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm the type fr not to talk about my past relationships unless I type love you dead ass. I just don't like talkin bout that em fr.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched all three hotel transylvania movies last month.  They are the best non toy story  animated trilogy.  The… https://t.co/HrvxtOlVWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHousefather you should be ashamed of yourself. Blocking an open discussion. Look forward to October.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today... We ski. #skimaine #skitheeast @SugarloafMaine @ Sugarloaf Mountain https://t.co/fCpQ1nWsQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gneitzel16 @ESPNRadio Listen to that show on the drive into work every day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puck. #snipe 🚨 (@ Pelham Civic Center in Pelham, AL) https://t.co/d3SW50y71S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yessss! I am now a proud patron of Garand Thumb on @patreon, and you should be too: #NewPatron https://t.co/xgXR3rqtgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally just said to my wife “I wanna finish this wine because I can’t find the cork” #truestory #wine #wineo  so… https://t.co/y2hMfzy4NL]]></document><document><![CDATA[All individual Hitter reports already in Coach Smitty’s inbox. Would have been faster but I had to fix my spelling mistakes ha ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lightfoot&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;Wade  @KUHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[How's does a black person birth a white person?  Or the person is chemist conversation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReliableSources @brianstelter @JaneMayerNYer @CNN @BretBaier @marthamaccallum please tune in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great way forward to living out God's love from @marshallsnider of @bpmpdx. I'm so grateful for a community of fe… https://t.co/NpfbhdgxRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does this person expect is gonna happen? Complaining on social media is such a cringy trend in this age of soc… https://t.co/LkkxezA0nC]]></document><document><![CDATA[2600yd Swim at Francos (Aerobic The Ladder 3) #tridat #baseperformance #nuunlife #teamzealios #phytorebel #altred… https://t.co/Q54lhTo08E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doggie Photobomb!  #happysunday  #brofessor #oldmanrunning  #santiagocanyoncollege tshirt by #nike. #Minkie… https://t.co/93SBMgiVve]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t already, go checkout my new Music Video for “Been Here Before” which is also live on all platforms n… https://t.co/LANuZaNFKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DonaldJTrump #DonaldJTrump #DonaldJTrump #DonaldJTrump #DonaldJTrump #DonaldJTrump #DonaldJTrump #DonaldJTrump #DonaldJTrump #DonaldJTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[The pessimist in me can’t help but think that wearing the whale again will end this magical run]]></document><document><![CDATA[Athletic trainers are healthcare professionals who collaborate with physicians to provide emergency care and preven… https://t.co/WPucL1a5Mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love yankee fans defending signing a guy who has a career average of .236 to a 7 year contract lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back home and I def feel better. Also yea I’m loving my new fav hat. I gotta thank one of my hubbies for just reset… https://t.co/BUYlPzmXT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would call this idiotic, was just another Democrat trying to figure out how to get more votes for their party by… https://t.co/UitgGgfqzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Your finance chair you mean? Y’all are either lying or stupid or both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s possible to respect all the career options while simultaneously being realistic about what the job market look… https://t.co/EjDquP1Ki5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simplemente el mejor lugar #Sabinas y tu cómo inicias tu dia ? #micafeparroquia  Ven a probar nuestras mezclas de c… https://t.co/g5SeZC7tHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrodhogfan @PigTrailNation That’s not the point. It ain’t about bringing in 5⭐️ players. It’s about recognizing th… https://t.co/Sdf3AU64Uc]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the Electoral College; surely the best option would be proportional delegate voting, instead of winner takes all… https://t.co/1aO9MNF4lh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just being beautiful. #lillymama #rescuepitt #findinglight @ Washington Heights, Manhattan https://t.co/DQc5B6JU0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Now please tighten up your message and delivery. You will be scrutinized to agony levels. No more mistakes. We need you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You thought he showed his discontent in Pittsburgh... this lasts 3 games...maybe...before we see the temper tantrum… https://t.co/CqtbCifmVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jaylon McLaughlin @thereal_lilj07 @NevadaBaseball creating havoc on the bases causing an over throw to plate em!… https://t.co/dJUnXfuFmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temp: 40.8°F Wind:0.9mph Pressure: 30.110hpa Falling Rain Today 0.00in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity When do you start a petition to remove Donald Trump for his multiple racist statements and actions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRMovieNews This prompted me to do an @IMDb review AND SO GLAD I DID!!! I’m O.A.F. so forgive me, but y’all keep y… https://t.co/tVtdhjxe4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[springtime tomfoolery | 📸 @Jor_Siegel | 🧥 carospange | . . . . . #lilacep #spring #treepose #photography #lol… https://t.co/X4GIKN1jSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn I used to wonder what it was like to be young handsome and wealthy but after listening to this here I am damn]]></document><document><![CDATA[(2:40am ET, Monday): Guys, this is #LakeEffect #Snow. Winds are so strong that it’s pulling snow squalls from the G… https://t.co/S2J1xe6kXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joyce_Karam That's a relief. That means her child isn't a US citizen either. Hopefully her country will prosecute… https://t.co/LFIYTWarD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[and why aren't there any of the in-between stages?? just monkeys and humans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump President Obama did it better and faster way before you. You are riding on Obama’s success which y… https://t.co/iLxEj7nqug]]></document><document><![CDATA[# just see it   @luchsasaras @austinmalestonr @Fernand31004793 @AustinLuchasar2 @Valerie_Perez @ImDanaDeLorenzo… https://t.co/5pCNOMIPCp]]></document></documents></author>