<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga @VanityFair We are thankful for your talent.  is it time for a song in Italian do you think? That would b… https://t.co/te65f3IH5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tayy704 Sometimes I think about you forgetting to park ur car and I laugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk With most inexpensive #Rockets going into #space I guess you might as well have the best guns too! 🚀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ministryoftest So many women: @DawnMHaynes @cheekytester @janetgregoryca @lisacrispin @charrett @FionaCCharles… https://t.co/RmK8nIDX7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙌🏻  • • • 🌜 #goodnight #toptags #bed #goodnight #photooftheday #star #instagood #nightynight #beautiful #kisses… https://t.co/7RFIeNZody]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealTarx9 @Mark_Lapping @NicoMartelle @stradlemonkey @Biggybadass @dfeague @therealwallbie @Brooksidefilms Did u s… https://t.co/eqEv2OIJS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cammy Dierking on Instagram: “The goats are enjoying the sunshine! The babies are growing fast! #babygoats… https://t.co/ftB8yudSvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvanDuque’s speech was ambitious and optimistic about social and economic growth in Colombia. He said he plans to… https://t.co/tFUk1XfPcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I talk shit to him but he makes her happy and that’s all that matters to me @_justduthu_  #BecomingAPierre #2021 https://t.co/zebObIyIqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlyingVGoddess @thehealthguy Propaganda—the story just came out (from 2017) because of recent events. Whatever. Th… https://t.co/4rkLcEP62X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Trump’s dirty;Mueller's team has now charged 8 Americans once affiliated wit… https://t.co/DYIPaL0wto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@niru__mahendran @Suzannek203 @sgbrauer @tandfnewsroom Congratulations @niru__mahendran! 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lamihacoolcat $65 for early cost  Then $75 And then $85 for the week of prom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Namiss ko block party ng Lady Spikers. Beke nemen lol. Di ako sanay na last place tayo sa blocking 😅 #UAAPSeason81Volleyball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaDelany Thank you. The wonderful Liza Donnelly drew it. No headband .... or marvelous dangling earrings either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachjjayson Tough district in LO starting Monday with Clarkston, Oxford, Orion and Adams...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportsrage Luckily I came across this in all my vast mentions since I’m so famous now. 🙄🙄🙄 Lolol. Thank you Gabe!… https://t.co/hMautizLrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’ll “lead the agency to greater heights...” I see what you did there Gov 😉👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLucasBlack Ha ha ha!! "I know what I'm doing!" "I still got it!" Great reference to Fast and Furious. @NCISNewOrleans]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t wait for this summer and sitw with my guy is gonna be a good way to start 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ns49Nanci @HWDSB @JNunnHWDSB @ShawnMcKillop @adelaide_HWDSB You are awesome, my friend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando a Otto ,hace casi 2 años lo atacó un perro y estaba recién operado ,llego a casa y ver q el gruñón de Napole… https://t.co/NVS3ISUeq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel @blaggerswagger Don’t underestimate the power of disinformation 🤔look at bot attacks on all democr… https://t.co/irjyR0Fc89]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol and I go, I read every Sunday, I see you on Saturdays when I'm volunteering so isn't that enough?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #snl Cha Cha slide sketch with @mulaney is everything I never knew I needed. https://t.co/Uoyu1TCvGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricHolder @Christiresist Can sitting congressmen be indicted for intimidating a federal witness?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spanther8 @BigRedBodyguard He hired a crisis management team!!! What does that mean to you?!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaceyPlaskett @jemelehill Love the look,on her face having to deal with Jimbo interuptuprion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OgletreeAllStar  Literacy Night was so much fun in part because I got to help DJ for @tsufrat1898 Book Walk! https://t.co/EppEXV3zuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC Sleep tight Roger. You are headed for a concrete bed asap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying our Sunday... my baby boy Dominic will be 6 on Thursday. #cincinnati #513 #pics #photography #kids @ Pleas… https://t.co/LNZKKbc43U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we get to see super cute photos of great couples! And then also some people who settled...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelbeatty3 @realDonaldTrump Maybe this is a sign that he has flipped. If so it would be huge since his laptop reveals the clear truth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone and their moms are in Sinaloa right now for the Carnival 😩 @Janitzza_ girl.... 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VaxWoke @IvankaTrump @realDonaldTrump @FLOTUS stop mandatory vaccinations. Don’t let them take our freedom. Don’t… https://t.co/MiSi9LCz0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember, even if the President has to hold his nose to sign this bill, we will be holding new elections in April,… https://t.co/Ce2qCI1DUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steve555M @marsspring1 @zeitgeistbabe @maydaymindy9 That’s beautiful. Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec But his background.  Why he is evenconsidered for this position ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judicial Watch: Justice Department Discloses No FISA Court Hearings Held on Carter Page Warrants - Judicial Watch https://t.co/LMOGfinG60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@G_Padraic @RedLawCO From what I can tell, they have rejected it pretty entirely. The first screenshot is state v.… https://t.co/u3Nbp5OUXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[We made a list for @thewildhoneypie!! These are songs we’ve had on repeat during long tour drives - they make every… https://t.co/PhwGXenivj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conradmuan I was like no ur not? Then this popped into my timeline https://t.co/rudlvNYrfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnapClapPat @feierabendmusic @Claire_Lynn1 I bought 2 this time (I get something every year). I'm pretty obsessed 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad my husb came to see one of my fav artists @jillianjmusic last night! I believe he loved her as much as I do… https://t.co/gO7gHU1IIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayer fui a una fiesta donde la mayoría eran chavitos menores que yo y me dijeron que parecía de 21. Ustedes me mant… https://t.co/6i9vcsvaK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cytherea Roller derby Manda is hardcore questioning any provider's decision not to send him straight to the ED. Do… https://t.co/Y4eW5mv8ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpirosMargaris @womensday @anjani_trivedi @BainAlerts @IFC @natashakyp @CHonerlage @oxana_zeitler @F10_accelerator… https://t.co/YtEgMNZIXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a very carefully crafted ordinance to address the desperate need for housing while preserving neighborhood… https://t.co/OGIPtXW6Oa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby Sure it wasn’t the first boob that this boob has signed !! https://t.co/kxhtBMtXRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crying - tips for writers. Now I know if I'm going over the top with my... #hilarity #laugh #smirk #funny https://t.co/9t0BkhZk64]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to need all of you to identify your purpose before wasting my time]]></document><document><![CDATA[What? @ACLU @Sifill_LDF @NAACP @RevDrBarber @TheRevAl @MichelleBernard @mayawiley @LisaBloom @GloriaAllred… https://t.co/PTrBnceYpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's another sticker for my book launch. Like it? https://t.co/NBFlm5zva3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TempleDrake00 Sounds like you're probably fine. But, when you do eat, eat well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ejrl Pues que dialoguen entre ellos y cuando esten listos para el cese de la usurpacion nos avisen]]></document><document><![CDATA[T-minus 5 hours until I get to see my favorite boy 💖💖 https://t.co/lNdRQnhyHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was literally me to the m66 the other day akxhskjss I really banged on the doors  https://t.co/8KRo3ujuGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those of  you who know what happened and havnt spoke up, y’all mfs are JUST as guilty as the POS who murdered him.… https://t.co/VI2NcmrJV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[E eu que descobri ONTEM que aqui no Estados Unidos só precisa ter ID maior de 18 anos  Z O A D O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I find it funny how my students get mind blown when they find out I know their older siblings or someone related to them 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Danny Martinello kick off another sold out Saturday! Great time! . . . . #goyukyourself #laughteristhebestmedicine… https://t.co/5kDlgoRqot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stfutony @stephyyspice @Hippie_ricky is this what you did last night lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bornabrit1 Trump &amp; his old dirty pedophile buddies. They are all vile. Not to mention cheap dirty old pedophiles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Sinophobia has a bloody history in Vietnam  Everyone: BUT WARS!!!   Me: okay all hail to winning at all cost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@r_bagby @WRAL @mitchcarrtv Aww sadly, no! But RVA will always have a special place in my heart! And it's his home!]]></document><document><![CDATA[teddy_j_johnson paintings at The Linda Matney Gallery #lmgfineart. @ https://t.co/XPnsneorRS  #lindamatneygallery… https://t.co/bEZ8tveFLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#5amwritersclub How is it #wednesday already???? What are you working on today #WritingCommunity I'm neck deep in e… https://t.co/yucBiGV4bN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharleyBailey_ @EdKrassen Well you are more welcoming than I am! I don’t want racists in the party. 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kansasgirl821 @colton They don’t HAVE to ask period. It’s just important to Coltan so he CHOSE to ask. Unless he’s… https://t.co/88ipPxge2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Wheeler @kristopherleec @LindseyGrahamSC Does the so-called Congressional District vote Democratic? Hahahaha S… https://t.co/4DnhseIXJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m 100% guilty of being a trendy millennial mom, but I draw the line at throwing cheese onto my babies forehead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latest issue of The New Yorker has an article on Barbra Streisand. Points out she was a graduate of my HS.  Erasmus… https://t.co/s8RpfZf36U]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @awhonn (get_repost) ・・・ #Repost awhonnohio 😂Happy Tuesday, everyone!! #AWHONN @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/qPxUNb2bTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deiberokirsten the problem is that you are looking. love comes when you least expect it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newbies: what I mean by "Group Play" there are lots of private chat groups who pick a stock,  usually one w hype bu… https://t.co/4MvD27RmEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[When things aren't working out as you wish, be patient. Stop trying to move ahead of God. His timing is perfect. @kxmvni 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[sick of this fucking job bruh! ion think imma EVER be satisfied with a job until im working in my career field. bc… https://t.co/NhhgcmWhri]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday #womenempowerment @ Coral Gables, Florida https://t.co/Cb0vwmPMEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are hungover and about to get hit with the Sunday rush https://t.co/yQlNBLgD6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evenml @zachRoth13 Same man. I saw I Feel Pretty. https://t.co/A15shSFhda]]></document><document><![CDATA[A machine gun on a trailer just showed up and killed a bunch of characters I don’t remember seeing at all before th… https://t.co/RuYNImTUZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t thank our all star ⭐️ team of @CoryBooker volunteers enough! Including @faithkeln @KatieStillman @RichSun908 &amp; @sullivans23]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ForThePeople indeed! Keep fighting for us @RepSarbanes! Glad you’re my Congressman. #ProudGreekToo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wssu #wssu23 #WSSU22  #WSSU21  #WSSU19  #RAMFest2019  #NCAT23  #NCAT22  #uncg23  GET BOOKED!! https://t.co/c4PYxzTY1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack I agree let’s look at the House and the Senate too. Let’s just be transparent !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late night rages with Paisleigh. I miss that crazy, lovable girl!💕 #PaisleighLyn #MyGirl #PrincessPaisleigh👸👑… https://t.co/BKO7KdSaRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont like these tweers tho cause he immediately proceeded to make fun of me for naming the plant Eleanor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tarawlevy @Speroman @chughesjohnson @lexir @gengster1 @reshmasaujani @kanadawomaninus @karaswisher @aparnacd… https://t.co/tv66ZOqNSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBenRyan @shayneholl @MaloneRanger959 @EricRaines1 @AllStarMornings @brettdillon @trrma I heard Randy Travis is… https://t.co/RZmX8cxhvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@etherleo If you gotta take something sexual off the table cause you aren’t married you should take it all off. All… https://t.co/FrLOFrdQTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@HighEdWeb is always there when you need them. #RainyDayAtDisneyland #heweb https://t.co/vi594NA5St]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥 Check out this MASSIVE GIVEAWAY by @RomanAtwood over at https://t.co/BRdXBVgeV3! 🔥🔥    WIN BIG PRIZES from… https://t.co/EurPe4ARJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting my lashes done next Wednesday and mine and Indy’s show is in three weeks, I’m excited]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanderpumpRules So let me understand this. U want to sue because a charity LVP started May get a spinoff. You are… https://t.co/RzjcgU7T81]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the Honor of remembering the fallen victims from Friday on the House floor and we paused for a moment of silenc… https://t.co/2kh2rJOCML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whittle2k @FoxNews The parts I don’t like are supporting infanticide. Killing an infant in an abortion that could… https://t.co/NwKWQSWoS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have nothing against big weddings, they’re quite nice and if you want one; you go for it!! Some people like mysel… https://t.co/IEdbrcjdPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think he’s tryna test my spending but ima just swipe my debit card for lunch 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burner2047 @PrimeVideo @neilhimself I’m sorry for whatever terrible thing is going on in your life that you feel l… https://t.co/4SkKo4RQJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been hopping the turnstile like a pro all wknd.  Thanks MTA for getting me to &amp; from safely!]]></document></documents></author>