<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The second girls semifinal is ao far a low-scoring affair. At the half, Gov Mifflin leads Wilson 19-12 @69Sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Crop Circus by @BauhausBrewLabs at @CraftandGrowler — https://t.co/3pMbGXVZmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want you to know when you fall its gonna hurt bae But its gonna work one way or another word to your mother… https://t.co/gZNc5SxymB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duke has no idea what they’re doing without Zion. In all honesty even with Zion we severely overrated this Duke team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikenedie @Cern_lXXl @tcunderdahl @PolyRhuagh @zypisfy @horusrage @debbiepalm44 @yourmumspants @dadbaddy… https://t.co/KWZmZf46ZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our office at @PhaseZeroDesign has  predominantly #femaleLeaders. There is no wonder why we have grown so much in r… https://t.co/GXtegb4WZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LieletteCalleja @BradCelmainis @QuickBooksUK @QuickBooks @HSatterley @LizQBO @qbappyhour @IntuitDev @kamsbaugh… https://t.co/kQwL8HyukD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for being anything but terrible Mr. Lindsay. #TedLindsay #terribleted #RIPTedLindsay https://t.co/gFAYPHR6EM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intelligent, Bright and Merciless: A North Korean Official’s Take on Kim Jong-un https://t.co/7WudoErtPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wavyboyvince Yo dad must be OG and the ones I be around must be double OGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to win 150 million REV Token Giveaway for Public Airdrop and TCASH Ho? I just entered to win and you can too. https://t.co/kPGyDho4TN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsCamtini @romansebastian @lbarronlopez @TomSteyer @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows Because YOU don't need a job or he… https://t.co/sJxZd6pMto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fridays @ @gizmo_bar! Friday March, 8th. 7-12. 21 and up. No Cover! Fine Wines and Craft Beers! The Technology Bar… https://t.co/SiwIldsvv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[To clarify, this is a mobile (Android) app those figures are for... For context, in the early 90s that app would ha… https://t.co/94wfNlbEX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m all for open concept, but maybe this is little too open. What you think? @ Victorville, California https://t.co/CPg0URl6tz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wells Fargo Suck I Had A Block On My Card For Bout A Week I Been Starving Up Here]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Blizzard_Ent! My $spawn0 thinks that @PlayOverwatch should introduce a New Orleans map where the payload is a… https://t.co/92uF3dXH4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuffyOhh I mean...yeah. It was a lot of snow! But Mel in the tank was maybe a bit much. https://t.co/QGt1LCkNm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥Tim Tebow - ML Hitter⁣ ⁣ Say what you want about the dude… I’m gonna say that this AB frickin impressed me.⁣ ⁣ Spi… https://t.co/y2saKiF5Hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Lord Jesus Christ for my Eternal life Salvation. Glory to God for our Lord Jesus Christ. https://t.co/E1ivPLupgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mindwbw good earnings for wb up 2.5 in pre market  - yeah can we get to 80-   haven`t checked Sina but i would exp… https://t.co/kJMlNE7urI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for a small business tax class.  #GDTBATH @GoHeels #BEATDOOKWEEK @Rameses_UNC #OurBlueIsBest… https://t.co/JOCUvS6FWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog @ChrisCoon4 Correct me if I’m wrong but our Mr. Big Shit investigators are most likely Democrats the… https://t.co/rTJWIr9zDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler Reddick is catching Christopher Bell. But I'm sorry guys, today has been a lackluster Xfinity Race  Hopefully… https://t.co/jKdTLq1L87]]></document><document><![CDATA[yo deja was amazing but i just slept for 14 hours in my own bed and that was the most beautiful sleep ive had in a while]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Bike Factory of Charlottesville - @bikefactorync in Charlottesville, VA https://t.co/BQytftfv8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a little to nice to be driving around on kids day, these orange vests everywhere really get ya but it’s #forthekids]]></document><document><![CDATA[View of San Francisco from Alcatraz @ Alcatraz Federal Prison https://t.co/r0gIGuFTbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most efficient fast food! (@ Chick-fil-A in Wilmington, NC) https://t.co/AXokgy5CvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#aboutlastnight 🤣 🤷🏻‍♀️ good times and good music with paulcauthen and new friends @ Love and War in Texas-Plano Au… https://t.co/6hcEfh1Y5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisWelch77 The original pancake house is in Burnsville too.  It’s terrific with its 10,000 calorie breakfast selections]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are going to piss a lot of people off when you start doing what’s best for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this news to you? Stay current with all the news from ASU and earn Pitchforks toward great rewards! https://t.co/Jktysq0j6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plan your next big change for next school year: (11) eliminate all vacation and weekend homework. Eliminate all homework below 9th grade]]></document><document><![CDATA[When all is gloom, may we sow hope @ NEW YORK CITY -  'Never lose hope, my dear heart. Miracles dwell in the invisi… https://t.co/hYHeNLdKDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current conditions. #snow #portland #actuallytigard #whereisspring #video #slomo @ Tigard, Oregon https://t.co/jUjrWEwwI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBrizz3 @marklevinshow Democrats are enemies of White Supremacist Nationalist. And proud of it! https://t.co/XECfiqwMJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh, it’s only Wednesday!!! 🐪🐫🐪 (@ UPS Orlando Hub in Orlando, FL) https://t.co/ESQ9GNd0Hx https://t.co/tRsPZ0CNWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing my sister with her newborn makes me wanna start a family so bad 😫😫😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwil @JTeague2Creeks @JasonIsbell I just think the federales were ok with the cause]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephen_Speaks @BigBubba74 @BIGEASTMBB @DePaulU @DePaulHoops @RamblersMBB What’s this from? Beating Memphis in the… https://t.co/vVjos6wCOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends invite friends to play Moon REKT on HXRO -  Get 100 $HXRO on me! https://t.co/C8EV0z9pQW   #airdrops #bounties #freebies #giveaways]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Maine’s Opportunity Tax Credit enough to lure professionals?  25 percent of engineering grads take first job out… https://t.co/shtdyan5Xs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkimflores @Tay_Floressss Congrats!  What a great accomplishment!  Go get ‘em!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulipsinJune Always will be loyal to my current Detroit underachievers... but love gritty, mad love for golden and… https://t.co/m5nQzs4DMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump former lawyer #MichaelCohen .@MichaelCohen212 is expected to accuse the president of criminal con… https://t.co/F197mjaZIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#50Cent on the Hunt for His $30,000 from ‘Love &amp; Hip Hop’ Star Teairra Mari, Wants #Bank Records https://t.co/SpERkBKKmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veryharrowing Maybe. But there'll at least be some heavy pushback against it on her behalf, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#westernkeychain #keychains #acrossleatherstudio #acrossleather @ Across Leather https://t.co/U4oSREFjgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every year is new shenanigans. Never gets old and I love it. #MakeItReal #LetsGoVCU #StuMagic https://t.co/7kvzvZ64gj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the brithday gift rounds_complete_11 @sennmama. Always great seeing you and the fam @ Sang Dao Restaurant https://t.co/zzQYFIxMpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Cohen sing at the gym. @ Texarkana, Texas https://t.co/WMvGho3ss2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lennon and Ella took me out for a hike the other day.... https://t.co/MBC8t57gPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's a beauty 😍  #251WpnWrx #Ruger #M77 #Hawkeye #Nikon #ProStaff @ Foley, Alabama https://t.co/txYjqwknO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RT_com I was hoping this was satire! Montana is a beautiful place. How about we sell them California, New York, an… https://t.co/QsoOH26RN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[PREP BKG: Charleston 55, Lincoln 32, FINAL  Lady Tigers go to 25-1 and are the No. 1 seed at the regional tournamen… https://t.co/JTVT1Jp8re]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful night in fort pierce. Good night world.  . . . . .  #aerialphoto #aerialphotography #airjournal… https://t.co/S9SuPbRDm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My prayers are with my UMC brothers and sisters. But sadly I don’t know how this ends without a fracturing of the d… https://t.co/MRvyjg1gAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Who shall ascend the hill of the Lord? And who shall stand in His holy place?” Psalms 24:3... #OnlyJesus #grace #faith #victoryinJesus]]></document><document><![CDATA[For an industry so dearly lacking in diversity, we have some talented and insightful women worth following. I did n… https://t.co/4tczdpYuRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rory also leads the charge against foreign fans. He’s a terrible example of football fandom and should not be asked… https://t.co/ltqS4tV7lg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me think of the tree in the Feywyld where Vex got the bow. #CriticalRole]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to run with the track team tonight! I miss running with the team! #bremencrosscountry #runtolive #livetorun @ B… https://t.co/2fnbzLPoKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few photos from Tech Rehearsal for Broadway/LA2 “If I Could’ve Been”.  Tickets for both shows on 2/23/19 availabl… https://t.co/XisFaX5O6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VISportsTalk @larryelder It’s not enough.  Buying an electric car and trying to reduce your carbon foot print, is not nearly enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SavedBy11413993 @socalaura @BOLLA67_ @WhiteHouse @PressSec It’s *you’re,* stupid.  And 3 million more Americans vo… https://t.co/70sRhOKHTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ron_1943 Thanks Ron for the @facingwestmusic song RT! Have an awesome night and week, my friend!__✍️😎🎶🎶🎶🎶🌙🌞🌞🌞🌞🌞🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, and we went to a globe shaped room made of stained glass. Run by Christian Scientists. They put #Hull on it cos… https://t.co/NFpdEuEomL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe Since @JoeNBC and the panel made such a point of trying to pin down @Hickenlooper on being a capitalis… https://t.co/mOnBJr9zGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle You live in the darkness,  come out you gym teacher in a dress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He did it again!! #TrueStory @FariasJacob go listen https://t.co/6rm17Xu7rb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffEKahn They’ll have to dfa someone making money to carry anyone they didn’t last year after Morrow comes back. It’s actually crowded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this day in 2010 I beat Heavy Rain for the first time.  (This is a very @MightyQDawg tweet)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else look at their own profile and pretend they are some random ass person of their crush and judge their ow… https://t.co/XIjWZNf3Sg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProspectJesus how high are you on Matt Strahm as a sleeper candidate? Would you give him a roster spot over someon… https://t.co/aooTBmzVWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confirming that @petermurphyinfo made it to @TheChapelSF!! https://t.co/t5uMW4iGO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zachary Miller, Beloit College Baseball - Sophomore | LHP   Pitch Relief in Game 3, the second game of a DH vs Conc… https://t.co/H6ph8AVdEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's amusing. #humor #snicker #smirk #cute https://t.co/prhcd8T0qK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVsJerry @FranchiseOK can we please have the normal post game show back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prime_tn I am so incredibly proud of the team we are becoming. The kids are sponges for knowledge and the coaches… https://t.co/6sADlM7fN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luiscarazo @GeekandSundry @erikaishii @BDaveWalters @vampiresnvino @Cyndancer @AlexWard777 An amazing and badass a… https://t.co/Wx3KHWescv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all really okay with the No opts for either side being a philly fan on the Harper contract? Y’all think he will b… https://t.co/DPQ6olHZnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera yapping his baloney about reasonable men who fear the insanity of Donald Trump. Get a grip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grand rising to everyone hope you have a beautiful and prosperous day.  The first step in connecting the dots is th… https://t.co/EvTDek8fuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You believe Putin and Un when they have no proof, but call Cohen a liar when he has plenty of proof.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old water pipes on 6th Ave being replaced. These cast iron pipes look like they installed during Mayor Howse’s admi… https://t.co/BxNiWGgzbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Johnny Storm: Voice of Reason?! This must be a “What If—?” Universe.… https://t.co/9U8GKBdLEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Not because I desire a gift: but I desire fruit that may abound to your account.” Philippians 4:17 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still sick but feel amazing today. Me not working out the last 4 days really took a toll on my body. I fault like shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHerd @ColinCowherd @JonGoulet @gregtoohey @JoyTaylorTalks @jasonrmcintyre  https://t.co/DL9oUYNVKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[CTE or no CTE? That is the Question. with @FluxBionetworks @EMPWR_FDN Available on iTunes: https://t.co/ri4k4PMEUR https://t.co/Ssaqb8ybqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Canadian Ladies kick buttock. #canadianpunk #winnipeg https://t.co/kJk1HVDUtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Everyone wants prosperity. Hard work gets us to the goal. Giving and taking, let the sharing pave the foundation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[México Star #ferry @bajaferriesoficial #somosbajaferries #bfmultimodal #bajaferriesoficial #lapaz… https://t.co/DT0YhMRZbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I do they can put on a dress but genetically you are still what you were born as there are definite physiologic… https://t.co/MT8FghD5wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing says canada quite like a can of labbatts https://t.co/lWpqlZL1pI]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to be kidding. The propaganda machine is live and well on the left. You afraid that the truth gets out in… https://t.co/KYu9IriwuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DestroyedMsnbc @mattgaetz ARE YOU INSANE? DID YOU HEAR THAT FROM ONE MAN ON HIS TWITTER? TREY GOWDY HAD 8 YEARS. https://t.co/btLxMYWQUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hatchjenn @ribeyeszn @steelerdiva @AphexCody I’ll say this all to see:  @hatchjenn HAS NEVER BEEN WRONG ON https://t.co/UyZybU2foS!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewdreeew @ayoitsramsey @ayyolex Me with a gold four loko and tequila]]></document></documents></author>