<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse He's seeking asylum with KJU in North Korea in exchange for a penthouse in a new Trump-Kim Hotel on the beach.  Traitor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Falcon Dive IPA by @LakeEffect_LLC @ St Johns School Bowling Alley — https://t.co/vNP2f7oJoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming up in 30 min! If you’re out of the listening area, you can stream here: https://t.co/x7eJxDrXTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WizardDeal @bourbonblog Slightly more refined spiciness but incredibly more expensive. I do like it though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheyCallMeAzul @JesseGladsaget No Lebron won’t be giving that fact to them . Neither will the fact their best  def… https://t.co/3aD6jEr4k3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Is ignorance required to be a Trump supporter, or is being stupid and amoral enough?]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are many REASONS why @risssaa_ritt and I can’t wait to party with @jillianjmusic and @zdevin on Saturday! 🌩🎸🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @BetoORourke, how much money are you and @SpeakerPelosi getting from #ElChapo to keep our borders open to drugs… https://t.co/D8Iazu0ydq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wonkmonk_ And they can only be forcibly exchanged for US$ debts...all other exchanges therewith are voluntary. https://t.co/1ESyyLalCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynxDeplorable what the heck is that fury thing and how did you get in your car?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brain: dang I'm so sleepy 😭😴  Me: go to sleep then  My Brain: fuck you bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaPerino “Stirring” !!??  Once again our President was slammed with no way to respond to Chairman Cummings’ untr… https://t.co/a1mSBOD8ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bartender Test. This guy asks you for another round. You— A) You slide him another Straffe Hendrix Tripel and dram… https://t.co/EKwqyXaquA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamGale2 I'd also highly recommend this debate between @jasonfurman and @StephanieKelton. My conclusion is tha… https://t.co/eolpesYmak]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘iin wees nimiipuu ✊🏽 One time in class someone told me “oh you’re an Indian” and I was like uhhh no I’m Nimiipuu..… https://t.co/dlejod37aE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephanieRoche9 Hi, We would be happy to assist you. See our innovative work here: https://t.co/0kK0depliy     Kin… https://t.co/9lzllZFmxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir Just want you to know you have a great employee. Beverly who was working the check in area this mornin… https://t.co/BdaihzIUKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is this one driver from Eagle Pass that always wants to beat everybody in Loads. Boy looks like a jack rabbit… https://t.co/enNFXNjOfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This movie has always left me inspired. So thrilled I finally got to see it on a big screen! #TheLastStarfighter "T… https://t.co/h5rTmi6QyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[June 2018 - when Dennis Smith Jr gave rookie Luka Doncic a “Hello Kitty” backpack and told him to wear it all seaso… https://t.co/MZIKj6ai0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNAM es la segunda mejor universidad de América Latina del QS World University Rankings | El Economista… https://t.co/RoHsZp2Hgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Date night with #furryfamilymember #rescuekitty #neveralone #mylifewithcats @ Santa Maria, California https://t.co/iRsDVCoaza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c3convertase People pay lip service about depression and mental illness, but when it comes to action and compassio… https://t.co/Ytd0XU9KUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeTrout will forever be our champion, dude is the nicest and most humble person you’ll ever meet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fbuechsel I’m so bummed that I missed this session. I’m @vtimd is too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kelly Services is hiring in Richardson, TX! Click the link in our bio to apply: Business Analyst #KellyJobs #KellyServices]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning!  Is it Raleigh or London?  Dense Fog Advisory in effect through 9am for most of our viewing area on t… https://t.co/1MrYcQkteN]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/7brmcCtzkg: NCIS Star Mark Harmon Reveals the Secret to His Long-Lasting Success: 'You Earn Luck'.… https://t.co/POxxWrG51D]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TuckerCarlson is not coming off well in this story. I normally appreciate his skepticism but the evidence against… https://t.co/JZhryhgMd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear to god if FDB rolls out with a 3-4-3 on Wednesday I will lose my mind. 5 games in and it’s not working. Make a change or get out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited about this, but have the slightly uneasy feeling it is the kind of thing that should be homed in… https://t.co/I8rvDPathA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rbnyc1995 @AAidanbird @Tristenb_ @RobertCGriffin @AOC @guardian Can’t we find a balance - with all our wealth and… https://t.co/MVw6lnPNRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont fake like you are helping! Get in there and force the pass! https://t.co/Q6yQ6qkRtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the craze!  Everyone is doing it.  Friends and family are invited to follow our Alamo 15P team page, live stre… https://t.co/cyVaeE8vOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CreoleAlliance @nolamomma @SteveScalise Ask about fake news. Its in ya schools, not on the news. Day1USA HISTORY 3… https://t.co/k67A0h0zGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting with the time a man trying to escape from the police ran up in this bitch and we had a whole police chase… https://t.co/bYbaDabBTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFR_org Congress willingly gave those powers to the President to avoid accountability.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a bunch of homework to get done today and all I got done was one short assignment :) but I bought AirPods and… https://t.co/wNWBa5pNry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look closely at his eyes. The pupils fill literally the whole iris. He was high.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Breaking News:     Sen. Martha McSally says she was raped by superior Air Force officer     Via @nypost        https://t.co/r0K6rIOjo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[New video coming out today stay on the look out don’t forget to subscribe to Rugenus to never miss out on a new video!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why's my mind on autopilot all the time? I'm feeling like the world's back on rewind, I can't seem to find the words to define]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lolalissaa My 2 yr old can prob catch cheese in his mouth SMH I’d fail]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve got Fox in the hen house/white house spreading propaganda for an unindicted co-conspirator. “We’re talking ab… https://t.co/EG6Jt3P1jI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tim42382232 @SenFeinstein @davidcicilline @NRA No argument. When they arrest Trump we do not expect the MAGA Terrorists to behave civilly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmann49ers @boscofootball @MelTurpin5 @oregonfootball @usnikefootball Oct 2017 it was up... https://t.co/pR8mhp57yw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make it the greatest Thursday ever 🚴🏿‍♀️🚴🏿‍♀️🚴🏿🚴🏿 @ Flywheel Sports https://t.co/iiag1OgqPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eloiseat6 @kim My bad MEADOWS was the 50 Shades of RACISM squatting like a toad in his chair pouting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spenceation19 @onemangang97 I hear the fries are awesome to @LambWeston]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I worked Pink Beautiful Trauma World Tour 2019 at Amalie Arena. https://t.co/gDlCIeZWyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3onyourside She was guilty since she was aware she could have a seizure while driving. And the judge just gave her… https://t.co/0JfWtcupIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_gundo @_KRock88 @MadDropBear @jbullbama listen, RESPECT! But damn it’s good it’s over! 😭🙌🏽🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WAF_Team has charged me over $1,120 in 2 visits to service and still didn’t fix my #ford. Now they say “it’s somet… https://t.co/dRZ7nIgAtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Millennials are saddled with debt and rarely use all their PTO. So, would you trade your vacation days to pay off y… https://t.co/3WYfhfdnK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think alot of said shit in text can be masculinized by emoji placement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanClarkSports Oh you mean the $3M man who’s veteran leadership contributed to a historically bad 2018 Os team?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieLittleTV @HailieDeegan @ToyotaRacing Hailie is definitely going places in @NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveRamsey my wife is utilizing envelope system for groceries. She says she’d be glad to negotiate commission for… https://t.co/Ritc1PfCFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems like a good start to the evening (post-fútbol). #nopo @ The Barlow Tavern https://t.co/iNeSXNLyt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learned something new tonight with my club shooting! Can’t wait to share these edits 📸🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajflynn43 I also have used with players to tell them to stop being static. Get into an “open space”. Move with spe… https://t.co/s6l4r3xmS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The very glare-y proof that it’s been so long since I last rode Knott’s Voyage of the Iron Reef, that I forgot it w… https://t.co/ULnA2ppB9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @PressSec the POTUS cannot create an environment of violence or stir violent feelings and thoughts and the… https://t.co/T1KRDKsSk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because you’ve got this... #goodmorning @ iHeartMedia DC/Baltimore https://t.co/aLdLPiyquL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up with a paragraph from my Ex... bruh I’m not bout to take the FCAT this morning 🤷🏽‍♂️ *Blocked*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sidney_capelupo Lot of shit in my mind yesterday. I swear boy, there’s some days that I just wanna wake up back at… https://t.co/vphvVCTZLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loc8ingoil Both teams looking to bolster their scoring. Dallas very much needs secondary scoring. Nashville he is part of Plan B options]]></document><document><![CDATA[We the people of the United States in order to..... Not us and them. If you can't follow the path to forever peace… https://t.co/64RVMzlGef]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy Family 170 pound junior Hunter Branson advances to the quarterfinals with a 10-2 major decision of Jefferson’s… https://t.co/AYTKIKk5yD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FelizMiércoles el paraíso si existe se llama #LaPaz Baja California Sur. Foto Alejandro Añorve https://t.co/dnwPrF4Pbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Vista do Quarto #View #Westgate #WestgateLakesResort #Orlando #Trip #Travel #Tour #Turismo #Viagem #Tourism em Wes… https://t.co/CGfpK7yKmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kent St. Gun Girl popped her pants. Ted Nugent is an admitted pants pooper. Is this correlation or causation!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrunchyKong @thepunisher6353 @Retrogamebrews @wrytersview @replicantpinky @AtariVision @AtariVisionWife… https://t.co/E4DXUW6LTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday to my mom piegemo and my sis stephcari2000 — thx apple for the apple watch challenge… https://t.co/4K4fD70MNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I get another Mac book air or maybe a pro or a completely different type of laptop? Help me out plz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter Soilder ha sido la única película buena del que ha hecho Marvel. https://t.co/AYUsTZQ8ds]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫This Is the Day by @normanhutchins, from #SoundHound https://t.co/3rn3C0Adtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated Tell the DNC not to let him run in the primary or just calm down and vote for your preferred candi… https://t.co/xd5Iq8378S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankEaves21 You were probably looking at all the fans in the Holmes Center 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always expect to see this guy at my favorite hangout @ Khartoum https://t.co/wgtOJ2jTi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein To any and all advertisers of FOX News, it's either them or us.., the American people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 Well most don't want to see her mug either. Might be one of few wins we all agree on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMek This is what we need to do in this country @realDonaldTrump  !!! FOLLOW HIS EXAMPLE!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We dont mean to kill or terrorize civilians. And I won't hear it from any mouth breather that the Taliban are in th… https://t.co/JnhdmetQr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren I hate to be negative but giving money to you is like flushing it down the toilet]]></document><document><![CDATA[ᕼᗩᑭᑭY ᗷIᖇTᕼᗪᗩY @mconforto8  HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE 26!! I forget 😂 https://t.co/8wszYdo7BF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VenusBatsonRuss @ridingwithc @RyanAFournier  I guess this little princess doesn't pass gas she's so perfect but stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your @JoanneFOX5 card here!! Signed for $1,000!! @GoodDayAtlanta #fox5atl https://t.co/IwojguZEzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Len9671 @Sequencer16 @Briteeye777 YOU ARENT A PATRIOT. ENEMY OF USA I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable t… https://t.co/qnyxi3yvTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suns up your already late dept. #50s #MarxToys R-35 tin litho #robot #battOp some wear but complete all original fr… https://t.co/cE8bWKMC1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dirkriehle @migueldeicaza Nope. The Thanos character in the comic books goes back to the 70’s. That was an intenti… https://t.co/P7eN9IeoC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MadeaFamilyFuneral was so poorly done. I feel like I could have written a better movie, or at least one that doesn… https://t.co/mdv8MZNGFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ballpark Hitting today in shorts 4:45-6:00 PM; You’re responsible to set up your station. Report at 4PM Bell.… https://t.co/TEPjqq6YlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coltybrah U need to work on ur boxing then. U should never be uncomfortable then]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 3 quarters game tightens. @TravisHoops now trails 46-41 to @HISDAthletics #SamHouston here @CyWoodsHoops gym.… https://t.co/jXjhMihClt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chasity_kerr @Education4Libs @justkoldad_eric All areas left open are to rough mountainous and too far from popula… https://t.co/vBCIshetNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just really wish I had someone to talk to that was as into power rangers as me. Today kinda sucked being the only o… https://t.co/IKQVV2Y2YC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeriatricGamer I hope so as well. Never got to play it either (don't own a PS4). Switch would be perfect. Fingers crossed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoscowTimes @IlvesToomas “They came back To widows, To fatherless children, To screams, to sobbing. The men came b… https://t.co/41bMz44zZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsROCK2019 @DocDarnell Altered beast...X-men...TMNT...Simpson’s...street fighter...off road...Area 51...Wrestlefest...pac man]]></document></documents></author>