<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@F2K_Slysssa @ZalaeHS @PathraCadness @Ike__HS Fixed it https://t.co/pWqliUQq8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[lost sight of the big picture for a second, never will i do that again 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thankyou #60days60verses  #charlesedwardmusic  #iappreciateyou  shout out everyone listening in if you havent hear… https://t.co/TgXtLqDLbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veronicavogx "...Y este maldito verano que me tiene dolidas las manos en mi cama sudando por ti..." Atte. Caramelos de Cianuro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WhenIGetBulliedOnTwitterI give a shit, it’s Twitter https://t.co/SwjPCXcwOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RCMB323 @renersharp @tobias_bass Something I think about a lot is if you took Tariq Owens and put him on last year… https://t.co/cws3Owm4Cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanAstin My 2week encounter with you parents agrees with what you said. Lovely, humble people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was amazing to meet my mini fans up close &amp; personal. Thanks for making it possible @CPG_Corp 👏 #respect]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealBrianMartin @primediscussion @JasmineLWatkins @FeitsBarstool Damn ok you convinced me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate 50 years of the Cincinnati Home + Garden Show with Tyler this weekend and Ty next weekend!… https://t.co/0nv1qc4iHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[High School Dayz @ Chatham Hills, Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/WWqh4bcaBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me in art classes i already made an A in at another school and cultural events lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So flippin excited!  My book is done and at the printers.  Shipping on April 30!  Presale on this link! 30% off dur… https://t.co/2ee6tKO6X4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandparents did me dirty. They knew I was coming home this weekend and went back to South Carolina. 😑 I’m really not loved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicenteFoxQue Estas pero bien pendejo , que lástima por ti , ni por tu edad te tienes un poco de respeto chachalac… https://t.co/MldBXzIlHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chillin 😈 @2kCompGames @Big_Brudda_PURP @ayo_RANKem @WizardsDG  https://t.co/kTocpCdFy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joining the 8G Band on Late Night With Seth Meyers for a few days, today’s day 1.  Thanks for having me @erx11… https://t.co/w42hxiMw9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andyscout I just sat here for a minute trying to think of a Weezer pun, but can't]]></document><document><![CDATA[A moment of silence for my Twitter drafts that met their untimely end when I got a new phone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the Springfield boys basketball team on winning the district championship 🤑👀😤 🏀@eynon12 @eohlin_10 @SLHS2state]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol here come the excuses 💀 yall have 3 potential first rounders besides Zion and still lost. i don’t wanna hear it]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Association of Blacks in Corrections and Justice, NAACP, ACLU! I have been in contact with all of them.… https://t.co/V9iOZZWiw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I be the law and we do like India at big horn pull together kick this boards shit ass we make sure… https://t.co/d3H1YGv3oC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jalusam @clubparagon Yes you will! Here is your reminder! https://t.co/rm2vRYzSG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Ms. Fat Booty by @MosDefOfficial on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/wUyroykgqU https://t.co/zX9VKdjaln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerGroepper I bought four pair of 3s last year. They are my favorite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleHamstra @mikeaustinwest @MsLeeTeacher @WCPSS @OppCulture @omearajen @Donnell_Cannon @WCPSSTeam Check out… https://t.co/nVrtYq3d9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart @frederickhiller To those of us across the pond this sounds depressingly familiar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pookah72450 @sam_vinograd @realDonaldTrump For someone who claims to be so smart you sure don’t look like life has… https://t.co/52pzTIzM4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yarby @iamkatyhill I can corroborate that, as I've used them now for almost two months at Yarby's recommendation. Difference maker for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clare had some amazing goals and overall a tremendous display of footwork !]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moral and intellectual vacuity of the right wing intelligence should be a primary topic in the national convers… https://t.co/vOj3403Tw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I think you said several trillion drug dealers and duct taped women have been caught.  Glad you’re… https://t.co/1x5cXmd4ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner Congratulations Andy.  I'm glad you are now a hope to live kind of guy now, helping the rest of us dea… https://t.co/fHSz5Kmd3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Erik Brown of Douglas Elliman Co.'s 1400 + SF Renovated Los Angeles Condominium off market, Coming Soon!… https://t.co/VOWlOw3Bxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newbalance for those who don’t live in gated communities. Can you stop branding the box for the whole building To… https://t.co/8u4RbNlP5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packed house last night, but these were my favs... #HawkEm https://t.co/0I5ivMfeP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy BDay to that guy @CoachEmbleton ......#GOILLini #happybirthday #ILLGang https://t.co/GuuZa60Xxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRA @Jim_Jordan This is disgraced Congressman Gym Jordan. He was a wrestling coach at Ohio State. He stood by sile… https://t.co/ZSCMJ7w4Yy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inside, in bed, under the covers with my electric blanket at 5, the highest it’s ever been. Not sure if I’m leaving… https://t.co/T5maiymOfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[$AMAT LOVE THIS NAME. Looking at March monthly expiry and like the $38, $38.5 and $39 calls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting my hw our the way for this week cause I’m a be lit next week for my both of my friends birthday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBrindisi12 @BostonGlobe Can I help you? WBCN 14 YR. I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth.… https://t.co/jxV6jWOtBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Why you so  hung up on rich  people? You jealous? or upset they beat you to the winners circle? Quit the f… https://t.co/NbLS67IzJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always forget that not everyone in ny knows that buffalo chicken should have blue cheese not ranch 😂 #AreYouWithUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what the situation is. #djfrankyuntouch #untouchabledjs @ Baldwin Harbor, New York https://t.co/hwSEq0LZQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller    Can’t make up an answer on this one.    Ted Lindsay.  #RIP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with love! @ymcnair has been such an incredible blessing to me on my journey. Aside from bringing… https://t.co/C3wYU4xfpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kailah_casillas @lindsaylohan If she wasn’t on drugs and that’s just her being weird then that’s sad too 😂😂😂 fucking love kailah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robd_statfactor @Beastof_Bourbon @BleacherNation @CubX3 Starter gets a DH in my plan bro. Stop arguing with what I… https://t.co/899dspJJnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeff_Portland @terrycrews Yes, I am white. But there are millions of blacks that believe the same way and refuse t… https://t.co/SG00cqoQQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have a great beer. Other times you have 4 great beers.  #cellarmanearl #nightshiftbrewing… https://t.co/P0lOxPTtXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelobULTRA Why did you stop making regular Michelob? The ultra version is awful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeytonRoyceWWE tonight looks a amazing!!! Her hair is on point!! #iconics #EliminationChamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aja1969 @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Your grandkids will roast in hell because Trump is doing nothing about cli… https://t.co/pVeOKgpHWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey friends, you like bunnies? Here's a page of lil bunny sketches I did for a soon to be announced Halifax biz.  .… https://t.co/lbjkXDitMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natashaxxgrey Are you overworking the poor man or is he maybe in the closet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scareesheree @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump You snow Mexicans need to mind your own business]]></document><document><![CDATA[The countdown to spring begins... 10 #onedayclosertospring  #iamcanadian🍁 @ Arthur, Ontario https://t.co/Zz9TwLHH0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danshield @Gazimoff Apple Music is $16 and change, no thanks :P I don’t need more than 5, and it plays nicer with… https://t.co/6e4JfqI6NB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DNuggetsfan @easybootysniper @SportsCenter Haha that program you have access to, sucks. Their offense isn’t better… https://t.co/q58RzBci67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricBehan2 @laurenruss2 @ChloeeMiller98 @AtticusBohr34 @Triple_PG @RMothersell @olivia_r10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gipsemoon @ModelosVipMx @EscortxxxMexico @Evas_Escorts @ESCORTSPREMIUMX Nos vemos en mty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing makes me more mad than realizing I left my charger in my truck once I’m already comfortable in bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to see Beck &amp; Cage the Elephant at FivePoint Amphitheatre from @ALT987FM. https://t.co/G88ECIVo8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think he goes to one the Bay Area teams, Raiders or Niners. #AntonioBrownSweepstakes https://t.co/xHkWMh3u3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard ESPN announcers say Dukes star Zion goes down with injury and air sucked out of the building. As a Racer fan.... I can relate]]></document><document><![CDATA[#gooddaydc I understand about how superiors treat you ,I was told at univ of md AFROTC that I'd never get a pilot s… https://t.co/gFmgW9GLgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[TAMBIEN URGE QUE EL IMSS MODERNICE SU CUADRO BASICO DE MEDICAMENTOS,PORQUE EL ACTUAL ES ARCAICO. franciscodueas35@yahoo.com.mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Jeni's Splendid Ice Creams - @jenisstl in Saint Louis, MO https://t.co/0Lm6VnEIYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[ISSUES 📰 | #Repost flawless.fab ・・・ #flawlessfabfashion - Elliot is an amazing Fashion Professional featured in thi… https://t.co/5qkUYtRjZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myCSPN is a looking for an experienced CX Associate.   Interested? Learn more at: https://t.co/m3R4fBAJnb or conta… https://t.co/twT387MUSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone go ahead and give @jordyinadaze a listen his SoundCloud in his bio please and thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stage is set. Literally.  #ThankYouDoan #Coyotes #OurPack #WPGvsARI https://t.co/KQpxvgbefL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianSciaretta @estyles_NYtoMN @DisgruntleUSMNT Long would be a backup CB to miazga and brooks anyway, but people… https://t.co/KWBBFatKW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, I though Thor was the God Of Hammers!?  Are you grinding my beans, @btlpodcast?  https://t.co/lMFmhHBuvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iron Sharpens Iron. Next Sunday: the Iron take on the talented @aafcommanders from the Western Division. Be at the… https://t.co/qrcNQpGezo]]></document><document><![CDATA[State 529 Consortium Launches Education Assault On Student Debt https://t.co/vVzN1MbMgp https://t.co/buTZfasjRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BayouBun It took my car from Youree drive all the way to 49 to get warm this morning 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[▕▔▔▔▔▔▔▔▔▔▔▔╲┈┈ ▕╮╭┻┻╮╭┻┻╮╭▕╮╲┈  ▕╯┃╭╮┃┃╭╮┃╰▕╯╭▏  ▕╭┻┻┻┛┗┻┻┛┈▕┈╰▏  ▕╰━━━┓┈┈┈╭╮▕╭╮▏  ▕╭╮╰┳┳┳┳╯╰╯▕╰╯▏  ▕╰╯┈┗┛┗┛┈╭╮▕╮┈▏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey y’all! There are just a few hours left to vote in today’s @KBOERadio New Music Challenge (link below)!☺️ Thank… https://t.co/zmrnJxIzTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zah_tab تا جایی که خاطر دارم سفارت به همون دفتر پستی که داستون رو براشون فرستادید میفرستند و فکر کنم همه دفاتر هم… https://t.co/Xy9ABJRGVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[my girlfriend will pop on Instagram at every red light on our 5 minute away destination, all in the name of dog videos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BujuOfficial - You have been missed more than you could ever know... #FreeBuju #Buju #MarkMyrie #BujuBanton… https://t.co/szSgihCp4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord help her forgive me for the side of me I showed her. Cuz god only knows I wouldve never done it sober. @RileyGreenMusic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even folks from Cleveland have chosen to fly out of @PITairport to PHX today (although to see the Tribe!).… https://t.co/QV3j9JjbxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmh_02 @CaptainKudles Ok, you’re trolling me. Nobody is this dumb. Consider me duped.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need Doris on the #PlayersOnly broadcasts. And all broadcasts please. @NBAonTNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curious to see how Weber looks tonight .. hasn't played well lately .. took a couple of 'therapy days' off practice… https://t.co/9PH7zMKpVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yvonnecarrasco @mikeoz “Now kids, when these hoes start to develop feelings, this is how you ghost em.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Romans58 @Patriot_Mom_17 @BreitbartNews Fantastic I'm glad Amazon is leaving New York again goes to show you how… https://t.co/0i1bmM9wQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday is #domesticviolence awareness. If you or someone you know is experiencing The Cycle of Violence, please s… https://t.co/aCkuq6Gf9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hollywood Casino Lawrenceburg - @hollywoodind in Lawrenceburg, IN https://t.co/FGMh3PqOm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Purdue’s last three field goals have been 2nd chance points, coming off rebounds any normal defensive team would’ve grabbed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian Yes, cuz i’m sure she can’t provide for her daughter without this event (not that I think she should… https://t.co/BgfKJyUQNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fox4kc Patrick, you should try our pizza place in Lee’s Summit, @pizzaandpours. It’s pretty awesome and On Deck Pi… https://t.co/LYE8blAWgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A chilly morning up north, but one full of gorgeous #sunrise skyscapes (the car fire against the blue was a #bonus… https://t.co/rkrj9fts3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I appreciate all @TorinDorn2 has done for our program including earning his undergrad degree and continuing to work… https://t.co/5wApy6ct0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Polixenes13 @CoverDrive12 @Andreas_Hopf I haven’t seen/ read anything that I’ve considered problematic from Andreas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burritoblaster You are living proof that Christ's death was in vain. You embody all of the worst aspects of our gl… https://t.co/SMOoZyhBtv]]></document></documents></author>