<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KrisCrockerKXLY Holy guacamole!! Funny and embarrassing at the same time i bet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@komonews This article conflates rich with middle class.  There are rich and poor in Bellevue.  There virtually is no middle class left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If people can’t figure out how to use #BirthControl to prevent #UnwantedPregnancies, then let’s focus on saving the… https://t.co/MZx4lfFF9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Grieving not only happens as a result of the physical death of a person, but also happens when experiencing the en… https://t.co/ou3Js1e5aR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grew up learning you take your hat off when entering a building as a sign of respect. You don’t really see that happen anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexHortonTX @GlennKesslerWP The linked AP article is worth reading too. “Prosecutors got court approval to seal r… https://t.co/ntIohPSWLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @realDonaldTrump Trump of course!  Mueller now needs to be investigated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 vídeos publicados, corre e t inscreve e me ajuda a construir esse material!!! #vidadeedutuber https://t.co/3DlTbLtI4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndrew_lawrence @chunkled Mike the headless chicken was a lifelong Republican!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX LYING LIKE TRUMP is unbecoming a new congressman and a veteran.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop the violence 🦍🥀.                                  #growingupblack #blackhistorymonth #blackhistory… https://t.co/3E9s3EdtFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our schools MUST adjust to our children. Not the other way around. Proud of this work. Grateful to thoughtful leade… https://t.co/EWCRO6b8ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[The work I do is extremely hard. My Eagles Crew makes all the work worthwhile. #birdsflyeaglessoar #Sherwoodmsccs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking News: Ukraine sends tanks and fighter jets to front line as Russian INVASION fears grow #BuzzVideo https://t.co/KE956OAx6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams you are trying to outrage the already insecure and angry Leftists with this ridiculous talk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasonstickers The Federalist Society, which probably has a fund for anonymous donations for various causes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whose rules? Digital Governance and the Pursuit of Technological Leadership. @CSIS https://t.co/Qke2R3H6Ff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Super Star! Love you more! @ Frontera Mex-Mex Grill https://t.co/mtMRsFrstP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/cZDzc2CI4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods Always blame me he woman Khloe. It takes two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe that seaess78 and markbobw’s amazing weekend is over!😢 So happy I was part of this lovely couples’ we… https://t.co/2Foss7Qy1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pongamos de moda la humildad y la amabilidad ....basta de creerse más o mejores por ser "bien perr@s" . #Miercoles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its really a thing 🙄 once somebody stole my hot pocket and left the empty box in the freezer. Somebody ate half of… https://t.co/ozR8ZZx8Gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[An interesting turn of events... #Oscars2019 #BestPicture https://t.co/LMLEZarVL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok but does anyone else wonder why one side of stairs in Hyland are super wide and the other you can barely fit one… https://t.co/VVOivxScgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who needs an alarm clock when there’s like 2 million birds outside every morning this week 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkraju Why are you still running your mouth about anything to do with investigating your swamp. YOU are big part o… https://t.co/sM2fFstAc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bedore I came away I said theres no way I'd be up at 6am in L.A. to be able to catch the match...  But it's coming… https://t.co/vjE63iYlRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday!!  The ☀️ is out and I want to play! 😈  Here ready to tease you @TheBrassClub 10-6 💋 https://t.co/90pZLBJeM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's opening night at tigersmusical! #guitar #ukelele #musician #musicals #musicaltheater #eastvillage #nyc… https://t.co/PcZ6OfftsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#elsaandanna The End.  #mskroll #secretlifeofteachers #ornerysisters #secrets @ https://t.co/ir0zEyW91pérèse, Littl… https://t.co/JBTbiRAXr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Designer Hog Rag from Hog Mob Merchandise! https://t.co/YosG6dKB2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaigenLeal FUCK NAH 😂 it's the type of shit that happens in Florida. I rebuke this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Untitled”  #Draw #Drawing #ProcreateApp #iColorama https://t.co/ni3JFRPVwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDenton_1138 I high-ly approve of these choices! ☺️🖤🖤 https://t.co/ioxL8uZk14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tipo se eu tocava em uma balada a parte só com o Ed Sheeran ou tocava só a parte com Beyoncé. Que loucura.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cricutexploreair2 #makingstickers @ Asheboro, North Carolina https://t.co/nwERspZqPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever look at your friends and just hope they find someone in life that will love them as much as you do? 😫😇♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCBSRadio can you tell me how strong are the wind gusts in the San Leandro area?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visiting Menomonee Falls and Student Board Member answers what is QI? “Culture shift-that puts power in the hands o… https://t.co/V3ezYGkYX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[To let someone know that they are noticed and appreciated is a good feeling and a great lesson for ‘my kids’!… https://t.co/AbuqZ9sAlv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldengateblond “I didn't wanna say it out loud but We can fix it if you don't like it sweetie...” 😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrystleKSN Hahha omg this is me everyday or on some random person’s porch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#caturday #calicosofinstagram #flerken @ Louisville, Kentucky https://t.co/hco68Z5LHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[We ought to be able to believe in justice but sadly that isn’t always the case!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the outside window cleaners are at your floor it can be distracting if you have focus issues 😁 but yay I have… https://t.co/ZBxfikSgZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my favorite twins in the entire world!!! I’d tell y’all to go out and celebrate well but I alread… https://t.co/TbhXn16NYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMei62 Curious..when did the Earth stop circling the sun and start circling Coulter?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewCoatney1 Luke doesn’t own a vest but he has a rain coat that his Aunt Sydney gave him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexXmlbfanx23 @MissCaliCarter @briteresi @MereGorman @juliiafrances @thekenzietaylor @Karma_Rx @VikingBarbie_… https://t.co/OGAl4d8JUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyHoffmeyer @AboutVirgos I think back on that sometimes like “how dare they”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets I would vote for any one of these. #votebluethroughandthrough]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Rocket at Paramount Studios During  Frieze Art Event bringing mission of bringing Art to inspire people’s inte… https://t.co/kFgw8rL6IQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Earthquake #Alerts See https://t.co/RqBRl60J9J Via @TheRealS0s ¤ 20% Ring of Fire;  ¤ Mag 5.5 - 8.9 ¤ Radius: 200… https://t.co/QZ9GzB7bgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You will not distract us from the Robert Mueller’s investigation.  You are a shamed man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trying to find the truth is not harassing.  However, calling people names and suggesting they have… https://t.co/uB5ggigNrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m convinced kaiti wants me to die of heatstroke and that’s why the thermostat was on 75.5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anselmoramos @claudesilver Completely agree, Anselmo! (And it’s what my next article is about !)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Is it really necessary to comment on impersonations? Just sayin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JournoRyan 😎my invitation must have gotten lost in the mail. Baseball has me now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EveLimpeiwen Maybe too long TT wake up like this fuck sad so down fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlySupport can you please DM me about an issue i’m having with an order? thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Since when did Limbaugh become the voice of reason? YOU are the criminal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosaIsiah @drjoy77 Often teachers have the strategies and skills, but they don’t get the resources that will make… https://t.co/jtGoHs4fyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blvck_hammer Gonna be waiting on it when you are old in a town too  It's never coming!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you wish upon a star.... 💫 🌟 🏰  . . . . . . #takemetodisney #takemetodisneytuesday #Tuesday #Tuesdaygram… https://t.co/SJeaFsTNhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackiedelbridge I LOVE YOU GUYS! I CANT WAIT TO PARTY IT UP W YOU GUYSSSS 😭 https://t.co/4nL1dkaPJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielTurnerPTF @RyanAFournier A bicycle is cleaner than both, I think the taxpayers in the Bronx should buy her one!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If I could write a check, I wouldn’t!” #Caturday  @venmo @ApplePayBR @Cassidy_Heiss @jackson_curve @suesue1258… https://t.co/SOQKUCu2Tj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when people come over because that means I have to put pants on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessWaltonYR And when will we be seeing you again on Y and R now that MY is out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brielarson @TeeVeeBen I find this less wierd than the Hertz/Captain Marvel commercial https://t.co/ieKWy2B7iM]]></document><document><![CDATA[when @Pouyalilpou said “so many people all around me yet I feel so alone” I felt that https://t.co/3k5mw3ZG9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Local businesses in Berwick are helping to honor Capt. Joel Barnes and the fire service community he leaves behind.… https://t.co/0mqFAGW3Ni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews He represents the all-powerful White patriarch who will mitigate the browning of America, punish gay pe… https://t.co/NADiNfm7kU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red 😍😍 #houstonnailtech #coffinnails #nailsofinstagram #valentinesnails https://t.co/JL8kCvYCqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s about a 10 day period each month where I’m either super depressed or super pissed off with no in between an… https://t.co/UvVGaZyhQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We will only grasp the staggering potential of our time if we create onramps that empower all people to participat… https://t.co/vzVM9nJEI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight I definitely failed all 4 of my tests this week https://t.co/kVjWaQMdaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the Oscars all cozy. 😇 #lulu #shihtzu #shihtzusofinstagram #bestfriend #puppylove #cozy @ Milton Hill, Mil… https://t.co/B9VXNKcWhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldie_berg1211 of course not holy shit lmao you know me better than that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan  "Fighting to do what we said?"  What was that? Run up the deficit to record levels? (I checked - you U… https://t.co/tIb8ImGxSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yard work and demolishing the sticks....pyro at heart! #pyro #firestarter #fire #yardwork @ Baton Rouge, Louisiana https://t.co/KvAxshCFH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_GrammarGeek Is there a chance that Bugs Bunny’s writers may have been parodying that poem?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamaalStreet @jillallenpv @rachelallen_10 @seakingsoftball @breezepreps @SoCalSidelines Way to go Hammer! 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GsjpJyoti @greatairi @SsanjayTaannk @IamSunitha777 @yogeychauhan @GCHDutta @u_mirella @panjami @UmeshBhadarka1… https://t.co/DzYtQIMkHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@viola_delgado @cinders404 @katie_wienke @catherinerusse2 @lyntonvilla @disolis @toongirl @berenaserena Excellent, Viola❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caption this. @ Main Street Station, Richmond, VA https://t.co/nJe7WZgyjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Neighbor chrishajjar_  jennahajjarmua #mua focusure #studio  3/07/19 #retired #bamf #photography… https://t.co/kJRgVEtNL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not lying when I say my friends snore louder than any mans I’ve ever slept with]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthonypjshaw So pretty. Was there gold at the end of that path like at the end of a rainbow? 🌈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accusation my butt. GOP DID NOTHING FOR 2 yrs. NO RISK TO DEMS. WE ARE NOT STUPID MR. BS. GOP LAP DOG. Your polls d… https://t.co/RKaVVPtGTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I realized how much of a defensive and overprotective bff I am wow I’m really out here giving all my love to my friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jflorez @_drazzari @boozychef @jillianne_gray @GailBenzler @cabernetfanc @SteveKubota @rr_pirate @DivaVinophile… https://t.co/Ry3xdfsPKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que triste que ya se va a acabar el mundo y aún no acabo la carrera ptm diosito]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking comfort, mama’s girl @ Porter Ranch, Los Angeles https://t.co/r9TkE1PhIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @RNcat50 Lock this slime up for life. Let the other prisoners deal with him!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fascinating research to inform how we evolve to meet their needs over the next 20+ years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope you happy, I hope you ruined this shit for a reason, I hope you happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FulmarsFinest You missed a great game! Hope your daughter had a great race!!!!]]></document></documents></author>