<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Interesting... I have had 3 friends sell their homes via Facetime ... saved a lot of money and said the transaction… https://t.co/ZwEGSAdA8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @justonepatriot Oh heck. Release it closer in and let’s enjoy the worm squirm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_dannyjameson @WONIDEE @WayneDupreeShow @AnnCoulter It's not over yet. Don't be so quick to jump and condemn. We'v… https://t.co/9FrX6lI9K6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaganotify @ElectricChap3l @ladygaga Don't misunderstand me Madonna's very important as far as reinvention and pop… https://t.co/GyhfzqLXEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Angieforbes_ Ya, the only ones that get a snow day are the schools  THAT HAVE THEIR STUDENTS BROUGHT IN ON A BUS, 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ Praise God that the mother has the patience of a saint and restrained herself from whooping that lady's a… https://t.co/tcXx654HDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 hours and I’ll be on a plane to go back to Virginia 🥺 Florida was so beautiful!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RRamirezVE Malparido hijo de puta ladrón y descarado. En el infierno se van a encontrar todos los Chavistas corrup… https://t.co/hAhYzsuAWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready @ Duckworth's Grill &amp; Taphouse Uptown https://t.co/04o0RaDzNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg Omg rabbit reveal or rabbit stew 😂 I'm gonna end up on #Scarypeople 😂 before this is over 😂… https://t.co/thnXi8Rz5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[sitting on the ice, roadtrips, bonfires, beers. love my girls🖤 @ Black Rock State Park https://t.co/h4e0WamWc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am totally blessed to have this wonderful man as my husband! He tells me I am awesome every day! @ Noblesville, I… https://t.co/YOkUuzqPfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sure miss those SAMbassador GiGs... talking bout all the wonderful things of Sam's Club. #samsclub @ Sam's Club https://t.co/Kr64JCfuTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MichaelCohen I want you to know that I believe you today. I applaud you on your difficult testimony to the Oversig… https://t.co/Ij4Dl4X7rl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaBujeda Good morning!  At what time Saturday morning will the Hart Bridge be closing for traffic? Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Chicago peeps! Headed to the Chi next weekend to be with my mama who will be on this panel to talk about her ex… https://t.co/DqID1iw5ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[Testing some makeup looks out for #SweeneyTodd the musical. I call this: TB positive-ly famished https://t.co/diHfqcabCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[5pm in Santa Barbara... @ The Lark Santa Barbara https://t.co/gtoyUQQmsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[we are watchin the spain park high school video in class today. pls pray]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Sister lives in Casa Grande and every time you go outside it smells like cow]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO..ALL MUSLIMS TAKE YOUR FGM, YOUR SHARIA LAW, YOUR HATE FOR ISRAEL AND AMERICA AND LEAVE OUR COUNTRY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrinceH16111945 Where were you?  You are so Royal that I understand why you are so protected. Must be very lonely for you at times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @thedailybeast Dear god wtf !  I miss the old days when I was pissed at Bill Clinton for getting a blow job in the oval !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@texas_fof My mind says why didn't I think of that???  Lol Have a great day. 😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so looking forward to gaining full confidence back with my body ❤️🥰😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Were really standing here taking bets on what @KaceyMusgraves is going to be wearing when she comes in stahe 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending @ASCDconf #Empower19?  Join me Saturday for an @ELmagazine #edleadership panel discussion w/ @a_rebora… https://t.co/UraqmjCN27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk @RepCummings Well congrats to Trump and N Korea!  And if u use AOC’s OWN WORDS. “I DONT SEE YOU TRY… https://t.co/OLOyBidyht]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all, this was me when this song came out. 4 years old pouring my heart out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do what you learned and received from me, what I am told you, and what you saw me do. And the God who gives peace w… https://t.co/w6AztfTiqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar Your degrading tweets about our president are not going to help you get elected. Just the opposite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMMOCOLLECTORR @Consti2tionAlly @scarletteskyMT @LaTiger7 @JoyHenley @javster87 @Ben11486471 @RainDownFire… https://t.co/CdWbRkkNZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Sales reps, The fastest way to ensure I never do business with you is lying to my EA and putting a meeting on… https://t.co/sPYUNROJQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evil_gnome So you beat me to her. For once you were thinking in advance. 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are either freezing in our apartment or burning in hell WHY IS THERE NO IN BETWEEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Is Agent Orange looking to take some FEMA funding for his wall?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5 - #7daybookchallenge - I challenge @Monica_Rahman25 https://t.co/X5psOkC7u6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s one of those days! I have headphones in my ears while sitting at my desk. I’m not listening to anything becaus… https://t.co/zqFGXa3Prp]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI - @wunc This Week in NC Politics https://t.co/Fg4TQFdgaR #ncga #ncpol @j_tibs @JohnLockeNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally fridayyyyy.....just want this day to be over so i can do some more baby shopping for his room 💙OGB💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yaya_iyana Basketball Highlights - Birdville VS Mansfield Legacy  https://t.co/sfBV2aAMyP via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferJJacobs Democrats/media are hated by most Americans for the constant attacks on our president @CNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter for a chance to win the Club 1924 Speakeasy Sweepstakes at https://t.co/IacihnmAhe https://t.co/qhIGsj3iz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stood behind a wall of girls at the sink with soap in my hands and I couldn’t get thru to actually wash them. I am still so sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[your life as a Christian should be attractive to people that aren’t Christians. we should be living in a way that s… https://t.co/WF8WWz9AKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the idea of two “tall poppies” holding each other up❤️ #WomenSupportingWomen #TallestPoppy #Empowerment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a lil sneaky sneak peak of my new un released single called VOID, performed live last night @HOBLasVegas 🌪🌪 https://t.co/jceeoEn9pS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is still a piece of shit.. keep banning me or removing my posts of me hoping Trump dies... I give no fucks..… https://t.co/CU5coXmd6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, I’m cool with trans people. Like I said: I think transitioning should be a last resort, but if you have, I’… https://t.co/B9gPnWPDiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you believe this is March?  We had a fantastic snowmobiling weekend at the cabin. The trails were better than t… https://t.co/w4SnwKPbjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BByrd_LMS My tailbone is actually going to hurt for a while. That’s what I get for trying to show off!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tony_sabol @MysteryCr8tve Wow... your “arguments” have just gone straight in to tinfoil hat territory. Put down th… https://t.co/wSCVntRPjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE TRUTH ABOUT NORTH KOREA! [DS] TRUMPED https://t.co/9g7d0ZsKvF via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’re living off what you heard because you don’t have the courage to find out for yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im about to beat the shit out of my sister is she doenst shut the fuck up every time she talks I hear a fuckinh whistle]]></document><document><![CDATA[You like my hair? Gee, thanks, just bought it. 💇🏻‍♀️😌 💁🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/uQC2czYaOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shakira - Chantaje (Official Video) ft. Maluma https://t.co/cWWcFDLpsm via @YouTube  🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomMorrisJr1 I like that shirt! #gunshow @danabrams @Sean_C_Larkin https://t.co/J4dH4vAw47]]></document><document><![CDATA[nuclear waste with radioactive content in 20 different areas populated by Syrian citizens of the occupied Syrian Go… https://t.co/HyiJu1BMTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing sucks more than feeling your heart break a little when a song comes on that holds so many memories]]></document><document><![CDATA[99 Virtually Free Marketing Ideas For Self-Published Writers | Self-Publishing Relief - Self-Publishing Relief https://t.co/VFcEgf2nnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saeger Robotics Warren STEAM Day 😎@WarrenFHSD #fhsdsteam @SaegerMiddle @FrancisHowell https://t.co/fK0iuvoe8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcarruthers He’s a legend I agree :) and yay for hugs!!! https://t.co/ojlgVRrzzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maxine madly tweetin BS because that little bartender in #NYC stealing her attention]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If I were to be an organ donor, it’d only be for my family because they’re my blood type” headass]]></document><document><![CDATA[and now i will recite my favorite poem..  you were alexa i was despacito and you played me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjxmas @jarpad @JensenAckles @RobertPlant @ledzeppelin @therealKripke I LOVED that episode, just saw it the other day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNNewsource @LorincJohn Sorry for the clark for their lost. Is Stephon's  baby mamma wasn't psycho and called the… https://t.co/fJrvuHkB5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so happy my mom didn’t have different niggas around me when I was a kid lmao some of y’all need to pump the brakes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Why shouldn't they? They are your station through one of your largest Donors Rupert Murdo… https://t.co/OawTZOqCCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[count your blessings, learn from the lessons life throws at you and don’t waste time dwelling on the past]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE this idea! Reminds me of @kimbearden’s tip in Crash Course to sit at each student’s desk to reflect on their… https://t.co/PO138aF5iw]]></document><document><![CDATA[DOES ANYONE KNOW SOMEONE WHO IS SELLING A WEEKEND 3 PAPAS AND BEER TICKET?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Invader 2019! Every contestant is Mr. Invader in my book! Sr. Advisory board well done! @ParmaSchools… https://t.co/smf053gcrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BL4K3Aspen @realDonaldTrump Really - you have no idea how much we give to other states]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just downloaded @AnnihilationMov and @AndoverMovie from @PrimeVideo to watch this afternoon while I knock out the 1… https://t.co/J8b5AdzkKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJRossReaders I just use the same one over and over - 😂😂😂. Not really 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s in our disruptions that real faith emerges. ~ Chris Railey #cmnetwork #CMN2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewsquitiro @FedEx @shoptalk 😆🙉😫I refuse to converse with robots. Does that make me sound so crazy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[a guy has a whole row to himself &amp; is sitting in the middle seat. satan]]></document><document><![CDATA[cording to guidance (let me get that wording!)F2F HAS TO BE RELATED so if referring for PT for strengthening, def c… https://t.co/2CtJhujXVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee has succeeded in nothing but increasing my anxiety, I’m still extremely tired and sad. Tomorrow I’m just drinking juice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AviBenayahu רפואה שלמה  אם אתה נשאר עם ברגים ברגל אתה תהפוך לחזאי התורן, לפני כל גשם תרגיש את זה. אם כך תצטייד במשכחי כאבים. והרבה. בדוק!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, my mom sent this to me at like 7:30am😂😂😂 She’s back on board with the #JONASBROTHERS! She literally watched… https://t.co/eQbVT7tfF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@humanekt @girlsreallyrule Yeah. My mother was 1,too. But she was poor. She flew under radar to appear sweetheart.… https://t.co/WM4yI609TZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[what’re some decent paying jobs in the cinci/dayton area that only require a high-school degree? i’m talking $11+/hour]]></document><document><![CDATA[People be telling me I can’t be a Pisces and I’m starting to believe it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_withoutalcohol Proud of you. I hate criticism, but when it’s right, it’s kind of better ♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll give you gas money I just can’t afford to use lyft cus it’s gonna be like $20 for two trips]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacLeodLisa @WomenON I’m Italian and this is an embarrassment. I  will never invite you anywhere. #AutismDoesntEndAtFORD #ResignLisaMacLeod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop Campaigns against anyone who did not like him, disagreed with him, investigating how Russian infiltr… https://t.co/YjzgPesMQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaeAnnChandra2 @WBrettWilson @BradWall306 @PremierScottMoe @jkenney @JustinTrudeau @liberal_party The motive behin… https://t.co/0ots6UlAQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Candice_124 hi, Candice, I'm  Pat. So nice to meet another *Dear* Dimash is so amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating 9 months with @Enterprise &amp; I could not be happier with my experience, mentors, and friendships 🙏🏽🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwardsMarc @rfhurt @JamesMartinSJ Good. Tell me home many homeless neighbors you shelter there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After working a show in Nashville and then 4 days at the lake visiting Dad, I am so thankful to have one more day o… https://t.co/2gvt0dSSmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emmett Till, and How America Remembers Its Darkest Moments https://t.co/7sg9abzEsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[You complete me. 🤤😍 @tacobell #foreveratacobellgirl https://t.co/GdlCRkkY3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can @express explain why I have size 6 columnist pants that fit great and I went to pick up a pair in a different c… https://t.co/qv851khfPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have such great credibility with people so whenever I mention things that I’m involved in, people are suddenly in… https://t.co/sOJarVdWyw]]></document></documents></author>