<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Better late than never. Here is fridays short video. The longer one will be up on YouTube later Saturday.  #Powder… https://t.co/k4RcoSKcr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was right around this time a year ago that h_rafferty22 and I first connected before we competed against one ano… https://t.co/vOMDyuqJ03]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump wants a wall! I want wall now! No one gives him his wall. It’s now an emergency! What’s the emergency? Sorry… https://t.co/BIkkACgUYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I take it with a grain of salt what a couple of unhappy players who are leaving have to say. If you are leaving put… https://t.co/Ps6icOlqd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Typical leftist Mr. Woods ....they spew  things all day / all night .  All emotional agenda driven… https://t.co/bBcH4sdoCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@venevision ustedes como empresa de medios y la familia Cisneros no tienen una solvencia moral para venir a hacerse… https://t.co/QwYBF6bM8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[That many miles left to go. What’s your lucky number? (@ Westborough Rest Stop in Westborough, MA)… https://t.co/hcS9HDV6vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garrettlittlegd @jasTHEEcreative Color lookups/LUTs and the gradient maps were my biggest game changers during my 365 project.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moshkovichnina @ChrisJZullo @SenSanders That's not take-home pay, and Amazon is an exception to the rule.  The vas… https://t.co/RIf7MwtmDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @WallinatWIS 8th Grade A-Day Science classes welcomed Mrs. Morrissey and Mr. Fisher to give their annual clean… https://t.co/7vP1KAtduz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaun_pletcher9 3 lbs 7 oz to be precise, I am very proud of the strength of my face thank you for noticing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrRuimy Ahem, many factors need to come in place for an Oscar nom, none being merit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy when you think about it 🤔  There’s a Difference in the type of women that become Mothers.... you could h… https://t.co/VwWcuq1Xgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Denied SSI or Workers Comp? If yes, please contact us for a free consultation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me gusta Janos, aunque no tenga Starbucks ni subway. en Janos, Chihuahua https://t.co/DtaNM5jZgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Washington MO at @stlmattress ,  Come see how you can save on @beautyrest 2019 collection #washmo #washmofair… https://t.co/BGHcjNKTeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mata_Diwi I'm always down as long as it's not raining and I'm not working :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Independent operators must commit to a relentless effort to be more efficient across all aspects of their business… https://t.co/w81WNGIPjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#watch this right now @MollyWhoppery #GSP #Pretends to #Retire - #Playing #Chess with the #King https://t.co/Yq0FhEDXh0 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Episode 7 of True Detective was great. Can not wait till the last episode on Sunday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s actually stopped snowing (there’s some sunshine there). Now it’s just the brutal wind blowing everything acros… https://t.co/ovGdp0wuLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loki2896 @gmtgames I found it odd that there’s only a bot for the FLN included. Wouldn’t some players want to play as FLN solo?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@art_stapleton Besides Murray/Haskins. The rest of the QBs are more comparable to Gabbert, Bortles, Locker and Pond… https://t.co/Ol7ZvSh1lF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really thought I was Superman today, walking around with my jacket completely open and leaving my long johns at home. Yes long johns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milikitty77 @carlosnatera69 @Vilma_Meche @Patria_ve @tuiteros_vzla @NicolasMaduro No tienen sentido del mega ridíc… https://t.co/EUg9o5aerl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly reminder: I'm a quiet man (not loud or talkative). If you hear talking, odd noises or whistling around thi… https://t.co/5CdVYhGiVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaltimoreSport3 tap fè pre-saison, konbien match li jwe apre apre match kont U-17 la?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theacesofficial Stoked To See @theacesofficial At their Sold Out @AnRMusicBar Columbus Ohio Show 3/8/19! Plan to b… https://t.co/pwxpn9k8YM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CHAOS has picked up a great new member in @WWENickMiller only time will tell how soon the ranks of the junior divi… https://t.co/5EJlevqs4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[In which the Mayor endorses physical assault by police of people posing no safety hazard, to punish them because so… https://t.co/8AsrX2pPia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go get some money and stop thinking about me. I’m changing the old me being the best I can be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come to @smoothiefactory for some creatinas and proteinas https://t.co/liveKTD33s]]></document><document><![CDATA[U16 Boy's Major Midget - Pool H - Toronto Triple Threat def. @MississaugaBall 71-63 #EBAThunder @exposurebball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@addisonalford They stayed open specifically so you could crush your seminar this afternoon 💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's insane what he's been able to do this winter... Can he keep it up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll get a @trailblazers tattoo if they win this year. #nbafinals #NBAonTNT #ripcity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrLastChantz @KarenTrujillolc @br_atkinson @CoachVelasquez @JonR1Lobos Clips of @tavyn_14 from our Silver and East… https://t.co/M6v6ZUfwnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisZellner "Life and Death: it's all part of the game!" Is pretty intense for a magazine cover. Any idea what that one covered?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blind faith is something I’ve never understood, facts need to be in play somewhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cause end of the day, start of the day they said we wouldn't get here anyway. Ya blink and Wolf Gang is in this bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I guarantee you that more than half the questions asked (if DeCosta takes questions) will be about the contra… https://t.co/WNWdUyq3eI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justlucky190 @LisaMei62 Its in ya schools, not on the news. Day1USA HISTORY 3/5/1770 Boston massacre Soldiers were… https://t.co/XMVrHJdWQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_Blair28 Got to appreciate his sense of humor. I laugh out loud at him at least 2-3x a day at him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyNicolaides @JMendel815 Follow-up! I cleaned up a bit  😅 https://t.co/4qaaACwrzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c2e2 I bought tickets before the mail deadline, should I have received my tickets already?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know, if Bernie gets the D nomination I’ll vote for him; but I will do everything in my power to make sure he d… https://t.co/eUqNUknxHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we all still SINGLE single in the morning... 🤦🏽‍♂️ where is the unity? Phone a friend? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other, ACC tournament quarterfinal Friday. In the afternoon teachers rolling the TV cart into the room to watch… https://t.co/9cFBwGc6ge]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of those extra step actions that are unnecessary but so thoughtful. What a great program at St. Charles… https://t.co/iISosX3ch8]]></document><document><![CDATA[With UofM needing help on D-line, this makes sense. Excellent pick up for Harbaugh. Danna is extremely athletic and… https://t.co/KytxQ26Hmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stills frames from a film shot last summer. #ActorsLife #shortfilm #casting #talentagent #talentmanager https://t.co/jenJ8CKrEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthonydefrenza @seanhannity I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quincy… https://t.co/p0Pd3aedsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A taste of spring to round out the week in RVA. Who’s feelin it!? 🙋🏼‍♂️ #springfever #tasteofspring #RVA… https://t.co/FEMDahudC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think imma kill 2 niggas and turn my self in ? Smh y’all gon have to find me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped listening to the press conference for the night, need to sleep. But I get the feeling that there just wasn'… https://t.co/ZC2P1qLfuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muy bien que deje de ser prision, pero mucho mejor que continúe como un sitio libre de contaminación - que ha sido… https://t.co/UsBNhIuevw]]></document><document><![CDATA[No excuses, We change everyday physical, emotions, mental and spiritually!!! For your information  #community… https://t.co/gHzdjO2JkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArthurManfredJr @Cbt_Diver @merry123459 @theJagmeetSingh @AndrewScheer Valid point 😂😂to some degree but you see yo… https://t.co/DquVz4hH4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlbernstein just dropped “it’s all about that base” on @CuomoPrimeTime and it was perfect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Bodega sketch was funny but it should have been all Wonka or just Wonka once and every song is from a differen… https://t.co/JnNe5vvxaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quite the collection in this lake.... @ Eutawville, South Carolina https://t.co/Tqg1k1cOqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day to all our Global Women. #happyinternationalwomensday #women #global @ Oakville, On… https://t.co/Scp91RehXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess you don’t get arrested for Duke on Duke crime. Frank Jackson takes out Redick and no call. https://t.co/8Dv8EBP0vK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kelly Catlin dies at age 23 | https://t.co/IFsbZRyIeq https://t.co/i8QlkQEIwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Asbypirate @f3FruityPebbles @F3ENC @F3Nation @Cartrette_ECU Good work @Asbypirate! Numbers were great — seems ever… https://t.co/ah6RbXjywr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Durham_Transit Bus 8583 at OC 13:15 has EXTERNAL announcements inside the vehicle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/2 Siendo la filosofía, en su sentido más amplio, las conclusiones de la inteligencia humana en cuanto a lo que es… https://t.co/0IluAFlgxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4YrsToday @AnonomouslYours If you voted yes, then go find a mental hospital and check yourself in or find the clos… https://t.co/6emFGyWDIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGMacDougall @gmbutts Yes we feared butts we feared he was going to ruin Canada!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trumptrain1111 @Debra39541192 @bigleaguepol NEVER FORGET !!! 🗽🗽🗽🗽🗽🗽🗽🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4thAndDude @beaconstball @ForBlogston Doesn’t the lack-of attractiveness of the job factor into this decision?  Re… https://t.co/yLDMnBV9qB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joy_Villa @PARISDENNARD @Nigel_Farage @ChrisGarciaUSA @RaheemKassam @willchamberlain @HumanEvents @CPAC @CalvinKlein Nice!! FUN!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/2mLL1WpZKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you turn off the auto shutoff on the @VW 2019 Atlas?  And by turn off I mean permanently disabled]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaWatter10 @ChristiJ1989 @smoss319 @catturd2 WHERE DO YOU LIVE? Regular people take down kings I got fake new… https://t.co/4Dh4m66WAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out with my son at Kennedy Middle School learning how to build websites. Thanks to @uncc @CharMeckSchools a… https://t.co/z65nayVRXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Derek TheChangeMan Smith is blessing us today!!!! @ New Mt. Olive Primitive Baptist Church https://t.co/4AD0jXxSad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkHammett @Metallica The whole album is fucking awesome but I am gonna have 2 go with sanitarium as my fav bit r… https://t.co/hzrFkTF6dj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realUTAmerican @ChadShively @KySportsRadio @jdunnlex18 Meth?   You been to TN bro?   We beat you by more pts just… https://t.co/GBQPV7n0Gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #Friyay y’all. #WilliamJacksonLifestyle #follow #InFluentialMagazine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Houston??? This shit dumb. I’ve been to Houston several times and to NRG Stadium several times and the only thing b… https://t.co/zcCKEAm2Dv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#childcare #nightowl #noisy #mother So the mother and daughter took a little break until acting off their shenaniga… https://t.co/tOlT7lmUmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty much... these MLM people steady thinking they can fool you. Lololol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhalilArnold4 check u out.. But ✔ out his sudden wiggle to get him to bite..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariannaAlfa @JESUSED71770925  amiga @MariannaAlfa  te escribo para pedirte una cancion de timbiriche  y una de se… https://t.co/BOPGi57fQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[After thinking about it some more, I think Jon and Dany are half brother and sister. The attraction they showed for… https://t.co/GXY0OrowMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is better than the Dominican republic? Cool video, indeed East Africa is on the rise, I LOVE AFRICA...........… https://t.co/tHgOAPa6bP]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 2, 1900 - Composer Kurt Weill was born. Ida McKinley First Lady at time. Ida met William McKinley working in… https://t.co/BKafowFOSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThinkBlue47 We’re talking a lot about our defense today but things may get pretty ugly on our Oline, if Saffold si… https://t.co/cFbunoTfBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yung cook ups 👨🏽‍🍳👨🏾‍🍳 with @MichaelAMontoya 🔥🔥🔥🔥 🚨 🚨 🚨HMU for beat specials🎛, loops♻️ or mixing/mastering deals🎚… https://t.co/2vKEhxkc5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was the best text message ever. I started crying in tab when I read it. I am so happy and proud of this amazin… https://t.co/IjJeLc2vqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@legend_f22 @MelissaCarlee @YaDontDoThatv2 @yaf @benshapiro @realDailyWire "[R]isk"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Algo parecido a las cantinflandas de aquí, con el plan que planifica mejores expectativas de lo planificado]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LBoucherAuthor Hotel room, broken, waiting for a bed to open up in rehab. Opened up a Gideon Bible in the room. Re… https://t.co/sQahdGChsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEwockey @nuhusky65 @Stuckey_Alec Yep. Absolutely know that shit happens. That doesn’t mean I can’t be suspiciou… https://t.co/REMV7Lv9xG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been 4 hours since I dropped my car off at Ford and I already miss it smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read this article and give me your feedback.  What is preventing you from purchasing your first home?  I truly beli… https://t.co/a0TimfK17K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seksi @thehill You have to wait 25 seconds. Then, you can watch the video. You have to click the X so that you can hear the sound]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson The interviewer was throwing out different dates...referring to different meetings...meetings Mueller… https://t.co/7aPA3P5Mdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful late winter day. @ Madison, Wisconsin https://t.co/r9XZj3zZEi]]></document></documents></author>