<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#SundayFunday Here’s a fun song to put a smile on your face. 😊 https://t.co/nmPQi3QPQR @NastaZiazm @Mastesy_… https://t.co/vHZqZjm9Ib]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so blessed. I got given these joyous souls as children. Lucky me 🤗😍 @ Studio City, California https://t.co/fsHEOp1WHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The riot has been cancelled for tomorrow afternoon. That will be all. #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skalud @joerexrode I don’t think we cried after one loss but 17 or 18 straight, and the two worst season in progra… https://t.co/Op048pZM6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knew? Turns out I’m Filipino 🤷🏽‍♀️ #SHOCKED https://t.co/vE89i5hw7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacquel01037887 @Rubiconski @SandraK93322487 @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/I5C52YWHm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gramies1 @kenolin1 obama was born in kenya but his father was an american citizen. obama released a photoshop doc… https://t.co/f1yEkO89l0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 2 years to my beautiful girlfriend. Thank you for making these past few years some of the best of my life. I… https://t.co/z2MBPMn3QU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Debate?! You spelled procrastinate completely wrong! Glad you jackasses didn't "debate" Pearl Harbor!  Bu… https://t.co/EyGl09SwAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamtylerdonovan Hi, We would be happy to assist you. See our innovative work here: https://t.co/0kK0depliy… https://t.co/g4AUCKfaDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broke-Ass City: The best way to beat the devil is to support a union https://t.co/hXFAuzCACk  #inners #uppers… https://t.co/YeesWP9iub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio @AfterHoursCBS Who do you think will end up with Brown and Bell?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your indictment will happen one day  trump! You are guilty of to much! #YouCantHideTheTruthTRUMP @MSNBC @foxnewspolitics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching a grade 3/4 at St. John in the Beaches today. https://t.co/LwrSjSYhxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeSullivan @PistonsHooper I think it’s only fair that valenti visits hooper for his birthday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zisi Emporium for B Movies: 4Got10, Dolph Lundgren...Danny Trejo...Natassia Malthe: https://t.co/uA1BTrHiHk https://t.co/niKDTq8cjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[kalua_discotheque en una súper noche de domingo Arreee @ Kalua Discotheque ( oficial ) https://t.co/6fhFn1FXkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrandmaShark18 @commondreams @IlhanMN Love talking to grandmas. I always learn so much...just by listening..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenmorrisonlive @MichaelAngarano I wish you success with your new project, whatever it may be! (((Hugs)))]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elrenecito2 @JavierEnrikez @CARLOSEES @nhaiper @ulisespena @tonymarquezroon @arielvmachado @luisaguilerahmo… https://t.co/zxDaBM147Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk @seanhannity @RealJamesWoods @MaryMcDonnell10 @BetteMidler @IlhanMN @RepAOC @RepRashida to dems fou… https://t.co/xGs8cA7ybq]]></document><document><![CDATA[With a loss tonight, Al Skinner will conclude his four year tenure at Kennesaw State with a 40-84 record.  I think… https://t.co/92LJhL9Oe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure I clogged up a water pickup idling through a boat chute to get to the ramp. This could be a long day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had djs all night. F%ck every dj and f%ck edm. Damn. Ridiculous cartoon button pushing. 6 hrs of douchey build up,… https://t.co/5h2REhoccX]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was the best part of the stereotype videos. Condolences to the family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1968 London cast of HAIR featuring Marsha Hunt. https://t.co/ekNzcrSDWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmendezm @Saselandia Jajajaajajajjajajajajajajajajajajajaajjajajajajaaajajajajajajajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rockstar causeways gonna be a long day (at @ARCO in Fremont, CA) https://t.co/TProhjvw8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnneThrelkeld1 Because people would rather believe a ridiculous conspiracy theory than accept the less-exciting re… https://t.co/A1lRGR3A5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bette Midler (American singer actress comedian) She was first noted for her mezzo soprano singing, an... https://t.co/s7vRH2S5ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisneiman @hrslaton You Cali boys must have forgotten how until clocks spring forward you leave work and the sun is setting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aka_blonde Good morning Sky aka and happy Valentine’s Day from my alternative music station 😘😘💖💖🇨🇦🇨🇦]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ridgual311 @Brigade311 Just saw DH is closing though. Might have to do Hartford instead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YsuanMoon @DuneAuthor No I think the Conan Exile game is great. It has excellent building good combat and a satisf… https://t.co/1Ir3v3nfh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pug_life_4_Blue “They’ll get there.” There are no excuses now (other than injuries). For the first time since 2000… https://t.co/9HB2a2OWV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMullin @POTUS It’s time for you to resign as well you are totally against the American ppl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@looisrivas Cuando te vi te me hiciste familiar. Cuando entraste a saludar a Gia. Luego cuando caí en cuenta que ha… https://t.co/EsZEUyPCQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@t35ch @LaVelleNeal Who would you rather risk losing more than Cron? Astudillo? Gonzalez? Garver? Adrianza? Yes Aus… https://t.co/uTR5k3scoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jolteonbeast Yea! Just workout in moderation and sometimes treat yourself to some junk food! It’s no biggie! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephen Jackson. I usually teach guys to run into things. But I like to air it out...sometimes. @gctitansfb in AL… https://t.co/wsRUqwjB82]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brodie07Perry a that Jordan scarlett pick on that draft board 👌🏿i think bra gone be a goon next yr he nice too]]></document><document><![CDATA[“....using carbohydrate restriction with nutritional ketosis and weight loss, improved overall sleep quality in pat… https://t.co/qSWjycf1Ju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@testisfidelis What is in contention is: What is the content of God's favor extended to Mary? The passage doesn't s… https://t.co/p3ilePp0b3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaRoch3353426 esses caras que tiram foto assim só mostrando a parte de baixo do calção tem um ar de pedófilo que da até medo as vezes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarieAl @Turki_AlOwerde @RealthingUlli @B0RedS1 @305local @Alkofide @ceasere @awwadsalotaibi @travlnjak… https://t.co/Mz9Se1MLKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[BuzzFeed has posted some dumbass shit it the past, but this one may take the cake. Holy...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Finance manager"? What did you like most about that job? #Finance #Dallas, TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blockbustercast I could go on and on about this film! ASIB was my No.1 for the year until I saw The Favourite on New Years Eve!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I told a female friend of mine about paying $25 for 5 boxes of cookies thinking I was actually helping I was t… https://t.co/dmio1yKoK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a High Falut'n by Weathered Ground Brewery @ Black Bear Burritos — https://t.co/fZG2MiIkwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[5604 Wilshire Blvd 5604 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036 https://t.co/64kwQqoM2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[We goin? @RyanSiggins @zechcastillo @ky6ka @Shep_72 &amp; @djgavinflash the projectile slut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen Do you have milk, yogurt, and cheese nights? Because that would be Legend-dairy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@browndawg14 @SteelVideos @btsteelcurtain Thank god they got juju at least]]></document><document><![CDATA[War and Peace drop this month. Ides of March no longer scare me. However March Madness right around the corner, I like]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom Clancy’s The Division 2 all trophies revealed!  WATCH 👉🏼 https://t.co/g7b4iwuDIN https://t.co/3FK1Af7rid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big thanks to everyone that's already listened to my new single, Moment. If you haven't heard it yet, give it a lis… https://t.co/0A8xtEy33O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therunchat @Rashaan A4: Make your run a way to experience the city/area you’re in and enjoy it. Don’t focus too mu… https://t.co/G4a8sJJXwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brace yourself.  Before The Storm by @KayzoMusic @blessthefall https://t.co/2LKSZy3v0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[2:16 left in the game: Vincennes Rivet 52 University 45. Patriots ball coming out of the timeout. #Sports10]]></document><document><![CDATA[#300 ❤ In 480 B.C. a state of war exists between Persia, led by King Xerxes, and Greece. At the Battle of Thermopyl… https://t.co/5lg2K5ZJTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@speakingabtpain @AjayManhapra @CarlynZwaren @marykayconsult3 @tal7291 And what that means is: of all the patients… https://t.co/YCK4l1X67H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smart move Jacob some might refer to that as the Clinton strategy? Please don't tell anyone you're going to testify… https://t.co/cWtWhb3Hvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luhhcourt @H_dimez Your response defeats the whole purpose of “minding your business”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Days Before Astroworld... 🤮🌵🔥💀🎢🎡🎪🎠🚀💫🌎🦅 #Astroworld . . . . . . . . . . . . #EveryPairHasAStory #WishYouWereHere… https://t.co/KGgSsdvBB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pictures of each other taken by the other. #wildkrattslive #durham @ The Bagel Bar - Durham https://t.co/7I7ahsBR4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@popularffwriter Sean McVay isn't even old enough to run for president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at The Creative Group? We're hiring in #Dallas, TX! Click the link in our bio for details on this job… https://t.co/XH0m5LG1m9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp I remember when your wife was eagerly awaiting John McCain's death. She must get happier every day that h… https://t.co/unzTofKcID]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiaJaxWWE are you going to be at the live event in Atlantic city NJ in a few weeks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheri and I just had the shittiest Monday and I can’t wait for it to be over :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[No.... no it's not.... they weaponize their religion but it doesn't prove the relationship itself is.... nevermind]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y sabes, se da mucho en los medios radiales de los estados, narran incluso con la playera del equipo local, más bie… https://t.co/hCObmKfyrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[ARIOCH killed it tonight! #arioch #regalinn #lakewood #adhdentertainment #longbeach @ The Famous "Regal INN" https://t.co/ez2QmHsa6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliasTheodorou Thank you so much for the kind message!! Can't wait to see you get back in action 👊🏼🇨🇦 #THESPARTAN https://t.co/UXiB5EOn42]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many times have you watched the 2005 @IlliniMBB comeback against Arizona? https://t.co/4UKCxTFnOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmyStrang Actually I worry he isn’t likable, plus those rumpled suits of his.   Oh, he’s another old White man who needs to sit back down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBajanen @seanhannity Look at government statistics and turn off Faux News.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashmcbee Wow. Okay I see you! How did those biology classes turn out ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Among the leadoff hitter possibilities, #Rays Cash mentioned look Joey Wendle, Daniel Robertson, Brandon Lowe, Aust… https://t.co/aenCzYsW5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatgirlondeck That after 1973, the Mets would be in the World Series every year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s #breakfast #lunch #brunch #egg #eggs #skillet #food #instafood #calories #hashbrowns #meal @ Lincoln Square… https://t.co/y5xlrpLJMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VSB_Dean @VU_Business @MJNovaAD @NovaMBB Bob is one of the best in the @VillanovaClubDC !!! #GoNova ✌️✌️🏀👍✌️🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arsenal moved into fourth place in the Premier League table   https://t.co/Es568dh27k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think The Favourite is a brilliant movie, but I wonder why Olivia Colman was billed as the leading actress. He pe… https://t.co/n55fMcD7uO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh wow. He blocked me. Apparently he can pick on women all he wants, but hides from me. Cool story, bro. “Much alpha. Very man.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WakandaForever I’ve probably have seen/watched Black Panther a thousand times. And the more I watch it and pay att… https://t.co/st2Os7YCmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevemouzon I trash it every year but new photo rules make it impossible from afar without public press kits which I have not found yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richconte I’m always looking at the best places to live nationally and then regionally as well. I’d love to get to… https://t.co/eAOBJBbJ1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was an honor and privilege hanging out with you guys.  😉🙏 @afterbuzztv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think that the bishop who just got defrocked confirmed me. Does that mean I’m not confirmed? How does this work?… https://t.co/u1vWSY4LxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyStewart @AudienceSports @DIRECTV @directvnow looking forward to it.  Smoke, he is one of the few media types w… https://t.co/3gt48CXjX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a:  ⚪️ Man  ⚪️ Woman  🔘  Tea pot (Short and Stout)  Looking for:  ⚪️ Women  ⚪️ Men  🔘 My handle and my spout… https://t.co/Jjx1gSZnfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@e57e38655ab84b0 Muy buenos días Amiga y feliz jueves y día de san Valentín saludos cordiales cuídate mucho y Bendiciones ,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courage and perseverance have a magical talisman, before which difficulties disappear and obstacles vanish into air. - John Quincy Adams]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alejandra_ncba @UNCTicketSales @NCBAorg Thank you for taking time for us @CoachMackBrown @kzmyers @joshtarheel https://t.co/TVE63ym8qj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brutal modernism. Gold bars. @ The Westin Peachtree Plaza, Atlanta https://t.co/vyh7TsviMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why The Democrat Party Excuses Ilhan Omar’s Anti-Semitism ~~~~~~ THAT IS WITHOUT QUESTION OBVIOUS!!! IF THEY “REALL… https://t.co/lEbPUPU83e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @IlhanMN It's hard to watch because you're anti-semitic too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This mans gonna have me working late on a Saturday and have the Audacity to not supply beer. Sike boy]]></document></documents></author>