<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods With this mind set I can sell her followers the Brooklyn Bridge . With no foggiest idea of ANYTHING… https://t.co/C7iy8AyjPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm learning a few new techniques from the guys over at Reuzel. Now all I need is a samurai sword and some willing… https://t.co/DXmKD2pIMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paws4AKF @Team_SamW @jarpad @800273TALK Waiting for March 1st to purchase tickets cannot wait to get there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bc he doesn’t know how to ride a horse, ya gotta loosen up on the reigns lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thenickgohde @tyjordann Haha. Great game. We will meet again and we will be fine come tournament time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamthathooper is THAT HOOPER! She so @Candace_Parker with it!! #Bravo 👏🏿✊🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday Roundup: Syracuse Takes Down Johns Hopkins, Rutgers Owns New Jersey  https://t.co/J331YtORTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytopinion @AOC No the national emergency is the terrorist movement of socialist communist ideology trying to pois… https://t.co/EhmVBRC5Is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalksWithLenny Seriously you had no clue? That was the highlight of the whole design! 😂 Thanks, Lenny ❤️🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[With @WWE_MandyRose it's the same as with @LaceyEvansWWE the guys who hate her want her and the women who do wannabe her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetrocch @outmagazine @mathewrodriguez The author may need help but the editor who allowed this to be posted to t… https://t.co/1a2t4P676V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McguireScotty @shelliecorreia I don’t think that will last long before the fighting starts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMopLady He’s more than just a shooter.  He’s a basketball player.  All shooters think is shoot.  Basketball pla… https://t.co/N0sVSA7w0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[She believed she could, so she did. https://t.co/ZMfx0rwwO1… #WomensHistoryMonth⁠ ⁠ https://t.co/lvMvdR6dWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @SenKamalaHarris @GavinNewsom the UN has declared the next decade to be The Decade of #Ecosystem… https://t.co/Hcn3W6z9vf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dgwbirch Geez, I have to look into this. I’ve got a great application!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox News, stop using the same “derp” face pictures of AOC and leave her alone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marquese Chriss finna text Dejounte Murray to ask for LaMarcus’ phone number so he can text him for back up on Serg… https://t.co/xHGdD5p2Lo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thousands of dudes like this in downtown manhattan, y’all should take a look.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So that when they win another title, they'll have a player who wants to go to the White House. #SavedYouAClick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoryWalund @AAFFleet @custer103251198 I’ll tell you what, that running game is on point. But that home field advan… https://t.co/X3Op6BeR4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of hours of work went into this. Always nice to see the final product. Check it out today! #northernpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do so many people run away from what makes them happy? CONQUER YOUR FEARS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday March 6 - MSNBC Daily:      Cohen lawyer: ‘Literally no way to dispute’ that Trump committed a crime;… https://t.co/GuKvn4Bpre]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not upset with the Foles signing only an average of 12mil guaranteed per year.... should be able to make the of… https://t.co/WpNYtF5Xhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[More skiing with these two today. #happydad @ Vail, Colorado https://t.co/2t0IAqT7Bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is social media heading next? | https://t.co/DuHRhtlyqQ https://t.co/64gTPUQbqz by @robertjoseph]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the way up, shattered now #la #holiday #hike #bb #standardmate @ Runyon Canyon - Los Angeles / Hollywood https://t.co/Z7sCOyGXEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhD_femme @CFBHome What do you suggest instead? Bloomington, where Memorial Stadium is literally covered in feces? https://t.co/ywwyrTSDP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[We welcome our last speaker @anthonystaj from @rapidnovor talking about Biotech Clusters. https://t.co/D11EwjAqgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One ! !    http://www.oceangrownseeds. Trup is DELLUSIONAL! https://t.co/dOsZbH4tKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saylumcroft @Faedoria1 @No0b3_tv @DeadByBHVR Doesn’t take me longer than 5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Yeah right my mother raised four kids after my dad died she worked two jobs and my oldest siblings helped… https://t.co/UY6EQU6WdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerbox12 @TexasStars @sarampage Oh cool, how recent was your move? As of today I’ve got one week under my belt 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite people are people who are disgusted at the idea of a world where you can retire earlier and maybe like… https://t.co/fwtW27bdBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I begin to laugh by smiling today? @ Hollywood Walk of Fame https://t.co/eswpDv9JRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caro_Villa78 I've been hurt And I've been blind I'm not sure that I'll be fine I never thought it would end this way!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pandoramusic is literally the hardest to unsubscribe from and it’s really annoying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fotoqueen24 @JoeBudden @thisisrory @parksmusic Lmaooo oh wow he gets his own drop and now he’s different smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guyrleech @adbertram I add a Pester test to every project to make sure there is an example.   When you are testing… https://t.co/ph74s8mJEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una es de Obregon!! @kioscomayor @pauliieC @antillons @riesquer @beckerg123 @FMLalo @riesquer @lacy_aida @jrosasm73… https://t.co/0BCSp2FZXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s ready to watch Team Adams @AshlandClockers defeat Team Vieira @ClockerPride tomorrow at the @AshlandPto Clock… https://t.co/288ahZFnL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check this article out by my guys @Atrainliner and @JibberJabberin   https://t.co/rn5aXUTPGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you expect me to get up there? There better be an elevator all the way to the top cause they’re crazy if the… https://t.co/fnldUZFRQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL Happy Birthday   I'll have a drink for you tonight and toast you and your daily knowledge you share wit… https://t.co/z4fPWEa79N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning my a.m. crew and Happy Friday from my alternative music station. ☕️☕️ @TomKochABC13  @TJParkerABC13… https://t.co/D1onUOAFDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[In addition to showcasing very talented young musicians, From The Top also provides invaluable leadership training… https://t.co/FfqvXG7apL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAngelBaby99 @AverageJoeCraig Show must go on, good old fashioned lover boy, spread your wings, scandal, I’m goi… https://t.co/llf1CcJjbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @FLAGALine and  @bigloud! The ultimate #RideOrDie team for the long haul!  Class acts! Game collaborates… https://t.co/TNURxc9f7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @emilysears @DarthLux @nina_staub @LindseyPelas @SitaraHewitt @cheycasee 😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods What about the millions paid to your husband for “Speaking engagements” #goaway]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolute Units @ Arnold Classic - Columbus Convention Center https://t.co/oAWrceNuke]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wanna drive in the snow but abq drivers are so fuckin dumb it’s scary 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This tweet will surely fix everything.  Your idiocy continues to amaze us all...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gettin’ it done. #KeepMovingForward @ New York, New York https://t.co/b1KnTUT7DW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like music that makes me feel like I'm riding a steam train in the 1800s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your first tarriff killed farming, cost many jobs in the auto industry and crashed the market. You… https://t.co/EAox6jBKWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenePetrovLMC @ChrisDucker @jessikaphillips @PatFlynn @Mike_Stelzner @briansolis @MadalynSklar @NealSchaffer… https://t.co/YGVt7MSSxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing about the rep Omar’s comments is that Isr**l itself has been infinitely more anti Semitic than anything s… https://t.co/r1ObZcQmNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're 33rd on the gotdamn upgrade list. #FirstWorldProblems https://t.co/LODV0v6wD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChicagoDemons 16U &amp; 17U boys tryouts this Sunday!  @BallBoysChi @PrepLegal @LendaleR @khaleb_rouse2 https://t.co/gS6nT5yIv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKimCampbell @dwancherry Kim, you obviously have chosen to ignore what happened during the last DNC nomination process. Go away, please]]></document><document><![CDATA[@247Sports @247recruiting @BSnow247 @EvanDaniels @JoshNewkirk7 @JoshHenschke @BriceMarich @TremendousUM @_ZachShaw… https://t.co/u6ml8pqM6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@budget At rental car counter in Pgh, I told the associate I may need the car another day.  I was charged an extra… https://t.co/SeKEnKPc84]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a reminder, no booster passes can be accepted for tournament games. Entry is $7 without a NCHSAA pass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edit2505 @Naysalvatori @pes @hugoericflores @PESDiputados @amlo No comprendiste el discurso de la legisladora. Vue… https://t.co/q3qUqI21TV]]></document><document><![CDATA[First night of vacation the 8 year old is sharing a bed with the 3 year old. We wake up to the 3 year old laughing… https://t.co/eAgKslWbW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NCStateBaseball I haven’t been back there since I was an extra in Bull Durham. Looking forward to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst Looking forward to tonight.  Been waiting for this. So excited!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@survivorcbs I'm begging #survivor please no more of these stupid cliff hangers. You're better than this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noharmon03 I learned yesterday that a " certain " mining equipment builder here in Decatur that build " yellow" eq… https://t.co/Au8zjAc64D]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I’ve been on Twitter for a couple years now, and I guess my timeline is just cobbled together, but there’s one… https://t.co/mlolz8ITOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels like -20° outside. I don’t know why I am going to the office and not working from the couch but here we are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We need to provide safe neighborhoods and quality schools” #ChiMayor19 #ChiMayorForum #BringInTheLight]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:27.4°F WchillLow:22.5°F Wind:0 mph Dir:WNW Baro:Rising slowly Rain2day:0.00in Hum:71% UV:0.0 @ 04:30 03/12/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lane910 Lane stfu damn, no ones wants to ride with you. No ones freaking likes you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SJTimes13 @TheMikeSnyder @Hermann22 Dude was a pedophile and likely a rapist. A rapist of children. Okay, I’m out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #findingneverland and this has to be the most boring documentary ever filmed. Zzzzzzzzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am now a proud owner of my 1st artwork by artist @rello3000 oil on canvas for my growing art collection. Thanks J… https://t.co/KPp39hJyjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else watching @startrekcbs #StarTrekDiscovery ?   Red Angel theories please. https://t.co/I5qVzaYCpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sadieannmartin @WDWNT Don’t take it personally. @WDWNT likes to sensationalize stuff and make mountains out of molehills.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please send all good vibes my way 🙇🏻‍♀️ I’m manifesting great things to come into my life in the next few days and… https://t.co/b0M2OBrMND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jensilvermath @mathillustrated @hpicciotto @ex_trantorian @AlexKontorovich @mr_davis_math @MrATeachesMath… https://t.co/TA0gadKUe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYG_Andrew @UncleGusNyc Matt Ryan is overrated has a water pistol arm he'll never win a SB he's too inconsistent a… https://t.co/Pjcx3I2stO]]></document><document><![CDATA[All are welcome to this free online presentation coming this Friday night! A review of basic osseous augmentation p… https://t.co/2KOdDQDmvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Dead Guy Ale by @rogueales @ Pies And Pints — https://t.co/pFSHGSx6kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiddleAgedMezzo I mean, it did take him three days am I rite https://t.co/3YbVMRJfDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Briteeye777 @ADeSenze @Old_Tx_Geezer @WendySonlin @enjaylady @RonaldAbeyta @LibsRNutz @MarshaPatriot… https://t.co/80nhAVkUMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allycollummusic Chicken and waffles. As Jules says in Pulp Fiction, pig is a filthy animal. I don’t eat filthy animals. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is BYU really down 42 points, having scored 25, in the middle of the second half of a WCC quarterfinal game... #GoodJobNiceEffortProvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to ask @NashSevereWx if there’s a chance the rain holds off until after Friday, but the answer is going to b… https://t.co/QzufljCkxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been looking for a new job and I think I want to work for @FoxNews. There, you can sexually harass and sexuall… https://t.co/CbQNvJOLo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is the list of the #leecountytornado  In Alabama. https://t.co/nOgdAAXbP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@and_annoyed @2wayvy @alwayskeepitRIL THEY DID ARREST HIM FOR FUCKING UNDER AGE GIRLS...a friend of his posted $100… https://t.co/sJ7l2y1Bmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisEgan5 @BrockESPN Come on Chris, from what I understand, you were quite the Jock yourself.  Happy for you guys. #ProudMammas&amp;Pappas]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never really thought about life and death, but the loss of someone close really does make you think. I’m glad… https://t.co/yQXr7aHY3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[straight men see that it’s -20 outside and they’re like....”hmmm should i buss out the cargo shorts today?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[J. Cole AMAZING Full Halftime Performance at 2019 NBA All-Star Game https://t.co/NxViw4nx0i via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very good bloody mary mix. Breakfast of champions https://t.co/cLHuDb9I6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw this on my timehop and had to reiterate... #TweetOfTheYearCandidate]]></document></documents></author>