<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RealPaulAhnert @sues3jewels @BubleFanGermany @i_reverend And for some reason they don't regard the icon or your pr… https://t.co/iOCJElnivM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BasedPoland @TOMMORBRITISH1 This has to stop!  The handicapped and elderly are being abused]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheJoyOfPics! This is literally a sliver #SneakPeek of our #NewListing in Hillside #ComingSoon! Great potential 2… https://t.co/gVRCy7uhIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had 3 interviews in Indianapolis today, and today of all days my car decides it doesn’t want to start...God doesn’t wanna see me succeed]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so dead tonight 😩no intakes no one in temp obs all my relias are done and up to date  So I’m just sitting here bored out my mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favourite thing about going back to work the day you get home from vacation is definitely when you’re made to st… https://t.co/X3jfDNDmwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now THIS is the kind of client EVERYONE dreams of - @wordsby_bob (with a bit of help from Hollie!) @HollieWrites13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FairyDustBeccs (Young) black professional here! Soon to be business school graduate + MBA candidate with lots of e… https://t.co/IPjJ0juTpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LordStrath_LDSB thanks to Fruity Fridays Owen has gotten excited about fruit again! Our fruit basket is much more… https://t.co/EaUCfV7FLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m old enough to remember when an emergency 🚨 meant lives were in imminent danger.  #oldenoughtoremember #NationalEmergencyDeclaration]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder In my dreams, they both seek asylum on a foreign shore. I don't care which one. Preferable somewhere withou… https://t.co/KR8TIiP7CK]]></document><document><![CDATA[These new cheerleading rules about makeup and uniforms may not be the worst thing for the sport.  I love our sport’… https://t.co/mnOaolLdvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited for @MGCCCSoftball Coach Long and the Bulldogs! This is awesome. Good luck this season!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been told that this should go viral 😂 "Phone stay charged for 14 months we ALWAYS open for business" 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw some gneiss schist and also lovely flowers in the White Tanks yesterday while Jim was trotting a bunch of mil… https://t.co/e8qxH6n8Ke]]></document><document><![CDATA[This makes it hard for me to feel warm and fuzzy about my leftist friends. When will people with a brain and a hear… https://t.co/LSezD3tILZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Student had to bring his baby daughter to class so his professor watched her so he could pay atte...… https://t.co/8ndCYfDFyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just left the muffins I was making in the oven 20 minutes longer then they were supposed to be in and somehow they didnt burn....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeLanaHarvick @RonHornaday Awesome! @DeLanaHarvick I’d be there to support it, would be a heck of a show!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes yes yes. Good lord I never thought this might happen on my lifetime. That it’s even being discussed and written… https://t.co/8dYiucniR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our quarterly Flag Raising Ceremony honoring #BlackHistoryMonth2019 #PresidentsDay &amp; Love ❤️ @DuvalSchools… https://t.co/MLya1w33d5]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a mission 🎒🏃‍♀️ . . . #manhattan #nyc #newyork #newyorkcity #usa #travel #ny #photography #fashion #love… https://t.co/B3PF1vuOzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[A mi hermana le da risa que cada vez que huelo loción de hombre digo "Huele a macho".]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible show, incredible actors. Freddie Highmore is an action genius. Sean is so real that you just wanna reach… https://t.co/3Tv7w1pEKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atlanta rapper 21 Savage booked into South Georgia jail on felony warrant this weekend: https://t.co/7Qtt6QHqQG --… https://t.co/iNMw4e888w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Signs Bibles At Alabama Baptist Church, Twitter Users Throw The Book At Him  https://t.co/PUnHZaN4Dw via @HuffPostPol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gayle King: Are you an older woman who likes younger women?  R. Kelly: I’m an older man who likes allll women. Gayle: ohkay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen I can’t wait til my ID comes. I’m missing tooooooo much money. $75 for two hours plus tips 😩😭 my heart is broken. #bartenderslife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaviTrance06 omg no, don’t worry about it! I’m just tryna be funny lol but I really ain’t from there 💅🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Sounds like 10 hours of witness prep.  What is this a  bet the company litigation?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abianne @SouthwestAir Ugh this is upsetting because I’m such a @SouthwestAir fan for plus size reasons and long distance bae reasons]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was out running 1.09 miles with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/Kxvxf58MY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@i_s_e_b @ohthatlook If Ignis was me. 😂 Pet all the cats even if they zap ya. lol.  This was adorable. Thank you so much for sharing it. ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asmgaiter Yes - know ppl who work there! Best of luck for future job opps. Thanks again for reaching out — a rando… https://t.co/2fPUfLlssw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NitaLowey @RepDanCrenshaw The biggest comments on Omar about her Israel comments are from Evangelical Christians.… https://t.co/xNWLmly0o8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuck Dowdle and @wsbtv visited with coach Jack Bauerle and freshman Olivia Carter! Watch them on Saturday at 10 on… https://t.co/lWwAkHDjUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch Unfit to be considered a human being, these FOOLS want to (FIX) the country when they're not even ab… https://t.co/zOyYzwLDkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyVirginOK @CathJSweeney The nerve of you two. 🤬 #BestMealOfTheWeek https://t.co/LQuosKYHEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/xgTCuaKWnZ  Rest in Peace Luke Perry. 💖 I always liked and respected you as an actor. Hugs and Love to… https://t.co/VArzxoEG5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALL MY DRUNK ASSS WANTS TO DO IS FUCKING CUDDLE BUT DONT HAVE ANYONE TO DO THAT SHIT WITH, AINT THAT SOME SHIT :,(]]></document><document><![CDATA[how do we bring back webcam selfies but also myspace??????emo night ~inspired~ me last night. @ Astoria, New York https://t.co/95YTUkJRgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[if literally anyone wants to come with me to the banda event on Mar. 30, you know, hmu. i’m fucking down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[just danced bachata with the loml and @ohjessss_  didn’t even capture ANY of it on video and he’s gone forever https://t.co/eIoti4jNfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#naturalinduction #theacademyofacupuncture #annadolopo #balancemethod #acupuncture @ Elements in Harmony Acupunctur… https://t.co/n73Ky32N2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this was the exact reaction @KTcrewdson and I had, except when we cried, the little girl in waitress made d… https://t.co/qT35W13hdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pic from my best friend right now. Hoping everyone at Lakeland Community College in Kirtland, Ohio is okay... repor… https://t.co/06tAcU4jEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZemanLynnZ @revrrlewis So, who tied his tie for him? And probably his shoes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GsjpJyoti @SsanjayTaannk @greatairi @IamSunitha777 @yogeychauhan @GCHDutta @u_mirella @panjami @UmeshBhadarka1… https://t.co/ugoV9w17Xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will definitely be gathering up some items from my work storage for this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst I’d watch two hours any time.  :).  I’d skip thru the commercials.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my assessment of todays $VYST Panic Selling. So gr8ful To Rob to bring 2 my attn. The RS word was being use… https://t.co/QaKNHUfSHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to visit this morning to get some #coffee and celebrate their opening, but they were closed. Anyone know if… https://t.co/Lm5ZuuDKRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KarlaaBoo @christian_x3x3 Ok well shoot hopefully even more Dj’s I love are on the lineup🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 They were discussing a cover-up. How can it matter what anyone suggested; it was done. And if Trump tho… https://t.co/ekNT1dH32h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump we here in ALABAMA Have supported you, Mr. Trump, from the beginning. The senior class at Calvary… https://t.co/zz7fVKM0Ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[The little things in life are important. Those everyday interactions that leave you with a smile, the people who ar… https://t.co/MdvLC2Z9Ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[2do Show #TributoalaReinadelRock  #AlejandraGuzman #SoyAsi #MalaHierva en The New Jalisco Bar https://t.co/U3SDkexP6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[my lil sister took my dogs to a mother fricken dog birthday party IM DEAD https://t.co/pNT9PIMnNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[You get mad and depressed by the news watch these local news reporters and laugh so hard you cry tears of joy  https://t.co/eHEg2aUb9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hellocyberdream @BANTUFAG I feel like they are. From what I got, he didn't have a problem with same sex parents. J… https://t.co/TwYEpo77RE]]></document><document><![CDATA[you need to find human morales in the tech and get the tech to talk back to you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump plans to allocate $8 billion to fund border wall, source says  https://t.co/mPYs1lPoQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Caliber Portfolio Lending Suite is comprised of flexible loan solutions for borrowers whose background may not… https://t.co/0QY3KhUS92]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRUMP asks PEOPLE to REMEMBER who freed Otto Whambier. I ask people to REMEMBER who sided with Kim Jong Un. Who we… https://t.co/Go7HqQjL3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tooafrid @hussiresvlog @heaathhussar @zanesbubba @msglasswoman @Heaths_peskie @HeathHussar @MariahAmato 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz día de la Independencia Dominicana #Dominicanasoy🇩🇴 https://t.co/pmPmEy9Hsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElissaSlotkin great job on Morning Joe.... And your questions to @SecNielsen who needs to go... This administratio… https://t.co/BUSkHHnLk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“caffeinate and dominate.” ☕️ 👌🏽😌💋💎™️ @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/fhG9JokuLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[“That's why everybody was applauding for me at the end. My guts and my heart, and while I eventually puked my guts… https://t.co/XH7lzYp3ZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapotesClaws @RodneyRohde @MissaMHx @maie_lynn @Ryan_Mac_Phd @MCBazacoPhD @RyanMarino @maureen_ferrari… https://t.co/L7uiSg2q2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding the good snacks I forgot I hid from the kids is the #parenting equivalent of finding money in your ski pants from last year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmaynard123188 lmao jooheon could but i can’t stand eminem anyways so my opinion is biased. and i meant fans necks not other celebs 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is wrong w ppl? We just don’t have the patience anymore to get the whole story about anything do we?]]></document><document><![CDATA[An acid trip without the acid   #justinwood #bowerydays @ New York, New York https://t.co/AKfwOD0435]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the promise of verification, hackers are targeting Instagram influencers @CNN https://t.co/dCnT3nXf8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strength &amp; conditioning💪♥ @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/mVmvPDJmHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earpers are FAMILY😍 NoChill 👊  We are here and We stay 💕 #FightForWynonna #WynonnaEarp @SYFY @IDWPublishing]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's neat how if you invest deeply in something like a sport, then sometimes it opens you up to new and glorious ex… https://t.co/fi1j19KiMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out what I'm selling on Mercari! ESTEE LAUDER Vegan F… https://t.co/Syz25bfcVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to sing our hearts out!! ❤️ 💞💕🎶🎵 @sarampage #ThisIsPassmore #PassmoreMusic #ElementaryMusic #Choir… https://t.co/Vi5zwCSm1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhIoeK People are so friggin stupid!! Girl!! Keep your nails fuck what these people say!!!💅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@underscorebriee I honestly like L.I.F.T. over super whatevr and With Confidence 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EniAlu Me too! I would have been kicking him in the ass all the way back to the sidelines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingofn0ne @Jackiem157 I do this knowing damn well I haven’t  had sex in a long time, and it would be damn near im… https://t.co/MVTJE55gfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing girls in toxic relationships breaks my heart U R DOPE GIRLFRIEND WHY U LET THE SCUM TREAT U LIKE TRASH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Protect your house as it protects you https://t.co/1ea8suFEmZ via @REM_Online]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hazy Little Thing by @SierraNevada at @embassysuites — https://t.co/Og7bLcWNvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was all a dream (Big Poppa voice)! Smdh. And 13 yrs, 330 million with no opts outs... Is stupid money, but not t… https://t.co/4uAdc2ajBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aries's 1st hike. I still need to alter the bag for her back legs. But she is getting use to it. @ Great Falls, Vir… https://t.co/U0n7HBArIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you were a Starbucks drink, what would you be?   I would be a venti cold foam cold brew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Normans_Edits @i_GhostTwd @ringleader1010 @fuckedchic @ItsKatieLester @Stef_Helen @Walkingdeadluv3 @twdandmetal… https://t.co/ajwIm4cxft]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys know what I hate about @KaceyMusgraves? Nothing absolutely nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE’RE BACK ❗️  ⏰ says 5:30 a.m,   Time to Grind!   #Hokies 🦃 https://t.co/f6YbJhWnIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of the snakes, if I snap you can you snap me back with a PIC AND NOT A MESSAGE bc now I have random ass p… https://t.co/BClyQDPuka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RnH_Org @TheAcademy Ahh- It Might As Well Be Spring! Love Dick Haymes beautiful voice! 🌸💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its a democratic saying it so I don't trust that the fire fighters  are the answer may just be a political scandal… https://t.co/71lRrJU7UK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scarlettgj20 @jonasbrothers Midnight needs to hurry it the hell up. I need this 😐😂 https://t.co/JOqxPnO9XP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday! Up working in my office today. Feels good to be at my desk. Ginger tea in hand, Charlie at my feet.… https://t.co/OhV2Wfzaex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrimeCreator2 @AboveTheBurgh @HeARTofGod99 @2newearth777 @davidsodell @tee10202 @WILLOWOOD2 @glammalg11… https://t.co/SXD0w0Kvxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[8:54pm on paczki day, no paczkis have been obtained, morale is low- about to knock on the door of the polish embass… https://t.co/phhwDzzZHb]]></document></documents></author>