<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence Parading an ignorant black woman at the Cohen hearing didn’t prove that Trump Isn’t racist. It proved tha… https://t.co/wjZkgr0vDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisForsberg_ He needs to run up and down the court to get his leagues going and we him to be on point]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newly-restored footage shows terrifying power of nuclear bomb tests https://t.co/GfVqC9uvkc via @MailOnline]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3b1rIQxGPl #EiRogerioCorreiaVaiTomaNoCu aguardado o comunismo/socialismo dá certo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even IF you wanted burger flavored ice cream, why  t h e  FUCK would you use a whopper..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrisRamosStar You are all winners.  Your voice is awesome!!! Best wishes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @davidharsanyi @FDRLST Nancy Pelosi on Thurs did not call for Rep. Ilhan Omar to apologize for  her lates… https://t.co/2TfIeqKAVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legit watched this for 5 minutes thinking they were filling it to the top]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you half sleep otp and say something dumb asf. “ Yea I was running too fast in the water “ 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[If résumés are meant to streamline your qualifications and accomplishments...then why is so much emphasis based on… https://t.co/SQ2GFGuUCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hangin waaaaaay Uptown with my PRETTY PRETTY #BigChiefMonkBoudreaux and the Golden Eagle #MardiGrasIndians.  Add a… https://t.co/VAP9micsuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the usual suspects #steakday #familydinner #cattletales #winelover @ Dodge City, Kansas https://t.co/xuJtA8UONh]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 games....how many did that giant Russian fuck get for an attempted decapitation again? Oh yea 1 game...Voracek ge… https://t.co/vj9COhHp82]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafetyPinDaily I watched the video. She just didn't storm out of the meeting she read them the riot act first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The babies' real identities were kept secret, so the girls took to giving them names like Denny Domecon (for domest… https://t.co/t27xy9KMWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost dog (Aurora, CO): Our dog got out the yard and is missing. His name is Jax, is 6 years old, about 70 lbs, has… https://t.co/FQWsDh33wQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump For Republicans to get behind a sociopathic liar and treasonous Trumph is the real twisted wind.… https://t.co/QjYFdSvp9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlightyF @Nonpartisanciti Sounds great if u ever wanna  do Hangouts with me your welcome to😊😊🤟🤟]]></document><document><![CDATA[George Quaintance Is the Gay Artist Who Taught Tom of Finland Everything He Knows https://t.co/sOXKaSJ9rG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Little_NickyS @totalgolfmove How would you know what reaching a par 5 in two feels like? 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good evening. Got 4 hrs. of nap accompanied with a day off tomorrow. God has smiled on me oh yes he has!  https://t.co/1UUim38zX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robopz @feedtheball YOU are joining these nutters on revising history? The majors are major. Doesn’t matter who di… https://t.co/Nlt77A57a6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DHSgov @SecNielsen Any lie that will make the boss look justified in his dam wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @realDonaldTrump I don’t think you’re getting enough oxygen to your brain from having your head up Mr. 🍊 ass all day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_Winns1 Whoah buddy, the country music stopped after you left, nigga played chief keef too]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much would you pay to watch a Pay Per View camera in @realDonaldTrump’s hotel room during Cohen’s testimony???… https://t.co/qf9t4SazAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pau comes back onto the San Antonio hardwood for the first time as a Buck, instantly gets scored on. Leads to a Mil… https://t.co/F0LoXZkFmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time catching up @liannelaing Living Your Life podcast next week!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Congrats ” to Holmes and Watson for cleaning up at the Razzies tonight.  Looks like Braun Strowman and Billy Zane escaped unscathed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies.... My blood is boiling.... Some rando keeps trying to take my seat in sociology!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyTeton @EarlYorke @perlmutations If you say so, Jimmy. We're talking about, maybe, a dozen extra votes? 'Cause that's all he's getting]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Main Event Entertainment - @mymainevent in Plano, TX https://t.co/pll54vnKkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameOverGreggy @SamWitwer Good to hear!!! I’m excited to hear @KindaFunnyVids discussion!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Metro Bus Stop 35 Grand/Washington in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/kiubIG8XW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to an ax throwing bar tomorrow... what could possibly go wrong? 😕 https://t.co/sMSPynXjho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gut punch to my faith in the justice system. Seems like this lacks a “deterrent to others” component.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish all I could do is play video games eat well and workout constantly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandsmartin @JussieSmollett The stupidest part of the @JussieSmollett situation is that now these Neo-BLACK cons… https://t.co/g2R5egzl9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[This project should include black banks, realtors, lawyers, and builders!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duquesne WBB Vojinovic &amp; Omogrosso 3/2/19 | PSN https://t.co/1lpr9swgM6 via @YouTube @ChasOmogrosso2 @DuqWBB @Coachdanburt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas woman sentenced to 5 years in prison for VOTING while on probation... Manafort gets 47 months for innumerable… https://t.co/yJRS4nHlku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puedo tener un año más de prueba en esta app llamada vida?  Estos primeros 25 años como que ya le estoy entendiendo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Mr. President,  Please calm down. There are no witch hunts. The special counsel who is investigating the Russi… https://t.co/lrwWiMKu7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoLABolts @MTCovington MT knows whats up...you believe carson was legit....thats all i need to know]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/oAir3pNMFM @ Buy Here - Pay Here - $0 Down Options https://t.co/9OYB43torQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIpatriotIZ @dustingardiner @SecretaryHobbs @VoteReagan @GeneralBrnovich @azcpolitics I knew I was forgetting something🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm just glad it's over. Time to move on. Let's get back to Steeler Football.  We have a draft coming up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[REALLY. Go screw some more ISIS fighters........oops you can’t. They’re all running away or dead 💀. Made your bed s… https://t.co/5fmKAuilxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ddawareness19 @ The Arc of The Bay / St. Andrew Bay Center https://t.co/Ml0m7QGrLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst @survivorcbs also, you put @JohnMCochran on the show for writing about it in college. What do I get for… https://t.co/NkDi1NCXtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siwertell hard at work unloading a dry product barge at the Port of Morehead.  #chazsworld  #draftsurvey  #ports… https://t.co/DZZteDxU9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeSizemore9 Not sure what a whip is, that hurt in my day... Nice ride though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xbabygirldreaax @angelcentenoo Hahahhaha! I’m dead! That’s freaking hilarious! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had 4 cupcakes for breakfast.. now there’s a storm brewing brb..]]></document><document><![CDATA[LHP Matt Krook worked out with #Rays minor leaguers yesterday then got a call afterward that he was invited to join… https://t.co/MaEod59sZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexGoodwinTSM The rumor is Klutch Sports is going to try to force him out, so he can be an unrestricted free agen… https://t.co/9PyYqx47Nk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganRPark @JordanOloman Man, I need to replay this after I replay Mario Odyssey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PdXShecky @efilnikufsin A couple years ago there were forums for matching people with teams. When I was a captain… https://t.co/2uBfbKd7yz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realworldrj @nytmike @maggieNYT @adamgoldmanNYT @anniekarni Ivanka is a phony in a nice suit, who suggests sophist… https://t.co/15z3Zz9n3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VClinebarton @AuthorMBTosi @AuthorEllie @PletchaPJWebb @MJLaBeff @deann_native @awlasky @DianeShute @birdwriter7… https://t.co/l2XKJ2GanN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because some days demand pancakes. @ Claudine Kitchen and Bakeshop https://t.co/6i0F9Zfoo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@superboy8500 Right!?! Like can I start you an application so your ass can  be working too? https://t.co/BHKOeiTGu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Happy19111 @Birdseye1 @Dannaja64Danny @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1 @billcrowley3rd @Flavio72162205… https://t.co/IJQJrug4PV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShinSolidus @tinka_nichols Tinka snatch yo chain https://t.co/av2VOYIpQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔  I really enjoy that this segment on the economy suggests 2 &gt; 8.  It’s just 😙👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yeah!! @jamesdelow @SKILLITWORLD @AshroseUK @MattDaviesAdams @WWEGP https://t.co/iu3uVVZrNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@islacharlatan @eponawest I highly recommend reading the books and essays by Donella Meadows including  _Thinking i… https://t.co/tBhXx6nOjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarlerFm @WBIRWeather @10weather @TNHouseReps @tnsenate @ltgovmcnally @GlenCasada @BillLeeTN @POTUS… https://t.co/mPxSF0B9i6]]></document><document><![CDATA[No relationship is perfect but it sure  as hell gets alot easier if you know how to communicate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My soul is highly irritated at the fact @BhadBhabie was made famous and is now rich for being a dumbass delinquent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsTalkBarry Let’s see the list of ones you wouldn’t want dating your daughter. Kareem Hunt is a give in....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m proud and happy to be connected with talented people @pierrefitch 😋🔥😈  Follow him guys @Pierrefitch and give so… https://t.co/lfpYjU0vjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume Your network polishes Donald Trump’s knob, Daily. For you to call anyone else embarrassing is hilarious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this month has been the most shittiest month i’ve experienced in awhile :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I have tons of expenses related to sept 11. I lost my business during an exhasterbation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McMittBabe @newsyCaitlin The second one in Lehi was shorter, but I we felt a huge "pop" and it felt like our whole house shifted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieCoyle_3 man, we’re going to miss you here in MN. Thanks for being such a class act with the @mnwild . This… https://t.co/yF9615LkZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything I thought I could love about myself is for no reason. A waste of time. No need to have even built up thi… https://t.co/wY0dm6Yngb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uuuuy qué gusto prender la TV y ver que @LaJugadaTD la conducen @AdrianaMonsalve @lucia_villalon @Mariazelzel… https://t.co/xcniwCfWej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Players that have leadership skills like Aaron Donald definitely deserve to be in the super bowl every year !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Stan Lee tribute had audiences clapping on Captain Marvel's preview night  https://t.co/RJYJXctlO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a new driver from Eagle River in the NASCAR truck series named Natalie Decker. She's 21, she's extremely be… https://t.co/e7ojLbUYr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias Better news- Garrett’s Popcorn at concourse B is the best popcorn in the know universe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRFegan It would seem from the Machado case that more often than not it does just come down to throwing as much gu… https://t.co/8jbbTRBzcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekapman @MeganMawicke Kap, that pic looks like Paul Rudd and @MichaelKeaton had a baby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well now that @MSHSL #TheTourney19 is underway, I am anxiously awaiting the #AllHockeyHair team! My favorite time o… https://t.co/QLwUqjmVOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[whoever continues to call me off restricted can u like uhhhh fucking not ???????]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you wake up at 2pm the next day covered in puke and a headache that feels like satan is hitting you with a ham… https://t.co/naymwuo3jy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp there it is, Bochy announced his retirement at the end of the season.  Didn't take Farhan long to run him out of town.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- what do you think will be the end of this? C- this is spilling into the real world.  All who have broken the law… https://t.co/OwHPdqRipH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monchy &amp; Alexandra Best Hits!! omg best track ever:  https://t.co/GJHvNGaDfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suesswassersee @spintheiryarns Jesus truly does save.   Come on guys. That was super easy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its about time the truth comes out about Democrats.  They went from Physical slavery to mental slavery]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebirthOfbritt @__Gallis__ @jpaigenoelle You ain’t delete it doe https://t.co/TVIEa40zN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigSomething @AqueousBand round 2 next year! whadduya say gentlemen??!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @Indians need @TheJK_Kid to have a big year and I think he's poised for just that. He played last year with a t… https://t.co/70BJeEIJTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisODavis #vintage2008 #caroussanne #southerngravy #gumbo @ McMinnville, Oregon https://t.co/aD7t4nkXu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaVinciPode Oh man let's make it 48 hours the flyers got 2 more points from the devis while trying to beat up thei… https://t.co/AsnqWWUVkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drmauvillalobos La historia de la humanidad no es sino una larga guerra con interrupciones de paz cada vez mas cor… https://t.co/W1J6o3xLtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten Personally I hope the Jay's keep Pompey &amp; Alord for center field and DFA Pillar offers has little upside.]]></document></documents></author>