<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I worked with this girl over the summer who I became really close with. Over the last 6 weeks I was home, we hung o… https://t.co/aHx2z3oPGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all being pregnant but your mind still stress eat is the worst! Tryin to save money but that bagel called my name… https://t.co/ez6yUYeFPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatMixxedNigga @OG_Rojo @zav_24 @_victorbustos I love y’all and appreciate y’all so much ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks goes out to The Marshall Community and Schlotzsky's for your support of our AKA, Nu Omega Chapter fundraiser… https://t.co/gmGy7J3qvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 Wishful thinking? One nail in the proverbial coffin at a time, although that event would be exquisite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love his little voice 😭😍 #Malakhi #blippi @blippiofficial @ Lexington, Kentucky https://t.co/Az9Kos3lcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ITSDJFLOW Give it to a mom! Cuz we spend money on kid shit so much you don’t even shop for yourself! Moms be feeli… https://t.co/t6dZpeS3NB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left #CaptainMarvel feeling powerful and inspired. I stopped to chat with strangers. A dude said; “Iron Man is mo… https://t.co/UB4Br9rOxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think about your face and how I fall into your eyes, the outline that I trace around the one that I call mine]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to target today to get a new baby gate and just remembered I forgot to get a baby gate 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Mariah I was born in April My age is not working I like to see you and your family]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m wondering if @GovEvers is up to speed on this. https://t.co/bkG6mIVimF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jesus_Luvs_Us @Jilliemary @ClockworkHamma @MelindaYoe @roads2 @Iluvinspireu @Peeperpea29 @SherryBretz05… https://t.co/SGGUubu5m8]]></document><document><![CDATA[God our Father, You have promised to remain for ever with those who do what is just and right. Help us to live in Y… https://t.co/Fg2CqFKqtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, sure. But also, Iger is in charge of keeping that entire company steaming along which honestly isn’t easy.… https://t.co/F6GjRq0i6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its ladies night! Both North Hunterdon and Voorhees girls basketball teams advanced to quarterfinals in their respe… https://t.co/NSyN5zhSh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_shireenahmed_ And I owe each and every one of them my heartfelt thanks. 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @MickelsonGeorge I miss you every day come visit me pls. You make me laugh. I LOVE YOU https://t.co/TsWSQi0oS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Enough212 Tell the whole story. Person calls cops says they r smoking mj in room. Cops have to chek it out. Its th… https://t.co/paOgywZvZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[15 minutes ago i thought it “wouldn’t be a bad idea” to listen to angel olsen in the lyft line and now i’m silently… https://t.co/Du7c2IalL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: @VisionZeroSATxDot -Say No 2 Distractions while U R  walking, biking, running and/or driving! Distractions can… https://t.co/PAbxOmaVLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Embrace your embarrassment. Learn to love it, laugh it off &amp; have fun. You’ll liberate yourself 🌄💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irisastraea @mannyslays thank u so much. this is exactly what i have been coming across a lot lately and i realize… https://t.co/55CnHjBILe]]></document><document><![CDATA[what a journey it has been. can’t fully explain how much this sport has given me. from teammates who have become my… https://t.co/MVIVAfvgIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jules_heaven @cxlleee @josettteee don’t watch it all tonight silly 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@motherboardsnyc @TGirlsnyc @LaceAngelica @TrannyStrip @sandymichellehk @_NYCevents @KasandraSnchez3… https://t.co/z7to8o0Omq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachDavidSisk @mjessenhoward @MinnesotaRivals That dunk should be on as one of @jordanmurphy24 career highlights.… https://t.co/m8OVJ984bI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nintendo: “you start out as a mercenary traveling with a group led by your fathe-“ Me: NO NOT THIS AGAIN… https://t.co/NahPrBoV5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women will soon reach another milestone! 👩🏽‍🚀👩🏻‍🚀 https://t.co/UJVop4OcPx via @nbcnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcm1115 @50cent Wake up it’s wasn’t hourly and you do not respond no matter what like he did. Get the strap on you girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StehlarTerry @justinhendrix @tonyposnanski @lynnbixenspan https://t.co/c0lbcOH8V5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all this man was trying HARD to convince me to not wear makeup and why I didn't need it but all the while, insulted me and my craft 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am sure he could find another birth certificate like he did his other one just give him enough time and he could… https://t.co/cK3ShhM1Kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShePersisted421 @LarkinWarren @the_real_mwp @urbanrocker @tonyposnanski https://t.co/nQ9Bf9resM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg it’s literally the best feeling ever to be able to breath normally and walk without coughing after being sick all week #hallelujah]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always love the Epcot loop. 💕😍 . . . . . . . #MonorailMonday #Monorail #MonorailOrange #WDW #wdwmonorail… https://t.co/vGzSxIs22v]]></document><document><![CDATA[the LORD gives sight to the blind.  The LORD raises up those who are bowed down; the LORD loves the righteous.  The… https://t.co/13XRCwJheT]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1UDIPHM9yq  #bassethound #bassetthound #beagle #beaglesofinstagram #dogsofinstagram #gofundme… https://t.co/UcqzAvTcPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrlandoOchoa Para este apagon se aliaron para el sabotaje: la lagartija, la iguana, la ardilla, la culebra, el rat… https://t.co/fzPcpLpSzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacquel14277925 @LoganMurphy1 @RepMaxineWaters I remember seeing that headliner earlier. How bout you start fact c… https://t.co/XwlZiKimY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisAllen02 Jake and Freddy are hanging out in heaven.  This was my dog, Freddy.   He lived for 18 years.   Happ… https://t.co/2LV5UNDYMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I filled up my hydro flask this morning and of course I left it in my room smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY BBYS IM GONNA CRY ARE THEY PERFORMING TOGETHER https://t.co/gONvd7dII9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Relatable!  To see more relatable posts, check out so-relatable.tumb...  for teen quotes, funny... #laughter… https://t.co/W3AGPjtpgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djuhnk @Twitter 😔 you will be missed. Best of luck in whatever you do!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Tell her she can't FLY she better catch a TRAIN! She must not be a polluter???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was one of those days where I wanted to eat all the junk foods. &amp; it’s not event that time of the month. #ControlYaSelf 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dylan is going to flip when he wakes up to see what songs I downloaded 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nadinesomething We often rent a van when we need to pick up drywall or such. It’s $20 per day (plus gas &amp; extra insurance if needed).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKarem Trump will even *pay you back* if the bid beats out all other bids on all other *pieces of art*. https://t.co/tp3QWvRzFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am obsessed with #NKOTB’s new song, #BoysInTheBand! And love that they redid their looks from Hangin Tough Live!😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be waking up in Canada and looking forward to our first day skiing 🎿 Lots of snow last night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part Two of the yearly Autoshow! Love that Purple Lambo! #autoshow2019 @ Metro Toronto Convention Centre https://t.co/8R3WLRQfKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AandGShow just read Newsom killed bullspit train project???? Hope it is true!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was not feeling well this morning after a rough pain night. I woke up this and felt instantly better 🥰… https://t.co/EONOycijzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@htxnena Nooo. Never that. Snowball fights hurt. I said let’s build a snowman!]]></document><document><![CDATA[one of my ex boyfriends got a face tattoo and now it’s a meme for my friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cloud21wAM @seargantgoober @not_mchammer 😂😂😂😂 prayers for my new roommate whoever they are]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uber drivers are dumb af! My sister got into an accident today in an Uber and he managed to get hit on both sides a… https://t.co/WtbSySUdAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally we have longer days! Sunsets at 6:50p today 🥳🥳🥳 - #artofvisuals #chicagoland #enjoyillinois #moodygrams… https://t.co/WOWxS4oUi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNCWBaseball @CoastalBaseball Can’t be there😢too much driving but Seahawks will dominate ⚾️❤️🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls High School Hoops... Section Class AAAA Championship... Hopkins  vs   Wayzata. https://t.co/Fg5sthQEr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone’s feelings should be taken into consideration. You can’t have all of your feelings being taken in by someo… https://t.co/LTwbUa4Szf]]></document><document><![CDATA[i know about 6 ppl visiting the vatican rn and i only know theyre there bc ive seen 6 illegal pics of st. peters ba… https://t.co/gHe7zUNs2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffAbramo @CarolineKepnes I loved You and Hidden Bodies - hope Deanna treats you well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamID @JoeyKing @PattyArquette @TheActOnHulu Yay ...@PattyArquette  I got tickets to see the new show “The Act an… https://t.co/0ajMy9FsWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you might get to wear jeans for a whole 2 weeks... You buy $100 worth of meat lol https://t.co/v0aSpPKTMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lionel_Layton @joabaldwin @AbrahmLion "When I get out of here, I'm going to wear out a LOT of official stamps and pens..."]]></document><document><![CDATA[That comment applies &amp; is addressed directly to @georgiagov and @BrianKempGA #GeorigaGovernor  #Electioncheater2018]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel bad for the people who always have good things happen to them then the worse comes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn You're the clueless one. Is it 2020 yet? #TexasDeservesBetter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patssi Valdez, ‘Scattered’ (silkscreen, 3 colors), 1987 (and detail) Self-Help Graphics, 1983-1991 exhibit… https://t.co/PxYEGVYqe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Max_n_Ruby @Beatlemaniac201 @Michael28710212 @wrestlejasmine @OfficialLivePD @LHVanhorn Sweet dreams Ruby!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maribella Right now I feel I need to up my prepper game and get more emergency supplies. Or I should start by teac… https://t.co/MW0Mmk1NMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up feeling blessed to see another year of life. I’m wearing 36 good 😉.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaBertrand @joshscampbell When you see them together like that, they look like a smacked ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@filming_chicago Want to go check out the Med filming but it’s really crappy out. We’ll see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obianuju Muslims can preach their religion but Christians can't Bible prophet is being fulfilled Jesus is coming back soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brunching with my 5 am gym rats and my baby goat. https://t.co/E7zWGqKRcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lenacarolinag @nickccerino Mozz Sticks make me weak https://t.co/7JnXDlVog7]]></document><document><![CDATA[People don’t like me for the fuck of it, never spoke to me a day in their life but got alot to say. shits crazy out here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my co-worker calls to report it and we're told that unless you can determine they don't have food or water they… https://t.co/Khs51RvMHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[i video called my bestfriends in ph by surprise ‘cos I simply wanted to greet them Happy Valentines, only to find o… https://t.co/cudQWewt5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Δ9‑Tetrahydrocannabinol, a major marijuana component, enhances the anesthetic effect of pentobarbital through the C… https://t.co/JEVNCo6kLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nomanchesfrida2 ya empezamos las entrevistas! Les presento al director #nachovelilla @PantelionFilms estrena 15 de… https://t.co/f24P5SH60F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy happy birthday davethecoronas !!!! ❤️❤️ @ The Short Stop https://t.co/037wEiKZ31]]></document><document><![CDATA[A “journalistic channel”?? 😂😂😂😂😂The fact that the Left is so upset about this just proves how left-leaning/biased t… https://t.co/wxJXypS5Qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marshall13543 Thank you! Hadn’t seen this, gracias por compartir! Thanks for sharing :) @ELBURRITOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Looks like pretty soon you will be able to add Roger Stone to that lineup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1.5 X matching donations! I love this teacher's idea for helping students:  https://t.co/40bs7AQM2z via @donorschoose]]></document><document><![CDATA[For people saying Karl Lagerfeld was the most prolific designer of the 20th and 21st century, you know Chanel was a… https://t.co/GPpEuQhdo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philosophrob Sorry to say this - but the trust factor is with NO ONE who is a declared candidate. Except Bernie.… https://t.co/xtsc8XLSLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[More unpopular opinions.  Hate it when a man doesn't remove his cover when in a restaurant (most of you will know w… https://t.co/2iBduna64d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottGendel @ZackShapiro @anildash I think you kinda have to get that tattooed to your ass now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoIIaback @BallStateMBB wow you are so incredible grace I can’t believe i’m lucky enough to call you my friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robwhisman I've been in therapy for five years and still have self-loathing thoughts daily. What's the secret?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having fun at the Hypnosis Show!!   #hypnosis #hypnotist #hypnosisshow #comedy #pattiefreeman #hypnosisbypattie#ari… https://t.co/nl0AD6SYYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennline10 I'll make it official...yes you were right. #OneDayAtATime #RitaMoreno https://t.co/H2RNXreGRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[ain’t gon whip it up like me, she ain’t got the recipe https://t.co/AGXaiuSwIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg omg omg!! It’s @ThomasRios17 birthday!!! Happy birthday, have a great and wild day!]]></document></documents></author>