<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[clear sky -&gt; light rain temperature down 56°F -&gt; 51°F humidity up 67% -&gt; 87% wind 3mph -&gt; 16mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormOrnstein The rats hold hands every time a big truck goes by! (One of my late dad's fave lines!) You can't slee… https://t.co/ujonBvP2R3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Hampton Inn Kansas City/Liberty https://t.co/4FKKA9zUW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[120: Highly anticipated bout between Devin Flannery and Justin Bierdumpfel. Rematch of the District 1 final #njwrestling]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m having a really sad day but 90% of my job at work is reading to and holding little two year olds so that helps]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you aren’t listening to Darci you’re missing out! https://t.co/ljomEr4KZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s still hilarious to me how Gohan basically just became a meme after the Cell fight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews if you think for one second that illegal immigrants are going to a gun srore to “buy” a gun, your nuts!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpitballersPod Shirly you can't be serious?  @jasonffl can't even get his movie quotes right. "Every man dies, not… https://t.co/Q0L5RqVITu]]></document><document><![CDATA[From my secret Monday location. #allengittelson  #mentalwires… https://t.co/wAUeh8v79Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the Baddies that use Big Girls for Body Guards and Transportation had to leave as well lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[guidedogmaster. 6 mins ago. burned 1,326 calories doing 60 minutes of Stationary bike, very vigorous effort (bicycling, cycling, biking)!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonnterreyNL @javierzapata10_ @TigresOficial @jurgendammr25 @Lucazelarayan31 No pues si]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealStevenAdams Go back and watch the 4th q and OT’s tonight and just see how bad you got your ass destroyed. Gobe… https://t.co/yt8UP3f3GC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin Angelica cries out to me everyday that she loves me and she wants me to help her to be set free from slav… https://t.co/3z362WeHtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@global_ju @JasonGraystone Couldn't agree more. It's a favorite part of @JennieLakenan and my Sunday afternoons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first HC to work for always said, "Nothing about flip flops (he called them slippers) screams Championship menta… https://t.co/26Rp2fcFgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWifeYouLove @CrazyAF_ButCute I take care of myself by taking care of those I love]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tannertrezise No way, that’s awesome. Holler at me if there’s a next time! And, how about that Price fight? 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Context is everything, follow the flow of the tweets. That’s like reading a hot take headline and summarized the st… https://t.co/B0soYgjcMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible. Sad that it had to end that way with the refs so heavily involved in both ends. No flow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fishy and cautious smells rotten but a cover up of the truth can fix it all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alpwrdsb I think I have the best job ever. #gratitude and #optimism in action]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burnsy2155 @NickDiehl6 @Evan_ODonnell7 @CatholicU_FB https://t.co/dAhKf45DRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish speed cameras would give people tickets for going to slow past the speed camera]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePhightins33 I got done early today. My "normal" Commute home is about 75 minutes!! Today 25!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[El 90 % de las personas tampoco y los que sabían la mayoría nunca han usado algo #Chanel lo FIRMO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[if he doesn’t make this Bill Self ships him off to a foreign country and we never hear from him again]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy to me how different 6 minutes feels on the treadmill vs scrolling on my phone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a Lebron on the court guy, big on him off it. That being said, that leather jacket he got on walking into the locker room?!?!?! 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to book a trip to Chicago with the $$ I got for my Hamilton tickets! So that's not really "Throwin' Away My S… https://t.co/K20cXRVKD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @AudreyNBC4 @bethNBC   @EllieMerrittTV @JenniferNBC4 @Katie_Ferrell @KatieLoveSocial @mdrayer1 @NBCMonica @ElyseChengery @MeganMullally]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another example of Ridiculous California governing                       Mr President please come to Sacramento and… https://t.co/DyS3XYYQsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[McDonald's french fries are the best there is, the best there was, and the best there ever will be. shoutout to the Hitman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom @i_blanden Are you saying that Israel should have more control of the U.S. Congress than we do? That… https://t.co/ehusbiLN5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddFriel You a hell, fire and brimstone preacher? 🔥 We need more preaching like it. Jesus talked more about hell… https://t.co/RjPUC9ew8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenloitelusnet1 No..I'm saying that ther's no guarantee the Habs make the playoffs next season with a signed Duche… https://t.co/Dw6KvSmAoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieWGME @wgme  Happy #MardiGras #fattuesday #TheBoris https://t.co/VNVTWjSkBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeMcKenna56 @KBizzl311 @AlexOn11th Great photo Alex!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 @shitebart Black Hole Buffoonery! https://t.co/O7V1iio2gB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosterWatch He is one of my favorite under-the-radar backs. He will make an NFL team next season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cedarflats @cellmavin @SierraNevada @CATbrew13 @ManvsAle @beerhunter74 @linda_lballis @JacobGrimes @zappafaye… https://t.co/KsozUz5KP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today on @greatdaywash why folks believe @busboysandpoets will boost the #Anacostia neighborhood https://t.co/CRBy3KJyeP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuyInSeattle1 I never said ‘faked,’ but how do you mess up someone’s body fat?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephGillMA @Northshore_Dave @MartinMonster22 @ScottDKushner And we’re going to pretend that professional sports,… https://t.co/wN9TS5BmdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a day... @imaginedragons were AMAZING!! Some gig, some craic! #trainerlife #LasVegas #giglife #instatraveller… https://t.co/kOj1XjFtLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT #Traveler #RinconesdelMundo🌎 #Nature en Red Rock Canyon National Conservation Area https://t.co/J8o9zVps1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dragonthekid @dumdommy That was more centered around Hubie with the awkward handshake]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ipv6tech It’s been months in the making. I can’t wait until my next brew day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brown not 'angry' with Steelers, still wants trade https://t.co/sOl6zLujTl via @ESPN App https://t.co/69E1fOMlMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a Godmother is rad. Just look at those cheeks! @ Texas https://t.co/K5e9DIVTPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohshawr Lol trying to, but yeah already got one fully planned and drawn out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sc22657 @IvankaTrump Make larger payments and it will be obsolved faster.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anson Seabra - Robin Hood (Official Lyric Video) https://t.co/87NVLlsaNI via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was hiding from myself, she found me. When I was alone, she gave me a family. And after a lifetime of knowin… https://t.co/KKt55cu5kF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want to hear whining about Manafort’s sentence when #katesteinle killer #josezarate didn’t get convicted of… https://t.co/CfzguGJA2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though the fig trees have no fruit and no grapes grow on the vines, even though the oliv…… https://t.co/Vbyj0aBvhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Budden beat his dark skinned pregnant black girlfriend into a miscarriage only to go on and have a child by a w… https://t.co/HW6JaGkVhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you guys for always coming through and for making this all fun. Great job this morning and always keep pushin… https://t.co/xI8tjOBSHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@raebo13⁩ Rachel Tetlow ACOG Director of Federal Affairs skillfully briefing OB/Gyns on our upcoming Hill visit to… https://t.co/mlvPBOAQtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshnilson @SeanWebster13 @SouthwestAir Haha I’ve had the absolute worst luck with my last 4 weeks of travel. Good to finally be home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why isn’t the media reporting people are receiving less on their tax returns or is it fake news?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geography_kes Awesome! I'm going to have to check that one out! Thanks Kate! #worldgeochat]]></document><document><![CDATA[The replies to this are basically:  - Men should protect women from war.  - You’re devaluing women!!!   Wait ... wh… https://t.co/78TDojqhyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EAristeguieta En Venezuela hay más generales que en los EEUU y la UE juntos. Los sobornaron con grados inmerecidos… https://t.co/DwNBs9xHkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Realmommabear @Tennesseine @asmith702 That’s an indictment against the bought congress that he’s served in, not of him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Shining_237 , you are killing it with these podcast guests for this final run of episodes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to find a sociologist to write this Kendrick Lamar/J. Cole article with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@btsvotingteam @BTS_twt #TwitterBestFandom⁠ ⁠⁠ ⁠ #TeamBTS #SoompiAwards⁠ ⁠⁠ ⁠@BTS_twt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsaacParejo @PSOE Perfect! On Target!  Tienes mucho valor para decir la verdad.  Gracias]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pam_brundige @PbbResists Neither will we, but your side certainly tries to silence us plenty fine.... Tomfoolery on both ends?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gp_wisconsin @atDavidHoffman @denver_rose That’s an excellent word to describe who they are (or were at the moment… https://t.co/s33AcBIa7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pilgrimdear @lumperslump I dont really rotate, im sure there are towels on the bottom of the stack that only get u… https://t.co/sntsi35h8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josie_Blow You're beautiful. And with a cock in your mouth you are sensational. ❤️💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Since Medicaid is a Joint State Federal Program, a State judge cannot order the Federal Government t… https://t.co/Qn4N2HqRGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twinqueen53 @PeaceVibesPromo @mikeonmyradio @buttahslayslay @RoniLynn817 @Voice4yourPets @LuckyASSETS… https://t.co/S2qpeTFCZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@airwright @CoachDBattaglia I feel compelled to remind everyone that the Big 12 has 10 teams and the ACC has 15. If… https://t.co/ZvTi3b3mCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LamonyaShotwell @nortoriousLKL @notmaassa @CamiyaMccary naw...naw its still white racism that's actually killing p… https://t.co/aWFRNmtJf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG totally misses my subway stop! Long walk in the snow? Well campus life offers Infinite Corridors and Underground Tunnels!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salute to the Executive Producer @CliveDavis #Legend #GRAMMYsAretha #ArethaTribute https://t.co/vMvf94lR7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[14:49 Temp. 47.5°F, Hum. 92%, Dewp. 44.6°F, Bar. 30.01 inHg, Rain Today 0.0787 inch, Wind 100° 2.7 kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[El café ayuda a quien duerme poco y sueña mucho! #ootd #entrepeneur #phrases #picoftheday #instagram en Punto Valle https://t.co/lGIvqRXeOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Princess and Pop back from the Doggie Groomer looking all spiffy for St Patrick’s Day (and March Madness).… https://t.co/m5Q3E3G6RH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stevenkrosz @SebGorka @TheDemocrats Yes, we need stupid people running, it’s not enough to have 1/2 the us dumb enough to vote in AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpenbookWriter @anthemgame I think if you know thats an issue as a content creator you either optimize and fix sai… https://t.co/pKmFetrmb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charge all these fools as adults😤 EVERYDAY ITS SOMETHING NEW IN THIS FUCKED UP SOCIETY. I wish i could talk to this… https://t.co/b0GAvePRnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously, what is mentally wrong with #DJT ? Is he truly trying to ruin our relationships with these big allie of… https://t.co/3MvKTLmy37]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dustin left for work early so as soon as he left i got sad and started crying.. why am i like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[HIPÓLITO MEJÍA EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en… https://t.co/raRQkwQ6p1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ianjfrance @BBCWorld @greta The Palestinians aren’t the subject of this discussion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roman Reigns returns to Raw tonight to give us an update on his battle with leukemia. Hopefully it's some good news]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halsey I don’t even understand what they all mean guess I’m getting old]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @JussieSmollett Since he lied to police in 2007 and was cited for such how does he show impeccable character?]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do u have a ship carry cargo but you have a car go and carry shipment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive got a pretty great job. @Wessjosh #legendshasit @ Legends Nightclub Complex https://t.co/fuMo5T7MXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LennyMelnick @rotolady When Harper’s contract expires Bobby Bonilla will still be getting paid]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a digital design gets fast enough, you treat the digital as analog and the analog as slow-speed. Fun stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The exploding federal deficit is all @realDonaldTrump and @GOP . Trump is the #kingofdebt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanBertheau estaría a toda madre que le pusieras algo así a tu nave 🤙🏼💪 https://t.co/gwvRUXIjgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollectorVt 2012 heritage Yankees plus a mattingly, if ur interested https://t.co/AWnAuKdaBV]]></document></documents></author>