<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Twitter I'm just learning Twitter and I don't understand all this I don't know what's going on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Another Funny Quotes and Sayings Compilation - StumbleUpon #comedy #chuckle #smile #farcical https://t.co/SWV41Iz2Mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmsteltz My wife had to practically force the nurses and Dr.'s to let her breast feed because they were so concern… https://t.co/8OhN7mroiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump NOT ONLY ARE YOU A LIAR, YOU SUCK AT IT ! That footage is from Sept. 18 showing repair of an exist… https://t.co/dTQyjKqRhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicaramos Well, since your book isn't the Constitution, we are all still safe and sound.  And will continue to… https://t.co/IkwZOND9bN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just at Weis in Endwell no people to check you out except oversize lady telling me how to check myself out 6 o’cloc… https://t.co/oIDCGjuCeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@synredae @Myminimine @Seajay603 @Elinor27652146 @kneadinghands @Observer2541 @danielbkof2 @jibukc @KirkHaffland… https://t.co/nbrY5DDDr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Kuzma said that the Lakers were going to surprise people this year, I didn’t think it would be like this 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conversely, you can say the Flyers were losing games earlier this season because they were getting (well) below ave… https://t.co/KTV4W3lSeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@300Coupe @DaveOceanAir @DullesDistrict @sarahdeal Some FYI trivia. Sid Morris who did some Wrangler racing materia… https://t.co/YVQ6rncETP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritYah 3)If we sway too far left or right, we tend to develop tunnel vision.... doesn't mean we don't see anyth… https://t.co/lXZTtTA4XV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aprés ride 😂 #atlanta #cycling @ Jack's New Yorker Deli - Atlanta Road https://t.co/yiibcxklh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Used to worship these guys growing up. Had their poster and everything. I thought of them as Gods walking amongst m… https://t.co/rR8VKfTpEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you handle the truth https://t.co/fxSWZUBg7h                #integrityrestored]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is a story unfolding before your very eyes | #ComingSoon @therealsokaine #Angelz  ......  #DirectorEscobar… https://t.co/jnoEhr8ehr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great work by @OmahaHKY players on the bye weekend volunteer refereeing  with Special Olympics floor hockey https://t.co/n4LlYU5ywD]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Those who dare to fail miserably, can achieve greatly.” - John F. Kennedy  🏔🔝 • • • #capstonewealthadvisors… https://t.co/491GO1R1RV]]></document><document><![CDATA[hingefinger B2B @BenUFO  📸: @mellow_my_man @ III Points https://t.co/XqgHnXmk85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traciethoms @TheDannyPino I remember cold case wow you guys go back like ODB and Mariah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reesetheone1 Especially when none of the candidates have explicitly used the term or described it in ways that trigger people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcn4eva @MAGAGirl8 @peppertrumper @Wblscott1 @debit_mullins @dfalls1552 @gloscovfefe @glo4itnow @QmagaMike… https://t.co/0hA9JTR5co]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChazNuttycombe @vahousegop Truth is while house gop wanted me to stay, they respectfully didn't ask me not to run… https://t.co/KtHC4ixXw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizroscher Second, spring training is not for the TV viewing public. It’s for those that go down to FL or AZ to en… https://t.co/3KKFXAyCld]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Original Crabby Bills in Indian Rocks Beach, FL https://t.co/72TF49PzYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to start this new journey at a great institution! Thankful that Coach Chadwell gave me this great opportunity!… https://t.co/nXFwtJjrCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michael_mantis @pedrostarfleet @TheOrville @planetary_union They were LCD monitors to could press for the pilot. S… https://t.co/YlnFXeGiQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeatonPatti If you're going to save lives, you might as well look good doing it, amirite?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hip Hip Hooray👍👏👍👏👍👏👍👏👍👏👍👏👍👏👍👏👍👏👍👏👍👏 @ Prescott, Wisconsin https://t.co/zfMzTJjiZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it's practice but if I ever see Eloy Jimenez batting anywhere lower than 5th in a Major League lineup...]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t always have to travel to find adventure @Gigi_na . . . #pointdume #whalewatching #malibu 📸: sxmspxctxr @… https://t.co/Q0HYS8LptZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know the refs were not the best , But if the #Hokies lose they gave this game away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkenya_bingwa Wow. May God have Mercy on their Souls. My Condolences to the #Bereaved Family of the Lost]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped at the outlet to take a meeting. Misty still getting it done.  #mazda #protege5 #windy @ Carlsbad Premium O… https://t.co/P71XB2y4Na]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaiPan_StraunCo In 16 states you found only 1 type of bread and pork ? I don't believe that for one second. Unless… https://t.co/yyhYaxJdFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martinwb10 hey it’s my best friend @RonnieHass birthday over here in the states! He’s 27, could he get a birthday shout out please!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I threw a hand grenade. It's probably one of the most terrifying experiences. It gives you the chills...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes be stuck listening to every heartbeat like damn these shits beatin slow asf]]></document><document><![CDATA[La soirée débute à l'instant.  Je suis très fier de partager la reconnaissance de @GaudrjoJohanne ce soir au… https://t.co/bwZu3LIbUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeastModeManny You and me both! lol I'm watching that click like a hawk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido La gente sigue muriendo! Hasta cuando??? Ya empezamos de nuevo a perder las esperanzas!! Quizás se repita… https://t.co/rHjI5b5T8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xotigbitties @discordapp @RapandTV Also interested to know for a friend 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some oldies! I need to get some color soon after seeing these lol                                       #tbt… https://t.co/MQgL77msci]]></document><document><![CDATA[This winter has been the perfect advocate for personal flamethrower ownership. #FrozenHell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emdavies1 happy Thursday to you beautiful lady from John in Manhattan NY ❤️❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/FWIvCk1FYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeSuisAParis @FollowTheLogic_ @kingofthistrill https://t.co/qnfz9Vuzpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great opportunity with @iSchoolUI for @HathiTrust research center development!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders I don't see how Bernie can win by beginning by making list of people who can't give us advice. Peopl… https://t.co/a3C3TyG7Rb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday me olde Mucker davidflintwood 💛 @ Harbour Island, Harbour Island, Bahamas https://t.co/NeFN4sgUmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Domingue on if his eyes light up when he gets an empty-net opportunity to score a goal: “Oh yeah, I cleaned the fro… https://t.co/4RFfLTCLQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[comedy at it's best. 25 Signs You Should Be A Fashion Blogger via @WhoWhatWear #laughter #snicker #smile #farcical https://t.co/nZP15QlOi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @AOC You a t like she is spending your personal money. Surprise! She isnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jillibean557 If the Senator from Hawaii is representative of their State then there is NO reason to ever go there!… https://t.co/i9nActXoix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RondaRousey I know you are leaving after Wrestlemania but please give both Charlotte and Becky some "stiff" shots… https://t.co/pcX7TMGbTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normally when I see his tweets I get angry but this one is just plain sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How well do you know your Disney? Come test your knowledge tonight at 5:30.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skinnypheel When you still vote manually abi? To get Nigerian embassy abi consulate to pick your call or reply you… https://t.co/tw4zCeki79]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1: I’ve accepted a challenge from @KatieNedved to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanation - just covers.… https://t.co/5t5Fjp7sFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The accuracy of this is unreal 😭 she’s just missing a bag of limon hot Cheetos and an Arizona!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayotiff @sapienist @HobbyistBrendan @marthajeanburns @MEPFuller Please stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah what was that crap @GOPLeader was saying about working for everyone? You might wanna tell @realDonaldTrump tha… https://t.co/145wkzJQlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the coalition of Americans who want anybody but Trump in power:  We need to be prepared for a reality where Trum… https://t.co/zJRGpsyrpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SNCLavalin #SNCLavalinGate  Separate from everything else, the question arises if there is another Cabinet Ministe… https://t.co/UjxCaCkT04]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will miss you Luke, the world will miss you. I just hope that your soul has found peace wherever it has gone to.… https://t.co/HGICoiK3ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EczemaItsFine @Marie30734307 @AOC And put people who need jobs out of work. Good plan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FULL VIDEO of @RedVersDude an I now available   Like Follow Retweet and Subscribe‼️👇🏾👇🏾👇🏾👇🏾👇🏾👇🏾👇🏾👇🏾👇🏾👇🏾👇🏾👇🏾👇🏾… https://t.co/OjurPJCgWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lights out shooting. His name is Orlando Spicer, I think. Watch the dribble step back at the end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hope4future3 😡🧞‍♀️😡the American people have lost confidence in Justice]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a sports and Hawkeye fan who is ignorant about this sport but love learn and watch it more why isn’t this stuff… https://t.co/QB98mRyNvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I’m scrolling my own feed and when she does her little finger thing my face emitted a prolonged and disgust… https://t.co/YmMt4Z7D3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He was your “fixer” for many years. He knows a lot and is going to tell it. Are you afraid ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you one better @Sean_Nerny. Goodfellas. Henry &amp; Karen were one for the books.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing Can Come Between Us by @SadeOfficial on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/xnqUU9zXAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@salimvalji Format the same, style very different! More docu-type features, more statistics, more knowledge all tog… https://t.co/KHkqnSsLI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@all_eyezonmi @BertJ4411 @r0xie_f0x @FREETOMMY8 @SwettmanF @Atheist_Dragon @Hybrid1979 @DeanoMartino1… https://t.co/cXw9n67035]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaielb I can only presume all trolling occurred via snail mail with hand written capital letters]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine Pleading Guilty Because You Can’t Afford to Call Your Lawyer https://t.co/CeqQV8YDls via @truthout]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dish_answers Why would the local Univision station be taken off?  I pay for ALL of my local stations?  Not fair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sights from our #austintexas travels @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/wnEOccNlXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnAngryChild @kingtisemedia I’m sorry that I simply want you to support your opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FactualLiberal @Merri__Magic @Barbara44461653 @juliet_benoit @realDonaldTrump His supporters are no longer ignoran… https://t.co/2hupqs1cO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a T2D I totally disagree with your suggestions. Forget lentils, apples and any sort of bread, carbs in any form… https://t.co/LkbjMDRdlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@superjazzzzz Tom’s got some live videos from practice but that’s about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch the Steelers not Trade Brown and then him just sit out for like two years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WinterChillOut #ForbiddenFrontier #CedarPoint I can hear power tools from Frontier Trail. I can’t see anything though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t miss this Podcast: The Power Of Sales Objections!    https://t.co/zOfU0UwIsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristyInCA Good luck Kristy, and enjoy that beer https://t.co/fNU1wpMEui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Yeah, just like you should be president too... hahahahaha hahahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFugelsang @SonjaMcDaniel94 That’s my favorite deplorable table-turn. It was OBAMA’s fault for worsening the ra… https://t.co/7fRz0vOhCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amir_Sarofiem @y_atonna @Bill82918747 @mark_ghergo Bill is an Orange Blooded Rockstar!! We are so lucky to have hi… https://t.co/5GFHwMVBAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you been missing your Man Made Soap?  Stock up every Tuesday afternoon from 4-7pm at the new East Bank Market… https://t.co/oufpxizJmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EnricoGARFF - 'Diana in Venice'  CURRENT AUCTION !! @FineArtAmerica (https://t.co/qpmaYNhJD3 … … @artpricedotcom)… https://t.co/ielggQw2TH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicki Minaj Cancels Show, Fans Start Chanting “Cardi B” https://t.co/dh8DjUlAt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids are characters let me tell ya. This 6 yr old just asked me to “keep track of his paper cut” and then ran away.… https://t.co/jfsNIk2LCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[1m fake accounts being shut down every day on facebook. The scale of the problem being debated at #SXSW2019 https://t.co/fnVEQovwcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steve_Dangle @Sportsnet @MrsDangle Hey Sportsnet make one with green bell peppers under the collar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizKellogg_ @JessicaNorthey @WordPress Electronic Press Kit! Lots of labels do that for new artists:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsIzzyMania I would still by izzymania wrestling merch from ya!! I also support this!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lalaamax @BlakeLastinger @kelliecoleman18 Woooooo! #WinnerWinnerChickenDinner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_SactoCA @shawnosterhus @bobbyMiniaci @YatPundit @ForecasterEnten Your slavish devotion to him is, er, admirable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching some nice late-day light while playing personal ski photographer. @ Bear Creek Mountain Resort https://t.co/yeUjD4ySW5]]></document></documents></author>