<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Come to #ANTEC19 and be part of the story! @4SPE_Plastics Look for real time streams from the show floor from… https://t.co/KMTkIVvSdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Phillies sign Harper—Dick Harper. 300 million shares of Globodyne stock and a new lawn. #bryceharperwatch https://t.co/kXShQsUyDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noodles &amp; Company is hiring in Denver, CO! Click the link in our bio to apply: Shift Manager #Veterans #SOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StonyBrookBASE LEGEND @Daniel_Zamora32 looks to be impact for @Mets by @AmazinAvenue https://t.co/FvjCJHer29]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cookie Monster donut for Cooke.  Amy’s Donuts brought in for our meeting. Thanks Gardner! 🍩 #donuts #meeting @ Amy'… https://t.co/hUxk1oBbYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC After watching Trump’s CPAC performance can we at least all agree that he; is either insane or; thinks he ha… https://t.co/BAgqkvzNRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HerringLiz @charliekirk11 Especially if He doesn't want you to have it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtracey Sinners can get things right, and Saints can get it woefully wrong.  Truth's independent of Character.  PS… https://t.co/kJcOYu8ibP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hump at good morning happy hump day it’s a cold one @paullyricjl love ❤️ u @ Jones Home https://t.co/bqvP4v3zSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gary Scheiner, MS, CDE, speaking now at @JDRFCapital #typeonenation summit #dc on tips for managing blood sugars du… https://t.co/1Wwc4tE2VS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bitch....Let's ApPeAl To BlAcK PeOpLe. They tried this trash with Hillary. I absolutely despise @KamalaHarris… https://t.co/WzCQaejAyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFBARTalert Dublin/Pleasanton was delayed for medical emergency at Fruitvale, why wasn’t this reported here?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was round 3, and the most insane concert I’ve ever been to. #ASTROWORLDTour https://t.co/6NDdUjJeAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joerb31 @iainbartholomew @Playlikeajet1 @Jetsbum2004 @JCaporoso @Smitty0066 Matt didn’t lose that game. He didn’t… https://t.co/CEcA4fq0Jf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heard_walker @ProjectCasting You have to have 2,5000 followers on IG which isn’t fair 😢 @SouthwestAir]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost count of the # of times I’ve been cut off by drivers while cycling/walking.   Most fail to signal, even when t… https://t.co/eff3J7wwOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a radar update at 4:43 a.m. Most valley locations have already picked up 0.10" of rain and more will fall as… https://t.co/2QPT6ord3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UStrucking @Unclegtruck If those cops forced them to get up there at side of highway, wonder who be libel if the d… https://t.co/wxsMz03WMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time with this one in NY has been spectacular.  Love you richjcv @ Gran Morsi https://t.co/GyoS2DKSXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legislation Introduced To Create Coin Honoring Former President George H.W. Bush, Barbara Bush… https://t.co/tkHOO8ETlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at NewYork-Presbyterian Maternity Ward - @nyphospital in New York, NY https://t.co/hpDpZHEvQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half of y’all judge other people relationships and don’t have one of yourselves.... how that work? lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adley doing Adley things; Go @BeaverBaseball!!! https://t.co/mmHBbfhNty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HorrorMovieBBQ @williambwest We just went through this all with Bray and JoJo. The story only trended for a few days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan You sick twisted evil dirtbag, where is your fake outrage over the Republican/ Trump Debt??? Hypocrites… https://t.co/NkSANgHLXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart just skipped a beat reading this. Get well soon, .indd file...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ff get the best burger this weekend @FandBeatery !! Arrr #stlfoodscene !!! 🍔🍟🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[QOTD: In order to understand what wins, you have to understand what loses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pugh with the drive and dish to Frazier for the 3-pointer. Roadrunners sharing the ball well here in the first half… https://t.co/FaBp9sMG8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RetireManifesto 😂 my wife is wondering if after I retire in a few months I will get up after 6:00 am. I’m quite a… https://t.co/EZo5szNPnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me tell ya... having an 8:30 teacher who has attendance as “optional” is the real MVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fightinabox @AdeptiCon Also it’s a fun game. Thanks for letting me play!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmanta25 @RealFacelessMan @PaulCounelis @Manruss @AOC Which Murdoch are you talking about? Because the two that ar… https://t.co/EsbryGsYtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amccallWDAY @LydiaBlumeWX @DisneyFrozen You both have great singing voices🎶🎵🎶🎵]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our greatest glory is not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall. Confucius * One of my favorite thin… https://t.co/kgTiD6ly9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNRIVALED #EarnhardtVsGordon is great!! Nicely done @JeffGordonWeb @DaleJr @MartySmithESPN @RayEvernham @LarryMac28… https://t.co/0jG2fOaTe1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kenneth Branagh made a Frankenstein movie with Robert De Niro and I’m just now hearing about it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[End 3Q: Commodore Perry 27, Tidioute 21. Alex Sabella with a couple big 3s off the bench to get the Bulldogs back in it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I notice that you’re not debating the sign’s premise: that you and other progressives cost NYC 25,000 jobs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Trump_Train I would take a counted ballot and scan it into a database.  That database would then be bumped up… https://t.co/An9TXI5mYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/202qhJ4oem ya check it out. Lmk ya opinions and what not. Thanks 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyWahlstrom To make hay with. We have pasture but put up hay for people with horses. It's about a 30ac piece tha… https://t.co/XLu27mdNyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattymalek @T_S_P_O_O_K_Y @AOC @BillNye Bill was an entertainer also. From his Almost Live days.   https://t.co/yhHz7FMsRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByMHarrington I remember talking about it in the schoolyard the morning we found out. We all walked to school, old… https://t.co/HMLecKovp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edgarwright I first heard this in a bar in Tournai, Belgium where I would hang out after school.  Amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakersNation This points out the differences of Lute and Magic as coaches.  Magic quit when things were not going… https://t.co/TCeByGAYT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gothedistance49 @jjrhetoric And Lamar Odom was in his prime and really awesome too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dry. Far left. - Drinking a Nitro Stout Pig by Arrowood Farms @ Arrowood Outpost  — https://t.co/TAfwaRvdqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonCarr__ @YoungCultureNY Let’s be real if we play any of these songs we’re gonna make them cooler now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DhruvKoul Hmmmm.....Kevin White with pick #8? League mvp with 50 tds or trade  up for Tribusky? Big misses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What you think , @ South Side, Louisville, Kentucky https://t.co/byFrPfGGZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care what you guys say but Jerry O’Connell was the best glow up of all time, from Vern to Jerry https://t.co/jEGWi6XmYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hers the narrative from Jussie: I perpetrated this lesson to educate the American people on the evils of President… https://t.co/jFwUZK4luL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Translation: Smollet knocked the Neonazi off the headlines so I’m satisfied.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little elms Dre Rose has been consistent in his role all year. Brings a Ben Wallace type toughness to the lobos as… https://t.co/JSD3hkuN65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ralph_prive @JuliaDavisNews @AshaRangappa_ I could not stand him as governor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice way to welcome daylight savings time I guess. #MontanaMoment #mikewilliamsphotography #missoula #gogriz… https://t.co/mN8JkB4VMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ευχαριστώ πολύ Παναγιώτη το ίδιο εύχομαι σ εσένα και στην οικογένεια σου]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit RINO in the same ink as McCain and Flake were. Vote these people out we are sick of do nothing losers in Congress!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited to witness the tremendous work of RCPS teachers and support staff. They are absolutely amazing! So dedicated and committed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come and see the incredible Lowlight ( live ) and Greenday ( on the gallery wall) at Transparent Gallery this after… https://t.co/w8XsQu3XPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnTargetFishing @WildernessPaulD @UltraAngler1 @Sheld_a @info_alen @LureTv @TeamBailes7 @bassfisher3k… https://t.co/xESsUeo67N]]></document><document><![CDATA[prefer the Nightman cometh .. perhaps Bryce stars in the next @alwayssunny stage performance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabyiscools @slwein @AJontheguitar @astros_dude I'm talking about Astros dude not the Nazi fucker. But thx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_najchalant What’s your idea &amp; I’m going to start a petition to stop u from working overnight buddy lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m also so loaded with decongestants for these flights today I am tweaking like a meth-head on Day 16 of the sinus… https://t.co/irP6wUVEUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamInTaunton @BOSsportsaddict @onetime72 @BajanRebel @m_anderson2015 Devin freaking bookers numbers are better tha… https://t.co/50JO1X93gl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LennyPotts3 @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump Why apologize? Apologize for just being cautious? For making sure the pre… https://t.co/6A88l2AHUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[La mujer de Pedro Sanchez tiene sueldo y es secreto de Estado. @FernanMartinez @LuchyB  #EnSocialismo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNCastaldo @RyanAFournier Oh my gosh, that's exactly what Trump is doing for us!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grrl_geek @GFritchey @vStudioCode Inside code, have you clicked the plus icon in your terminal dock? That should o… https://t.co/6i1vzoU4tR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwoodley05 @SanAntonioRodeo Good luck is the result of when preparation meets opportunity Best believe it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pierre McGuire with the “double secret probation” line from Animal House Lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristenATolbert And when I'm performing music to an audience, that's about the most I feel alive. Certainly, that energizes me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought a 59 cent Liptop Matzo Ball &amp; Soup Mix, was about to eat it, noticed it was produced the day… https://t.co/8FLdsQKOQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost rachelrohrich with get_repost.  My daughter rocks 👍🥇✅💕! ・・・ Performing with such amazing people in a beauti… https://t.co/I96voSlZoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgetPhetasy Are you you planning on getting vaccinated or something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[this was the same professor who claims to be nonpartisan.. only the finest at @BrockUniversity https://t.co/E3s5yYM1F2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbrauer Unless u are talking good hardwood furniture or china stuff in garage will not survive temp variations or mice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KerdellFlowers @pspismyname2 @ya_boi_helix @Mr_Weddig @FlareforThree @Under6ftNoBeard @goknickstape Lmao you tripping 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tahececlayborn @Ashtoncigar @fStogies I need warmer weather, would enjoy these much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza So true Mr. President, keep up the fight and get plenty of rest we need you at your best. I have neve… https://t.co/pguCfJMtyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXPLICATION.  Eternal purpose.—A design or intention, existing in the Divine Mind from eternity, or before the comm… https://t.co/jb7kFEhgMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roger Launius @NASA #Smithsonian spoke about Space Exploration and #Apollo history at U of MN. Awesome talk. https://t.co/D9VGNL4HEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLOW_GTO if the rockets see the warriors in the playoff you can bet that ass I’m on my way to Oakland for the whole series!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EyesEverywhere @Mark870freq @BernieSanders No, we just need to get back to the compromise of democratic capitalism… https://t.co/BiaA1xdMXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODAY!  @BigDaddyGraham has stated Bryce Harper will sign with the Philadelphia Phillies.   (15th consecutive announcement)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordynWho @khloekardashian You must have watched the wrong RTT cause she clearly said she knew where she was going… https://t.co/JUKst7MGKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmarkdownRadio Episode 14 "We're On The Passing Lane To FastLane" https://t.co/PX5dLpY9wc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaPerino @JesseBWatters @terryschappert @PlanetTyrus wow this is totally a @greggutfeld story... 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was an impressive display of offensive 🏀 Chargers had 8 👌🏻 in the first 9:30 minutes of the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police departments are using “reverse location search warrants” to force Google to hand over data on anyone near a… https://t.co/rAraFKV8Dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crookedmedia @SharonBrous @BulldogShadow @WStatesCenter 2/ The description of equating the broad terms “Hollywood”… https://t.co/HYbdzlIA1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[How @Uber minutes are calculated in the app? 3 mins real life = 1 #uber minute? #publictransport #nj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @JussieSmollett The FAKE racist, homophobic attack on @JussieSmollett is an affront to our humanity.… https://t.co/bOmqeoYz3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @KamVTV @RealJamesWoods @RedNationRising @BreitbartNews @johncardillo @JoeTalkShow @chicksonright An… https://t.co/zWyeOZh6Mo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MojoCaster @vurnt22 Don’t believe everything g you read on the internets. I trust over 40 years of Guitar Player m… https://t.co/XfkZumeSuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MapleLeafs players just happy to be wearing the pretty uniform.. think the world owes them something #soft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@softly_sighing2 Where’s your bunker located? 😂👍🏻 https://t.co/KgADzBXM7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[De acuerdo a las conversaciones, el abogado solicitó inicialmente cuatro millones de pesos para neutralizar una inv… https://t.co/unoarFLXfI]]></document></documents></author>