<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This was your big moment! Finally joining @SaucyDanielle in the circle of trust! And you blew it! I don’t know what… https://t.co/R2BnNIKs5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TriviaChicago Do you have some breaking new news about The Radler the rest of us don't know about? Last I heard th… https://t.co/UqjzuouRJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Born In The U.S.A. by @springsteen on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/saTmTLYPJt. I love this song, I am so proud to b… https://t.co/6K7RrtqCZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taino315 @Darkskintigga Regardless of separating to 4 species or races it’s just different terminology. Pedophilia… https://t.co/bUa6YlcN9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the fruit of the Spirit is love, joy, peace, forbearance, kindness, goodness, faithfulness, gentleness and self… https://t.co/VQkrR51s1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jon50376907 @Renevelation @ITDave2 @TrewSkye @ASJBaloch @IlhanMN Being "filled with the holy spirit" is a self del… https://t.co/lb1sTHL1RM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chasepwilliams It was never going to be a great deal for Steelers, AB is a HOF talent with a TO attitude, team nee… https://t.co/0ZM27Imh2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a completely nastyy guy don’t get me wrongguhh it’s just I’m not tryna be one of them scary infected sounding l… https://t.co/DmPcV4GLEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Thompson Building Materials https://t.co/wgXr7jBpRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now hopefully everyone stops hating on Roman Reigns . He’s always been a beast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yeah, and it delivered gallons and gallons of milk and chocolate milk and egg nog and ice cream to our front doo… https://t.co/NNpJ3Ho9v1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Powder by @Rhinegeist @ Whiskey Business — https://t.co/VQmmbD4WGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time to be sellers. It was an amazing run, but this season shows that it’s over and it’s time to rebuild for t… https://t.co/nO1qQb399S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayUseFullLane @RafaelMandelman Noted. Supervisor, your silence today in the wake of Tess Rothstein's tragic and p… https://t.co/eoOaNS2oTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful to learn with everyone in #SLC for the #QualtricsX4 #XM Summit this week. My initial queries: how are #K12… https://t.co/4msKANgIMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@31jwhite How is that a dig? They lost their best player, but they're not a one-player team. They're still good. That was my point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wlbeeton @puntanenyahoo @rln_nelson @EthonRaptor @ladyspat1 @SlowMoneyGreen @Stephen90045069 @puremoneylife… https://t.co/XGVWtAKFJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without capitalism the feudal system would likely remain in place, and we would have NO upward mobility.   @AOC is… https://t.co/UMPShl8Kms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for everything you have done for the Deacon Family Mr. Wellman 🎩 Forever grateful! @RonWellman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeOfABruin @bj_metta Bruh, Lakers were a big draw but he probably doesnt take that leap if no Magic. You're real… https://t.co/NAPkwBuZ7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep Going. Keep Doing You. All The Right Things Will Fall Into Place, Just The Way They Are Supposed Too. Keep Doi… https://t.co/qrn2KRBoOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made Honor Roll for first semester with a 3.83 GPA.  https://t.co/KVNsmYl32f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danmccay Sure did. Both gave our house a good shake for a few seconds. So far we’re good though! You?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solo mentiras y maldad eso es lo único que sale del régimen chavista de Nicolas maduro... solo eso mentiras y malda… https://t.co/NCrpU479d9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mom_norie Di ba hindi naman sila maniniwala sa ALDUB natin. Bakit tawid nang tawid pa rin sila?   #ALDUBxADNHappyAccident]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpontaneousMis1 @Ash_Kirksey @StephLDV And that’s what kids do anyway hahaha !?!?  Did you NEVER go against what y… https://t.co/QmLeSpKmjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LoosFromTheHip Feb 18, 2019 #PresidentsDay2019 do you know the oldest military honor of merit created by… https://t.co/dkC9luH2HW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein The good news Mister #frump is we'd be happy to fund the walls that are closing in on you ! ! !… https://t.co/32x5LfQiXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrwellNGoode I mean, to be fair so do humans. Trans men and women fulfill their respect gender identities pretty damn well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirstenPowers Good Night and Good Luck is useful. Especially the second disk. Shtrill or entertainment, even media… https://t.co/GZJpNegzFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael47309670 @CNBCSuperRich @belairdirect @CityofBevHills  I just love Chinese food. My favorite dish is number… https://t.co/4krN86xEFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EAFIFAMOBILE there appears to be a problem in H2H with a “connection error” that occurs only as the match is compl… https://t.co/mHCJWCej12]]></document><document><![CDATA[This video took me back to my childhood and it was only released 9 hours ago https://t.co/PwaRSBNxlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y aún hay “aficionados” que se pelean y son capaces de hacer daño a quién traiga la otra camiseta...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus, relieve the suffering of those with mental disorders, and support their families and caretakers. https://t.co/vdKqDWXGUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoMcCormick7 Your a rock star MO- long time fan  of yours - truly love ya- thanks for so many great memories https://t.co/aI0tLnD81N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Azure Stack IaaS – part 3 https://t.co/HK0ujamdee https://t.co/DuwHT4j2G9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couple bright flashes... power goes out to the buildings surrounding me. Wonder if I’m next... #STLwx #isitsleeticeorrain #idontknow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joe_nca @IgbogirlinNYC @mrjefflane @real_defender @realDonaldTrump Don't you have a cow farting protest to go to? https://t.co/1qpEwYVjg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithPlaysPC Keep up the great work man! You’ve been a benchmarking machine lately. :D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse @blueofthebay Kevin, why do you want the children of America to starve? Why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[People will overshare literally everything but when it comes to saying the truth suddenly it's too much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsmarymi @h3h3productions Even dismissing Jordy you would have to dismiss 4 other accusers and their detailed accounts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Issac11_fit @MelKiperESPN 198 on Wednesday and was 205+ all last fall https://t.co/E59cUa1iYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coaches, players, fans, and supporters... please donate to our fight against cancer! Every little bit helps!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog Glad you’re able to admit you’re an unprincipled, partisan hack!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried reporting it to @amazon, but apparently that's not something they make easy to do. @AmazonHelp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinimiGigi @sortezdmachamb9 @TMZ @TheShadeRoomm @PerezHilton Nikki MINAJ losing her fans and her silicone she need… https://t.co/un0YS6zckB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McElfresher i would bet a lot of money on the fact that darla was one of the shares]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your unfit for the office your a criminal justice needs to be done]]></document><document><![CDATA[4x4 predictor workout Newell - 48 Ndjebe - 50 Olofson - 51 Shaw - 52 Booker - 54 4x4 should be a great race this year.🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mhunt017 @jBSTEEL_ Thats what my first thought was, too. The draft picks Pittsburgh received are less than ideal,… https://t.co/8KNDAoIiDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just beat and platinum trophied @DragonQuest XI. 109 hours in and I didn't want it to end. One of my favorite JRPGs in recent memory.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Xbox is so lit, I paid a total of $2 for 2 and a half months of gamepass. #BringOnTheTombRaider #gamepass  #xboxone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebastianSB 5k per person is still pretty extreme, but this wouldnt be much of an issue if someone (coughGOVERNMEN… https://t.co/xrEn3O8RrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake up America ✝️ He’s all you need @Indian19751 @SticksMix @POSITIVEandUPL1 @SarahRachel16 @yeshua_porvida… https://t.co/kq1sBnqx5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wildethingy They hate everything. Except hate. Can't seem to get enough of that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle Laura, When I heard about the Jussie Skillet case, I knew it was a hoax. The last place you would fi… https://t.co/udoZxi8MDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sad to say I was right to question Smollett the actor from Empire. His attack in Chicago was staged. I question… https://t.co/fBHeeyAW0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aimes_sweethrt LOL I don't have a joke about normal or psychotic people, but there is a joke somewhere underthere...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tassyn is 100% Veronica from Better off Ted.  #AnthemGame https://t.co/UlfXKoUayb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NOLuv__ has the heart &amp; soul of a great entertainer. #atlanta #newyork #detroit #chicago #fashion #actress… https://t.co/SV3JG8Jlm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out your cost of ownership see how your car stands #avondaletoyota #toyota #trd #toyotanation #phoenix… https://t.co/leaMjL9ZZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aDrive_tK That would be sick. Just dm me if you need help with anything!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckleGear @AlexHonnold It’s like, you KNOW, he lives and you still white knuckle the chair throughout the movie!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizaenbloom @Yerbatero5781 @sydneyleroux @ORLPride @lulajackie1 @LuisSolerDT @la_abogada_ @DiegoArcos14 @aguschmer… https://t.co/8tJYBkGjP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brianne_Howey Can’t believe we are already up to the finale! I am so going to miss seeing Brianne and this incredi… https://t.co/H2nB7QlSrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayGee_1978 @feta04 Any hockey fan who thinks islanders fans are being pathetic just doesn’t understand hockey and… https://t.co/uC9jXBd2CU]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/aFwGtFBKh6 @INCIndia get your 🙌 out of #Kashmir @GreaterKashmir let it be. It's obvious the majority o… https://t.co/QkXhHbLb63]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bethenny @Dior You are not only a brilliant businesswoman but you are very simply stunning! #STUNNING]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are ever in Aliquippa PA, you should check out PA Pinball. They have all kinds of classic arcade games and p… https://t.co/kgHG3OWJba]]></document><document><![CDATA[“...I ...I wanna CUT a diglet up... and see what’s underneath...” @CarolineDirectr half asleep, terrifying me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhiattsteele @davidhogg111 @char4mtgs Amazing how a country with an economy the size of Texas controls everything… https://t.co/4pXnx5cQR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leoangelesmusic That’s right dawg !! Looking out for your new tracks keep em comin🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 6th Birthday to Abira. A girl I met at CDM Church who's family is good friends with my Sister mhernandezcibri… https://t.co/CIxdOOq8m1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giolito threw 68 pitches, 41 strikes. Longest outing by a White Sox starter in 2019 Cactus League action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conservativma @TpartyAnita @HarrellRyan1 What is their infatuation with the old McDonalds characters?  He has her… https://t.co/3R2LI1uRSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @iam_twalk and the 2017 squad for getting our renaissance started.   The new standard of success if de… https://t.co/F2tkWR20jy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something I learned during my talk tonight: it’s important to be honest and vulnerable about your experience interv… https://t.co/ZR4RZsOIfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lonzo, open up that vino 15 minutes before halftime so it can breath -Lebron "Yes sir, will that be all?" -Lonzo @TylerIAm @MickstapeShow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetenthkabir @TilmanEhrbeck @ArjunaCosta @EmmalynShaw @FlourishVC This is awesome! Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump When will he invite the families of people killed by everyday white guys with access to guns?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan Adams cover of TSwift’s 1989 album seems really really creepy now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkHertling @eliehonig The thing is, if the judge is going to weigh in on Manafort's sentencing with something ab… https://t.co/ZC9AnNb06P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great leg day today, took inspiration from Ryan Terry’s Instagram post and did a variation of that workout… https://t.co/GXiewHOHie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hrtablaze At end of clip did he actually say the motive is a mystery? Lol. And cnn denies being fake news. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“James Comey, Andrew McCabe, James Clapper, John Brennan, Peter Strzok, Lisa Page and all of these conspirators att… https://t.co/HqMOGW8aJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlemay74 @Potsy_70 @JoeWhalen19 @Trege33 I disagree, I have not seen enough of him at C to say he’s a top 6 C. If… https://t.co/iFlmndnCOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Edita_NYC should just #LearnToCode instead of pushing Draft Equines into the brink of Extinction because #Condos… https://t.co/7bVhNZKw1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Filipenses 2:3 No hagan nada por egoísmo o vanidad; más bien, con humildad consideren a los demás como superiores a ustedes mismos  NVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate a “I hate a ‘I don’t like spicy food’ ass person.” Shut the fuck up coo we get it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting piece. Reminds me of some folks JSOC’s drone campaign has killed in Kunar/Nuristan seemingly mostly bec… https://t.co/xnchBVXbR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[eigenvalues of the natural symmetric bilinear form on the middle cohomology. Etc. Now all of these must vanish if t… https://t.co/rXmvpiCdEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The universe really be out here speaking to me...and my dumbass keeps ignoring her. I’m sorry sis 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EuroTone Most of them got to spend most of their careers with HOF coaches too. Sloane, popavich,Jackson,riley,aurbach etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torontomike Such a challenge to potty train little ones. I'm struggling with my two youngest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/eDLaHPZcSb @buholocoz93 está #zalsa no se oye en la @Z93PR  @caciquez @Chris_Montz @SalsaTrending… https://t.co/q2jqdeBuo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video shows Alabama high school students using n-word, anti-Semitic slurs https://t.co/BTBnuYcuY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjfree, your right❗️he’s a 🐷 sadly he’s what @realDonaldTrump voters want 👎👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucci gonna end up putting a baby in Nae bruh he love Her to much that it’s scary]]></document></documents></author>