<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mitchlafon @Cherie_O Sammy doesn't need the headaches (love Eddie to the moon and back, but seriously, I'd move to… https://t.co/hRgN2uVc6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarikaSboros @me_blud @garytaubes Gary Taubes is many things. But a scientist is not one of them. Dogmatist, zealo… https://t.co/LlssqJ1Z2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flying back from Tokyo last night and just landed in Seattle and I just have to say, I had the best views the whole flight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carnestm @fccincinnati @FloFC_ I don't recall talking about this. There hasn't been a council meeting since December]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Lakeshore Fog by @stbcbeer at @harborctr — https://t.co/uqCJUeB86j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonaldKlain I think that’s right, and also think Trump will twist things regardless. But I still wish Dems would h… https://t.co/COSUehz3SF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Garth Brooks. And yes, because his timeless, catchy music will distract anyone so we can escape.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew! One ! https://t.co/y7l8Op8A1E 💚☯️☮️🤬 https://t.co/7hWhmsjF5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are zero things surprising about this result. https://t.co/0RVYC7igYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg @mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 You should file the complaint and forward the tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Always Sunny In Feltonville in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/Km4DpXYr1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[A pimped-up ride suited for our Premier, Doug Ford. Hope it has a fridge for his buck-a-beer! #ONPoli #ontario… https://t.co/yMSTgv2Vxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Business is booming, and we are nearing our busiest season.  We are looking to add several people to our staff, esp… https://t.co/OWbLXd7fI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darriel5 @finebaum @stephenasmith @JohnHayes730 @DannyBrams Paul are you still defending dabo the coach for Clemso… https://t.co/RHbFn52f5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st place match — 113 #8 Kole Biscoe, SCA (NE-3, 46-6, Fr.) #3 Jackson Arrington, Forest Hills (SW-2, 40-4, Fr.)  B… https://t.co/GVlzLq8mBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I eat hot Cheetos I add melted cheese to them and my friend makes fun of me calling it ebt food. 😭😭💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al rey de gloria la tierra se une en alta voz Santo, santo es nuestro Dios Hacia a tu trono alzamos nuestra adoraci… https://t.co/3gFk5jJPU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/F7kTHYCrAu Our Internet Explorer Help phone number is 1-855-479-3999 (toll-free)… https://t.co/nEE1pEfHp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelley_AK I gotta try Chick-fil-A next time I'm in 'muhrca. @MarioLopezExtra put it at his #1 P4P fast food last week on 3 Knockdown Rule.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarrieJrSharks @natspooner5 Fave female player with my fave female junior team I LOVE IT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 of my most favorite people in the world @DezBryant and @OfficerNorman both follow me back live you 2 guys you make America better salute]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sure hope the @PGAEuroProTour does in this week's tournament in Oman what @PGATOUR did @genesisopen by restarting… https://t.co/hjnMSUTtFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickSutton @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Comedian? I wasn’t laughing when]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawilc01 I'll just be glad when the day comes where these rideshare and delivery workers have to be classified as… https://t.co/GOGxgejze5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un equipo con tanta calidad no puede depender su juego de un solo jugador, que diferencia es cuando no juega Gignac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@20002ist @DDOTDC Change starts at the top, and clearly the Mayor isn't listening...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DoTheRightThingESPN #McAfeeForMNF @PatMcAfeeShow looks like the McAfee mafia coming out strong. Start selling some… https://t.co/0dGAa8HLde]]></document><document><![CDATA[No exactly what you mean they tried to do it to us ! During the Obama Clinton Kabal and now we have the NJ Murphy K… https://t.co/4MjbEQOgyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to chuckle. Baby Beer Bottles! and 9 other games to play at your co-ed baby shower | Offbeat... https://t.co/wJwMghscyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I come across a poll that I vote on I will RT your poll to help you get more votes]]></document><document><![CDATA[George Tan completed the Austin Half Marathon! Time 01:37:42 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/tg6K0pC897 #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if other FAs see the Exodus out of Baltimore (even if they are good moves overall) and think they don't wa… https://t.co/PHEOENNrSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[me on the verge of tears in Sylvia’s room is just my eternal state of being at this point in my existence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amead93 @SteveStuWill If entertainment with real or simulated violence decreases bloodshed outside of arena or pla… https://t.co/MdwoiN5EMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all think eating pussy and eating ass is the same thing? I’m tryna prove a point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexEmmanuel72 No se trata de eso Señor, qué fácil es decir “adopta y ya”, es un asunto de raíz, en cuanto a la co… https://t.co/eF6ts4PbYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeffmapes @AOC Do you think she would be less recognizable, less of a target on a bike? I think it fear that keeps… https://t.co/8EfLSSjSkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petrogustavo Se combate con plomo... el que le faltó al gobierno darle cuando se dedicaba a ese negocio “señor” #aliasAureliano .....]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York Jets proper 2019 offseason blueprint excludes Le&amp;#8217;Veon Bell (ESNY Video) https://t.co/0pQauAaeuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan Three blonde rats. Three blonde rats. See how they lie.  See how they lie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to say that over the last few days from being back home from Disneyland, I've had a lot of time to think. Fi… https://t.co/x3xDVJGieJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicatlanta @JuddmonteFarms Estoy súper enamorado de ese Caballo, esperemos demuestre que no solo fue un destello de Calidad]]></document><document><![CDATA[But for real.... @manilaluzon was just ROBBED! But if I had to pick, Trinity totally deserved it as well! Shoulda b… https://t.co/L1UkRbGSlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work at lowes and today i broke a sink that was on display lmao everybody looked at me and i said everything has… https://t.co/QHwSbHekLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTrueVanguard I don’t think they think Trials would be worth it for their time and effort. What I worry about ev… https://t.co/eAAl07tD8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desvergonzados hijos de la chingada con su, con su ambición y su corrupción, nos han llevado hasta este punto. Ya c… https://t.co/eW30xZuPwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjewing2 @philafelines @mor100 @Mybabykitties @nesjloch @3coolkatz @RhondaHendee @catgirl321 @ersle @Barbi_Twins… https://t.co/WUsfRMjoNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can i work a 9 and 8 hour shift within 27 hours without sleep? Stay tuned and you might find out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to Panera earlier today. Got a sandwich full one not just half, a small cup of bacon Mac two drinks. It came out to 22 bucks 🤣 crazyyyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UfoJoe11 @SpacedOutRadio @OmniTalkRadio Luis will be on with @alejandrotrojas  next week correct?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you bought a book at the book fair you weren't enjoying your childhood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@49ersCamelot @BHolmesNL @BayVegas @GeneralSiKWiDiT @MaioccoNBCS Knocks would be that he only played edge for one y… https://t.co/jozJuyoc6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffclarenz @ingress The athletic skill of rounding that corner... And not dropping their phones or ext batteries.… https://t.co/7KYV2b2Dmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbycblanchard Pennywise showed up, pyrokinesis / telekinesis were table-rollable traits, druids could be gunslin… https://t.co/DNqVqxP3px]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is gonna take #significant new #volume to turn this market around... #bitcoin #price #volume #analysis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another productive and safe Sunday out there 🙏🏻. Looking forward for a new week . . 👊🏻 Set your goals... Train smar… https://t.co/TTSInB5lbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ouch. My wife would probably divorce me I did this. LOL I would never do this. I love my PS4 but let's be for real… https://t.co/ylAOIo1Czi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Folks really repeat that Brie Larson is wooden/uncharismatic/bad and I just... can't. Dislike #CaptainMarvel all yo… https://t.co/CWlOCXdvV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boeing @BoeingAirplanes @MailOnline Had Boeing Grounded 737 Super Max 8 as I Recommend in a Tweet after 1st Crash… https://t.co/774ZqBqq9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you saw any snippet of the gayle King/ r kelly interview, you saw it all basically. The @cbs special is trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump U got nerve calling anything or anyone dishonest! Yur a POS baldface liar(Over 8700 lies) that thi… https://t.co/WRpHS1IvjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol Scary Jerry doesn’t have the top clearance, even Trump denied that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjb4276 You want your toilet smelling fresh fleisch potpourri ?????  🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/ThlQHYflnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to all the Kanines &amp; Kitties out there 🐶❤️🐕❤️ 🐈 #ValentineDay #HappyValentinesDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hSXbltZ1LG @CarBombBoom13 I often think of this study when I read your tweets. It's amazing how many a… https://t.co/kzSPjzJuOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got 1 Free Spin on Spin &amp; Win in 8 Ball Pool! https://t.co/2gRs2va22N]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I was the New Orleans Pelicans i would sue Klutch Sports for collusion in the NBA and make Adam Silver deal with… https://t.co/sU5BdNpFGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So turns out the postal service lost and then found @broskivafli 's holiday card to me and it finally got here desp… https://t.co/9Rm0ipp7ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @carolynnphw with get_repost ・・・ “Distance cannot matter - ours is a friendship of the heart.” - Mary Anne… https://t.co/vda4ezQes6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andrew Vickers leads a 2 unit charge. 6pt run by himself, 66-63 @WhitmanMBB takes the lead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liked it more from the bottle. More barrel character, still slight bodied, yet less cloyingly sweet than regular DS… https://t.co/dtxiPJ2Kw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nine Inch Nails - The Fragile for me.  Massive Attack - Mezzanine or M83 - Junk would be close.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever gun girl   You bring a whole new meaning to the term party pooper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antiqueboy Why are we giving people like him airtime ? It’s gross. Dude belongs in prison for the rest of his days… https://t.co/it8AqLLasM]]></document><document><![CDATA['We want to manage and maintain it in a rustic, natural way': First public meeting on Turkey Mountain master plan s… https://t.co/bf5LbqzXIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are looking for a buyer on 9725 Third Avenue #StoneHarbor #NJ  #realestate https://t.co/xEdqG8hJ0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kongo vs Minakov just went from: this is pretty decent, to: this sucks, in one round. #Bellator216]]></document><document><![CDATA[The server at this kreation cafe is SO over dogs.  I’ve never seen anyone look at a pup with that much disdain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReginaA1981 @mmurraypolitics @HotlineJosh The funny thing is, the economy was so bad in 2008, that that is not tru… https://t.co/QfvspEomE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrichardShow please do a show about @bullnakanokeiko https://t.co/Purz9pip0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually, Charles, it ended only when congress refused ti pass legislation authorizing a larger Court! But imagine… https://t.co/WFgLfxzz9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@berryluis11 @MaryWar45276492 @aj0314 @MickieJames @WWEAsuka Mickie doesn't need it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start to see the real, tangible value you and your skills bring. This might not be immediately obvious at first gla… https://t.co/WQowgwR9Q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you make bad choices and deep down you know you should still do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scott_lowe @davidmedberry That’s an increasingly transformation. It looks great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IJustLearnedThat @SashaBanksWWE is the hottest thing, coming out of cold Boston. https://t.co/Ymvz29ILYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedsCowboy Welcome home Cowboy.  Great job with your interview today.  Hail State and Go Reds!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have been to ShortE’s yet in Johnston tonight is the night. Serving smoked beef ribs that are great. #texassmokethebest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of the Republicans war on women Vote American Vote Democratic Voting or not voting has consequences for ordina… https://t.co/p5J1H2i7BA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The friends I’ve made in this Conservatory here at Kean is crazy. I love each and every one of you guys and you kno… https://t.co/3FflC6cvS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find out using our trade appraisal tool!  GO: 👉https://t.co/BiVKvux2N4  #DealerForThePeople 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸 https://t.co/0bDMH4aOzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DouglieDoWrong aye did you hear the news that Antonio browns would want to play for dolphins]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who don’t know how to mute their phones on a conference call, webex, etc. should be banished fro society. It… https://t.co/xvCfsW6plc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pernetti leads Ramapo with 10 points. Hunt has 9 points. Whooley has 3. Quinn has 2 points #NJhoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Tik Tok,       I don’t want to download your app. I don’t want to make short videos to share with everyone. I d… https://t.co/c5pGgHZr14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Potluck, bowling, and almost dying makes for a great night @ Donelson Bowl https://t.co/MNIwcxCiAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Jussie Smollett did was wrong and dispicable. No debating that fact. But to hold media responsible is silly. T… https://t.co/XRT4N7ySL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OFemmeFataleZ Red Sox? Do you go to the casino 🎰 and root for the house? 😂😂😂😆😆😆 (Yankee joke)]]></document><document><![CDATA[My homegirl said Jussie Smollett situation reminds her of when Fanny lied about being raped by two black men on Rosewood lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jochysantos #vainamia nadie puede subirse a mi cama y mucho menos con ropa que trae de la calle! Tampoco pueden en… https://t.co/AzuIqMcVEc]]></document></documents></author>