<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DerronEShort I always tell people, when they say I feel so sorry for you, my response is always “God didn’t give m… https://t.co/EF5vE5r1ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been on meleah couch for 2 hrs watchin Bernie Mac and I can’t get up lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE KNOCKOUTS - ''DARLING LORRAINE''  (1959) https://t.co/ZhtsrOPo62 via @YouTube Written by my beautiful and talen… https://t.co/2n6Iuhq3m0]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 23, 2019: Pro-life activists plan ‘Day of Mourning,’ call for repentance after ‘revolting’ NY abortion law https://t.co/3PfJLMEkFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rollbarann @jax_persists Hahaha I’m glad someone has taken my tweet in jest :) I love ur yardsign face and I would… https://t.co/wPGnKZF9R7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrtrStat @EssayJack @eisaiah_e Agreed! The more the merrier! Glad to connect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting with Kayla Ancrum, author and really cool person. Buy her books!!!! https://t.co/nKMQEtdCIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t ever be too good (or to fragile) to get your hands dirty. You’ll never get to the top if you don’t start at t… https://t.co/AZWMnbIljJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwing it back to last year when I got to live my #DemiLovato dreams at #BroadwaylovesDemiLovato! https://t.co/xqKAiUHm1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[going into hibernation phone off mind on ill be gone for sometime brb 🕳]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I see Jason Momoa in a pink velvet suit I think about how much Beau Brummell would hate it and then I laugh and laugh and laugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your friends plan play dates around your schedule with your son 🙌🏽 #besties]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ferengi rules of acquisition are an ideal guide to entrepreneurs today. Keep reading to find out how!  Contact… https://t.co/pRSa9o1IJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SoftBank fund invests $940 million in #SiliconValley startup's self-driving delivery vehicles | The Japan Times https://t.co/ZTpXnfUXMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyLond3 @TyMurphy19 @Rhondita44 @LegionBobo @tribelaw @TrisResists @tsoamerica @tuszyb @tweetmommybop @unbrokeMs1… https://t.co/v17xjW3Sj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This but you would be prepared only to hear the kid in front of you reading your part and you panicked and sounded… https://t.co/qaYO3uI4Qv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @realDonaldTrump @GOP Why this is not about Nancy. It's about the lying worthless trump in offc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost showtime at @NorthviewMS - you have two more chances to see this great show on Saturday!! Love @msdwt suppor… https://t.co/StLszWdGRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamChadAndAbby @happygojackie Yeah...it was a little odd to say the least 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sickomode is the raps equivalent to #queen #BohemianRhapsody will go down In history a classic @trvisXX https://t.co/F0JXPXLyLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[As usual, late post and I've been preoccupied with life that I haven't had a chance to upload these two pictures fr… https://t.co/gsWMlGfRDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤢🤢🤢🤢 that’s why ion gas horrres most Of them gotta do this to keep up their lifestyle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jprast1 @iamwonyae @tonibraxton "literally had only one hit"…REALLY? #STAYwoke https://t.co/f1P1G2WA3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Один только Вестерн приносит в бюджет города полтора миллиарда долларов ежегодно. Родом из Лондона Онтарио Diply, B… https://t.co/OVdw3Qu4Hi]]></document><document><![CDATA[damn I really wasted 15 hours of my life watching this Chinese drama with literally the crappiest ending I’ve ever seen in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JokerRoyal I shall make you an honorary DCP roomie of mine to fill ur void]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, what does it mean when your boyfriend keeps having dreams where you're bald??? Asking for a friend-]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule @lovetogive2 @DonaldJTrumpJr @SarahPalinUSA WOW WOW WOW transportation secretary?????? 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think about my future a little bit much.. I need to enjoy what I have now as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kennethtobey on #oldhollywood #entertainmentnewsnettv #oldmovies @ Hertford, North Carolina https://t.co/SguTrVUoiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[não acredito que fui obrigada a ler uma MERDA dessas a essa hora. realmente é só o cara ter um rostinho bonito que… https://t.co/miF0RtvJK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My personal favorite Valentine's day box today. Because obvi 🦄 #ilovevickery  #ValentinesDay https://t.co/ZNz5RXM9uH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GrayWolfNation we need you tonight!  No. 2-ranked @LourdesVolley and No. 6-ranked @AQVolleyball are primed for a s… https://t.co/XKkYqM7d2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikewickett Love your tweets Mike! So kn point. Congrats again on the new addition to your family!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I turn the corner and what do I see? Beautiful cherry blossoms right in front of me. #washingtondc #sakura… https://t.co/XGROvCqKNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone going tamu or blinn-bryan needs a roommate at an apartment complex dm me :)) #tamu23 #blinn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuzLuzgromero Sort of reminds of that swimmer in Brazil but even dumber. I dont know why he'd think he'd get away with it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agent_merry @LevineJonathan @AOC I thought she was chewing/eating something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly living for @derekhough’s reactions on @NBCWorldofDance this season. https://t.co/fifKkGGLZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodShepherd316 Thank you for protecting your heart and your marriage. God bless you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see the beauty, what do you see?  . .  It’s taken me a year to try and unlearn the fatphobia behaviour I was taug… https://t.co/qmh3A68kfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤙REPOST . . . #reposting #repost #again #reminder #checkmeout #publicfigure #shoppingaddict #sexymodelsgirls… https://t.co/auPUFW1Lvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for some fucking music. Fuck this shit today  https://t.co/WrKilL2B6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Girl’s Day!  Hinamatsuri . . Image by: JapanLoverMe @ Da Kash Crib https://t.co/mzor2RNqRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelheldevans @theboyonthebike Looking forward to hearing the podcast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posting this sweet review from Tatiana here because the review site put it in their “Reviews we don’t recommend” or… https://t.co/jf3uNca8Ci]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lights are on and early voting on whether to add a penny to the sales tax and expand MARTA in Gwinnett County,… https://t.co/qa8moBOboi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just signed up to be an eegee's Taste Bud. You should too. Click here. https://t.co/JyRo0P3LHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being an analytical and introspective person can prove to be a blessing however I can foresee it being my own Achilles heel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahRemini Ive keep everything back from my 25 year old till now 7 year old..thst is so special...You have a good kiddo&lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hamul2020 @YossiGestetner @TheLeadCNN @jaketapper @LouisFarrakhan @GOPLeader @Ilhan @RJC @thealexvanness… https://t.co/RAGgtLgoIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @seanhannity @FoxNews @LindseyGrahamSC Putin’s wind up doll going on FAKE PROPAGANDA @FoxNews what… https://t.co/32oPmGVmBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just crappy weather outside.  Warm and cozy inside... ☔️🔥😊 https://t.co/zMpn2LnoeP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Night call thoughts: For people leaving against medical advice— “Please do not hesitate to come back if you’re feel… https://t.co/HG6VSUD7vG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 @FLOTUS There's no way I can describe her in the limited characters of Twitter. But gold digging bitch is a good start.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picture says it all! Enjoy this gorgeous sunny day #Dufferin #Caledon #buylocal https://t.co/mP6CXKCn6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanAndShay ‘s music goes on to inspire young kids to use their voice and add their own twist to spice it up and ex… https://t.co/0hSz1cFlUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️I don’t feel athletes “need” to be advocates but I think athletes have a platform to “do good”-if that is what th… https://t.co/9Y9nbpL75w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi. I was supposed to be leaving for work 10 minutes ago but I can’t stop throwing up. Love that for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My twitter feed was a bit shocking yesterday. Between the increadible Pink Shirt Day tweets, and then breaking news… https://t.co/7BS3E0EidK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keselowski @jeff_gluck @PaigeKeselowski @PaigeKeselowski @keselowski.  I made pork chops tonight too.  #goingfor2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how my freezer lights up the box of ice cream sammiches, allowing them to shine with such beauty and grace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsheSchow @RonColeman There's been 31 since the act was signed into law. President Obama activated  13, more than 1/3 of the total.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Glen Park BART Station in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/y2RqYSCwnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a baby throw up on me all day and then we cuddled till she went to bed. So yes she loves me   Happy valentines my sweet sick girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DICEY63 @FoxNewsSunday @MSNBC Fox  news is the compulsive liar new outlet]]></document><document><![CDATA[“nothing clever, nothing conceived, nothing contrived, can get the better of GOD. do your best, prepare for the wor… https://t.co/QBXz3Ynx9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que haces? Va conmigo a 2019 Quince Expo! Estamos aqui a 3 hoy! What are you doing? Come see us at the 2019 Quince… https://t.co/OUkeUL7htO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trishgarman Thanks Trish.  I want to take as any pics as I can to treasure.  ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dirrymoir Make sure you eat! If you don’t it’ll make you feel even worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Petersburg will miss all the @IndyCar teams. I will especially miss @simonpagenaud &amp; Norman's adventures. 😢 🐕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuscleCell @pushkinforhouse @kazweida @WVGOP It has nothing to do with her religion. It has everything to do with… https://t.co/CUsDZeJd5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at @NHLCanes  @Capitals @BlueJacketsNHL @NYIslanders @penguins.. it will come down to game 82.. for Metro. #TakeWarning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thaaaankkssssss! I think this is going to be my new hobby when my ligations fail 😅🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a feeling Twitter is going to be blowing up come next Monday #SaveShadowhunters #Shadowhunters]]></document><document><![CDATA[Odd how conservatives want the constitution read with exacting literal definition regarding 2nd adm but support Tru… https://t.co/3MtXErWZTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @Heisi12989491 Everytime she opens her mouth the more dumber she sounds! OMG why was she elected]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uhhh @kyleejo22 just called me to see if we could make bracelets tomorrow... Can someone please drive to El Reno to check on her?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mklee_andhearts @_valereta Omg look at all those boys living in 305... so sad 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#promdresses gowns #downtownsaintcloudfl #saintcloudfl #osceolacounty @ Ellas What Not Shop https://t.co/0RB9rUFSuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brett_CBC What a lovely family.  You have my condolences.   I hope the father gets well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer #Trump #FY2020 proposed budget heading to Congress from calls for 23% slashing at #StateDept. I agree w… https://t.co/Di9C4UZmAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 1300 NW Mitchell Rd #Cullman #AL  #realestate https://t.co/JI3dkjHpNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gullwulf I’m not using the cloud version. I wonder if there’s a way around that. There’s gotta be a way to save locally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan and I in FL: cheap, stay in, smoke everyday  Ryan and I in NY: spends at least $80 a day, go out 5 days a week… https://t.co/h36rXjMHCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior I believe it’s hell instead of purgatory. Trump is Satan and all those cult members are his little demons]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game Day 🏀💜  Excited to share soon on the blog about our behind the scenes tour of the amazing @golden1center! . .… https://t.co/MdU0eXLeAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of asking you if you're still watching, Netflix should ask Bojack viewers if they're still running away fro… https://t.co/I89tOV5N4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sweet lil nugget was talking about going to a concert all weekend only to fall asleep after two songs (we're t… https://t.co/J3dvd0e8uo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comcastcares 3 hours and repeating myself to point of compounding #laryngitis no help re #CustomerExperience of fe… https://t.co/f3mLweS60a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyWS You are killing me with these tweets! What is so wrong with 105 degrees + 40% humidity?? *makes mental not… https://t.co/hybW4IIqo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disfrutando de una tarde de café con mi compadre Ricky Treviño... Café CU-CU tradición en la ciudad. https://t.co/icCqD5p0zR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's WEDDING DAY!!!!! ❤️😭❤️ @elisapizzaqueen @jesse_ortegon #ForeverJessesGirl https://t.co/Y1qVH6eQTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up from a strange ass dream. I was at a casino with @Sethrogen and he morphed into @blakeshelton. Then he st… https://t.co/xkgBk2A3sz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plaidamdriver if i give you my directv log in i think you can watch what’s saved in my DVR. LETS TRY. i have # 1-7… https://t.co/KiZj360Lx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson Yikes! So, a radio piece I did in the late 80's,  where I said something "suggestive" about a pop-st… https://t.co/x3NCV4MUuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdcblifn @MaskedSingerFOX Right no way @donnyosmond should have beat @MsGladysKnight]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t ate anything since Saturday at 10am thanks to Shawn. I think I will just die now]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m taking a trip with @DariusJones1995 next year!!! This man don’t mind shooting out. He stay on GO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSeanMaloney Just when I thought I couldn't love you any more....please be my Representative!!?]]></document></documents></author>