<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@thegoodgodabove @TrishaW04 Apparently to the Bible thumpers and Republicans it does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Verse/day. Psalm 100:1,5. Make a joyful shout to the Lord all you people! For the Lord is good;  His mercy is everl… https://t.co/Tq6WKgLtnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Mariabermudez_ @IlhanMN Thanks for that, but any desire to explain why you love this nut job?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Saycheese_Media @mo3badazz Lo profile =longevity in and prepares you for the aftermath if you don't  od on the hustle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan The thing that gets me about Pence is that he’s always so ‘pious and self righteous’. He actually belie… https://t.co/o7Aq5BDsm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@link_Tin Can't believe such a great game hasn't received a reboot yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA['Free pass for mobs': India urged to stem vigilante violence against minorities  Complicity by local officials and… https://t.co/mTa5pKX4Bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@syd_dixon I want to get to Harpers Ferry Brewing   Want to see that view]]></document><document><![CDATA[AO-91 1724z 10° pass from DM12. I heard myself get through a couple of times, but couldn't complete any QSO. Too ma… https://t.co/zNs7uhAIRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Gym you and the rest of the Republicans are the biggest swamp monsters there are thanks to Trump you ha… https://t.co/A55nCNijM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[You summed it up perfectly! Question: What does that say about the folks that vote for these miscreants?]]></document><document><![CDATA[BS Trump. We r not fooled by your dementia and other mental illness. Resign now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oglal5 @whitesox @ChuckGarfien @NBCSChicago @Danielbpalka @ManofSteal_15 Hopefully Eloy someday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@staticssound is always finding ways to help people while furthering his vision of positivity at the same time! He’… https://t.co/Vy9xAmw69R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias por la oportunidad de perseguir mis sueños que @UIS me dió, hoy me alegro que mi querida Universidad siga creciendo @e3t_uis #UIS71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Truth2Come This woman own the sex trafficking massage parlors.and the trump white house seem to be friends with he… https://t.co/YyNo1IMKXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course! When the law is closing in blame your stupid shit on drugs or alcohol. Put this POS in jail and lose the… https://t.co/FacfPhfFKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow (Wednesday February 27th) is pink shirt day. A day to wear your pink loud and proud to show that you will… https://t.co/7EF0S8Hzm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[As an editor, you'd think @KarenAttiah would know what a retraction looks like...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaridadSan But with San Diego weather, has there ever really been an opportunity to them to be in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neilhimself I think I've said it, but "I haven't" feels more natural. Born raised in SoCal, have also lived in Col… https://t.co/HGQMqOPq93]]></document><document><![CDATA[#reparations lets go there. Let's all acknowledge Christ as Lord of All. Stop the theological incompetency. https://t.co/YSWCtmxxgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[New episode you guys! Let’s talk X-wings, Tie Fighters, Episode IX, a possible third tv series for Disney+!? So muc… https://t.co/Ejdvfmnjfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations new residents for matching!  I look for to working with you at the @HeartInstitute  !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMT_Sarah @Chelsea_Purgahn Chelsea really deserves all the credit there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics @ABC Sure let her fly back, arrest her at port of entry, and try her for treason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeekVibesNation @reielys1280 Leia as a kid because I used to be a Star Wars fan; but as an adult, on this list any… https://t.co/FHZctUMWZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JoeB @thatotherguy41 @TimW_GT Same plus Brian Noonan. And Brad Shaw, but only because he was a coach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angieforshort_ Let's make it happen! I would love the opportunity to assist you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skittlesweirdo @Samamohsen20 اللهم ارحمها واغفر لها واجعل قبرها روضه من رياض الجنه]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FranklinRec and DPW will be running Earth Day 2019 again on April 27, 2019 from 9:00am-12:00pm at Beaver Pond.  Co… https://t.co/HHu1fVdvDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitePrivIsReal @Mediaite What’s her point if not to divide the Democratic Party? Obama’s not running for anything… https://t.co/jwAjqZ8tqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING EVERYONE!!!! Last day before this week vacation #TeamDOE Today is a good day to have a good day!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another opportunity to seal his fate. @jaredkushner is a criminal who will see more jail time than his father.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they ask to make a gourmet meal suitable for a baby...sure!   #babyfood #gourmet #plating #dinner #baby #puree… https://t.co/jc8nMQP6RA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevDrBarber Rev. Barber—don’t you know-people of color are forbidden to have, or speak, an opinion.  So, Spike Lee… https://t.co/HUbKa7r0y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyWGR Might not have to do with the weather, but the city as a whole unfortunately. Also probably why BUF was… https://t.co/VBOrG9WD2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its sad day when a President or any other leader of the free world has sign an order to allow free speech on colleg… https://t.co/saujFdGPGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattHarmon_BYB I am panic stricken; he is the foundation to my keeper league, 2 championships in the past 4 years 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BakerAndTymo @PalatMyJohnson @EASPORTSNHL Probably still crying like that. That’s a rough shot total for no score]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burnku Lightning and it’s not close, but the Blues’ line is still respectable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnehill @LoveAlwaysIris @DelSchilling You think you’re gonna have a conversation about me, in a conversation I’… https://t.co/PLme3GeD3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Susann_G @ArthurAtkinson0 @Ghettoman15 @trishkatree @Pepperfire @suepeac @MPxMcConnell @MaggieRicker @gtlem… https://t.co/oj4evMGxKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching Hoosiers. I know they started with 6 players and then added Jimmy.  But I just saw a scene with three… https://t.co/nboQHDSdbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thosjleeper Not sure if you are aware of it, but there's a related sampling problem regarding inference abt when a… https://t.co/DgxFFsWWZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ejrl Cupulas chavista y militar y asociados del rgimn no pasan calamidades por q pasa poblacion Tienen comida segu… https://t.co/TW4inp6qCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[But loneliness doesn’t make 40 year old men coerce 16 year old girls into sexting. Loneliness doesn’t exploit talen… https://t.co/m2SJm3io3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NotOneMoreMinute #NotOneMoreLife #GunControlNow @AMarch4OurLives @ThisIsOurLane @davidhogg111 @RepJahanaHayes… https://t.co/mJwtbYRpea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coupleofgaming @PokemonGOHubNet @PokeGOElite @SecretLeague1 @ProdigiesNation @JTGily Staying with thw valor club! https://t.co/XMKGjw1kit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSinger @DavidBCollum @The_Real_Fly @RampCapitalLLC https://t.co/mRet0LYg5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKendraCoates @trevorvflaherty Emily doesn't do that  Taking our Teachers out to the Wood Shed: Phonics is a Kont… https://t.co/X5c9cHyIqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final: Redding Christian beats American Christian, 54-50, for the D6 boys @NSCIF championship, with the help of a l… https://t.co/vFsB8LQg1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GODDOGKILLA77 @that5280lady @CocoDavies Nate, headed back to Denver for a visit here in a week and really appreciate this primer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Calebtor I've never played this myself, only watched Super Best Friends play it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clinton was too busy with Monica Lewinsky to protect us from Osama bin Laden when we had him in our sights. Hillary… https://t.co/zWDzOaAQnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, @Ant__World @gershomtadesse @AndrewHartje  let me ponder my response before I share.  🏀💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I'm surprised Cosmetic Animal Testing is not illegal yet, especially with the industry already moving in that d… https://t.co/qtvLc4Lmb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deer 🦌 trapped in the garden. How will they get out. We were listening to the @TheMoth on @wvpublicnews in the car.… https://t.co/dkSXq5bz9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g8rgroel @NDrecruiting01 @CFBHome @247Sports Lawerence, Fromm, Herbert, Tua, Hurts (maybe) and that's it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trash cans at the end of fast food lines for those punk-ass receipts/straw wrappers &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SiblingTrip #BeachBum @ Gulf Shores On The Beach https://t.co/GbGtoHc6aO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stuck on the water with them strolling and getting called a GDI nah this a hard pass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pitt_BASE excited to see you play penn state. I went to WVU but was raised by a panther. Any chance I could throw… https://t.co/Gp0u9eSEUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeniseDresserG Pues claro! Ellas buscan ayuda, un lugar donde estén protegidas ellas y sus familiares. Que coraje en serio!! 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenhorRaposa @politicsluo There's been a murder here https://t.co/l958piogql]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is disgraceful. Paper making it all about themselves. Aren’t we clever!!! That kid played his ass off and made… https://t.co/xuvZi089vc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathyYoung63 @Noahpinion Skepticism should attend all claims, but especially those 'too good to be true' like orga… https://t.co/D5jUbFhJrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's get this Bread, Son 🥖  #bread #bake #bakery #fresh #freshbread #letsgetthisbread #son #myson #boy #myboy #eat… https://t.co/3R2505dgqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when @TheGoodDeath once said in one of her vids she didn't like whales because they would one day rise t… https://t.co/cLq16KsGp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFULLSTRENGTH Wait a minute. Last year we were talking about the S8 Samsung and I still haven't gotten one yet. I'… https://t.co/94H1ukOcPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Enabledgrls4God I've been there and still am. Praying can change everything. I am certain you will come out strong… https://t.co/gQpD1hxz9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeBlitzNFL comment les Ravens peuvent avoir si peu de jeu sous le plafond sans Suggs Flacco et Mosley out!  Je com… https://t.co/D86wDACflk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being ugly asf sucks especially when you tryna just spoil tf outta someone 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @DickSchellens i say that every day - when will it ever be enough]]></document><document><![CDATA[Para su conocimiento Secretario @AlfonsoDurazo y del Fiscal Alejandro Hertz Manero, en relación a la ejecución extr… https://t.co/eiWO2wEzjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Starting with Whittaker, then with #MattSchlapp it seems the plan was to get #Barr s… https://t.co/sDcZHqMKNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bzank17 @RonnieHSHOW @Chiefs Trout wouldn’t change the @Royals ( just won a World Series 3 years ago) Suban to MU(… https://t.co/0GEJdhNXRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[DeBlasio says your money is in the wrong hands, Harris says we can improve you. Frightening how quickly it has beco… https://t.co/GVsX2GTcsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duarte no solo está salado sino que también rezado, cagado y con el hp agua lejos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slowly clawing my way out of credit card debt is awesome, just paid off a huge pain today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A winner is someone who works to become a champion all the time, even when no one is watching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stuntpants @brhodes John Kerry's record of ugly betrayals – from Hanoi to Jerusalem https://t.co/0i07pC0DjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@falz01 @TheGregoryE The same preferential ballot gave us 12 Years a Slave, Moonlight, Spotlight, Shape of Water in… https://t.co/GiLAUoIexR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabrielzamora There was a car ad and then some make money quick scheme on your last video]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rmasher2 @NutherFineMess @realDonaldTrump The 25th Amendment should be considered today.  Trump attacks the media,… https://t.co/fABI4OFwa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the #Angels saving face for their fans. I think with anyone half a brain knows #Trout is leaving. He will g… https://t.co/sLaCbzNDah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFactRat We could argue that the area Party lost California for the GOP, but their march to extremism has been a… https://t.co/sob1Nfe9tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii See, Bill’s just another drone that believes tromp over the free press. This is how those domestic ter… https://t.co/y3qeJYO9te]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gr00vyp I fucken hate that shit!!! Literally laying in the ground still flopping too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bailey__McClure SEASON PREMIERE THE 14th. BATTLE OF WINTERFELL THE 28th!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un brindis por lo que sabemos la verdad, pero queremos saber hasta donde llega la cinismo de algunos. Salud!🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamSandwchWoman @tgshepherdvan @kyle_scanlon04 @_MegMuckleBones @bodgei @savagehulkstan I’m just SO TIRED of it. I… https://t.co/O2CaqVBU28]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickInfoSec Similarly, I got a bunch of esp32 boards and sensors to play with recently.   Happy soldering. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[ME ESTOY CURANDO"....  Si me preguntan el porqué he decidido estar solo, la respuesta es simple: me estoy curando,… https://t.co/FTLPOft03b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FHS_Swim_Dive is sending eight different swims to the state tournament this weekend after a phenomenal Section 1AA… https://t.co/nlgttaZVEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[After one, it’s 2-0 Duluth East. Hounds are controlling just about everything, and also have a 15-2 SO🥅 advantage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #HilldrupMoveUp Haiku:              Will we sit front row?                    Patiently waiting our turn.… https://t.co/7LZlUIfbwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrenDee85 I mean, I know what you’re saying is true but it just shows how stupid people are]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spontaneous #NYR tilt tonight!! Let's go Rangers!! Close to maybe this guy's last one in our sweater 😭😭 #zucccccc https://t.co/N2K89ssPeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[On record &amp; character, @KamalaHarris should not even be in the Senate.]]></document></documents></author>